Hello everybody and welcome to a very special podcast that I'm doing. I'm doing an interview with Patreon.com slash Ben Saint.
Patreon.com slash Ben Saint. That's what my mother used to say as she dand-dandled me on her knee.
I-I real- the inspiration for this came from me realizing that me and you have never done a, uh, a just direct me and you collab before.
We have never collabed. We've never even had like a one-on-one conversation except- except through text.
And, uh, we were gonna- we were gonna work on that thing. I don't know if I can- you- you mentioned hiring-
Yeah, you mentioned hiring me one time to draw an- an- an animatic for the sort-out-online rewrite, but, uh, I guess that hasn't gone anywhere.
Yeah, there's a- I- I came up with this whole alternate version of sort-out-online that, uh, that I was excited about.
And then as I was, uh, talking about it and stuff online, people kept telling me that that's essentially what sort-out-online abridged is.
Yeah.
Where their show is- they're trying to like make it like a good- like they're- they're trying to make a good version of the show and, um,
But I'm sure theirs is completely different from mine because they're using assets that are in the show already, so there's only so much they can even do with it.
Whereas mine is like a total rewrite, um, but- and I haven't watched it yet.
And that's kind of like the main thing is that as I was writing this, I kind of felt like I should know everything about sort-out-online before I do this.
You know, like, maybe I should read the books or watch SAO Abridged and like make sure I know that my version's unique and interesting.
Well, I really like the idea of the project. I really liked, um, the thought that I might get paid, um, at all. It was pretty nifty.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, it could still happen if, uh, if I ever get around back to it. It's just a- like, I don't know how excited you decide to do it.
Yeah. It's basically supposed to be like the Star Wars- what if the prequels were good videos by belated media was the inspiration.
So, um, for our audience who might not have an image in their head, uh, where he was doing with the animatic versions of his remake and I was going to have Ben draw them for me,
because Ben is really great at that kind of animatic work, because you have these- you're-
You, uh, you were really excited about my, um, the things that I drew in the comics jam at BronyCon that one year.
Yeah. You said you were really impressed by the- by my swiftness in just turning out like a multi-panel little bit.
I've been impressed with all your work because of the fact that I think you have very dynamic panels. Like, regardless of the- like, you can draw something with no detail and it looks good,
because, like, you could draw a good stick figure drawing, because you know how to frame stuff in these dynamic ways, which I think is the biggest weakness of most, like, internet artists,
is that they know how to make things look detailed and, like, pretty, but the poses are terrible.
I agree. I think that a lot of comic artists- like, like, I go on- I go on Reddit r slash comic crits a lot.
And I'll see- I mean, some- some people are just terrible, you know, obviously, but other people are, like, kind of good.
But, I don't know, there's one guy in particular, like, he posts and, like, he does really great pages, and they're really highly detailed, but, like, they're not interesting.
Like, they're really- like, he'll draw, like, a monkey screaming and he'll have, like, every, like, you know, line in the monkey's face and every hair on his face, like, you know, painstakingly inked in and, like, it's a gorgeous rendering.
But, like, it's not- it's not any better, you know, I think simplicity. I'm all about simplicity. I'm all about that Scott Pilgrim's iconic simplicity.
Well, I think that's kind of one of the most interesting things for me about you is that you have, like, a very clear taste.
I feel like me and you are alike in this regard, and not- like, not that we have the same taste, but that we have something very specific that we look for,
where, for me, it's density. It's like, I like for there to be as much going on at a given time as possible, but I also-
Yeah, I like that too. I like things with a lot going on, but I really hate-
But I think you also value brevity a lot, you know?
Well, I mean, the brevier something is, the denser it is. If there's the same amount- if there's the same amount of stuff in it, but it's briefer, then it's also denser.
That's why I like- yeah, I like Fully Coolie more than Ava, because I think it does more good in its six episodes, you know?
Like, per- like, minute to minute, I think it's got more going on.
Yeah, and you tend to value this from YouTube videos as well, that you really like the shorter ones.
I do, and that's why I complain to Jesse all the time, that his videos are too long. They've got, like, funny nuggets in them.
But then there'll be all this, like, ranty stuff, and I'm like, just get the good part.
I'm willing to waste all day just sitting through every Jesse video, you know?
And, like, if one part of it makes me laugh, I feel like I didn't waste my time, but I also am not doing anything, so it's-
But you're always, like, the- you like those little three-minute ones, the ones that are just, like, a gem of, like, hardened gold, you know?
Yeah, I liked Man Child Marsh. It was, like, pretty concise. It had stuff going on throughout. It was always progressing.
And I think that's what attracted you to Davoo's videos as well.
I love Davoo. I love his- his- his conciseness.
Yeah, he definitely values that. He does- he doesn't like to have to over-explain anything for the sake of the audience, which unfortunately, I've had to, like, talk him into adding more clarifications,
because, like, when you're on YouTube, people just don't get it, like-
Davoo is hard to- he's hard to understand sometimes. His point doesn't always come across that clearly.
I think it's a matter of, like, you know, you can be obtuse and some people will get it, and you're never gonna make everybody understand, so you don't want to go too far out of your way to, like, over-explain anything.
I mean- I mean, Best Guy Ever is that other extreme. Best Guy Ever explains too much, and goes, yeah, and, like, recounts the show.
But at the same time, you know, it means that nobody watches Best Guy Ever's video and doesn't get it, you know?
No, nobody doesn't get it, although someone like me is, like, just get to the fucking point already. What are you trying to say?
I know this stuff. I don't know. Yeah, but he says he writes his videos as, like, I don't know, he writes them to be accessible, which I guess they are.
Right. And I also think that another thing that me and you have in common is that the work we make very much reflects our taste.
You have- your artwork is usually pretty pared down. You like sparse dialogue, I've noticed a lot. There's almost never any, like, long dialogue sections in your comics.
I'll tell you what. I'll tell you what, Digi, this new one that I'm working on, Champion, is really wordy. Like, I need to go back and cut it down.
Yeah, because there's a lot of, like- there's a lot of- I mean, maybe it's just because the first chapter and I'm establishing the scenario, but, like, a lot of characters have to deliver a lot of exposition in this first bit to, like-
Well, this is more of a-
Fill in what's happening. It's really wordy. Like, some of the pages are, like, half-words.
It is- it is- I mean, there's more of a- there's more of an actual plot that needs to be presented instead of the, like-
The Vapors has almost no dialogue. Like, the Vapors is just, like, images of people being miserable or being terrible.
It's, like, very- I think it's kind of remarkable that you have the whole scene where, like, Vincent walks into the anime club or whatever it was.
It's a game- gaming club.
Yeah, gaming club. And completely no dialogue. We understand everything he thinks in that moment, because he just starts fantasizing about himself with this girl and, you know, the A-rank.
Yeah, yeah, the one-
This epic fantasy of him with girls on both legs and stuff, and it's, like, you completely get his motivation, and there are no words there. So I think that's really impressive, personally.
Thanks. I, um, yeah, I don't know. I guess something about-
Something about the story or what I was presenting with the Vapors, I just felt like dialogue wasn't the way to do it, uh, which is, uh, I think it came out alright.
I think it- I think that's what makes it, uh, kind of sets it apart from, like, because you've compared it a lot to Watamote.
Yeah, Watamote explains itself very clearly, though.
Right. Watamote is always internal monologue and everything.
Which I think is-
Honestly, like, I think in comparing Vapors to Watamote, that's, like, the big difference that stands out to me.
Yeah.
And that kind of made me want to make my next thing wordier, because, like, the thing about the Vapors is it took me months to make, and you can blast through it in, like, five minutes.
You can read the whole thing in, like, five, ten minutes tops.
I think that's always the biggest problem with being this kind of artist is, like-
Yeah, because, like you said, you're doing, like, long- it takes a lot longer to make than it does to read, and I think when people read something that fast and it doesn't have, like, a clear punchline, then they feel like they haven't consumed as much.
It is. The Vapors, you know, like, much like its name, the Vapors is- it's kind of insubstantial, you know, it's like-
Yeah.
It only takes, like, five minutes, whereas, like, the more words on a page, the longer it takes, and, like, the longer you're looking at that page.
Right.
So I kind of wanted more words, and, you know, more of a plot, things like that.
And I would say, like, when I first read Brunswick, I was, like- I was, like, taken aback by how fast it moves.
But I think it still worked, and it was really interesting to me that, like, the emotional gut punch at the end was still so strong, even though I hadn't spent much time with the characters or talked to them at all, you know.
It's very self-insert, where, like, you have to put yourself in the mindset of the trainer and his, like, sort of, cutthroat attitude in everything that he has, which I really love.
I love that your characters are all dickbags. Like, that's the best part to me.
I mean, I didn't set out to make the trainer in Brunswick a dickbag, although he kind of is, but that's just because he- everything he thinks is what I would think.
So he's just kind of like, well, kill these guys, kill everything, whatever. Brunswick, you're ugly. I hate you. Oh, now you're cool. Well, now I like you.
He- yeah, I tried to give him- I tried to give that- even though he's sort of a non-character, I tried to give him an arc of, like, he starts out being totally impartial to Brunswick,
and he only wants him for utilitarian purposes, and then he kind of gets- like you, the reader, hopefully, you kind of get attached to him.
I just spend a little more time with him. He grows into a big badass, and then you're like, yes, yes, but then no.
And it's just the phrasing of how, like, he's so disappointed in it, but then as soon as he sees it, he's like- he's like blown away.
Like, you're a badass! It's the perfect choice of words, you know? A badass!
Yeah.
Yeah. I wanted it to- I don't know. I tried to make- I tried to make it a little goofy, you know?
Like, when Brunswick shoots the ice shards, and just, like, skewers that gravel area, he's like, ah, shit!
I don't know. I had more fun with it, and with Brunswick.
Like, I always- I worry a bit, and this is part of why I wanted to interview you.
Like, I worry a little that your readers might not get where the comics are coming from as much.
Where, like, for me, because I know you, and I've known you for a couple years now, I've met you in person, and, like, the way these comics are is, like, exactly how you are.
It's-
I'm happy to hear that. I'm glad that you think that.
Yeah. I think a lot of you comes through in these comics, and your general attitude towards the world where you don't really hold anything on us pedestal.
No.
You have a very, like, what's the word I'm looking for? Not grim, but, like, cynical view towards other people and to yourself, and you're not easy to impress.
I'm definitely not easy to impress, and I'm very, like, I don't know, I guess I just see the world in a very pragmatic way, but, like, I've come to terms with it, like, I don't see that as a negative way to look at things.
It's just how- it's just the easiest way for me to deal with the world.
Well, it makes it great when you- because you're the kind of person who, when you pay a compliment to something, I always feel like it's, like, yeah, I've done something great, you know?
That's what I want. Like, I don't- yeah, I don't want to be willy-nilly with my praise or my criticism, you know? I want it to-
Right.
Yeah, I- you know, I mean, you talk a lot about authenticity. I try to go for authenticity as much as I can.
I think that's a pretty common element among the procrastinators in general, is we're all very, like, you know, this modern internet kind of person of kind of bearing it all and we're not really-
I don't know, you're more private in terms of, like, specific details of your life than maybe me or Jesse, who is, like, here's a video of me eating a taco, you know, like-
I think-
This is what I did today.
Yeah, I mean, I think people- yeah, I feel like I have a decent grasp of, like, your day-to-day life. Jesse's, like, not quite as much, but, like, I kind of have a foggy idea of it.
I've been thinking about doing some, like, draw vlogs, like Will Terrell does, where, like, he'll draw and talk at the same time, just so I can try to, like, I don't know, I feel like people that-
even listening to the PCP, people don't really know, you know, much about who I am. Like, yeah, like you were saying, like, you've met me in person and you kind of know what sort of person I am.
I feel like a lot- like, no one else- I wouldn't expect anyone else to really know me, except through my comics.
And I mean, for a lot of- like, I think for a lot of people, they wouldn't- like, what does it matter? Like, you're an artist, but-
Yeah.
Like I said, for me, so much of you comes through in the comics that it enhances it for me, where I really- like, especially with Brunswick, where the character feels so much like, I know this is totally what you went through, you know?
Like, this had to be the exact thoughts you were having.
I mean, I've thought about this a lot, and like, even though I haven't produced that many comics, I feel like there's a real strong thematic thread in all my protagonists.
Like-
Yeah.
Like, Phantom Horn is basically Vincent, and Vincent is basically Sophia. Only Sophia's in, like, this magical world of, like, bullshit.
But yeah, they're all the same kind of dick.
And something about their, like, stories in the world they live in is that they're the only dick in a world of, like, otherwise nice people.
Pretty normal people, yeah.
Yeah, but like, they're the biggest dicks, but they're the most- they wear their heart on their sleeve.
Right. And they don't try to. They have this mental image of themselves as that they are great, and everyone can see through it quite easily.
Yeah. But at least- but they're honest, you know? They're honest about their disdain.
I think to get a little analytical about the Vapors versus Watamote, I think-
Yeah.
I think Watamote much more invites the audience to, like, to say, like, I'm totally like that. Yeah, this is relatable.
And I think with Vincent, there's a little bit more of, like, being out- like, you have to really- like, how do I put this?
With Watamote, she kind of makes it easy for you to say, like, oh my god, I'm just like her.
Because she's, like, kind of a cute girl, and she's, you know, kind of- like, that's always been my biggest issue with the show is just kind of that-
Why would a cute girl be so unpopular?
Yeah. And I mean, they do a decent enough job of, like, I love that when she tries to look cute, then she comes out looking hideous, you know?
Yeah.
Like, the art definitely makes it like, okay, she looks fucking weird when she tries to, like, you know, dress up and stuff.
But her normal mode looks pretty- her normal mode looks pretty good, though, just in that generic way that all anime characters just kind of look cute, no matter what they do.
And I think it's just- it's very easy to be on her side and to sympathize with her, whereas-
I mean, I hate her. She's like- I think she's terrible.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm rooting for her to get better.
Right. I think with Vincent, though, it's a lot harder to be on- to, like, to say, yeah, that's totally what I'm like, you know?
Yeah, I mean-
You know, he's- if you- you look at him and you're like, he's a real shit, but then if you have the strength of mind to then admit to yourself that you do have some things in common with Vincent, then, you know, it's like even- even more powerful, I think.
I mean, he's-
In a way.
He's just like me.
He's just like me, did she?
But he's-
It's me.
But he's got the fedora in the-
Yeah.
Or the-
Well, he's like- he's like a caricature of, like, my younger self.
He's like-
Right.
He's like how I used to be only worse.
He's just the worst parts of myself.
I just- I love how completely hateable he is.
And-
I love to hate him.
Yeah.
He's great.
I-
Yeah.
I connected with him pretty- like, I love Vincent as a character.
Like, even though it was only two chapters, like, the speci-
It's just that the specific things you made the characters do were all so great.
Like, Magda turning on the shower with her clothes on just because she wanted to avoid people.
Like, I thought that was like a powerful image where I was like, oh man, that's- that's heavy.
And it's just one thing, but I completely get her character now, you know?
I didn't need anything else.
I mean, that's- that's something that I have done myself.
I've just, you know, pretended to be in the shower and the bathroom just to wait for people to leave
just because I don't want to make eye contact with anyone.
You know, when I- when I'm feeling more antisocial than usual.
Yeah.
I've- I've been there in- in my own weird- I- I like a- you know, if I have to take a shit in a public place,
I don't want to leave while anyone else is in there.
You know?
No.
Like, I don't want people to see the guy who took the shit.
Yeah.
I don't- I don't like people hearing me in the bathroom.
I like to turn on the faucet so no one can hear me- can hear my- my gross body sounds.
I mean, that's so, like, I don't want you to know what my poop sounds like.
That's- that's fucked up, dude.
I totally get it, though.
Oh, yeah.
Nobody gets it.
And then, of course, like with chapter two, like, of the Vapors,
just the fact he was reading Infinite Jests made it so perfect.
Like, that book was the optimal choice.
And you yourself have read it and carried it around.
I had finished reading it, like, a couple months before.
So, like, I know- so, like, I know what the- what it looks like when someone reads that book
because, like, I was aware of it and, like, I picked it up to read based on that image that it has
of being, like, this big, like, important quote-unquote, you know, a fucking complicated thing.
Incredibly long.
Yeah.
And it has a title, like, Infinite Jest, you know?
It's, like- it's-
Like, if you finish it, if you read the whole thing, it's, like, a- you know,
you put a little feather in your cap because you're a cool, smart guy.
Yeah.
And it- the title is, like, that- it's that perfect mixture of, like, Infinite,
like, all possibilities, and then Jest, it's all a joke.
It's, like, everything's a joke.
It's, like, the ultimate irony, you know?
True.
And then that level of irony, nothing.
But it's- it's also a Shakespeare reference.
Oh, I did not even know that.
That just takes it to the next level.
I hope I'm not- I hope I'm not wrong, but I'm pretty sure it's from Hamlet.
Probably from Hamlet.
I wouldn't know.
Yeah.
Not a Shakespeare guy myself.
Uh, Shakespeare, uh, he wasn't that cool.
I agree.
Unpopular opinion, I know.
Yeah.
Um, so I am consistently fascinated whenever you tell me about some of the things you've done.
Because of the fact that I think most- you're a little older than the rest of the PCP, yeah?
You're 28?
I think- I think I am the oldest by, like, a slight margin.
Like, I'm slightly older than Tom.
Yeah, how old are you exactly?
I'm 28, yeah.
Okay.
I think Tom's 27.
I want to say it goes you, Tom, Nate, Jesse, or-
Is Nate older than Jesse?
What the fuck?
Jesse turned 26 this year, I think.
Uh, yeah, I guess Nate's turning 26 next month in, like, a month.
Yep, shit.
Yeah, and I'm turning 25 in August.
Um, but yeah, you- you have, like, a bit- like, I think because the rest of us got into, like,
you know, for me, I got into YouTube kind of young, so I haven't had the opportunity to have done all these other things
before settling into a career that involves being at my desk at all times.
Yeah.
Um, and you've done a lot of other stuff before YouTube in terms of, like-
I did a lot of bullshit.
Yeah, I did a lot.
Like, I went- I went to school, like, I went to college.
I did thinking, and by the time I graduated, I thought I was going to be a scientist, so I majored in-
I majored in physics, but you know, I also was kind of a- kind of a cool, pretentious, intellectual dude,
so I double-majored in philosophy, because that's fancy.
How many years were you in college for?
Four.
I just did-
This was, like, right out of high school?
Yeah, just did the usual, you know, graduate high school, four-year degree,
bada-bing, bada-boom.
Okay.
And, uh, yeah, so I went for physics, got my physics degree,
and then the first job I had out of college was teaching at Astro Camp,
which is like space camp, but on the west coast, and up in the- up in the mountains of Southern California,
and it was all about taking kids on nature hikes and telling them about constellations and stuff.
So what, like, did they, like, fly you out there for that job?
Because you're from Boston, right, or outside Boston?
Near Boston, yeah.
They- um, yeah, I think they paid for my ticket,
and they flew me out- they flew me out there to this- and drove me up to this mountain,
and we're like, well, you're here for six months, and I said, cool.
And then all these classes of kids, every week a new fucking bunch of kids would come,
and I would pretend to like them for however long it took- however long it took to get them to go away.
Had you been living at home, like, in college and everything?
No, I lived- I lived the dorm life.
I had a rose- I had a rose-colored campus life, did you?
Okay.
So did you and Nate ever, like, go to the same school at the same time or something?
Yeah, he was a- he was like a freshman in high school when I was, um, a junior.
So yeah, we were in the same- for two years of elementary and two years of middle and two years of high school,
we were in the same school.
Okay.
Because I've had the impression that you guys had a lot of the same friends,
like, in college and stuff like that.
I became friends with one or two of his friends, and like, he has met a few of mine.
Like, we- I mean, we had our own distinct friend groups, though.
Cause you know, I've got- yeah.
I've got, you know, Victor and Shade, and me and Victor just have one-
You guys all have, like, a big cadre, is the impression I get.
Well, Shade has his own friends, cause he's, you know, much younger.
He has a few friends that we don't really- I mean, his friends know our friends.
They hang out, like, they're right now actually, hanging out, playing board games downstairs.
But like, you know, there's a little bit more of a divide, but yeah,
because our house is the meeting place for everybody,
then, you know, anyone who knows one of us ends up knowing all three of us.
Cause Shade is six years younger than me, so he's quite my junior.
But yeah, I was always curious about that, cause like, when Nate was talking about the guy who called you
the king of fives or whatever in college-
King asshole.
Yeah, that's one of my friends, but not anymore.
I'm gonna go tell him that I hate him.
Uh, I will, I will destroy everyone.
But you had a great counter-argument that he himself is the real king of fives.
That guy likes fat chicks.
Yeah.
I happen to know.
So maybe his entire scale is off.
Yeah, definitely.
So, alright, you taught at Astro Camp, and so what did you do after that?
Well, I learned how to expand marshmallows with a vacuum pump,
and then I moved home.
That was what they taught me.
For your physics degree.
Yeah, but hey kids, look how big this marshmallow gets when I suck all the air out.
Uh-huh.
Um, oh yeah, and then I went back to Boston, and I got a job in like a lab,
and I had this really cool-
Holy shit.
Give him a lab coat?
Yes, I wore a lab coat.
Oh, you fucking badass, that's awesome.
I had to get decontaminated when I went into the lab work area.
I operated an electron microscope and shot electrons at the head of a pin
to determine the radius of its pointiness.
I did lab tests and stuff.
Oh man, I used some devices that really looked like some high science,
some super science shit, some weird glowing rings.
Oh god, that sounds awesome.
It was.
Well, that one was like specially designed so you could see the interior,
because it was a mirror sputter-coater for like making mirrors and shit,
and what you had to do was you put the silicon disk in
and then you like fucking super heat it to a plasma so that it spits off atoms
and they coat the stuff you put in there,
but when you open it up and look at it, it's like,
yeah, it's given off this like weird pink ring of light.
Holy shit.
Yeah, it was pretty sweet.
It was a boring job, honestly.
Okay, if I asked you to explain what kind of stuff you were doing,
would I be able to understand?
No.
I mean, I mean, I mean, well, I mean the day-to-day things I was doing.
Yeah, it was like, like, it just, I just had to like put samples in this thing
and then this thing would like, it would take this pin and like scratch across
the mirrors we'd made and like the pressure it applied would change
and I would have to record like at what pressure did the mirror coating
start to like break and peel off.
And this was like, yeah, that was the majority of what I actually did.
So that's actually pretty easy to understand.
Like, the fucking-
I just don't know why you were doing it.
The quantum excitement of the atoms that leads to the sputter-coating process
is like even I don't fully understand it, but yeah.
So you worked in a lab for a while.
Yeah, about six months.
How long would you say it?
Okay.
I was there for about six months.
It was just like an intern position.
Like it wasn't, I wasn't salaried.
And I guess I didn't do that great a job because after a while they were like,
well, your internship's over.
And I said, okay, I'm gone then.
I'm just like, I'm thinking about, all right, history of the PCP, you know.
Yeah.
Jesse, who I know went to college for a while.
I think he dropped out.
I don't know if or what jobs he's ever had other than YouTube.
He worked on like a farm, right?
Jesse?
Yeah.
He told me, or that's like a lumberjack or something.
He told me he worked with like his uncle on a farm.
Oh, I think he worked for his dad doing something like that.
Maybe he was, I don't know.
Yeah.
He's never really told me about his-
Surprisingly, I don't know what his previous job was.
He's definitely mentioned that before, but I don't remember the details.
I know that Jeff, I don't know if he had any normal jobs,
but I know he wrote for a gaming magazine, an internet gaming magazine.
Yeah.
Works for his dad as a window cleaner.
Yeah, cleaning windows and gutters and stuff.
And then we've got you who worked in a laboratory doing physics experiments.
Yeah.
I'm an actual fucking scientist slash engineer.
And I worked at Target.
That's my background.
It was real boring.
Like, even though the machines looked really cool, the job was quite dull.
So I wasn't too sad when they fired me.
What did you get fired for?
Just like-
Not being needed?
Just the-
It was just that like the internship period ended and they didn't-
I guess they weren't impressed enough with my performance to keep me on as a full-time dude.
So where'd you go after this?
Let's see, I got some job working as like a document editor for some comp-
I would just fucking go through and like control F and like find typos and stuff in like textbook documents.
And that was really easy.
It was really easy for me to just over-report how long editing any particular document took and then they would pay me more than I actually deserved.
It was great.
See, this is why I love talking to you because you do-
Like those kind of things seem to come naturally to you that-
Like sneaky fucking shit.
Yeah.
And screwing people over? Absolutely.
I think for-
I don't know.
I doubt this has to do with the age difference because you're not that much older than me.
But like I feel like for a lot of us internet kids, a lot of us are more like goody-to-shoe kids
who the reason we stayed inside is because we never did anything wrong, you know?
Like we were scared of getting in trouble.
Like that's kind of for me anyways.
Like I grew up you very like not break any rules kind of guy, you know?
I was like that too as a kid.
Yeah.
And I ended up through college.
Like I never smoked a cigarette until late in college and stuff.
When I got into college, I actually voluntarily signed up the first year to live in the substance-free dorm.
That's how much of a fucking idiot I was.
Of course it didn't actually stay substance-free.
But I was like I'm not going to drink at college.
I'm going to be on the straight and narrow.
Yes, Suri.
But you know, now I have a more pragmatic way of looking at things.
I just have that deeply ingrained fear of like if I misreport something then what if it does go wrong?
Or just generally I'm just like too honest.
Like I can't bring myself to lie about that kind of thing.
Like even if I think I should, you know?
I'm not the kind of guy who thinks that you're always morally in the right by not fucking anybody over.
Sometimes maybe they deserved it and you deserved better.
I mean they're a company, right?
And I'm a person.
My moral value is higher than theirs.
So fuck them.
That's my opinion about everything basically.
I don't disagree necessarily.
It's kind of like how this is like a real stretch of an example.
But I just did this video about Kanye West's album, My Beautiful Dark Twisted Fantasy.
And I was saying how I can't bring myself to buy it because I know he has so much money.
His record label has so much money.
It's like I want to buy it on vinyl, but it's $35.
And every time I see it, I'll look around the store and I'll see like an artist who I know needs that money a lot more.
And I'm like alright, you know.
I'd rather, or with like Patreon, you know.
I only patron people who like make less than me.
Yes, same.
That's why I unpatroned Nate because he passed me.
But then I went and fucking passed him again.
So I should probably repatron him.
I mean there's some people I'll patron just because I really, really love their work
and I couldn't bring myself not to be a patron, you know.
But like when people, like I'm, as much as I love Red Letter Media and I watch all their stuff,
like they have enough money, you know, on their Patreon.
As far as I know anyway.
I don't even, you know, I'm not the biggest fan of Red Letter Media.
Right.
But yeah, I kind of have that, like I'm not necessarily stealing from Kanye
by not buying his album even though I do, you know, listen to it all the time.
It's more of a, like I don't know.
I don't believe that quote unquote stealing music is stealing anything
because there's no product that's being lost.
There's no loss of money for the recipient, you know.
If I download an album I was never gonna buy, then there's no profit loss.
But yeah, I think it falls into the same kind of mindset that you have
of like, fuck the bigger guys.
If someone's rich and you, I mean, this is, even if it was a person,
I mean a company is not even a person, but even if someone has a ton of money
and you take their money, you do way more good for yourself than you do harm to them.
I would agree.
I think everyone should always be punching up all the time.
Everyone should always be trying to tear down the people that are above them.
I'm coming for you Digi, by the way.
I'm fucking on your ass.
I'm gonna destroy you.
Regular Robin Hood over here.
Yeah, that's right.
Except you don't give it to anybody, you just give it to them.
Yeah, like Hippo said in the Sly review, he said,
they rub from the rich and keep for themselves because they're not idiots.
Yeah.
I don't remember that line, but that's great.
I love your Hippo voice there.
Cause they're not idiots.
Yeah.
Alright, so after you did this job.
I only worked as an editor for like, yeah, probably for another like six months.
My life comes in like very clearly delineated, like six months or one year chunks all the time.
Mine is similar, mine's three months though.
Yeah, six months for me. Sometimes they double up though.
Oh yeah, and then I quit that or got fired or something.
I don't know.
Oh yes, and then I answered an ad for a physics teacher in Poland.
So I went to Poland for like a long time.
So that was just for an ad.
Yeah, there was just a Craigslist ad that were like,
hey, we need a physics teacher over in Poland.
And I was like, hey, I have a Polish last name.
I'll probably have like an in.
They'll probably be like, hey, yeah, let's get this guy.
We can understand what the fuck his name means.
Yes, spoiler alert for the audience.
Your last name is not Saint.
No, no, that's my pen name.
Yeah, Ben Saint is a pen name.
My real name is a bunch of Polish gobbledygook.
Yeah, it's not, neither of you and Nate do not have the most attractive last name.
I would certainly say that pen name was the right way to go.
I wouldn't say it's unattractive, but it's hard to fucking pronounce.
It's impossible to spell. It's hard to pronounce.
I'm not too partial to it, but yeah.
Yeah, so I answered that ad and then I went to Poland and I was a physics teacher
and that was cool for like three months or so.
But I guess the kids, some of the kids liked me,
but I guess enough of them didn't that when they all got pulled about,
you know, how do you like your teachers?
My ratings were overall negative, so they fired me,
which honestly, I hate teaching. I hated teaching at Astrakamp.
I hated teaching these fucking Arabs.
They were all Arabs, by the way.
They were all bunch of Saudi Arabian kids that were studying in Poland for some reason.
I have no idea. I don't know why it was set up this way, but it was.
Anyway, I hate education. I don't believe in education.
After having done some of it myself,
I no longer believe that formal education is even a thing that anyone should do.
It's dumb.
I'm very down on the entire school system.
I'm not a fan of it. I don't think it works well for most people.
I think everything after middle school is fucking useless.
Even if college was free, I wouldn't necessarily recommend everyone do it.
I think everybody should be in trade schools.
You fucking find a thing you're good at and do that,
because college is so much general knowledge.
It's like people going to college just to get a degree,
to get a normal ass job.
It's raising the hiring standard above what it even needs to be in some cases, I think.
I don't know. I feel like college and high school do not teach the discipline
that is what people need for regular jobs.
We get someone who will say,
hey, we've got an open desk job.
Let's hire the guy with the college degree and not the guy with just a high school diploma.
But I don't think going to college teaches you the things you need for that job.
I think we should have something that's more of teaching you how to have work skills.
For me, I can't complain too hard,
because I honestly do believe the old line that everyone says that
even if you don't go into a field that matches your degree,
it's like an edifying experience and it's the experience of college
and all this broad learning.
My school was a very broad liberal arts education.
Do I feel like it culturally enhanced me and edified me and improved my life?
Honestly, yes, but only in a very unpragmatic and lofty and hard to define kind of way.
The sort of way that is really a privilege that I'm able to even find any value in.
That's what I mean by, I think instead of college or instead of high school even,
it should be work training, how to have discipline to do jobs
and how to have the mindset to talk to other people.
Because you do learn those things kind of incidentally in high school and college.
It's like, yeah, you learn, because people, whenever they say,
oh, it's the experience of meeting other people and working in groups and stuff.
Then why don't we have school for meeting people and working in groups,
as opposed to world history class that no one needs to know.
Just teach a class on working in groups.
I don't know if that would work. You have to be doing something.
You can't just work in a group for the sake of working in a group.
You have to do something.
There has to be some goal.
Make it so instead of the world history class,
let's say it's a class where we have to build something together as a team.
It has to be finished by the end of the month.
It's something fucking practical that we will all need this skill in five years.
How about we have just a whole class dedicated to building a car.
Everyone has to learn how to work together and build a car.
Now everyone who graduates high school knows how to fix their fucking car forever.
That would be great.
Much better than knowing world history would be knowing how to fix a car.
I'm one of the rare people who actually did use all that fucking math and science
that everyone says they'll never need out of high school.
That's why I picked world history.
I never used my world history, except to not look like an idiot at parties or whatever.
That's what it's for, right?
That's what knowing history is for.
It's so that you'll be culturally up to date and not look like an asshole at parties.
Which you're going to anyways, because there's going to be some dumb shit you don't know.
Eventually you will.
But the more you know, the less likely it is at any given party that you'll go home in tears.
You finished your working in Poland. Where did you go from here?
Oh, yes. Well, they fired me for bad student reviews. Fuck them. Fuck them all.
And I was like, well, I saved up some money, and here I am in Europe.
So it's time to have an adventure.
And I just like hopped on a train and like traveled across northern Europe.
And I went from, I went north to Estonia for New Year's Eve because a dude,
actually, funnily enough, a dude, a blogger that I followed back when I was into the whole pickup artist thing,
because I was into that for a while, this guy.
You innate both with that stuff.
I did it first. I bought him the Tucker Max book because at the time I thought,
I mean, I don't think I would like Tucker Max as much if I went back and read his work now.
But at the time, like I was kind of coming out of college and I was like, yeah, fucking bitches and money.
And yeah, I know, I see how the world really is. And Nate was still this fucking goody two-shoes.
Red pill, literally.
Yeah, sorta. It's embarrassing now, but that's how it is.
Yeah, so I got him. I tried to like gently nudge him in that direction because I was sort of embarrassed to see what a fucking nice boy Nate was at the time.
But anyway, yeah, in Poland, at a total happenstance, that guy, Roush, was there and I met him and was like,
dude, I follow your blog and he was like, oh, cool.
And he told me that I should go to Estonia for New Years and I did and it was a great fucking party.
And then I just went south and I went west and I went to Germany and France and England and Ireland.
And then I flew back to Poland just in time to catch a flight home to America,
but not before stopping in Sweden where they told me that I overstayed my welcome and I had to pay them 700 euros.
Oh, Jesus.
Yeah, I was fine because I exceeded the legal, you know, how long I was supposed to be abroad.
I just didn't pay attention. Yes, I paid out the ass for that.
I had to do that when I went to the Philippines because, you know, I went there for a month and like,
this is fucking stupid.
I landed there, I get through, like I'm going through customs and the guy is like asking me how long you're going to be here.
And I'm like, well, for a month, like just what it says on my ticket, right?
And he's like, well, are you going to be like working here or whatever?
I'm like, no, I'm just here to visit.
And he's like, well, I'm going to mark you for three weeks and you can come back and get an extension later.
And I was like, why?
But the guy was like a total like hard ass.
You know, like one of those like bureaucratic doesn't look you in the eye,
just fucking writes what he wants to write on your shit.
So he gives me a three week stamp.
And of course I don't go back to get it renewed.
So then like when I'm leaving, like I'm about to fly out of the country and like the lady at the desk,
like to give me my ticket is like, oh, you overstayed your welcome.
So there's like a $75 fine or something like that.
And I was like, what the fuck?
Like why literally why?
And there it was like fucking five in the morning.
And like all I had on me was they were just like just make $75 appear or you're not going home.
Right.
Well, all I had on me was like bank checks.
And like I had a I didn't have enough Filipino money.
I had like a bunch of American money and some Filipino money and they didn't have any open banks there.
And I was like, the bank's not even going to open before my flight.
So like this like police officer like over like really young police officer guy overheard me.
And he's like, yeah, man, I'll just exchange my money for yours.
And like he didn't have like even distributed.
I think I gave him like almost $20 extra just because I didn't have the right bills to break.
And I was just like, I don't fucking care, dude, I need to get out of this.
I need the money so I can leave, you know.
Yeah, dude.
They were yeah, I said Sweden before, but I meant Switzerland.
Yeah, it's like, like I couldn't not pay.
Like I had to fucking get out of this predicament and fly to America.
700 euros though.
What was the conversion rate?
Or maybe 500.
I don't know.
A euro is like a dollar and a half.
So it was, I think it was a lot.
Like it was a, it was kind of a big fucking deal or a big illegal thing.
I was a trader to the America.
They were after my ass.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
And I went, oh man, I went to Amsterdam and I smoked weed outside and then someone was like, hey,
you know, you're not really supposed to smoke weed just like out in the open.
And I was like, ah, shit.
Then why am I even here then?
I don't even, I don't even like weed.
I said fucking throwing this giant fat blunt I had just purchased for an outrageous price
onto the ground and accidentally burning a prostitute in a red, in a red box door somewhere.
That all happened.
Oh God.
So then you came back and while I was there, oh yeah, let me tell you about when I was working
for the, the, the teaching company, they, they paid for my apartment.
They got me this fucking, all right, for like the, the price for like $500 a month was about what it costs there.
It was 1500 Zlotties a month, but it was like the swankest apartment.
It was like this high rise fucking giant like studio, like beautifully furnished with a big like full balcony.
It was like, it would have been like thousands a month here, but it was just in such a shitty piece of shit.
Eastern European block fucking like racist ass city in Poland with fucking white pride symbols of fucking spray paint
all over the town.
Oh yeah.
I mean, it was a college town.
It was, it was a little bit metropolitan.
There were colleges there, but like the Asian kids that went to college there would get hassled all the time.
And like my, my Saudi Arabian students would occasionally get hassled by people who were like, yep, not white.
Well, don't care for that.
No, sir.
Jesus Christ.
But my other teacher guy was like this guy who apparently, I guess he had gone to high school with LeBron James.
And he had been in the NBA for a while.
He was a giant black man.
He was like seven feet tall.
He was enormous.
Nobody hassled him due to the fact that he was physically terrifying.
He was, he was an okay guy.
He was, he was really boring.
Like all he ever talked about was money.
Yeah.
I mean, in fairness, we talk about money a lot, but we do it in a cool way.
It's, it's cool when we do it.
It's, it's not cool when, when, when basketballers do it.
I don't know.
Maybe I was just intimidated by his, his massiveness.
Oh, that guy, that guy was real popular.
That guy had, that guy had sex with girls.
Oh, but then you've always been, uh, I've always gotten the impression that you,
you've been well laid in your life.
Well laid.
I could be better.
Oh man.
All right.
Well, like, uh, not in a while.
I mean, I've been, I've been working.
I've been drawing like every day or trying to draw every day all day.
So I haven't had a girl over in a while.
I guess like a couple months ago, I had a few Tinder things.
I would say that compared to, uh, the entire internet, you have more of a, a normal healthy
sexual, uh, you're well laid.
I don't know how to phrase it.
Like you, you don't, you're not like me who had one girlfriend one time and hasn't had
sex in two years.
I had at any time before that.
Like, well, let me, well, let me tell you my tragic backstory.
Did you, um, when I, yeah, I was in college and like, I guess, I guess I lucked out because
like, um, I mean, I never had a girlfriend in high school or anything.
I never even kissed a girl in high school.
Right.
And I got to call.
Yeah.
And I got to college and just, just as luck would have it, I met a girl who would like,
just, she was another freshman like me and she had just broken up with her boyfriend
back home or something.
There was like a little bit of drama where like she wasn't quite broken up with him when
we first met each other and it, you know, bothered me a lot, but whatever.
She eventually dumped him and we dated and we dated for like three years, right?
And we were very much in love and stuff and we loved each other a lot and it was beautiful
and it was fucking boring and it sucked.
And I, and I said, that's it.
I'm done.
There's, you didn't do anything wrong, but I'm breaking up with you.
Uh, and she was like, oh, that hurts my feelings.
And I said, I, I figured, but goodbye.
Uh, yeah, it was all very sad and emotional at the time, but now I don't care.
Yeah.
And that was, that was the only like real relationship I've ever had ever, ever since
then it's just been like, well, I met a girl who's cute and maybe I'll have sex and maybe
even more than once.
Uh, but if not, that's fine.
Um, yes, nothing matters.
Uh, that's the story.
I don't know if I want to, I'm way happier now.
I'm way happier not caring about anyone.
It's awesome.
Well, I don't know if I want to get too specific about it, but I was extremely impressed with
your performance at Bronycon two years ago.
I did have, I did have sex at Bronycon just because it was like, cause we were all, you
know, we all went to Bronycon and it, Bronycon is this weird duality where all of us want
to hang out together, but also everyone really wants to use the opportunity to try to get
laid.
Nate was very explicit.
Nate, Nate told me before the con, he was like, you know, it's always been, you know,
I really want to get laid at this con.
Like I, it's always been my dream to get laid at a con and I was like, cool man.
And then I didn't, he didn't.
And I mean, I felt a little bad, but mostly it was hilarious.
Believe me, every, every con I've ever gone to, I go into it with the mindset of like hoping
it's going to happen, but I am just, I don't make things happen.
Like, I, yeah, I used to go to con.
I used to want to do it at cons.
I did not have any expectations of getting laid at Bronycon though.
And maybe that's why it happened because like I really wasn't looking for it or anything.
But you, I think you, like in the time I've spent with you, like, I think I'd said this
before that I consider you the most personable of the procrastinators.
You did say that.
And I, and I find that weird because in the chat, I feel like I'm always, I'm always
naysaying and criticizing.
Like I feel like I'm very negative, like in the chat, but like not so much on the actual
podcast.
Right.
Well, I think in the, I think in the chat, we're all friends.
So us being negative to one another is not like anything special or different, I think.
Like, I don't know.
Yeah.
I mean, obviously when you call out Jesse, then he goes on a whole fucking tirade because
that's, it's Jesse.
If you imply that he's not perfect in any way, then he's going to have a whole fit about
it, you know.
But, but for me, like, you know, if you were to, I mean, you don't really criticize me
often ever, but like if you were to, I'd be like, yeah, you're, you're right.
You know, like I trust your opinion on my work or not to say that I would not to say
your work is so consistent.
Like there's, it doesn't really tend to veer off in like new directions that like I need
to point out like what are my thoughts on them.
Yeah.
I'm not saying I would change anything if you criticize me, but just that I understand
your taste well enough that like when you criticize Jesse's work, it's not at all surprising
to me because I know what you value and I know that you don't necessarily value everything
he's putting out.
So like not to say that there's anything wrong with him continuing to do the work he
does because obviously people like me enjoy it, but like a lot of it, just a lot of it
is not to my taste at all.
Some of it is the exact opposite.
Yeah.
So I think that's fine, you know.
But when I say personable, I more mean that out of anyone, I think if, if each of us were
to walk up to a random person and try to talk to them, I think you'd have the best luck.
That's what I mean by you being the most personable where maybe I think I'm not terrible at talking
to people.
Because I won't talk to anybody unless they talk to me first.
I, I don't walk up to people.
I don't initiate conversations, you know, when I'm at cons, I never get any pictures
of the cosplayers I want to unless they're like right in front of my face and I get the
chance to go, Hey, can I take a picture real quick?
You know, but like, I won't walk up to people.
I won't initiate conversations unless there's like a really good strong reason like they're
doing something that, that like I really want to say something about.
But you know, when I go to conventions, I'm surrounded by people and I'm not talking to
any of them, you know, because for me, like, I don't, I don't ever expect to go into a
conversation and it to be like good, you know, I wait for other people to want to talk to
me and then I talk to them, but I don't pursue it.
And so even though there's usually a lot of women that I have the opportunity to talk
to at conventions, I don't end up doing it because I'm waiting for them to try to talk
to me, which they're not going to do because they're women and they don't do that like
most of the time.
I mean, I've said it, I've said it, I keep coming back to this, I feel like, but yeah,
the whole pickup thing back when I was into that like part of that was like go up to strangers
and like hit on them.
And like I did a lot of it.
And I think I guess it was good because yeah, I don't, I don't feel a lot of like, I mean,
I, it's, I mean, it's a little nerve wracking to like strike up a conversation with a stranger,
but like I've done it enough times that I, I guess I'm kind of good at it.
And I don't, and I don't feel embarrassed.
Like, I don't know, like maybe I'll say something and they, even if they don't care and want
me to go away, I'll just be like, well, you know, I tried, you know, I mean, I don't take
rejection personally.
To speak for, for Nate, like, I've observed him because when we go to cons, I observe
you guys a lot and try to like, sure, I, I like to pair people's actions with how they've
described themselves, you know, like figure out where the discrepancy is and things like
that.
Or just like, um, I think a lot of you comes through in your art and with Nate, there's
this duality of what he's trying to present himself as and what he actually sees himself
as.
And it comes through a lot in his videos where it's always like the self-aggrandizing persona
and then there's always the, the nerd underneath the whole, the character, I mean, he's told
me a bit about some of the future videos he's going to do for best guy ever.
And yeah, it hasn't come through quite as much so far, but like in the upcoming ones,
like the whole character of best guy ever is that duality of like a character who presents
himself with, in this like a grand eyes way, but is actually this fucking dweeb and kind
of knows it.
It's keg standard where with keg's whole review of that, uh, one pony episode was that like
he was originally this, this dumpy nerd and then he decided to become an alpha bro.
You know, he, he, he, she's like, I'm, I'm going to be cool.
I'm going to be cool no matter what it takes.
But I think that the, I think the keg standard more successfully became the alpha bro than
the best guy ever character who's more like still, he just kind of like, he just kind
of like is just sort of barely hiding it.
Right.
But I think that's exactly what Nate is like.
And like when I see him in person, like when he tries, cause he always talks the big pickup
game, like he's going to go and talk to all the girls and be the charismatic guy.
But then when we're all sitting around, he's like the one who's like, should I, should
I do it?
Should I go up and talk to that girl?
What if I went up and talk to that girl and you can tell he's really nervous.
And I love that his, even his art, when he drew that one, do you remember his scissor
picture in the, the procrastinators, uh, draw cast with, with the heads and what.
Yeah.
Well, the way it was like sweating and looked all nervous and like, yeah, Nate gravitates
towards those kind of pictures a lot.
Like he loves like people looking nervous.
Yeah.
People having that like sweaty, like, like, Oh God, am I about to do something completely
fucked up?
And that's exactly what he looks like to me when he's in social situations is like that,
like, I have to do that.
I had like, he knows that he has to be this charismatic character in order to succeed,
but it's all like forced.
He has to make it happen.
You know, well, I mean, I think, I think part of it at Brony con, like, yeah, I think he
had more, he has sort of had more writing on it reputation wise.
Like he kind of, yeah, he kind of has this like character of being, you know, this keg
standard best guy ever, like this kind of cool pick up a guy.
But like because he's got that persona, it's like, it's more important that he not fail.
You know, I think that is maybe the source of some of it with you.
For you, it's more like, I don't feel like you have that same anxiety.
I mean, you walk up to somebody and you just kind of start talking to them, like especially
artists because I saw you talk to like everyone who you saw drawing almost felt like you were
talking to them at Brony con, you know, yeah, which I mean, for being someone who draws,
you can easily have something to start a conversation with, but is that not how you ended up getting
late at Brony con?
Because the girl was also an artist and I don't, I don't really remember exactly like
how I met her or what we were doing, but yeah, she did end up hanging out with me and Munchy
and we all and we all drew together when we did the the comics jams.
Right.
Uh, yeah.
So yeah, so that probably was part of it or involved in it.
I don't know.
I'm just a wicked cool guy.
Yeah, everyone wants to hang out.
Really fascinated watching how for you, it seemed like talking to other people was kind
of natural and easy.
For Nate, it was like something he had to like force himself to do.
And for me, it was just I gave up before I started and it didn't talk to anybody, you
know, in spite of constantly talking to people who are walking up to me, but I'm not pursuing
anyone.
I'm not like going up, you know, like there was all those like when, uh, cause there's
these two cosplayers who, one of whom, uh, Jesse is currently dating.
Oh yes.
Yeah.
And I, and I, I almost had sex with the other one, the hotter one, but I didn't because
the other one, because that girl that Jesse knows, uh, she fucking came in and interrupted
us.
Oh, that was the angriest I've ever been.
Cause I thought I was really fascinated that that girl, the, the, the Pinkie Pie cosplayer,
we all agreed that she was super hot and nobody even tried to flirt with her.
I guess you did cause I didn't even, I didn't see that, but I spent so, it was so arduous
the process that I went through to try to sleep with that Pinkie Pie cosplayer.
We, I had to walk like blocks and blocks back to her place.
We got lost.
I was sweating profusely because I, we were outside in the heat walking around, uh, it
was terrible.
I won't, I don't want to describe the emotional gauntlet I had to go through once we were
actually there.
It was a fucking nightmare, but it finally, finally was panning out and then fucking
what's her name and their dumb, and their dumb brother or whatever come through the
door and I'm like, oh no.
And I hung out.
I stayed there for like another hour or two hours, uh, like hoping that the opportunity
would re-emerge, but no, it didn't.
I felt like it was some kind of conspiracy.
Like the two of them had agreed ahead of time, like let's, let's, let's make Ben think he's
got a chance here and then just, just fuck with him.
You know, let's just ruin his day.
That was the second BrodyCon though, right?
That was the second BrodyCon.
And then Jesse and, uh, that other girl were already like, uh, you know, like a thing together.
So, yeah, yeah, they even the, like the first year though, like, cause they were both there
and nobody even tried to flirt with the Pinkie Pie girl.
Cause I think we all just thought she was out of our league.
I kind of tried.
I talked, I talked to her a bunch.
Uh, it didn't go anywhere.
Right.
Um, well anyway, yeah, I don't know how we got onto this topic.
I was still, we haven't finished your life story.
You were coming back to America.
You said I was well laid, did you?
Yeah.
That's how we got onto this topic.
Uh, oh fuck.
So you, you came back to the U.S. after your trip around England or, uh, Europe rather.
Yes.
To, to Amsterdam and Belgium and, and Ireland.
And how did you fund all that?
Estonia.
Well, it's cause I had, I had had a little bit of savings left from the, the lab job
when I, when I went.
And then, you know, I worked as a teacher.
I, I just saved up money from my teaching to, oh yes.
And then when I got fired, they wouldn't pay for my apartment anymore.
And I was like, well, I, I'll run out of money if I keep living in this 1,500 zloty a month
place.
So I went to my landlord and was like, can you give me a cheaper place?
And he moved me immediately downstairs into a like comp, into a like two room complex that
I shared with a 90 year old woman, uh, there was no like appliances except for a simple
hot plate.
Uh, the heater was a giant column of stone that would occasionally get hot and emit heat
into the, yeah, the bathtub did not hold water.
You had to, you had to pump water into a fucking pan and sponge bath yourself with it.
Um, there was like no furniture, uh, or there was like a mattress on the ground and that
was it.
The walls were concrete.
From heaven to hell and they're right, right above each other.
That's incredible.
How, did you ever like look up at the ceiling like wistfully?
Like God, I was, I was, I was up there, up there, up where the skies are so much blue.
I can be there and live without a care.
Yeah.
And you know what's funny, um, I had, I had sex with two girls in Poland and the one that
I had sex with up in that nice room was way less attractive.
The one that I had sex with down in that piece of shit, dingy, 90 year old woman room was
10 out of 10.
Amazing.
Uh, so that's, you know, fucking, I don't know, believe in yourself or something.
Uh, that's, that's my lesson.
Oh, um, yeah.
And that place costs 15 Zloty's a day, which is like five bucks a day to live in this piece
of shit apartment.
Uh, pretty solid.
I've kind of resolved that like if, if I decide, like, cause I don't think I'm ever
going to get laid just like in my normal every day to day life, cause I don't go anywhere
or do anything or talk to anybody.
So like, I think if I made the conscious decision that I was going to start dating, I would
have to just completely redesign my room just because there's no way I'm bringing a woman
in here.
I'm not even necessarily, I'm not saying, I don't think you should worry about that.
Are you aware that there is a bed sheet stapled to my ceiling of a girl touching herself above
my bed?
Are you aware of that?
You know what?
I think if that's who you are, you should just wear it on your sleeve and women will,
and women will appreciate that.
I mean that.
I think, I think maybe just at least that one should come down.
Maybe.
And the thing is, cause part of it is that I don't care, like, I don't like, I don't
have it up there for my own enjoyment.
It's more for like, I just want to have my room covered in posters.
Like, I don't even like a lot of the stuff I have up in my room.
I just want to live the life of someone whose room is covered in posters.
Like, it's, it's more of a status thing than like a, than like a passion thing.
Imagine if you were like, I got to make my room girl friendly and like you took down
all your anime posters, like imagine how creepy that would be to go, to be like, to have bare
walls.
I wouldn't, I wouldn't take them all down.
I'd take down the ones that are like half naked chicks, you know.
The raunchier ones.
Yeah.
I've got plenty of like normal-ish.
Oh, whatever.
You're supposed to, you're supposed to like half naked chicks.
It's fine.
Leave up the half naked chicks.
Leave up all the anime.
Yeah, but they're like half naked lolly girls and stuff, I don't know.
It's cool.
They'll just conversation stars.
I guess it, it really depends on what kind of like, you know, I mean, you know, it's
like, assumably by the time a girl was in my room, she would know what I'm about.
Absolutely.
All I talk about is anime and YouTubeing and being like an internet weirdo, you know.
So, you know, maybe if they're well primed, but if, if I'm dating a girl who's not even
into anime, then that's when I'm like worried, like.
Oh man.
So I went, I, I went and met up with a patron the other day.
I think he patrons us both.
Yeah.
This, this guy crack.
I went and I, he invited me out for a beer and I went and I got a beer from him.
And yes, at the bar, there was a cute girl and we talked and I struck up a conversation
and fucking, you know, fuck me sideways.
God help me if I couldn't, if I couldn't prevent the conversation from steering itself
towards anime and, and she said, I don't know, some dumb crap.
It didn't go anywhere.
I was very sad.
I really liked her glasses.
That's my story.
I got a good image.
Thanks for the beer.
Crack.
Yeah.
Um, all right.
So you came back to the U.S. after this tour of Europe.
What did you do after?
Oh yeah.
Uh, yes.
And I paid for the trip with the money I got as the teacher and then I came home and
I was totally broke.
Um, uh, what, I came, okay, well, I remember that shortly after I come back from, from
Europe, I was like, I'm going to get serious about drawing because I think it was right
after I came back, I read Bakuman and I was like, oh my fucking God, art is pretty good.
So I went out and I, oh yeah, like at first I wanted to do it like they do it like traditional,
like with a G pen and a nib and stuff and ink and paper, but like I have no, I don't
know how to do that.
Yeah.
I can't, I can't do it that way.
It's expensive to do it that way.
So you constantly have to buy materials and shit.
Yeah, kinda.
I mean, the nibs and the ink are pretty cheap, but like, cause you always want like different
sizes of stuff and you always need, yeah, it's, it's a, it's a nightmare.
Um, yeah, but for a while I was, I was sticking with that like pen and ink aesthetic and I
made my first website.
It's also ugly.com, which was like a gag strip site.
Uh, a few of the like gag strips I made were sort of funny.
A lot of them were just really terrible and confusing and like I don't know what I was
thinking.
Um, I, I've been posting some of those, but only the ones that I'm not completely embarrassed
by.
I've been posting them on my fucking subreddit, which I spent like three days editing the
A, the, the CSS, and it looks amazing, uh, reddit.com slash r slash St. Thomas.
Sorry, let me take, I want to scale this back a second because you started taking art seriously,
but weren't you drawing it all before?
Like had it ever been a career you had thought about?
It had never been a career I'd thought about, but it was something I did for fun, uh, occasionally.
Like, all right.
I mean, I mean, I took like, I like to draw as a little kid.
My, I like to draw Pokemon and my mom would take my like Pokemon.
I mean, they were just basically like exact copies of pictures of Pokemon from books
I had.
Like copy them onto pages and my mom is a teacher and she would bring my like line art
Pokemon drawings to school and her kids would like color them, which was nifty.
So yeah, I drew a little bit as a kid.
I might have done like one like little summer program or like I had like a very basic drawing
class or something.
In college, I took one drawing class because it was something I kind of like to do for
fun and I was a little bit good at it, uh, but I never did it a lot or anything towards
the end of towards the end of college, I started going on to, all right, I started going on
to the 4chan, um, T G board for traditional gaming, which is like D and D and stuff.
And I had a character that I really liked that I was playing at the time and someone,
I like, I posted a description of him with like a little sketch I'd made a terrible little
MS paint drawing because I couldn't draw that well.
And someone drew him like beautifully, like they fucking drew this beautiful image of
this character that I had made and I was like, wow, how did they do that?
They did it so fast that like, like it didn't even take them along.
They just churned out this really amazing piece and it like really, I don't know, struck
me or something.
So I stayed on T G and I would, I would do the same thing for other people.
I would like to describe your character and I'll draw them, but like mine would just be
this little like MS paint, sort of like pixel Chibi, like I tried to keep it really like
a little simple, like very cartoon-ified thing.
And I did a lot of those.
I probably did like 20 or 30 of those and that was about the extent of my art.
It was very like occasional, like I would just do it sometimes if I was bored.
And then I went, you know, I graduated college, I did work, then I went to AstroCamp and then
sometime after AstroCamp, I read Homestuck and reading Homestuck was like, well, it did
two things for me.
It made me, like no one particular image in Homestuck is like that complicated.
Like any individual piece of it would be easy to make, you know, because it's pretty like
low fidelity.
So reading, it made me feel like it was something that a real person could do.
Like it was something that was, like the level of craftsmanship on display was something
that was attainable to me, which made me feel really close to it.
I had the same exact experience after reading Homestuck, actually.
Did you?
I tried to make my own Homestuck-like thing where like a, like a, yeah, like the, choose
your own adventure, text, well, no, mine was just going to be a web novel, but with the
images at the top, you know, like where each page had a, like a picture and then the text
under it.
Cause I had been trying to be a novelist up until the point when I started making videos.
So, so I had all these different ideas and one was called Shovel Rock and it was, there
might, this might be a website up somewhere, shovelrock.wordpress.com probably, I don't
know if I have the poster public, but it was just like a story about this girl who decides
that she's going to dig a hole at the beach because like, you know, as a kid, you always
dig holes at the beach and then when you grow up, you still want to do it.
So she decides to like, she's like, I think 11 at the start of the story and she's like,
I'm going to dig the biggest hole ever.
And then she and all of her friends start digging this hole and they basically burrow
into like a whole underground society and shit.
I never really planned anything beyond that, but I just thought it would be cool if I like
drew each image and it was like, you know, after Homestuck and what I, what I tried to
do was each picture would be me taking a, like someone else's art and then drawing
over it in MS paint, but like different enough that it's not the same thing.
That's, that's such bullshit.
Well, I was a huge fan of that, like you've seen my inverted sweetie bell thing, like
my old, my little pony avatar where it was like, I think the first video years I ever
saw I had the inverted sweetie bell.
Yeah.
Well, that wasn't the one I drew, but like the, the avatar I had was like, I flipped
the colors on it and then drawn over it in Photoshop.
So it had that wobbly look that my art has and like, I would do, like I was trying to
do a, like something, not quite like Homestuck, but another image based like adventure game
thing with that character.
And like, so I would be like, we're going into a cave.
So I'd go onto Google and find a photo of a cave and then draw over it in MS paint.
So it looked all blue be and weird and yeah.
And that would be the, the like the locations.
So that was how I tried to do after Homestuck.
It didn't go anywhere.
Um, do you still have any of it?
Yeah, I think so.
I'm going to, I definitely have the inverted sweetie bell stuff.
I'm going to look up shovel rock and see if the, um, yeah, I felt, I felt really close
to Homestuck.
I never, I never tried to like, uh, I'll remind me later.
I'll go check it out.
Yeah.
Um, but, um, yeah.
The other thing that it made me feel was like, I was so into Homestuck, right?
Like I had read Scott Pilgrim the year before and I had been really into Scott Pilgrim,
but like the level of into that I felt for Homestuck was like almost beyond anything I'd
ever felt before.
I thought about Homestuck night and day.
I thought about punch card alchemy and I thought about all the classes and aspects and I thought
about the whole like weird confusing mythos behind the whole thing.
And I was like, oh my God, I'm so into Homestuck.
You know, I will never be into anything this much again, unless it's something that I make
myself, something that I'm so interested in that I did, that I designed specifically
to be a thing that I am into.
So that made me like, that made me really want to like, you know, do my own work and,
and, and start something kind of like Homestuck and not, yeah, would you ever like just generally
artistically inclined, like not just to, not just to drawing, but like, but did you
grow up thinking you would be an artist or anything like that?
No, no, I thought I would be a scientist.
Yeah, because like, I know, for instance, Neil, I mean, I did, I did, I did creative
things once in a while, but like, not, not that often.
And I never really saw it as who I was.
I just kind of saw it as distractions.
And I kind of look when I was like college age, I kind of looked down on the arts.
Like I thought, you know, like science is real.
Science accomplishes something.
Art on the other hand is just some bullshit.
And I mean, now, did my opinion about art?
Total flip.
My, well, no, my opinion about art hasn't changed.
Art is all bullshit, but science is bullshit too.
They're, they're both, they're equally, they're equally stupid and pointless, but art is more
fun.
So I'd rather be doing it.
That's interesting.
Yeah, it's, it's seen as such a like, you do one of the other kind of thing.
And like, you remembered Neil X, the Elements of Brony.
Yeah, absolutely.
He was like, he was a lawyer and he, he had that kind of mindset too of like, you know,
lawyer, like it makes a difference in the world and like does important things.
And then by the time he finished college was a completely disillusioned to that.
And like through making Elements of Brony was like, maybe I want to be an art guy, you
know, and I think it's really fascinating to see people make that transition because
I never didn't want to be an artist.
Like my whole life, that's all I've thought I was going to do was creative work.
Like thinking back, like I think I really liked the idea of being an artist.
Like I think that concept appealed to me, but not in a way that like I actually ever
planned to do it or thought that I would.
It just seemed like a nice idea.
Yeah.
I'm literally the thought has never crossed my mind to not be an artist unless it was
like, like not until I was an adult and having to like face the reality of whether or not
I could be an artist, you know, like that was the only time it was like, oh man, maybe
I can't, maybe I will never be able to do this and I have to get like a normal thing,
you know?
Yeah.
I gotcha, man.
Was Nate like that too?
Was he ever like, was he an art boy?
I think they, no, not at all.
I think Nate was the same.
Like Nate said he wanted to be a doctor as a kid.
You both made such a dramatic flip.
You're trying to do comic scenes.
Yeah, I don't know, man.
Maybe it was, maybe it was just that little, maybe it was just that little taste of fucking
having an audience that came with TBAP.
I think, I think it kind of, well, I mean, I had actually, no, that's not what did it
for me, because like, yeah, I had made my old comic site, it's also ugly, like that
previous year, like early in that year, and then, so yeah, I was, I was already kind of
making like an art, an art, like a go of being an artist in some sense or fashion.
And then, I don't know, fucking TBAP happened, like at the end of 2013, I want to say.
Yeah, and then my drawing was mostly limited to like doing the poses and the title cards
and stuff for that was where I put most of my efforts.
I also find it like really fascinating that you were so influenced by Bakumon, because
like, I wrote about it before that-
Bakumon was like the straw that broke the camel's back.
Like if there was, like, oh, oh, I want to say I did, the biggest, before I ever decided
to make like a real go of being an artist.
There was one kind of big project that I did, and that was I ran like a homestuck RP for
some friends, but it was like we would meet every once in a while or like get, I would
talk to them on Skype because I was in Europe for a lot of it, and like I would lay out
the scenario and their character would do something and you know, they eventually discovered
their, their, they went, they eventually went God tier and like, you know, had to solve the
riddle of their world and stuff, but I would then, we would role play a little bit and
then I would go and draw like what happened.
So this still is, yeah, this is still up on a tumbler somewhere.
I might transfer it to my, to somewhere else at some point, but yeah, so I have these like
sort of illustrated sequences of these like homestuck style fan characters that my friends
made doing, you know, a bunch of, a bunch of like random things that don't really make
sense to read in context because you had to understand what the role play aspect had,
had happened in the adventure to know what the images mean, but it was a big project
and it took me like a year or like, I think I did it over the course of like two years,
but like, yeah, it was a big fucking project that lasted a really long time.
That's great though, because I feel like a, I feel like what hangs up like a lot of artists
and stuff is like, they're constantly trying to draw like original ideas or things from
their mind and stuff and like, I think it's better practice to just have something like
that, like I'm going to draw every scene from this, whatever RP, you know, like it's, it's
a good way to have a lot of ideas to try to translate and like, you know, instead of like
conjuring an image in your head that you then have to draw, it's like the image is already
there and you just have to like try to translate it, you know?
I guess it was kind of, yeah, it was kind of like a crutch that I could lean on.
It was like, I didn't have to, like if I was ever in doubt, I could just look at the original
source material and be like, well, make it look like that.
Right.
Uh, it was, man, it's so weird to think back on, oh, by the way, it was called Sperg.
It was the name of the, you know, like, like, like Sperg, but you know.
That's awesome.
I know.
Yeah, I'm pretty proud of some, I mean, I'm pretty proud of some of the pieces of it.
I'll definitely like, I'm definitely going to post those somewhere because they're pretty
neat.
Um, yeah, so, so I did that, like, and then I came back, I think I finished that in like
2014, like towards the beginning of 2014, like I finally sat down and drew the final conclusion
of it.
So T-Bab was already going by this point.
Yes.
Yes, it was, it was.
So like, all these threads kind of overlap with each other.
Cause I, I'm like, I'm trying to get a sense of like how fast your progress happened because
when you started T-Bab, this was like one of the fastest I've ever seen, like zero to
a hundred on like video quality, where you guys started T-Bab in like late 2013 and the
first couple videos were just a static shot of the two OCs, um, that were not that well
drawn.
It's just a still image.
Um, and.
Hey, come on.
They looked sort of show accurate.
They were, they were okay looking OC characters and you had like shitty audio and it was just
a static image and then all of a sudden you like completely revamped the character designs
and I already was a fan of like your art style by this point.
So like, I would have assumed that you were like a regular artist, like you've been doing
a lot of it and it doesn't seem to be the case.
T-Bab was like, I mean, yeah, I would say that taken in its entirety, T-Bab was like
the biggest art project I'd ever done.
I would say that it.
Yeah.
I would say that it involved more art than Spurg did, uh, yeah, uh, I don't know what,
I don't know why I designed the characters like that.
I gave them the big eyes and like the weird pupils and it made them really, I don't know,
they just look cool to me.
It was, it was great.
Like they had the best facial expressions of any OC pony by far and they were the best
OC ponies of all time.
Like, I mean, dude, they justified the concept of original characters to me.
I still, I still love them.
I still love Phantom Horn.
I'm not even embarrassed.
Like, I'm kind of embarrassed to tell people that I did like my little pony, I don't know,
it's in the past.
So I'm not really that embarrassed about it.
I used to be embarrassed.
Like when people asked me what I was doing on YouTube.
But now I'm like, I don't feel anything about that about Phantom Horn.
I think Phantom Horn is a great character.
He's funny.
He's just a, I'm a genius.
I'm such a genius is how that is.
I almost like.
And keg's not bad either.
I feel so like for me, I, I think I'm in the best position of anybody in the PCP because
I've already had my career as an anime guy is longer than my pony career and it's all
my best stuff.
Like the pony stuff was okay, but I've gotten so much better since that like it's, I don't
even, I would, even if you were a My Little Pony fan, like if someone came up to me and
was like, I want to watch my little pony analysis, I would hesitate to send them my videos.
Like some of them I would, but like, I, I don't think they're like indicative of my current
level of skill at all.
The stuff you make does not, no, they're, I don't know.
I mean, I actually rewatched like a whole bunch of your old video.
Like I mean, I'll put on playlists of like, you know, other PCP members or, or Mr. B tongue
or Matthew Matosis or something and just listen forever and ever.
And I did that with your, with your pony stuff.
If I put it on the playlist and just let it go for a while, it was pretty, I don't know,
it's pretty good.
It is a lot different than what you're doing now.
It's more, it's less concise.
Like when me and DeVoo were looking back, I would definitely say that it got a lot better
as it went.
Like the, the really early videos are like terrible and then they get, you know, there's
some, definitely some interesting ideas in there and stuff and some well argued points.
But like, the reason I bring it up is that it makes me sad because with someone who goes
to my channel right now, they're going to see my best videos like on the front page.
But then you've got like, uh, Jesse, who's like the best thing he ever did is the horseshoe
saga in terms of like concept and this epic execution.
The best thing he ever did was butt chugger.
Well, yeah, but that, that, that is well, but like it's, you can't like, unless someone
knows MLP and knows what the culture was at the time, you can't really appreciate it.
And the same goes for TBAP, where it's like outside the context of watching My Little
Pony every week.
How do you send someone TBAP, you know?
Um, yeah, you can't, I don't, I don't tell people that TBAP anymore.
There's so much good stuff in it where the characters were so good and the two, the,
the Phantom reviews and keg reviews were like some of the best videos that ever came out
of the community and all the intro guys, I never, every time I think of TBAP, the first
thing that comes to mind is the intro gag where you had the live action phantom horn
hands and it was like him doing a live draw and he spills ink all over everything and
like, I remember being like blown away when I saw that.
Dude, the video quality on that was so bad, but like the gag is so great, like I can't
believe, like we went to such incredible lengths to film that bit and like put that bit together
and match it with the audio and make it work.
And the result is so fucking amateurish, but it's still, it's so good enough to like,
because I, you know, we were, but we were all doing this where we were trying to get
our videos out like today, the episode happened.
So you would pre-prepare these intro gags and outro gags and stuff after a certain point,
we would do that.
Yeah.
And so I'm putting out these videos where it's like the episode comes out, I immediately
write about it.
I immediately, you know, stitch together this shitty haphazard video of a bunch of pony
expressions and whatever random clips from the episode are there and I fucking throw
it out.
And then T-Bap would come out and even though most of it is just this podcast with these
two ponies talking, there'd be these intro segments that are of more artistic merit than
anything either of us were doing, you know, like.
Yeah.
Like we, like we just recreate the game grumps, but with our own logos, right.
That was such an intensive process.
It took like, it took like an entire day's work to do that, but it came out looking pretty
nice and neat.
Right.
And I just, I feel so bad that like now we're in this like post that era and like when you
have to try to sell someone on why is Ben St. Cool?
And it's like, well, we've got a bunch of podcasts and, you know, we have these, these
few comics, but like I have way more content.
I have all these old T-Bap videos.
I've seen you do all these different creative things that were totally out there and different
and, you know, yeah, my whole characters, the fucking the episode, the T-Bap video that's
just keg talking to this girl about all the other OCs you guys made up is like legendary
fucking ultimate pumpkin and horse fist.
Wait, oh, oh, the, the animatic, yeah, yeah, the animatic, oh my God, but I always wanted
to do more like story segments with like keg and phantom, but like, I don't, with my current
skills, I feel like they'd be a little more feasible.
But like back then I was so new to the whole thing and just so, just so bad and so slow
that like, but again, I think your dynamic poses though, make them like great to watch
and that's, that's like, if I, when I, when you were talking about the sword art online
thing, like why I would choose you, like, I think if people just saw your comic book
art, they might not necessarily understand why I want you to do an animatic because
like I've seen you do those and I loved them, you know, so like the, you're right, you're
right about, yeah, like T-Bap content is not, it's not relevant anymore.
Like it was a, it was a, it was a, what's the word, it was a time and place thing and
it's not, yeah, it's not what it, it doesn't have the same relevance now.
It's impossible to send somebody an MLP video from that era for any of us because it was
all so contextual where it was like, you know, you'd make a reference to something that,
that was only relevant that week and then, you know, even for me, like I'll watch some
pony videos and be like, what the fuck was I talking about there?
Like I don't remember this, you know, I would, like my end cards on a lot of my videos.
Seemed important at the time.
Yeah, exactly.
And I'd be like, why, why am I bringing this up?
So, yeah, but, but yeah, that, that worries me too about like what I said before, Vapors
is so, it's so short.
It's like, it took me so long to make it, but you can read it in like 10 minutes.
Oh, I lose sleep over this sometimes.
And that's like, that's a big part of the incentive of why I wanted to interview you is
like, I want people to understand how like, like have a substantial amount of how cool
you are because like, like when, when Brunswick came out, my first thought was this would
be the absolute perfect Tumblr, uh, like share comic, right?
Or like something that gets passed around anonymously, like where people don't know
who the author is, but they just find it because there's so much stuff like that on
the internet where you go on like 4chan and there'll be those like comics that get
posted all the time, kind of like a Nanna's everyday life where you had never heard of
clone.manga until I sent you the website.
Yeah, I had, I had read, I had read Nanna's everyday life, but I did Nanna who made it
until you told me about clone.
And then I looked him up and was like, oh, it's, it's a guy.
And yeah, yeah.
And I, I have, I do not understand what he does now.
He does like 4chan quest threads about a bunch of like bunny girls, but like, I don't know,
I don't get it.
Like Nanna's everyday life was sort of independent of him because it was like a 4chan comic
that would just come out of the ether and be there, you know, um, another good recent
one that I doubt you or anyone else will have read, but there's this comic called take the
iron pill and never heard of it.
It's just these, like the only way to find it, there's no website for it.
There's just an Imgur, like, like image dump, like the guy literally will just update a
new chapter to this Imgur folder and like no one knows who's writing it or where it
comes from, but it's like really funny and entertaining.
So like when I read Brunswick, I was like, that's the way I would expect this to get
around because it's this short emotional story that's relevant to a certain fan base.
And yeah, and so it could easily get around because it has that gut punch feel where everyone
who reads it will be like, this is a, like people won't say, this is Ben Saints comic.
They would say it's a emotional Pokemon comic I found, you know.
Yeah.
I was, I was prepared for that.
Right.
Um, let me not to go off on a tangent, but I feel like, um, yeah, I don't worry about
like my art getting passed around anonymously.
I feel like that's just kind of in the nature of what an artist does.
Like you make your art and you, and you put it out there and like it just kind of goes,
you know, it's, it's independent now.
Uh, I've, so I've never been one to worry about like, you know, we'll like get stolen
and uncredited.
Well, like if it does, that's, I don't know, that's just, that's just what happens.
That's just part of the job.
I actually have a certain degree of like jealousy of people who do like great uncredited work
because like I want, I always wonder about like what the, because for us, we need the
credit so we can make money.
Yeah.
I don't have any attachment to fame and I don't think you really do much either.
It's, it's like, uh, no, I really want to be popular.
How do you?
I really, yeah, I really want to be famous like I personally, I mean, I like the fame
for the power it gives me that I can like recommend a show and everyone will go watch
it.
Like I love that.
Um, but for me, it's like the reason for popularity is because without it, you can't
make money.
Whereas like, uh, I mean, that's one reason.
No, I think popularity is an end in itself.
I just, I want to be relevant so bad.
Yeah.
What's like the benefit for you of like that, just emotional, like just, it's just, uh,
I don't know if, if people care about me, then that means I have value, you know?
Uh, yeah, I guess it's some kind of weird, like, like self image thing.
Hmm.
That's interesting.
Cause I, I kind of get it, like, again, I guess I like, I like the praise, but popularity
mostly comes with like this huge negative caveat of people shitting on me all the time,
you know?
I don't even really, I mean, not to say that I don't like praise, I do, but like when,
when people praise me and also when people criticize me, it all just, it all just kind
of rolls off me because like those opinions are not mine.
Right.
Like unless it's, unless, like, yeah, like I only really care about like what do I think
about a thing?
Like other people can have their opinions, but it's not that big a deal, but like, I
don't know, just, I don't know, just the fact that they have any opinion at all is important
to me.
Yeah.
I want, I want people, I want people to like know me and, and think about me.
Okay.
At least something so that, so that I can, I don't know, feel like I really exist.
I kind of feel like if, if I could make enough money and like my work wasn't even, like didn't
even have a name on it, I would be okay with that, but, but the thing is that having a
name means you can always make more, like I would, I would never want to settle for
a baseline.
Like if somebody said you'll make $50,000 a year forever and you just have to like
make this anonymous work for us, I wouldn't take that because I know that by having a
name, I can get up to $100,000 a year, you know, because I'm working on, like, because
my, like how famous I could get myself is how much money I can make, you know.
Well, I mean, yeah, the most, the most important thing is having enough money so that I can
do what I want, you know, with my time.
That's, that is, that's more important than fame is, is being self-sufficient.
But like if all other, this is kind of what, along with the whole homestuck thing about
how I'll never like anything unless I make it myself, the, the whole reason why I wanted
to be art was like, you know, they ask you the question in high school, like, you know,
if you had all the money in the world, what would you do?
And my answer was, you know, I would want to try to make some great work of art that,
you know, got like famous and was like remembered for all of time.
Right.
You don't even need money to do that.
Well, you need money to have your ability to do that.
But yeah, you need, I mean, you need a little bit.
Right.
Yeah.
So like, yeah, the most important thing is having enough money, but that's not that
hard.
I don't need very much.
It would all, all of my money goes to funding my life so I can sit here and try to make
stuff that will get out there and people will remember for it.
I'm always really surprised by this, this interesting dichotomy with you where you're,
you're very into self-promotion and you're promoting your Patreon, but you also seem
to have the least desire to make a lot of money out of, out of anybody I know.
Like I don't know what I would do with more than like, I mean, even as much as you make,
I don't think I would even know what to do with.
I mean, it would be nice to have it because like there's, there's no such thing as too
much money.
Right.
But.
That's my mentality.
It's like, I'm, for me, it's, it's, it will never be enough because I can always think
of something to do with the next step of money.
Like if I have enough to buy a house in a car, that's great.
Now I want enough to buy my friend a house in a car, you know, I want enough to, to put
up all my, I think if I got to the point where I was making enough money that I could legitimately
move all the procrastinators into a neighborhood where we all had houses near each other and
we had a studio space and I had enough money that I could personally pay for all of that,
that would be enough money and I wouldn't need any more than that.
Like, but.
That's an absurd amount of money.
But like.
That's, that's, that's high.
Yeah.
But.
But that's the only way I'd hit a point and be like, all right, there's no reason to go.
And be like, this is enough.
There's no reason.
Now I don't need any more.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, if I had, if I had shit tons of money, you know what I might do is I might
like, I might, I might, I might not, I might switch from comics to doing something else.
I might like hire like an editor to like make my art into like, I might hire someone to
turn it into like a motion comic or something.
I might hire a composer to do music for it or something.
I might, I might, yeah, I might make like bigger, bigger budget productions.
Yeah.
Um, but like.
I wouldn't mind like the stuff I'm doing right now.
I could hire you to like, like, hey, let's just, instead of just editing videos, let's
also just animate all of them because like $2,000 a video, I don't care, you know, like
if I could do that.
Hot shit.
Yeah.
I'd love to.
I mean, that reminds me of, of T-Bap, like what you were saying before, uh, like you,
you talking about all the, like the jokes and the gags and stuff in T-Bap, like, I mean,
I don't think all of them were great.
Some of them were really stupid.
Yeah.
Um, but they're, I don't know, there were some really good, like, there were some really
good funny creative bits that me and Nate did together and like, I don't know, I feel
like my, my comics don't come out fast enough for me to like, yeah, be like putting myself
out there and like being creative in a way that I used to be with like every week we'd
have a new T-Bap out and I'd make jokes and also like, yeah, I liked, I liked making jokes.
My comics are not like, they're not full of jokes, you know, they're not, they're not
funny in that way anymore.
Well, that's the thing, like, kind of going back to what I was saying about like, uh,
both with the doing anonymous work and with the thing that you were doing where you were
drawing all those, uh, those scenes from your RP, like, um, I think artists get so hung
up on making a big thing that they forget they can also make like a million small things,
you know, like what if, like if you could afford to in between each comic to just draw
some fun wacky picture that's like a funny thing or to make like a 30 second sketch comedy
thing on YouTube or something, you know, just to like, because I've seen some guys who do
stuff like that, even, uh, Andrew Hussie before he got so into Homestuck where he would do
like those Star Trek edits, like, you know, just to bounce off and he had like all the
different, uh, blogs and stuff like that, just to bounce around and do all these different
kinds of things. Um, you know, and it like for me, I personally, I would love to do more
of that kind of stuff. And I actually, now that I finally like have so much free time,
I've actually made some anonymous content where like people know I made it. But like
for instance, I have this gigantic anime depth and obscurity chart that I made that like
gets posted on 4chan all the time. Like I just, I just made it for 4chan like here,
there's a chart and throw it around or like a, like a magical girl, um, recommendations
flow chart. Like I've just made that stuff with, there's no monetary gain for me to make
this thing. And I don't care that it's attached to my name. I just want it to exist. And it's
because like I can make, you know, all I have to do right now to make enough money to live
is I have to write four scripts and pay the divu to make videos out of them. And the rest
of my time doesn't have to be dedicated to making money. You know, I made all those vlogs
last month, I made like 30 vlogs and I did make money off of them, but that was not the
incentive to make them. It was, I felt like turning on a camera and recording something.
And I think it's good that you, it's, it's healthy for your, for your feeling as an artist
to not feel like you have to make a big thing or else no one's going to patron you, you
know, um, yeah, I think that's where Tom's trapped to, you know, where he's like trying
to make this giant monolithic series that he's working towards because he has to like
have a breakout hit, you know, he said, he said one time that he thought the series would
go for like 10 years. It'll take 10 years for him to finish a chapter at the rate he
knows.
Oh God, don't say that.
He literally spent a year drawing six pages, like he, of an action scene.
Listen, I was talking to him through that year and like there were lots of little moments
where he kept changing his mind and being like, no, I'm going to make it a motion comic.
No, I'm going to make it a web comic. No, I'm going to do pages. No, I got to, yeah,
it was, yeah, that's a whole, that's a whole story.
Yeah.
I mean, I can't, I can't do anything right now because right now it's crunch time because
I'm trying to finish up sketches of this first chapter of champion to submit it to Hive
Works before the 15th, because I would really like to be a part of the Hive Works network.
I think that would get me a lot of new.
Am I like, by doing this podcast, am I wasting a lot of your time? I just looked at the calendar
and it's the third and that's 12 days.
I tell you, I tell you what, Digi, I mean, I meant today has been a complete fucking
bust for me. I have just completely failed on every level to achieve anything that I
set out to do when I woke up. So I finally was like, Hey, Digi, you want to, you want
to record this thing? I can't.
I know the feeling.
I'm too, yeah, I mean, I have to do something.
I, if it makes you feel any better. I, before the month of May started, I got all my work
done and gave it to DeVue under the, like the idea was, I'm going to have a whole month
that I can do whatever I want. I can make the biggest project imaginable. Like that was
the plan. The ideal was I could take on like a hundred episode show if I want or I could
cover a whole franchise. I could write a novel length video in the span of a month.
And I did literally nothing. I did not write a single video the whole month. All I did
was record vlogs and play Doom. And now it's June. And not only did I not make a giant
video, I don't even have any normal videos for June.
So now I have to from scratch make up a bunch of videos for this month. It's already the
third and I have nothing. So, you know, and I have no ideas.
So it's all like, okay, I fucked up. What did I do wrong?
Um, just, hey, you should review patreon.com. There was a moment too when you messaged me
to do the podcast where I was like, I don't know if I can afford to do that right now,
but I don't have any plans yet. So let's just fucking do it. Because last night, last night
I blew all night on four and a half hours of commentary with DeVue. So, you know, yesterday
I was talking to the chat. I was day drunk. It was great.
That was great.
I woke, I woke, I just like, so that wasn't a productive day. And then I woke up hung
over today and just, you know, God, I lost, I lost two days to that, to the miracle of
alcohol.
Yeah, it's like Kanye said, the plan was drink till the pain over, but what's worse,
the pain or the hangover gets me every time.
Well, I don't know, maybe I can squeeze out a panel or two before bed and then, and then
I'll have them and then I'll get back a little bit of momentum. I'll have a little bit of
momentum going and I can wake up tomorrow and be like, gotta keep, gotta keep on the
roll.
So to get back to making this interview like before we wrap it up, I want to know some
stuff about your process because I was fascinated that you tweeted out like you'd sketched
out the entire chapter of champion.
That's like maybe a little more than half of it.
Okay.
Like two, two thirds, maybe.
Because I was just surprised that it's all like, I don't know, I guess in my head, I
was thinking you would like finish each page as you went, but it's like, like a half way
complete the entire thing at once.
Well, well, let me tell you, Digi, all right. Vapors, I sketched, I sketched the pages out
with pencil and then, and then finished them on, on the computer. And then I guess that's
what I'm doing for a champion to only I'm just sketching them digitally because, because
what I, like I said, I'm going to submit it to Hiveworks, but I want to show them the
entire story thumbnail doubt. So I want to have it all roughed out so they can read it
even if all the pages aren't finished.
So that's a good plan.
So that's deliberate. I'm, yeah, I'm not, I think I, I think I finished like, I think
I finished like three pages, but the rest of them are still rough. I got a, oh my God,
I got to finish like, I got to get like at least one page done a day if there's any hope
for me to get it in on time.
Yeah.
Um, Brunswick was different. Brunswick, I would fit, I would, I would do a page all
at once. I like, I didn't even sketch except for certain poses that were more tricky and
I needed to like do an underlayer sketch and then trace over it. But like half of the Brunswick
things, I didn't even sketch ahead of time. I just like went right in and drew them. Um,
and it was great. And I should probably do more of that.
Yeah, you had said you were going to do that for champion, but I'm guessing you changed
your mind because of this whole submission thing.
Well, well, yeah, kind of due to the submission thing. Also, I mean, a lot of my sketches
are really good. And I think a lot of the better ones, I might just use the sketch as
the final art. Um, and only like only touch up the things that I think actually need touching
up like, like the backgrounds and stuff. Uh, yeah, like I think if I tried, I have a lot
of really good and expressive faces sketch that I think if I tried to like trace over
and clean up, they would lose that energy. So yeah, I don't know. I'll, uh, just use
what's good and change what's bad.
So here's another important question that I should have asked like way earlier, but
uh, I was trying to get through your whole like life story to get up to this point. How
are like, first of all, where do you live and how are you funding it? Because you obviously
aren't making enough on Patreon that it's paying for your life. You're not living off
your art.
No, because like,
I made that, I made that little diagram of myself parachuting with Patreon and just
the different trajectories down into the fire of, of, of, of poverty.
Cause like to go through the, the PCP real quick, like I know that me and DeVoo are living
off of my channel, uh, currently, I think Jeff is full Patreon now. I think he kind
of was from the start. I don't know.
Um,
He makes a bunch.
Jesse's full Patreon hippo still in school. So he's still on his parents dime. We don't
really know where he's going to try to, like, I think he, he wants to be graduated now.
Right. Yeah.
Didn't he like just graduated?
He just finished school. He has a graduation ceremony. Um, so he's either going to get
a job or he's going to go full YouTube. I know he wants to do full time YouTube. It's
just a matter of how quickly can he grow, uh, as a channel.
Tom has been in this weird fucked up Patreon slash art limbo for the last two years.
I think he, I think he got a job.
I think he did too. He mentioned something to that effect because there's no way he's,
yeah, that was another one where I was like, how are you living off of this still? Like
you, cause his Patreon went down a lot.
I mean, he makes it. Yeah, it went down a lot. I mean, he's still, he's still making
more than me on Patreon, but like, I mean that, I don't make anywhere near enough to
live on. So he's like probably is,
And I think we all know that Nate, he apparently pays out the ass for Nate has like the best
normal job, like, yeah, he's got a real job. He, he doesn't want it, but he's been forced
into it by circumstance and he's got to do it to like finish his degree.
And he's, he's, he has been seriously contemplating cause he just finished his degree, right?
Like he's, he's also graduating.
No, he's not, he's not quite done with it yet. I think he's, I think he's got a last
to December. I think he might get his degree in December.
I was under the impression he was almost done. So
He is like, I mean, he's been almost done for a long time.
I don't even understand how he's still in college.
He fucked up many times.
But yeah, so he's, he's been contemplating like taking the plunge to go full YouTube,
but it's just a matter of like justifying the fact that he doesn't make nearly enough
money yet. So what are you doing that you can afford to live?
Well, I tell you, I told you before how much I hate teachings.
Well, now I make, all right, so I have this gig on the internet where it's like a service
that you can like basically just log in and tutor kids up on with and yeah, it's, it's
Chegg. I have, I have an account on Chegg and basically, all right, the last house that
I lived at was I moved in with into their side room hoping to pay, you know, pretty
low rent. But as soon as I moved in, um, there happened to be this kerfuffle between the
people that live there in the landlord and there was legal action. There was like a court
case going on. And while there was a court case, nobody was paying any rent. So I managed
to live in this place for no rent for like six months, just out of total happenstance.
And then when the court case went through, everyone was evicted. And I was like, so I
went home to my parents place for a couple months. And for a while, let me stay without
paying rent. So then I didn't, and then eventually they made me pay a little bit. Um, but, and
then finally, at the beginning of this year, I found a new place with some friends and
we split the rent. It's like not very expensive. It's like $500 a month or less. Anyway, the
point is all those times that I was living on my expenses being very, very low, I was
tutoring and making money and saving up money. And now I have like a little bit saved up
that and my costs are low. So I'm just trying to like, I just have some time, you know, I'm
in, I'm almost in financial free fall, but I can last it out for a little bit longer. So
I'm just trying to get as much art done during this period, try and get my Patreon up to
try and extend, you know, my extend my financial possibilities here.
So basically you're I'll have to tutor more eventually at some point in the future, but
it's not your only income is from this tutoring. And it has been for a long time. And do you
like, would you say that the amount that you are capable of making doing that is like at
all comfortable or like, is it really like this art needs to fucking pay off soon before
I'm in trouble?
I have managed to get by on tutoring money before. I mean, right now it's summer. So there's
very little of that kind of work to do. So like right now, if I needed that, I would be in
trouble. But once the school year starts, if I put my mind to it, I can use it. I mean, I
don't make a good living on it, but I can make like, I can, I can keep myself afloat with it.
So like, yeah, when, when the shit hits the fan and I completely run out of money, that's
going to be what I fall back on.
But you're hoping that if the art takes off, you won't have to do that anymore.
I mean, if, yeah, what kind of Patreon numbers would you need to have before you could like
scale back your tutoring to like only for pocket, like, like that's the secondary job,
like the pocket change job?
This should be, say maybe five or 600, that should be your Patreon goal, by the way, like, put it
up there of, like, if we reach this, yeah, right, right now, my, my, my Patreon now, it's the goals
are structured with like $1,000 a month being the goal of like, at this level, I can sustain
myself. That's, that's a little high, like, that's, that's, I mean, that would be how much I need to
make like a comfortable living, which I mean, is still really low, like $12,000 a year is not
very much money, but, but like, that's what I, that's what I feel I would need to get to like be
comfortable and not have any like concern about my money.
At 500 a month, I would be like, basically breaking even and like, I could make it on that much
unless there were some crisis or unless my situation changed somehow.
Personally, I want everybody in the PCP to be making a lot of money to make the whole moving into an
area possible, you know, like, because we've talked a lot about either, because like, right now, I think
we're at the level where a lot of us could move into a place together and afford it. But I don't
consider that the most ideal scenario, like to me, the most ideal scenario is we all live close to
each other, you know,
I've, yeah, I've heard, I heard you talked about this on a doozy brothers lately, and I totally agree.
Like, I mean, I don't, I don't know, I don't know how good of roommates, all the PCP would be. I'm sure
it would be fine. But like, I mean, I think probably I would get annoyed at Jesse. I just, I think he
would probably get up to shit that would piss me off once in a while. And like, no matter how good a
roommate someone is, I mean, living in close proximity always makes you hate people. So I wouldn't, I
wouldn't want that.
Yeah, I don't think I'll have like, I think you, DeVue and Nate would all be really easy for me to live
with. So I don't, I mean, maybe DeVue, I'm not 100%. I think Nate would be a pretty easy roommate. I
think DeVue is, I mean, I think DeVue will be an easy roommate because and this is this, this word, I'm
not using it to the extreme that it'll sound like, but he's sort of obedient in the sense that if, if there
were DeVue, if there were rules, DeVue loves you, DeVue is, DeVue is so on board with everything you say.
Well, like if, if there were rules that everyone had to follow in a household, DeVue would hold himself to
those rules very strongly. Like if, if I was like, yeah, I could see that if I was like, this is how much
we're paying every month, these are the boundaries, like socially and what we need to do, DeVue would be
like, and also you, you're sleeping in the closet. He'd be down for all of that. You know, he said it
himself, like that he would live in a closet.
Would you say he's a very, he's like a very rules abiding person?
To get what he wants. Yes. Like, because the benefit of living together would be so strong, he would be
willing to make as many sacrifices as possible to make it so that it worked well. You know, like he
would be oriented around, how do I make this experience good for everybody so that they will keep me
around? You know? Yeah. Whereas I used to be, yeah, go on. No, just whereas Jesse does not follow rules
unless it aligns with his interests, you know, I think Jesse might, I don't know, it might not be as bad as
I'm imagining, but I could see it being really tough to live with Jesse. I mean, he'd always be fucking shouting
in his room, but he's doing his recordings and whatever.
Yeah. Well, depending on the size of the house, it might not matter. Like if we all lived in my house, it would, you
would never notice that was happening, because everything's so spaced out.
The, um, I used to be a terrible roommate. I used to be, I used to try to be real sneaky, like I'm like, I'm a
sneaky guy. And I, and I, and I fuck over people that I think don't need, that I, that I think won't be hurt too
bad by like fucking companies and stuff. And like employers, I'm totally happy overrepresenting my hours worked,
because I don't care about their welfare. I used to be like that for people too. And for like my, my roommates and
stuff, like I would try to like sneakily like not pay rent or like pay it late or like, you know, see how much I
could get away with. But like, I don't know, the last couple places I've been at, like, I learned eventually that
that stuff is no good. And like, when you, when you're an asshole like that, like, it hurts you in the long run. So
now I'm very, now I'm like very like up on my shit has mentioned that I'm always, I always pay on time.
You know, it's funny, Nate mentioned that you apparently don't do dishes. And Nate was like, man, that never
does the dishes. And then DeVue, DeVue apparently just as of this month, has struck up a deal with his family, that
if he does all the dishes, he doesn't have to pay any rent.
That's fucking awesome. What a sweet deal. And he said, he actually enjoys doing the dishes. So
yeah, I can see it. And I was just like, it's not a terrible job. I was thinking like, Nate's telling me Ben never
does dishes. And I'm like, well, that's a problem. But then I've got DeVue over here to cancel out that
problem. If it got too bad, do you know, but, but did Nate mention why I never do dishes? No, he did not. I
mean, well, the place I'm living at now, um, like the guy who found the house, he eventually like, he tried to
borrow money from other people living here, and like tried to fuck, he had this big web of debts, and it
eventually became too much. And we kicked him out. But his dad, who is technically homeless, still comes to our
house, like every morning to do his laundry. And when he does his laundry, he does our dishes for us. So we
have, we have a homeless man doing our dishes for us every day. That's, that's why I don't have to do
dishes.
Whoa, that is a mind blowing story.
It's, it's, it's convenient.
See, I have all these weird, like, pragmatist ideas about what I will be like if I live, like my whole idea is if I am no
longer dependent on my parents in any way, I will have two plates, period.
Two plates, I will only have two plates, because
Lamau two plate, do you even lift, bro?
That's just like the idea is I can only, I need to just because sometimes your food takes up two plates, if it's like, you
know, soup and grilled cheese or something like that. But like, the idea is that you don't put soup on a plate. But
anyway, I would have to just wash the dish to use it. So instead of having dishes that can pile up, I just have one
dish, I eat off of it, and you just wash it when you need it. I eat off of it, and then I clean it, and then I pick it up and
eat off of it again. And it's, it always gets cleaned, because I don't have another dish to, you know, to cycle through.
So like, if I was in like that kind of living situation, I would just have like my one, like I would have my one plate, I
would put food on it, eat it, take it out, wash it off and keep it in my room, you know, so it would never be, no one else
would ever assume it was their dish. It's just mine, you know, I've kind of done the same. I have a mug like that. I
kind of do the same thing with like groceries where like, when I started buying my own groceries, I leave them all in the
bags. And I just put the grocery in the so everyone knows it's mine. And like, and they also can't see what it is and get
tempted to eat it. So yeah, I have lots of those little salute. I like the idea of we all live in one place, but we're all
doing our own thing. It's like we don't live together, you know, so it doesn't feel like a family where I don't, I
wouldn't want to run the risk of there being like, you know, disagreements and confrontations and us like coming to hate
each other, I would be really sad if that's why like my ideal is that I could pay for like most of it. Because like the
only thing I really see being a problem is like debts and rent. Like it's always money, money is what fucks up
friendships. When people all move in together as soon as one guy can't keep a job, can't keep you know, paying the
rent. That's the guy who becomes the problem. That's what that's what happened to our friend with the with the dad who
does the dishes. He just like, it wasn't even that he didn't pay it was that he like wasn't honest about it and kept
promising that he could pay right up until the rent was late and he didn't have it. Oh man, I'm so I'm really used to like
living with because my family we've taken in like countless relatives like almost up until a couple years ago, we had
like a constant revolving door of people living with us. And so finally, like, like, like my grandma lived us for a while
and then my dad would just like, you know, buy her a car and get a place that was cheap for her and like here now you're
somewhere, you know, and like, we constantly had like people around and they would always be fuck ups, you know, they would
never get their shit together. Nobody ever gets a job fast enough. They don't save enough money. And so like, I'm used to all
the reasons that this would happen. There was one time I had both my cousin and one of my friends both shared my room with
me, you know, like no walls or anything, we were all in the same room for like years. And, and then like, you know, they just
couldn't seem to get a handle on their cash well enough until finally my dad was like, you guys got to go, you know, like you
have to make enough money and get out of here. So I mean, my my dad's had to do that to me a bunch of
right. So over the years, I'm used to seeing that happen. And but like the reason that we've been able to put up people
so much is that my dad just makes so much money that he can afford to take care of an extra person, you know, but it was
finally just at the point where like, my parents are getting older, and they just don't want to have to deal with that
anymore. You know, they're like, we're done with this whole putting up people randomly thing. But on the other side of the
coin, my dad really wants to move him and my mom out and get their own place and just leave this house to me and my
brothers. And like, dude, and he wants that's like, that's a huge value. That's like, that's a really valuable thing.
Right. But I mean, he wants us to be paying for it, you know, but he's also because like the thing is he kept offering me
like, Alright, the house costs about $2,500 a month to run. Can you move in enough people that we can all afford it?
You know, and I was like, how many, how many bedrooms are there? There's like four clear bedrooms and three rooms that can
be made into bedrooms. So the place I live now, the rent is 3200 and we have six people living right, which is pretty
good. Like I it's pretty here's the thing. So he changed that though recently because he kept saying like, you know, like he was
saying 2,500 is like the amount it's going to cost a month. But what because what he was talking about at the time was him and my
mom and shade moving out into their own, you know, into a difficult shade still completely dependent on him, then moving
into a place and leaving the house to me and whoever I can move in. And they were also kind of in the mindset that Victor
might be moving in with his girlfriend at some point. But right now, Victor doesn't have a job. And he's probably not going
to move with it with her anytime soon. And shade, they don't really need to take him with them because he's an adult now.
So they're like, What if we moved and got our own place? And I my dad puts up $1,000 towards the house to cover shade and Victor.
And I just move in enough people to pay $1,500 a month. So for me, I'm like, Well, I've already got me in DeVue. And I can easily afford
500 a piece for us. So if I can just get one more guy who's willing to pay $500 a month, we're set, you know,
I, I want one thing that I want Jesse to move out of his house. He's his situation seems so right. Seems so rough, you
know, he's always talking about like his mom and his family. And like, it doesn't sound very good. I really want him to get a new
place. But he seems so he seems like he's kind of got inertia, you know, like he's pretty like he's pretty set up where he is.
Yeah, it's like that his his room and his house is so big a part of who he is. And like his mentality, it is his, his basement is
like, like, imagine, imagine a fucking Jesse would video in a different room.
Yeah, it's it's hard like a set or something.
Like, that's my like, I honestly, like, when I was talking about like moving people in, I was like, What can we possibly
what room could we put Jesse in that would be like, enough to cat like to have his personality in there?
You know, I hope to God, you have a furnace room.
Sadly, no. Well, we have, we have a stairs, a little, like, barely you can even fit in their room that that cold Corona could
be it. It's next to the furnace. Well, not a furnace, but I want to I want to live with cold Corona.
But yeah, I, I, again, I think the ideal situation is everyone makes enough money that we can all afford houses close to
each other. And like, I really want the red letter media lifestyle. Like, that's been my personal dream, because they
all just kind of are a bunch of guys who live in Wisconsin and have a studio and they hang out and they make stuff, you
know, like, or Game Grumps is essentially the same. But a lot of them like live together and stuff like that, or have
been in like arranged living situations.
You know, I would I would love to I would love that just for what I was talking about before about, you know, my
comics take so long. I would I would love to work on like little smaller things with people. I think I think that
because if I literally had anyone, I could I would use I would use you constantly. Like if you were around here.
Yeah, use me, digi. Use me.
Well, I would put you in I'm yours for the taking you in everything because like if I had people that I like, like my
biggest problem is I don't have anyone around who's like interested and talented in the kind of work I do or like or
can do, you know, like, because if I had you guys around, I wouldn't stick to just this kind of rigid analysis video
type thing that I do, like how me and Jesse have always wanted to do the plebe and the weeb where if we live
together, we can easily do this like talk show about anime where we play these like eccentric characters. And, you
know, like the reason that analysis videos are the only thing I could really do is because that's the only thing I can do by
myself, you know, or just hiring someone who lives a fucking all the way across the country, you know, to help with like if I
had someone sitting right next to me and I say, let's film a thing where I'm a character and I'm running around doing
something weird in this video, then just having someone who can hold a camera is like a huge opening of doors, you know, kind of
like when Nate bought that like nice camera and I was like, you know, you're going to have someone who you're going to need someone
who could just adjust the focus. Because like, you can't adjust the focus on a camera pointed at yourself if it's a nice
camera. And that's such a huge limitation that just having someone there who can move the little focus bar, you know, is like
such a huge advancement. So that that's why I want people around so bad, because like all my friends are totally
uninterested, totally unambitious, none of them want to do anything, not at all interested in YouTube. Victor is starting to
get interested because he can't find work. And he's kind of getting desperate, which is why he wants to do stuff like he's
trying to get that that thing he wants to do with you off the ground. The only problem is he has no money to pay you.
So I want I want to do that. Like I liked the script. But I can't I can't do it for free. I can't do it pro bono.
That's just not a viable life with the time it would take, although it is only like a two minute thing. But I mean, I told
him it would take me a couple days. And it's true. I wouldn't do it for free. I mean, I can't I just can't you just can't do
stuff. I mean, I mean, I'm trying to be a I don't know how much you would charge him. How much do you think you
would charge maybe like I don't know. I mean, I don't know exactly how much work it'll be. Let's say like 250 bucks.
Yeah, he doesn't have the money. Is that high? I don't think it's high for the for what the job is. It's just that he
wouldn't be able to afford it. I could pay. I mean, I'm trying to be reasonable. I don't know. I do more than that to edit my
videos. So like I don't know. I think if I was con that sounds like I'm thinking about it. And I'm like if I was confident
there was going to be a return on that video, I would just pay you and have Victor pay me back through ad revenue. I don't
know. There's no guarantee. There's no guarantee of that. 200 views for all I know, you know, although I would promote it if I'm, you
know, a producer on it. Naturally, but the producing. Yeah, I guess that's what I guess that is what you would be pretty
literally funded his creation. Man, talking about cameras, though, before reminded me that me and Nate filmed scenes for like two
of his upcoming best guy ever is like six and 10 months ago. I know I know about that. And like, oh my god, they were he was
describing the videos to me back then and they sounded so good. And then he spent six months on fucking Undertale, which like
came out fine. Don't get me wrong. And then and then he did one punch man kind of released. He said he was working on it like
basically the same time. But they did. I wanted those other two. He's still working on it. I wanted the he's I know but I want
that like he has like a pecking order of when each video is going to come out and like they're all set up.
So long ago, like, like we got one of my friends, we wrote one of my friends in to like help us film it. And we
promised him that it would come out. And like, I mean, I'm sure he's forgotten about it. But I just I want to be able to tell
him like, Hey, Conrad, this is also guys also named I see. Yeah, he's like, Hey, Conrad, remember that film you made a year ago?
Well, here's the YouTube video. I just I want that for myself.
I can't believe you know two Conrad's.
Um, it's weird. I don't know any. I've never met another Conrad.
Yeah, I he's more of a friend of a friend. Like, I don't know, he's he's alright. He's he's bipolar as fuck.
He's he's he's cool though. He's got a red beard.
But yeah, all those things I was just saying is also like why I wanted to talk because like I've always wanted to do a project
with you. And like, I don't know, I feel really strongly about the artistic abilities of everyone in the procrastinators,
we're like, I desperately want us all to collaborate. But it has to be the right thing. Like I'm not going to force a fucking
that guy with the glasses collab and like, Oh, Ben's in my video because Ben's in my video. It's like, if I'm going to do
something with you, I want it to be something that uses your like that will impress people and make them want to go seek you
out. You know, like, whoa, who drew this? You know, I want I want that to be the reaction. Like if we did the sort of online
one, I want people to be like, who did the art for this? They're great. And I can say here's his Patreon, you know,
doing doing the thumbnails and the faces for TBAP was very satisfying. And I would really like I would really like to do that
kind of thing again. I mean, it wasn't that hard, like the actual like, I mean, the editing, honestly, editing the faces in was way
harder than drawing them, like 10 times harder. Yeah, I'd like to I'd like to be providing. I'd like to provide art to
things. And I know you said Victor would use me as an actor. I mean, I don't consider myself to have much acting
experience. Well, it's that he likes writing around you, because the first time we got out, it was like, because the way you
and Nate communicate is like so character like, like, you have this very fast, like almost, just we didn't ask like back and
forth thing going on.
I was thinking about this lately. Like, like, yeah, everyone who likes who liked TBAP said that like me and Nate's dynamic was
like a huge part of it and made it and it's like, it's a I think it's a waste that me and Nate don't like aren't making
anything like that anymore. I think so too. I was under the impression that was entirely because you just didn't want to be on
YouTube, though.
I don't know. I mean, we tried to keep it going with TBAP plays. But that was like, that was such a slog. And we don't I mean, we
don't want to do TBAP anymore. So like, what else? I mean, I guess we're on the PCP together, but like, it's
usually anime reaction videos, every every week, every every new anime come out, you talk about them like, I mean, me and me
and Nate and Jeff have been trying to launch like more anime podcasts, like ourselves and just are having such a hard
time with like, having something we all want to do because like when it comes to like what made TBAP work and what made
like podcasting about MLP, like make any sense is that it came out every week. And so everyone was on the same page. And like
for me, I hate watching current anime, like I never watch stuff while it's coming out. So like, you know, me and Nate and
Jeff, like every new season, there's like this big great excuse to talk about all the new shows because they all just
started and we'll watch all the first episodes and we can talk about them. But then I don't keep up with any of them. So
like, we're always like, Oh, what if we did one like six weeks later, like how did they all turn out? And I'm like, but
then I'd have to watch them all. I don't want to do that. But I do think that there's like room in the world for that to be
a thing like people doing a episodic podcast about shit. It's just there's not enough like good people. That's what makes the
TPC so great is like, I feel like I've gathered all the best people here, you know, like we are all here. Who else would we
possibly want around, you know?
I like, I like, I like our group. I like our little TPC. And yeah, it's, it's I mean, me and Nate, and like any other
pairing you could think of, I think, I think if the if two of us collabed on the right thing, it could be really
great. But like, yeah, man, that's why I love getting Jesse into my raps so much. Because like, I've, I have this
Rodin was really good, dude. Rodin was glad you liked it. Um, yeah, I don't. Jesse probably doesn't know this. But he is
listening to us right now. But I, what? Yeah, they Jesse and DeVue are both listening to us right now.
Ew, they came in about like 10 minutes ago, I want to say.
I hate those fuckers so much. But anyways, um, I at one point, like Jesse made, I think it was when he made asshole boy
where I made like this weird random thing and sent it to him. And he like wrapped over it and made a video out of it and
patron did. And I was like, wait a minute, shouldn't I be getting some of that money? I couldn't help but think that. And I've
done a few things for Jesse where I've given him like random stuff and he's made videos out of it. And I was like,
well, it's fine because I'm gonna eventually get him to do stuff for me too. Like I want to have, you know, Jesse
parts in my videos. And so far, the only time I've ever done it was with the My Little Pony leap of faith video where I got him
to do all these cancer jokes, which was fantastic. But like all these years, I've just been like waiting for the day that I
have a good Jesse Woods spot to put in my video to mark on Patreon and not give him any of the money just so I can have payback.
Your videos don't really lend themselves to like celebrity or, you know, cameos. That's exactly why, like I said, I want like if we all
live together, I could do different kinds of videos that like would because there's plenty of ways that like, again, with red
letter media, like it makes perfect sense that there's five guys in some of those videos, because that's just the type of video
it is. But like the stuff I do, like, you know, if you watch the stuff that the collabs I did do back in the pony days, like with
me and Tom, it was always just kind of two reviews smushed together. You know, like, I talked for a little while, Tom talks for a
little while, we both make our points. And that's it. Like with the leap of faith video, what made it a good collab because I had
Jesse and Gibb and take both in there. And it was like, I had this whole segment where I said, this video is too dark, quick.
Jesse, make some jokes. And then Jesse comes out and makes these like really dark jokes that were, you know, like not at all
lightening up. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I remember that one. I wasn't I forgot. But I just it's all coming back. But that's like the only
context I've ever had where throwing some random comedy bit into the video like flowed well and was a good idea. But I mean, I
could have like if if I was making a video about like commercialism or something, and I wanted to throw in random
advertisements, I'd get everybody to do that. Or like with Nate with the Monster Musume one, like that was genius to have each
of us act out like a weird monster creature. And then they're it just like cuts to those scenes. Like that was great.
I liked I liked that part of the video. I don't think it was a great video. It was kind of halfway. I think he made some good
points. But I think the the audio made that hard to listen to because it was the audio was too loud. Mostly I just don't
care about Monster Musume. I mean, that's really what does it for me.
Right. But I do love the I think the monster parts are like fucking hilarious.
I like my little thing where I'm in the bathtub and I just pour a little that part. I think that's my favorite part. I
maybe I'm biased, but I think I just I need more of that. I need more of the procrastinators in things together. And like,
I, you know, when you say it like that, I really agree. I'd like I missed I missed being in things. I think I said this
the other day. Yeah, I miss being like, I missed having appearances. I mean, the PC, the PCP is my only outlet for it.
And it's good.
Well, I love the PCP because it's given like people are starting to understand why we all hang out and like why we're all
friends. And like that we're all friends. Because like back in the day, when we were calling ourselves the horseshoe
crew, and we did a few podcasts together. But like, I felt like not a lot of people were connecting the dots and like
putting us together, which led to that hilarious scenario. I'll put a link to this fan art that you drew for me in the
description of
Oh, the best friends party?
Because I was talking about how people who draw my OC character with like all these other famous brony analyst people who
like I wasn't friends with at all. And a lot of them I couldn't stand. And they draw us and these same people had no idea
who Jesse was, even though he was your best friend.
Because there would be tons of art of like, OC characters hanging out and it'd be like me and KP and like maybe Tom would
be there because people knew me and Tom were friends from way back. But like, Jesse is like my best friend and he would
never get drawn in anybody's fan art. Like he was always left out of group shots and stuff. And it would like it would kind of
piss me off because I'm like, I don't I don't like that I'm being represented this way as like friends with all these people I
can't stand. And you know, the people who I love aren't even in the pictures, you know.
The I really like that I really like that the PCP has sort of developed its own little community. I mean, it's not a big
community, but there is definitely a PCP like PCP fan club, apparently, which is a little weird.
Oh, yeah. I make that I'm curious about that. Like, I want to know what the heck's going on in there. What are they
scheming? Are they plotting against us? Are they plotting to take our places? I play like double agent for us because I
think he's been there. We can have him feed us the download and what's going on.
I've considered like secretly joining and like pretending to be I don't just show up and be like, Hey, fellow PCP listeners,
just you're at run of the mill fan here. What's going on? Oh, shit. But now I can't because I'll know it's me if I do
that. I'll have to change. I have to change my approach. Yeah, yeah. But yeah, I like that it's got its own little
thing. And I mean, people really like people really like Jesse, like some of the most positive comments videos ever got
were about the editing on the one that just come around so much because like when we started PCP, like we got a lot of
like comments that were like kick Jesse off and stuff like that. And then we like, wait, we did. Yeah, no, at first
people were like, like, like Jesse was the one who people were having like the most negative reaction to until the first
time he edited one. And then everyone like completely flipped like was like Jesse's the best guy on the podcast. Like it
totally changed the perception of him. And like now people love him. And which is all I've ever wanted is that people will
look at our whole group and appreciate that we all think each other are great. Like because that's the basis of this
group is that we were all like, we all like each other's content. And like, I think, to me, that's the glue that holds it
together is like enjoying one another stuff. And the fact that we're all very brutal towards each other about like how we
feel about each other's work. And like, you know, show like, I can show up and like Nate wants to like knows he has to
work faster because he looks at me and he's like, how am I not making as much money or getting as much views as Digi?
And it makes him mad, you know, and then he works faster. And I look at Jesse, and I'm like, my videos don't have enough
personality, I don't have enough character. And so then I get mad and make 1000 vlogs, you know, and like, so I think we have
that feeding off of each other, because we all look at each other's work and think I need to be as successful or I need to
be as good as him, you know. So like it puts us in combat to like in combat, but none of us hates the other guy, none of us is
like, Oh, God, like, it would be different if someone was in here who like, you know, was making shit tons of money, and we all
thought that their content was garbage, then we would be like, Okay, get the fuck out of here, you know,
I, I wish I wish that I felt more of a hot blooded rivalry with either Tom or Mage. Unfortunately, I really don't.
I think Tom started to feel it towards you.
I need a hot blooded rival of my own God damn it.
Tom's jealousy over your skill has started to make him like more like really he sent me this really long message yesterday, like,
basically asking about like for advice on whether he should be trying to quit YouTube or not and like where he should be going.
On the basis of realizing that he's just know you, like he's like, I'm no Ben, I'll never be as fast as Ben and as cool as Ben.
So how do I, what do I have to do?
I feel so, I feel so slow, you know, like I look, I got, I look at the like that post I made the other day of all the pages I did this
month. I mean, it looks like a lot when you put them all together, but like it's less than a page a day and they're only rough.
They're not even finished.
I feel like I'm not
you're comparing yourself to fucking Bakuman and to the Japanese where like, I do, I compare myself to the Japanese all the time,
like, which is not, I don't understand.
I don't understand why like Western creators just, they just don't produce at this prodigious rate.
Like if it's possible, why aren't they doing it?
It's just that I don't Japanese are like have a very different mindset about work like in their in, I think, I think that in Japan work is seen
as like a duty that you must do.
And in America, I think work is seen as something that you force yourself to do.
You know, like, I think the general cultural idea of work is that it's not fun.
And that's why so many people want to be artists and like to do something that, you know, or to be famous, more less artists, more famous.
People want to be famous because they see it as like a fun, easy version of work, you know, getting paid to do nothing, which is not
what it is, but that's how people see it.
And that's why we idolize fame in our culture so much.
Whereas in Japan, they really don't idolize fame.
They idolize hard work, you know.
But like, but like, like Brian Leo Malley is a world class, you know, comic maker.
And he makes, he took him, you know, he made six books in like six years.
That's like, you know, maybe a page every day or every other day or something.
Yeah, I guess every other day.
H-ero. Yeah, like, I mean, less than a page a day.
H-ero Oda makes fucking like 30 pages a week.
Well, Oda makes 20 pages a week and I'm sure he has a team of assistants.
He does. I mean, I mean, Brian had assistants, but like he, yeah, Oda probably made more extensive use of his like team of assistants.
I don't know. I want to, I've been in a rut lately.
I'm trying to get to a place where like the next panel, like I have the
next page and the next panel, just like, I know it in my mind.
And I just like, I can just like, like slam it out.
Like, I know what it's supposed to look like and I just do it.
But like these past couple of days, I've sort of been in a rut because like I'm sort of on a bit of like exposition-y bit.
That's like, it's not really the point, but it's necessary to set up the point.
And it's, it's not, I'm just not as invested in it as I am in like the beginning and the end.
I don't know. Hopefully that won't mean that it's going to be boring when it comes out.
But I'm trying my best.
Yeah, it's been, it's been, it's been a little, it's got a little art block,
got a little bit of an artist block going right now.
That's, and that's why I'm here doing this instead of, instead of drawing.
I mean, obviously I'm in a fairly similar position.
I'm, I have a lot of ideas of things that could be the June month videos,
but none that I'm like jumping on right now, you know, they all kind of feel.
They all kind of feel like, maybe that one, but it's hard to force yourself.
How do you feel about that?
Do you have a hard time like forcing yourself to do something that you're like,
for me, I have to be like enthusiastic about the video, you know, in order to write it.
Like if I, I have like a long list of like video ideas that are great ideas that like,
like I'm just not up for writing yet.
And like the idea of like making myself write one just because I know it's a good idea is so unattractive.
Do you have that?
Yeah, the, I mean, I, yeah, I, I'm no good at, I'm no good at getting myself to draw.
Like, like the best days I ever have are the days where I wake up and start drawing immediately,
but I can never do that.
Like my motivation is, is low in the mornings.
Like my motivation increases as the day goes on always.
Cause like the less time I have left in the day, the more urgently I feel like I need to get something done.
But yeah, like, like, um, I can't, I'm really terrible at forcing myself.
I have no discipline.
I pretty much just have to like wait, I pretty much just have to wait for some bit of like enthusiasm
or at the very least a bit of like less having like less lethargy than usual.
I kind of have to like wait for, for the time and then I can feel it's like now I feel
like drawing might be bearable now, I have to do it now or else I'll miss this golden
opportunity.
Do you ever have like, uh, do you have any traps that you set for yourself or techniques
for psyching yourself up like, uh, like DeVu, I know is pretty good at this where he'll
set weird alarms.
DeVu told me one the other day.
The other day DeVu mentioned that he like puts up a timer and like every time he accomplishes
something he resets the timer, like a certain, every time he does a certain and I actually
started that like yesterday, I opened up a little timer app and I've just had it going.
Um, oh God, what's it at now, uh, 22 hours, oh fuck, uh, 22 and a half hours, no, no,
fuck you DeVu, you fucked me, you fucked me.
For me, there's like a lot of, um, I would say I'm, I'm relatively bad at, at like those
kind of things because they're self-imposed and it's so easy for me to go, yeah, but fuck
it, you know, like I'm the, I'm the type of guy who will set myself an alarm and then
like when the alarm goes off, I'll turn it off and go back to bed or go back to whatever
I was doing before because I'm just like, yeah, I have the control here and tomorrow's
another day, you know, but I'm, I'm the same about alarms, but I like this timer thing
because it's passive and like all it does is like add an additional stressor, remind
you how shitty you are.
Kind of passive urgency, yeah, uh, so it's, uh, I mean, I think it might be helping a
little bit.
It sounds kind of just started using it, but I like it.
Maybe I should try it for this fucking, uh, videos I'm trying to do this month.
I'm a lot more into like weird superstitions.
For me, because, uh, I like the whole like, um, June is going to be the month, you know,
and so it's like leading up to June starting, I made sure to get anything, like any unfinished
work I had had to be done by then, like the biggest one was Digi Bros.
Like I forced Victor for us to finish the Dark Souls 3 Let's Play so that it would be done
and then the entire month of June, I'd be, I wouldn't have to worry about Let's Plays,
you know.
Ironically, I've then recorded a commentary and a podcast immediately, but, uh, like,
I like that, um, like clean my plate and now here's the set time and like, let's do it.
Let's put all everything into this one thing we're about to do, you know, do you ever have
those kind of almost superstitious feelings, like, I have to get it done on Friday because
if it's before the weekend, then I know I did it, you know.
Uh, I have been weirdly, I have, I mean, not like the last day or two, but for the last
couple of weeks, I have been weirdly good about getting a page done a day, like, just
like not, like, no matter how long it takes, just, I just don't go to bed until I get something
done, I get a page sketch that day, which is why I have like, you know, 20 something
done for the month, uh, and like, like, it's not an optimal workflow, like, I'm basically
just slacking off all day and then rushing it done at the very end, but like, hey, I
mean, at least it's getting done, right?
Um, so yeah, kinda, it's not exactly a superstition.
I've got a system to propose for you.
This is how I finished my nano-remo novel back in 2010.
You know about nano-remo, right?
Oh my god.
I'm aware of nano-remo.
National write a novel month?
Novel writing.
Yeah.
Month of November every year, and the goal is to write a 50,000 word novel within the
month of November, and in order to do that, you have to write 1,667 words a day, which
for some people sounds way high, for people like me, doesn't sound very high, I can crank
that out pretty easily, but it's a lot harder with fiction, and...
I think I would have a really hard time doing that.
The website, um, like, because there's a lot of like participatory tools on the website.
There's like, you know, an extensive forum, lots of little things it'll give you to like,
try to motivate yourself, but the biggest one is that you plug in your word count at
the end of each day, and you know, it keeps like a graph of how you're doing, and like,
it tells you how many words you have to do to catch up, or like, you know, keeps track
of how you're doing and stuff like that.
So, um, when I did it in 2010, I was like, the first two days, I think I wrote like 5,000
words a day, so I was like way ahead of schedule, and then I didn't write, like, I think I had
about, I had 26,000 words at the end, like, within two weeks, and then I just stopped
writing for the entire rest of the month, and then on the very last day, I was like,
I'm going to try to do this, I have 24,000 words, so the goal is write 1,000 words an
hour.
How long did it take you to write 24,000 words?
Like the first two weeks of the month, I wrote the first 24,000, and then the last day of
the month, I wrote the entire rest of it.
So what I did was I said, I said there's 24 hours in the day, so I have to write 1,000
words per hour.
Any time I have, like, if I finish before the hour is over, then I get to do something
other than write for the rest of the hour, but then once the next hour starts, I have
to get back to writing.
If I write 2,000 words within before the hour is over, then I get the next hour off.
So starting from midnight, I wrote 1,000 words each hour for like 6 hours, and then I wrote
like 2,000, and then went and ate lunch during the next hour.
And then I, you know, I think at one point I had 20 minutes left in an hour, and I took
a nap for those 20 minutes, set an alarm to wake me up as soon as the next hour started,
and I wrote 24,000 words in a day.
It was a fucking nightmare.
That's fucked up, man.
That sounds like, alright, here's, I know I wouldn't be able to do nanoremo, because like
here's been my process lately.
I visualized what's going to happen on the next page, and I can draw it, and sometimes
there's a little bit of struggle, but like it's usually relatively easy, especially
if it's just like characters talking or something.
Like I can draw the page in like an hour, but then I'll spend hours thinking about what
they're saying, like the words, like choosing the words is so much harder.
I hope I get better at it, because it's been a real, it's been a real training, honestly.
I feel like that's the opposite problem Tom has, like he seems to be really naturally
good at writing, and then like he second guesses-
He considers himself more of a writer, I think.
Yeah, and he second guesses everything he does as an artist, like.
Yeah, his, I was talking to Nate the other day, and we both agreed like, his stuff is,
his art is professional looking, like the stuff he's put out on Sorceress Lost, like
it looks as good as it needs to, like he knows what looks good.
It's only that he's not getting it out fast enough, that is the killer.
Maybe you had the same reaction I did, but like when he, when you guys did the draw cast,
like everything he drew looked fine, like it looked perfectly fine, and I was like,
you drew that in 15 minutes, some of them he had colored, you know, and I was like,
clearly you can draw fast, it's just that you want it to be perfect, you know.
He's got, it's doing, doing Brunswick really helped me, because like I didn't care that
much about how it looked, I just wanted to get it done, I just want, and like it was
going to look how it was going to look, so like I wouldn't sketch ahead of time, I would
just draw like a face, and just like there it is, that's, that's how it looks, no correction,
and like it came out fine, so like I'm trying, I'm trying not to worry about like planning
it out in my head, like I'll just like, I'll draw a face, and like that's how it looks,
and if it's totally wrong, I'll do it again, but like I just, I just do it.
I think for me, I've been trying to do that more.
Like what appeals to me is like all in the composition really, like it's kind of like
a Kill La Kill, when people say that that show like is like badly animated or something
like that, or like that it doesn't look good.
Assholes, fucking assholes that think that it doesn't look good, I'll kill them.
You know, I watch like a, I'll watch something like Snow White, or like an old Disney movie
or something, and like everything's moving constantly, but none of it is memorable, like
no one image is memorable, whereas like in Kill La Kill, sometimes it'll just be like
a sliding still shot, but the composition is so strong that it like really sticks with
you.
But like, it's funny, and it's like funny, and it's good, like yeah, it's like, it was,
it wasn't hard to do, but it looks good the way they did it.
I hate it when people complain about those shots, and I remember there was one guy who
made a video where he talked about-
It was a demo.
That fucking idiot.
Yeah.
A demo.
We did it, the demo?
Say that about Kill La Kill?
I hate about the scene where the guy flies back off the podium and like, yes, and he
was so fucking wrong.
Right, that scene is hilarious.
No one's ever been, no one's ever been more wrong.
I am with you.
God damn it.
I told him that too.
I hate him.
Conversation.
Good.
I'm, I'm glad.
Ugh.
Um, wait, I was gonna say, um, uh, oh, uh, Prince on the Popper, you ever seen that movie?
It was like unfinished.
Yeah, I've seen parts of it.
I haven't seen the whole thing.
Yeah.
I mean, the whole thing doesn't exist.
Yeah, it was all, and it was hand-animated at 60 frames per second, and it's all big
and fancy.
It looks terrible.
Parts of it look-
Like, it's creepy looking.
I think parts of it look really cool, but like-
Okay, there are, there are impressive parts, but like-
I actually think some of the best-looking parts-
The visual direction is not attractive in much of the, in much of the film.
I actually think some of the best-looking parts are the unfinished parts, when it's
just like black and white compositions and stuff, and like some of that looks, uh, cooler
than the actual finished stuff.
The part where, the part where he's running around in like a big tile maze, and like there's
weird like visual, um, illusions going on, that part's pretty cool, but like, it just
looks gr- it just looks gross half the time.
Yeah.
Um, all, all this is to say that, yeah, like, being technically advanced and like having
a high frame count and stuff is so not the point.
Right.
And like, Scott, Scott Pilgrim looks so much, Scott Pilgrim looks way better than like,
you know-
You're typical, like-
The ending of Brunswick, like what made it so work was just simply the amount of black
on the page.
That was like all it took to make that ending like, look, like feel so dark and dramatic
just because it was like, suddenly the whole page is black and you've just got like little
flames on there and I was like, oh man, this feels fucking intense, you know.
Oh, you mean like when it's in Claire's cave?
Yeah, in that area.
Like.
Like I did, I did go heavier on the detail at the end because I wanted it to feel really
like, I don't know, dramatic or whatever.
I just mean like-
I really like-
I don't mean that the detail made it like more dramatic, just the fact that it was so
dark, like it, you know, that made it like, it wasn't that you had to draw-
That was, I mean, that was intentional.
I meant like, that scene is supposed to be darker in tone and also like, just, I mean,
it's a cave.
It's just like that-
I don't know.
It's much more creative than trying to like, like you said with the guy who drew the super
photorealistic like monkey screaming or whatever, like, if you want to make an intense picture
of a monkey screaming, it could be fucking scribbles as long as the composition makes
it look intense, you know.
Yeah, it's like high fidelity renderings or not.
I feel like, I mean, it's the 80-20 rule, right?
Like you get 80% of the benefit out of the first 20% of the effort.
So like, just draw a simple thing and get that 20, get that 80 out of the 20 and move
on.
Uh, that's, I mean, that's what I want to do with my work, um, yeah, like the early
part of Brunswick, it's all outside, so it's all like white and light and the backgrounds
are pretty simple.
And then he goes into the cave and then he's in the Claire place and it's all very dark
and fiery.
It has this like, descendants feeling to it, which is effective for the narrative of it.
The emotional stakes growing.
Yeah, I guess that was, I guess that was semi-intentional.
Um, that's, that scene of the two dragonaires coming out of the lava is like the best thing
I've ever made.
Yeah, that's fucking awesome.
I love that panel.
Yeah, yeah.
Um, someone, um, someone messaged, I'm going, going back to Tom, I don't know why, but it's
interesting.
He messaged Tom about me and like he re, he retweeted the post and he said, like, this
is not how you encourage an artist.
I guess he, he didn't approve of the tone of the, of the tweet.
And um, I feel bad calling out this guy because he's obviously a big fan of mine.
But yeah, this guy was, he made a really dumb comment and he was like, you know, I know
you're no, I know you're no Ben Sainter or anything, but you know, you're still okay.
You might even be better than me talking about himself.
And like, I went and looked at, I went, I went and looked at this guy's deviant art
and like this guy is, he's, he's a fucking amateur, you know, his stuff's not great.
Like yeah, obviously Tom is way better than this guy.
Um, but yeah, I was, I was taken aback.
I mean, obviously this guy was like a big, this guy's commented on my other tweets.
I mean, this guy really thinks I'm, I'm hot shit and like he's obviously correct about
that.
But like in particular, this guy is a fan of me.
So that the guy said that I'm like that this guy thought I was, that Tom wasn't as good
as me.
I mean, I mean that that's this guy's opinion.
Uh, I don't know.
Like when you said that Tom messaged you about that, like, I wonder if it was brought about
by this one commenter because like, I don't know, I felt like he's got under his skin
because he tweeted down on his own art and I do think that because your stuff is so like
emotionally strong so quickly that it, you know, has more strength to it.
Like I don't know.
I'm a big fan of your art style in particular.
Like I really appreciate Tom's art and I feel like if someone was a fan of his art style,
then it would be like great, but I personally am not as big a fan of just like the way he
draws things.
Like he has that very like everything's about those variable line widths and everything
and like these very, uh, I don't know how to describe his character.
Yeah.
Tom has like, he has like a, they're very different.
They're very, they're, yours is more of that anime dynamism one piece.
Everything just looks cool and slick kind of feel, you know?
I, yeah, I don't know.
I don't know how I do that, but I'm just so good.
I'm just such a genius.
I definitely think you got some touch and just can't help it.
You seem to be too good for the amount of effort you've put in.
I agree.
No, that's true.
I am too good for the amount of effort.
I mean, I've been drawing seriously for like three years and I feel like, I feel like my
stuff is like way above the level.
I feel like my stuff is near, is near the professional level.
I think that the vapors like, I think in, in terms of everything to do with the art,
the craft of it, I think it, it would, it should be professional, considered professional.
Like, I can understand why.
I don't know about that.
Some, I feel like some of the pages are a little cramped and crowded and I feel like
some of my layouts are not perfect.
Have you ever read any original English, English language manga like that Tokyo Pop
used to publish?
Maybe like a little bit.
If so, I don't really remember.
Most of those.
Like there used to be, there was a sort of wave in the late 2000s of like English language
manga, which is interesting because like it, like you can, it's so annoying that you can
tell it's not Japanese.
Like it, it, it, it, not just any in particular, it annoys me that it is possible to look at
like a manga and be like, clearly this is not Japanese.
How do you get, it, it bothers me that that is the reality.
Well, here's the thing.
But there's a guy called Ogui Maniacs who wrote a fantastic post about this way back
in the day.
I think I have read it.
Is it about the use of tone and about how Western manga overused tone?
They all use tones because they make it look like anime as opposed to like manga, whereas
manga is usually very simple shading and stuff and not using tones much at all.
I think I somewhat overused tone.
I mean, I had read that article before I did the vapors and I tried to keep it in mind
and not overuse them that much.
I think I did go overboard with them in certain places.
I don't know.
Like I, looking at the vapors, I would immediately know that it's not Japanese, but I would not
consider that a problem.
Yeah.
And like, this is speaking personally.
I mean, I wasn't going for Japanese looking.
Like speaking personally, I am disgusted with the OEL look, the like, the overtoned like
shit.
When I see like American comics that are trying to look Japanese and failing, I have like
a visceral like want to vomit reaction kind of thing.
Like it just looks wrong to me.
And so the fact that your art doesn't look that way, where like you clearly had Japanese
influence and yet it's felt like a good comic in like a distinct art style.
I was like, yeah, you know, kind of like Scott Pilgrim, like I said, where I definitely
was not trying to make it look like manga.
I wasn't like going for manga.
I was, I don't know.
I was, I was just, I just drew it however seemed right to me and I didn't worry about
it.
And I think, I think my style as I've come to understand it emerged in the vapors, like
withdrawing the vapors.
Like my style didn't exist before that, but now it does.
And it looks like that.
It's yeah.
It's a miracle.
Well, I definitely hope to see as much more shit from you as possible.
Like on the one hand, I know you feel like you work slow and the first chapter of the
vapors did take forever.
Like I forget, I often forget how long you got that because it was pretty much from the
time Tbap ended until the day it came out, like was the amount of time you worked on
it, right?
Or yeah, it took me like, like I started doing it.
And I mean, I mean, I was thinking about doing it for a long time.
I think I kind of started actually drawing it in like May or June.
So like from when I first put pen to paper, it took me about six months, which is stupid.
But like what's great about it is that even though I know you feel like you, you work
slow and like your, your, your stories feel small, now that you've kind of gotten up to
like this, I think you're going to get a chapter probably once every month or two.
Like Brunswick took like a month.
I feel like I could do, yeah, Brunswick, Brunswick took me a month, but as I say, I really deliberately
rushed it even though I think it came out good and, and also the pages were only half
size.
Uh, yeah.
I'm, I'm excited.
I mean, I've gotten 20 something pages sketched in a month.
I think I'm excited at the idea that like, even though it feels slow and small now, like
if you were making a chapter every two months, then at the end of the year, you'll have six
chapters and it will feel way more substantial to look at all of them at once, you know?
So like, you know, I think it won't be too long before you have more of a catalog and
I'd like to see personal, personal request, make more even smaller stuff.
Cause like, like I said, like Brunswick small or even like, even if it's just like two pages,
you know, like just fun little random shit that like will more flesh out the idea of
like Ben St. has all this stuff he does, you know?
I was thinking about making autobiocomics, not like the stupid fucking like gag, like
here's my life.
I'm so quick.
I kind of hate autobiocomics like on principle, but I was thinking about making some kind of
because like I was saying much like hours ago in this podcast, like I feel like people
don't really know me except through my comics.
So I was thinking of making some that like, you know, actually try and show a little bit
about who, who I am.
I think I could make some, some okay ones and they would probably only be like, like
fucking white lion, white lion is an autobiocomic.
It's, I mean, it's only sort of about me.
I'm more of an observer to just, it was great though, because the situation is so fucking
weird.
It's weird.
Like to make sure I understand, he asked you if you were gay and you said no, no, no,
he didn't ask me if I was gay.
He invited me to a club and I asked him if he was gay and hitting on me and he said,
and he said, I'm bi, but I have a girlfriend, don't worry, and I was like, cool.
In the end.
It's, I don't know if it was a gay bar, but it was entirely filled with men.
There were a lot of, of men there.
It didn't really look like I depicted in the comic, but like the idea is the same.
Was his tattoo actually a one piece thing?
Like, he did not have a tattoo.
He had, or he might have, but like I didn't include that.
He was just wearing like a canvas jacket and like this weird mesh shirt and the white
lion thing, wait, I forget, does he say in the, in the comic that he wants to be the
white lion pirates?
Yeah, that's what he says.
Like.
Yeah.
Cause like, cause like we talked about, like in, I mean, the real conversation was longer
than what's depicted in the comic and like we talked about one piece and like he did
at some, I did ask him if he liked one piece and he did basically tell me that he's a huge
one piece fan and you know, obviously that's where his like thing about making a family
and sailing the seas came from.
I think in the comic you gave him a tattoo though of a white lion thing.
I, no.
I don't think so.
At the end I show like a flag that like is like, this is what the flag might have looked
like.
Hold on.
I have to go look now cause I'm wondering why I, if I remember that wrong, it's StComics.
StComics.com.
Patreon.com.
Anybody who wasn't clear on what you need to do, you need to type StComics with an X
C-O-M-I-X.
You can type it with a C-S and it will correct itself.
Oh, wow.
That's cool.
Fancy, right?
Yeah, he's got a one piece tattoo on his leg.
It's like the Jolly Roger.
Oh, you're right.
I forgot.
And I don't think he, I don't think he really had one.
Oh, yes.
I remember.
Yeah, he didn't really have that, but I didn't want to go and like have us have like a whole
conversation about it.
So I thought I would just give him that one piece tattoo to make it really obvious that
he's a one piece fan.
Which is a great idea, but I gave me pause to be like, wait, you really met a random
guy who had a one piece tattoo, you know, like I was surprised to learn that.
I mean, it's still surprising even the true story that he wanted to fucking live the pirate
life.
Like that's still fucking amazing to me.
Well he was a big fan and he had tattoos, so I don't think I didn't stretch the reality
too much when I did that.
It's still basically the same idea.
Oh man, this scene of us walking up the stairs out of the subway just looks fucking great.
So dingy.
Yeah, I love how like the art style for that is very different from your current stuff,
but I also really like it too.
Like I like that well, like this was, this was when I was in the grip of my of Bakuman
and was like determined that I should be a traditional manga guy and draw everything
traditionally with, you know, pens.
So yeah, I did these with, I don't think I used a nib pen because I was like too terrified
of like dripping ink because it had happened many times before and I can't control it.
So yeah, this, I did these with micron pens, which are like, I don't know, stupid.
I can't remember if I said this to you at the time that this came out, but like it actually
reminded me of a style that like when there was a brief period that I wanted to try to
draw comics, like I was just because I always draw in just pens, like not like artist pens,
just regular pens.
And I had like like fountain pens and stuff.
And I just wanted to like draw a story about like someone going underground and like exploiting
this underground society.
So almost everything was just like blackened pen ink, like just whole pages of just black
with like barely any white space, you know.
Is that the same as show?
No, totally different.
This was like way before.
Totally different story about digging into the ground and finding an underground civilization.
This one wasn't about digging down.
This one was just like, I think actually the main character went down into like a pond
and like he kept going deeper underwater and then eventually was in an underground city
kind of thing.
Like, I don't know.
I'm really fascinated with the idea of underground cities.
So like, I'm a big fan of the concept, but I don't think I've ever heard you talk about
underground cities before.
I mean, I've heard you talk about like sci-fi dystopias.
I don't talk much.
I've only got into sci-fi in the last three years, like, or four years after playing Mass
Effect.
Like, back when I was trying to write my own stuff, like the style that I was into was
totally different.
And like, I'm really into like, I'm really into like dense urban cities and like any
kind of weird hidden like village place.
Like if there was like a village in the trees or a village underground, like those kind
of things where it's like, I like the idea of stumbling into something much bigger because
I like to think that the world is super, super dense with shit.
Like, this is kind of, I know this is supposed to be an interview with you, but to get into
a little story of when I was like 18 or 17, I graduated high school and my uncle like
sent me, he sent me a book on bicycling and like this, this whole note, like this letter
he wrote about how like, I should go out and like bike around the country and see the world
and not be cooped up in my room and all this stuff, you know, like, essentially projecting
his own regrets about when he was my age, odd to be kind of thing, you know, but the
guy, this uncle doesn't really know me that well, like he hadn't been spoken a lot.
So it's kind of out of nowhere.
And the way I thought about it at the time is I'm not like discontent to, to have not
seen a whole lot of the world.
Like, I think a lot of people feel like they have this really limited perspective because
they've been in one place.
But for me, I'm like, I'm interested in like the little details of places.
Like I can go to like some like random place in town that I haven't been to before.
And like the fact that there's a dumpster I didn't know about will like blow my mind,
you know, so I, I've always imagined like writing stories about like a version of
Virginia Beach where there's way more going on than what seems to be the case, you know,
so like, like that, like this random, like, yeah, I mean, that was a huge influence on
me was like, and all the stories of that nature, like all the early light novels were
huge influence on me.
But like, um, it would, it would be partly like do not at all where it's like, you're
in the city and, um, I wanted to present both the idea that the stuff we do know about is
more interesting than people realize like that.
I feel like, like this, people have told me that I should talk more about my life.
And like, I, I don't find it interesting at all.
But like, I know that other, other people can find my stories interesting because they
don't know them.
Like to them, it's not old news.
To me, it's all old news, which is why I, I don't know.
I'm not usually inclined to, to bring it up, but I don't know.
Um, but yeah, I, I just, uh, I, I don't remember why, what I was talking about or why
you, that was a weird interruption.
You were talking about throughout what I was, yeah, it was, I have to, I really got to
apologize for that bullshit.
Um, you were talking about Dara Dara and the, and the idea of a Virginia beach that's
more, the idea that like, you could turn over a rock and fall down a hole and it turns
out that there's this whole other thing going on.
That's like as deep and dense as what you thought your society was.
Um, but you didn't even know it was there, you know, but then at the same time to, cause
I feel like there's a lot of stories where it's like, uh, this town is boring and then
you find out there's a secret society.
Oh, it turns out this town's interesting.
I wanted to present it like this town is already interesting.
And then also there's this whole other big thing going on.
Like, like there's just so much.
Like I wanted it to be as much stuff going on in one small area as possible.
And so like a lot of my older stories are like that.
They're always like about a city or about like a place where there's just so much
shit going on.
I wrote some, uh, I wrote some erotic Pokemon fanfiction one time.
Yeah, I, um, I think we were, we were talking about this in the chat and I
remembered that I had written this thing like in high school and I went and I
looked it up and like it's still floating around there, getting, getting
reviews every now and then on, it's on like a couple of different sites.
I wish that was still true of my old Tales of Symphonia erotica.
But it's, it's all lost to the fucking void.
Yeah, it's, uh, I would say no more about that.
All right.
We've been doing this podcast for over three hours.
I think we should wrap it up.
Oh fuck.
Um, oh God.
No, there's so much more to say.
Uh, well, let me just make the note on the subject of getting faster, that
these five pages of, of White Lion took me like a month, uh, back when I, yeah,
they, they took me so, I mean, it was a combination of not having an audience and
therefore not having any motivation combined with having no confidence,
especially in like the tools I was using because these fucking pens are a piece
of shit, fucking ink, physical media.
I hate it.
I'm totally, I'm totally digital now.
I'm so much better, I'm so much better with digital.
It's insane.
Like I tried to sketch something with a pencil and it's garbage.
Uh, my tablet is where it's at.
Yes.
I just wanted to make a note of that.
Was there any other notes you wanted to make before we wrap up?
And if people should know.
Patreon, patreon.com slash Ben St.
All right.
Well, now, uh, you know, you have a solid little, uh, artist bio podcast out there
that if anybody wants to know more about Ben St's art or like who he is as a
person, you can link them this, maybe get a little insight.
Yes.
Finally, I'll probably, I'll probably link this on as a patron, as a Patreon
post, but like a public one that everyone can see.
You know, it's funny.
I think most people love interviews with their favorite artists.
I doubt almost anybody gets one this fucking long because I'm the only guy who
would do a three hour interview with somebody.
This is, this is, this is a very didgy thing to do.
Just like, Hey, here's someone that doesn't, hasn't said very much.
Let's just delve as deep into them as possible.
But I appreciate it.
I've been looking for a whole, um, back when I was trying to do a magazine, this
is related to what I was just describing about Virginia Beach.
I had a magazine I was trying to write called the Virginia Beach Hermit Society
where it was basically a magazine about the town and like half the stories
would be real and half would be fictional kind of thing.
Um, and I had a section called interviews with friends where it was literally
just me interviewing my friends who are not creative or anything or doing anything.
It's just like, what are you up to?
And like, what are you up to?
John, pretty much an interview with an interview with Steve, an afternoon.
And Steve, this is like the far extreme version of that.
Uh, all right, thanks for listening, everybody.
Go, uh, give Ben St.
Money on Patreon so that he can make comics faster and better.
I'm in, I'm in financial free fall.
Woo. Save his, save his life.
And if you have money to spare, save my life and that's it.
I'm like, I'm like, just picture me like, picture me like a shield night
and you're, and you're like Shovel Knight.
Like by, by giving me, by patroning me, you're like Shovel Knight.
Just like leaving catch to grasp me.
Catch him, please.
All right, that's all.
Good night, everybody.