Hey, hey, whoa, everybody. Welcome to the first and only Bustercast with me, Ben Saint, and my buddy in anime, Tom Oliver.
Yes, the two most anime people in the entire Pro Crastinators Podcast. The only ones with the guts to fucking commit.
To watch an anime for this cast.
We talked about it for months, but when the chips were down, the other guys just couldn't swing the bat.
Tom, have you? Okay, I might feel stupid, but you've seen Fooly Cooly, right?
I've seen Fooly Cooly multiple times.
Okay. Well, never mind. I guess we should talk about Gun Buster first. I guess we should move in chronological order.
Gun Buster is based. It's the greatest anime of all time. It's got funny memes about time dilation and what else?
Isotonic crystals that retain mass and declining gravity or warp speed. I have parentheses, question mark, question mark, question mark, question mark.
I took a couple of notes whenever they talked about some weird science mumbo jumbo because I thought that's cool.
The one thing that I really love about Gun Buster is how seriously it takes its hard sci-fi shit.
Oh, absolutely. I think we should maybe frame this for everybody. We talked about doing this podcast and talking about Gun Buster and Die Buster a couple months ago.
We as a collective have referenced Gun Buster and Die Buster in the past, especially Nate because Nate talks about them in passing multiple times.
That was the first time I heard about it because you guys had all watched it. I'd never seen it before.
I don't know if Nate showed it to me if it was someone else, but yeah. I'd seen it years ago.
After Fooly Coolie. By the way, historically, this is the Gun Buster was Hideaki-Ano's first anime he ever directed.
No shit.
Yeah, okay. God, I hope I'm right about that. But I think it said so in Wikipedia.
Die Buster is a direct sequel to it, which happened in 2001 or something?
It was much later.
You know what? We should make sure we got, okay, Die Buster.
Okay, Gun Buster is 1988. Die Buster is, I think it's like 2001. No, 2004.
Okay.
Yeah.
And this is the same people. Well, a lot of the same people that went on to make Fooly Coolie, which was, no, Die Buster was after Fooly Coolie.
Really?
Yeah, Fooly Coolie was 2003. Okay, I had it backwards.
That's interesting.
It's weird how much watching Die Buster feels like watching Fooly Coolie sometimes.
Yeah, there's a lot of just aesthetic and vibe similarities. Of course, the aesthetics are the same because it's fucking Gainax.
But just the way the characters are designed and the way that they move and a lot of the down time stuff in between the high octane shit tonally, there's a lot of similarities to FLCL.
It's interesting.
A lot of the characters just resemble each other. A lot of the faces they make and the shots they use seem very similar.
Like the scene when the space monster or the fluctuating gravitational well or whatever they call it is standing up.
Looks exactly in the mist. Looks exactly like when the hand monster in the trench coat stands up in episode five of Fooly Coolie.
Alright, getting ahead of ourselves. We should talk about Gun Buster first.
Are we assuming that people have watched it already?
I would hope so. I would say right now, if you're just walking into this being like, oh, what the fuck is Gun Buster, Die Buster?
Go watch them first because we're probably going to spoil the fuck out of everything.
I'll just tell you upfront that they are the best anime ever made and you should definitely watch them and you probably want to do that before we spoil it.
This is my rating for each is 10 out of 10. They are both the best.
They are very different though. They are supremely different, which is one of the things I definitely want to talk about.
Gun Buster is like old Gundam crossed with Rocky. All the training stuff in the beginning with the coach, it just is Rocky.
They just ripped off Rocky and put Rocky in it. What if Rocky was a girl and piloting a giant robot?
Other than that, the shots of them running along the beach while the coaches on the bike and stuff.
What if Japan made Rocky? You get Gun Buster.
They straight up just ripped Rocky off. I'm 100% sure of it. I think Rocky was like four years before Gun Buster.
The training montages of her doing training exercises in the robot, jumping jacks and running in the robot is pretty funny.
It's very funny. It's very cool.
Do we want to point by point through the story or just gush about the cool parts?
The first really cool part to me is the first time when they get sent on the assignment to the space station and they go into sub light speed for the first time.
While they're in there, every minute is like six months on earth or something like that.
Someone who just watched this a month and changed it over the first time, I was like, this is a pretty good anime. This is pretty cool.
It's kind of hitting the notes. There's some cool little visual stuff, but yeah, this is good.
When they do that jump to high speed, they're like, oh yeah, we're actually going to take time dilation into consideration with all of this.
That just continues to go on to frame the entirety of the rest of the story.
I'm just like, oh, I am in for this. This is fucking sick.
That's basically what it's about later on.
I know there's that other anime by the guy who did your name.
You know what I'm talking about? One of his older movies is about a boy and a girl communicating across interstellar distances with time dilation.
I haven't seen it, but presumably it's kind of the same.
That was way after Gun Buster.
They go on this mission and I didn't remember this part from the first time I see it, but when she was a kid, her dad died in space.
When they go into sublight speed, they find the ship that her dad was in.
To her, her dad died when she was a kid, so it would have been like 10 years ago.
But because it's at sublight speed, the ship only two days have passed on the ship.
There's a serious possibility that her dad might have just survived and been camped out here on the ship for a mere two days.
What's the word?
Rotational frame? His frame of reference, right?
I don't know.
Later on, it happens in reverse where Noriko ends up spending time.
They come back from that mission and they were gone for 10 minutes and everyone's like,
hey, congratulations, six months have passed. Pretty cool, right?
And then it happens more. It happens a lot more.
There's this whole conflict with the space monsters and stuff, it's like funking up with humanity.
But the story really does focus a lot on the consequences of space travel.
Someone had the idea of, you should get that Rona check, dude.
No, it's just water.
This is water and pasta.
The whole story kind of feels like, you know, I guess, because the space mecha genre and shit,
there's a lot of glorification of space and stuff. Space is so fucking cool.
Wouldn't it be great to go to space?
Space travel is fucked. It's really bad.
Your romantic ideal of space travel is ignorant and dumb.
This is what it would really be like.
Time just stops being a thing.
Noriko going to space just ruins her whole life.
It just ruins everything.
Every relationship she ever had is torn apart by age difference.
I think the first time she comes back to Earth, her classmate that she was in the same class with
has aged like 10 years while she's aged like 6 months.
And then she's like a mom, she's got a kid.
They're in totally different stages of their life now.
They're all bully from school, has become the drill sergeant at the academy.
And they're just in a whole different league now.
They just don't even have anything to relate to each other anymore.
And then, I don't know, there's more of that.
But I think you get the idea. Time dilation, everyone ages while she stays young.
It's interesting because we kind of have an analog to that in real life, right?
You're close with somebody, you can go to high school with someone,
and your life beats are kind of on the same path.
And then you go to college, whatever, and your paths diverge.
And life becomes so much different.
And this is another stage of that.
Because time is a constant that we have in our lives.
But they're saying with space travel, even your ages and stuff can divide up and go on different paths.
And all of a sudden, you can be different ages of people you grew up with together.
It's such a fucking weird concept.
And the fact that it's grounded in some theoretical,
this is kind of how we're assuming it works, if all the science checks out.
It's pretty wild that way.
And that was really the fascinating thing that kept me invested throughout the whole thing.
This could happen.
This is literally real science.
This just is what would happen in the real world if we did this stuff.
I was saying on stream last night that, dude,
the way how Noriko suddenly finds herself confronted with her much older former classmates
who have completely moved on with their lives.
It feels like real life.
In my life, that's how I feel about my old classmates and stuff.
Only I also got old.
I just didn't do any of that other stuff.
So it's just worse in every way.
But still, relatable.
Yeah, man.
And then there's, let me say, I have some notes here.
So at some point, they're in space and shit's going bad.
The space monsters are being real, real toughies.
And then they reveal that they've got this super robot.
This real, super better robot called the gun buster.
And it's just really big.
And she pilots it.
And it's a really good robot that's really good at killing space beasts.
And it kind of comes out of nowhere to be honest.
It really does.
It's not built up at all.
We should point out that Noriko, the main character,
she's like a klutz and a fuck up and a dumb ass.
And that's the whole thing.
She wants to go into space.
She wants to find slash honor the memory of her father and wants to be a badass.
But she's just inept at every stage.
She's kind of inept at every stage.
The coach picks her and favors her at every turn.
And it's implied that he sees talent in her, that she is innately talented.
And I guess I have to just assume he's correct because it ends up working out.
She ends up piling that gun buster pretty good.
It's too bad that we couldn't see her potential.
You know what I mean?
He might be like, oh, no, no, I can see she's got potential.
But we just have to take his word for it because it looks like she's just fucking up and not that good.
It's the typical anime thing where they're just like, no, the guts and the tenacity.
That's what really matters.
Yeah, but I feel like it's established over and over again that Amino, her senpai, has more guts and more tenacity.
And yet, even though it's implied that Coach and Amino are gonna get married later, which is funny,
even though it's implied that they're in a relationship like that,
Coach still definitely thinks Noriko is the one who's gotta be the one to do this stuff.
I guess he ends up being right.
I guess he does know.
The funny thing I wanted to mention about Coach, and this just shows how much of a not anime guy I am,
is that the voice actor, the VA for Coach, is the same guy who does Johnny in Guilty Gear.
So the whole time, Johnny's just hitting on this little girl.
It's like, what else is fucking new, I guess.
It's pretty funny.
Johnny's the one with the...
He's friends with the anchor girl, right?
Yeah, he's the guy who puts the coins.
Yeah, it's the same guy.
So I was just like, man, that's pretty cool.
At first I was like, oh no, Coach is like fucking his student.
But then it's implied later, no, they didn't fuck or anything, but she wants to, and maybe they would have later.
If he didn't die of space radiation syndrome, which I guess he got on the ship that the dad also died in.
Space radiation is a thing that gets mentioned again in Die Buster.
I really like in Gun Buster how the end of the episodes have these little science explanation pieces.
Did you see those?
Yeah, I think I saw some of them.
It was a while since I saw Gun Buster, so...
Yeah, if you wait till after the credits, they'll sometimes have these little like the two, like Almanot and Noriko, like explaining science, and then Coach shows up.
And some of it's real science, like Lorenz transformations and like time dilation.
And some of it is fake, like ice, that thing called ice seconds, which I guess is some kind of like power source.
They never talk about it.
They mentioned that a lot of the science was discovered by a guy called Dr. Tanhauser, who created the Tanhauser Gate, which is just a reference to Blade Runner.
The guy at the end of Blade Runner references Tanhauser Gates, and I guess they were just like, we need a name for a scientist who came up with some fake technology.
Let's just use that.
Funny, I don't know.
I like it.
There's like...
Okay, back to the moment when the Gun Buster was revealed.
Basically, she gets in the Gun Buster, and all of a sudden, a space battle that was going to just like wipe out their whole fleet and kill everyone.
She turns the tides and beats the bad guy, and like all of a sudden like bam, like happy music.
Like it's like a tragedy, and then all of a sudden it's like bam, no.
No, we won.
No, it's good though. Everything's good.
Life is beautiful.
I thought some of the music transitions were a little abrupt.
I thought Gun Buster is definitely more amateur.
I don't know, not amateur, but it's definitely like less advanced.
I don't know. I feel like by the time they made Die Buster, they had like figured out how to like really pack a punch, like an emotional punch, and do a story better.
Because Gun Buster is like, it has a pretty emotional ending, but it doesn't...
It's not on the level.
It's not on the level of like Fully Coolie and Die Buster, which come later.
I feel like, you know, in between, like this is obviously the late 80s, and I feel like there's a lot of like kind of modern tropes and kind of just like techniques you can use to build tension and relieve tension in storytelling,
especially that anime is adopted that maybe weren't as commonplace.
Because like Gun Buster doesn't implement, you know, a lot of the kind of traditional Gainex sort of techniques that are used all the time in Die Buster, you know?
Because it feels like Fully Coolie.
It has those like, I don't know, it's kind of like hard to kind of pinpoint and say exactly this, but like that feeling, that feeling of like rising action.
Like when you're like, when like a really hype moment happens, like you fucking get rock hard, you're like, alright, this is the best shit ever.
Yeah, Gun Buster really, really nails that.
Like a bunch of times, and it's super fucking good.
Just like the Gun Buster is like really not built up or foreshadowed, like, hardly at all.
I kind of feel the same way about like, the ending.
Like, okay, they, there's more like time, like Amino ends up getting, like she ends up aging like another like 10 or 20 years or something while Noriko stays on the ship and she only ages like one year.
So for like the, they finally get back together again for like their big last mission or whatever against the space aliens.
Because the space aliens are like breeding in stars, so they have to go to like the center of the galaxy and basically like destroy the center of the galaxy, because that's their like breeding hive or whatever.
They gotta, they gotta have a black hole bomb, and they make this black hole bomb that's like, bigger than the fucking earth.
Or it's like, it's like planetary size.
Yeah, it's massive.
Yeah.
And they're just gonna fucking make a big black hole in the middle of the, of the galaxy.
And there's, you know, like the plan fails, but then they're like, oh no, we gotta go in there and we gotta use our degeneracy generator and, and we can add the necessary mass to make it happen.
I didn't understand, like, why did the bomb not have enough mass?
Like, why wouldn't you make the bomb just have enough mass?
Did something happen to the mass?
Did someone reduce the mass?
Why isn't there, where did the mass go?
What is a degeneracy generator?
What, does it supply mass?
I mean, I guess so.
They've, they mentioned degeneracy generators like a whole bunch of times over the-
Yeah.
They don't really, they don't really say what they are, I assume.
There are times when, like, the explanations turn into like Star Trek techno babble, and I just kind of nod my head.
I'm like, okay, the plot says that this, we need, we need a high stakes ending, I guess.
They're, um, by the-
And I've only seen it once, so maybe there's something I missed.
It's very possible.
Um, I'm gonna blow your mind right now.
Alright, go for it.
Um, so, like, oh wait, there's a gunbuster wiki.
The degeneracy generator was the standard power source for the buster machines, and other mecha up to the technology was lost sometime between, blah, blah, and gunbuster and diabuster.
Okay, there's like nothing else to it.
Boring.
Um, alright.
So, like, when the series starts, like, all the technology and science stuff seems pretty grounded, like, it's just like, you know, oh, time dilation.
Yeah, fair enough.
And then later on, there's like degeneracy generators, like, um, okay.
And then, there's like, one or two shots in the sixth episode, where you can see that, like, some of their technology is based on, like, diodes and, like, helmets that, like, connect to, like, the brains of dolphins.
Like, there's one or two, like, shots in the sixth episode where, like, a dolphin is, like, hooked up to, like, some machinery, and his brain is, like, doing the calculations to, like, pilot the ship, or, like, do the degeneracy generation or whatever.
Oh, god, I forgot about that.
But yeah, that does happen.
So, it definitely moves into, like, okay, we're moving into, like, some, like, softer, like, weirder side by.
The reveal of the gun buster itself is kind of like the pivot point, where it goes from, like, grounded technology to, like, we're going to start taking some liberties here.
And from then on, it's kind of like, all right, we're just going all out.
Yeah, it's powered by this so-called degeneracy generator.
So it basically just can do whatever.
It can shoot giant laser beams and whatever.
It doesn't matter.
Um, there's, um, hey, maybe you can explain this to me.
So, there's, like, three so-called buster machines.
And the third one is the black hole bomb that they end up, like, blowing up the center of the galaxy with.
And I guess the gun buster itself is number two.
But also, there's a number one.
And I guess by the end, there's just, like, two gun busters, and they, like, merge.
Is that right? Did I have that right?
I think so.
Cause I'm pretty sure Amino and Noriko both just have their own gun buster.
They both have a gun buster. That's implied, you know, by the end of Die Buster that they both have.
I mean, you see, you see, I think you see them piloting two different robots, and I think they combine at some point.
Yeah.
The ending just kind of go, the ending, like, the details of the ending just kind of, like, go by pretty fast.
Like.
There's a lot packed into the last episode, for sure.
Yeah. Like, the last scene, the big last scene of the last episode is when Noriko, like, pulls, in her cockpit, she, like, pulls the clothes off her chest.
She, like, rips her shirt open.
But outside, this action, like, the gun buster, like, pulls its chest plating off or whatever, and it pulls out, like, degeneracy generator heart.
And I guess this is the thing that's going to, like, create the additional mass that lets the black hole bomb go off, or whatever.
It's iconic. It's an iconic moment.
Oh, do we mention the Inazuma kick, the Thunder kick?
That's, I think that's from this series. I think this was where that started.
Just, I could be wrong. It might have been from somewhere else.
But characters all do Inazuma kicks in this fucking Google that if you don't know what that is.
It's pretty sick.
Yeah.
It just reminds me of Common Rider, because that's, like, Common Rider's signature move is, like, the Rider kick with a similar angle of just fucking destroying.
Really?
Fucking monsters and stuff. Yeah. I have no idea if it was a reference or not.
Hmm. I don't know either.
It's probably just fucking cool.
Which is absolutely true.
So, like, the point, the long story short, this, like, weird gambit with the degeneracy generator and, like, going inside the black hole bomb,
time dilation occurs and basically they end up getting time dilated 12,000 years into the future.
And then they come back to Earth and they're like, oh, Earth looks different.
Oh, what the fuck is up with Earth?
Oh, no. Did humanity die?
Are we in, like, a post-apocalyptic world and all of humanity is dead and there's nothing forward to?
And then, and then, and then the lights come on and the planet says welcome home.
They were waiting for him in the far future.
They didn't forget.
They knew.
It's beautiful.
It was a super time for that.
It's a beautiful fucking ending.
Because, like, the interesting thing about that and the reason why I think it's so impactful, obviously in addition to just, like, the character motivations of being invested in the arc,
is that, like, time travel throughout the entire series is shown as, like, this is pretty bad.
Dilation is, like, negative consequences and stuff.
Every time there's a time dilation from their travel, like, it's a negative or, like, somber kind of thing as, like, ages and stuff are being desynced and all that kind of stuff.
Yeah.
So you're expecting, like, kind of, like, a downer of this huge fucking jump.
But when that welcome home pops up, it's like, oh, yes, everything's okay.
It's like, it's not all bad at the end of the day.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
That's super hype.
What a, it's so good, because, like, you don't, you don't, I don't know.
I didn't, I didn't expect it, but it's very, like, like, say you're the world government in, like, the far future and, like, this, I don't know.
It's just, it makes sense that it would work, that they would, it would work that way.
And this is how they would, like, welcome home these two, like, at this point, they're basically, like, far distant past, like, folk heroes who have just, like, time traveled to the future.
And now you've got to fucking do something about it.
Myths coming to life.
Yeah.
You know, because, like, in Die Buster, they call this time period the Age of Myths.
They do.
Yeah.
This is, um, I mean, like, it's a, it's a spoiler.
I don't know.
Do we want to start with spoilers for Die Buster?
I mean, we said right at the top that you should have watched both of these before we talked about it.
Yeah.
Like, yeah.
The end, the end of Die Buster is the end of Gun Buster.
It's that same moment of, like,
Dude, that hit me like a fucking gut punch.
It was so fucking cool.
Dude, like, okay, I get, like, when you realize that, um, Nono Riri is Noriko, that the girl
that, uh, Nono's been talking about the whole time is Noriko.
It's like, oh, oh, okay, I get it.
It's a reference to the first, oh, this is like the, this is like the future of Gun Buster.
I get it.
But then, the ending, you realize it's not just the future.
It's that exact moment in the future.
Like, now is the time.
We saw it before, but now we get to see it from the ground.
Oh, dude.
Because, like, the whole, the whole, something that needs to be mentioned about Die Buster is that, like,
up until, like, that last kind of point, the last, like, 45 or so seconds of the entire show,
it's very loosely connected to Gun Buster because there's this huge time skip.
And it doesn't specifically tell you, in the beginning, how it's related.
You only, we only know that, like, oh, it's that future from Gun Buster from the ending.
In the beginning, you're just like, I guess they're space monsters still?
If you, if you just, like, watched, if you just, like, watched Die Buster, like, the first episode,
you might not even think it's an actually a sequel.
I would not.
Not at all.
You would just think maybe it was, like, a spiritual successor or, like, a similar anime by the same studio.
It's not even necessarily in the same world.
Because, like, there are giant robots.
There are space monsters, but the space monsters don't look the same.
Right.
And, like,
I mean, you can name, like, 50 shows that have giant robots as space monsters.
So that doesn't really mean anything.
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
And, like, the main character, you find out really early that Nono is a robot.
And, like, nobody thinks that's that weird.
They're like, oh, yeah, they're really rare around here.
But, like, you know, they're pretty common around Pluto.
You know, it's fine.
I'm a fucking idiot, because I totally missed that she was a robot.
Somehow I didn't...
I missed that line.
Maybe I looked away at the wrong time to grab, like, some chips or some shit.
But, like, I didn't realize she was a robot for a while,
and it took me by surprise when she's on Pluto.
Yeah, I was gonna say, you must have been confused when she goes to Pluto
when she doesn't need a space suit.
Yeah, I was like, what the fuck is happening?
Yeah, there's, like...
I'm an idiot, I guess.
I mean, in the first episode, there's, like, a pretty gruesome shot of after the space monster takes off
and, like, she gets, like...
I mean, you want to assume she's, like, burnt up in orbit
by, like, the act of this thing, like, literally taking off into space with her just on it.
But then it ends up, you know, she, like, moves, turns out she's not dead,
and it's like, oh, okay, she's a robot, so...
I just, I think I just figured the atmosphere burns hot,
but her heart burns hotter, you know, from fucking odorship.
How did you think she was able to, like, stand up on its body in space,
like, run along its thing and, like...
This is a Gainek show!
Deliver the Inazuma kick.
Shit just happens sometimes.
You just thought, oh, no.
I go into anime and just spending all of my disbelief.
She's just a regular girl, but she's just, like, got a lot of determination.
She's a main character in an anime.
She obviously has the deck stacked in her favor.
So she can just, like, kick the fucking exoskeleton off of, like, a space demon.
Yeah, sure.
Maybe. I mean, I don't know.
No, that's pretty funny.
I mean, I knew, obviously, she was, like, super human.
I just don't think I made the connection that she was a robot,
because I'm an idiot, and I must have missed a very personal line.
They say it? I mean, they say it sort of casually,
because, like, it's not that big a deal.
Because, like, yeah, they say, like...
Maybe it was the lack of big deal that made me just gloss over and forget about it.
They say, like, oh, yeah, rogue robots like this are, you know, unpluto.
They're not that rare.
They're like, oh, okay, cool.
Gotcha.
And then, like, they talk about how, like, can Nono pilot a Buster?
Like, well, you know, an AI has never piloted one before,
but it's theoretically possible.
Yeah, I feel like I fucked up,
because, like, that seems like such a huge part of the show.
And, like, it would have done two things.
It would have recontextualized my appreciation for Nono as a character,
because that's kind of important to her angle,
and her relationships with the other characters,
and the world building, because, obviously, machines are just a thing.
And I probably would have seen coming that she was a Buster machine
if I didn't know that she was a robot the whole time.
So, like, my one casual glance away
clearly fucked me for this entire show.
I'm not, I mean, like, I'm generally not someone who's good at, like,
predicting, like, where a show's gonna go,
or, like, predicting twists.
So I did not, like, even though I knew she was a robot,
I didn't think, like, maybe she's a Buster machine.
That was just like...
Because, like, what is a Buster machine?
Can just any fucking thing be a Buster machine?
The black hole bomb was a Buster machine,
so, yeah, I guess...
Well, that's kind of...
I guess a Buster machine is just any machine
that is powered by degeneracy generators
and is designed to defeat space monsters, maybe?
I mean, it sounds, it seems like, like...
Because that's the whole thing, like,
I was trying to figure out, like, what the Buster machines were.
Because we have this huge, like, 12,000-year gap
between a Gun Buster and a Die Buster.
So, like, I guess the point is that even in the context of Die Buster,
they don't really know what Buster machines are,
because they're just kind of relics from the Age of Myths
that they're kind of, like, inherited, and they don't even...
They don't have to make more, they don't understand really how they work.
Wait, no, no, no, don't they make more?
Like, don't...
Okay, the one that the white-haired girl ends up piloting,
wasn't that, like, a new one that they just made?
Did they make it, or did they, like, restore it?
Because, like...
I thought they made it, but I don't know.
Yeah, they do say...
They talk about how they don't understand how this technology works
or anything a lot of the times, and how, like...
Yeah.
And in the end, they're talking about how, oh, well,
Gunbuster, you know, number seven has abandoned us,
so we have to...
This is Earth's, you know, trial by fire.
We have to defend ourselves against the space monsters
under our own power and stuff.
So it kind of seemed to imply that they didn't have a complete 100%
grasp on Buster machines as a technology.
It seemed like it was talking about those as, like,
old tech that was lost to time.
Because when they find out that the space monsters
that they've been fighting in Die Buster are part of number seven,
and that's a whole, like...
They were supposed to be defending Earth against the real space monsters.
They don't understand that.
And so, like, they're gone and they can't control them,
so it's like they didn't see that coming, so, like...
I don't know.
The one...
Okay, the pink robot in the episode where, like,
there's the new one and Noriko...
Not Noriko.
Anono, like, wants to pilot it.
They say, like...
Or, like, the old guy.
The old guy who used to pilot...
I don't remember any of the robot's names, by the way.
They're all, like, really hard to remember.
Yeah.
The one that used to pilot, like, the main one.
Lalk's, or Princess Lalk's or whatever.
Onesama's robot.
They say that, like, these things...
Sometimes they just don't wake up.
I thought that what he was saying was that,
yeah, this is a new one.
We made a new one, but, like, sometimes they just don't work
and we don't know why.
So I thought that, yeah, they had made this one,
but, like, they didn't really understand the technology
because, like, sometimes it just fails
and they don't have an explanation for it.
But, um...
Yeah, they do...
They do send her to Pluto to go find one,
and they, like, they say that they uncover that one on the planet,
but it turns out to be the old space monster.
And turn... Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Go on.
Um, no, I was just gonna say, regardless of whether
they're making new ones and bad at it,
or retrofitting old ones, I guess the point still stands,
that they don't have full mastery of this technology.
Definitely.
Yeah, like, definitely they don't make them like they used to.
Because, like...
Indeed.
No, Noriko is, like, obviously better.
Sorry, Nono is obviously better.
Um, and, like, once it pulls the horn out of its head,
um, um, you know, number 19 or whatever,
is obviously better than all the other ones.
I forgot.
I had forgotten about, like, the twist with, like, the horn
and the... that one guy.
You know?
Yeah.
That one guy.
Uh, which guy?
I know, I know what you're talking about with the horn,
and, like, the buster, the...
Yeah, when he pulls it out and reveals his true...
The dicks, no, for whatever the fuck it was called.
And he becomes cool.
He strikes the gynex pose of, like, having his arms crossed
and, like, some sort of cape billowing behind him.
His...
Yeah.
His robot face looks a little too human, if you ask me.
They all kind of looked pretty human,
with, like, the human-esque kind of eyes and stuff.
Um, but, like, that's kind of like a throwback to, like,
old, giant robo-shows, where they did that a lot, too.
That guy looks very much, like...
That guy looks very much, um, like, um...
Gigantor, kind of, style.
You know?
That guy really looks like an old, old-school,
giant robot, to me.
Which I suppose is maybe intentional, because he's supposed to be old.
Old, by even, like, the standards of that technology,
because it's from back in the day.
Absolutely.
Uh, it was fucking sick, though.
I didn't understand why, uh, Lulk was still able to pilot it
after she lost her topless powers.
I didn't really understand what topless powers were.
It's, uh...
Yeah.
In, in, like, okay.
So in, like, the future, in this future time,
there are still giant robots,
but only certain people can power them.
And it's only, like, young people who have access to, like,
heightened emotional states,
cause, like, super brainwave events or something.
That's pretty fully-cool-y, when you think about it.
It's, okay, everything with, everything with the topless powers
is so fully-cool-y, how, like, you seal it,
you seal the power away with, like, a, like,
a sticker on your forehead.
Right.
And, like, when you, when you use it, like,
you're fucking the, the glow, like, emanates from your forehead
and shit.
Um, yeah.
Like, the whole, the whole scene at the beginning of her,
like, slap, of, of Lalk, like, slapping the,
the, the tag on Noriko, or Nono's head,
and it splits, is so, like, um,
it's so fully-cool-y.
Episode one is, like, so fucking fully-cool-y at her.
It really is.
Like, the whole battle with the first monster on, uh,
on Mars.
It's Mars or a moon of Mars.
Yeah, it was Mars.
Yeah.
And, like, very much felt like, you know,
uh, the, the, kind of the, the stuff at the end of fully-cool-y
or, like, some of the fights with Kanzi.
Yeah.
Very much just in terms of choreography and cinematography
and stuff.
Yeah.
It's, it's, there's the, the part where, um,
yeah, the part where, like, Noriko gets, like,
stuck on the, um, the leg of the monster.
It kind of feels like the part where now to get stuck
to the Medica Mechanica robot that has to fight Kanzi
in episode one, it also kind of feels like the part where,
um, um, Commander Amaro is, like,
hanging from, like, the wrinkles of the hand
as it's going down to grab the, the Medica Mechanica
building.
Um, there's just so, especially early on,
there's, like, so many little moments.
It's, like, this looks exactly like that other thing
that happened in fully-cool-y.
Like.
I wonder if they were using, like, the same kind of, like,
base two frames and stuff.
Honestly, I think they might have just traced some
of their scenes.
Like, I, I think that probably had.
I think they might have just done that.
Which is.
Which is fine.
Yeah.
It looks amazing and better than, like, almost all anime.
I guess.
It's just funny.
What I want to know.
Um, do you think that fully-cool-y takes place
in the same universe?
I think you could probably make the case that it might.
You could.
Yeah.
There's definitely, there's nothing really in,
in fully-cool-y that, that disproves it,
that I can recall.
I mean, I guess, you know, I guess we assume that
fully-cool-y takes place on Earth.
But, like, we see Earth in this world,
and it doesn't really look like fully-cool-y.
So, maybe not.
Or maybe, like, maybe it takes place in, like,
before.
Maybe it takes place either, like, before Noriko
or else, like, after, maybe sometime during,
like, the interregnum, like, when, like, after the Earth,
like, sealed away warp technology and, like, and stuff.
And, like, maybe Medica Mechanica is just from some other,
like, it's unrelated to the space aliens or anything.
It's just some, like, other entity somewhere out there
in space that is, like, kind of pursuing its own agenda.
Haruko's Vespa, the most powerful Buster machine ever created.
Oh, man, yeah, there's Vespa writing in this show as well.
It's, again, in the first episode.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's where Lalk gets her headgear and she's trying to get the Vespa started
and, like, freaks out and kicks it.
I'm like, yeah, that's an FLCL scene right there.
Yeah.
The part where Noriko, when Noriko becomes number seven,
like, is just, like, the part where Nauta gets the powers of Atomisk.
Yeah.
And, I mean, it just feels the same.
It has the same energy, too.
Yeah, I mean, it also has the same energy as when, like,
Simon finally becomes a man.
Like, it's the same kind of pose and the same angle
and the same kind of, like, you know, gutsy speech.
It's fucking hype.
That's what Gainex is fucking great at.
It's just, like, getting your dick rock hard
and just getting your hype dialed up to 12.
The end of Die Buster is basically, like, a smaller-scale version
of the end of Gurren Lagann.
She makes the big, like, planet-sized version of herself
by, like, combining all of the, like, mini-robots
or the mini-aliens or whatever.
Oh.
The red Milky Way.
The part where she, where Lalk fucking, like,
uses her, like, dimension powers
and, like, grabs the core of Jupiter
and just, like, throws it into the air.
So fucking good.
So fucking cool.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, so it's really interesting that, like,
okay, when the show started, I see the space aliens
and I'm like, those aliens look different,
but, like, maybe it's just an art-style change?
Yeah, because the aesthetic is so fucking different from the original.
It's like, okay, I think they're supposed to be the aliens
from Gunbuster, but they don't quite look the same,
but, like, they call them the same thing,
so I think it's just an art-style thing.
But then later on, no.
These space monsters are, they, like,
God, it's like, yeah, they're the defense system.
Yeah, they're part of Buster Machine Number 7
or, you know, no.
Yeah, they're a defense system for the solar system.
Again, it was designed to defend against the space monsters,
but it, like, was, like, an evolving organism,
and so it just kind of naturally evolved
to look more like the space monsters,
because I guess they're, like, well-evolved
to, like, survive in space or whatever.
Yeah, and then they started attacking humans
because the topless powers is the same, like,
I guess, like, the energy that the topless harness
is the same kind of fluctuating gravity field
that the space monsters are.
Yeah.
It was kind of unclear.
It was very unclear.
I want to talk about that.
They find one of the original space monsters.
They, they call it, they go, yeah,
henceforth they call them fluctuating gravity fields,
which is a really fucking weird name for these things,
which they don't look like a gravity field.
They just look like a big, like, weird, like, space amoeba.
So I don't understand that naming convention at all.
But, yeah, it's, the twins say, like,
oh, this is a, this is a comrade.
Like, this is an eternal topless.
Right.
So, yeah, I guess there's some kind of connection
between the topless power and the original space monsters
from Gunbuster.
They, yeah, they, they are the same in some way
tap into the same power, I guess.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's very unclear.
They're implying that, like, the twins were, like,
eating the fucking space monster or something,
because, like, the guy, like, pukes in his mouth.
He's like, oh, God, that weird crab meat they fed me
that I didn't want to eat, that smelled bad,
was actually this thing.
And, yeah, like, were they, were the twins good or bad?
They kind of seem like they were just out for their own thing,
and this entire operation was just an excuse
for them to commune with the eternal topless,
which happened to be a space alien,
because they send, they, they tell Nono
about the buster on Pluto,
specifically because I guess they already know
she's a buster, and they send her away
to have half of the space monster fleet chase her
so their fight can be easier,
so their forces can keep the monsters at bay
while they exhume the rest of the eternal topless.
I don't think they knew that Nono was a buster.
I think they just knew that the space monsters follow her,
and we're like, if we send her away,
the space monsters will go where she goes.
That's fair.
But, like, okay, I don't understand what's up with the twins,
because it's basically just outright said
that, like, they're actually really old,
so one presumes that they have some sort of, like,
unnatural way of extending their ability to remain topless,
because, like, everyone else that gets old
stops being topless.
You lose your topless ability.
Yeah.
And, um, but they, I don't know,
and I guess it's, maybe it's connected to them
eating the meat of this fucking thing?
Possibly.
That's the only explanation I can even think of.
The twins are introduced and discarded pretty quickly.
They serve mostly as just kind of a plot device
to get the real space monsters into the fray.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, um, what's his name?
The guy.
The sort, like, lalk sort of, like, boyfriend or whatever.
He, like, talks to them over the intercom in, like, the first episode.
But then, I don't know, they're just kind of in the back.
They just talk about them in the background until they show up,
turn out to be evil, turn out to be, like,
willing to sacrifice all the other topless pilots
in order to, yeah, commune or do something with this thing,
with this space monster that they seem to think is, like,
the key to them, like, never losing their topless abilities,
because, like, that's their worst nightmare.
Um, and it kills them because, I don't know, they're bad.
And it's a, and it's a fucking freak monster demon.
Um, and I guess these space monsters are just really fucking powerful.
Like, way more powerful than these, like, fake ones
in fighting than, like, the defense, the defense droid, drones or whatever.
Um, I guess, you know, I guess, yeah, they must really not make them like they used to,
because these, like, newer, uh, busters,
like, the old buster could take out a space, a space monster,
but these new ones are just shit, and just can't fucking do it.
The buster machines that they've been using are not nearly as powerful
as the original gun buster, because, like,
that was, I think, one of the really interesting things
of introducing, quote, unquote, real space monsters halfway through
is that it just really changes the power dynamic
of everything you've seen in the show so far.
You think that these monsters are, these busters are as strong as the original gun buster,
but no, the original gun buster was on a league in comparison.
They're shit.
These, everything you've been so impressed by so far.
Dog shit.
Total fucking garbage.
It's like, oh, okay.
Like, they've been, like, struggling fighting against, like,
one, one-millionth of Number 7's buster machine,
and, like, even that is giving them a hard time,
so it's just like, well, that's unfortunate.
Although, yeah, I guess, um, I guess the only reason why Laux can end up helping out
is because it turns out that hers is, like, even older than they all thought.
It does seem to imply that, like, the closer you are to Number 1,
the more powerful the buster machine itself is,
because, like, Dick's Newf, whatever the fuck it is,
I'm looking at the wiki right now.
Yeah.
That's Number 9, I believe, they say.
It's either 9 or 17?
Which one was it?
I think it was 19.
It might have, I might be getting confused.
It might be 19.
I don't know.
But it's like, it's in the teens.
Like, it's pretty low.
It's significantly lower numbered than, uh, than the other ones.
Like, was, was probably made within, like, a lifetime
of the original gun buster having been made.
I don't understand why Laux can still pilot it
after she loses her topless abilities,
other than just, like, you know, your, your guts burn hotter
than the restrictions.
Yeah.
Well, like, yeah, I don't know,
because, like, the original, the original gun buster,
and I guess gun buster 2,
the gun buster machines Number 1 and Number 2
that were piloted by Noriko and Amino,
they don't have, uh, you know, a topless.
Topless.
You don't need to be a topless.
Like, they don't even know what that is at the time.
Right.
Just, just, just, just any,
presumably just anyone could fucking pilot those things.
Well, I guess maybe it's because when he pulls the horn out,
that lets her get to the original cockpit.
And maybe if you're using the original cockpit,
you don't need to be a topless.
Yeah.
Like, I assume that that one, since it's that old,
must have been designed, you know,
similarly to the original one,
which, yeah, anybody could pilot it.
Um, I, I don't, I don't know if the show ever, like,
even hints at us, like,
I feel like there's something I'm missing here.
Like, what is, like, what exactly is the topless power?
Why are the robots designed to,
I guess the robots are, like, powered by the topless energy.
It says, like, when you do, like, a fucking super attack
with your super buster robot,
it's your topless, like, emotion power
that is, like, powering the beam or whatever.
Um, so I guess they're designed to, like, work with that.
But, yeah, the old, better ones just don't require it.
I, I, I don't know why.
It's, that's just how it is.
It's not made, I mean, both gun buster and die buster
both have narrative that don't go out of their way to spoon feed you.
You know?
No.
And that's, that's kind of cool.
I do like, I do like that to a degree,
but there are certain, like, key concepts, like the topless.
And, like, why does it even call the topless?
That's weird.
Like, I mean, that's a very kind of guy next thing to do.
I mean, they do find a, a chance in both the first and last episode
to have their main characters be topless momentarily.
So, I mean.
Yeah, cause no, no, it's like, oh, haha.
I'll just rip my shirt off.
Hey, look, you said you had to be topless to be a space pilot.
Now I am.
Haha.
Also tits now.
Yeah.
Based.
Um, um, I don't know.
It's maybe, I feel like the word might sound cool in Japanese.
That's very possible.
Like, cause they say it, I feel like maybe it's like kind of a cool,
like foreign sounding word that's like, oh, that's neat.
But like in English, it's like topless.
Like, what is that?
What, why?
Doesn't, doesn't matter.
Um, I was going to say something else about, um, oh, yeah.
Did I mention the thing about Nono, Nono Riri?
And how, um, the whole time she's talking about this Nono Riri,
and it turns out it's like her like corrupted memory,
just like misremembered, no Riko.
Yeah.
And like the first, the first thing she said when she came,
the, the scientists like broke her out of the comment was,
no, no, Riko.
And I, you know, I was like, uh, ooh, ah, ooh, neat.
Ah, connection, the connection is made.
It's pretty cool.
Got it.
Very, very cool.
Um, and I guess, I guess that whatever, I guess at the time that Nono was made,
Noriko was like a national hero or whatever.
And, um, they like, either they programmed into her,
or maybe she just like learned it from like being around in a world
where everyone loved her and like celebrated her as like the savior of humanity.
That like, oh yeah, Noriko, she was a real cool hero.
Be like her.
I mean, I would assume if you're making a Buster machine with a humanoid shape,
you'd want to like imbue them with some understanding of the history of the conflict
that led to its creation, and Noriko is a central figure to that.
Yeah, but I mean, since Nono is basically just like a person,
they might have just like, you know, told her.
Like, they might have just like educated her about it.
I guess, I guess my assumption was that before she got trapped in the comet,
uh, Nono was like, not as much of a dits and more of just like kind of like the badass,
uh, just destroyer that she eventually becomes by the end with less, less of the dits.
I always assumed that the kind of like, personality that we know of Nono
came from her upbringing on Mars and her interactions with people
as like a lower, just normal kind of person as opposed to that was how she was the whole time.
But that's complete conjecture.
It's, maybe, it's, I think it's the like kind of gruff like captain looking, the captain guy.
I think he speculates that like, the reason why Nono,
what, like, what would have been made with like a human form and a human heart
is because she was designed to like, guard humans.
Yeah, he does say that.
So, to me, that suggests that like, Nono basically just is like a Pinocchio.
Yeah.
Just is like a, just is a human, just has like a human's like, personality.
To give her that personal investment in keeping Earth safe.
Yeah.
She's like, she's just, so maybe she was just as ditzy before.
Uh, or not.
I don't know.
I never know.
We'll never know.
Ah, man, what a great fucking show.
That whole, they dedicate like basically an entire episode to after
Nono becomes, you know, Buster number seven.
I'm just like the topless who have been like this pinnacle of like human,
like ingenuity, like this is what we need.
There's just a whole episode where it's like, you just have a disease now.
You're, you're like the scum of the earth.
We hate you.
And like how all the pilots are kind of reacting to just like having their badge
of honor taken from becoming a blight literally overnight.
This was, this was like, they say a bunch of times in the series that like,
when you're a Buster pilot, like that's all you are.
Like your whole identity is wrapped up in your ability to pile this Buster.
And if you lose that, you're, you got nothing.
And that's why like when they go, when they go to Pluto to supposedly find that,
that like buried Buster, the old guys like, no, I could still do it.
I want it.
Like, I bet I can still be topless if I, if I really tried, but he can't.
It's too late.
His whole life is kind of just falling apart when he lost his topless power.
That's why it's basically like a space janitor essentially.
But he, he like, he gave it up on purpose.
He says later he, um, he just, he decided to retire early because he was like
afraid of like hitting the point when it, his power wouldn't work anymore.
And so he like quit before that happened.
So he would like never have to face the reality of, oh, I'm not like my topless days are over.
Right.
I can never pilot it again.
Worked out well for him as we can clearly see.
It was great.
Yeah.
Um, there's a message in there somewhere.
Fuck.
What was I talking about?
Um, how they were based and then they weren't based.
Yeah.
When once, once no, once no, no shows up and it's like, oh, oh, you're, you're Buster
number seven, you're like more powerful than all of our fucking giant robots combined
and like times a hundred.
Oh, bummer.
I like, we're all completely irrelevant now.
So like, it's not only that they're irrelevant, it's that they realize that the topless power
is what's attracting like the, the space monsters and stuff and like having no nose
drones being attacking humans in the first place.
So they have to stop using it because it's like putting humanity in danger.
Yeah.
But then I guess the reason why they end up piling them again is because like, I guess,
I guess once no nose in control of the fleet, she can like make them not attack the topless
anymore.
So it's fine now.
Well, it's because the reason they start using the Buster machines again is because no, no
leaves and she takes the red Milky Way with them, which is what was keeping the actual
space aliens out of the solar system in the first place.
So they really have no choice.
That's the best, the biggest guns they have.
Why did that?
Why did the, the, um, the space monsters show up again?
I know the one like hatches out of the black hole.
Was that just like random?
I guess.
I mean, like there's, there's the part where, um, they're, they're breaking out of the black
hole and no, no is supposed to stop them, but she doesn't.
She just like bombs out and then they just warp away.
So I guess like the space monsters are just back and that's bad.
Not, not super clear.
Does she leave?
She leaves because she's like, okay, I can't deal with this.
I have to like spend several weeks combining my red Milky Way galaxy into the giant robot
version of myself.
I guess.
That'll fucking tang on top of Gurren Lag in its ass.
Yeah.
Or whatever.
Uh, and then she just ends up like not using it.
Like.
Yeah.
It just kind of, it just, it's just there to get destroyed pretty much.
It's, it's just there so that like, it's just there so that like it and the like giant
like space projection version of lelks can have like a planetary scale like fistfight.
Yeah.
Like one micro comes out of nowhere like the Gurren Lag in battle.
Right.
And it's like, man, if you had, if you had that giant fucking robot that could take on
number seven, like why not use that against the fucking monster instead of throwing the
earth into it?
And another thing is like there's, they say that there's like 13 planets in the solar
system now.
We have options.
Why are we hugging the earth at him?
We got bigger guns we can use.
Come on.
Who needs mercury?
Fuck mercury.
I wonder if it's just because it's like the other ones are too far away or something.
Maybe, I guess.
Like, I mean, we clearly have sub light travel and like we can go pretty, I don't know.
It's very, I mean, I would assume the point is that a earth is the closest and that's the
target that this monster is going to anyways, and be the emotional impact of like, we're
going to have to destroy our homes so we can live.
They do.
When like, when she, when Lalk is talking to like the council of elders or whatever,
I remember she says like, they're like, oh, do we have to destroy the earth to save humanity?
Like, like, do we really have to go so far just to survive?
And Lalk is like, we'll let, we'll let whoever ends up surviving judge us.
Like, whoever, whoever does survive, we'll get to judge.
And then there's like, in, when Amano is going back to like her final mission with Noriko,
she's on like the elevator car or whatever.
And the cadet that's talking to her says like, she says something similar.
He says like, maybe we should, like, we don't have a right to kill the galaxy, to like black hole
the center of the galaxy to stop these, these space parasite or these space, these space
monsters.
Like, what right do we have to do it?
And she says like, you know, who like, like, we'll let like the history will judge us.
For now, we just have to make sure we're the ones that survive or whatever.
Right, right.
It's like the same kind of.
Both, both of the gun buster and die buster have tons of like parallels like that throughout
the entire plot.
That's what that my favorite part about them is just how they connect to each other.
Like, each one makes the other so good.
You'd be missing so much of either if you didn't watch both.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, for sure.
Yeah.
I mean, even just for the endings, having the context of the endings alone is worth watching
both.
They have the same ending.
They have the same ending from two different perspective.
It's like even down to the shot of like, you know, Lulk looking up at the two glimmering
busters in the sky and then them looking down on the welcome home.
And like, you can tell like the whole city lights up around Lulk because you know that's
where the lights are saying, well, it's so fucking good.
It's a 10 out of 10.
Perfect.
I know it is 10 out of fucking 10.
Okay.
May I ask a if you're if you're if there's nothing else you want to bring up, I want to ask the
question on everyone's mind.
I want to address the elephant in the room.
You ready?
All right, go.
All right, gun to your head.
Which one's better?
Oh, yeah, I'm pulling the trigger.
You got two seconds.
I guess gunbuster.
I'll go gunbuster.
Really?
Gunbuster.
Yeah.
Okay.
I really like you by yourself.
I like the aesthetic and I like the animation and the choreography and all that stuff of
gunbuster better.
But the concept of like the time dilation and how so much of the conflict was focused
around that really I really got me invested in gunbuster and I almost wished it was more
of that in diebuster because it was so fucking cool of an idea.
I feel like diebuster is like the one that like you if you just want to like sit back
and relax and like watch something really fucking cool you throw on diebuster again.
I feel like gunbuster has like a lot of really heavy impact and like there's things to like
really I mean there's things to think about in both but like that one just like the science
and like the kind of like very controlled start versus the wacky ending and the escalation
like it's I don't know it's just the one that I remember not that more but like I just remember
that hard turn of like we're talking about time dilation really like got me to strap in
so yeah I'll narrowly give it to gunbuster even though I probably rewatched diebuster
first.
Yeah I think that's the that's the big strength the big strength that gunbuster has well I
mean the like initial sort of like rocky style like training sequence I think do add a lot
to um gunbuster like Noriko doesn't or no no no no I keep mixing them up no no doesn't
really have to do any of that because she's just like a fucking badass robot even before
she realizes she's a buster she's still like basically a superhuman robot right from the
beginning she can survive in space and do the Inazuma kick and all that um and um and
so yeah gunbuster is good for that and yeah the hard like the like the real the real science
that's like real taken really seriously but used to achieve like sci-fi like weird like
crazy shit that is like played for drama in gunbuster is super good and diebuster doesn't
really have that there's like the they they like a point is made in diebuster that like
okay after yeah we sealed off the um we sealed off warp technology we sealed off like faster
than light travel and so there's not really an opportunity for that kind of stuff like
nobody does that stuff anymore in in the future of of diebuster um much to their probably to
their benefit um but they uh so that a lot of like a lot of the quote unquote science
in um diebuster is just mumbo jumbo that I do appreciate that like um they talk about
ether like um in in diebuster or gunbuster they say that like space is not a vacuum it's
filled of like an ether field you know it's the ether theory of like of like light whatever
um they they talk about ether like when the when the busters like do this weird like sparkling
thing because they're like powered up they say oh the ether is sparking it's like yeah okay they
occasionally reference like but like this yeah they don't have the same focus on like hard
science concepts and diebuster and it's too bad it's very like diebuster is very like um it's
very like ooh kind of like you know don't worry too much about it it's exactly what you would
expect from gynecs at the time it is and I think it's you know I part of me wants to roll my eyes
at a little bit but I do think that the hype moments in gunbuster are like more effective at
being hype than than than gunbuster are it's got more that like raw emotional stuff even if
it's cheesier at times yeah I mean you watch diebuster for hype watch gunbuster for think
yeah yeah I think so and then you know I mean the the ending was the ending was good the first
time when gunbuster did it but then when diebuster does it again you go oh like really
the ending of diebuster wouldn't be anything without gunbuster so like it's mandatory that you
like don't skip gunbuster oh no you'll fuck yourself you have to watch gunbuster first
definitely don't skip gunbuster do not do not do it I would I hope that nobody went I hope that
nobody went and listened to this and got the ending spoiled but if you did but if you did you were
warned yeah leave leave a comment if you fucked up so we can viciously mock you let me one of
my favorite things about fully cooly yeah tell us let us know if you fucked up you idiot I love
fully cooly because it's really good and it's really short and gunbuster and diebuster are also
really short I love that that's so good more more shows should just be like six episodes
the lost art of the six episode OVA it is real shame when when was there ever an anime that needed
to be longer than six episodes never there's never been one there never will be it's don't you find it
weird that they fucking compressed diebuster down to like what two movies or something one or two
movies I haven't have you seen the movies I haven't seen them I've not but I just seems like this is
already so compressed like wouldn't two movies be the same length if not longer than yeah this like
yeah they basically basically be the same like what what's the point huh I don't know man maybe they
like they might actually be longer maybe they just like added additional content according to the
Wikipedia article says it condenses oh no it's gunbuster and diebuster into two movies it's not just
that would be weird that sounds shitty honestly yeah like they're not meant that they have to cut
out a lot I'm sure they could do it and it would be okay but like imagine watching that movie and it's
just and it's just clearly to like completely different shows you know be really weird yeah if they
if they read if they did gunbuster as a movie and it was in like modern anime style I feel like so much
of the tone of gunbuster is in that like late 80s aesthetic oh yeah for sure no you couldn't watch
gunbuster in modern Gainax it would be kind of weird it would be I think it would be a totally
different show yeah it would you I mean hmm hmm like those fucking matte painted space aliens like
that really like that aesthetic is like so essential to a lot of the shots in that I don't know I wouldn't
want to see that like as a CG thing or something or whatever they were doing I'm trying to imagine
yeah if they just like read if they just did a like a remake of gunbuster but it looked like
diebuster oh I don't know that would just be like that would be dumb it would be it wouldn't be the same
I wouldn't even although it might be interesting I guess I would be interested to see it but it could
never replace the original because the original is so steeped in that like early in that 80s anime
look and like the whole like rocky vibes and and shit I don't know you just couldn't do it and yet
they did they didn't remake it what what I don't know if they did or not do they reanimated or there's
just a cut version oh god I hope I fucking hope not I think it looks like they edited it together
okay just like smashed two completely different art styles into one movie oh boy very weird well yeah
the uneducated because I haven't seen them but I would still recommend watching the OVA because
that's how it was originally intended to be I mean it's only six episodes it's not like it's not like
not a huge ask just unlike you like digi and Nate fucking idiot like all of my everyone else on the
podcast who didn't show up to this because they didn't have time to watch a six episode OVA I promise
you you have time to watch a six episode OVA and then watch another one I would argue the OVA is
easier to watch because you can watch it in half an hour chunks after work over the course of a week if
you need to yeah who pauses a movie halfway through nobody nobody no fucking buddy yeah it's it's it's
flexible you can watch it on your own terms you can have you truly you can have it your way yeah I
mean it's six episodes 27 minutes each that's what like just over two hours I watched all of
this morning before before instead of watching Avengers Endgame for the 15th time expand your
palette watch Gun Buster you'll be happy well and hopefully you already did or else you fuck yeah please
but if you didn't it's still worth it this is how you pitch it to your friends your smooth brain friends
if you if you did listen to this and you spoiled it for yourself now you can never experience the joy of
a first time seeing Die Buster but you can tell your you you you will have to experience it vicariously
by a strong arming people you know into watching them and you're just gonna have to watch and see their
reaction so you can thank God I God I wish that were me you'll be like the twins chasing the eternal
topless will be chasing the eternal rush of experiencing that ending the time yes yes there's
um there's a lot of there's a lot of there's there's Eva there's a lot of Eva in Die Buster there's
like especially in the part with the the eternal topless the fucking the gravity field or whatever
like when all the pilots start dying is like and then the old the old like ex pilot is like yeah you
know actually piloting a buster is like really fucking scary but he doesn't mean he means it's scary
and that like once it has its claws into you like you never want to stop doing it and like if you and
like eventually you will have to stop and it will devastate you and you will be a shell of a person
you know like me he says tragic tragic but I don't know we got anything else to say about these these
masterpieces um I'm pretty tapped I think I've said what what I wanted to say it's just fucking great
yeah it's aesthetic as fuck yeah it's good storytelling it'll keep you asking questions and those questions
will prompt rewatches which is always nice I'm sure I'll be watching these again at some point
uh yeah highly recommend it my like second or third time seeing them I mean we've been talking
now for what like a quarter of the entire runtime of the whole series so yeah if you couldn't justify
spending the time watching them but you listen to this entire podcast question your time management
oh you fucked up my friend no no no uh yeah all right like this has been this has been the first
and only uh it's episode of the buster cast um starring die and gun uh it's up to you decide who is who
die oliver and gunsaint or something like that um yeah all right follow our channel ring the bell
more on its way bye