One bag of green tea and one bag of perfect peach tea.
I got one on Twitter criticizing my choice of tea brands.
I was using a Bigelow brand of tea and some others, but he said, oh, you should get this
very patrician tea, so I'll have to go and look up what he said again, and buy that brand
even though it's more expensive.
He said, that's better.
I'll try it out, you know.
And tea.
I don't know if my voice sounds different right now, but I'm sick at the moment, but
I want that.
It's that certain phase of sickness where you just feel really relaxed, if you know what
I mean?
Like, it was all tumultuous and tepid, what is it, it just felt like a tsunami inside
of me yesterday, and then I was super relieved once I finally got to my bed and just laid
down.
And this morning, it's like a kind of sickness phase where everything feels like really relaxed
and good in a way, and my voice, which was a sore throat yesterday, so it sucked talking.
Now it's just like reverberation in my voice, like I can really feel and hear like my sound
waves in my own body for some reason, and it's got like this warbliness to it because
of all the mucus and stuff.
So right now it's actually really fun to talk, so I decided to do this, the only downside
of recording something in this current state is that I'm coughing a lot.
But I'll have to see if I can edit all those coughs out, here we go.
Was there a cough, or did I immediately begin the next sentence?
Because if it's the latter, then that means I competently edited this.
But yeah, I gotta keep drinking this tea.
Now, I'm pretty sure that my voice is just gonna sound annoying to people, whereas to
me it sounds fun to talk, but I'm in my own head, literally, so it sounds fun from my
perspective.
It's probably just annoying and nasally.
But you know, hey, at least I'm finally recording another one of these episodes, when I said
I was gonna do them every two weeks, it's probably been like a month and a half now.
Thing is though, I actually had recorded an episode of this well on time, like within
a week after doing the last one, but I didn't want to release it, and over the course of
the next couple of weeks I did like two more.
A lot of it was like me trying to reiterate what I did in the first one, since I didn't
want to release the first one, but I ended up recording like three whole episodes, not
releasing any of them, because I'm kind of like, I'm now at the point of being known
on the internet to the degree to where I have fans now, and viewers now, where anything
I say will become part of this narrative that people are constructing in their heads about
me and the rest of the PCP, because when you're a fan of something, you learn all the
details and like you construct like a wiki in your own head about it, and there is indeed
an actual PCP wiki being made at the moment, and it's like weird because it's not how you
interact with other people, it's like you go on Discord, you talk to like the viewers
of the PCP and they'll talk to you and talk about you in a way that's very different
than how you talk to like a friend.
A friend knows things about you, but then like when they explain you to other people
or like ask you to elaborate on something you said before, they like, how do I say this?
It's like they're always interpreting you, if you know what I mean, like you'll say
something to a friend and they'll get something slightly different out of it than what you
said, like I don't know, the point is when it's like a viewer of yours who just sees
you as like a cool content creator, I feel like they sort of like take what you say
word for word in a way, like when you say something about yourself, they take it like
it's this sort of like fact, like it's this sort of, I don't want to use the word objective,
it's just like, they take what you're saying like it is like this structured thing, like
there's this physical detail that is what it is, and then they just sort of pile that
on to the other facts that they know about you, and when they explain you to someone
else, they'll like explain it sort of like word for word, very similarly to how you explained
it to them or how you explained it in a podcast, they explain you the way they would explain
allure in a video game or something, and you know, that's fine, it's just weird at first
because I'm not used to that, and it means that you know, I need to like change the way
that I explain myself to people, you know, like, I mean, you know, fuck, these people
give me money, and also give me viewership and attention, and it means I can post anything
I want on Twitter, and someone's gonna like like it or respond to it, so it's perfectly
well worth it, I'm not saying it makes me uncomfortable, I'm just saying it would make
me uncomfortable if I shared the wrong information or said it the wrong way, and then people
sort of understood things weirdly, so yeah, I'm definitely not as just like freely open
with shit as like Digi is, you know, where it's like Digi will just like mention his
mom and his dad, you know, maybe even drop their names sometimes, show their pictures
on screen, you know, I don't know, I'm not as open about things as he is, but that's
fine, you know, the point is that's why I was like hesitant to make an episode of this
show for a while because I just didn't think of anything I wanted to talk about that wasn't
just a bunch of like deeply personal shiz, but now I just went on like a one week sort
of vacation, yeah, a vacation, me going to see my new girlfriend thing, I was calling
her my squiggle in the first couple episodes because I didn't want to like, I don't know,
it's again trying to be like secretive with information, but at some point it's like,
no, I don't give a shit, you know, but the point is, I had a lot of like things happen
or things I thought about because I was in a different environment, so I, you know, was
self reflecting in different ways. So on the plane ride back, I wrote like a whole bunch
of notes for things I want to talk about on this show. So here we go. So, you know, the
first day I was there, we like went because like we just had like a little like hotel
room for us since like she doesn't have any space in her house. So, you know, we just
ran out like a hotel and I guess it's more like a motel. The point is, you know, it's
like this little cheap kind of dingy place. And we went to Walmart and we bought like some
food and we bought some like paper plates and like plastic forks. And I believe we cooked.
What was the thing we ate on the first? Oh, yeah, we just ate like a like a frozen dinner,
Alfredo stoffers type of thing. And we shared that. And it was like, as I was doing all this,
I was like, man, this feels really like ghetto, poor white trash. But I'm like really excited
about all of this stuff. And I was telling her, you know, as as we were munching down on the
Alfredo, that all of these cheap, shitty amenities really excite me all the time. Even when I
think about them, but particularly when I have them, like like like on the plane when, you know,
in coach, the flight attendants will come by be like, Hey, do you want to drink? And I'll say,
yeah, I want some spray because my stomach's killing me. I want some Sprite. So she's like,
okay, she pulls out a little tiny miniscule plastic cup and pulls out a can of Sprite and pours it
in there with some ice. And I'm like, I get so excited about how minimalist and cheap it is.
Because it's like not in a saving money sort of way. But in a, it makes me and what I was telling
my girl is that it makes me reflect on it makes me think about how advanced our society is that
that with no money at all with with so little money, you have things that are this good, you know,
used to be if you were like quote unquote minimum wage equivalent in say the 1920s, you'd be like
whatever you'd be eating would have all sorts of terrible germs and probably some bug wings
inside of it, you know, that kind of thing. Like, it makes me so excited that we have all this
technology that can can make something that's so cheap and yet is so competent and functional,
like a Stofer's meal, you know, like we have all these preservatives that make for more efficient
transit. And we have, you know, freezing technology, that's like a recent invention that
allows it to stay fresh longer. And we have microwave technology that she didn't get invented
until the 80s, by the way, I didn't know that. But like, did you was like, Hey, did you know that
you know that like, microwaves didn't exist until the early 80s. And I was like, wait,
what? And he was like, yeah, I asked my parents. And I was like, well, I'll ask my parents. And
they said, yeah, and I was like, wow, the 80s. So me and her wouldn't have been able to have this meal
even 30 years ago, right? And like plastic forks and plastic plates, it's like, they're so cheap
and yet so effective. And when I think about the rest of time, the rest of human civilization
throughout history and most other places in the world, even today, the fact that we have so much
stuff for so little money makes me so hyped about like our economy and our civilization. And I was
just like, it makes me so excited. It just makes me go like, yeah. And she was like, how are you not
an optimist when you think like that? Because like, because she like, she says like, I'm an optimist
and stuff. And you're all like you and your friends, you and your PCP friends are all like
cynics, you're all like cynical and pessimistic. And I'm like, and that was a good question.
Like, I don't identify as an optimist, really. I was thinking about it. And the conclusion that came
to you is that I don't need optimism to be in a good mood. Like the thing is, is that I'm pessimistic
and cynical about like people in general, like, like any person, if I don't know you as a person,
then I'm just going to assume you're like terrible at things and you're going to fail and that you
aren't going to be smart, you know. And you know, I know plenty of people personally who I just don't
like think are like that good at anything. And therefore you're like, yeah, you're kind of
not you're not you're not useful, you know. But then like me myself, I value myself immensely,
like I think of myself as really competent. And I think that I myself can survive and be good.
And then I know all these people around me who I surround myself with,
who I also think are really good. So I think of like really good people as like a minority,
but that I, that I can work with that, like the amount of good people that there are,
I can associate myself with them and then things can be good, you know, I guess, I guess that's what
I think. I don't surround myself with people who I think are shitty, you know, I win when some group
or some entity or some association starts to piss me off. I disassociate myself with it. I don't
want to deal with that. I only surround myself with people that are good. People that aren't annoying.
So many times on the internet, I'll have like, like on Twitter, you know, there'll be people
like Jesse, especially who will complain about what shitty annoying people are saying on Twitter.
And I'm like, I don't follow shitty annoying people on Twitter. I unfollow them if they get
annoying or shitty. But Jesse, like, you know, I guess he's just sort of like a born cleanup crew
for human civilization. He can't help but surround himself with all this filth, this human trash,
and he just has to rage against it constantly. Like he's definitely that kind of person.
I don't want to deal with that. I don't want to try and fix the world, try to fix stupid people.
So I'm just over here only being with good people. Oh man, okay. I'm realizing my head is pretty
stuffy right now. I am like talking very circularly, saying um a lot, repeating my words a lot to try
and finish my sentences. I'm definitely not very coherent, especially after like a week. You know,
my head is just kind of out of it. But you know, oh well, at least it's content. Feeling like doing
some content. Okay, um, oh yeah, you know, like, I guess part of why I'm why I think so positively
about cheap amenities is that like, like when I got interested in economics a couple years ago,
like when I read when I listened to the audiobook of Basic Economics by Thomas Soule,
and I was all like, dude, this book is super cool. And it talks about like, you know, just how
just how fragile and special our current modern economy is, like it really goes against the
tide of what human civilization is by default. And yet at the same time, if you just have the
right kind of society that values, you know, personal freedom and like personal property
and respect towards one another and trust in one another, then wealth sort of just happens,
you know, like if you have a society that's that's safe and trusting and free and individuals can
keep what they have and earn what they and earn what they have, people just sort of become great,
like society can become great if you're if you're a morally good society, whatever morally good
means this week. And yet it's just not normal, like that takes a lot of effort to happen. But
when it happens, it happens really fucking well. And like, I believe Basic Economics goes into like
one little historical thing that happened in the late 80s, I believe, maybe the early 80s. And I've
heard a number of like people talk about it on YouTube and stuff that there were some USSR
officials who took their first visit to America. And the moment that like really like blew them away
was when they went into a grocery store in Texas, you know, they'd seen all the statues and shiz,
they'd seen all like the crazy buildings that we've built when I'm sure they have crazy buildings
too. So they were like, yeah, whatever, you know, but when they saw a grocery store,
just a normal ass grocery store, they were blown away. And like one of them said that like that
was the moment where like my my last vestige of faith in communism went away, or at least our
country specifically, because they were like, dude, like in our country, people they have to
line up for hours just to get some shitty bread, you know, like like the amount of stuff in this
store beats what our highest ranking officials and our highest elites have access to. And it's so
cheap. And it's so neatly arranged. It's so well lit. It's so colorful. There's so much of it.
Every shelf is filled with the stuff. And it's so much variety. And it's so normal. All these people
are just walking in, not feeling special at all. This is this is accessible to normal frigging
people in this country. Anyone can walk in and pretty much anyone could afford a meal from this.
And they could get a meal of pretty much anything they want.
You know, I guess I'm just always thinking about the other dimensions beyond me, you know, I try to
like to think about things from other people's perspectives. So when I see a thing that it
like cost a little bit of money, I think about how much value would be to have to be to someone to
like, who is from Africa and shiz, you know, shiz, I keep saying shiz today. And I also,
whenever I see something with technology, I think I specifically think George Washington being with
me and me showing it off to him being like, dude, George Washington, this whole, this whole like
freedom constitution thing, you helped create, you know, this country of America, United States
of America. We did all this, we made, you know, with the help of some other countries here and
there, we made all this like cool stuff. And we have all this technology and, you know, be like,
I want to know what your reaction would be, you know, like, I'd love to see the, I always think
about the reaction that someone from 100 years ago would think if they saw it. And then 250
years ago, we'd think if they saw it, but most likely George Washington, that's the main one,
who I'd want to show stuff. You know, imagine just like you have George Washington, you know,
it's a comedy family friendly movie where he gets sucked into the future into 2017. And, you know,
you have to like, you got to go to like a coals and be like, have a montage of like getting them
out of all those robes and putting them in like a, you know, like a t-shirt with a jacket. Guy
to like, you know, just take off the dang wig, just going to go bald today, man, you know, go to
the dentist, get some like actual teeth, get some dentures and shiz, you know, and be like,
yeah, now try to talk with like modern dialect and blah, blah, blah, you know.
I feel like there's just, when you're sick, there's like mucus in your brain too. So like,
your like thoughts have to kind of blow in order to open up the passageway to get to the other
parts of your brain that control what you're saying. I don't know if you can tell, but I am a
deliberately slurping more slurperly so that you can like tell that I'm slurping. I know that like
radio people do that with like say like holding a piece of paper, like like Rush Limbaugh does that,
where he's like, okay, so, you know, there's some certain things that were in the news today,
and I printed them out and he'll do this and be like, when he like reads the papers that you know,
he's reading a paper, like if you pick up a piece of paper, it's going to sound like this,
right? But he makes it go like this, right? But then eventually like people were calling in being
like Rush, that's so annoying, why are you doing that? That's so unnecessary. And he's like, well,
fine. So eventually it got to the point where he's like, so there was something in the news today,
I printed it out. It says blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Man, I'm so glad my sore throat is gone, like there's no way I can be in a good mood when
my sore throat is over. There's nothing more annoying than a sore throat. Well, okay, headaches
are worse. I, you know, I just, I generally have good health, so I don't have to worry about things
being painful on my body. And so therefore, the things that do occasionally go wrong, like a sore
throat, makes me really sad. It's, I really hate not being able to talk. Yeah, so, you know,
like I'm sure most of you know that like Digi has talked about, like there was this period where
him and his family were poor. I think there was like a couple of periods where that was happening,
I'm not really sure. And like I was always assuming like that they were like, poor, poor, like, you
know, like, like shitty house life, terrible, poor and stuff. And I was like, yeah, you know, I've
never like been poor like that, you know, like I was, I've always been like, yeah, you know,
like our families just always like had our, you know, her finances together for the most part.
Um, but then, like I was in the car with him one point, like, like, like a month or two ago,
and like he was mentioning like, oh yeah, yeah, we were so poor, we were on food stamps for like
four months. And I was like, wait, and I was like, wait a second, like there were times where my
family was on food stamps for like two years. And we're not that, and most of the time before and
after that, we were only slightly better off than we were during that period. And like, even now,
my dad's business is successful and all, but we have to pay so much taxes. And we're like three
years behind on paying taxes, my family is. So it's almost like we don't have all that money for
the most part, you know, like amenities and spending and splurging is still very, very
thinly spread even today. I was like, wait, have I always been poor? I was like, but I guess by
other people's standards, I guess so. And did you was like, yeah, if you're, if you were on food
stamps and you were poor, and I was like, oh, and did you was like, you know, I mean, I guess part of
it is that when we were on food stamps, we were also living with like annoying relatives. And so
that was what made it miserable. And like, it just wasn't a good life situation. And I was like, okay,
that really explains it then, because it's like, no matter what's ever gone on with my family and
our finances, they, my parents have just always acted really calm, like they're always on top of
things. They never freak out. They're never, they're never like getting overwhelmed with stress.
You know, there's only been like a couple of times when my dad got a little bit mad at me
from like stress, he was like, okay, let's go like that kind of that kind of burst out outburst,
like that kind that that's, that's like the most mad by dad gets at things, you know,
my mom only ever gets mad at me when I waste something, like sometimes I'll throw out some
boiling water and she'll be like, why'd you throw out that boiling water? We could have done something
with it. And I'm like, I'm sorry, mom, I changed my mind about what I wanted to eat. And she'll be like,
like my, my parents, they got like married when they were like 33, and they had me their first
child when they were 34. So like, they were completely competent adults before they had
children. So, you know, they'd had marriages before, but they didn't have any kids. So like,
I was their first child. So like, that's the benefit of having kids when you're old is that
you're really mature. So I never felt like we were poor, like we always had our shit together.
That's the thing, you know, I never felt poor. I just felt like I couldn't have nice things,
you know, like, and recently, I've kind of sort of gotten into Stefan Molyneux,
who's like this libertarian YouTube political guy. A lot of his modern videos are him going like,
oh, you know, Trump may be flawed, but the left is saying this about Trump, and it's completely
inaccurate. And you're just also completely daft. I can't believe you'd be like that. And then,
as I continue to reiterate the point over and over again, I start acting really raspy. I start
doing this really raspy voice where I stick my teeth out. I just keep saying the same thing over
and over again. Getting raspy, I'm raspy, I'm getting even raspy. The left is so retarded,
you're all put to altars. And then I get back to the topic and I have this very concerned look
on my face and continue with the subject and I never edit my videos. It's just one long take
of me being in front of my microphone and bobbing back and forth in front of my blue background.
and never editing out anything I ever say, and brilliantly I never say um for the most
part and I never stutter or have long gaps, I just keep talking which is probably exactly
why I reiterate my points over and over again and have to go into that recipe voice in order
to fill in all the space, I don't know why I don't just fucking edit my videos.
But he's been doing them for a fucking long time, I introduced him to Digi saying hey,
this is what I expect your body of work to be like in 10 years from now, because Devon
Molyneux has done these like podcast video things since 2005, like he was on YouTube
at the very beginning of YouTube right, I think he started his podcast before YouTube
was around, he has 3500 podcasts, like he does like multiple every week, and they're
usually like long, they range from 30 minutes to 2 hours every time, unbelievably prolific
guy, um okay, I really wanted to talk about Devon Molyneux because I find him fascinating
and like his early content is not really about current issues or at least not the ones I
listen to, a lot of his stuff is, his early stuff especially is just like theoretical
philosophy about you know like libertarian ideals of like hey what if the state didn't
exist or what if the state was like this instead of this, you know, and it's pretty good stuff,
a lot of it is definitely things I haven't heard before, it's really terrible audio quality
in the beginning, but it's interesting stuff, and there's one video of his, there's one
of his first YouTube videos, probably like his 250th podcast or so, but anyway it's
one of his first videos, and he's just in his car talking about stuff, talking about
like Nazis and like you know, can you, like okay, you can't blame a soldier that was said
shoot them or I'm gonna shoot you, and you can't blame the generals because the general
was told hey tell that guy to shoot him or I'm gonna tell someone to shoot you, and
you can't blame the marshals because the marshal was told to do this and that, now there were
plenty of Nazis who decided to rise up the ranks in Nazism and who like did more than
they had to, so you can blame them, but they didn't necessarily know that their government
was that evil, not at the beginning, you know, and even other people, like how many people
can you really blame, and what Stefan Malinu said was that the only, in my opinion, the
only people who are perfectly guilty are the intellectuals, we're the philosophers, the
people who sat in their colleges and their campuses and in their homes and just wrote
ideas, and their ideas were evil, that kind of thing, and anyway, I swear I'm gonna bring
this back to the whole me being not with money in my family thing, he's like, you know, so
many of these philosophers back in the day who spurred on Nazism were trying to, were
falling into a sin that many philosophers do, a mistake that many philosophers make, is
that they were trying to normalize the way that they were raised into an ideology that
the world could live by, all of these philosophers, many of them were raised by Lutheran families,
Lutheran fathers who had a very strict, harsh, you know, uncunning, unforgiving style of
parenting that was very strict, very harsh, very punishing, and so when they took to their
books and they took to their writing, they tried to like come up with a world philosophy,
a set of rules by which society could operate that reflected the way that they were raised,
they were trying to normalize the way that they were raised, trying to rationalize the
mistakes and crimes and sins of their parents as something that is a moral good or a moral
necessity, things like many philosophers fall into this trap, Ain Rand herself couldn't
avoid falling into this mistake, so I, you know, listened to that and it made me reflect
on myself and like, okay, well, how was my view of the world influenced by the way I
was raised and like, you know, because we'd never had money really, we never had like,
we always had enough money to be just fine and be comfortable, but never enough money
to like buy nice things, and like, I was really brought up in this like mentality that if
you want something nice, you have to work to make it happen, like if you want something
cool, you have to put in extra effort to earn the money to make it, if you want something
to happen, you just gotta make it happen yourself, that no one's gonna come in and just give
it to you, you know, and like, as I've grown up and had different life experiences, I've
been adjacent to like, people who it's like, their parents just give them a friggin' like
beach house or something or a little apartment condo next to a lake with a boat, like here,
you guys can have that, you just got married, have it, and it's like, wow, you know, I don't
have any, we don't have any like rich people in our family, and like, you know, my family
isn't poor enough to get like, that many government amenities, and whenever we do,
my dad's goal is to make enough money to where we don't have to have that, you know, when
we were on food stamps, my dad's one of his biggest priorities was make enough money so
we can buy all our own food, with our own money, I mean, we'll take advantage of handouts
if we're given, if we're given them, right, but you know, the idea is, you know, try to
not be dependent on that, and so I really think that that's kind of like where my mentality
comes from, of like, you shouldn't expect to be given stuff, you know, like, you just
have to make it happen on your own, and like, you know, as an adult, I can reflect on that
like mentality and be like, yeah, but like most people don't think exactly like that,
like a lot of people are like, you know, hey, if you're given something, you'll do something
nice with it, you know, if you're just given something for free, you're not just gonna
be lazy, you're gonna like put effort into like making that gift worth something, and
those people are right, you know, most people, if given a handout, are gonna be responsible
with it, but like my default mentality of things is, you can't expect to be given anything,
like not that it's wrong to be given something, but like, you shouldn't expect it, like, like,
like, as a teenager, learning about how like jobs work, and how like benefits and like
pensions work, I was like, why would you be given money after you stopped working, like,
why would you still be getting paid after you stopped doing the job that you're getting
paid for, you know, like, what's, what's the point of that, like, why, why is that
normal, right? And when I first heard of benefits as a thing, like as a kid, like, oh man,
a great dental plan, a great health plan, you know, they give you a car, I'm just like,
why not just give you more money? Like, why do they have to buy these things for you?
Why don't if they have this extra cash to spend on you, just give you the cash, you
know, just give you the money and let you decide what to do with it. And like, I'm always
thinking, oh man, if you get this, then what's it being taken out of, you know, like, if
you're given a car with your job, that just means you're going to get paid less in your
actual wages, probably equivalent to exactly the price of that car. But like, I talk to
my friends and stuff, not my PCP friends, they're all smart, but like, normie friends,
like, people who I've encountered in my life, and they don't, it doesn't seem like that
crosses their minds, you know, like, or like, oh man, this business doesn't give us a dental
plan, they can't afford it or whatever. And it's like, yeah, and like, if they gave you
a dental plan, they just pay you less money, you know, like, because like, anything they
give you is money, they're not giving you. Why don't they just give you the money and
then you can decide to go to the dentist yourself, right? And I know it's because like, with
insurance specifically, it's like, if more people get insured by the same place all at
once, it's more efficient, you know, obviously, there's lots of detailed economic ramifications
that make way more sense. But just my I'm just talking about my like, you know, worldview,
the way it was said, as a young age was like, you know, if I'm given something by my parents,
it's going to come out of somewhere, I was made very acutely aware of that, you know.
So whenever I think about whenever I like, you know, I mean, stuck in an airport all
night and CNN is in every single room, and they're debating the value and merits of like,
this government program that gives people health care versus this government program
that gives people health care versus this government program, it gives people this
and that, and gives people this and that, I'm immediately thinking, well, at the cost
of what, what are we not getting as a result of paying for that, you're not just getting
the money out of nowhere, is basically just coming out of taxes, right? And yeah, the
people who like, are the richest are the ones who are going to get taxed the most, but that
just means they're going to be spending less money on stuff, and spending money stimulates
the economy, which helps everyone. So it's like, you know, like, I just sort of naturally
assume that things are going to come from somewhere. And that's why when I listened to
Basic Economics by Thomas Sowell, and it said exactly the way that my worldview was, I was
that I got so excited about that. That's why I love that book so much. It just, it just,
it just, it just sort of gives like this structure and like, this like actual factualism to like
the way that I see the world already, you know, and I don't know how flawed that book
is. I don't know how many people have poked holes in its logic, but it seems it just makes
so much sense to me that that's why it's my favorite book. Well, certainly my favorite
nonfiction book. But yeah, again, you know, I try to be like open minded about things.
And I've sort of, you know, like, again, as I said, when you give people stuff, two out
of three times, they're going to do something good with it, you know, like think about the,
the parable from the Bible, right? Where the parable that Jesus tells his followers is
okay, there's this dude who owns like this, like this, this is like a real estate guy
has a big house, has a lot of money, has like some farmland, and he's going to go out on
a trip and he's got three servants and he's like, okay, a servant, I'm going to go out
on this trip, but I want you to do stuff with my money, do stuff with my resources, right?
So one servant, he gives 10 shillings to like, okay, do stuff with these 10 shillings, you
know, benefit my, my estate and you over there, the second guy, I'm giving you five shillings.
Okay, now you over there, the third guy, I'm going to give you one shilling, all three of
y'all do stuff with that money, make it, make it productive, um, do good stuff with it and,
you know, I'll, I'll be back. So when the dude left and came back, he was like, all right,
guys, the three of you, show me what you did. And the first guy's like, dude, I invested
the 10 shillings and now it's 20. The second guy's, dude, I invested the five shillings,
now it's 10. And he's like, you two are awesome, go to heaven, basically is what he says. It's
like, you get to have lots of reward. But then the one shilling guy, he was like, oh, sir,
you know, I know that you're all harsh and shit, and you're all like judgmental and unforgiving.
So I didn't want to risk losing it. So I just buried it, you know, and so here it is, I dug
it out, you know, it's got some dirt on it, but I hope you still like it. And, and, and the dude is
like, you're such a fuck boy. For first of all, don't talk to me like that. Like, what do you
mean I'm judgmental? Oh, shit. I mean, don't complain. Goddamn, Jesus Christ.
But also, you're a big lazy butthole, just sitting on all that money, you should take a risk, you
should try and be responsible with it. Don't lays out, I'm sending you to hell, or what he
says in the metaphor is, you're gonna get punished for that, go into the fucking dungeon or whatever.
So like, you know, it's Jesus telling the world that like, you know, if you're given something,
do something with it, take a chance, you know, any gift you have, be it a talent or money.
But the thing is, and I just realized this five minutes ago, which is why I told this parable
to you guys, is that this kind of shows that, yeah, two out of three people are gonna be good.
Like, overall, that dude's estate profited immensely from that, from those handouts.
Like, even if he'd given all three of them the same amount of shillings, like if you'd given
them 10 to each of them, he would have broke even on those last 10, but he would have made
20 shillings in profit on those first two guys who actually are good.
So, you know, like when you think about that, it have a harder time just thinking of government
handouts as these things that just promote poverty and shit. Really, the reason why government
handouts do that is because they're designed to do that on top of just being handouts. I don't know
if you guys know what like conservatives, but especially libertarians say all the time is that
if you're given stuff, then you're gonna be dependent on being given stuff, and therefore,
it's gonna be harder to make stuff for yourself. And also, those handouts incentivize you to not
do work, so therefore, you're gonna become less productive and you'll be even more dependent on
it. And so, people are like, yeah, we need to stop handouts, but I'm like, why not just do handouts
that don't encourage not working, right? Like, disability benefits. I have an uncle,
uncle bill, because everyone has an uncle bill. My uncle bill, like, my uncle bill was a construction
foreman and stuff or something like that. He's a construction dude, laying down concrete, and he
like destroyed his back doing that. He had to get surgery, and his back is all sensitive and like
easy to make him miserable at all times. So, he got disability for that. And it's like, you know,
like, I guess what I've been told by like other members of my family is that dude, like, he could
just be a foreman. Like, he could just tell people what to do and like not lift a finger. He is so
skilled. He knows his shit so well that he could easily make bank just showing up at a construction
site and pointing at what to do. And he wouldn't have to lift a finger. He could be doing like,
like physically, it wouldn't be that much worse than just sitting in his apartment, which is what
he does, right? Um, it's not like he does nothing. He is like a hobbyist dude. He does do some work
for people. He does like mixing music and painting stuff. But, you know, none of it is like making
him money. Um, he just lives off the disability for like, last, I don't know, 15 years or so.
Um, and he said that like, well, if I was a foreman, people would be screwing things up,
and I wouldn't be able to resist going up and grabbing something myself and then destroying my
back. Whatever. But like the point is, like, he's, I think he's like outright said, you know, if I
was better, if I did work and I wouldn't get the disability, and therefore, you know, my, my
income would be less secure. And it's like this thing, you know, it really encourages you to be
like that. Um, that's, that's how the disability works. It's like, if you're basically government
handouts, at least in America are like, if you're useless, then you get free stuff, you know, so it
incentivizes uselessness. So the thing is, okay, that's a obvious problem with handouts, right?
And like, you know, people talk about how like in the inner cities, in American cities, that's
where like handouts are the most pervasive, and that's where people are the most poor, and then
there's crime and stuff. And so it's like, you know, like, oh man, all these handouts have like
ruined cities and stuff, and it brings down the overall quality of life in America, on average.
And it's like, okay, but like, are those handouts disastrous, just because they're handouts, or
are they disastrous because they're disastrous handouts with bad ideas stacked on top of the
idea of just being free shit, right? So what I'm getting at is that people have been talking about
the idea of universal basic income, which is something I've talked about on my DeVugos
to Saturn channel recently, which is everyone gets a thousand bucks in their bank account
at the end of the month, every month, everyone gets it. Like each social security number gets
a thousand dollars in your bank account every month, no matter who you are or what you do.
Like even if you're a felon, even if you're a billionaire, right, it doesn't just go to poor
people. So if you're poor, you don't have to worry about making money and then losing the thousand
dollars, right, you're going to get it no matter what. So like it's going to be useless to all
those billionaires, right, like it's going to be wasting the money on the billionaires because
they don't need the money, right? But the point is the reason to give it to everyone is so that you
don't have the bureaucratic overhead of making sure you're not too rich, right? And you don't have to
make people afraid to become independent. If you give someone something no matter what,
then they won't be afraid to continue being useless. And of course, when you hear something
like that, you're like, okay, plenty of people will just never work ever. I'm pretty sure Ben has
told me like, yeah, if I was given a thousand dollars every month, I just wouldn't do anything.
And I guess that's fair enough. But I would do stuff with that money. I would still work.
And I know Digi would still work, I think. So that there we go. Once again, two out of three,
right? Now, can the economy survive if two out of three people are productive? I don't know.
But I'm just saying like, I find that to be an idea worth trying out or something. Try it,
you know, like just just do it. Come on, like all we got to do is just upend our entire economy
and legal system for just a couple of years. Just try it out, guys. Geez. God, I'm so annoying in
this one. I'm doing all these stupid voices. I'm the I'm the new Stefan Malinu, man. And people
have talked about how like, let's say you are a loser who like, you know, blows your money on alcohol
or weed every month. And like, you can't get a job because you're completely incompetent.
And in our current society, those people will probably either end up on the streets,
or more likely just end up crashing in their family or friends' couches forever
and ruin everyone's lives. They're their own and the people around them. They'll make everyone
miserable and they'll be shitty people. And what I've heard people say when defending universal
basic income is that it will take away those people's excuses to not do anything. Because like,
here's the thing, you know, in our current reality without universal basic income, if like,
the dude's sister who he's sleeping with is like sleeping, you know, on her couch and stuff,
he's like, I can't do anything. And she's like, dude, just go get a job, like clean up,
go try out for jobs and stuff. And he's like, no, I can't do it. I have no money. I can't do
anything. I can't afford new clothes. I can't afford to like shave every day. I can't afford
to like get a haircut. And you know, I can't afford shampoo. So like, how am I supposed to get a job
anyway? You know, I can't afford a car. I can't afford this. I'm completely out of I'm completely
out of resources, man. I can't do anything, man. You know, that's the that's the kind of excuse
that some people give. But in the reality with universal basic income, she can be all like,
dude, you're going to get $1,000 on the first. All right. So use that money to clean up. Okay.
And if you don't do it, I'm kicking you out. So it sort of like takes. Yeah, sure. $1,000 can
be people's excuse to not work. But it can take away your excuse that you're completely helpless,
right? It takes away your excuse that you have no power, that you have no resources,
that you have no choices. And I'm like, yeah, that makes that makes perfect sense. Again,
so many of government handouts are bad because they like give you something very specific. And
the government themselves decides what to give you and when and how. And then they give you all
these rules that you have to follow in order to do it, you know, they so it's like the government
trying to control you, which is obviously what the government wants to do. The reason why government
handouts are so popular with every government is not because they want to be generous to people.
They do it because it's an amazingly convenient way to control people's lives and the corral people
and the living the lifestyle that the bureaucrats want us to live. The fact that it's so politically
popular is what makes it so pervasive. I mean, obviously, the government would just tell us what
to do, you know, in a completely totalitarian way if they could. But that's politically unpopular,
you want to win elections like that. But handouts with a bunch of rules and the shit is a way to
tell people what to do and tell people how to live. That is politically popular, you know,
every politician can come up and be like, y'all, we're going to give you this free thing. And the
guy who is running against me who doesn't want to give you this free thing, he wants you to die.
So don't vote for me instead. And those people are able to win elections, you know. I mean,
you may think that in America a couple months ago, those people did not win. But even the
Republicans who won this time aren't saying we're not going to give you stuff. They're just saying
we're going to give you something slightly different than what you're getting right now, you know.
So, you know, there you go. It's still basically the same thing. There's no one winning elections,
even in America, who is outright saying we're going to give you less stuff. Even like hardcore
conservative people, like Ted Cruz, I don't think ever says let's give people less stuff.
He's just saying let's clean up the bureaucracy in the stuff giving committee. And obviously,
I'm not saying we should stop giving people stuff at all either because people are dependent on it.
You know, it may be a fucked situation that our government is in, that our society is in,
but you can't just stop doing it because people need it. It's like government bullshit,
societal bullshit is like a game of Jenga where you have all these blocks of bullshit that have
stacked up. But if you can't just dismantle it, you know, haphazardly, if you just take out the
bottom, if you just start taking it apart, it's going to collapse and cause a 9-11 all over everyone's
face. So, you know, if you want to dismantle it, you have to do it slowly and know exactly how to
do it so that not too many people die. I'm calling it, I'm saying die that way because there was
someone on CNN who was like, you know, if we were peeling, replace Obamacare the way that Trump
is saying it, people are going to die. People are going to die, okay? There was some doctors who said
that like if we take away Obamacare, some people are going to die. They're going to die. They're going to die.
I'm going to be so impressed if people can get through this without like their eyes watering
from the annoyance of my voice. You know, when I was in the airport being all sick and stuff
and sneezing sometimes, my sneeze are so loud that there's always like at least someone who will say
bless you. Like it's so loud that like there's always going to be like it's like like it's going
to turn like five people's heads and whoever says bless you first is going to say it and I'm going
to be like thank you because I sneeze so loud whether or not I'm sick. What the hell was I talking
about? Oh yeah, yeah, the money with the you know, there's one last thing I want to say about it. Like
I think one of the moments that really started to shift my perspective about the idea of giving
people free stuff was when I watched Scarface all by myself on VHS in my room because that's
something I do. You know, my whole why don't I like movies series which is on my main channel
is a reflection of something that I used to do a lot which is just look at my
collection of VHS tapes and then sometimes randomly watch one. So that's how I saw Scarface.
And my favorite scene from the movie, my favorite moment, my favorite line is toward the end when
Scarface is in his giant you know gold studded jacuzzi just hanging out being topless being
naked probably underneath the bubbles and like his girlfriend or whoever it's been a while I only
watched it once but like you know the lady person is all like you know trying to like talk to him
or do a thing and Scarface is just Charles Foster canning it up to like no tomorrow he's just being
all like yo man like don't don't give me this shit bitch don't talk to me like that I'm I'm the best
I'm the goddamn go to I'm fucking don't I'm the best fucking fuck you you know he's being a total
asshole to her and she's like why are you being such an asshole he's like look at me see all this
I'm the look at me I'm obviously the best I made all this happen I sold coke and shot dudes in the
balls better than anybody so I earned my place on the throne and she just says I wish you had been
given your money I wish you'd been given your wealth instead of earning it because if you've
been given it you'd feel guilty and you'd feel an obligation to be nice with it you'd feel an
obligation to do good with it and then she like you know stormed off being all mad and stuff or
something like that and he's all just like you know and that's what happened and I was like
and I watched that scene and I was all like man yeah that's actually a good point when like
sure on one hand you can say that if someone earns something they're gonna be more responsible for it
and uh and if someone is given something they're gonna be irresponsible with it but sometimes
it can also work the exact opposite way where if you earn something you feel like oh well since I
earned it and I could do whatever I want in a minute but if you were given it you're like oh
shit I don't really deserve this I need to like do good with it and I'm like yeah that's a good point
okay that's enough of that topic you're listening to free to view radio
and now let's move on to the next subject I wrote on my uh my notes here so um you know my girl's
been like I don't want to call her okay her name is Nikki okay Nikki was telling me you know hey I want
to meet your friends like turn on you know the facebook messenger face cam chat app or turn on
audio call and then shove the phone in front of your friends I want to talk to them I want to
introduce me to them and I'm like no I don't know that'd be weird and she's like why do you
why don't you want to show me off me me me and I'm all like cuz they'd be weirded out by that
and she's like why and I'm like I don't know it's just how guys are geez you know it's like
digi specifically has even mentioned like yeah you know I don't I don't like it when guys show
off their girlfriends to me you know like if you show that to a bunch of dudes they're just gonna
be like oh fuck you all happy in a relationship go die on the washington memorial by landing on it
from an airplane ass first you know that kind of thing and but you know meanwhile if a girl shows
off her boyfriend or her friends it's like they're all like oh hey I'm so happy for you and I'm like
okay I guess that makes sense you know and so that's why I mean like like I only know you know like
specifically because digi specifically says I don't like it when guys show off their girlfriends I
mean like I'm not gonna do it to him I'm only like like look Nikki you'll meet them at some point you
know it'll just happen naturally she's like why doesn't it happen now what happened now I'm like
so meanwhile when I was visiting her for a week just now there was a day where like we went and
met a bunch of her friends and their family and stuff and I thought it was a fun time you know
we didn't talk much but you know they were all hanging out with each other and I was just sort
of there hugging the shit out of her and you know I was like okay cool you know and and we met them
and and and that was that but then the next day it turns out that like most of her friends hated me
like they were like they were mad at her for how I was quote unquote acting terribly or something
like I was specifically like not talking for the most part I was just trying to be quiet you know
so I didn't so that wouldn't be annoying you know like I don't know what these friends of nikkies
are like I don't know like what kind of topics they'd be interested in I'll just like sit here
and wait for them to like bring up a topic and then I'll I'll say things and and you know if they
ask me questions I'll answer and I'll be like okay now I'm asking the question of you in return you
know I didn't want to you know yeah I was just trying to be quiet you know I said things you know
I was like I told jokes here and there but for the most part I was quiet but turns out some of her
friends hated that they were like why wasn't he opening up why was he being so reclusive
but what really um took me aback was that uh like a couple of them were saying that I was like
we're telling her we're complaining to her that I'm like so egotistical and arrogant
and I'm like well that's true but it really took me aback that like it shows so easily
like I can just sit there not say a damn thing yet it still comes through so strongly apparently
like it really it really left a big impression on them in that regard and I thought I was being
really polite and I was being really polite but they were still they they apparently were like
stealing with rage at me about it like okay there was a part in the car where we were in the car
and like one of them not the one who was driving it wasn't her car but she was like in the front
seat in the shotgun and she was like putting on some pandora in the car and it was like a bunch
of like billboard top 40 pop songs for the most part and it was like um a weird rock cover of somebody
I used to know was playing and I was like huh and and I and I looked at niki and I was just like
man you know when the uh when the interesting musicality of this track is taken away I notice
how kind of stupid the lyrics are lol you know I just I just said that offhandedly and then um
like at another point they were playing drive by by train and I was like oh man niki you know I heard
I watched this one youtube review of this song it was like deconstructing how it's like in a way
the worst lyrics possible like like hefty bag to hold my love that's a weird way to express love
and I even mentioned like I'm really enjoying the song though I love the beat of it I'm enjoying it
at least sitting now I'm enjoying all this music you know it's a fun time we're having um I was
even complimenting the scenery of that we were driving through I'm like man all this countryside
and these buildings and how the roads are like brown instead of gray that's so cool because like
they're like it's like brown tarmac which was totally unique um so those music comments were
interpreted by her as quote belittling my music taste unquote and I was like oh shit I guess you're
right I didn't think about that you know I my main friends my primary friends are people who
we we do podcasts where we just shit on each other's opinions constantly and then we have a
little discord chat where we shit on each other's for our opinions constantly I'm so not used to that
you know like for me just like making critical statements of some piece of media that is put
in front of me is totally normal and so natural I don't think about how you know it could affect
people now I mean I do I do think about it I don't try to be an asshole like it's just that it was
the kind of song she was putting on she was putting like pop songs that I've heard already and I never
listen to pop music I'm talking about music that's so popular I've heard it like again somebody I
used to know number one song of 2012 drive by by train one of those songs that was like a big hit
and is still played consistently to this day I feel like everyone is entitled to a positive or
negative opinion of those musics of those songs and is totally of their right mind to express them
openly like if the friend if that girl was even putting on like a full album of something or
was putting on something that was a little bit more obscure was putting on something with a little
bit more like specificity to it wouldn't have said a damn thing because I would have known that it was
like special to her you know like she did put on a bunch of like like mid-2000s like Disney pop
and she said yeah I love 2000s Disney pop like I know she was being ironic with it but like no no
no she wasn't being ironic with it she was being self aware about that fact but she was being sincere
like I love that that era that style you know that I'm so nostalgic for and Nikki even was like
yeah I totally agree you know and all that pre 2010 Disney pop I'm totally down with so just that
level of personal affection I wouldn't have said any critical thoughts I would have only said positive
things right but when you're when it's drive by by train I'm it's completely okay they'll be like
lyrics in this song are stupid because like those those songs belong to everyone you know
so I I don't think I did anything wrong I honestly I stand by anything I said that day but
it is I'm not like I don't like have a grudge or anything I just find it really interesting how I
come off to people you know like it's okay that they get mad at me or whatever like they can have
their opinion of me and it I was I was sort of getting the vibe that they were mad more because
Nikki spent so much time with me on chat and audio call that she doesn't spend as much time with her
friends as she used to and they're like kind of upset about that so the fact that when they finally
met me I wasn't like eminently charming or anything and was in fact really awkward and quiet
probably you know they were probably getting ready to they were probably kind of ready to get mad so
you know that that's perfectly understandable you know again I'm not saying that people shouldn't
be like that because people like that I don't really care about their opinion of me at all
which I guess is kind of a problem I guess that's where the arrogance comes from but still I do think
it's really interesting because it just goes to show what a weird social circle I surround myself in
in the form of the pcp we're like oh yeah it was like a culture shock sort of the sort of thing you
know and by the way Nikki herself is not like that at all she was like yeah they're my friends are
totally overreacting you didn't do anything offensive at all and Nikki will tell me if I do
think that they're awkward or weird like she will be open with me about that uh but she stands by
everything I said so I think I'm fine but yeah it's just normies man people with normal uh music
taste is a thing okay well that's the gradual annoying petering out of that topic as well
let's see what's else on uh what else osos or else is on my notes here
you know I was uh I was kind of upset when when the last day of being over at my girl
met Nikki came I was like oh man now I gotta pack it up gotta go away and she was like really
upset about it she was like no and I was like yeah don't worry we're gonna see each other again
you know um but I was packing and I was like getting really sentimental about the week we'd
spent in this little tiny hotel and like I whenever I'm packing to like leave a place
that I know I'm not gonna come back to again I get really sentimental about it like I'm like
okay this is it this sock here is the last sock that I need to pack and once I'm done with this
I'm done with the sock packing and like oh man this piece of trash right here is the last
piece of trash in the apartment here we go and I like hold it above the trash can and I'm like
and I drop it I need like slow motion falls into the trash can and I'm like that's the end of the
trash you know and like um when I'm going out the door I'm like this is it this is the last I'm
gonna see of this room done done done and like when I um when I was moving when I was moving out of
my parents house to come in you know live in Virginia like um I just had this really like I
packed over the course of like two days and I like did it really methodically and was like yep
that's this is the end I even filmed my room right before I left I was like this is what my room
looks like you know and and when I was stepping out the door on the way to get to the airport I'm
like okay I actually filmed myself walking out the door and like filming the last shot the last
glimpse of my room the way that it looked before my sister moved into it and made a mess out of it
like a mess that's even worse than a mess I had it in which uh you know I've been to my
room again I visited my family for the holidays but you know yeah um which reminds me of like um
another move that happened previously like three years ago um when I when my family moved in 2013
I was all prepared to pack sentimentally but then I got fucking sick and I was sick for like a whole
day and I couldn't get out of bed and then when I was finally better we had like a few hours to pack
and I was like I had to pack all like frantically and I couldn't be dramatic at all I couldn't be
like nostalgic at all and I was so pissed off I'm like I was cheated I was cheated out of my sentimentality
you know I just realized if we develop space travel and people can like move to Mars and stuff
will they be sentimental for the earth like will I be sentimental for the earth like I bet um like
you know the the travel company that will like hey no for 20 000 bucks go to Mars you know and
live there start be on the colony I bet they'll be like hey for an extra 3 000 or it'll probably be
like 100 000 to get to Mars and it's like oh hey for an extra 20 000 trip around the world for like
five months so you can finally see the earth you can finally see all those wonderful locations
that you never got to see on your home planet you know like just give them one final goodbye you
know before before you before you go on the ship to go to Mars and stuff that'll probably happen
so yeah yeah I packed it up and then I uh gone like gone the plane you know what and then I ended
up in the Chicago O'Hare airports which is which was the step the stepping stone to get over to
Virginia so I was like okay so which terminal do we got to go down and I went the wrong direction I
got to the end of like the C terminal I think and I was like okay so here I am actually no it was
like the E terminal or something or the F terminal I think it was E terminal and uh I was like oh wait
I'm at the end of the terminal it's a dead end wait this isn't the right place oh it's in the B
terminal so I began walking and it was a long ass walk you know every airport I've been to I've
always been told this is a small airport and I'm like what are you talking about this place is huge
like oh man the Virginia airport kind of a small airport I'm like what the Virginia airport is like
five times the size of the Kansas City airport that I come from you know um the Chicago airport
was like a Lovecraftian experience of a walk like it was just like giant giant endless
hallways one after the other it was ridiculous and it wasn't great on my ankle either incidentally my
ankle is is definitely still still healing and especially after this whole week where I spent
walking around with my girlfriend constantly now I'm now I'm back to sitting down and not walking so
hopefully it'll be healed up by by summer hopefully geez anyway you know it was a lot of walking
right and it's cool I love walking except for the fact that I have my ankle problem but other than
that walking is cool it was a really cool scenic trip and I was like man this is a cool place and
then my flight got delayed a couple times and then canceled and it's like yeah um you're gonna
have to go your flight is gonna be like 15 hours from now and I was like oh so it's like go to the
customer support place and they're gonna give you some meal vouchers and a hotel voucher and I'm
like okay so I went back to like the sea terminal or something and the line was super long and some
customer support lady was like hey go actually no no it was the B terminal that I was at but then
the customer lady was like hey the um customer support lady was like hey go to the sea terminal
and I was like okay because she said there's another line there that's not as long
I hadn't been to the sea terminal like on my trip from the E terminal to the B terminal
I didn't go to the C terminal so that one was like this huge like there's this underground bridge
you have to get through that's like all colorful and like just just felt like some sort of purgatory
land with those automatic runways walkways and then you get into the C terminal and it's like a
totally different section I didn't even see for lack of a better term and so it's like man this
place is so freaking huge and uh so I got up to the customer support and they were like okay
here's your meal vouchers and uh I actually declined a hotel voucher I was trying to negotiate for
just more meal vouchers but I didn't get the negotiation but I just refused the hotel voucher
and here's why first of all I don't want to have to um deal with like transitioning like
it was a difficult transition mentally to be like okay I'm with I'm at the hotel now I'm in a car
now I'm in you know the airport now I'm going through security now I'm in the airport then I
get on an airplane then I'm on an airport again right so what I wanted to do was then get on an
airplane then go to the Virginia airport then be in Digi's car then go get sushi and then I'm home
right that's the number of transitions if I get if I take the hotel voucher it adds two more steps
the step of get out of the airport get on a bus like a shuttle that they were gonna offer
go into a hotel check into a hotel just to be there for like one night then check out
then go into a bus again get into the airport and then go through security again for a couple of
reasons one I haven't done it enough times to be natural at it like I like the first time I went
through it I was like okay electronics go here but not big electronics but like what but like what's
a big electronic where is the scale there where is the line drawn you know and okay like sometimes
they just look through all my stuff but sometimes they just scan it you know and also uh this time
on the trip back I have a um a vibrator thingamajig that Nikki wanted me to get so I was like I don't
know how many times I want to like take that out and put it in a little plastic tray for everyone
to inspect you know but oh well um but the but the other problem with going through security again
was that over the course of packing leaving the hotel and like going through security the first
time uh my zipper just died like this is like a this is like a 13 year old um suitcase so the
zipper just died from pressure and so then when I was wading around in the Chicago airport the
zipper like just came completely undone I had no way to secure it and so like the the airport
people gave me some like tape okay they gave me tape to just seal it shut with tape so it's like
you know obviously I just have to get more tape but that'd be a pain in the ass I wouldn't want
to inconvenience them like that to rip off the tape and then ask them for more tape because they
might not have it with them uh I wouldn't want to have to buy my own tape I wouldn't have to
blow money on that and so it's like if I go to the if I go to the hotel I'm not gonna be able to
open my suitcase anyway right like I might be able to tap hazardly retie the tape but that would
just be such a pain so it's like I'm not gonna be able to be comfortable anyway because I'm not
gonna be able to open my suitcase not until I get home and now I am home I I still haven't opened
the tape yet but uh yeah I'm recording this before I put my clothes on and stuff but anyway
so there's there was that right all those reasons why I didn't want to go to a hotel but the number
one reason why I didn't want to go to the hotel was because you know I was getting sick I'd gotten
sick on the way packing from the hotel like like when I was leaving Nikki and I was like I was
getting a sore throat I was getting stuffy so at this point I was like thoroughly sick and I was
like okay in combination with my deliriousness from like transitioning from a hotel to an
airport and stuff I'm tired right I'm tired from expending all this energy I'm mentally
like tumultuous I'm like turbulence in my mind and I'm sick and I'm tired probably so what I assumed
would happen is that I'd get to the hotel I'd fall asleep at some point it would probably take me
a few hours to get to sleep and then I'd sleep so hard that my alarm won't wake won't wake me up
and then I'll miss my flight right like knowing me there's a decent chance that that could happen
not like a high chance but like not a chance that I would want to risk right
and uh and so then what I thought was that well obviously what's most likely is that I'd be so
afraid of that happening that I wouldn't be able to sleep at all like I'd never be able to be calm
enough to go to sleep because I'd be so nervous that that would happen so then I wouldn't be able
to sleep anyway so then what would be the point of going to the hotel and dealing with all the
inconveniences of that you know like just just stay in the airport so I refused the hotel voucher
and I thought I'm just gonna stay in the airport I'm gonna do the whole sleep in an airport thing
right because I knew that if I'm sleeping in the airport I'm not going to be able to sleep
comfortably enough I'll still be on edge enough that like I'll wake up easily right and indeed I
was only able to sleep for like 20 minutes here and there and lay down for a couple hours here and
there so you know but yeah uh so and also the other reason was that I thought being in this
in this airport for like 13 hours 15 hours would be pretty cool you know I'd just be wandering
around doing whatever I want have 20 dollars of free food you know so so I did it and um
you know uh I like the movie Terminal starring Tom Hanks where a dude gets stuck in a hood in an
airport for like years like a year and a half I think so or nine months I think yeah so that was
that was a cool movie and I was like I want to do that you know being on an airport for like 15
hours so there's this sort of like romanticization I have of it in my mind of like you know living all
it's like living on your own it's like this weird vagabond in this place
and it really didn't like get me down at all because it's like I'm always just thinking you know
when I get home I'm just gonna like lay down in bed and play earthbound a bunch on my phone using
a moga 2 pro controller where you can play a controller on your phone with an emulator of
super nintendo with earthbound inside of it right so like I'm just gonna do that when I get home
so if I'm stuck in the airport for 15 hours I'll just play earthbound for 15 hours same
difference just with a bunch of noise and fluorescent lighting around me I ended up not
playing that much earthbound though I was mostly just on a call with with nicky because she was
all sad that I was gone and so she just needed to keep talking to me and you know I was getting
pretty lonely so I guess the point is I felt really productive still like the small amount of
earthbound I played I felt really accomplished in and like the other things I was doing I felt
really accomplished in um there's like this uh the sort of narrative that unfolded with a towel
at the airport when I was there at the whole time uh which was the hitchhiker's guide to the
galaxy reference um to explain the joke to people in hitchhiker's guide to the galaxy they mentioned
that if you have a towel with you a towel with you while you're hitchhiking you're gonna look
much more competent as an individual you will look like a hoopy fruit and a hoopy fruit means
someone who is really amazingly together someone who's really competent and knows what they're
doing if you have a towel with you so I read hitchhiker's guide on the flight over to see nicky
and I was like huh a towel and they just so happened to buy a towel at walmart when I was
with her because I felt like having an extra towel for the hotel and then when I was packing up I'm
like you know what it's going to be an unnecessary waste of space but I'm going to take the towel
with me uh just for the sake of being hoopy so um yeah and I tweeted about it extensively so I
recommend going to my twitter and scrolling down to like um February the 21st and just reading I
highly recommend reading all of my tweets from that from that uh section from that timeline
uh from the 21st up through march 1st yeah being in an airport uh I felt really
competent I felt really put together you know the only thing that sucked about it was being sick
and not being able to walk too much without my ankle getting sore
and motorcycle came and went anyway um yeah uh I felt really I felt like I was really using my
time really well and it was just that looming overhead knowledge of a schedule of like a time
you have to do something right like you know I've I've I've I've I've flown a bunch of times now
in the last in the last five months you know flying over to Virginia then flying over to my
family and back and then flying over to Nikki and back so it's like I've I've done the airport
experience a bunch of times in a row now like three times in a row now and every time I feel
really like I'm I'm managing my time well because there's again this looming overhead
schedule that you have to conform to but it's a schedule that mostly involves sitting around
right and whenever you see business dudes who obviously fly all the time with their laptops
they seem really wired they seem really plugged in they seem like they really know what they're
doing they seem like every second is being maximized for efficiency and that's what I felt like
um in the Chicago airport that whole time like I felt like I was always doing something
whether playing earthbound or talking to Nikki or tweeting something funny so and I was like I
wonder if that's part of how of where Casey Neistat gets his power because Casey Neistat's a very
prolific person who makes you know who did like a whole vlog series where he made a fully edited
vlog every day for like a year and a half just to do just for the sake of itself um and he still
makes a pretty decent upload of videos and he does all sorts of other business things all the time
I mean and it's because well not because but in addition to that he flies places all the time
like businesses phone him up be like hey fly to this place they give him a first class ticket
and he's just flying all the time all over the place and I'm like uh man I wonder if that's part
of where his productivity comes from that he do you always have these these these upcoming dates
where you have to do something but most of those dates involve sitting around and you can open
your laptop and do something then you know and I and I was like yeah it's it's a very distinct
different feeling from what I do normally and what Digi does normally and what Ben and the other
pcp people mostly do is you're just in your room for weeks on end not even really needing to leave
having to completely motivate yourself to get stuff done and I love doing that I love motivating
myself and and making it all happen and like I feel like I'm pretty good at it and stuff
but I do think it was a very interesting different feeling to have this whole airport thing going on
so maybe if you know maybe if when I'm rich and I can just fly around all for the sake of it or
I don't know like I do all these business things involve flying around a bunch maybe I'll be even
more productive then maybe I'll really dig that lifestyle I don't know but you know I don't probably
not necessary I'm pretty good at this being at home thing probably as a result of being home
schooled you know like my parents policy was basically like hey you can do what you want right
with your life like if you're willing to work and it's something sensible and you're going to be
responsible you can take the life path that you want to take right so like my younger brother he got
into like uh into like hunting and guns and like knives and just being like an outdoorsman kind of
dude so that's kind of the life he leads and also working with my dad and playing video games and
stuff but yeah he's just sort of he's sort of like that uh and you know working out and being slim
he doesn't work out enough to like have like visible muscles but he's got like a nice fit body and
stuff plays sports I think that kind of guy my sister you know she got into dancing and like
performing the performing arts so that's kind of her life and she actually wanted to like go to a
school so eventually she convinced my parents to be like okay you can go to like this sort of
Christian school thing you know um so that's her lifestyle right me I was just like oh I guess I'll
just stay in my house all the time you know I'll just stay inside I go outside a lot but mostly
just my backyard that's kind of what I like I like being outside I like fresh air and sunlight
but I'm okay just being on my own property you know that's what I like about trampolines you
know that's actually should have probably been on the list is uh it's a great way to like just exert
physical energy without leaving the site of your house you know it's a whole lot of activity
without without even going away from your back door and you know pools are the same thing so
that's kind of what I'm into you know I like getting out and going places but I'm perfectly
content to just stay still all the time and when all of your school work is also homework I guess
I just am good at at doing that kind of work where you just have to motivate yourself you're in your
bedroom you could be playing DS right now but you're gonna do the work anyway you know uh so so
there you go that's that was like my lifestyle choice in combination with the lifestyle my parents
sort of gave to me uh you know the downsides are that you know I'm more awkward as a result because
I didn't want to go out and like talk to people all the time so like you know I come off as like
quiet or when I do talk I'm way too loud uh you know that's a downside but the upside is that I
feel like I'm really well specced to be a youtuber like all my stats are really uh leveled up in that
regard uh to be a youtube person who can also work at making programs and stuff yippee whoops
and uh that's it that's the end of this episode of the devu hadron collider episode four even though
to me it feels like episode seven because of all those other ones I recorded that uh I don't know
maybe I'll release them at some point maybe I could um release them as bonus episodes only for uh
hmm maybe for the pcp patreon I could do that yeah maybe I'll do that I don't know
tell me how badly you'd want to listen to them I guess you'd probably want to listen to them just
because you have no idea what they're about but you know most of them are redundant off of each
other because each one was meant to be a replacement of the other one I don't know okay whatever
that's the end um I'm gonna take a sip of this tea even though it's all gone for dramatic effect
sighing for dramatic effect