Well, that didn't sound very aesthetically appealing, appealing, unpeeling, you know, I'm
all about going fast, and hard, and doing lots of things. I hate being slow, and I hate
feeling like there could have been more I could have gotten done in the day. You know,
I hate feeling anything less than really motivated and really energized with whatever
I'm doing. And you know, listening to Digi's decompressions about how much he does that
all the time makes me go, ah, I gotta do that. But you know, a lot of that really comes
down to how long it's been, how long I've had to build up speed, or rather to build
up mental clarity. You see, I guess in two days, no, probably, okay, it's basically
right now, it's basically the anniversary of when I finally left my job, which is the
thing I had wanted more in my life than anything that I have ever had ever wanted before or
since it actually got. So this is like the first anniversary of something that I really
deeply care about. Because there's a number of reasons why, just the fact that you spend
most of your day doing something you don't want to do. But that, even when you get back,
it doesn't work as well because you're so tired. You get back from work and you're frigging
tired. You don't have quite enough energy to do the work you wanted to, you know? That's
what really made it stressful and annoying and made me hate it so much is that being
at the job makes it harder to do something else that you want to do instead, that you
want to be able to turn into a career. So it was like every video I was making, it was
really suspenseful to me whether or not it would be successful because every video that
was successful brought me one step closer to being able to quit my job. But if it didn't
get successful, then it wasn't necessarily a step closer, which meant another whole week
or two added on to the maximum time limit it would take for me to keep doing the job.
I became an absolute monster of antisocialness during this time. I became very much a nope
not going to do this, not going to do that. I feel like I've already explained this in
multiple different podcasty areas, but you know. So when I did quit the job, it still
took time to get into the right mental gears. Because like for example, when you're working
full time, working say five days a week on the other two days, it doesn't quite work
to just then do a different job. The whole point of having those two days off is because
you need the time off to unwind, to decompress if you will. So working on those days anyway,
it's still jumbled and messy and confusing and aggravating. Particularly when the thing
you are doing is blue collar and the thing you want to be doing is white collar because
my body is like there'd be times where I'd get like a whole week off, but my body is
very much used or at least was very much used to physical movement throughout the day. So
sitting at the computer was agonizing like every single day until about five days in
I would finally get used to it, but then it would be back to work again and I'd have to
readjust the other way. So you know quitting my job took me really took me months to really
get efficient at what I was doing throughout the day, but I could never be quite that efficient
because I was still living with my family where you know, there's something inefficient
when you live at home with people who are off doing their own things that aren't related
to what you're doing, which I know I'm sounding like a psychotic selfish maniac with this.
I'm not saying this is a terrible thing. You could obviously have a successful career
with this, but I'm all about being faster, being more efficient and like living now as
I do with you know, the guy who I work with and then also like another guy who also makes
YouTube videos and does art stuff. Like something about it clicks more. Something about the
fact that we're all doing the same kind of thing makes things faster. Maybe just the
fact that I'm living with roommates who are friends rather than family. It speeds me up.
I don't know. Maybe it's a presenteeism where I feel the need to be more efficient around
friends. I don't know what it is, but I just always feel like every time I'm in the kitchen
and like my dad walks in, it feels like it slows me down. Every time I am in the kitchen
and Ben walks in, it feels like it speeds me up. Don't know why it just is. Don't even
know how psychological it is. It might just be purely in my head, but I do think it does
make a huge difference. So after quitting my job in like the very end of the year last
year, it took me months to really build up speed, but I could never build up that much
speed because I was with my family. And then when Radcon happened and I moved over here,
I got slow all over again. I was like totally discombobulated. I mean, there would be moments
where I'd sit down and crunch out like the whole Kuriko vs. Haikyuu video in like two
days or like my whole how to understand themes video on my channel, which I put together
in like nine hours from concept to completion. So I still had plenty of moments of like being
fast, but there were just so many not fast moments in between them, you know, so much
build up and so much standing around. What am I doing right now? And it's okay for people
to live like that. Most people do, but I find that depressing. So finally, at some point,
I finally everything has just been snapping into place. It was really going back to my
families for a bit because I went back to my family's house for five days for Christmas,
although the days I was actually there was December 15th through the 20th, not on Christmas
because my family wanted me to do a specific thing on the 18th. And I'm like, well, in
that case, I'm not going to be there on the 25th. So I celebrated Christmas a week early,
got back home and I'm like, this is my chance because I took five days off probably the
first time in like four years, I took five straight days without with while neither working
on anything nor planning on working anything, nor feeling bad about not working on something
like I'm always I think I've taken like five day periods where I did nothing. But I was
like frantic about it and always eyeing the keyboard for when I was going to get back.
So I finally took five days of actual break, came back, and I'm like, this is my opportunity
to finally get fast. And it was and I did it. I fasted and I am still fasting
to take that pun more literally, I have been losing weight. I have been
showering more often, you know, almost every day.
My ankle situation is finally going to get resolved, I hope.
I sprained my ankle really badly way back in summer of 2015.
At work, I totally blame the job stupid fucking clean windows getting off ladders.
Grass was wet, sprained ankle, never completely healed. I guess because I'm a trampoline
addict. And I walk around weird, both digi and my brother have told me that I walk funny
when I bring up my ankle situation to them. So apparently I don't walk right. And that
makes it hard for my ankle to heal. And again, for a long time, I just couldn't stay off trampolines,
man, they're so much fun, they're so much fun. So I mean, most of the time, almost all the time,
I would keep my left foot off of trampoline, I wouldn't put pressure on it, I bounce on one foot.
But don't think that really helped because, you know, it's still bobbing around and stuff.
So I'm sure that kept it from healing. But I've been over here, living in Virginia,
no trampoline in sight for over a month. And it's still my ankle just gives, you know,
it's just a little bit achy, not enough pain to be annoying, but enough pain that I still
have to worry about it. That's the problem having to constantly worry about my ankle.
And did you was like, yo, you should get that looked at because I can't like take like a 30
minute walk before it starts to hurt, right? And it'll stay hurting for the next three days.
That's a problem. So I went to the ankle doctor and they said, try stretching it and take this pill.
And I did. And it didn't work at all. The ankle is still just as bad, possibly worse. So I went
there again the next month. And he was like, okay, don't stretch it. Don't move it. Don't use it.
Put on a big friggin boot thing. You know, if you ever see it's sort of like a cast,
but it's also like a boot. It's just got like these metal beams and straps all over it.
So if you've ever seen that kind of person walked around on their foot with that thingy,
that's what I've got. So yeah, now what happens is now everyone asks, what's wrong with your foot?
What happened to your foot? It got better. That's what happened to my foot. I am better off now
than the last time you saw me without question. But it didn't become visual until now. The problem
is finally being fixed. I can finally walk around without having to worry about it. It used to be
even having to walk over to the kitchen or walk it over to the other computer would be like,
I don't want to do it and use up ankle points. Now I don't got to worry about that.
So that's good. You know, I still can't like take long walks or anything, but you know,
I got to be moderate with my walking. But at least when I do walk, I don't have to worry about it.
And that's really nice. Incidentally, this is unrelated to what I was talking about. But sometimes,
you know, when you get like a throat bubble and it like feels all weird and it's really itchy and
you want to cough it out immediately, I've trained myself to just keep talking when it happens and
hopefully have a recording on when it's happening. Like I'll usually bust out my phone and try to
record it. But I'm usually not able to get it before it goes away. But thankfully this time I'm
actually recording something right now as I got the throat bubble caused by this angry orchard apple
apple cider. I think the bubble is mostly gone by now. But yeah, I'm gonna keep
Oh gosh, it gets really annoying and hard to not cough out anyway.
Oh, I'm spiking the microphone like a crazy man.
Okay, I turned down the gain. Look at these gains anyway. So yeah, my ankle is doing better. Friggin
What I mean is throughout the day, I have fewer and fewer things to worry about and be distracted
by. Because like, you know, I move into a new house, everything's in a different position,
everything just walking around takes some mental effort for the first like couple of days. It was
only like a couple of weeks ago where it finally everything evened out and I could walk around
without any any increment of conscious thought, you know. So that's good. Just no distractions,
nothing getting in my way, no medical problems other than the ankle. But again, it's it's more
when you work from home, having this thing on isn't an issue. The only time where I have to
walk around a lot is when I go to the groceries. And the only problem then is like old people going
how to let them ankle. I'm like, yeah. And they're just looking at me like, so yeah,
I'm like, mm hmm. I mean, I know what they're talking about because they're looking at my foot.
But you know, if you're going to say a random comment to a stranger in the grocery store,
prepare what you're going to say, like form your statement in your head fully.
Make sure they're looking in your general direction and then speak clearly or else
give up. Don't say it because they're not going to hear you. So with that in mind,
you know, I pumped out that whole Digi video about the fan service and I sat down with a list
of anime to watch. Because earlier this year, I believe in April, May or June, Digi made a list
for me at my request of shows that I might need to watch for upcoming videos. Because one thing
that was kind of annoying for me is that every time Digi had a new show to talk about, it would be
a show I haven't seen before. So I'd have to watch it from scratch every time, pretty much.
So I was like, hey, you know what'd be cool is if I could just like, watch all the shows in advance
that you plan to maybe at some point talk about, right? I think that's how it came about. The point
is he made a list called the shows for a debut to watch for possible upcoming videos. And he made
a list of all of them. Um, it's like 80 to 90 shows on the list. No, maybe it's more like 70,
I don't know. But, uh, by the way, the list isn't actually complete. He actually got all
the way up to the letter S and it gave up. So any shows that he wants to talk about that are
between T and Z, he has not listed on that list, but whatever. I decided to watch all those shows,
or at least as many as I could. And so I have been. I've skipped shows that are really long,
like a record seven, and I've skipped some things where he wants me to also read the manga, like,
frickin, uh, King of Bandits Jing, for instance. So like there, there, those are the only categories
that I've ignored shows where you have to also read the manga because I'll read manga when I'm in
the mood for it. And I've read manga, I've read some manga, not quite in the mood for it at the
moment, but when I'm in the mood, I'll do those ones. Not in the mood to watch something super
long out of nowhere at the moment, you know, so I discounted the manga ones, discounted the long
ones, but I've been watching everything else. And so yeah, I think it was like 60 or 70 of those.
And over the course of the year, I've been plowing through them, getting really good at
marathoning as a result. So after I came back from my trip with my family, I sit down and I have like
six or seven shows left. And I have nothing else to do for the rest of the month, right? I finished
the fan service video, that's the only video that needs to be made for the rest of the month.
So I sit down and I start watching them, and I watch one episode of Martian Successor Nadesco,
then I decide to take a shower. And then in the shower, I'm reminded of video games again. I remember
the idea of making video games, what it was like to make that one RPG that I made half of and posted
onto new grounds. And was reminded of how I keep going into video game holes, which is what I call
them, where I have the insatiable desire to program video games or do whatever I can to make video
games, you know, because, you know, artistic expression, man. And then I'm reminded of a video
that I had watched just a week or two before called object oriented programming is bad.
And that video remind reminding myself of that video made me realize that I should try
programming yet again. So first I'll tell you the story of how I gave up on programming. But
before that, I'll tell you the story of how I tried to program the first time. So I guess I'm
now just going to tell you my whole relationship with making video games. Yeah. Let's go.
My whole life I knew I was going to do some sort of entertainment media thing, right?
I didn't know I didn't realize that you're supposed to just use the word artist as a kid. I
didn't realize that the word artist from of any medium was the term to describe it. So as a kid,
all I could phrase it as was a someone who works in some sort of entertainment field. That's
probably even more articulate than I would have phrased it as a kid. So you know, throughout my
childhood and adolescence, I would go from one to the other like making cartoons on new grounds.
I was big in the new grounds for one year. I really thought that making flash day flash games
and flash animations was a cool idea. But you know, didn't really have the patience for it.
And I didn't I didn't know how to pirate flash, you know, how to make how to get flash or how to
I didn't have the desire to pirate it and I didn't know how I didn't even realize that
almost everyone was like I didn't understand yet at the time that most people on the internet
pirate everything, at least in communities such as new grounds. And even then, there are free
alternatives like live swift or at least there was I don't know that program still exists. But
you know, it's crappy and dated even for its age. But you know, it's still sufficient for animation.
If I really wanted to make animations, I would have used live swift and I would have made something
but had no patience, you know, tried art, you know, got went from being abysmal to being terrible,
which is an improvement. You know, tried this tried that, you know, made like one or two songs.
I felt like I was always getting something done, you know, I didn't ever go that long just doing
nothing. So I got I got like a familiarity with many different mediums. And at some point,
I decided that it's going to be video games, like that's the best one.
As a kid, I did make one video game in Windows PowerPoint, which is the slide show presentation
software. And because I because I realized at one point that you can program buttons in that
software, a button in Windows PowerPoint that if you program it, it will take you to whichever
other frame in the project you want to go to. So it was like, oh, hey, you could just arrange a bunch
of these buttons, and they take you to different frames, different slides. And you could essentially
program a game that way. So I just made a very simple choose your own adventure game, where
basically, you go up to a situation, and you're confronted with a problem, and you have three
options, and one will succeed, and the others will get you killed. So yeah, it was inspired by that
one episode of Arthur, where a bunch of the kids were playing that particular game. It was just
like it. I had based my entire design document off of that Arthur episode, not on any actual games
of that sort. I remember the project ended up being exactly 1111 frames long, and I felt pretty
accomplished in doing it. Made it when I was 10 years old, would have been 2004 on a laptop,
Windows XP, not like I had anything better to do.
When I was 16 or so, I was messing around an RPG maker, making some levels, making some items,
but then I was like, you know, I want to tweak things. I want to make the main character walk
slower or faster, or I want to have a specific set of animation frames for this item, and
doing all that just always was such a pain. It was like having these pre-built programs
that do all the work for you. It's like if I want to change something, it just sends me to the forums,
trying to figure out if I even can change it. It's not really that fun for me.
But over the course of watching YouTube videos on the internet, I got more and more inspired into
video gaming. At some point, it just became clear to me that games are the things I care about,
really the most in a way. I mean, not really counting YouTube videos, and YouTube analyses,
those are technically the zero thing I care about, but video games are the first thing I care about,
and videos like AVGN, getting me interested in how to think about games critically,
and getting me an appreciation for old games, and then the Game Over thinker was a big deal for
me. That really introduced me to the concept of artistic expression in a more meaningful way,
and creative voice, that kind of stuff. Also, extra credits, framing. It really framed video
game development as this huge series of insurmountable challenges, and that made it really sexy and
cool, and like, oh wow, all these incredibly impossible things that people are trying to figure out.
I'd like to figure that out. What really pushed over the edge was Jimquisition, presenting how
shit, and corrupt, and bad so many of the game developers, and even game publishers, and even
some game developers are with their business practices. And that made it even more interesting
for me. It seemed like not only would it be a fun challenge, but it would also be an easy way to
feel morally superior to lots of people by not being shit like that. And I was like, yeah,
I gotta do video games.
Now, when I was 17 and a half, that was when my dad finally started making me go to work with him
all the time. He finally brought me onto the family business full-time. He had gotten me to go and
clean windows with him sometimes, as early as like when I was 13. You know, just once or twice here
and there, you know. When I had free time, nothing better to do, and I could make some money that
way. So it was a great way to make money as a teenager. But when I was 17, that's when he finally
started to make me work full-time. And when I was 18, by then, I had built up finally a work ethic.
I finally had the ability to just push past being tired, or frustrated, or not inspired,
and just do the work anyway. An incredibly important and valuable ability. That's in combination with
really being inspired with video games and really thinking that I have them. I figured out what I
want to do with my life. So mentally, I was ready. Work ethically, I was ready. And I was really into
MLP at this time, and now it's kind of really uplifting me after a couple of years of teenage
depression. So the tide was right, and I just decided time to make a video game. So
what did I do first? I believe what I tried first. Don't remember exactly which one I did first,
but I think what I did first was I downloaded Multimedia Fusion 2. And that's a game making
software. And I messed around with it some. And then I made a game called Impossible Maneuvering.
It's basically one of those games where you move a symbol around an object like a square,
and you have to dodge other objects like an amaze without touching any of the objects
and to get to the goal without touching anything. It's basically just like that,
but where every level is totally different and every level has a different mechanic
and different graphics and stuff. So that's the kind of game I like, you know, games where
everything, there's always a lot of variety, things are always changing, there's a lot of
character involved. So it's that cliche genre of flash game tweaked to be exactly my kind of game.
So I'm still pretty proud of it, to be honest. Like, yeah, Impossible Maneuvering. I would
honestly recommend it, you know, it gets way too hard, way too fast, though. So it's something to
get frustrated bail out, unless you like a steep, unfair challenge. So then I thought, okay,
multimedia fusion is great and all, but it's not really a programming language.
It's basically like you throw a bunch of squares together, like it's,
it's sort of like trying to make a user visual interface, even though it is legitimately a
programming language. It's just kind of a kind of a shitty one. So I thought, I want to learn
action script, because that's the that's the code that flash uses. So I messed around with that a
bit. I bought I didn't just mess around. I bought a $50 action script 3.0 manual, and started
studying it over the course of a few weeks. And I was getting me I was learning some things like
object oriented programming, which basically is a way to like, chop up the code, like instead of
reading all the code at once, you can look at different little chunks of code at different
times without having to memorize all of it. And also stuff like classes where,
um, like certain objects can inherit properties from other objects. That way, you don't have to
like, type out everything all over again all the time. So that's a great that you know, that's,
that's a popular way to program and stuff. So I learned about that. Because when I made impossible
maneuvering, I had no idea what I was doing. Like, that game has very little complex programming
in it, because I knew nothing about how to make a game really. So it was a good idea for me to
make something so simple. But I wanted to make, you know, I wanted to get more of an idea about
the program. I couldn't, I was able to understand the idea of like how programming works and stuff,
but I couldn't even like, in terms of actually making something, even get so far as successfully
compiling something. I just couldn't figure it out. It was just, no, no, no, no, I just felt like
I really needed like someone who I was friends with who knew this stuff to explain it to me,
you know, going to a class would probably be beneficial at first, like just a couple of weeks,
so that I can get off to a good start. Really, just the best way would be to hire a personal tutor
or for the best, awesome, perfect tutorial to be out there somewhere. But none of those things were
true. I didn't really know anyone at this time. I didn't really know anyone on the internet very
well. Certainly not anyone who was like good at anything. Good at programming, I mean. So I put
an action script down, went back to multimedia fusion, and was like, okay, let's make something
else. Let's make something a little bit more ambitious, but not too ambitious. And I just,
I really wanted to do an RPG, like not like a big 50 hour Final Fantasy type thing,
more like a tight, short type thing. That's more about just being quirky and fun, very
Superstar Sega-esque and other games, you know, like Earthbound and stuff like that.
I've actually not played Earthbound, because as a teenager, it was not on the virtual console,
so I couldn't play it that way. And now as an adult who's finally willing to pirate games
and Earthbound is on the virtual console, I just don't have time for an RPG anymore.
But I have been very familiar with Earthbound and what it's about and what it's like. And I've,
in a sense, been a fan of it for a long time for like 10 years, because of that.
You know, because of Smash Brothers and reviews and retrospectives and such. And I did play the
first couple hours of it. So I'm a fan of Earthbound too. You don't have to play something to be a
fan of it. You know, taking influence from those kinds of things. From like, you know, Paper Mario,
other quirky RPGs. And I decided to make one of those. And, you know, not necessarily the
best idea. I ended up spending a year and a half making it. Late 2012 to early 2014,
that was how much time I spent making it. And I only made one half of it. I realized I'm not
going to be able to finish it. I'll just release the first half of it. So yeah, it was long and
tedious. And I did it way too slow. And I didn't know what I was doing. But I was like,
what am I going to do? Am I just going to sit around planning shit, learning shit forever
and ever and ever before I decide to just jump in? Let's just jump in now. Like, yeah, I'm going to
jump in prematurely. And I'm going to suck at it. But at least I'll be getting experience points
in knowledge when I do so. So I just did it. And yeah, I think it was a reasonable use of my time.
I wouldn't have been doing anything else in that time. You know, I would have had nothing else to
do once I came home from work. And I will say, I have no regrets about my work ethic during that
time. I really hampered myself into oblivion, almost never taking any sort of break, you know,
just using almost every single ounce of spare time I had. So yeah, for like a year and a half. So
it was messed up, you know. Over the course of making it, early into making it, I discovered
Digi Brony, MLP, and I became a fan of him and then other horseshoe crew people as that whole
group started to form. And here in Digi and Jesse talk about how hard it is to be a YouTuber on
their podcasts, made YouTubeing sound like a really interesting challenge instead. And I was like,
you know what, I think I want to get into this instead, because the whole 2013, that was when
like the analysis thing was really becoming a thing and a lot of different mediums. And I'd
finally learn to understand what I really liked about YouTube videos that I liked. Like I finally
figured out what I liked about certain kinds of reviews. Also with stuff like Roger Van Der Weed.
Roger Van Der Weed. That is a guy who does this series called Sonic Dyssected, which really
introduced me to the fact I really liked the idea of an analysis over a review. And I was like,
yeah, this is what I need to do instead. I'm going to drop video game development for now,
because this RPG I'm making, I'm only going to release half of it and I don't think anyone's
going to like it. So April 30, 2014, I finally posted the game on Newgrounds, got like a 2.5,
got like two views, no 2000 views, which is like basically nothing got like five or so reviews,
most of them complaining about the load time because it was like a 20 megabyte download,
which for like flash, for a flash application is a lot. And that was basically it. And I'm like,
you know what, whatever. The fact that I made something competent, something that only sometimes
glitches out, bugs out and crashes on my first attempt isn't too bad. And I like, I like the
ideas in it. I mean, it is basically boring, but I liked, I like the style of it. I like the feel
of it. So yeah, I don't regret any of that. But it was time for me to move on. It was time for me
to put video game development on the backboard or focus on YouTube instead. So I spent, incidentally,
the reason why I said I came out with everything with that game, April 30, 2014, was because I
specifically wanted to get it out before my birthday, so that I could tell everyone, yeah, I came out
with my first fully specced out game when I was 19, you know, that way I can make myself sound like
I have experience, you know, like, yeah, I made an adventure game when I was 10. And then I made a
a freaking dodging shapes game when I was 18. And then I made an RPG. I made half of an RPG
when I was 19. April 30 is my birthday. But I got it out 30 minutes, no, 15 minutes before my
birth minute. And I'm in the same time zone. So yes, it was when I was 19. I then immediately had
to spend three hours after posting it three hours fixing a game break and glitch. But, you know,
all video games have patches these days. No one counts that. So yes, I released my first fully
specced out RPG with a level up system, battle system, overall system, overall puzzles. Yeah,
it has puzzles, man. It has some somewhat complicated puzzles on it. Okay, it has one
somewhat complicated puzzle in it. And I made it all before when I was 19. I have so much experience,
man. And then it was all YouTube for me for the next solid year and a half or so.
And then Undertale came out. Had people recommending it to me up and down the street
corners, you know, because it's exactly the kind of game I like is the kind of game I want to play,
the kind of game I wanted to make, you know, it's very much I call YouTube. The genre I give to
Undertale is good RPG. It's like an RPG, but where everything is interesting and unique, you know,
it's not usually about grinding. It's usually about experiencing characters and a story and
interesting mechanics and having fun and doing creative things all the time. That's my favorite
kind of game. So that's why people were recommending it to me because everyone knows how much I like
Superstar Saga. And I was very much sold just by the fact that people were recommending it to me
for that specific reason. So I finished the video project I was working on, set that game aside.
Well, I set everything aside for that game, played it, made a video about it, really got into it
as much as I possibly could have hoped to.
And again, you know, I feel like I like that game probably more than a lot of its biggest fans,
but for a slightly different reason. Like, you know, the great music, the story, the characters,
the unique mechanics, the way it touches your own personal meta with video games. Like, everyone
has this meta with video games where they feel that strange sensation when they restart a level
and they experience the story again slightly differently. But no one knows about it. But you,
you know, that's like a meta element that everyone feels that that game taps into that really,
that really hits people really hard. And all of that brings the game up to like a 9.5 for me. But
what really pushes it into the 10 territory is just the personal connection of it being so exactly
like the kind of thing that I want to exist and the kind of thing I want to make and the kind of
thing I want to play. Toby Fox, that game really feels like I can feel Toby Fox's creative voice
every step of the way. And that I can, I feel like I come from such a similar place as where Toby
comes from, you know. And so that really stuck with me. And I'm like, I got to mess around with
multimedia fusion again. I just have this incredible urge to work on video games, not going to set
aside YouTube, not going to actually try to make a game, but I'm at least going to mess around,
I'm going to tinker around. And that's when I decided that I probably will make a game at some
point. But I'm going to do it the exact opposite way as I did the first time. The first time the
RPG, I deliberately ran into it with no planning, because I didn't even know how to plan. I didn't
know nothing about planning. So planning it for nothing wasn't going to work. I knew I was going
to have to go in and fail so that I would at least know what it's like so that I could then foresee
what the what the second attempt would be like, you know. So this time, I'm going to plan up the
wazoo. I'm going to come, I'm going to learn every single thing I'm doing. I'm going to make sure
I know absolutely everything I'm doing down to the bone before I actually start making it. So
this, I can spend, I can spend all the time I need, because it doesn't need to be my full-time
job. I can be doing YouTube in the meantime as my main job. This can take as long as it needs to.
I decided multimedia fusion wasn't the best choice for me. I decided I want something that was a
little bit more like an actual programming language, because as I just, as I said, the programs just,
they try to make part of the game for you, but it's hard to then make the game exactly the way
you want, because part of it's already been made for you. And I'm someone who always wants to tweak
you know, all the little variables to feel just right and just a little bit more unique, you know.
So I checked out Game Maker, right? I believe I actually bought it for like 100 bucks. I also
bought a $25 book on design flow. What's it called? Like design methods, ways to use the
object-oriented programming in a good way. How to get the program to communicate with itself,
to get the code flowing up and down the tunnels in an efficient manner. I know I worked around
with that for like three chapters, and it was just kind of going over my head, and I was just like,
okay, you know, this is fine and all, but you know, time for me to get back to videos. I really got
to focus almost all my timeline videos. Another six months or so goes by, or nine months, and cut to
a few weeks or so, or a month or so into living here in the Radcon house in the Colin Castle,
where I suddenly fall into a video game hole again. I'm supposed to be making videos, supposed to
be watching anime, but I make the foolish decision to watch YouTube, which is a decision I make like,
you know, 50 times a day, but I watched the wrong video this time. I decided to catch up on the
Gymquisition's Best of Steam Greenlight Trailers series, where Jim Sterling will watch a trailer
for a Steam Greenlight game and commentate over it sarcastically. Specifically, Steam Greenlight
trailers that are obvious like, big rigs over the road racing tier shit, right? It's like hundreds
of episodes along this series, and I'd watched like all those episodes last year, but I decided to
catch up again, which was like 50 episodes. And remember when I said about how much I'm drawn
to challenge, but I'm also drawn to the idea that things are easy, or rather that no matter how bad
I end up failing, I'll be better than a lot of people. I'm like, wow, watching these greenlight
trailers, it's like, if I made a game, no matter how bad I fuck up, I will be better
by leaps and bounds than all of these people. God damn, I should make video games. I should
make video games. I should make video games. I should make video games. I should make video games.
This chair is loud, and I decided I should make video games. So I did what I described as falling
into a video game hole, where I wasted three days messing around in programs, even messing around
in Unity. I was kind of kicking around the idea of like, you know, what about 3D modeling? You know,
I don't plan on trying, even trying to make a 3D game anytime soon. Anytime this decade, probably,
if ever. But you know, 3D modeling, it can still be fun.
Open up multimedia fusion again, just because I'm much more familiar with that program.
I was trying to mess around with certain, I keep saying mess around, but you know, I was trying to
like, hash out like a certain mechanic that I had in my mind. And I was having a fun time programming
it and all. But then, very quickly, it just got too complicated for me. It just got too tricky,
and I had to give up. And I'm like, God damn it, I think I just don't have the brain to be a programmer.
I don't have the attention span. I don't have the ability to study, and like, just, and just be good.
You know, too friggin' dyslexic for that shit. I don't know if I, I don't know what it is. I guess
just being on disciplines, blah, blah, blah. I don't know, I don't think it's not discipline,
I just think I just literally don't have the mental capacity for programming. That's the
conclusion I came to at the time. But stick with me here, okay? I'll get back to that in a minute.
So I decided that what I should do is get other people who are actual programmers and hire them
to do the programming. Now, I know what you're thinking. Well, what some of you might be thinking,
which is, oh, you're an ideas guy. You have all these great ideas for games, but you just
need someone else to make them. That's not what it is at all. I can have the idea for a game.
And design all, like, and design all the mechanics. Think about how, and like, draw it all out.
Design all the levels. Do all the art. Or at least most of the art. I mean, I could do competent
art if I put a lot of time into it, believe me. And if it was a certain kind of style.
I could basically do everything except for making the music and doing 80% of the programming. That
was my conclusion. My idea was not, I don't even have to think about the programming, but rather,
I would hire a professional programmer to do like the main meat of the work, but I will closely
observe. And he will tell me, he or she, okay, equal opportunity. Here she will tell me
what they're doing and how the mechanics are working. And they can guide me through it.
And then I can plug the rest of the game into that, you know, like, they design the basic
controls. And then they design, like, how, you know, like, certain objects react to it. And I
can study that and they can tell me and they can teach me. And then I can make little tweaks to
it as I need to. That was my idea. Through that, through that idea up on Twitter. And a certain
fan of mine and TPC fan in general, I think, Joji's magical supplies, or Joji's magic supplies,
contacted me saying, Hey, I'm a programmer. I'd be interested in this. So we got into contact. And
I was like, Okay, here's some ideas for a game I have. I'd like you to put together a really basic
prototype that would do this, this and this. If you do it, I'll pay you this amount of money.
But Joji, listen, you can take as much time as you need to. Rather, I want you to take as long as
possible. Because I'm busy. I'm making YouTube videos and all, you know, I'm busy with all that.
So I want you to take a long time because I think it's going to be well over a year before I'm
even starting to seriously plan about games I want to make, right? He's like, Cool. So, you know,
he comes out with some early drafts of the prototype in Yada Yada. And again, he's taken a
long time like I told him to, which is fine because he has things to do and stuff, you know,
he has school and stuff. So all that was kind of on the back burner. I went back to making videos,
you know, went to see my family for five days, you know, came back, make a fan service video,
you know, decided to finish off that anime watched one episode of Martian Successor in the Desco.
Then I went off to take a shower. And as in the shower, I was reminded of all the things that I
just told you about, except for one thing that I forgot to mention, which is that a couple of weeks
prior, I happened to stumble upon a video. And this video is what really triggered me to remember
all these things as I was taking a shower. It's this video called OOP is bad, which OOP stands
for object oriented programming is bad. And I was like, huh, I got to click on this. And he's like,
this will be the most important video you will ever watch object oriented programming is universally
accepted in the industry. No one will listen. No one will believe me. But it's actually the worst
thing ever. Okay, I'm sorry. He doesn't sound like a libertarian. Okay, he's perfectly rational.
You know, it's a 40 minute video. I understood like 60% of it perfectly, I think.
And it yeah, I was like, huh, interesting. But that made me think about game design again.
So fast forward to a few weeks later, which is now a week ago, I get out of the shower.
And I decide to not watch that episode of Nadesco episode two, I decide to download
Godot, which is a new game design engine, similar to Game Maker, similar to multimedia fusion.
But like supposedly better, maybe it'd be better for me and it's free. So I downloaded it. And I'm
like, yeah, this is an engine. It's good. Oh, I got tired of it in like five minutes.
And that was what really made me realize I don't think these programs are for me.
Maybe I'll move up to them and later on, I know that professionals use them.
I mean, like, okay, look, you know, Undertale, made in Game Maker, sure, but like
Undertale isn't the most technically impressive game out there. Whereas like, okay, with multimedia
fusion, for instance, you know, I released it in 2014, that same year, five nights at Freddy's and
Freedom Planet come out, also made in multimedia fusion. You know, five nights at Freddy's is
fairly somewhat technically impressive, but just the fact that it has pre-rendered graphics, I guess.
But Freedom Planet is quite technically impressive, just the fact that the character has 360 degree
movement, I think. It's like, how do you even do that in multimedia fusion? Dang.
So clearly people know how to use that stuff professionally, but I didn't. I just think
having these programs that do have to work for me just messes me up when I want to tweak things.
So I'm like, you know what? Forget about it, though. I want to try C++, but it's programming.
Can I really do programming? And I was thinking about that OOP video, and I watched it again.
Why object-oriented programming is bad. I watched it again, and this time it really clicked with me.
Basically, what the guy is saying, and I'm sure he's making plenty of arguments that actual
programmers have already heard before, because Nate was telling me that he's already heard
all the arguments before. Because Nate's an actual professional programmer, by the way.
I don't know how many times he mentions that on TBC, but he's a professional programmer.
That's his main job right now, that he's trying to quit. But his job involves a lot of objects
and classes and stuff, and he tells me he's heard what the problems are. He knows what the problems
are. I've never heard of the problems. I've only ever heard good things. What this guy was saying
is that basically, let's say you have 10,000 lines of code. That's too many lines.
Let's split them up. If you split them up, like, okay, let's have 100 lines of code over here,
and 500 lines of code over here, and 200 lines of code over here, and 30 lines of code over here.
That way, you'll only have to keep track of so many lines at a time.
But what the guy was saying was that, basically, when you have all these different sections,
you still, you still ultimately have to know everything in the program, if you want to really
make stuff happen. But now, not only do you need to know all 10,000 lines of code, but you now
have to know dozens, or even hundreds, of all the tunnels that connect them. You just added
more complications. You have more stuff you have to keep track of, because you have to keep track
of how all the different sections communicate with one another. You have to keep track of all
the different tunnels that you've dug. So what he says is that it basically only makes things more
complicated, not less. And with classes as well, you know, you make an object like, say, box. And
box has its own programming. And then let's say you want to make a blue box. Well, you don't have
to make box all over again. You just make it blue box and give it the category of box to give it
the class of box. So the blue box immediately inherits everything that the box had. And now you
just add a little bit more onto it to make it the blue box, you just add a little bit more detail.
Then you could make blue box with a spike on top. And then you just give it that you just give it
the class of box and the class of blue box. And then you add a little bit more code to account
for the spike. That sounds like a great idea. But like, basically, it seems like there's a lot of
people out there who are like, yeah, but then what if you accidentally change something in box
or something? What if you want to change something in box just slightly, but then it makes the spike
go haywire or it makes the blue turn pink? You never know what's going to happen. It's like building a
house of cards, they say. And I'm like, oh my gosh, you're right. Fuck object oriented programming
in the ass. Now since then, you know, a week has passed since then and I've learned more and I'm
like, okay, I think there's like a middle ground here. But there's no question I really abused
objects and classes when I made my RPG. And with that in mind, I looked back into the memory banks
of when I was making that game. Because like, if you were to play that game, you would probably
be astonished that it took me a year and a half to make that took me 18 months to make that because
it's you can beat it in four hours, it has almost no mechanics really. It's a very simple, like linear
level up system to looking back, I spent at least 50%. But honestly, maybe up to 80% of my time that
I spent on the game was spent trying to get the code to work. And usually that was because majority
of the time I spent trying to get the code to work, not writing the code and structuring the code,
but just going back and forth, figuring out what I'm doing wrong, you know, debugging things,
figuring out what the glitches are. Most of that involves most of the thing that was slowing me
down. Most of the thing that was eating up my time was trying to figure out how all the different
objects were communicating with one another. That's what was really tricking me out and slipping
me up. Unless I'm remembering it wrong, but it was a pretty big part of my life. So I think I
remember it correctly. So I'm like, I'm going to try and program now and not and like do as little
objects as possible, as little classes as possible. I'll only do it when I find it to be absolutely
necessary. And with that in mind, things were so much more clear for me. And I picked up C plus
plus and I, and like, I'm having a great time with C plus plus because for one thing, it seems
like I don't know if something about it just really just really clicks with me just really
click clicks with me as if it as if there's a C making a clicking noise and then some plus
signs making me click multiple times. But also because of Bucky Roberts of the new boston.com
and his god tier tutorials. I've known about Bucky Roberts of the new boston.com and his god tier
tutorials for like five years now. Because like five years ago, I was messing around with HTML
wanting to make a website. And I found out about his tutorials and I watched it and it was it was
great. I actually made another website on just this year for my dad's business. Basically that
was how I was able to quit my job was my dad was like, make a business for me and you can take the
winter off. So I was like, sorry, make a website for me and you can take the winter off because
the winter is very slow for window cleaning anyway. So I did that. And by the time winter was over,
I was making enough money on YouTube to leave. So yeah, I made a website, but I don't think I
would have been able to do it if it weren't for hit if it weren't for the fact I went back and
watched his tutorials again. And and yeah. And so when I wanted to get to C plus plus, I'm like,
yeah, I'll watch Bucky Roberts's tutorial on C plus plus. And he's just such a good everyone
every tutorialist should just study how he does it. Because he'll he'll always give you a metaphor.
He'll he'll always try to really truly analogize what's happening in the computer. He'll be like,
now you may be wondering why I'm putting an equal sign here. Well, the equal sign is telling
the computer to do blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, you know, if you didn't have the equal sign
here, the computer would be going, so wait, what do you want me to do with this? So like he'll
he'll always be he'll be walking you through every step. And he yeah, it's it's good. Another great
thing he does is he'll acknowledge misconceptions that you're likely to have. We're like, it's
kind of hard to phrase it unless I use an actual example from an actual thing that I can't think
of one at the moment. But like, he'll understand he understands what a normal person thinks like
as distinct from a program. And he's like, Okay, now that we've typed out this bit of code,
you're probably going to think because of logical sense that you would do this, right? Well, let's
try it out. And as you saw, the code actually did something different than that. So you're probably
thinking, So what the heck? Why did it not do the thing I thought it would do? Why did it do this
weird thing? Don't worry, let me explain. And then he'll explain like he'll really walk you through
it and give you a true understanding of what you're doing. The other thing that I love is that you
get immediate results with with any good tutorial. Like I just can't do a manual man. I just I just
can't learn anything unless I do it myself and internalize it. That's the only way I can learn.
I'm sure that means I'm sure that equals I have a learning disability but oh well.
You work with what you got, man. Because like with with C plus plus, it's like you just you open
up a new you go and download a compiler software, you open up you make a new file and it has the
default like text in there already has the default code. And you just you just type in
something like hello, blueby, you hit F nine. And then you see a command prompt show up and hello,
blueby showed up, you have this immediate feedback with what you did. And you can change things you
can learn one step at a time and learn how to change what results you're really building on it.
You know, it's like finding out the one plus one is two, and then going on from there until you
eventually get to algebra. And then more, I guess. Whereas, you know, if you read just a manual that
just goes through everything like as like an encyclopedia, it's like it's like if you don't
know anything about math and you're reading about all of math before you actually do any of it yourself.
So yeah. That's what's great about Bucky Roberts' tutorials. And so I got halfway through his C plus
plus tutorial. And then he started talking about memory and assembly. And I'm like, okay, this is
getting pretty high level. I'm going to take a break for now. I'm going to I'm going to wander
around with other types of computer stuff. I was figuring I should learn C plus plus from
other people to to get other perspectives and learn other things. And I basically like,
basically, there were people with videos saying, you should try to learn assembly, you should try
to learn binary, and how assembly code works, because that will give you a better understanding
of how C plus plus works. So here's if so let me explain what assembly is to those who don't know.
Um, imagine you're watching YouTube, if you use your mouse and you click the middle of the screen
to hit pause, that means basically, you know, your mouse has told YouTube to pause the video.
But it's more like this, YouTube, like YouTube's, the website of YouTube, which is, you know,
like the video player is probably JavaScript, I assume. So the JavaScript code that represents
the YouTube player has been told to stop the video. So then JavaScript goes over to what I
assume is C code. No, no, I don't know what I don't know what code JavaScript is based off. Is it
based off C code? I actually don't know. Based off something like that. And it tells that code, hey,
let's pause the video. And then the C code or whichever one actual programmers, please correct
me on everything in this video, I want to learn and I want to not be wrong. Okay, then the C code
looks down and goes, Hey, assembly, we want to pause the video. And assembly code goes, okay. And
then the assembly code goes to the actual friggin computer and tells the actual like wires and
gates and hardware of the computer to do a different thing to pause the video. So assembly code is
directly controlling the computer. Even if you have a programming language, the program like C++
or JavaScript, or Python, I guess, those languages are only telling other languages to tell assembly
what to do. So learning assembly is can be very useful, because then you'll know exactly what's
happening with your computer. Well, you won't automatically know, but you'll know how you'll
know how to figure it out. You'll be able to look into the individual numbers and the individual
memory registers of the computer. It's sort of like indirect, it's sort of like putting up a
microscope to your actual to those actual wires going on down there. It's like putting up a
microscope to the actual memory banks. So I thought I want to get into assembly. I know it's way more
complicated. But as long as I can find a tutorial like the new Boston, I know I'll be able to do
it just fine. But there just aren't any. And I'm like, well, dang, I learned a decent bit about
assembly, I learned more about how binary works, and that's super cute. But just no tutorial guide,
which is here, let's incrementally add stuff on to a compiler. I mean, there are some tutorials
like that, but they're like weird and have terrible audio and like want you to download a stupid
program. I don't want to download. So and it wasn't working out like there is a guy who has a series
on assembly, where he goes through it step by step. But he does it badly. He explains what's
happening badly. The first 14 episodes are just him reading from the book and not actually giving
you a tutorial. So my standards are just way too high because of Bucky Roberts, man.
So that's what I've been doing, you know, trying to get into the arts, trying to get into other
mediums, because you know, I feel like a couple of weeks ago was when I finally got over this sort
of obsession with analysis that I've had for a couple of years. At this point, there's no analysis
that can come out that's like fundamentally more amazing than anything I've seen before. Like,
I'm impressed by it a lot still. But I'm like, you know, I kind of know all this stuff now.
So yeah, not really. I'm finally at a point where something being analysis doesn't make me
more interested in it. You know, I'm basically just as interested in just a normal review,
if the review is entertainingly delivered, and makes good points, even if it is still a review.
And I'm just more interested in any other kind of ways to make a video entertaining.
So I feel like I basically got as good at YouTubing as I really need to be. Like, obviously,
I could still be a lot better at writing, and I could still be a lot better at narration.
So, you know, I might still be putting a lot of effort into those at some point.
But with editing, I don't really need to make that many more improvements.
Like, I could, I'd like to eventually. But really, my goal was that for all year,
my goal has just been to get faster. Because there's really no need to make something that's
specced out with lots and lots of new effects, like Nerdwriter always does. You know, he's always
trying to find new tricks and traps to use. I mean, basic editing is really fine.
You know, making the editing really special all the time doesn't really add that much.
But you know, if the videos I'm working on ever get boring as a result, then maybe I'll
reconsider it. But for now, like, the level of editing skill that I have at the moment is fine.
And then I just wanted to get really fast at it. And as of now, I'm pretty much as fast at it as I
need to be. So don't even need to worry about that. So I guess I had gotten kind of bored,
but I didn't even realize it. Like, I'm really content with how videos are going. And when I
got into programming, it was like super exciting. I'm like, this was the most excited I've been
since getting into analysis. But when I got into analysis, I was still out of clean windows
almost all day. But this time I get to spend all day every day working on it. And I also got
myself a tablet, a drawing tablet, just a simple Wacom bamboo, no screen, nothing fancy like what
Digi has. But Digi getting a tablet and talking about how much he wants to do art, motivated me
to do more art because I'm like, my I have one goal with art, which is to never be less good
than Digi. My goal is to always be better at art than Digi is. Because otherwise, that would be
embarrassing. So I might have to like just do a whole comic series, just so I can get experience
in drawing and stay ahead of the curve, depending on how good he is. So yeah, getting into all these
mediums and entertainments, other mediums. I was thinking I was just going to focus more and more
on making videos and watching anime so that I can buff up my anime expert knowledge when making
anime videos. And I'm going to do that. I'm going to be making lots of videos. I'm going to be spending
lots of time watching anime for sure. But not as much as I thought I was going to. I thought I was
going to be making lots more videos and making lots more money. But really, the way that this job
is right now is basically perfect. Because the amount of money I make from the job as of the last
couple months is high enough that I only need to make like three to four, sometimes five videos a
month. And that's how much Digi seems to want to be making as well. And it's like that gives me so
much more time to do anything else I want with all that free time. On some level, I guess I'm
supposed to feel like I'm cheating people out of their money because they patron Digi and
indirectly me. I should be spending all that time and time to make more and more videos, right?
But technically, if I'm making an average amount of videos, three to five, the fact that I get
them done so quickly is just because I've worked really hard at getting fast. So I have earned my
ability to spend 10 straight days doing whatever I want for the last week or so of December,
which is what I've been doing. So I guess my goal is to get the YouTube work done as fast as
possible most of the time. Make sure it's good. Enjoy it. I do love making videos. Don't get me
wrong. I just don't have any I just am not there's just not a whole lot more new stuff for me to do
in a way. So really just focus on getting it done as efficiently as possible while still being high
quality and then be super speedy on cramming and all these other things I want to do in the meantime.
Again, I thought I was gonna be spending all the free time just getting better and better at videos.
I was just squarely focused on videos for like two straight years. But now I think I've I think
I think I'm basically leveled up as far as I need to be for the most part on videos and I can focus
on other things. This is a really big deal for me. Okay. I have been like, I've just obsessively
think about videos, how I'm going to do them, how am I going to get better constantly for like two
and a half years now. It's completely consumed in my thought, except for you know, sometimes I'll
be in a video game hole, but then feeling bad for it because I'm still obsessed with videos. I've
just been so completely consumed by writing and the narration and editing and all those things
all this time. And now as of just a week ago, you know, I walk back in to watch Nadesco episode
two but decide to not and I've gone on this completely different curveball direction.
So I just feel so excited. I feel so phoenixed from the ashes right now. The ashes of having a
great time. I didn't burn up. I'm just doing even more good. And then just today, I took another
random curveball down the path of memes. I've been getting really into the Shrek butt or
B movie butt meme. What a great concept. You know, I think what makes that meme work
is it feels like something that a computer algorithm created. Like throughout the internet,
there's just certain things that like algorithms do that are funny. Like I don't know if you guys
know, but there are certain YouTube channels that YouTube generates itself algorithmically,
where it'll take a topic that's popular and then like make a channel out of it like a tag like
anime topic or you know, Lord of the Rings topic is a channel that just compiles popular videos
that have that tag. That way people can subscribe to that and lots of people do subscribe to those
channels as a way to get like a feed of good content from that category. But it's funny because
it's it's done automatically like when YouTube decides that there's a certain topic that's
popular, it'll make one. Not like through any human, it's just through a computer. And what's
funniest is that the about tab, the about page of these channels is always the first paragraph of
the Wikipedia article, copy pasted in, and it always cuts off randomly at some point,
followed by this channel was automatically generated by YouTube. That kind of stuff is
really funny. And I feel like these, these like, you know, Shrek, but every time Shrek shows up
the video, it speeds up by 10% videos. It feels, it feels like it's a parody of that kind of thinking.
Because there's no humor to the way that it's delivered. You know, it's not like, here's a
funny video guys. You know, there's no like text on screen being like, I hope you like it. It's just,
it's just exactly what it says it is. You know, like Shrek, but every time Shrek shows up,
B movie plays instead, you know, it's as if some algorithm out there decided that this needed to
exist for some reason. Hippo made an amazing one. A feat like just yesterday, which is a Shrek,
but every time Shrek's face appears, the video ends, which made me giggle so hard. That was like,
okay, I need to make one now. So today, I was looking around for something to meme. And I
decided, and I had an idea, and so I posted it. So you can go to my channel, Devugos to Saturn,
to check it out. It's a, the Ghost in the Shell standalone complex opening, but every time Motoko
appears, the Sherlock Holmes in the 22nd century opening plays, which I'm quite proud of, quite
satisfied with. Then they got lunch, and then I was like, I got to make another one, got to make
a more challenging one. And I came up with Big Hero 6, but ever, but with all the nouns
replaced with things you can do at Sakurakan. But then when someone dies, the video skips
ahead to the end, because I gave up on making it. I spent three hours making like the first 20
minutes of it. And then I'm like, okay, I don't have time for another hour and 50 minutes. I'm
I'm just going to come up with an excuse for it to end. So it would have been amazing if I'd
actually put in all the work, but not quite worth my time. And that made me, uh, yeah, doing that
made me kind of burned out. You know, I finally made me like, huh, that was like really exhausting
to do. Like it wasn't hard. It wasn't complicated. It was just tedious, which was interesting,
getting something so tedious to do after like six straight days of this programming stuff,
which has been all fun, because I'm not actually making any programs, which can be tedious when
you're like debugging it and like figuring out problems, but just learning it, which is super
fun. I totally forgot how fun it is to learn a brand new thing. Yeah. Oh, yeah, suddenly did
something tedious and I felt like having a decompression or a rather to compress myself even
harder to go crazy, which is why I called this this video what it is. I don't relax by relaxing.
I relaxed by going crazier, I guess. I relaxed by like doing something intense.
Like, you know, my goal was to talk softly and slowly during all of this, but I feel like I've
been way too fast and loud for that. Not very good at relaxing ever.
I guess I probably just sleep extra long to compensate for it.
Where am I going with this? I guess I'm basically done with my point.
Yeah, that was my idea was to, uh, was to record this because of that,
so to book in this weird turn in the memes I did today and to tell people what's been going on
with me, you know, I haven't mentioned any of this in on my Twitter or anywhere else. I mean,
okay, I've been mentioning that I've been programming, but none of the whole background
narrative behind it. I actually, I actually re-recorded the last like hour of this, by the way.
You may have noticed that right around what I'm talking about PowerPoint,
uh, the audio made change in sound. That's because the last latter 40 minutes of my original
recording, like just shat itself and died. And I'm like, well, that's weird. But now I don't mind
because, uh, like I delivered this all way better and more extensively this time. So it's definitely
better as a result. But I guess it was even less like a decompression or a recompression because
this was now me putting in a lot of effort to make all the points again. But more succinctly this
time, I did a much better job explaining myself this time. Um, now I'm just going to hope that
this recording doesn't die on me again. Uh, yeah. Okay. So get relaxed and compressed by the freaking
music, man. So long.
Yeah.
Hey.
You