Hello, everybody, and welcome to yet another Pro Crastinators Podcast interview.
It's me, Digibro, once again interviewing a fellow member of the PCP. Today we have The Davoo.
Hi.
Or The Davoo Collective, as the meme has become. Thanks to Jesse.
Yeah.
How do you feel about that meme? I've never gotten an impression of whether you are indifferent towards it or what.
I'm on don't acknowledge policy because that makes it funnier. That's how you do it.
If I did anything that gets in on the joke, then that doesn't work, right?
Yeah, I guess that makes sense.
Alright, so Davoo, in the last interview I did with Jesse, I talked about how the PCP sort of formed
out of what was originally the horseshoe crew with me, Jesse, the T-Bap, and Hippo, all becoming friends
because we all admired one another's work. I didn't mention in there that the reason Tom came in,
which was sometime later, was because me and him had been longtime friends, he came down.
And by longtime you mean like about one year prior.
Yeah, before Jesse though. I met Tom first. He was my first Brony friend back then.
Now it's longtime. It's been well over three years.
Tom came to BronyCon the second time with Nate and Ben, or maybe it was the first time they came.
They brought him with them. They drove down with Tom. He talked to them the whole ride down, became pals with them.
After BronyCon we threw him in the chat, so that's sort of how he got there.
But you were up until very recently with the addition of Jeff. You were the most recent addition.
So I want you to tell me about your experience with us from the outside, because you're the ascended fanboy, essentially.
You're the guy who was just a fan of everybody else and eventually became a part of the group.
Well you know, I kind of think that Hippo was also an ascended fanboy, although he ascended very very quickly.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Obviously he has more talent than I do and he was doing the right things in the right time.
He's better at manipulating people, I think.
He puts it that way himself, that he started making videos that he was trying to get the attention of the people he was a fan of.
And when he said that in podcasts, I'm like, oh, I need to do that.
But the funny thing is that we had all, or at least I had heard of him long beforehand because of the fact that the reason his give and take channel has so many subscribers is that he did these compilation videos where he would take every single time that a certain word was said in MLP and make a video of that.
So like he would have the Twilight Twilight Twilight collection where it's just every time someone said the word Twilight in the entire show, he'd compile it all into one video.
And those would always get their own posts on Equestria Daily and stuff, so I had heard of him way before he started doing the analysis compilation videos.
But that was what got everyone's attention and, you know, like when he started doing the stuff that addressed us, that's when we were like, oh, this guy knows who we all are, that's cool, you know.
You, my first exposure to you was that you were a commenter and a big fan.
Yeah, man, duple do.
So how'd it happen when all went down?
Okay, so let's see here.
I found out about you first.
I mean, everyone in the TPC found out about you first when you think about it.
Yeah, probably.
I posted a My Little Pony video and I wanted to see how the views were going.
So I checked it on my phone when I was at work and your videos kept appearing as the suggested videos.
And I just had this moment of, you know, I want to get into new things.
I will look at this Digibroni with his analysis.
So I put some of those videos on and then I thought this is pretty, pretty cool guy.
He's like, analyzing and I like that and he's making a distinction from reviews.
I like that too.
And I thought, yeah, but just wait, you know, he's all intellectual sounding.
Like I'm just going to prepare for the moment.
I don't know if this is going to happen.
I just need to emotionally prepare for when he's going to make videos about how the
Broni community is homophobic and racist and how we all need to shape up or something.
I just been burned by that experience, won too many movie bobs in the past.
And so I had to prepare myself.
But then my perception of you started to clear up when you came out with this vlog with you and your brother.
It was just an audio log talking about why it's totally fucking okay to cutting square guy.
Damn it.
And I thought, wow, that was really cool.
Like you were like totally being in favor of swearing and it was, it was all, it was just nice.
I was like, this guy is pretty cool.
And then you came out with a video saying, all right, guys, I know how you say that Twilight Princess,
the Twilight Princess has become an unrelatable character now to the character of Twilight because
now she's a princess and now she's perfect.
But I think she's very relatable because I'm a princess and I'm perfect.
And I just had this incredible moment of ascension like Twilight did.
So she's totally relatable to me.
What are you guys talking about?
And I'm like, oh my God, this guy, I can't believe you can get away with being this egotistical on the internet.
I want to be like that.
So yeah, that's when I became like a fan of you.
And then through just sheer chance or something.
I don't know.
I happened to look at my YouTube feed of like, I don't know.
I somehow looked at the videos that you had recently liked at one point a few months into being a fan of you.
And one video that you had liked was a podcast you had done with Drowning and Footwear.
And so I just so happened to find out about Jesse before anyone else did.
I just so happened to see that you would.
Okay.
So I knew about Jesse before the horse shoe saga ever began.
What was the podcast I did with him before the horse cast?
You did three podcasts with him before he became a full time pony guy.
Okay.
What were they called?
Um, the first one was called Footwear and Digi Brony.
No foot.
I don't know whatever.
I remember the second one was called Footwear and Digi Brony ride again.
And that was the first one I listened to.
Okay.
I just thought because I knew there were three before, but I thought they were all called horse cast.
Like I just thought that that was the name before our podcast.
Now that name, that name showed up as the first.
Yeah.
After he made his horse shoe saga beginning.
And, uh, yeah, so I listened to that second one first.
Uh, that podcast made me a huge fan of you.
And then also at the same time introduced me to and made me a huge fan of Jesse.
Uh, within 30 seconds, he had me sold when you were talking about equestria girls.
And he said, Oh yeah, but you love that shallow, shill, shit fest.
And like the way he said it, which obviously I can't imitate at all.
It was like, Oh man, I love this guy.
He's like, uh, he's like that quirky drunken uncle character, you know?
Yeah.
He's such a cool.
Especially because that's what his, his avatar looked like at the time.
Yeah.
And these, these podcasts I'm talking about are deleted.
Uh, I mean, I have them on my computer, but I don't think Jesse would allow me transmitting them to anyone.
So, you know, we're going to have to like, we'll have to like forge it into his will or something.
So, yeah.
So like you just, the things you talked about in that podcast, I just had never, I take for granted now that whenever anyone in this group opens their mouth, something interesting is spoken.
I really take that for granted.
Like, you know, there was a time when I listened to this podcast three years ago where that was really astounding to me.
That podcast I listened to, I was like, every single thing that is being said is like changing my life forever.
The most interesting inspirational thing.
And, you know, I really have to step back and remember how, um, a hundred, like statistically a hundred percent of podcasts are meaningless and boring, right?
And like, there's just, none of them are good except for biggest problem.
And I guess the two offshoots that they have now, you know, that kind of stuff.
But yeah, I was just like, you talked about how doing YouTube videos just got you laid a week before recording the podcast.
I'm like, whoa, that's really cool.
You told Jesse, yeah, I lost my virginity 20 times.
And I was like, dang.
So I think that I was probably the first fan of the procrastinators of this affiliation.
I was probably the first huge fan of it.
Maybe. I mean, there may have been a couple of people, but yeah.
So that's what I would say.
And so I witnessed the whole, the whole rise and fall of the horseshoe saga.
I would say I would agree with the idea of you being the first, the first fan of it as a collective, I think.
Yeah, because I was like, oh man, these guys are great.
I hope they do more podcasts.
And you guys did not make this whole chat.
You guys didn't start talking all the time until a while after that.
So I had this burning desire in my heart for you to become friends and to do all that stuff.
And then that ended up happening.
And I was like, yeah.
Yeah, it was an exciting time.
So you found out about us before we even started this chat.
But you didn't come into it until much, much later, like a year and a half later.
So you were like a, like a long time fan, essentially, before joining in.
That's why I like to think of you as the Ascended Fan Boy, just because it was such a long, long period.
And what you just described with that first podcast is something that you don't do this nearly as much now,
but for a very long time, you were kind of infamous among all of us for your constant revelations,
where it seemed like every video you watched changed your life in some, like, definitively...
It was true.
Taboo had messaged me with these, like, emails that are, like...
It would be like, I'd put out a video and you'd send me, like, a seven paragraph email about how everything in the world was different now
and everything, you looked at everything completely differently.
I think that maybe only happened a couple of times, but okay.
It felt frequent. Like, it would be comments or emails and stuff like that.
Hmm. Well, it didn't feel frequent to me, but whatever.
You know, so this is like the narrative that I want to clear up about the TPC and, like, where it came from.
Because I feel like a lot of people, if their introduction to it is this channel and these podcasts,
they might kind of subconsciously think of Nate as, like, the headmaster of it, and I don't know.
He's obviously the one who talks the most, and maybe if that's your definition, then fine.
But I do think of, like, if you were to, like, write the band Wiki, the founding members were you and Jesse.
Right.
And, like, the fact that all of us found out about you, and even Jeff, like, all of us, like, whether it was in the pony community
or the anime community, they all found about you first, because you've always been the most popular one.
Right.
So, you know, like, that's...
So, at the time Jesse found me, he was more popular than me.
It was just that he happened to find me...
Oh, for, like, a couple of weeks.
Yeah.
Well, he happened to be...
Because I think he found me straight from the R My Little Pony subreddit, because he's, you know, a Reddit perruser.
Yeah.
Not so much comment or anything, but he...
Yeah, and actually, at that time, I even had more subs than Jesse did when I listened to that podcast,
because I had just done a couple of pony videos that had a lot of views that people subscribed for.
It's worth mentioning that you had...
You have a few...
This has continued even past the pony videos, but you're a person who...
Not unlike Jesse, has a few videos that way exceed your sub count and what is typical of your channel.
Yeah.
What are these videos, and why are they like this?
Um, we'll see.
Back when I got into My Little Pony, I was like, I gotta make some sort of content out of this, right?
Right.
I gotta make something, because that's what pony does to you at the time when it's new.
Yeah.
You have to make something, and I'm like, what can I make that's different?
I'm not enough of an art to do art, can't do music, I wouldn't do fan fiction.
And I was on the MLP board on 4chan, and someone was like, hey, what's your predictions for season three?
And I'm like, predictions.
Predictions could be a YouTube video.
I can do YouTube videos competently, so I'll do that.
And so I did a video of My Little Pony season three predictions, you know, pretty crappy video,
but I just kind of wanted to do it, just to do a pony thing.
And YouTube fucked me over by not giving me a thumbnail for it.
It was just a gray with like three gray circles inside.
So no one watched it at the time until custom thumbnails became a thing later.
And so eventually that one got like 50,000 views.
But yeah, that did become the most viewed video on my channel.
Are you still there?
Yeah.
Okay.
And then I made one for season four predictions, and it ended up getting like a total of 400,000 views.
Yeah.
Which was more views than any video you've ever made up until like last summer, I think.
Like that was, it had more views than any video that you had ever done.
And I would like to say more views than anyone in this chat had ever done,
other than that one Jesse video that has like three million views now.
Because if you want to talk about, if you want to talk about videos with an anomalous view count,
look any further than horseshoe review bats.
Yeah.
Which was the most, I have no idea what happened with that one, but anyway.
Fluttershy's ass.
That's all that happened.
But he put more asses on more thumbnails after that, and it didn't have the same Fluttershy effect.
Well, it was also bats.
It was something about that episode, dude.
I don't know what it was.
Something about bats, everyone's bats video got more fucking views.
I don't get it.
It's such a weird anomaly.
Maybe it was Batman that it got all these, like YouTube algorithms got fucked up or something.
The streams got crossed.
Yeah.
So then, so that was my My Little Pony season four predictions video.
That was how I was looking for views on it, and that's how I found about you.
So very worthwhile making that video just to find out about you.
Yeah.
And so then I made a season five predictions video, and by the time season four was ending,
I was like, okay, it's time for me to become YouTube.
So I thought, well, I might as well do a season five predictions and have actual production value or something this time.
And I'll use that to kickstart my channel, because everyone's going to watch that, and I'll promote myself afterward.
Everyone watched it, 200,000 views, tons of people subscribed as usual, and then none of them watched my videos.
Oh well, you know.
So yeah.
And then, as I was doing YouTube videos, talking about stuff, I'm like, well, time to talk about, time to do the thing that every YouTuber does and talk about something that's really important to you in your own personal history.
So I made Roller Crooks to Tycoon videos.
The first one is sitting at 40,000 views right now, and the second one has about 150,000 views, which is nice.
Yes.
And again, this is like-
A constant stream of terrible comments that eventually led you to finally close them.
And which then have led to some people going to my discussion tab and commenting there instead.
You know, but whatever.
And keep in mind, we're talking less than 1,000 views a video, then a video that ultimately got 150,000 views, and then a bunch of videos with less than 1,000 views after that.
Right.
And then I did an Undertale video, and that got 350,000 views, and was the eternal-
And it seems like it's going to forever haunt Nate, because, you know, his Undertale video is the huge, perfect one, got no views.
But it's the inverse for me, too, because his Undertale video got him $100 of patronage, and mine got me none!
300,000 views!
I promoted my Patreon at the end.
No one thought it was that good, apparently.
Yeah.
Because it wasn't written in a way that anyone could really get the point, I guess.
Your Undertale video has all the views, because it was both timely and had a great title.
Whereas Nate's-
Or a provocative title.
Nate's was-
Apparently.
That's what a great title is. It's a provocative title.
Nate's has a- came out six months late, and has a title that just makes people pissed off when they read it.
So, yeah, it wasn't the best competition there.
Yeah.
But, alright, so that's-
That's it. That's all the videos I've done that have gotten a substantial amount of views.
Actually, you know what? Let me see.
I think my- what is it called? Nuclear Throne video has gotten up to 20,000 views, I think.
Okay, that's not good.
Let me just check.
This is, like, weird. The sheer lack of middle ground that my videos have.
Let's see.
And I ended up hiding the Season 4 predictions and Season 3 predictions, along with most of my old videos.
I kept the Season 5 predictions one just because it, like, advertises my channel, so I feel like it's part of the narrative.
But let's see here.
366,287,000. I'm going in backwards order.
185,000. Then it shoots down to 49,000. Then it shoots down to 13,000, which is my Gravity Falls video.
And the Nuclear Throne one has less than 9,000. So, yeah, there's just, like, I have a grand total of- of two videos that are in the tens of thousands of views.
Only two videos are in that status.
Very messed up.
Very- very large.
But I deserved it. Didn't ever make content that was consistent and, like, made sense to people and was frequent, you know.
I don't care anymore, um, because I decided to put my channel into whatever I want to do whenever I happen to get around it with status,
because now I'm just an editor for you.
Yeah.
And, uh, it was a really hard decision to make, but once I made it, uh, it's not hard to live with that decision at all.
But I will say, it's probably- it was probably the only hard decision I've ever had to make in my life so far.
It was deciding whether or not to work on my channel or work on yours.
Every other decision I've ever made in my life was pretty straightforward.
It was- that was the only complicated one I've ever had to do.
But now that I've made it, I'm definitely glad that I did.
All right.
So continue the- oh, god.
To continue the narrative that I was sort of building towards there, um, about getting to know you, so to say.
Um, so you had these- these big pony videos. I never actually watched them, uh, the predicted ones.
Good.
Um, and-
I'm glad.
I think- I don't- like, when was the first time that one of us acknowledged you?
Like, because I remember that you appeared as a commentator.
I remember, like, responding to a comment.
Responding to a comment or, like, saying my name.
Uh...
You know, because that was, um, I actually recorded it.
Oh, my god.
It was on the, uh, so- well, I mean, I downloaded the, uh-
Oh, the pump call. That's right. That's how I started talking to you more.
Actually, no, no, I downloaded that episode when it came out and then I isolated the specific spot where it happens, you know.
Right.
Yeah, I was gonna keep this.
Yeah, so, um, how I- I guess how I was trying to, like-
I was trying to convince you that I was a huge fan of you, so I would-
Yeah.
In the pub crawl, I would be making weird references to things that only I would know because I'd listed all your old podcasts.
Yeah, see, that's-
I could've done better if- I could've done better if I'd actually, like, read all of your blog, but I haven't done that yet.
Well, nobody has, but, uh, unless they've been around since back then.
But, yeah, it was because-
Because I get a lot of comments, you know, and I have a lot of frequent commenters.
There's- like, anyone who comments enough of my videos, I will eventually recognize them.
And I get a lot of emails and stuff, but it's not usual for me to, like, you know, end up talking to those people in any capacity other than, uh, comments and- and emails.
So, like, I forgot that it was because of the pub crawl, because pub crawl, for those who don't know, in the audience of this podcast, which is probably not too many people, um,
the pub crawl is a show that I still do, go search DJ Cider's pub crawl on YouTube.
Um, that's been going since, like, I've been on it since early 2013.
Originally, it was a radio show for a My Little Pony radio, like, internet radio station called Celestial Radio.
Yes, guys, that was a thing. I think some of them are still around. 24 hours of Pony stuff.
Uh, I think.
Yeah.
But yeah, we had a show on there. It was run by DJ Cider, and, like, at our height, we had probably close to 100 listeners.
By the end, we had, like, less than 30.
But, um-
And you may be like, hey, why doesn't Digi ever promote the pub crawl? Why have I never heard of it? Why is that, actually?
Uh, well, before it was because it was on a My Little Pony radio station.
Right.
At the time, it was impossible to find out about, to figure out how to even listen to.
Yeah, and it air- I mean, it runs late night. It was always, like, 2 a.m. to 4 a.m., like, in Eastern Standard Time,
because Cider's an Australian, so for him, it was, like, the middle of the day.
Um, but yeah, like, even after- because after I stopped doing Pony, we kept doing the show, and it wasn't about ponies anymore.
It was just still on that radio station.
The slogan was Celestial Radio, All Pony All the Time.
But then, as season four of Pony was going on, and everyone was losing interest, it became mostly ponies some of the time.
Then it became No Ponies, None of the Time.
Right.
And it became Die Horse Fags, Get Outta Here, something like that.
You know, it just, like, the slogan deteriorated, and eventually they left, and then- and they left the network,
and then it just became a 45-minute YouTube podcast that you uploaded.
Now, here's the thing about, like, the pub crawl, right?
Because another thing I take for granted is the fact that you're- you always upload a lot of your- of talking of you on the internet all the time.
You got Digi Bros that's been going on for a year.
It's like, like, 20 minutes of you talking every day, and then the PCP, 2 hours of you talking every week,
and then you do other podcasts, you do interviews with me, um, or this one.
But the thing is, like, not too long ago, that wasn't the case.
Right.
All I had to go on were these- these podcasts you did with Jesse.
Like, the horse cast, which came out, like, every couple of months, just whenever you happened to feel like doing a podcast with Jesse.
This was before Nate organized it into a weekly thing.
And then you had this old podcast that you did mostly with your offline friends, mostly Brandon Tolentino,
and I listened to that, like, 50 times, because it was like- it was like a comfort blanket,
because I was all stressed out at work and making videos, and I just listened to that over and over again,
because it was the only thing in my life that was consistent.
Yeah.
Um, so I was, like, desperate.
I- I remember, I think, like, asking you on Tumblr or wherever, like, please do more podcasts.
Right.
So I was so desperate for your voice that-
You've answered your own question of why I don't promote the pub crawl, because, uh, cause, yeah, like you just said,
for a long time, that was the main way to get two hours of me, uh, you know, twice a week.
And then because of the fact that I started doing Digi Bros and started doing the procrastinator's podcast,
I started doing all this other stuff that, like, cause the pub crawl is probably the best now that it's been in a long time,
where it's now- it's almost always just me and Cider and, like, maybe one other person, cause most people have lost interest,
and it's only 45 minutes, and it's only once a week.
And so we've gotten to the point where now it's like, we get in, we really get everything we have to say out,
and then we get out, you know, and it's not as meandering and pointless as it used to be,
cause the thing about the pub crawl is that-
It was pretty bad.
Yeah.
It's- it was just a show where we'd get really drunk, um, talk about alcohol, and then whatever came to mind.
And so for-
I mean, like, if you just- if you imagine just a normal Skype chat that, like, people do regularly without recording it,
it was a lot closer to that on the spectrum than it was to a podcast on the spectrum.
I guess so.
And even in your- I mean, at its worst, I guess.
At its best, there would be plenty of great discussion, but, like, there'd be so much empty space,
and, like, I don't know, a lot of things Cider talks about aren't that interesting,
and then all the other people weren't that interesting, but whatever, and I don't know.
Um, so, but even in the pony times, you didn't promote it, like, very much at all.
You never, like, here's a link to the pub crawl, guys, so I had to figure out where to listen to it.
I had to, like, read the schedule of when it even came on.
I had to adjust for the time zones.
I had to, like, figure out how to listen to it at work if I needed to.
It wouldn't ever-
Well, I had advertised it in a few videos, um, but it just- it never seemed to help,
because it was so esoteric to find.
It's, like, you have to go to a radio station, which, even just going to Celestia Radio,
like, understanding how to listen to it is, like, a thing in itself,
because you go there and there's, like, a weird play button that's not that big off to the side,
and it's playing a whole fucking radio network.
It's just- it's a very antiquated way of doing things,
that unless you're familiar with the concept of internet radio, people have no idea what to do.
But it did make for a great atmosphere where you could say whatever you want with, like, almost no consequences,
like, no one- I mean, like, the only way for there to be any consequences is if there-
is if, like, a co-host on the show deliberately liked creating drama with people you talked shit about on the show.
Which was sometimes true.
So as long as- so as long as there wasn't anyone who- anyone on the show who would, for no good reason,
start a lot of drama for no good reason, then everything would be fine on the Celestia Radio pub crawl,
and you could say whatever you want with no consequences.
So I- I wanted to listen to it because I wanted to hear more of your voice,
even though it was shitty, but it was a nice way to relax as well, even though I didn't have any beer or whatever.
And obviously I- obviously I think it's a fun show, or else I wouldn't still be doing it, you know, after three and a half years,
or- we'll say three years.
But, um, yeah, like-
So on there, you were, um, I believe you were talking about how you had been doing-
You were- on that- on one time when I was listening early on,
you were talking about how you had done pen and paper roll RPG playing with your friends.
And I remember you talking about that in depth, in like your Q&As and stuff, and in like, like other places.
So I was able to remember that, and so then I was making really obscure references to those pen and paper RPs in the chat.
And you were reading a chat, and then you said on the show like,
Oh hey, I see DaVoo over here, like, knows all about Snoop Lion, and how he got his dick cut off or whatever.
Or no, that was someone else. I don't know, I can't remember all the characters now, but, uh, yeah, DaVoo, he's-
Oh yeah, so yeah, DaVoo, uh, he, you know, he's a stalker of me.
This is how I know I have stalkers, but, you know, but- and you said,
But that's the DaVoo for you.
And I just made that like its own separate sound bite.
That was really nice.
You know, what's interesting is that, in that moment, you solidified how to pronounce that name.
Because I had never really considered that before, because I never- the name was never uttered verbally, right?
I always thought of it as DaVoo, but that doesn't make any sense, you can't say that, that's really awkward.
So, you were the responsible one for this pronunciation.
Well, DaVoo makes sense for the origins of the name. Do you want to reveal that to our audience?
My name is David, and I don't like having usernames, but I have to have something distinct.
So I'm just like, uh, DaVoo, I don't know, I don't even know how the heck I came up with that.
Turns out it's a terrible name for, uh, for search engine optimization.
Because it seems like a lot of, like, I don't know, I think like a lot of Spanish people get that as a nickname or something.
So you got to search the DaVoo in order to get anywhere with my name, I think.
I did not know that.
I think so. I mean, I think now I'm big enough that you can just search DaVoo and you'll get me, but not for a while.
So David became DaVoo, but then I pronounced it DaVoo, and at one point,
Which is way better.
In one specific song, DaVoo, just because it sounded better with the song.
Oh yeah, the song, yeah.
Which is the song Three Hams, which you can find on my SoundCloud.
Indeed.
Yeah, the first song that mentions me, and, well, let's see, there's been two songs that mention me now.
The other one is Jesse talking about me talking about The Force Awakens.
But I don't know if that counts as a song.
I didn't remember that you were mentioned by David then.
Yeah, anyway, okay, so back on topic.
So basically, I just proved that I'm a big fan of you.
Yeah, because as you know, my ego is enormous, since that's part of how you got into watching me.
Oh man, yeah, what happened was another particular fan of you who has since disowned everyone,
and we've disowned this person, at the time was like, oh, I'm the biggest Digi Bro fan,
and I'm like, we'll do a trivia off.
And apparently that really blew up your ego, but whatever.
Yeah, I love it when people know too much about me.
Because to me, that's the ultimate evidence that they're really into it.
It's like that they know all these obscure things.
Because that's the kind of stuff that I know about the people I'm a fan of.
You know, like, I'm the type of guy who when I become a fan of somebody,
I watch all their stuff and I learn everything.
Just now, I just got into Monkey Jones, the YouTuber, and I've already watched all his stuff.
Everything he's made other than his Elliot Roger autobiography reading,
which I might listen to anyways, just because I'm fucking curious about it.
But I'm sure I could mention things that he's forgotten he's said before in a video.
So, although he hasn't been around that long, so I don't think he's forgotten anything that quick.
But yeah, when other people can do that for me, then it's always something special.
It's like, oh, wow, you know that, you know, and you're still around?
You heard those shitty things I did and you're still here?
Yeah, I see, yeah.
Yeah, I think that's how I came to acknowledge you.
And that was a big deal because now explain to me, because I don't know how it's possible.
I don't remember this because I typically have a great memory for most things,
but I legit don't remember how you became my editor.
What did you do?
You posted on Twitter, you made a tweet saying,
I have eight videos in the works right now.
Seven of them could be released right now, this very moment, if it weren't for the editing process.
And I was very familiar with how much you didn't like editing at this point.
Like you had made that very clear in podcasts, you hate editing and you said,
I can't wait to one day just ship it off to someone.
I believe even at this time that was already a Patreon tier, a creator goal.
If I get to like $500 or whatever, I can have someone to edit this shit.
So at this time when you made that tweet, I had already been making my own videos for a couple of months,
so I knew how to make videos at this point.
I didn't know if you'd seen any of them because they weren't that good, whatever.
I know you've seen a lot of them since then, at least.
But they at least proved I could make videos competently.
And so I said, I'll make one, I'll make one, I'll make one.
I make videos, I know how to edit with like exclamation marks.
And then as I was at work on the way home, on the commute home,
I got an email from you saying, okay, here's one.
And you gave me some instructions on how to do it.
And I was like, oh my gosh.
Dang, sweet, yeah, okay then.
It never would have happened if not for the fact that you had proven that you knew my stuff so well because...
The fact that I knew to install blue highway fonts immediately.
Right, yeah, stuff like that because...
Do you guys even know that everything that Digibro does has blue highway font?
It's always the same font.
It's either blue highway, blue highway bold, or blue highway condensed, or blue highway linocut.
I don't know if you've ever used condensed, but...
I don't know if I've ever used bold, maybe just, I don't know.
I almost exclusively used bold.
It looks way better than regular, but I've never used linocut actually because it looks dumb, but...
Yeah, well I only used it for a few videos.
So you gave me some basic instructions, don't have any black backgrounds, do lots of fades, do lots of stuff.
And so I did, I spent like a day and a half doing nothing but making that video and got it out to you.
Which one was the first one?
Why Nostalgia is good and does not blind.
So that was the first one.
Yeah.
So yeah, that...
Yes, indeed.
Because I was trying to think what era I would have had eight videos stocked up and it was indeed because I broke my foot.
Oh, yeah.
Because it was August 2014 and I broke my foot at Otacon and then...
Singing database.
Yeah.
And then I had moved a bunch of my stuff downstairs and just because I didn't feel like being at the computer all the time,
I had started writing out videos, like writing scripts in a notebook.
And so I wrote a bunch of scripts out in a notebook and then I just didn't want to edit them.
Some of these are just too much of a pain in the ass.
There's a few of those that never got made just because they never made it out of the notebook.
I wrote a review of...
Because I wrote two videos that were supposed to be in Jesse and Hippo's style.
One was...
Oh yeah, I'm re-talking about those little podcast ones.
Yeah, Jesse's...
The video I wrote that's in the style of Jesse, I've sent to you before, it was a weird anime sex.
And it's just like, why liking weird anime porn is okay, essentially.
Which is actually not that original of a sentiment.
I think most people are either...
Anyone who still thinks it's not okay is never going to be convinced.
So what's the point of making this video?
Well, I think you're absolutely wrong about that.
I think most people haven't heard that message yet.
Particularly in an audience as big as mine.
I don't think most people have heard that message yet.
And I think there's a lot of people who would be convinced just because it's me saying it.
I mean, for me, I guess my very tainted perspective, I've been eminently familiar with weird anime sex much longer than anime.
So my perspective is pretty off-kilter.
I think a pretty sizable portion of my fan base is 16-year-old casual anime fans who still think Lolli's kind of weird and don't understand how someone like me can be into it.
So if I made a video like that, I think it could convince a lot of those people.
And also, a lot of the point of it was just to be a stylistic parody of Jesse.
It's written in his very fun linguistic style where there's lots of alliteration and little fun sentences and stuff.
He loved it when I sent it to him, but I never got it made.
And the reason I never got it made was because I wanted to stand in front of a camera and deliver it the way Jesse does, but I had a broken foot.
And so the prospect of standing was just too much and I never made it.
I remember you did send that one to me saying, hey, I might have you edit this one later.
I didn't have you do it just because you expressed such disinterest in it.
And I was like, I will fuck you.
Like what you just said to me is exactly what you said at the time.
You were like, this isn't that original sentiment and I don't give a fuck.
So I said, well, I'm throwing it away.
This is before I was like, because I made the first video that first editing because I had to.
I had the opportunity to.
Then you said, hey, so you want to do more?
And I was super tired and I was like, I got to focus on my own videos, so I'm going to have to not do it.
Then the next day I was like, no, don't listen to me.
I want to do more.
And the other video that never got transferred to the notebook was a review of Reciteer,
which I only played a couple hours of, but I wrote a hippo style analysis of it.
But then I just I literally never copied it to the computer because it was too much of a hassle.
So I didn't do it.
But then yeah, I gave you the nostalgia one was one of the ones I wrote in that notebook.
So I gave that to you.
And I remember just being like, like the idea I had was just you seemed to know my video so well that no one else could possibly be better for the job.
Like, because that's all I what I wanted out of an editor was not someone who could do super advanced stuff.
I wanted someone who would do what I was already doing, you know, someone who could emulate my style and do it just as well as I could and not put in anything that would seem unnatural to me.
You know, like nothing that would that would that would feel like this no longer is my voice.
Right.
And I've always put a lot of I've always put a lot of focus into that intuitively just knowing that that's how I should do it.
Genius that editing your videos.
I was always like, well, obviously I'm not going to put anything in here that doesn't represent your opinion, you know.
And so like really the only time that was in the Astroscore sucks part 10, I believe, where I broke where the writing voice.
No, wait, no, no, no, no, no, what am I trying to say here?
There's only one time where the right where like the voice of the video responded to you.
And that was in 10 best things happening in anime this decade where it says you forgot this one.
Roll eyes.
Yeah.
Because I didn't know how else to do it.
I didn't know how else to convey that that message that you forgot one of the moment of God trees.
Yeah, I think you might have done it another time before that, but usually with my direction, like I'll say, oh, I fucked this line up.
So put something in there to notify the audience that I fucked this line up.
Yeah, but I never did it in a way that like broke away from the writing voice, you know, like that.
In other words, making it you talking to me.
Yeah.
But yeah, that's like I was always afraid because I knew other people who had editors in the pony community, especially.
And there were people who had offered to do it for me.
But like when I see someone who sends me like a like their sample video, they're like, hey, here's a flashy video I edited.
And I'm like, yeah, but I would never make something like this, you know, like if someone's got like typo, like I think there was one guy who sent me a video example.
And it had the like typography thing where it's like the words appearing on screen as the person says them like, oh my like Holden reviews does.
And I don't like that style at all.
I think it's just don't get the point of it like remotely.
So I saw that and I was like the last thing I want is one of my videos to have like a fucking typography thing going on at it, you know.
Right.
So yeah, I took you on.
And the thing is, like at the time, my perspective on you was that you were this commenter who would leave these incredibly verbose comments had a sort of strong political opinions.
It seemed to be at least at the time, which you would clarify now that they're not that strong, right?
Right.
Yeah.
You have political opinions and you get frustrated when other people don't understand your perspective, but it's not that you feel super strongly about them.
Yeah, I guess I would say so.
Yeah, I don't know.
I just, um, I don't know.
Okay.
So, and then I think you had around this time, you had gotten Jesse on Skype somehow.
Yeah, so what happened was right after, like right after listening to that one podcast and made me a fan of him, I watched or listened to a bunch of his videos.
I was a big fan of him and I'm like, well, hey, I currently, thanks to ponies, have more subs than this guy slightly.
So that makes it okay to talk to him.
And I was like, hey, man, like, you ever want to like do videos together?
Like I can like edit videos for you or whatever, blah, blah, blah, you know.
I have gotten close or almost close to editing Jesse videos for like three years now.
Yeah.
It's just that he's too, um, auteur to like ship it off to someone wirelessly.
So at some point, if we're ever doing analysis HQ, then that'll probably be the final, finally the time where I can like do videos for him too.
So that he can chug through that massive backlog of videos he has because he can direct me or like, you know, like punch me in person.
There have been no shortage of times where he's been like, I'm finally going to get DeVoo to do this one.
Like, I can't take it.
There's been like a lot of times where it's like, I can't fucking take it anymore.
I hate this.
I don't want to.
He's never said he's never said that for as long as I've been in the chat.
I think he did once.
I think there was one time he was like, DeVoo edit this for me.
And then you kind of just were like, oh yeah, I did.
Like he obviously was going to take it back though.
But like, yeah, there was a time where like I would I had like almost like slated it onto my calendar for me to edit for him.
And then he like pulled back on it.
Yeah.
Um, so what the heck were we talking about of like, yeah, well, the thing is, I had Jesse on Skype.
And you know, I guess I said, I was just barely able to not be too annoying to him on Skype to the point that like he didn't remove me.
So I was like, oh good.
I figured out how to, um, I was able to pretty decently understand Jesse's Skype voice at least.
Like I was able to figure out how to not annoy him, I think, before a lot of other people were because I was able to practice on Skype there.
So yeah.
Well, he kind of apparently he apparently he said to you that, oh, DeVue talks a whole lot and you know, long-winded stuff.
And then you said, and you thought to yourself, well, I better not add DeVue on Skype because then I'll end up talking to him a bunch or whatever.
And that's for the best because then I would have wasted a bunch of time myself back when I really needed to make videos much more quickly.
So yeah.
It was at a time where I was trying to like really scale back internet communication like all together.
Because, you know, after post-pony, like I stopped talking to a lot of people because like back in the pony days, I had like a huge circle of people I talked to in that community.
And you had post-pony stress disorder.
Yeah.
And so I kind of had put a large distance between myself and most of the internet and we had started the horseshoe crew.
So I really had those like ever since this thing started, ever since the procrastinators chat started, like I think for all of us, we largely stopped talking to most other people online.
Like it became, it became like, well, there's no reason to talk to anybody else about this stuff because we have this group.
So, you know, unless it's something that I, there's only one person I could talk to about something that's not a member of this group, there's no reason to leave it.
So like, you know, it got to a point where anybody who wasn't in the procrastinators, it was like, I don't really want to talk to them because I have to repeat myself to multiple people, you know, like something I've already talked about with my friends.
I now have to describe to the next guy, you know, or get into the same conversation with five different people and stuff like that.
And yeah, I kind of had, like Jesse had told me that he was like, oh, Davoo will, you know, he'll really talk your ear off kind of thing.
It was just like one comment he said to that effect.
But I was like, yeah, I don't know like how long me and you are going to be friends, how long we're going to be working together because I've had a lot of people who like tried to work with me and then just kind of flaked off over the years.
You know, like I had a lot of co bloggers back in my blogging days who would get really excited and want to work on my stuff with me.
And they were always big fans.
They're always people who love my content and want to be like me.
And then they, you know, would be around for a little while and then they disappear, you know, like a lot of them literally disappear.
Like this is one dude.
I don't remember what username he was using at the time.
He changed it a few times.
But like he got into gets into blogging and is like, dude, your content is the greatest thing ever.
I'm so passionate.
I want to become the biggest otaku in the world.
I want to be just like you.
Right.
So I'm like, all right, cool.
Right for my blog, you know, he writes a couple posts and then just literally disappears off the face of the earth.
Like I didn't hear from him again for like a year.
Then he started his own blog, made two posts and disappeared again.
So like that's the kind of experiences I've had.
And so I'm like, I don't want to talk to this guy who's going to have super long conversations with me, which is inevitably what happened anyway.
It's what's now we do talk.
And of course, it's exactly what I was afraid of.
But we're friends now, so it's okay.
But we do talk exactly as much as I was always afraid we would talk.
But so for the longest time, we were communicating solely through email.
All of our video work was only done through email.
Discussed through email.
Yes.
And again, you know, I do agree with that whole policy of not talking to me at the time because if I'd spend that much time talking,
well, it had no time to make videos.
I mean, think about it, making videos all the time, being at work all the time and talking to people in a chat.
That's the situation dates in and it takes him forever to get videos out.
So yeah, you know, clearly I'm glad I wasn't subjected to that.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was it was interesting too, because I liked the emailing stuff just because it felt it felt so much more professional than anything else I'd done before.
Because like, you know, I'm used to that, like casual, we're all in a chat, we're all like hanging out and stuff.
And I thought it was cool that, like, you know, my editor was someone who because it seemed like you were really trying your hardest to present yourself as professionally as possible.
And so, I guess, like, you know, we would only communicate through email and we'd have like,
they'd be very detailed and it'd be like, you know, oh, is this exactly what we want to do? Yeah, okay.
Well, I mean, I just didn't want to annoy you. I didn't want to talk unnecessarily.
Well, that's what professionalism is, not being annoying.
And then of course, you had like already dozens of podcasts talking about how you don't like it when people talk to you unnecessarily.
So I just sort of got the idea, you know.
But so then at some point it got to where you were editing, like, because at first I was only giving you scripts that like the first few I gave you were like things that I didn't really care that much about.
So it was like, even if he fucks it up, I can just throw it away remorselessly.
That's good planning. And I definitely did not get that sent at the time and all those videos are pretty good.
So like the nostalgia one, I wrote it and then I kind of like reread it and wasn't sure I got the point anymore.
So I sent it to you. I was like, well, if it's any good, he'll find the good in it and make it worthwhile.
And I thought it was good. So I posted it and then, you know, sent a few more your way and then finally gave you the big sword on online series.
And that was when it was like, okay, this guy's now my guy, you know.
And then particularly with Psycho Pass. That was the first one where it was just like you had complete reign over it.
I didn't do anything. I just sent you scripts and you you did this like huge epic series.
And then of course, that was also the end for the time because I was like, okay, I'm never getting I'm not getting out any of my own videos.
I'm never going to I'm never going to get the I'm never going to get the algorithms if I'm making videos in between making yours.
It just takes too long. It took me months to make the Psycho Pass videos because I was still slow.
So I was using slower software. I didn't know how to optimize the editing process.
Tell us about your software. You used. Oh, yeah.
I went to get the software. I was just like, well, did you says to use Sony Vegas, but I don't really trust Digi when it comes to which software to use.
So I just like so back when I first got my software, I just Googled best editing software and I the top result on there's like this chart saying like which are overall the best softwares.
And the number one was on power director. And so I got that and it's fine.
But it's obviously for like plebs who aren't doing videos professionally, I think, and it's like really slow, at least on my computer, like everything just takes way too long to move the clips.
There's just too much delay. So editing was really tedious.
And at the time, I didn't know how to optimize files using handbrake. So it was even slower.
So yeah, it was just kind of long and slow and hard. And I was also trying to make my own videos at the time, like you had started working on the psychopaths videos.
And I'm like, great, I'm going to quickly finish up this roller coaster tycoon one versus three video, which turned out to be the hardest video I've ever made.
So, you know, like, you I think you had finished like both the script and the audio, all your work was done.
And I was still making this roller coaster three video and I'm like, oh, this is going to take like weeks more to finish.
I'm going to put this on hold. So then I had to watch psychopaths. And at the time I was really bad at watching shows.
I just could not focus, could not sit still and pay attention. I just was not trained for that.
I was trained for being a blue collar worker, someone who like just watches something for like 20 minutes when you get home, you know, so I just couldn't get into it.
I had to watch all the psychopaths psychopaths too. Then I wanted to because I wasn't as you know, wasn't a very good editor at the time.
I had to watch all of it again and make extensive notes of everything that was in it so that I wouldn't know exactly what to put in every spot.
Don't do that anymore. I could just do it from memory. But at the time that was the only way I was able to like guide myself through because prior to this, I made a Gravity Falls video for myself.
And it was torture trying to figure out like which clips of which episode to put where I'm like, oh, torture, torture.
I'm going to make a guide for myself. But that ended up basically it was like a month and a half before the first psychopaths video came out after you were done with it.
And then like after that, I'm like, oh man, I need to like play video games because what happens is I'll spend like a week making one of your videos.
And then I have to come up with a new video idea for my own channel and it's suddenly been two weeks since I've played any video games.
So then I had to start from square one when it comes to the conceptual phase.
So I'm like, I need to play video games while working on videos that did not work at all.
When you have a full time job, you cannot do anything else on the side.
So like there just be like weeks where I didn't get any progress done and I'm like, so when I was done with the psychopaths videos,
a very long drawn out tedious process, but very satisfying.
And then no one watched them, but whatever I got paid.
I'm like, okay, time to finish the roller coaster video.
Sorry, Digi, but I got to make my own videos, you know, because you're at the time you weren't making enough money to pay me enough to live off of it full time, not by a long shot.
You only got paid like $60 apiece for the psychopaths videos, I think.
Yeah, yeah, that is true.
I mean, the first couple of videos, the nostalgia one, I think you paid me like $50.
But then after that, you were like, hey, I can't make you do any more of these because I can't pay you at all.
And I'm like, oh, you can just pay me five bucks.
So I accepted that because guess what?
That was more than I was getting paid at the time because I was getting paid zero because, you know,
I didn't want to make a Patreon campaign until I had some people watching my content.
And I had built up like $89.
I had built up like $50 of ad revenue from my season five predictions video.
But after I got 50K views, it got demonetized.
So it's that $50 sat there for like a year before it finally spilled over into 100 to pay me.
It's worth mentioning that because when we first, when you first started working for me, you were offering to do them for free.
You were like, I won't be able to do them often if they're free.
But I just want to edit your videos was kind of like what you proposed to me.
Oh, yeah. And I was thinking also, I could get some exposure from it.
And this is what like really messed me up a little bit more is because like in the psychopaths videos in the like the redirect videos where like you'd promote the video.
At the last one, you promoted me.
And I think that gave me a little bit of a bump, right?
So that gave me just a little bit more money.
Like you had been linking some of my videos on Twitter and I finally got like a couple of patrons after the roller coaster video.
So at this time, I'm like, I don't know if I'm going to do any more Digi videos.
I love doing it, but I'm not making any money from it.
So I got to work on my own channel, which I'm also not making any money from.
Like it's a big decision.
Like, and again, I'm working full time and it's tedious and torture and hell and I hate it.
And I'm going to do a podcast with Nate someday, which is just us talking about how horrible it is to have a full time job when you're trying to do videos.
The worst thing in all in all of time, like the YouTuber schedule is to be awake and asleep whenever you believe me.
I was there briefly.
Yeah, but with a blue with a blue with a regular job, you got to be awake at a certain time every day.
Yeah.
That's death.
True death.
My time was 4am that I went to that my job started for and 2am for actually a lot of the time.
So the point is all I wanted to do was just do whatever it takes to make enough money to do it full time.
Right.
So I'm like, well, which one is going to get me there faster?
My channel or yours?
And at the time, your channel hadn't really taken off yet.
You were already one of the leading anime channels around because they're worth that many.
We didn't have a lot of faith in the idea that you could get super far with anime.
That was the thing.
I had kind of hit what I thought was a cap with Pony where I had the most subs that if anyone doing the kind of videos I was doing.
And then there was a sort of upper limit to what the biggest pony channels were.
And it was like 300,000 for the guys who were doing parody animations and shit.
And it was like that to me was the cap.
And then when I got into anime, I was very aware of that.
And the guy with the most subs was Misty Kronexia with like 450,000 at the time, which he's actually grown a lot more than that now.
But it was like that to me looked like anime can't get bigger than that.
You know, so I thought maybe maybe I would never like, you know, unless I eventually expanded into stuff beyond anime.
Maybe there was like a limit to how big this would ever get.
Got to build the Otaku Land theme park thing that they were trying to build in the future.
How did that feel when you watched Otaku no Video where you like, oh, this is what Digi's been trying to do all this time.
This is his life story.
I kind of relate to that character guy, you know, who's like already an adult kind of knowing anime, having seen a little bit of it.
And then getting into, of course, I wasn't a normal person.
I was just into other stuff adjacent to anime and like video games and stuff.
It's not quite the same trajectory, but you know, anyway.
But the feeling of those two guys like starting their company together is a lot like me and you being like, yeah.
The way that it is now with you literally being my employee at this point, which I guess we'll just build up to that since we're still in the middle of the story.
We should have opened with that.
So I definitely proved after leaving my editing role for you.
I proved that I can make a pretty good channel because I got a video out every week after that, like a little bit extra than every week.
All in a different style, all interesting at least.
My voiceover was getting progressively less annoying.
I was getting faster.
I was getting slicker and I was getting no views, no money.
I was getting nowhere.
And you know, I have the patience to make videos all the time with no results, but I don't have the patience to go to work all the time with no results.
So I'm like, oh geez.
And what really killed it was the Donkey Kong video.
I'm like, it's a Donkey Kong country video.
It has the word analysis.
I was surprised that didn't figure.
And you even emailed me about that.
I'm like, finally, this is my big hit video.
This is going to get me views.
And it got like 600 views, you know.
Now it's sitting at a few thousand, but at the time, like a week had passed, less than a thousand views.
And I was so bummed out and then you sent me an email saying, bro, it's pissing me off how few views your videos are getting.
And that was like a really impactful moment for me.
Since that email, I've never been frustrated about my view counts ever again, just knowing that you were also frustrated.
It's like I allocated my burden on to you.
And so now when I see Nate coming out with videos, all of his masterpieces and then fretting about how few views they get,
I'm like, when's he going to have his Donkey Kong country moment?
Like when it just like, you just realize you're never going to get the views until at some point there's no logic or order to it.
So I'm like, OK, I'm not making any views, not getting any money, not getting any patrons.
Digi, I'm going to come back to you.
I think what Nate is currently misunderstanding is like, I keep telling him he has to make a video every week.
And I think he's in the mindset that you have to do that because having regular content means more people will care about your stuff.
No, you have to have a video every week because you're trying to get the video that'll get big and you don't know what it'll be.
That was one of the reasons you did your Oktoberfest 2014.
Like, let's make 30 videos. Some of them got to be big.
And it worked. Two of them got unbelievably huge.
And those two out of 30, but it's just playing the odds.
It's like, if you only have one video every six months and you don't know, let's say only one in 30 gets really big,
then it's going to take a long time for you to hit 30.
You'll be having heart disease by the time you're making any money.
Some people have one video, their first video explodes and gets fucking huge.
So you would even come out with a vlog. I had been telling you about how I wanted to get back into editing your videos, maybe.
And at one point you were having this creative drought and you made a video of vlog on your after dark channel talking about how it's so hard to come out with a video
and do all the work on it because by the time you're done with all the editing, where's your inspiration?
I just hate them by the time I'm done with them.
And I have a little bit of that with making my own videos.
To some extent, I'm tired of it by then, which is why it's nice to have not been involved with the writing process if it's a video I didn't write.
So neither of us get the frustration as much. We share the load.
It's almost as if most art is made by more than one person.
That's the funniest thing to me. We've had to argue about this.
I was re-listening to one of the old PCPs where we get into this argument where those guys were making fun of me for having an editor.
And they were like, oh, it's not all your vision.
And I was like, yeah, you listened to any music. It's almost always a band of four guys.
No one of them, it's all their vision. Everyone fucking puts in something into it.
It's completely fucking normal to have a crew to make your art.
Just because we have gotten ourselves cornered in an industry where it's all bedroom production and it's harder to have a team.
But I didn't hire you because you were some editor.
I hired you because you were the fucking devout who had seen all my fucking videos and knew what to do.
I mean, I've never seen all your videos because you have so many and I've always been so busy.
If I had been not having a job, I definitely would have read your blog or something like that.
You're like my favorite internet guy, man. You're like my favorite internet dude guy.
So you had this vlog saying, oh yeah, I sure wish I had an editor.
The devout said he might be editing for me again, but it's so hard. I can't pay him enough.
I'm working on this video about the Nanoha franchise and devout would have to watch all of Nanoha.
I can't pay him enough to watch all of Nanoha and make a video about all of Nanoha.
So then after that, I watched and made a video about all of Nanoha with you.
So that was cool.
I want to clarify because I was saying earlier that you said you would do the work for free back at the very beginning.
And I didn't let you do it for free because I don't believe in that.
I've been following a lot of random posts from random websites and stuff about culture and shit.
I would always hear about this phenomenon where people would promise artists exposure in exchange for work.
It's a very common thing where they'll be like, let's say there's a festival going to happen, like a music festival.
And they'll get young artists who are desperate, who don't have anything.
And they'll be like, oh, if you perform at this festival for free, it'll get you lots of exposure.
So they'll get people to do shows and then not pay them for their work under the guise that it's going to get them exposure, which it's not.
Because nobody knows who they are and nobody cares, so it's not going to get them exposure.
I mean, it is true that for a YouTuber, you can get some exposure and you did, but obviously it didn't launch a career for you in the short time.
Well, it did make things a lot harder, right? Because here's what happened, right?
So I'm like, hmm, maybe my channel isn't going to go anywhere because I was getting like $5 of patronage, a video, less than a thousand views, a video.
So I made the Nanahu video, part one of three. Most people probably haven't seen your Nanahu video.
Like, you know, I'm sure all your big fans have, but those don't have a ton of views.
So you did the three part Nanahu retrospective.
So this was sort of like me returning to your channel and I was thinking, hmm, maybe, you know, you were able to pay me a little bit more money because you were making a little bit more money.
I believe this may have been like during the summer where your channel got bigger.
So like your channel had gotten bigger at this time. This was around the time where some of your videos were finally really blowing up.
There was like three waves to your channel getting bigger.
The end of like October or November 2014, the summer of 2015, and then the winter of 2016.
Those were like the three waves of your channel getting big.
The third one finally did it in, of course.
But yeah, Nanahu part one. At the end of Nanahu part one, you say, hey everyone, this was edited by the DeVoo.
He did a good job obviously because he's amazing.
But also he has his own videos and they're also great and he's criminally under recognized.
You should all go watch him.
So then a lot of people did and made this decision about which channel to work on a whole lot more complicated.
There's one patron in particular who like patrons a lot of came to, I got a $35 patron.
I was like, I'm just like, I'm just laying in my bed one day waking up.
Oh, I got a $10 patron. Oh, I got a $5 patron. Oh, the $10 patron.
Like I got a $1 patron who changed to a $10 patron.
Oh, the $30 patron became a $35 patron.
Well, okay then, you know, and then I started getting 1000 video views of video then.
I'm like, this is suddenly even more complicated.
So I did the other Nanoha videos and I'm like, okay, you know, like, what do I do?
And then what happened was you went for a couple of months not being able to come up with anything for me to do.
Like you were like, DeVoo, I might be doing a video about Full Metal Alchemist.
I'm like, okay, I watched all of Full Metal Alchemist and then at the end you were like, DeVoo,
I think I might not want to make a video.
No, that wasn't really how it happened.
What happened was I just thought, hmm, you know what would be really awkward for Digi
is if he decided he didn't want to make a video about Full Metal Alchemist
and so I told you, hey, if you don't want to make a video about Full Metal Alchemist,
that's fine because I'm as Full Metal Alchemist.
I'm glad I watched it.
I'm glad I watched FMAB anyway because it's a great important cultural reference point
and I was even able to talk about it in a video that I did immediately afterwards briefly.
So I was able to use it as a reference point.
I got my money's worth, obviously, but yeah, you bailed on the FMAB video.
Pretty much the second you said that.
Like the second you said, hey, don't worry about it.
I'm glad I watched it.
I was like, okay, because I had quickly lost desire to do it.
That was important in me being able to figure out how to marathon things again.
Like I was when I was younger and I had nothing to do,
you know, marathoning things is like a state of mind you got to hype yourself up for
when you have a job, you know.
So yeah, it didn't, it went a couple months without knowing what to give to me.
You're like, hey, Davoo, edit one of the Ava videos.
Everyone is badass in even going on episodes six and seven.
So I did that one.
And then it was like another couple of months.
And then after that was the asterisk war.
Oh my gosh, I didn't, there's no thing in between that.
Yeah.
It was a slow period for my channel altogether.
But yeah.
But the asterisk war, that's when I was like, hey, we're fucking Davoo, we're doing this.
Like we're going great.
We're going big.
Well, it wasn't quite, it wasn't actually all the way yet.
You had been making more money.
You were able to give me like a hundred dollars per video, which is like cool.
But you know, at this point, I was losing my mind.
Like, I mean, I'd been losing my mind since.
Yeah.
The post asterisk period was like unbelievably tumultuous.
Like in terms of what?
Yeah.
So yeah, we're all built to that.
So at this point, I've been like, I'd already lost my mind like a year plus ago.
And now I'm just like, my soul is shredding in half.
I'm just like, I can't break out of the cycle of work.
Actually, it wasn't too bad because my, I got into an arrangement where I could like
pay some money and work part-time.
But man, doing it part-time is almost worse in its own way because like you get used to
not having to work and you have to anyway and blah, blah, blah.
So I was thinking, man, the asterisk war videos, they're getting a lot of views.
They're great.
Like it's 12 parts long.
They're all getting views.
Your Patreon is going to hopefully explode because these are great videos and everyone
loves them.
And like, you know, parts four and five went along and your Patreon went up a little bit.
And then, so like part four or so came out at the beginning of the year of 2016.
Now that border of the year was really big for me because December 31st, 2015, I was
headed to the TPC chat.
I had managed to Paula take my way in by getting everyone else on Skype.
What I did was like, I got you and I already had Jesse and I, because I had, I had added
you on Skype back in September by saying like, Hey, you know, just let you know.
If you do want to add me on Skype, that'd be great.
Well, is that the point where we were doing more and more work together and it was like,
this will be smart, you know, like, we've been talking for long enough that I was comfortable
with you and I didn't think it was going to be weird.
And I was like, we're clearly working together for the long run.
So let's do it.
Right.
Yeah.
In fact, we may have, I may have added you on Skype like slightly before the Ava video
even.
So then I was like, okay, my plan was then to add Hippo and then Nate and then Ben.
And that's like the five main members, I would say, like, you know, Tom and Jeff wasn't even
there, but Tom and major kind of like side members in a way, because they're not that
active, you know.
Yeah.
So I went to them all on Skype and then I just made sure that everything I said to them
was funny and interesting to prove that I'm good.
And then I waited a week and created my own Skype group called the DeVoo Association, which
I guess was a proto collective, I guess, where it was a chat of just all of us, but with
me in it to prove that I could be funny and interesting in a group, I guess.
I think it was my plan.
And then it worked.
You guys kept talking in it to where you added me to the chat.
So I went, I did it.
I forgot it was that recent because you said December, right?
Because I very distinctly remember exactly what you did.
You pulled everyone in and you said, ha, you idiots.
I was doing a flowy impersonation by the way.
You did a flowy.
Just by the text.
Yeah.
Because we were all super into Undertale at the time and I think you were aware of that.
Yes.
You flowied us all.
And then I was just like, because we were all, you know, we were all like, oh, DeVoo,
you card.
And then back in the other chat, we were just kind of like, is there any reason not to have
because like at this point, I think, because Ben was already a fan of your videos.
He liked them.
I think Hippo was vaguely aware of them.
You know, me and Jesse were both talking to you already.
So it was really.
I was mostly worried about Hippo because I had never heard anything that he had as
an opinion on any of my videos and I was afraid that he didn't like me.
Like Nate, I don't care if Nate likes me or not.
I don't care about that fags opinion.
But Hippo was like, oh man, I hope Hippo.
And I know that he was the one who like bitches about my old avatar from my old videos the
most and has the most problems with my videos, whatever, you know.
Well, Nate had never seen any of them and that was the thing.
Right.
That was like what, he was the last person who hadn't seen any because he had always
just been out of the impression that you were like some weird guy who like, who just edits
my videos and was just like.
Right.
And then it was actually, I believe he watched my roller coaster three video and that's the
kind of video that he likes.
Huge, way too elaborate, way too drawn out.
The opposite of Ben because Ben liked you because of your short videos and he thought
they were really smart and funny.
And it was just kind of like, I guess Nate just literally hadn't gotten the memo that
we liked your videos.
He literally had only seen the trampolines one, which he did like, but then he was like,
oh, I just assumed he was dumb or something.
We were like, no, do you watch his stuff?
And he was like, oh, okay, this is good.
Yeah.
And you know, like the first thing he said to me on Skype after what's up, you black
nigger was, now dude, I got to say, I've never really watched any of your videos and it's
because of your icon.
It's so shit.
You got to fix that man.
And that did eventually compel me into changing my avatar, you know.
But yeah, anyway, to the one I have now.
But yeah, so that's how I got in the chat December 31st, 2015.
I was like, yeah, cool, awesome.
And then that turn of the year was also a big deal for me because that's how I was finally
able to get out of work.
So just to let you all know just how privileged I am.
I work for a family business that my dad created.
So it's not really a job.
It's just eight hours of chores that makes it even more torturous.
And so it's just like, I can't, it's not like I can quit my job because it's just my dad
telling me to do it, right?
And it's not like he pays me money.
He like pays me some, but then most of it is just you get to live here, you know.
So it's really hard.
I have to use all just family bonding as negotiating currency.
So my dad wanted to have a website for his company and I know computers.
I don't know how to make websites really, but I could learn it.
So he's like, Hey, David, if you make a website for our company, I'll give you the winter off.
And I'm like, okay, you know, this is after like a straight year of me making it abundantly clear
that doing the job was making my soul split in half.
And so like, I guess I was, I sufficiently guilted him into it.
So he, he came up with this contract.
I had the winter off, right?
Cause that's an off season for our business anyway.
So I'm like, this had better be my escape, right?
Yeah.
Um, I even named my computer ticket out of here.
Back when I, man, I'd never even told anyone that before.
That's great.
Um, yeah.
So that's what I wanted to have.
Um, so the Astroscore was going on this series.
And I was like, good, this series has like eight more parts to go.
It's going to get even bigger.
It's going to get Digi all of these patronages.
And I've been doing an impersonation of your impersonation of monkey Jones.
Yeah.
I could tell actually.
It's just, it's just most of my impersonations are impersonations of impersonations.
Those are the ones I can understand better.
So anyway, um, and I'm like, good, great, awesome.
Your Patreon will go up and then I can make enough money to like just go full time.
Hopefully.
So part six and seven came out, part eight and nine came out.
And it was like the Patreon wasn't going up that much.
And I was like freaking out and you were like, well, what were you expecting?
It always goes up slowly.
And I'm like, just, just no, it's got to go up.
The winter is winter is leaving the opposite.
Yeah.
I have it, you know, I've gotten used to this rhythm of like, I put out a video, I
might gain five to $10 on there, you know, and the thing is it, it adds up quick, you
know, like it's not quick enough, not that much time left.
And of course I had to devote like a week of that winter to learning how to do HTML
and then another week to make the website and like, can I even do all of it?
Incidentally, I didn't make the website, but I've never even posted it because my dad
had to like approve of it and read it.
And as he, as I would know, it's impossible to do anything internet related when you have
to clean windows.
So he's never gotten around to it.
The website still hasn't been posted hilariously enough.
Yeah.
So anyway, so I want to, I want to be able to, I want to talk about what happened at the
very end of this, of the asterisk, because it's fucking hilarious.
So part nine came out and I was like, this has got to be the big one.
This is the best one.
This is the nerd writer one.
This is where it's got to go get big, but it still didn't happen.
I'm like, so I'm over here calmly.
Every video is coming out.
It's great.
Every video is a masterpiece.
They're getting lots of views.
I'm gaining, you know, a decent amount of patrons, but not an amount that is like changing
the game immediately, right?
And so like after the last asterisk was done, like you sent it to me and you're like, it's
done.
I have like, I can't edit for you for a while.
Like I need to go soul search and do all this other stuff.
And you literally said that.
I think you said it was like the rest of the month you were going to be off doing something
else.
And I had given you this script for myriad colors phantom world that I wanted you to
edit.
And I wanted it to be done before the month was over.
But you were like, I got to go do other stuff because, you know, like this, the channel's
not growing fast enough and you were super stressed out.
And what happened was I had saved up, I had saved up a bunch of my money, right?
I saved up a bunch of the money that I'd been making from the asterisk series because I
don't have to pay rent this winter.
I can save up the money and I'm just going to politic my way out of having to work again.
I don't want to go back.
To clarify for the audience, because you had these three months off, exactly what your
plan was, make enough money during those three months and become enough of an employee of
me that when the time came that you had to go back to work, you could tell your dad,
I'm already making better money than I would be making working for you, essentially.
Or enough to pay rent.
That's not possible.
That's, you know, he is a business.
I mean, you're not making anything for working for him.
I never said that.
He wasn't even paying.
Well, I'm making rent.
I'm technically making, I'm creating the wealth that is paying it.
Like I'm creating the money.
It's, you know, like he wanted me to pay my own expenses.
He didn't want to like millennialify me, you know.
But the idea was that if you made enough money, you wouldn't have to go back to work.
Well, actually what happened was I demanded that he create a list of all of my expenses
and like show it off.
Like, okay, like what I, one time I just like, okay, I'm just not going to eat this month.
And so that's how I was able to politic him into me having to pay less rent because he
just cannot stand any of his children not eating.
So I accidentally hunger protested inadvertently.
That worked really well.
But I gotta, I gotta get to the delivery of this because I want to say this part because
it's so fucking funny to me because like, yeah, you basically, it wasn't panning out well enough.
You weren't making enough money that you could bribe your dad.
No, I got, I'll, I, this is an important part of setting that up.
Right.
So I like, okay, I decided I was just going to do it and not tell my dad that this was the plan.
So like, normally I pay him $200 a month and then work two days a week on average.
Right.
So what I did was like halfway through March, it's like, oh man, starting April, my dad might
make me work in.
So I pay him $200 for April preemptively.
Yeah.
And then I just threw in another $400 and I said, this is the premium.
That's all I said, which is, this is the premium.
Such a fucking thing.
And then, and then, you know, we're, we're getting home from a Ted Cruz rally and at the, right
before we get out of the car, my dad's like, so David, I've been scheduling the work that
you'll be doing starting as April.
And I'm like, what?
But I paid you the premium.
He's like the premium.
Like, like you just accepted that money.
Because he totally knows what the fuck the premium means.
So I was like, um, and I was like, but I gave you $600 in total.
And he was like, oh, but that's not anywhere close to finishing off your expenses.
I'm like, oh, so I bolted out of the car and then went upstairs and okay, there, I'll leave.
I went up to my computer, logged into the chat.
Now I'll throw it back to you.
So Davoo tells me like, you know, it's not working.
I don't have enough to bribe my dad.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
I'm freaking out.
You're like, I think you had decided to like completely log off Skype and like log off the internet.
I uninstalled Skype.
Uninstalled Skype.
Just to make sure he wouldn't be on.
So I've got to make videos right now.
Like, what am I going to do?
I'm going to make a video.
I started playing thief and I just kept, I just played thief all night.
Got to make a video about thief.
And I couldn't come up with any ideas.
I'm like, ah, so, so Davoo's like trying to fucking desperately make videos for his own channel so he can grow it.
Because mine's not paying him enough.
Literally the same day that Davoo leaves the internet was the day that we posted the last asterisk war.
And it just so happens that within like 30 hours of posting the last asterisk war video,
my Patreon goes up by a hundred dollars.
A hundred dollars!
It was, it was insanity.
And I'm sitting there like, where the fuck are you, Davoo?
What are you fucking doing?
This is the last time you should be leaving.
I can pay you anything now.
What's happening?
No, I mean, you couldn't at the time.
Like, your, your, your patronage had to go up another couple hundred dollars over the course of a month or two.
Right?
But it was, it was a really fucking hilarious time.
Well, well, here's the thing though, right?
Because I was there when your channel had that second wave in summer.
And I remember saying on the pub crawl chat,
huh, I made such a good decision to work for your channel.
I always make great decisions.
Because I thought, great, you're going to explode now, but you didn't explode enough.
So I'm like, okay, I'm not going to like, lie around and like, bank purely on the hope that you're going to be big enough for me to be able to do full time money on it.
It was like one day though.
No, like, like, no, no, no, no, no.
It like, it took a couple more weeks, you know, like, it was just like before it was like,
because who knows, maybe it would just be like a hundred dollars and then that's it.
But it was immediately obvious that this was the worst possible time to not be on the channel.
I disagree.
I think, well, I mean, in terms of my own content, screaming too much.
Sorry.
Too loud.
You know what?
Uh, no.
Anyway, I'm going to be, keep being loud.
Did somebody just come in and tell you to shut up or something?
No, my dad texted me too loud, but you know, whatever.
Um, so the thing is, I had to make my own videos because like this, this is what offended me in the interview with Ben is how you guys were talking about my videos in present tense.
Even though I consider all of them before the slipperiness versus tightness video to be my old videos that don't represent my writing style.
Like, because I had been going through this phase where my writing was too tight, was too concise that no one would understand it.
Like the Undertale video, which no one got.
And you were telling me that you should slow down a bit and say things in ways that people are going to understand.
And so I made like all of two videos that were in that style because I'm like, I know how to write even better now.
I need to make good videos now.
So I ended up making like a couple of videos like that to prove that I can be good.
And I'm glad I have like two videos that are really great, I think almost.
And that way I can prove to the world that like, you know, you all know now exactly what I am denying you.
And that's all I need for my pride.
Like, like ultimately, um, I am more intro just slightly more invested in the narrative of your channel than I am of mine.
Like part like the amount of creative satisfaction I get working for your channel just barely edges out my own.
So as soon as I was able to make those two videos toward the end of March, I believe, or April.
No, toward the end of March, whenever it was, um, I believe it was March.
I really remember a quote that stuck with me forever about like, when you started writing for me or editing for me, rather,
and I sent you like I was asking you like if it was like if it was creatively fulfilling for you to edit my videos, like, you know,
is it really more fun than doing your own stuff or something like that?
And you said that whenever you read one of my scripts, you feel like all of the energy of it immediately transfers to you.
Like something to that effect.
Like you get like this, like you read it and you get excited as if it was something you wrote yourself, you know,
like you want it to exist so badly that you make it.
I remember saying that in relation to just your videos in general.
Like I see, I could watch a video and I feel like I'm in the video and stuff, yeah.
I take that for granted now too.
Obviously if I was editing for anyone else, which I wouldn't be, I would be able to tell by contrast the sheer lack of enthusiasm I would have.
Well, I think a big part of what makes me like you as an editor so much is that you'll get one of my scripts
and if you like it enough, you'll say like, I have to make this good because this script needs to be good.
Oh yeah, the worst was the 10 best things happening in anime.
Yeah.
I was just like, stop making it good.
No, stop.
No effort.
No.
Effort.
Because for me, like, I mean, that's how I feel when I write it.
You know, I reach, like I write the post and in my head, it's the greatest thing in the universe.
I'm like, I finish, you know, something like the Psycho Pass videos or something and like, when I'm done writing it, I'm like, this is the best thing ever.
But then the process of editing just drains me of all giving a fuck and eventually I'm sick of it and I just want it.
Like in the Three Ham song, I said like, I hope Davoo likes the show and continues with the edit because if I'm doing that shit, I'm fucking setting it to Deus Ex footage.
In the event that you hadn't edited the Psycho Pass videos, I would have just set it to video game footage and been done with it because I just couldn't take it anymore, you know.
But for you, it's like you get the script and it's like your first instinct is, well, this is great.
So this obviously has to exist and be good or else, you know, it's going to be a failure on the part of the universe, you know.
Yeah.
And I love that about your editing process.
So the trauma hadn't ended there though because then, so like, because like what had happened is that my Patreon was still growing steadily and I was getting slightly more views.
And so then it was just like an issue of like, oh yeah, I guess I wasn't sure how did this go.
I wasn't sure how much money I was going to have to pay my dad for me to ransom myself away from his business.
And I just wasn't sure what I wanted to do more.
My own channel or yours.
And there was just like a million variables to consider.
And I don't remember how I just ended up deciding on your channel.
Yeah.
So then that's the end of the story.
How has that been going by the way?
Like, because here's the thing, like I was saying earlier, you used to be infamous for the way that you'd have all these revelations, that everything would be this life altering, crazy thing.
And all these things you're describing to me with this fervor that you're describing it, that fervor was even more intense in the moments that these things were happening.
You would email me like the entire world had just come to an end, you know, on like a daily basis about how your finances and your situation with your dad was going and stuff.
And it was like overwhelming.
It was true though.
And it was always like, it was always like this madness that you were emailing me and I'm like, all right.
I remember especially a couple of times I'm like, I need to definitely get across how insane I'm going.
You need to know.
And it was well communicated.
But finally, after the Myriad Colors fandom world video that it wasn't.
Yeah, it was.
No, it was immediately after Astroscore that I hired you full time because we hit the benchmark.
And that's when I sent you the doc where it was like, we're professionals now.
You're now my employee.
And oh yeah, you sent me that.
Here's the videos we're going to do in April of 2016.
And it was like five videos and they all had a schedule and they all came out ahead of schedule.
Well, one of them came out on schedule.
The rest came out ahead of schedule.
And it was like, whoa, I'm glad that you made the schedule so easy.
But well, we made a great, cool schedule.
And I was like, you're now my full time employee.
You're going to do all the main series content, all the main videos on my channel.
You're now the editor.
And I can pick, like, because the way you had said it was that you needed to make,
because I asked you, like, how much do you need to make to keep your dad off your back?
And you said probably like $900 a month.
And I was like, cool, I'm going to write enough videos that I can pay you $900 a month
and I still will have enough money to get myself through.
That's been my goal ever since.
So with that month, it was five videos is enough that I'll have enough money and you'll have enough money.
And then the next month, we only needed four videos for us to both have enough money.
And then this month, hopefully three will be enough.
Well, okay, here's the thing.
Let's get to the month.
Once again, the inadvertent hunger protests have been taking effect where it was like,
I was like, hmm, dad, you know, like, I can pay you $900,
but I think I'm just going to pay you $600 and not eat much this month.
Like I just, that's what I just said.
And my mom was like, how about you just pay $600?
They just can't, they cannot live with the thought.
I swear I'm not doing this deliberately.
I'm not that evil, but just how it happened.
Because like my dad grew up poor and not always fed.
So I guess he just can't deal with that.
My dad is the exact same.
My dad will not stand for anybody like being hungry at any time.
I just love how like both of our dads had such similar upbringings
and but then like went on to have such different personalities.
But they're both very super hardworking and entrepreneurial.
Well, I guess your dad's not entrepreneurial.
Anyway, but better.
If it was, my dad was a hardcore Christian for a brief time,
just later in life, he became disillusioned very quickly.
Fakers.
You're not a real Christian.
You're a faker.
So anyway, let's see what happens then.
Then I, yeah, it's been great doing, oh, where are we?
All right, I'll pick up for you.
Yeah, we're essentially, you're full time now.
And now the goal is move you up here to Virginia.
Right.
Because your internet sucks.
It always has.
It's like a fact of life.
The internet sucks if you're the debut.
So indeed.
So we want to make.
I'm really hoping that I won't bring the curse over.
We're trying to get you over here.
And you also just don't want to live at home because you don't
like that feeling of describe what your revelation was after the
biggest problem of the universe episode about.
Oh, yeah.
Well, it wasn't really a revelation.
It was just like a logical conclusion.
Dick brought in the problem of adults living with their families.
Because before this, I'm like, you know, the only reason to move
out is just to say that I moved out.
Like it's not necessarily that important.
And then, but like Dick was like, you know, like whenever I go
home to my parents, like whenever I like visit my parents, you know,
there's a part of my brain that like becomes 13.
And it's like, I can't, if people are just like that all the time,
they can't mentally develop.
Yeah.
Now I think that to an extent it's like not only that he's living,
it's not only that he's staying with his parents,
but also he's taking a break from work.
If you're working full time in your bedroom,
I don't think it's the same quite, same quite of an effect.
But when I listened to that podcast, I remembered the fact that one
time my parents went out of the house for like a couple of days for
like an anniversary thing.
And so I had to kind of be the one to watch over my siblings,
although my brother is more equipped for that.
But I was suddenly much more aware of my surroundings.
I could feel the locks on the doors.
And then when my parents came back, those sensations went away.
And I'm like, oh my God, maybe I'm not mentally developing correctly.
So as soon as I got in, got it in my head,
I should probably leave the house just to like have a more dynamic
and excited life of like being a little bit more stressed out,
a little bit more on edge, but in a productive way, not an anxiety way,
but more of a being an adult sort of way.
Then I started deliberately looking at living at home as negatively as possible.
And that was the cause of all of my railings against Christianity
that some people who follow me on Twitter can find out about today,
where I was praying to Satan and asking that he revokes any prayer
that is made upon me by my parents.
Yeah, it's an interesting prospect.
For me, I definitely feel what Dick was saying.
And I don't feel like I encounter it too much because I don't spend much time around my parents,
because our house is fucking enormous, my room is very secluded,
and there's times where I barely see them for days.
They're always just on the couch down there and I'll just pass through and I'll go, hey.
I'm pretty much the same way. I mean, I don't have as much audio distance as you can tell,
but I also just go without seeing them that much for a while.
Well, it's finally sort of cracked it.
Because for a long time, when I am around my parents, when we do something as a family,
it is exactly that problem Dick was talking about.
And as you'll know if you've listened to Digi Bros.,
making dinner in my family has always been this weird nightmare.
Because everyone has different tastes and no one wants to do it.
And it's the kind of thing where we were kind of forcing ourselves to all eat the same dinner,
even though it didn't make any sense.
And it would always be this ordeal where I'd go downstairs,
living my life as a guy with a job and doing all this work and everything,
and then I'd go downstairs and for 45 minutes just enter this fiasco of trying to organize dinner.
And my mental age would just plummet down to 14.
Because it's the same exact stuff we've been doing since 14.
The same arguments, the same indecisions everyone has, the same everyone just being lazy and stupid.
And finally, like a month or so ago, it's completely cut out.
We don't do it anymore.
Because my dad became a vegetarian, along with my mom, who's been one for a long time.
My dad became a vegetarian and Victor and Shader grown now.
And it was just like, no one wants to do this anymore.
Let's all just make our own food.
And ever since then, I haven't had any of those moments of like,
wow, I feel like I'm fucking 12 again.
Because I see my parents in a very...
I encounter them at random sometimes.
And I'll hang out for a little bit and talk the business what's going on in my life.
But it's never like I have to rely on them for us all to make a decision about a food we're going to eat or something,
which is a fucking nightmare, you know?
Yeah, I hate that.
I don't think my family has done that for a while.
Actually, we just all have the same tastes.
I guess I take that for granted.
My mom is able to make something that all of us like 85% of the time, I would say.
Yeah, that would be zero.
Yeah, so she doesn't make stuff.
That's how it happens.
She eats it, and then my dad and my brother eat it when they get home from work.
And my sister eats it.
And then I eat it three hours later out of the fridge.
Because I never eat it at the same time everyone else does, like most of the time.
So that's not as much of an issue for us.
Although outside of dinner, we do always just cook our own meals.
And then that causes dishes to go out of whack.
And my mom actually said, hey, David, how about you don't pay any rent.
You just wash the dishes.
And my dad is not sure about that.
But I'm going to accept the proposition from my mom.
I'll just wash the dishes.
Great deals.
So all right.
We ended up talking about me and you's relationship for way longer than I thought we would.
But you kept getting so excited about it and going on and on.
Yeah, if you want to hear this stuff really in depth, go to patreon.com.
Did you bro?
Pledge five dollars.
Get access to our massively long commentaries where we will be commentating on all of his videos.
We started with the sword art online ones and then we went back all the way to his pre pony days.
We sped through all of his pre anime stuff just kind of showing you the highlights.
Then we're going through all of his anime.
Yeah.
Okay.
And then we're going to be going through every single one of his main videos since then.
And we don't just like let the video play and then like talk over the video.
No, we like let five seconds of the video play and talk for a long time.
Some videos we talk about for one hour or more we talk about.
So it is definitely the final statements on all of your work.
Yeah.
Like it just it will exhaust everything I want to say about this video.
So if you want to hear every little minutiae of how he writes and how I've been doing the editing, you got to pay money.
Yeah.
But there are a lot like this discussion we've been having.
This is almost like a, as soon as we started getting like way deep into it.
I had to kind of like remind myself that we're not doing a commentary that we're doing an interview with you.
But I don't know.
I mean that's what, that's kind of what your life has been for the last couple years, right?
Like have you been doing much of anything other than work and editing my videos?
Like work, editing your videos, making my videos, making NesQuest.
Which is your videos.
Every once in a while I write like a chapter of erotic fiction for myself.
That's about the only other art I think that no one knows about.
Well not just art, but like is there anything you do as like a hobby or out of the house or anywhere you go?
How are you about eating?
Because I eat out twice a fucking day.
Oh yeah, I never eat out.
I don't want to, I mean for one thing there's not that many restaurants around here.
And I don't want to spend the money.
I don't have the money.
And I hate leaving the house because, I mean I like leaving the house but time elapses at like 300% as soon as you leave the house.
And I get home and I'm like where the fuck did Monday go?
Is that kind of feeling when I get home?
So I'm like that's why I'll just start, I won't even go to get groceries.
Even though I desperately need food to get groceries.
I don't want to leave the house and lose like five hours and twenty minutes.
So I just starve instead, you know.
You still use your trampoline, right?
Or didn't it get destroyed by the storm or something?
Oh we got a new one.
I couldn't figure out how to make a video about how, hey guys actually we got another one.
And then my brother bent it slightly but not quite so it still works.
I'm like, yeah there's a lot of trampoline lore that I haven't been able to translate into videos.
So I don't really do anything else other than videos.
I have a basic understanding of your dad is a guy who is a hardcore Christian, works a lot.
Those are kind of the two most important things.
When his phone is on he's working because he has a business and he also, along with my brother,
are the only people who do the actual labor of the business because, newsflash, no one wants to clean windows.
My dad's business is perfect, the customers are satisfied, the customers don't stop pouring in.
But no one, he can't grow the business because no one wants to work for it and I would know.
Because I don't.
It's a sad story.
Yeah, so that's your dad.
Your mom is a normie.
She's just a great mom.
What does she do, just hanging around the house?
She's just like, yeah she's like a house, I mean most of her days spent driving my sister around
because my sister is one of those kids who goes to places to go to a class for a thing.
She's like a dancer per person.
I can't believe I forgot to ask this earlier but we took so long before we got to your personal information.
How old are you?
I am 22.
22 debut, when's your birthday?
April 30th.
Okay, so.
The same birthday as Tom Fulp, the founder of Newgrounds.
Okay.
Yeah, you're 22 so you're the second youngest.
Are you younger than Hippo or older?
No, I'm the youngest TPC person by like nine months, yeah.
Oh man, I didn't think about you being younger than Hippo.
It's true.
So you're the youngest TPC and you've got two younger siblings.
Right, my brother who's listening to this is 18 I think.
Yeah, he was born August 12th, 1997.
Is he listening to this because he listens to the procrastinators or because you're gonna make it?
Well, he probably will listen to this and he listens to all of the procrastinators, yes.
When I talked about him being epic in the bed, like with the light descending on him at night,
he was like, oh man, David, when you talked about me, that was like really weird.
So anyway, yeah, my brother was born August 12th, 1997, one day before the airing of the first episode of South Park.
That's how you can remember that.
He said April, what day?
August 12th, 1997, that's my brother's birthday.
He's like 18, he's about a month and a half older than Shade, yeah.
Yeah, something like that.
And then my sister, who is 12, was born March 9th, 2004.
March 9th, the same day that Smash Brothers Brawl came out.
Brawl came out on her fourth birthday, so that's whenever...
I was gonna say, I thought you meant that she was born the same day that Brawl came out.
The reason why that's significant to me is that every time, that's significant to me,
especially because I was waiting for Brawl with every bated breath of my life
and it got delayed twice to March 9th, and then every time March 9th comes around,
I'm like, hey Abigail, guess what day it is?
The anniversary of Brawl!
And I leave, you know.
So yeah.
If you wanna see my sister in action as an actress,
you can go to my channel, go to my dumbness playlist, click on promotion tragedy.
It's a video that was written by my sister and she stars in it, directed by my brother,
and he did the soundtrack, and I did like, some supervising and editing.
It's a... oh man.
I'm getting a call about how loud I'm being from.
Turn off my phone now.
You know.
You're not gonna answer the call?
I'm gonna try and actually be quiet now, maybe.
Hey baby, I'm gonna turn up the game so I can be quiet, I don't know.
So, yeah, so those are my siblings, so my sister is 12 and stuff, so yeah.
I guess that was the end of that.
Yeah, nothing interesting about them at all, just a couple of brats.
Um, well my sister, you know, I do greatly respect that she's like a dancer person,
she has a lot of, she's very serious about it, like she's like one of the only people in her dance studio
who's like serious about the, about the profession, you know?
Like she's pretty into it.
So I do like that, but I can't get into dance at all, I just, I watch it and I'm just bored out of my mind,
like I don't know what to do.
It's just like, I can't really relate to that art at all, so.
It is weird though seeing my sister how dancing is such a fulfilling thing to her
and she got into it when she was four, and I told her once, do you know how weird it is
that you got to be like fulfilled in your life, like for as long as you've been alive?
Because I haven't, and I told her, I only started being fulfilled in my life three months ago, actually.
Hey Abigail, you notice?
She doesn't totally comprehend that being that she's 12.
She's smart, I talk to her all the time, so she knows my line of thinking.
I was able to induct her into this, into this philosophy because I told her like, hey,
you notice how up until a couple of months ago, if anyone stood next to me in the kitchen,
like if I was cooking something on a burner and then someone was cooking something next to me,
I would immediately seem really angry and uncomfortable and want to die.
That's because I wasn't happy with my life until a couple of months ago.
Now finally, people can be cooking something on a skillet next to me and it doesn't bother me.
And she was like, wow, you're right.
So yeah, so that's kind of a weird thing that my sister has, is like takes for granted that having a good life,
or I don't know, maybe I'm totally wrong, I don't know.
And then my brother is a dude who's very talented, but he doesn't have like, hasn't like yet taken the initiative
to like really go full force on making something specific, although he did make one,
he is trying to do let's play videos now or something because I told him he could be a great let's play guy.
So maybe he'll be doing it, but he doesn't have, this is both, you know, a good and a bad thing.
It's like, it's a different way of being an artist.
He doesn't have tireless agonizing, burning passion, like, or more like agony, more like,
not, I don't want to say passion, that sounds too positive.
It's almost, what compels me to make art professionally is like 25% positive and 75% negative reinforcement, you know.
So, I don't know, my brother just doesn't, he's just more okay with like cleaning windows and stuff.
So, you know, he's just like a different kind of dude, but it does make it hard for me to like collaborate with him on stuff
because he'll just like lose inspiration more.
And he might be, he might be really upset right now listening to this like, yeah, David, you told me about this.
And I don't know how he feels about that.
And I don't know how he feels about the fact that I've acknowledged that he feels that way.
I don't know how he feels about the fact that I've acknowledged the fact that he's acknowledged.
I got, we won't talk about your siblings and family anymore.
So, I've gotten the impression, there's a sort of odd duality with you because on the one hand,
you have been on the internet for a long time, I think, and seem to have a lot of sort of worldly knowledge
and like understanding of other people around the world because of that,
but that in your actual personal life, it seems like you've been extremely sheltered, would you say so?
Kind of.
Because you went to homeschool your whole life, right?
Yeah.
And then you worked for your dad.
Right, my parents triple sheltered me, right?
What's the third one?
Well, just being a regular shelter that like most kids these days get.
You know, then homeschooling, then a family business.
So yeah, it's been like constant exposure to family, mostly only.
But I think that maybe, tell me if this is going to be a revelation for you because I just thought of this.
And I don't know if I'm going to finally blow your mind for the first time in a few months.
Alright, so you know, I as a kid had an understanding of other people from school
and then a different understanding that I kind of got from the internet where I sort of relearned people online.
Would you say that your understanding of other people is more based on the internet?
Because you ran into fewer people growing up and you've been online for so long.
Still there?
And also I want to know exactly how long it's been on the internet.
I'm going to say slightly no.
Like I do get plenty of social interaction.
There's plenty of church stuff like, you know, every week tons of social interaction.
So I'm going to say, I don't know, I'm going to put that on hold.
I don't know the answer to that.
So my history with the internet was I first started using it occasionally on my dad's computer here
and there to play games or something in like 2002 probably.
And then I got more into like browsing the internet on my own in around 2006
and got into forums in 2007 and that's how I became part of internet communities.
And I've just been doing it constantly every day ever since.
So yeah, that's my internet history.
My computer history starts when I was like two.
I've just been on the computer most of the day, every day, my whole life.
I think everyone in the procrastinators has been a long time internet user.
I've gotten the impression we all got on before it was normal.
I know that for some of our audience who are younger, they might not know.
And maybe even you, do you know that there was a time when it was weird in our lifetime?
I think 2007 was slightly the...
Yeah, I'd say that's...
It was still slightly the period of it not being normal.
Like Facebook wasn't like a huge thing yet.
My space was still around.
That's the era we're talking about.
I'd say that 2004 and 2005 was when it was like kids at school knew what the internet was.
And then 2007 was when it was...
2007, 2008 was when it was like, oh, your parents are on there.
Everyone's on there.
Now it's widespread.
But yeah, I've been on the internet since 01.
So it was significantly before it was super-duper mainstream.
Although, of course, people who were on in the 90s will still be like,
2001, you weren't on DOS.
I'm sure Maddox would scoff at...
Hey, man, I've been on the internet since the 90s.
What, you were on in 2000s?
Well, what if you were in the 2030s?
Then you wouldn't be anything, huh?
What about that, buddy?
Yeah.
So yeah, you've been on for a long time.
And I've always gotten the impression that you've been in a lot of...
Yes.
I know the rest of your sentence there.
Yeah, that's where I spent most of my time, I think.
Like fetish websites, I guess, is what I'm getting towards.
Yeah, or fetish communities on DeviantArt.
That's where I spend a lot of my time.
I still occasionally do some of that.
It's easier to stay motivated with that.
But I've also been into...
My main thing has always been internet review stuff.
Dang, your video game nerd was really into nostalgia critic
and always wished I could like any of the other hacks that were on that website for a long time.
Obviously, I'm not into nostalgia critic anymore,
because it's not cool anymore, and it's nostalgia critic.
I've been into YouTube for a long time.
I mean, I was into YouTube a lot in like 2007, 2008.
And then people started migrating away from it, YouTubers anyway,
like review people because of copyright.
But then they all started coming back in around 2010,
and that's when I got big into YouTube more.
So I've never really been someone who spends a huge percentage of my time talking to other people.
There weren't a whole lot of people who I stumbled into who were worth talking to for very long.
So I'd never had like really great internet friends until now, really.
That's interesting.
So for you, it was more following content creators and less like Skyping people all day.
Yeah, kinda.
Yeah, there were a grand total of two people who I had like long relationships with,
one I still talk to, and one I do not at all.
So yeah, there was only really two people who I really made connections with,
and even then it wasn't like a huge deal.
There weren't people who like, I would like lie and wait,
waiting to hear what they had to say about something until this, probably, pretty much.
That's interesting because that's the opposite for me.
I did talk to people a lot, just not for very long, you know.
I don't know what it is about this particular interview,
but this is the one that's making me like look forward to when I get one of you to interview me.
Maybe it'll be you since you...
Maybe it'll be you.
You'll just be like, hey, Digi.
I'd rather not.
I think...
No, I'm kidding.
Yeah, I can interview you.
I think you would be the best interviewer.
I'd probably be the best one.
Only because of the fact that you won't ask me shit that I've already said as much.
Yeah.
Because you've heard me repeat myself countless fucking times,
and I'm sure you're sick of hearing some of those questions, you know.
Where it's like Nate, who's probably listened to the least of my shit,
would probably ask me asinine questions.
I've answered a thousand fucking times.
Indeed.
So...
All right, so you can't...
I think it's funny, you know, I'm gonna go ahead and play a defense for you here, Dubu.
Because I think probably the fact that you have kind of weird fetishes
compared to, I guess, how people perceive themselves
seems to be well known,
because we all make fun of you for it all the time.
And I gotta say, I think, I will definitely step up in defense of it,
because I think that's A, what the internet's for,
and B, I don't get where people draw their line, you know.
Like, everyone's like, everything up to what I'm into is normal,
but as soon as you go past what I'm into, that it's not cool anymore, you know, like...
Like someone who's only into, like, straight, normal porn
is always like, how can you be into lolly,
and then people who are into lolly are like, how can you be into guru,
and then people who are into guru are like, how can you be into scat, you know,
and it's like, guys, look at yourself, you know how you like that thing,
you know how you look at it, and your pee-pee goes poo-poo,
and then you get your jacket, and it goes swish-poo-poo,
that's what all of them are doing, you know.
I haven't even been into, like, the fetishes that are weird to you that much lately,
I've just been just going on galburo mostly these days, so, I mean...
How long have you known about that, did I introduce you to that, or have you just always...
I don't know how, probably you, but yeah, the last couple of months I was like,
oh, this is a much better source than D on 4chan, you know,
but I don't know, like, I don't...
Like, how D is your go-to porn, like, I feel like that says everything.
It's not, it's not really, I've never really had much of a go-to before, so, I don't know.
I'm like an E guy myself, but that's so much a D guy.
Yeah.
Yeah, um...
Yeah, I don't really see...
I don't know what...
I don't know, you say you're playing defense for me, I don't know,
I don't see where the defense is needed, honestly.
You say, oh, we make fun of you for it a lot, like, I don't know, like, once a month...
No, I'm just saying that, like, I'm just saying that, like, you know,
I have, there's people sometimes who will say things to me, like, just be like,
wow, Davoo's really into that, like, like, off to the side, like, is he really into that?
Like, you know, like, in disbelief, I'm like, why is that so hard to imagine, you know,
like, that people are into weird shit, you're into weird shit,
we're all into, like, the person asking me, you know.
Yeah, you know what I think actually is, what I've realized is actually probably my number one thing,
is mind control art, that's the hottest thing ever,
like, you just get out of, like, a mind control device, then they're mind controlled,
like, wow, it's like, all of the non-consensuality of rape without any of the screaming,
like, that's really cool, you know, so...
I totally get you, uh...
Yeah, like, you know how, like, in the sleep cast, how Ben said,
uh, I'm really into, like, the loss of humanity or whatever, or the loss of identity?
Uh, and I said, yeah!
No, it was, uh...
Ah, fuck, it was something like that, but it wasn't that phrase.
Well, okay, well, that kind of stuff, I like that, you know, like, people losing grip on themselves.
That's pretty, like, I don't know, it's like, frightening in a way.
No, yeah, he said dehumanizing, he likes the dehumanizing.
Yeah, man, it's like, it's such a frightening concept,
and it, like, the fright goes into your brain and it, like, forades its way into your libido or something.
I don't know how that works, but, yeah.
So, um...
Next topic?
Yeah, um, well, I'm trying to think.
We're like two hours in, uh...
I don't know, it's harder with you, because I don't, like, I know that you've been just, uh, since...
Well, you didn't really have high school, but I know that since the finish of...
whatever you'd call it, you've been cleaning windows.
Giving up.
You haven't, uh, gone on a pan-Europe trip, or, uh...
or sat around in a barn.
Do you have any, like, super exciting stories about things you've done with your friends?
Are there any stories you break out every once in a while, when you're like, oh, man.
Let me tell you about this one.
I can't tell if you're doing that, ironically, or if you're trying to think of something.
Um, well, it's hard to think of something when I'm doing it, so I guess I should just be quiet.
Um...
We'll see. Does it have to be, like, not internet-related, or...?
No, just whatever. Any cool stories you want to share that would make people think,
wow, Davoo has done some cool things in his life.
Well, I bought a sheep kigurumi, took some photos of me in it, so...
Kigurumi.
I should make that the background of this video.
Send me that picture, and I'll make that the, uh...
Well, there's a fanart of it, and I'll send you that. That's much better.
Someone did a fanart of me in that.
Those words are pretty adorable, so that's good.
Um, you have these alt channels, uh, Davoo Goes to Saturn,
and, uh, the NesQuest channel.
It's called NesQuest, right? Or is it Davoo?
It's just called Davoo Plays Games, yeah.
Um, tell me about NesQuest. How did this happen?
Well, uh, I always felt like no matter how much I learned about the NES,
there's always more to learn, so I needed to just play every game that's on it,
and I thought, well, hey, I could make a series out of it by playing all of it and making it a Let's Play show.
Play all of the NES games that were released in, like, order of release date.
And thanks to MobyGames, that wasn't so hard to keep track of.
And about 98% of all NES games you can find ROMs for.
So I'm not gonna play all of them, but, yeah.
Got my friends to do it, and my brother got on it, but he's like your brother.
He can't be on a Let's Play unless he's playing it, so I haven't played most of them,
but I've watched most of them, or up to 1987 or so.
And then, you know, the whole conflict of which channel to focus on resulted in me not working on it much.
But, uh, now that I'm poised to leave home and abandon my friends,
my friends were like, well, what about NESQuest?
I'm like, well, if you guys can put in the effort to do it every week when you come over for, like, at least an hour,
maybe we can finish it before I leave.
I don't know if there's a lot of NES games to get through.
Yeah, the first, like, 10 episodes were pretty bad.
Mostly my commentary is terrible, because I was trying to make it, like, a show where people are talking.
You know, like, a Let's Play that I would listen to.
But it's not a Let's Play for commentary, because it's a new game every five minutes.
You gotta focus on the game and just make a bunch of dumb jokes and reactions and occasionally say something.
And I didn't, and so, like, it gets a little bit better after episode 11 or so, or episode 9.
But, uh, now that we're into, like, episode 45 or so, I think it's finally gotten a little bit better, I don't know.
So, uh, it's definitely not, like, a show that you can, like, put on and have a fun time with.
It's more like you sit down and, like, veg out.
Yeah.
And, like, just kind of go insane.
It's kind of, it's that feeling.
It's that feeling of, like, it's at 2 a.m. and your, like, your friends are playing video games,
and you're, like, in this limbo of tired and not tired and stuff.
Yeah.
And, like, everyone is just dead.
That's kind of the atmosphere of this quest.
That's fantastic.
Um, I love the idea, like, because I'm also, I think me and you kind of have a similar mindset towards, like, um,
culture that we're interested in, which is, like, I just have to fucking consume all of it.
Like, I will, I need to know everything, and there's no other way.
Yeah, well, I became more like that by being influenced by you.
I didn't, like, ever, like, take to that as a way to do things.
But you are a big fan of, like, epic projects and, like, keeping to something for a long time.
Like, I know you were a big fan of the Titanic bit on The Biggest Problem in the Universe,
where he was watching all of Titanic in 30 seconds, I want to say,
versus, like, every time Maddox lost, he had to watch 30 seconds of Titanic.
It's like, wow, if Maddox loses 600 times, we'll get through the whole movie.
I hope they have a thousand episodes, not even close.
Didn't even make the bit last that long, whatever.
Um, yeah, so, like, yeah, the whole commentary thing,
commentating on all your videos, uh, that was partly my idea, too.
Like, I was, yeah, so...
Yeah, well, yeah, you just tend to like to get into these big locked in things,
and I appreciate that, because, again, like I just said, uh, you know,
I'm currently feeling that way about anime, where I'm like,
I want to watch every single one, uh, until I can't anymore.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I'm doing that right now, like, I want to watch all the anime.
Probably not all of them, but, like, I'm sure I'll know when it's time to stop watching anime,
but it probably won't be anytime soon.
I think you're doing an amazing job of the marathoning.
So, to tell our audience what you've been doing since you started working full-time for me,
uh, because you haven't, you stopped cleaning windows for the last, uh, all year, right?
Right, yeah. That's, yeah, 2016, this huge revolutionary year for me,
not ever having cleaned a single window.
You know how I was naked? Maybe I'll do it one more time, as like, as like a...
No, that's how they suck you back in, man.
Well, well, well, and I was like, I felt like maybe right before I move out,
I'll clean one more time, but get this, right?
My ankle still hurts sometimes, because I sprained it one time,
getting off a ladder, and the grass was wet, because my dad had hosed there.
My ankle still hurts sometimes.
So...
Fuck windows! I don't ever want to clean another one again.
Yeah, um...
So, you haven't been cleaning windows anymore,
and you have been editing my videos non-stop, and you've abandoned your own videos,
so I don't write that fast.
What the hell have you been doing when you're not making my videos?
Yeah, just been watching anime, man.
I wanted to just do that, because the more anime I watch,
the more I can edit for you, because that's the number one deficiency I have as your editor.
I haven't been much of an anime guy, especially like a year ago.
I didn't...almost, like, the vast majority of percentage of everything I know about anime
was just things you'd talked about.
I've just not been a person who just hangs out all day in communities in general,
so I'm not a person who just knows all the spoilers of anything I'm into.
I got bored of the typical run-of-the-mill boilerplate internet communities a long time ago.
I stopped even being like that with video games a long time ago,
and so I just don't know...I know very few basic things about anime,
but I know a bunch of really obscure stuff only because of listening to all of your content.
Well, at this point, you definitely know more than the average anime fan,
even just by watching my videos.
I mean, a lot of my videos are about a thing that I feel like no one knows,
and therefore everyone needs to, and I think it's more important than all the knowledge they have.
Like, the video that was a...what's it called?
Like, the one about different aspects of visual design and, like, how...
Oh, yeah, that's a great video.
What's that video called? Do you remember?
How to define the quote in quotes, best-looking anime.
That's the kind of video that I feel, like, that was born out of years and years of frustration
of watching people not know how to talk about visuals in anime,
and I still don't think anybody does.
Hey, just talk about that video for a bit while I go to the bathroom.
I have headphones that go all the way to the bathroom,
so I can hear all of what you say.
I still don't think anybody fully gets out of talk about visuals
because there's so many different elements to it,
and I think that people look at anime and they say,
alright, you've got story, characters, animation, sound,
and, you know, the personal enjoyment factor, and that's it.
And it's like, no, it's not that because it's not just the visuals,
it's the character designs, it's the setting design, it's the backgrounds,
it's the animation itself, it's the directing, the staging,
like, all of those are all layers that can add something to the story,
where if there's a show that has great animation
and somehow shitty character designs and backgrounds,
then it doesn't resonate with you as much as a show that has all of those things good.
So I think that it's a widely misunderstood phenomenon
and so many reviews don't get it right,
and I've yet to see a channel that I think is good at it,
other than myself, at talking about all the different design elements
and breaking it all down,
which is part of what's been fun about this video that Davoo's editing for me right now,
which is the Steins Gate, like, an analysis of the first episode of Steins Gate,
where I really do talk about, like, every single element,
even if it's only in brief, like, you know, for the character designs, I'm just like, they're gorgeous.
But, you know, I talk about the way that shots are composed, the way the color design is done,
the way that everything feels.
Actually, I talk more about the character designs than I just said,
because I talk about how they look realistic and how that affects the tone of the series.
So, yeah, there's so many different little elements that can all contribute,
and by way of Davoo having seen that video and, you know, editing the Steins Gate one,
he now has the capability to talk about all of those same factors,
and so I feel like, for me, I'm waiting for the day
when Davoo watches a show and writes an analysis video
that's, like, better than anyone else other than mine,
because I think that he already has the tools, like, you know,
he has an understanding of what anime can be
and what makes a good show that is, you know, second only to mine,
but then it's just a matter of having enough context to watch a 10 out of 10
and know what the difference is because you've seen everything in between, you know.
Well, hey, you know, context. I watched Pany Pony Dash,
and it makes a bunch of references to all sorts of things,
including a lot of really obscure NES games,
of which I recognized all of them because of NES Quest,
and I was like, whoa, context, anomaly, paradox, whoa, it was so cool.
All these really lame NES games, I only played for five minutes,
or watched my brother play for five minutes,
and I recognized all of them in the background of Pany Pony Dash.
I'm like, whoa, mindfuck.
Yeah, interesting. I probably didn't get most of those myself.
Yeah.
And now I can give you an extra piece of context,
which is that Pany Pony Dash was, like, co-directed by Akiyuki Shinbo and Shin Onuma,
you know who both of those guys are from my videos.
You do know who they both are, right?
Well, I know Shinbo. I can't remember which guy Shin Onuma is.
Which one?
One of your best edited videos that you've done.
Just tell me. Just tell me. I can't remember the name connected with the thing.
Chivalry of a Filled Knight.
Oh, okay, yeah, yeah, cool.
The guy who basically runs Silver Link Studio,
but before he left to go form Silver Link, he was with Shaft,
and he trained under Shinbo, and...
Yeah, I knew it was a Shinbo thing.
Yeah, and Pany Pony Dash was like the...
I think that was like the first show that he was like a full directorial position on with Shinbo.
But according to the liner notes that came with the DVDs,
all of the video game references are Shin Onuma's thing.
Like, he's...
Because Shinbo's old and probably doesn't know shit about video games,
but Onuma's a gamer from back in the day.
I see, yeah, yeah.
I was thinking, watching Hitamara Sketch and Zetsubo Sensei and Pany Pony Dash,
all of those I've seen now, and I'm like,
man, you know, this kind of style could totally be like a pop video game review series,
this style of directing, where you could throw together stuff
that just is all about having crazy backgrounds and a bunch of weird frames.
Kind of like a...
Shinbo-ify Zero Punctuation.
That could be like a new format to talk about all the new big games that come out for five minutes
in a memorable, funny way.
Because the thing about that style is that you can be profound only as much or as little as you need to be.
Whereas Zetsubo Sensei can sometimes make an interesting point and sometimes be total nonsense,
and it works either way because of the way it's thrown together.
That's something I thought was cool.
So if I was doing video game videos, I was thinking like,
oh man, maybe I should do that, but I'm not.
That would be pretty interesting.
And I was just thinking about, to give you context into how much context you have,
I'm thinking about how when I started anime blogging in 2007,
it was at an era when I was starting to care about creators a lot,
and Shinbo was the first director I became like a big fan of and knew his work.
And I know it was that I had seen like a few episodes of The Soul Taker when I was younger.
And then Hitamari Sketch, I was watching while it was airing,
but I only saw like five or six episodes because it was taking a long time to get subbed.
Then Sayonara Zetsubo Sensei started and I saw like five episodes because it was taking a fucking year to get subbed.
And by then I was calling myself a big Akiyuki Shinbo fan and writing about him all the time.
And then Pantypony Dash, I watched it not long after that.
So you've already seen more Shinbo than I had seen at a time when I was talking about Shinbo at a level that no one else understood him.
Like no one knew who he was.
And I was like a huge fan and I was like, oh Shinbo is like this, this is what his style is like.
And you've already seen more of his work than I had at that time.
So that's why I think, you know, it's like you have a funny perspective because you edit for me
and most of your exposure to anime is from me and I know more than almost anybody, you know.
Like there's, I can count on two hands the number of people who I've heard of who know more than I do about anime, you know.
And most of them aren't doing YouTube, none of them are doing YouTube.
Yeah, that was something that I definitely like recognized in you pretty early on.
Definitely when I listened to your old podcast where like you'd be talking about something unrelated to Brandon Tolentino
and then all of a sudden you'd be talking about anime for 45 minutes non-stop with like perfect mental clarity.
And I'm like, I think this guy like knows everything about anime.
You know, like I definitely put a lot of, it seems like a lot, like some people don't necessarily put that much faith in your knowledge immediately
or they don't care, but like I feel like I was pretty good at recognizing that immediately.
Yeah, like everyone like has like anime that they watched when they like, you know, on Adult Swimmer or on like Toonami.
I didn't, I wasn't watching any of those. Like I don't even have that like rudimentary experience.
I just watched like a couple of really random stuff before actually trying to watch anime.
I didn't watch any of the, you know, the Naruto stuff.
But like most of those people who grew up on like, you know, a few Adult Swim shows that they really loved have no breadth of knowledge.
Like they know those shows and that's it.
And there's a lot of people who, like if I took someone like, let's say the YouTuber Jacksblade, who is a fitness workout guy,
who is a die-hard Dragon Ball Z fan, he knows everything you could possibly know about Dragon Ball Z.
And there's probably like 10 shows that he's super into and has seen multiple times.
Like, you know, Yu-Yu Hakusho, he was big into Attack on Titan when that came out.
He's probably seen all of One Piece, like he's seen all the basic stuff.
That guy would definitely call himself a big anime fan.
You know, he has a lot of collection, he dresses in the costumes.
But I doubt highly that he's seen as many different shows as you have at this point.
Because you've watched like, what, 10 shows since this fucking month started?
And that's more than most people watch in a year or two, like most casual anime fans.
So I think that you've probably seen more than most of my audience at this point.
With the exception of the ones who are the big fans who've probably fucking seen everything, you know.
And there's really like, there's only so many.
Like, you've been watching a lot of obscure stuff because I like it.
And that, like stuff that I want to eventually talk about.
Like, Pantypony Dash will never come up in conversation unless I bring it up in conversation, you know.
But like, as soon as you watch-
I brought it up in conversation on NesQuest to talk about how NesQuest allowed me to know all the games on Pantypony Dash.
I mean, in like a-
Yeah, actual conversation.
In the YouTube sphere, you know.
You're not going to see another YouTuber make a video about it unless it's someone talking about how they found this weird obscure hidden gem that no one talks about, you know.
Yeah, you definitely talk about anime as though it's like all part of the same narrative.
Yeah.
It's all there.
It's all on the same level of existence.
Oh, you just- thank you.
That's the perfect way to put it.
There's not like this other weird thing that's like different from the rest of the flock.
It's just like some things that no one's heard of but you and things that people-
You know, there's only one video on your channel where you're like,
Hey guys, I went to FYE and found something I'd never heard of before.
But then by the end you're like, oh, so that's show.
Yeah, okay.
I guess it's like differences in scale versus differences in kind kind of thing.
Like where most anime fans, I think they have this perspective of like,
I think most people don't realize that there's thousands of anime.
I think that's the first thing that most people don't get is that there are thousands of anime in existence.
And that's what makes it exciting to watch, to know that there's so many to watch.
Actually, it's like the daringness of the challenge of watching all the anime is part of what makes me want to do.
If there were way fewer anime, I would not have nearly as much inspiration.
It's the same thing with NesQuest actually, because after we'd played like a couple hundred games,
my brother was like, so I guess I don't know if I want to finish this project.
There's probably only like 50 games left, right?
I'm like, no, we've gotten about 10% done.
He's like, oh dude, we gotta finish this.
There's like a thousand NES games to play.
Exactly.
Knowing that the challenge is we do things not because they're easy, but because they are hard.
Yeah.
Plus it makes it exciting.
And with anime, it's like, you have to first realize, like let's say, let's just spitball here.
Let's say that there's 4,000 anime that have ever been subtitled.
Let's try that as a random number.
And then let's say that 2,000 of those are definitely worth a look.
And that 1,000 of those are definitely worth finishing.
Then most people's perspective of anime is the ones they've heard of are the ones that exist.
I don't think most people look at anime and think, oh, well, there's definitely thousands more where that came from.
They watch all the shows that are on TUNAMI.
And then when they find out about another show that they hadn't heard talked about, they're like, what is this?
What's this treasure?
I'm just now realizing that I've actually, for a long time, had the perspective that there were 1,000 anime because of one specific event.
Because whenever I wanted to listen to video game soundtracks, at the time, the best resource was KHInsiderDownloads, right?
Because it has this pretty, I think even today, the closest to complete list of all video game soundtracks.
And then at one point, they opened up an anime section like Download Anime.
It wasn't even like Torrance.
It was just download them from the website.
I didn't know how to Torrance.
If I had known how to Torrance, I probably would have watched some anime.
If I had had anyone give me anime recommendations that were like, because I wanted to get into anime.
It's just that all the people who watched anime weren't hardcore into it who were going to force it on me.
So I just didn't get into it that much.
Didn't have anyone recommending me stuff in a way that resonated with me.
And of course, most of all, I didn't buy into illegalizing things until a couple of years ago.
You always use that word.
Yeah.
And my dad is like, are you sure you want to get your Adobe products wrong through pirating?
Don't even want God's blessing on your work.
And I'm like, I was like that for up until a couple of years ago and I completely regret it.
Everyone says you get talent from the devil, not from God.
So yeah, they opened up an anime section.
And so I looked at the list.
You can just look at all the ones that are on the list.
And I noticed how many flicks of my index finger on the wheel scroller took to get to the bottom of that.
I just like, whoa.
And so I guess I've just always had this idea that there is a million shows.
So I guess that was something that I've just always known.
I didn't know which one to click on.
I just clicked on, what's this?
Twinlove.
I'll click on that.
Watched four episodes of that and wasn't that interested.
Yeah, so that's how I've watched four episodes of Food to Koi randomly five years ago.
But not Food to Koi alternative.
Not even the alternative version.
So that's like, I'd say that if there's two things, no.
Here's the holy trinity of anime knowledge that if everyone had it, they would all see anime the way that me and you now do.
I've just come up with this.
The first one is like I was saying earlier, understanding all the different components of it.
Because I think so many people, you know, think of it in terms of just like five things, story, animation, whatever.
Knowing all the components of it, knowing how much of it there is and the fact that it's this big, deep, you know, rabbit hole of media.
And the third one is knowing how incestuous it is and knowing that it's the same fucking people making all of it.
Because when you have that weird, like because you were saying that I see it all as like kind of equal and like it's all on the same plane.
And the reason I see it that way is that the same people are making it.
Where from my perspective, the reason I've heard of Pantypony Dash or Hitamari Sketch or Sayonara Zetsubo Sensei is because I've heard of Akiyuki Shinbo.
And I was a fan of him, so I sought out all his work.
Now, at some point in 2009 to 2011, this crazy thing happened where he directed a show called Bakemonogatari and then a show called Madoka Magica.
And those became the two highest selling anime of all time when they came out.
And everyone's heard of them and everyone knows about them.
But none of those people know who Akiyuki Shinbo is.
So none of them went back and watched his previous work and found out about all this other shit that he'd done.
So like from their perspective, like Madoka's this show that everyone knows.
Yeah, it's Madoka. Everybody knows Madoka.
And then Pantypony Dash is what's this weird thing I found?
And it's like it's the same guy. It's just like five years later.
It's like a drop in the bucket of a lifelong career, you know, that he did these two shows.
So yeah, I think that's why I see them all as equal.
And at this point, this has become a conversation and not an interview, but...
Yeah, whatever, you know.
I've just been like looking at Sakugoboro while talking.
You know, I got the, I just hit random.
I got the building explosion from Zankiyono Terror.
I don't know why I pronounce all these shows so weirdly.
That's how you pronounce it.
And I found out that...
Okay, then I found out there's a tag on Sakugoboro called Seven Years Hand Drawn.
And it's just like...
Is it just Red Line? Like, is that...
It's just Red Line and I think like the Tale of Princess Kaguya and Third Aerial Girls Squad.
Okay, interesting.
I love that that's a tag.
That's gotta be a meme tag or something.
That's fucking hilarious.
So yeah, you've got, you love you some Sakugoboro, yeah?
Yeah, I've looked at it quite a bit, you know, I need to...
I don't know, it's just I want to be able to like do...
When you need to compulsively click on an internet website,
but you don't want it to be a social media which feels unfulfilling most of the time.
You know, you can click on that and get cool animation.
So I made it to where the random page is the page like that I got on my bookmarks.
So I clicked on that.
That's how I got a much better understanding of what is a good animation.
Yeah.
That was something I did not have a grasp on until recently.
Yeah, that was one of the harder things in the early editing was I would say something like,
you know, a lot of this episode looks like shit and then you would pick a moment that didn't look that shitty to me or like...
Yeah.
And I'm like, oh no, you gotta like re...
You'll know it, you'll learn one day what shit, like when you've seen enough good,
then the shit starts to really become apparent, you know?
Yeah.
Or the big one was in Astroscore part one when I...
Yeah, I didn't show it.
We said like, oh, there's some great stuff from the OVA of Black Rock Shooter.
There's some clip cuts that are really stellar and I just put one in that wasn't stellar.
So you're like, here, here's the stellar one.
Well, just then it happened that part of it was done by my favorite animator, Utaka Nakamura.
And I was like, that's the clip I wanted you to show.
And I guess I just thought it would be obvious, but I should have fucking said something.
But I think I can do it now.
I think I know what is a good, because I go on looking at the seven years hand drawn tab.
I wanted to say you seem to be someone who even more so than myself, I think, correct me if I'm wrong,
seems to care a lot about aesthetics or have a deeper appreciation for it than most people.
Yeah.
Yeah, most people I'd say.
I'm not sure about you.
Well, because you have this...
Your favorite anime is Kill Law Kill.
And you've watched almost everything else.
I've given a 10 out of 10 and nothing has touched Kill Law Kill
because it has this raw aesthetic resonance with you in a way.
How are we?
I stopped caring about the story a while ago or the characters.
And then sometimes I'm like, is this my favorite anime?
I don't know.
And so I watched part of it and I was like, yes.
Because there's this one Kill Law Kill video that you wrote and you might make someday
and it's about one particular moment from the show, the part where the ditzy girl shows up with the other half of the scissor blade.
How are we new?
And it's just like, I watched that part of the show and I'm like, oh my god.
The moment when Ryuko witnesses the other half of the scissor blade, the shot that they use is this really weird angle of her
covering up the bottom right corner of the screen and her face is really blown out of proportion.
And you only see her eyes and there's a whole lot of detail on her skin.
And when I was looking at that, I was like, this looks like one of those meme faces.
It's like from 4chan where they put away heavy amount of detail on the face skin.
It's like one of those things and it just happens for like half a second.
And every moment in the show has a different thing that adds so much impact.
I would say I do care a lot about aesthetics.
It's just that what aesthetics I've been focusing on has changed recently because for a while I was really into prettiness.
What's a good color palette?
I spent so much time making color palettes because I made a video game once and I had a lot of color palettes.
So I spent so much time picking colors for things.
I think I just get colors now.
There's not a whole lot more to get in my haughty opinion.
If you read Cucumber Quest, that comic has every color palette ever and done really well.
So I got tired of colors and a lot of this is reflected in my editing of your videos.
The early stuff was I was trying to make sure that things were always pretty at all times,
which is why I sometimes fail at showing shitty scenes.
Because I just wanted everything to look nice and feel crisp.
But then there was at some point, I think I was definitely influenced a lot by Jesse,
whose editing is never pretty, but a lot of times has a whole lot of impact.
And that's really the word I've been going for lately is impact.
How can you have something that you can feel with just the right amount of visual information,
which is actual directing.
Once you understand that, you're getting into...
Wait, hold on. Did you listen to Jesse's interview with me?
No.
He describes exactly what you're saying in the same terms.
I am a Jesse knowledge person.
Because he was saying how his favorite aspect of doing videos is the directing aspect,
and that his favorite thing is to make a shot that perfectly encompasses the entire idea of the video in one shot.
Oh yeah, and also every frame, a painting was also really influential.
To everyone, obviously, he's changed the world of people who aren't educated.
And I think the part when he talks about Satoshi Kone,
and how Satoshi Kone will remove visual information, that's why he liked animation,
because you could have a purse hit someone's face in two frames,
and you can tell it's a purse because it's drawn.
But if it were live action purse, you wouldn't be able to identify it as a purse.
Oh yeah, and you were talking about this with Ben in his interview,
about having less information, creates more impact.
Obviously, all those old shaft shows I was watching has that,
where it's like, my favorite is in Hitamari's sketch, how they go up and down steps,
and the steps are just squares, just rectangles.
That's so cool.
And I'm like, man, if I make a video game, and you go up ladders,
I'm just going to do that because everyone hates going up ladders, it's so boring.
So you just click on it, have some rectangles, and then that's it.
We don't have a lot of money to animate things,
so how do we communicate everything without needing animation,
and they come up with all these really creative solutions?
It's genius.
It's great.
Yeah.
It's funny though, because Pantypony Dash has way more stuff going on than Hitamari's sketch does.
Hitamari is really minimalist.
Hitamari takes up in its later seasons.
I think it was really like, the first season was really like,
this is a show we don't expect anyone to watch, so it's very minimal.
If you watch the show they did before Pantypony Dash, which was Tsukuyomi Moon Phase,
that one is like, there was famously, I think it was episode 16 or something,
an episode that has literally zero animation in it.
It was so, they boiled it down so much, because they just had so little money and people to go on.
I've never known, people have always said budget, and of course,
that's the phrase that everyone throws around, and people always say that they quote unquote
blow all their money on the first episode, because usually the first episode of a shaft show will have,
especially if it's like a second season, will have way more animation,
and then the rest of it will be way more basic.
So what the heck do they do?
They blow their budget by hiring more people for the first episode,
or they just put way more of their time on the first episode?
Yeah, it doesn't make any sense, and so I think what it is, because I've heard before...
Digi, did we blow most of the Astroscore sucks budget on part nine, which was the best part?
Yeah, we definitely spent more on, well I guess I did, because I bought McDonald's,
so I spent the most money on that part.
Yeah, that is true, oh my gosh, never mind.
That's fucking great.
But yeah, the thing is they're also understaffed.
They've always been criminally understaffed, and I think it's...
Or maybe they're just lazy.
Yeah, I think it's just a matter of them not having enough people to get shit done on time,
and being terrible at scheduling, because with the Monogatari series,
there's two episodes that very infamously were completely unfinished when the show came out.
There's long sections where there's just nothing on screen.
They put up a frame that says missing frame, because they didn't have the frames animated.
But then when the Blu-rays came out, it's all there.
So the way I see it, and all those scenes are animated by the same guy.
So I think that guy just didn't have time to finish those scenes before the show went to air,
and they had no choice but to broadcast an unfinished product.
And then when the DVDs came out, then all this shit was there.
They don't have enough people. They're spreading their few animators thin.
And sure, it could be a budgetary problem that, like, why can't they hire more animators?
But it could also just be that they can't find people.
Maybe there's studios in a weird location, I don't know.
Kyoto Animation is like no one who works there works for anything else,
because they're in fucking Kyoto, and they hire local.
Yeah, you were saying before how anime is very incestuous.
And it's like, that's so cool.
In all of your videos, you'll be like, oh, by the way, this guy worked on that other thing.
And whenever you talk about the history of something or where it came from,
it's always this really cool revelation that really enhances a video.
So I was trying to do that with video games.
I found out how not true that is with video games.
At least back in the day, the majority of video game careers was a guy who needed a job.
And then he made like four games.
That's like the majority of people who've worked on video games,
at least up until the triple A proliferation.
Video game development cycles are way longer, too.
And they're huge. Yeah, they take the average video game cycle is 50 years.
It's just like, yeah.
It's funny, but yeah, I think, for me, it's always a revelation.
And I'm glad you enjoy those elements of the videos.
I feel like every time I talk about something like that,
I get the impression that most of the audience doesn't get why it's relevant or care, you know?
Because again, most people don't have the perspective that all of anime is connected and all that shit.
And that's why, because if it was, if I was watching a channel that's like my channel,
I would watch every video on that channel.
You watch every video on my channel.
You don't know what half the fucking shows are.
But there's a reason that some of my videos have 500,000 views and some of them have 5,000 views.
And it's because people don't care about every anime.
But to me, it enhances your understanding of the one to have seen the other.
The first Sakura compilation you did, which one was the first one?
It was the directors who had been animators before.
Oh yeah. And man, every single one of those, like pretty much, there were things that were similar about them.
Like one of the directors had a lot of lateral movements.
Like a character is flying at 50 miles an hour left or right.
And then like all of like Hiroyuki Imaishi's ones that you showed were like very prominently,
a character in the middle of the frame doing something that dominates all of the attention onto themselves.
And then like Hideyaki Yano overwhelmingly is a big wide-angle shot with like a bunch of stuff in the background,
mostly just background, getting destroyed in some way.
Either melting or blowing up or freezing over.
Just like a big background that happens.
A lot of animators have specialties, you know?
Yeah, all these directors have specialties.
And it's just like, every once in a while I'm reminded of the fact that I think animators are the best artists in terms of people.
Like if you think about like the percentage of artists who are dickholes, I think animators have the best track record.
Probably because they have no time to have a personality.
But like think about it, like who are like the asshole animators?
Hot diggity demon, Ralph Bakshi, but those are like lovable scumbags, right?
Yeah, I wouldn't say hot diggity demons.
I wouldn't say he's an asshole, he's just a weirdo, you know?
Yeah, okay, but like Ralph Bakshi is like this anti-hero guy, right?
But like he's also likable.
And it's like there's no one, there's no animators who are like Chris Brown.
Who are like, you know, even if you like the music, which no one does, like no one likes them as a person.
Every animator is like a decent person.
I feel like even like artists who like just draw pictures can sometimes be total dick.
What about Animated James? Didn't everybody hate on him for some reason?
I don't know, I'm not familiar with Animated James.
But like certainly good, oh yeah, but certainly like good animators.
I just think, I have a theory that to be able to animate, you have to have an empathy with the world.
And a level of empathy that makes it impossible to also be a bad person.
That's my theory, because I just think animators are the best people.
Interesting you say that, because that's kind of a Miyazaki's whole criticism of the anime industry is that they don't look at the world enough.
Yeah, they just look at other anime, but like I don't know, they still have to like look at something, you know?
I don't know, I feel like there's still an amount of understanding how the world is, how it moves.
If you want to be able to draw good, you want to be able to animate good.
I think it's more that the amount of time it takes to become a good animator and to do that job and make no money leaves you no time to do anything else other than animate.
Yeah, like the amount of dedication that the anime people have, like especially in Japan, where they just tirelessly animate for such low wages.
And it's like, man, these people just love what they're doing.
That's the scene in Shirobako episode like 24 when she's asking everybody why they're doing anime.
And they're like, I just kind of started and I like it, so here I am.
That's like almost everyone's answer to why anime.
And it's weird because like I've never heard of, I mean, I wouldn't know I don't look into this stuff myself, but I've never heard you talk about like really vicious, hateful feuds within the anime community.
Like, oh man, this guy hates that guy because he did the such and such.
Well, it's hard because there's not a lot of information and it's like I'm sure some of that exists, but also Japanese culture is to not be that way, you know?
Like probably the guy who's probably the most vicious person in all of anime is fucking Miyazaki, who supposedly like hated Tezuka, the fucking father of anime because of how he ruined animation by making it cheap and easy.
I don't remember where I heard this rumor and I haven't corroborated it with any information I've read elsewhere, but I heard supposedly that he got up at the funeral or the wake of Tezuka.
And like, the game of speech insulting him at his fucking funeral.
About ruining anime.
I don't know if that's true though, but like, yeah, that guy is-
The fact that you aren't sure it's true says a lot about Miyazaki.
Well, because he's also a man who mailed a samurai sword to fucking Disney that said no cuts on it.
And you know, constantly rails against it.
And like, is known for the fact that he's like a tyrannical leader of his own studio.
I know Miyazaki's full name by the way, I just slipped over the tongue because I was thinking about that cool video of him with Hideo Kiyono, like on a bench or in the desert.
Like, is that what anime directors do? They just go to the desert and just like stand there?
I've gotten the impression and I did not think this before I started making videos about directors all the time.
But I've come to this realization that anime directors seem to think that they are the fucking coolest people.
Because-
Because they're like, well, yeah, like they try to like stand in random directions.
Did you not notice they all wear sunglasses?
Every fucking anime director wears sunglasses.
And it was when we were putting together-
Because that's why, you know, in the Cowboy Bebop video, that thumbnail where it was the three faces, it was just like what the video gave us.
But it was the director and then Shoji Kawamori, who was the director of Macross.
And then Yoko Kano, the music producer, all of them wearing sunglasses.
It's a Victor like photoshopped them into like this three-headed monster.
And then like, we were editing that video and every fucking person we would find, the only picture would be them in sunglasses.
And I'm like, because at first I would find one or two and I'm like, I was like, oh yeah, I'm gonna pick the sunglasses.
When I want to make this guy look cool, then I realize they're all doing it, you know.
So I thought it was fucking hilarious.
And it's like just the directors, no one else.
They all have to wear sunglasses.
They all have to look like badasses, you know.
So I definitely think there's like a huge cult of personality element to it.
Yeah, they got a direct cool character doing cool things.
They got to be in that mindset, you know.
I remember how like in the days of Atari, the 2600,
a guy who had to make the Indiana Jones game or whatever, or something.
And he's like, so he had to become Indiana Jones.
And so he grabbed a whip and he just started whipping everyone.
He tried to like, he'd like pretend that the hallways were trapped.
So he'd like, like walk along the walls of the hallways without touching the floor, you know.
Yeah, yeah man.
So like, yeah, that's what you got to do to be an artist.
You got to like, get in the mindset of like what character you're gonna be, you know.
And like, I remember you saying that like they're, you know, anime is so incestuous.
That's why all the protagonists want to fuck their sisters.
Yeah.
I like, I love that logic.
I want to believe that's true.
Well, we've gotten onto a long tangent about how cool anime is,
but I feel like I've failed at interviewing you properly.
We got like two hours of like interview and then 40 minutes of we've been talking about it.
I don't know, I feel like, I think that's kind of in my failure too.
I've kind of not been like leading into talking like,
I haven't been like leading into talking about myself more.
Don't mistake me for not being as egotistical as Digi is or more.
I don't know, like it's debatable.
Well, I don't want to like, because the thing is with Jesse and Ben,
I got into a lot of details of their work.
And aside from your videos that you are deliberately distancing yourself from
and calling your old work, you've mostly been working on my videos.
And we talk about my videos in our long ass fucking commentaries, so...
Yeah, I guess that's what it is.
I don't want to start asking you about like the creative decisions you make
in the Astroscore videos or something when we've got a whole...
Oh yeah, we got a, we got a artificial scarcity of commentary.
We got to make people pay for that.
I guess it would be pointless to ask what's your favorite video of mine
because it's probably the Astroscore series.
My favorite video that I worked on too.
You cut out in the sentence there for me, so I didn't hear all the questions.
Yeah, I just said what's your favorite video of mine overall,
but it's probably the Astroscore.
Yeah, I'm going to say so.
I've completely lost ability to like evaluate it.
Like I don't like spend time just like rewatching all the stuff
and like marathoning it, and I don't spend a whole lot of time watching
anyone outside of the TPC anymore.
It just takes me forever to watch anyone.
So I've just, I've really been losing perspective of like how to...
Yeah, that's been really interesting for me because like, because you don't...
It's, it's, I'd say the biggest discrepancy between me and you at this point
is that I watch tons of YouTube and you seem to watch very little of it these days.
Yeah.
Which is interesting.
It's been that way.
Honestly, I've never like been watching a ton of people
because there's never been a ton of people that I like, although now there is,
but now I don't have the time for it, so, you know.
Well, it's just funny because it'll be like I'll get all inspired by some channel I've been watching
and then like...
And then you'll watch all of it.
Yeah, and then I feel like, like you don't even realize
and then I won't really realize like after a while
because I fucking forget why I wrote things away.
Well, I think it first really sank in when I found out about Noah Caldwell-Gervais.
Yeah.
And then I told you about him and I was like,
yeah, you know, I don't know, like I don't really recommend him that much
because he's like, he's not that good.
His videos are very long.
I haven't even watched any of his videos that much.
I've tried to listen to him at work.
I can't even finish listening to him.
As I described them, but Tosus dwarfingly long.
And so I told you about him and then like three days later,
you were like, so now that I've watched all of his videos,
I could definitely say it.
I'm like, well, hold on, what?
You know, I was like...
In his case, I didn't even really like them.
You just watched them.
He's never made one that I would like recommend to other people really.
And you just, you just watched all of them.
And I'm like, well, although I don't pay any fucking attention now
because he stopped being interesting.
Yeah.
So I'm just not that interested in watching all the YouTube.
You know, like I watch enough to where I know what's going on.
Like I watch enough nerd writer to know what I need to imitate.
Obviously, you know, fucking terrible.
I bet.
Um, it was like the kind of, it was bad in a way that made me mad.
Where I was like, I feel like a, you know, let me, let me just rant.
Let me just vent about nerd writer for one second.
Every nerd writer video ends with him saying, uh,
I had a lot of fun making this video.
It was a real blast to edit.
I got to do all these new techniques and thank you guys
for letting me have the opportunity.
And just once I want him to come out and be like,
this video was hell to edit.
Cause like some of it must be, right?
Cause he puts out a video every week.
Every week.
And obviously not all the scripts are of equal quality.
Not all the videos are of equal quality.
Some of them he has to like write something and realize it's not as good
or edit it and realize that the techniques didn't work as well as he thought they would.
Like, right?
There must be something.
And so like this week.
Yeah.
I've seen a lot of editing decisions in some of these videos that are like really awkward.
I'm like, huh.
And this week things that I probably wouldn't have let.
He did this video on a Bob Dylan song and it was like seven minutes long
and didn't sell me on any of the points he was making.
He was, he made all these grandiose points that, that, that he did.
Like I shouldn't say he made grandiose points.
He like suggested all these big ideas.
Yeah.
But.
Which is like the whole point of his channel is that everything he's saying is grandiose
and whether or not it like is like the only time he has said anything that really blew
me away with his Game of Thrones one where I was like, wow, that's really a good.
That's an amazing point that I love.
That's by far my favorite video of his.
Yeah.
That was a, that was a point that he sold me on like because he built it up so well.
He explained the idea of where the story comes from and how historical stuff happened
and why it's not happening in this story.
That makes sense.
Okay.
Cool.
It was about economics.
I was like the coolest thing.
I love that.
The Bob Dylan one is more like this.
He'll be like, this song, some people say that this song is an illusion to the Bible.
There's a bunch of Bible quotes on the album.
So it seems like it's probably true.
And then I'm like, you in no way justified the idea that this is a Bible thing.
And you see this is, that's why like when he first was coming out, he was first getting
big and I was like really ripping on him.
Like you were saying how cool he was.
And I was like, oh, this guy really pisses me off.
And I think it was because he didn't have that filter that I was always crippling myself
with where I was like, this isn't good enough.
This isn't good enough.
I've got to throw this out.
You know, and I just got the sense that nerd writer will come up with an idea, right?
And then make it like there's not that whole doubt period.
And I know that you are, you've always been way better at not doubting yourself to some
extent, but you have the doubt.
Okay.
No, no, no, no, no.
What I mean is you're better at working through the doubt sometimes.
Like you seem to be better at it.
Certainly better than me.
Maybe you're not great, but you're way better than me.
And so I was really jealous, you know, in a way of nerd writer's ability to just make
it anyway.
I definitely throw away way more than fucking nerd writer does.
Like I throw away lots and lots and lots and lots of concepts.
Like it's pretty, it's pretty clear that like he writes immediately what he has as an idea
and immediately starts working on it because how else could he have that kind of early
schedule?
Right.
Um, so that, that pissed me off at the time, but now that I'm not making my own videos,
I don't have, I don't have to feel that jealousy.
Like I'm, I'm, my content is your content and you come out with great stuff.
So I don't have to care anymore.
There was something very gratifying I got to do though, because my friend Trevor is a
very big Bob Dylan fan and him and Brandon Tolentino, who's also, you know, well versed
in Dylan, because I don't fucking care about Bob Dylan, but I, I sat them both down and
I showed them the video and I was like, I don't think this video is any good.
And they both ragged on it the whole time.
Like they were like seriously pissed off at like every point he was making, like refuting
some of the things he said and shit like that.
Um, just making it, like it was funny because they're not people who've like deeply researched
Bob Dylan, but I'm sure they've, there's like a long ass documentary they've both watched
on them.
And like there's just stuff in nerd writers video where he just presents something as
if it's fact when it's not really that much of a fact.
Like it's just kind of a suggestion, you know?
So yeah, I wonder if he only has so many ideas before he's going to burn up.
Hey, maybe he seems like someone who would have the ambition to be like, Hey guys, I'm
going to stop doing a video a week.
I'm going to like really work on one each month since I have since I have infinite money
right now.
I can just take a year off or something, you know, like, yeah.
And if this nerd writer discussion seems totally out of place in this interview, just know that
like a lot, a lot of what the PCP chat is, is us talking about YouTubers is by far the
biggest slice of the conversation pie.
Yeah.
Probably is the biggest.
And again, I, yeah, like, you know, and not just the shit talk them, but it's kind of
like talking shop.
It's like, yeah, I mean, I've, I've often made it very clear that I'm like a fucking vulture
when it comes to other people's ideas where I, I want anything I see that's good.
I want to take it into myself and make it a part of my powers.
And anything that's not good, I want to understand what I don't like about it so I can avoid
ever being that, you know.
So like nerd writer at his best, it's like, Oh, these editing techniques, like we have
to rip these off.
Like that was as soon as nerd writer appeared, it was like, we all felt like, Oh, we got to
step up.
And you know, I think a lot of the stuff that he was doing was stuff I was already doing
to some extent, but he definitely showed that it's a great way to do it.
So I started doing some of those things more often, but, you know, like he definitely,
he convinced me of that certain writing style being a way to go that you can take a detailed
image and then zoom into it slowly.
And that's good video for like 15 seconds.
Sometimes that he convinced me of that, you know.
Um, yeah.
So I guess this is, uh, yes.
Being annoyed by nerd writer's voice was something that I also was at the time, you know, because
I was just like, I didn't like, I just didn't like his, you know, like everything is so
serious.
But the thing you have to remember is that while Bob Dylan was sort of an experimental artist,
his vision pushed the way forward for all of music.
Hey guys, thanks for, uh, subscribing to my Patreon.
Oh, right.
And I was so pissed off at it.
I did actually do a parody of his style.
Oh, yeah.
Why we, uh, how weird Al is similar to Yoshi, which was.
Yeah, that was a different writer.
Yeah.
It was a parody of nerd writer and PBS idea channel simultaneously simultaneously.
Right.
So, uh, um, you know, uh, in regards to like not like getting mad at other channels, like
a lot of it was because like you'd be like saying how great they were.
Like two years ago, you were all about PBS idea channel.
I'm like, this guy's annoying and he, he sucks.
And you were like, uh, no, he's awesome.
And then like two years later, you're like, uh, made a lot of good videos, uh, back in
the day.
I don't know.
I mean, it may have just been, I wasn't prepared because his whole stylist at like say something
totally different than, uh, the video title suggests.
It wasn't always like that.
There was a time when even in the old videos, even in the videos that I watched like two
years ago, it was like this, this is, I don't know where this is going.
I don't understand.
Maybe I clicked all the wrong ones.
I don't know.
Um, there was definitely a time where he had, he had videos that had a topic and stuck to
the topic and, uh, and the topic wasn't just whatever is the current flavor of the week
in the internet.
Um, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
So here's the thing.
I was, I was kind of hesitant to talking about this super bunny hop because at some point
I realized that you, I found out that you considered super bunny hop to be like the best guy other
than you and Jesse.
Right.
And I was like, really?
Super bunny hop?
Like, I was just like, like, that's like the guy who makes like the most amazing videos.
Like, I know he makes the most good videos outside of you and Jesse, but I was like,
his videos were amazing.
Like, I just, I just didn't think any of his videos were like, like mind blowing to me.
Over time it became very frustrating.
Like why I couldn't see what the heck you see.
And I like, you even like ranked your favorite bunny hop videos, like the top 30.
And number five was the fitness games video.
And I'm like, what?
I just remember thinking that was just like a video.
I didn't think it was like a big deal.
So I watched it again and I was just like, blink, blink.
I don't know, man.
And something that like bothered me was like, after I had started working for you full time,
I was like, yeah, you know, thanks to my two videos, tightness versus slipperiness and platformers
and my Prince of Persia video, I've proven that if I were to do videos all the time,
I'd pretty much be the best guy doing video game analysis within half a year or so.
And you said, uh, I don't know.
I don't really see you topping bunny hop.
Do I sound like solid snake?
Oh, is that, is that a, is that a Digi Bro impression or is that a solid snake impression?
I don't know.
I just, I just wanted to say it very differently so that you, I don't know.
So that people would know that that's what you said.
And I was like, oh really?
What just, what, what does super bunny hop do that I couldn't do?
Because I also get the same sense from bunny hop that like he'll write something that I would have felt insecure about.
Like this isn't good enough.
This isn't right.
But he like makes it anyway.
And, you know, cause he's in the rhythm of making a video every week.
He doesn't have to like constantly doubt himself like I was like, oh man.
I just don't think he ever writes something fucking terrible.
You know, like we're nerd writers.
Well, I mean his, his, uh, his, uh, Lisa Undertale and their earthbound connection video was pretty crappy.
I'll say that's one of, that's definitely one of the worst videos he ever did.
And I, I get, I think that video wouldn't have come off so badly if Undertale hadn't become a huge success.
Like if that had been Undertale's introduction to the world kind of thing, then it would have been like okay.
But, uh, yeah, he said the least about that game.
If anyone who talked about it, probably.
Yes.
That like, but anyway, yeah, other than that, when all of his videos are all right.
And I just, I just don't like his, I am the most picky person about voiceover in the world.
I am the most annoyed by it.
And like him being all monotone really gets to me and makes it hard for me to like keep track of anything he's saying.
I just, it all just kind of, his, just all of his videos are just kind of white noise to me because of that.
Um, I, I, I mean, I, I have a problem with it sometimes because of the fact that sometimes he'll, he'll read a script about how good a game is in a tone that makes it sound like he wants to die.
And that could bother me sometimes, but I love his voice in general.
And I just, because his, there's like two voices.
Yeah.
Like all of my videos, all of my videos, especially old ones, by far, I can't deal with my own voice, like especially in my old videos, I didn't know how to carry my voice.
I hated it.
And I hated it when I was doing it.
It was torture, you know, um, and like a lot of Digi videos, like he has a lot of ones from like around 2015 where like you got really tired of voice acting or something.
And like a lot of them came off really stiff.
And I felt like really compromised the quality of a lot of your videos.
And, and like, like, um, some videos, I'm just like, there's no way I could edit with this because you're just going to have to redo the voice, man.
Or else I'm going to die.
Yeah.
And your, uh, details versus flow in manga panels, the original voiceover for that was so awkward for me that I couldn't even get the inspiration to do a good video out of it.
So like, I made this really boring version of the video that for me matched the audio and you were like, oh, this is boring.
And I'm like, yep.
So we redid that one.
Yeah.
It's worth people who, who are $5 patrons and who read all the behind the scenes posts will know this.
But, um, in the month, like at that video and then three of the ones we did in May were ones that I had written like six months prior.
And all of them we had, I had to redo the audio because I just did like a run of it and send it to DeVue.
And he was like, eh, and then he would like send me like a demo version of the video.
And I'm like, this is, this is fucking terrible.
I'm going to redo it.
You know, um, it was like details versus flow and the shima nets of video and the Ava 10, um, 10 directing tricks video.
Yeah.
Well, that one had to be different because like originally we weren't planning on it having all these pauses in the middle.
And, but it's like, if you want to have pauses, you have to read, you have to talk slower to begin with.
Um, yeah, it was after the details versus flow one where I, I realized I had to like say all of my criticisms of any post going into it.
Because before I didn't want to like bitch you out.
It's like, why not just do the video?
Like don't complain.
But because I didn't communicate my disc of my lack of enthusiasm, I ended up kind of wasting a bit of time making a boring version.
So ever since then, I've been more open, although since then you've only been writing new posts that are all amazing.
You know, like the, uh, you know, the, uh, the first, the whole Steins Gate video will probably be out by the time this is released.
Probably.
You think this will be released in six days, seven days?
I think I, I don't know, maybe I can get it done that time.
Who knows?
Let's hope so because then we can try to get two more out before the month is over and make some money.
Yeah.
But I was trying to write them already and, uh, instead of doing three hour interviews with, uh, you, um, yeah.
The bunny hop thing was funny because we really did like, are you over that for days?
And it's like, well, I eventually I was able to get you to say that like you, like if I were doing it full time on my own channel, I was after like a while, I'd probably like be around his level.
Or like at least make mostly as many interesting points as he does, but like with a slightly better, uh, delivery and presentation.
What I value out of a channel is like an even mix of interesting and frequent.
Like, like my channel is to me is the ultimate channel.
Like I want every YouTube channel to be mine because I'm doing everything I want a channel to be.
Like that's, I don't necessarily work as fast as I'd like to because sometimes I get uninspired.
But I think I agree with you that it's better to take two weeks to get inspired than it is to put out something shitty at the end of the week.
And in that regard, I am like, I don't think bunny hop releases anything that's outright garbage like what nerd writer just did with that fucking Bob Dylan video.
But I do think that bunny hop has had a lot of like simple reviews that maybe didn't need to come out.
And if he had spent that time working on something bigger, then I'd be happier.
And there's, there's obviously a reason he hasn't made a critical close up in two years because he's been doing weekly video since.
But he does get a lot of good, like he's done two, um, like videos on the Witcher DLC that are both, uh, like, I mean, I haven't played them in the like story discussions,
but they're really well written. There's a lot of like legitimate analysis in there that, uh, you know, it's like, wow, you got this out in a week.
I'm like impressed.
And as I, and as I said before, I did prove in that one window of time where I wasn't making any of your videos, I got out something every week and then some.
So I'm like, yeah, I could have done it.
But now I, once I got you to admit that I could be like, I don't care about like whether or not I'm the best guy.
It's just a matter of at, I just can't be like worse than people who I think I'm better than, you know.
So if I, once I was able to like convince you that I would be able to be at least on bunny hops level, then I'm like, okay, good.
I could now not do anything on my channel in peace except talk about trampolines and Dow Jones.
Part of the reason I say that is because you are a person who constantly improves.
You've always made better videos than your previous videos.
So there's no reason to believe that would stop being true.
You know, you're editing for me always gets better.
I'd say the 10, 10 best things happening in this decade was your best editing job to date.
And I'm glad you agree.
I didn't want to say that when I was making it.
I didn't want to like jinx it.
I'm very glad you felt that way because I did, I did think that like, yeah, I'm like, I've gotten good on the impact.
Cause what makes what I think, uh, it actually made me realize like just how much value there is in the right clip choice.
Like, you know, we think of, we tend to think of like, uh, cause historically when I give you a video and it's all just like finding a clip and putting it in place.
You've always had the mentality of like, that's the easier stuff.
It's the stuff when you have to like do the editing that it gets really hard, but there's so much value.
It's pretty much the opposite now.
I'm so good at, it's pretty dang easy to just have images flying in the screen and I try to avoid that now.
You know, if you can just do everything with a full screen clip as much as possible, that's usually better, you know.
And I think it was, it was really the first like, the first like 15 seconds of the video where it's just showing a bunch of clips from new shows that, uh, that I told you to put in there.
But you found like, you chose a clip from Space Dandy where it's like this stylish clip of him like putting his leg up on the dash and like it, it's like all dark and brooding looking and there's like flashing lights on it.
And I was like, whoa, that's a beautiful image from Space Dandy.
I don't even remember.
I don't know where you got it from.
I don't know what episode that was in.
It looked awesome, you know, and like all the clips you chose for the very beginning where like each one was the most, like the most beauty that you could capture in three seconds for a clip to be on screen.
And that was what impressed me so much about it, uh, like right off the bat.
And I was, and yeah, also in regards to like impact and like trying to get the aesthetic down, I've definitely been putting a lot of focus into finding the exact right frame on which to cut.
I had already been like kind of in that mentality for a while, but then every frame's new video about exactly that subject, like blew the lid open on that for me where I was like, oh my God, you're right.
Like the exact frame can make a huge world of difference.
Like, yeah.
So like that I've really been putting a lot of focus into that lately on how to like, and that, and that was like most of the like effect in that cowboy bebop video.
I think it's like cutting at the right moment in between sentences where like, like you cut in between words in between sentences at the beginning of a word, like in the, in the middle of a word, you know, that kind of stuff can really.
The video had a lot of flows.
And it was, it was interesting too, because so much of the bebop video was sentences that had no obvious clip to choose.
So the fact that it felt good, even though it was like, what the hell do you show here, you know, but it would always felt right to me.
I was, I never had a moment where I was like, all right, I don't care about the video aspect anymore.
I'm going to tab over it.
Like I always felt engrossed in it, you know.
So yeah, you've been doing good work.
And so that's why I say, like, you know, I don't necessarily think that if you made a million of the Prince of Persia video, like of that level, I don't think that would necessarily make it exceed bunny hop with him also.
Yeah, all of one type of video probably would not be as interesting overall.
But I think it was all about game feel.
I think you, if you were making videos consistently, they would always be getting better.
And you'd continually find new things to talk about.
And yeah, you could be one of the one of the best gaming YouTubers, but instead you're one of the best editors for an anime YouTuber.
And I still think, like I said earlier, that the day is going to come when you're going to want to write an anime video.
And I'm just going to put it on my fucking channel and fuck your channel.
And I'll just put it on my Patreon.
I know, like, don't care. My channel is just, like, whatever I put up on there, you know, like, debating with a commentary and stuff like that.
Do you remember the time that I offered to host your videos on my channel?
Yes, I do remember that. Because back when my channel was not getting any attention whatsoever, you were like, hey, you know how the game theory has, like, the editors make some of their own videos sometimes?
And yeah, that wouldn't have been a good idea.
Well, I'd still be up for it if you started making stuff that was, like, I don't know.
I even offered that to Victor at one point, because when he was, like, desperately trying to, like, last month when he had no work and he was like, I might start getting into YouTube and I'm like, hey, man, I got an anime channel.
Like, you make an anime video and I like it, I'll post it here.
Yeah, we'll see how that goes, you know.
So, yeah, but I no longer care about video games. I'm like, okay, no more video games, right?
Now I just play video games to, like, as a distraction for a bit or, like, to fill time or to, like, relax.
Yeah.
And now I'm just becoming a pure anime. Just pure anime in my face.
Alright.
And then, like, I've just been getting so into that, just become my existence. It's great. I like it a lot.
Davoo, we're getting up to three hours. I really pushed myself to make it to three hours, so it's gonna be the same length as all the others, even though my eyes are in searing pain.
And I actually, my nose is actually running now. My eyes hurt so much that it's making my nose run.
I don't know how that works. I mean, I was pretty drunk at the start of this. I'm not anymore. I'm just tired and beaten down.
But we made it to three hours, so do you have any closing comments or anything you want our audience to know about you?
Um...
The Collective will absorb you all Sunday. Be warned.
Alright. Well, that wraps up this interview with the Davoo. I don't know who the next one will be. Depends on who's awake when I decide I want to do it, which is how we decided it this time.
Thanks for being on Davoo, and thanks for listening, everybody.