I've been trying to get into beverages of all types. All shapes and sizes. Well, okay,
I guess beverages don't have any shape or size. They are liquid. But all types, you know.
As a child, I was really into milk, and I still am. But milk is like the thing I've
always been into. I always drink milk with every meal, pretty much. Very few things.
I don't think go best with milk, you know. Then when I was 16, I got into water. Didn't
like water before. But one time when I was 16, I got sick. And I felt better every time
I drank water. But then I stopped being sick and found out that water still makes you feel
better. So I did that. And then when I was a little bit older, I started getting into
tea because I often have a sore throat or an upset stomach. Partly because I think I
have like acid reflux, I think, because my dad has it. So I probably have some of that.
But a green tea cures sore throat and herbal tea, peppermint tea, sets your stomach. So
I just have herbal tea after like every meal. So I'm a big time tea guy. You know, then
I turned 21. I got into drinking a little bit. Then didn't really have anyone to drink
with though. But since moving here, I now have lots of people to drink with. So I've gotten
quite into that. Really gotten into white wine specifically. So easy to drink. It feels
all tasty. And then I get to have fun time. Yeah. And yeah, and I've also kind of been
into juice my whole life as well. You know, but sometimes I'll buy myself some juice. And
then I'll have that. So it's like, okay, you know, I drink water all the time. I always
have a cup of water with me. I drink milk with every meal. I drink tea after every meal.
And then sometimes just for the hell of it, I, you know, I drink alcohol sometimes. Sometimes
I just have a beer with me to get a little bit buzzed, you know, to focus my focus a
bit. And then, you know, I'll have the occasional cup of juice. I'm like, sweet. I'm into so
many beverages. Now one beverage I avoid is soda just because, like, you know, I'm not
a fan of the way it tastes. I've never really been into it. It just feels gross. And it
just feels like way too much sugar for me. And then of course, everyone says soda is
really unhealthy. So I'm like, okay, I will avoid it. I love soda. It gives me an opportunity
to feel so superior to normal civilization being like, Oh, that thing that everyone says
is bad for you. I don't even want it. I'm just naturally amazing. Although it sucks being
at a restaurant because, you know, most of the time the only thing you can get is soda
or sweet tea, which restaurants would serve milk. That'd be great. So yeah, I'm avoiding
soda and energy drinks. But then there's still one other beverage to get into, which is coffee.
Now growing up, I'd assume that coffee probably hurts your health or like slowly kills you
or something. Because I mean, if it gives you more energy, it must be taking away from
your life for us, right? But CGP Great has that whole video about how caffeine supposedly
doesn't have any negative side effects at all. So I'm like, Oh, I guess I'll get into
coffee at some point. So you know, like a year or two ago, occasionally I drink a cup
and I just didn't didn't really seem to have that much of an effect on me. So I would drink
like one cup every day. But then as the days went on, I just got more and more delirious,
not more energetic, just weird, like four days of coffee in a row. By the end of it, I was
just like running around me like, where am I? Who am I? I felt like someone could just
come up and stab me right through the chest. And I'd be like, you are stabbing me. I understand
you have attacked me. What is happening? Like I just felt like I just felt like numb to life
itself. So that was starting to be scary. So I held it off. But you know, nowadays, I really
just want to work super fast. I want to make videos super fast. I love I'm super romantically
into this idea of like sitting down and cranking some some project out in one session, right?
And I'm like, I can rarely do that without getting tired, at least at some point. So
I that coffee keeps sounding attractive to me. So I tried coffee the other day. And at
some point I started cataloging a timeline of how the day went. So I will now redo the
timeline. Okay, so I wake up, I believe at some point, I'm not quite sure on exactly the
time, but I woke up at some point. And did you had a video ready for me to edit? Like
he had recorded the audio for it and he linked me the script. So that's my cue to start making
it. But you know, I'll wait a couple hours before I get to it. So first, I, you know,
do some C++ tutorials again, you know, I'm still in decoding the stuff. And then I make
a six page list on a notebook listing off all of the must play video games that I haven't
played yet. So I do that. It takes me like two hours to write that down. Because I had
adapted it from a text document that I'd already made. But I wanted to get on a notebook and
tighten it up some so yeah, that took me two hours. Then I spent like two hours like watching
like, let's plays and summaries of some video games, you know, just to like, I was just curious
about it. So that was another two hours. Then I recorded a vlog about how many things I want
to do with my time with my life. I actually recorded that vlog twice. So that was basically
like a full hour I spent on that vlog. Then I sat down to get the log horizon video ready.
Before I can even make a video like that, I first have to convert all the files and stuff
to make it ready. Because when you download anime, it usually is an MKV file, but you
need to have an MP4. So you get a process of that. So I started that processing. Then
I spent like an hour or two like doing other stuff, uploading the video, the vlog. Then
I sat down to start making the log horizon video. And I got myself a cup of coffee. I
drank 500 milliliters of it like immediately, or two cups, right? So yeah, just this tall
stein filled with coffee. I drank the whole thing over the course of like probably 20
minutes. And I started very quickly feeling like total shit. I felt like all sickly and
gross and nihilistic as hell. And I started editing the video and I just, it wasn't even
feeling right. It felt like it was straight up making me not good at art. It made me feel
like I didn't even know what good clips it were in existence. I just felt like I'd lost
my touch even. So I just, I went away, I went into my room and started talking to a
squiggle. I have a squiggle now, and I talk to it sometimes. So, you know, started having
a conversation talking about how I feel like shit. And at some point, I'm like, all right,
better get back to this video. You know, started editing it again, kept working at it, feeling
weird. Ben comes into the room and I'm just like, Ben, what are you doing? Hey, I'm making
it. I'm trying coffee. I'm just feeling like a huge weird grumpy pants who doesn't even,
I didn't even feel like me anymore. So I'm just like hammering away at the video being
like, why doesn't this work on me? Why doesn't coffee work on me? Why doesn't coffee work?
Oh, it's been 10 hours. And then that's when I realized I had just been editing the video
for like all night long, nonstop, without even blinking, without even feeling slightly
tired. And I'm like, oh, this is where everything started to come together. Now, toward the end
of the video of making it, I started to almost pass out. I started to get totally dead tired.
So I'm like, oh, let's see if I can make this video in time. And so I finished the video
at 440pm. That's I'm able to calculate this because I can look at, you know, the file dates,
the dates of files. And I had made the video in about 11 hours straight. And I'm like,
yeah, sweet, it's a 10 minute video made in 11 hours. That's pretty fast. I was really
satisfied with that. And at this point, I somehow attained a second wind. I was no longer tired.
So I'm like, oh, so I go back into my room and talk to my squiggle some more, have this
huge dramatic conversation. Then I start singing a bunch of songs to the squiggle, like I just
play a bunch of music that I like, but but music where I've never actually looked up
the lyrics and I can't entirely sing along. So I learned some lyrics to some songs I like,
and I'm like, yeah, super satisfying. It's something I always want to do, but I never
take the time to do it. So then I go and wash some dishes in the kitchen and I make some
food for myself. Then me and Digi watch a movie together that we're planning on like
doing a video about. And it's a three hour movie. And over the course of it, I almost
passed out like a bunch of times. But then at some at some point, I somehow attain a
third wind. And the video ends, I mean, the movie ends and it's 10pm now. So I've been
awake for well over 24 hours at this point. I go into my room again, have a third intense
dramatic conversation with squiggle, like three conversations in one and one waking cycle
of mine. Then I talk to Digi about the movie some and we kind of are like, you know what,
let's not make a video about this movie. We changed our minds, but we talked about other
video project ideas. And then I start washing more dishes at around 1250am for 70 straight
minutes. So over the course of the next hour and 10 minutes, I finish washing all of the
dishes. And at this point, I'm like, how long have I been awake? So I go over and I look
at all the dates and the times of all the stuff on my computer. And I wrote out the
whole list of sequence of events that I've been reading to you so far. And that took
me like 30 minutes. So at this point, I'm like, okay, the power of this coffee so exponentially
outweighs that initial burst of anxious spiraling crumpiness that I have to drink coffee way
more often. And this was on only one cup. This is only one stein, a 500 milliliters
stein of coffee, approximately. I'm like, I still have so much energy. I'm not even
tired yet. I'm not even tired yet. So then I go and I do my laundry. Then I make some
more food. Then I then I relax for like three minutes, just laying on my bed and crushing
tiredness sweeps over me. So then I stand up and decide to brush my teeth. And then
suddenly the tiredness goes away. And I'm like, huh. So then I shower, shave, dry myself
off, and I rest for 15 minutes. So at this point, it's four 10am. I basically just rest
just so I can dry myself off more. I don't know. I can't even remember exactly. So it's
four 10am. I do the rest of the laundry. I do the rest of the laundry. So I've cleaned
so many things. I've cleaned all my clothes, all my frigging sheets, and all the towels
that everyone uses. And I put away all of the dishes too. I put away all the dishes once
they're all dried off. And it was the first time since living here that all the dishes
in my room in the house have been cleaned at this house. So it was an incredible moment.
And at this point, I'm wondering, I actually don't think I will become a coffee drinker
because I don't think I ever need to drink coffee again. I think that one cup was all
I needed. I've broken my sleeping mechanic. I've achieved the broken brilliance. I'll
never have to sleep again. Holy shit, this is the greatest thing. Then I start organizing
my room. Because, you know, my room was a mess. Halfway through, I start feeling bad
about it. I start feeling all down, crying for no reason. I guess just because I've been awake
for so long, I've become a weird bitch. So squiggle comforts me. I get back on the horse
and I finish organizing my room. And then I finish organizing my room at 8.40am. So it's
like, yeah, I'm moving slowly here. I am doing things slowly because I've been awake for so long
and I've become a weird, fragile person. But still, I was awake for about, for about like
44 hours. So just under two straight days of being awake. And it was this incredible moment of time.
And yeah, so that's interesting. I did fall asleep though. And I guess I'm probably just
gonna be randomly falling asleep all week. Anyway, I'm gonna try and talk softly here.
Hippo is asleep in my room on a inflatable mattress, six feet away from my microphone.
All the rad con guys are out there talking, probably shouting, screaming,
laughing. Don't know how much you guys can hear that. If you can, I'm sure it's totally
ruining the mood of this series. But you know, Hippo being a slave deer is forcing me to talk
softly. So hopefully that increases it. Or maybe makes it totally creepy. I don't know.
So yeah, you know, still doing the programming stuff. Still having a great time with that.
So cool. I have made a couple of like C++ programs. Mostly just stupid text things.
I'll put a link to them in the description so you can download them. If you use Windows,
they're simple exes. You know, it's just me to train myself and learn in programming stuff. But
I think I made a couple of funny little pieces of text. And you know, as I learned more and more
about programming, I immediately am taking the experience and knowledge I'd built up
in YouTube analysis to this new field. Because like there's one important thing that I've learned
as an analysis person and review person is that most people in any given field are not that good at
it, even among professionals. Because it's like I'm, I'm watching video tutorials about programming
and like lectures on the nature of programming. And I'm starting to get the sense of like,
how many of them are people who aren't really that good at what they do, but they are technically
professional. And like even, you know, comments and forum posts around the internet, and there's
people who like sound like they really know what they're doing. But you know, maybe they're they
know what they're doing, but what they're doing is garbage. So yeah, that's kind of, it's interesting.
Because you know, obviously, I literally don't know shit about it. But I'm already starting to
like get a feel for it, get a feel for like who the who are the people who I can respect are
in this situation. Because you know, with YouTube reviews, I mean, 90% of people I don't
wouldn't take seriously with their reviews, even if they are making money from it, even if they are,
even if they do have 100,000 subs and stuff, you know, like all the normal boots hidden block
people are people who I would not really go to for any wisdom on how to make videos, or telling
anyone to go to and learn from, except for like, basic production values and upload schedules,
and stuff like that. I mean, not counting Jean Tron, he's obviously a totally different animal
from everyone else in that field. But you know, so like, because the video that I'd mentioned
before about programming called object oriented programming is bad. I watched that video again,
and I watched its sequel videos, which are object oriented programming is embarrassing,
and object oriented programming is garbage. And it's like, man, this guy, Brian Will,
is smart. And I respect him deeply. He's so sure handed and, and just so subtly smugly derides other
other techniques and stuff, but like, just so just so competently, and, and clear headedly.
And I'd admit, he's really, really convinced me. And I know that a lot of I'm probably get a couple
comments being like, that are very like, sincere and like, well informed, telling me about, you're
like, well, I know he said this and this and this about object oriented programming, but you know,
this, this, this and this. And on one hand, I'm inclined to take you seriously because you know
more about comp coding than me. But on the other hand, I'm not like, I have to admit, like just
because you've you actually are a good programmer, I have to admit, I might not take you seriously.
I'm not, by the way, people who've commented before on the last one, I'm not referring to any of you.
I don't remember exactly. But I don't know, it's just it's just a weird thing,
feeling like I'm already judging people's skill at a field I have no skill in.
Yeah, I'm a pretty bad person. You know, it's funny, becoming successful in life has done
simultaneously good and bad things to my moral character. Because, you know, when I'm a depressed
teenager, I'm more inclined to lash out at people and be mad and grumpy. But now I'm not,
I don't really have any incentive to be grumpy at people. But I'm so satisfied with my self image
now that I don't care to not be grumpy to people, you know? I just like, I'm so satisfied and content
with what I've with the cool stuff I get to do all day, that I don't need the approval of people
at all. Like I'm someone who's rarely needed much approval from other people who I don't care about.
But that dependency is at an all time low with me, like I really don't give a shit.
So yeah, it's just, I feel like I've been becoming a weird asshole to people.
And I don't know, maybe I'll fix that at some point. I'll be like, you know what,
I'm gonna stop being an asshole this time. But I don't know. It's strange because
like, you know, I know Digi was saying similar stuff in one of his decompression chambers and
stuff like about, he doesn't think of himself as a great person. You know, he just thinks of
himself as maybe a strong five to a light six out of 10 on moral quality. I'd probably wreck
myself, you know, maybe a light to decent five, depending on who you are, how I'm treating you
specifically. But like, I feel like this is gonna be weird, but I'm sure almost, I'm sure there's
a lot of people who are gonna agree, but never really thought that they should say it, which is,
I value interesting people more than good people in the world. I mean, obviously, the more good
people the better. But I kind of just don't care. Like if someone is a great moral person who helps
people, I'm like, yes, I appreciate you. But you're not really doing anything to help me,
since I don't have cancer. I don't have being a starving African child disease. So you go off
and help them. That's great. You know, like, you know, at some point, if I ever have like,
if the time is right, maybe I'll do something to help you, you know, I do think you are valuable.
But I don't care, because you don't do anything that amuses me, you know, you're off in Africa
helping them, you know, I'm over here, you're not doing anything for me. So I don't really care,
you know, people who are interesting, educated and creative, and people who I can respect is
something that I want, that I want from people way more, you know, those are the kind of people
who I want to talk to or, or understand or research or that kind of stuff, you know.
Like all my life, all I've really wanted is just respect from people who I respect,
you know, like fame is cool and all, you know, people knowing about you is fine, although kind
of annoying too. But really, all I've wanted is just to be someone who is mentioned in a
retrospective of what was important about the world, you know, like this person came along,
took influence from these people who came before him, and then these people took influence from
him in this way. That's where I want to, that's, that's, that's my goal, man, that's, that's who I
want to be. But you know, I guess if you're a more nice person than you can be more respectable to,
that would probably help. I don't know, maybe, I don't know if I'm either underselling or
overselling the amount of assholeness I am. Guess that's for other people to judge.
Mwamp. Mwamp, that's a, that's supposed to be a horn sound, like mwamp, mwamp, mwamp.
Sometimes I'll type it in a chat, like someone will talk about something that was like derpy,
and I'll be like m-w-a-h-m-p, and they're like, wamp, what does that mean? I'm like, it's a freaking
horn, man. You know, when I started doing the programming stuff, I brought a chair back into
this room, and I started sitting at a chair. But it started to make my back hurt. After two weeks,
my back started to die. So I kind of gave up on that. I mean, I am sitting on a chair right now,
but I'm leaning forward. I'm not leaning back on the chair. That's what kills your back, slowly.
You know, I had mentioned before how I really liked the idea of making a video super fast,
which is what I did, you know, a 10-minute video in 11 hours. I'm really, really satisfied with that.
But it's really because making videos is harder than a lot of other mediums in a way,
where I could sit down and start drawing and just never stop, or I could sit down and make a video
game, or at least try to, and just never stop, you know? When I got into C++, I was like, wow,
I can just go at this all day with no breaks, or at least very, very few.
Whereas with editing video, it just feels like I have the need to get up
and do something all the time. I always feel at risk of getting distracted.
And it's strange. It feels like my work ethic is entirely different depending on what medium I'm
working in, and I've been trying to get to the bottom of that. And I feel like I've made some
progress on figuring it out. But okay, let's say there's two categories here. One category is
sort of a more abstract form of art, which is like you're drawing something that doesn't exist,
you're programming a video game, you know, which is entirely a simulation, or you're doing like this
more hard media stuff, where it's more high art in a way, where everything you're making is totally
purely created by your own hand. Then on the other side, there's more abstract, no, no, there's more
remix type of art, which, you know, editing videos is that you're taking this show that's
been made by someone else, and turning it into a different form, you know, you're re-editing it
into your own video. And also in this category, I would even put blog writing, like even the
process of writing a video like that. It's like you're taking the things that have been said in
this show, and then you're reinterpreting its meaning and its message and making it your own.
So even the writing process is very much like a remix of the writing of the thing.
And like even if you're blogging, like say you're just doing journalism, you know, that's also an
art form, but you're basically remixing life that way. So those are the two categories, right?
And I feel like the first category, the more high art, I'm not saying it's better necessarily,
it's just it's more, I'm just gonna use the word high because it just feels like the right word
to use, okay? Don't judge me. No, please judge me. But those mediums, it feels like it takes more of
my focus, it takes more of my, it takes all of me, you know, to make something like that, to draw a
thing, takes all of my soul, and the whole world around me doesn't matter anymore. Everything goes
black around me. And it's just me and my friggin' chisel and my chunk of stone and I'm making the
thing chiseling away at it until it's done and nothing can slow me down. Meanwhile with editing,
like a lot of the, of editing and making videos like that depends on like being culturally aware,
you know? That's a, that's a medium that's very much about like feeling connected to the
life stream of the culture around you, you know? You have to feel the world at all times
in order to like be good at it. So I, like, I can't phase out the world around me. I become more
one with the world around me. And when you're in that state of mind, you just get distracted more
easily. Or at least, I say you, but I mean me, okay? Like, yeah, the whole time I've been making videos,
it's like, you have to take breaks. You have to hang out on the internet in order to like be in
the right mental state to be able to make a video like that. And I don't know why that is.
Because back when I was making that RPG, I could just, I could just shut myself out from the world
completely and never lose my touch, or at least I felt that way, you know? So that's a weird thing
like that. And that's, and that's why it's harder for me to stay focused when editing videos.
Hopefully coffee will be my life hack to win the world. I will destroy everything with my new
don't need sleep power up. You know, I've always said I like the idea of sleep and I do find sleep
very satisfying. I just wish I didn't have to do nearly as much of it as I do. If it could be,
you go to sleep once every two to three days for three to five hours, that'd be ideal. No,
I don't know if that's medically possible, but if it were, that would be my favorite.
Well, that's, that's everything I had to say. I think it's been like a week since the last
episode of this show. So how about I just release it now? You know, it's only 30 minutes, but
that's what I'm going to do. Yeah. By the way, I'm going to change the titling system for this show.
Originally, I named the first episode like January or whatever, you know, gave it to date.
And then Nate came out with his solo podcast and also gave it a date. And did you was like,
actually, I was thinking you guys should just not have dates because that just gets confusing.
We can't have too many shows that are named after a date. That's just confusing. And I'm like,
I don't really know why, but okay, I might as well. So I think I'm just going to name these
episodes is like give them a title named after what I'm talking about. Not sure. I don't know what
I'm going to do about that. But yeah. Anyway, I got copyright detected on the song I'm using
on the last episode. But that may just be because I played two straight minutes of the song
with no talking over it. So I'm going to find out if I'm still going to get copyright detected,
even if I don't do the fade out. So yeah, unfortunately, this video is not going to end
with two straight minutes of just music, even though I really like that concept. So goodbye.