During RADCON 2, I think I overdosed on PCP. I really love these PC people. The most in
the world. They are the coolest people and the most interesting guys. But there's no
possible theoretical human who is so interesting that I want to hang out with seven of them for a
straight week. Constantly. It was hard actually. It was actually really surprising. Uh, because
there were so many fun things to do and so many fun times to be had, but then there were just so
many moments in the middle where suddenly it's like, uh, oh, I'm just sort of sitting here not
knowing what to do, being like, hmm, so I just kind of retreat back to my room and then just do
what I was doing normally, but this time way more distracted because I know there's people out there
and, you know, every five hours or so, or every 30 minutes, someone will be banging on my door
being like, hey, here's a fun thing you can do. And I'm like, you know what, I agree. And so I
could never get anything done. That, uh, that Digibro's Discuss Yuri on Ice video, for instance,
is a, I was working on that for like a week and a half, I think, because I spent like a whole week
just barely trudging through it over the course of days and days because I had nothing else to do
in between sitting around during Radcon, um, but I never was able to give it a good consecutive
session. So I just felt disorganized the whole time, you know? It was still good, totally worth it,
but it felt kind of burnt out. And I had like this moment of, gosh, am I slipping away from the
PCP? Am I like becoming a bad? Am I becoming shit? Am I like, does everyone, does everyone still value
me? Am I basically just being a parasite on this establishment? You know, I get, I feel like I've
been too worried about what, um, the other PCP people think of me, or rather I know this for a
fact. I think it's because my whole life, I've never given that much of a shit about what people
think about me. Like it's, it's, it's always been like, you know, if you're not related to me, then
the only thing that can make me like you, or like an absolute requirement for me, like caring about
you is you caring about me. And like, if you don't, if you don't like me and you don't approve of me,
then you don't matter to me. And I'm genuinely like that. And even people who I do like, I don't
value them so highly that like their opinion of me can make me seriously question, like instantly
question my own opinion of myself. But then, like all the PCP people are that, they're people who I
think are so good and interesting and good that things that they say can really affect me, like
inspire me and whatever. And if they say something like critical towards me, I'm like, oh no, no.
And like, you know, I take it too far and I'm trying to get over that hump stump. I don't know,
I think, I think, I think I'm fine now. I just don't, please don't give me advice on how to deal
with this problem I just stated. I have it under control. But I mean, it is true that like,
it does cause problems sometimes. Because yeah, I guess I just, I guess I just want to shock it
up to inexperience of giving a shit what people think about me. Like I'm so not used to it. I'm
so not accustomed. I'm so not accustomed to people saying things and me really caring immediately.
That it's like bothersome to me. You know, I'm trying to, I kind of have the gain up right now
to encourage me to talk more softly, but I'm just not good at talking softly. It makes me
awkward. So I'm going to turn the game down. Yeah. Yeah, don't don't don't get me wrong.
Well, did I turn, did I turn the game up? No. Yeah. Anyway, don't get me wrong. I had a great
rad con to it was a great experience and all, but it just, you know, it just had to kind of like
recover afterwards. And I was, I was kind of kind of in a depressive funk for a couple of days,
because I was feeling like I was pissing people off and stuff. And they're like,
but now I'm recovered. I, I was just like, you know what, no, this, this whole operation we're
doing is too good. It's the best thing ever. And I get to be a part of it. And it needs to happen.
It needs to work. I want it to work. And I want it to work well.
I value it extremely highly. I mean, the position I'm in now, which I know I talked about this in
the first episode of my show here, but the fact that doing Digi's videos doesn't take that much
time. And like, that's really the privilege of this job. Like it doesn't pay that much yet.
Like it pays like a normal amount of money. But the privilege is how little time it takes. And I
can spend all that time working on other things. And I have in fact continued to be consistently
working on programming. That's the main thing I've been doing still. I mean, I wasn't doing a lot of
it during Red Contour, but I am definitely getting back into it. And I just want to let you know
that like, yeah, every, every Patreon dollar that is coming through Digi and then going on to me,
I am using, I am really using all of my time. I am really maximizing my efficiency. Because
because it's a good way to live. I don't like being bored and I don't let myself be bored. Like,
again, I was in kind of a depressive funk for the last couple of days, rather the last like 36
hours. And I almost never liked that. In fact, I don't know if I've ever been exactly like that
until just now. And it was terrible. I was like, God, I can't get out of bed. This sucks not having
the motivation to get out of bed. So what I did was this is a hashtag life hack. If you can't get
out of bed, throw your phone somewhere else in the room so that you don't have it anymore. And the
only way to get it is to get up. That's how I, that's how I did it. Oh, God, I'm, I'm just like
springing back so hard from that funk. And I'm now I'm like so high again. Like, yeah, I know Digi
on his most recent episode, or at least in the first half of his most recent episode of his
decompression chamber is saying how like, you know, don't think that even though I'm having a
fun time making videos, I'm always having a fun time. I spend a lot of time being bored, he says.
And for me, that is just really not the case. I am, I'm wired all the time. That's why this show
was called it. That's why this show isn't named after letting go and like disperse. So it's named
after I specifically thought what's the opposite of decompression? What's the most intense compression?
What's the most intense collision that happens in the known universe that can be recreated by man?
And that was the idea of this show of the title anyway. But also the theory behind the show
is I don't really relax much. It's just fun being stuff all the time, you know.
Maybe, maybe I have some optimism chip programmed in me because I was raised to believe that there's
a God and everything will be great at the end. I don't know. For those who listen to all of the
apescape playthrough by peace by us on this channel, you'll probably know that I was saying
this before in that show, but to spin it in a much more positive way, I feel like on some
fundamental level, the way my perspective of the universe is wired is kind of, is kind of
programmed around the assumption that God is real and that like most of what the Bible says is
accurate and stuff. Even though I completely every second intellectually don't think that,
I feel like it still sort of affects, like it's still part, it's still intrinsic to my core
understanding of the universe. And so I guess that just kind of makes me optimistic. Maybe I'm
wrong though because that I should be at my core depressed because I'm not upholding Christian values
in my life. I mean, I mean, I'm kind of upholding most of the agreeable ones. I don't know. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. So I want to give you an update on my, my, I mean, on me becoming a hashtag code boy.
I finally figured out that C plus plus, I can kind of retire that one for now. Like it was,
it was useful learning programming through that. But I was thinking more about what specifically
my goals are, what my, what am I, what's my demand here. And really what I demand is,
is a, as a platform on which I can make a game or make a program 100% all manually by myself,
like where I'm in control of every detail, but where the details are not that obtuse and they
don't stack up to become that complicated. Because like all the ideas for games I have are nothing
mechanically revolutionary, right? I'm not like, well, specifically the main idea I'm thinking of,
I'm kind of running through it in my mind and I'm like, no, there's not going to be any
ridiculous programming challenge in this. Like it's all going to be basic stuff that already
exists in games, um, simple games, but reconfigured. So yeah, I'm confident that I don't need to become
incredibly amazing at detailed stuff. I just need to be organized and push on and stuff, you know,
you know, you know, you know. So a C plus plus, the problem is that just getting graphics on the
screen requires like downloading, like you have to build an engine for that, but like there's
ways to like have the engine built kind of for you sort of, but even that's kind of complicated.
You have to install SDL, which seems like a good program, but it's just every five minutes I run
into a thing where it's different for me than it was for the tutorial video that showed me how to
do it. So I was like, okay, I need to put this down. And like, so I was kind of, you know,
shifting around some, I looked at Game Maker again. And I was like, yeah, I can't do this,
because it's just, it's so, it's so much about menus, you know, menus that I didn't make. So I
don't feel like I'm completely in control. Like I know all the little twists and knobs, definitely
not into, um, drag and drop programming. And I mean, I know that you can make Game Maker without
using any drag and drop, you can do it entirely in GML, it's native programming language. But I'm
like, I just, I don't need this, I don't need these middle managers, you know, like every time I got
frustrated with C plus plus, I was like, you know what, fuck it, I'm going to go over to Godot. I'm
going to, I'm going to figure out that program. And before I even get like three minutes into a
tutorial, I'm like, I can't do this. I can't deal with like having my hand held by this other thing
that's trying to make it easier for me, because that just means I understand what I'm doing less.
So I finally got into Python. And I think that this is the, this is the, the sweet combination
of elements, the sweet spot that I've been looking for. Because I think it's, it's definitely centered
more towards people who are more simple minded, I think. I'm not, I'm not sure. Maybe I'm wrong.
I believe Google uses Python actually, so maybe not, but you know, it just seems like it's more
about being clear and like, like, sure, you have to do all the work manually. It is a programming
language, but it's more straightforward and like things are much more what they seem to, what they
look like at face value. There's no like sucker punches that you don't understand. I assume I
have barely just now scraped the surface of Python. So, you know, I'll see how that goes. But I, I
skipped ahead in some tutorials a bit, and it seems as though getting graphics on the screen is
more straightforward with it. I'm not sure though, but it, if nothing else, I can tell just by the
design of the graphics of all Python and Python accessories that they care more about aesthetics
and presentation and like smoothness and feeling good than C++ does. That's, that's kind of the
thing. Like C++, it always looks so dorky. It looks so like Windows 95, but hold the vapor wave,
where, and then like, meanwhile Java is like, well, you know, Java is universal and stuff,
but it's like, so I'm sure I could figure that out. But like the Java logo is so crappy looking
compared to other things. And like, and like the Java installer looks so ancient and cruddy. And I'm
like, for one thing, on the surface level, on phase value, it makes me feel less aesthetic. But
more importantly, if the Java people saw fit to make it this way, to let it look like this, then
they're not the kind of people who I think I can work with. They're not the kind of people who I
think designed something that I can understand. Because I think they just don't look and think
the same way I do. Um, yeah, doing all this coding, learning stuff has really made me
reconsider or made me consider more deeply for the first time. What is complexity? What is
complicatedness? Because I know those two words are actually different, complicated and complex.
Um, complex, I believe, means things that just has a lot of information. Complicated means the
information is confusing. It might be the other way around, but I'm pretty sure. Like, basically,
I think a lot of people have it backwards in terms of trying to simplify things,
or maybe I'm just weird, I don't know. But like, for example, imagine a list of a bunch of things,
a bunch of stuff on a list. And if it's a bunch of stuff, it's like, man, that's hard, that's
confusing, that's complicated, because there's so many things to remember. But meanwhile, I think
a comparatively small number of things that are like woven together in a very weird way
is more, is more difficult to learn. Like, the relationships between them
is harder to learn. Maybe it's an autism thing. Maybe I should get myself tested. I don't fucking
know. But the point is, I think people in general, I'm going to assume, are better at learning things
from a big drop-down list. Like, where every piece of information means the same kind of
things. Like, they have the same parameters, and they all relate to each other linearly.
Because that way you can like, it's like your brain can like, store a method for how to
take that information in, and you can apply that method each time to taking in each entry on the
list one by one. Meanwhile, if something is like, you know, only five or six things, but they're
all woven together with this complex web, you have to keep reformatting your brain in order to
take any information. And I think that reformatting your brain to make a new method is more difficult
than simply running an existing method. Now, obviously, both are different forms of learning
that are very enjoyable. You know, I'm just saying that one is harder than the other, which,
when successfully done, makes you feel even more satisfied. Like, it's sort of like the difference
between, you know, like watching a movie that like adds new elements to your friendly, familiar
format, and it's enjoyable and fresh and new for that reason versus a movie that, you know,
challenges what your definition of a movie even is, which is, you know, it can be even more exciting,
but maybe less enjoyable, who knows. So I feel like with object-oriented programming, I feel
like that's the mistake that people are making, or at least the mistake I made. You know, I don't
want to speak for anyone else because I haven't done a lot of programming. I mean, I've done a
decent amount. I did make half of an RPG, but, you know, I'm not super experienced. I haven't like
watched other people extensively. So I don't want to speak on anyone else's behalf, but on my own
behalf, I feel like what I was trying to do was to try to reduce the size of the list of how many
things to know by weaving them together in this tight package so that it would look smaller on
paper, like it would all be intricately woven, and therefore it's all organized and everything
connects. But connections are difficult to keep track of, and that if I just had the discipline
of just, you know, grind down until you're done with the list, then you did it. You know, just
study and practice. Basically, that's what it is. It's the difference between study and practice
versus trying to come up with a new method to cheat your way around it or get it more easily.
You know, you need both in your life, but, you know, keep in mind when one is appropriate and
the other is not appropriate. Yes, yes, yes. Going back to the whole, you know, feeling like I'm
falling apart from the PCP, which I no longer do. That's just, you know, sometimes an emo
bullshit, like feeling sometimes, which, you know, I think I won't have anymore. I'm gonna be perfect
from now on. But like, I guess I get afraid of that because I feel like I've been like that in
the past. I feel like as a kid, I was always like that because I've just, there just weren't people
who I liked enough to give a shit, you know? Like, again, you know, I was homeschooled and all,
but I had plenty of social interaction. Just like not, I guess most people in life, you're either
forced to hang out with the same people all the time because of school, so you just have to
fucking deal with it. Or you find people who you like and you can retreat into them, you know?
So I guess the difference is that I didn't have that forced to be around people who I don't want
to be around. Like I could just, in my life was, my life has always, has always been pretty dang
modular. You know, I've always been able to do what I wanted to and work on what I wanted to.
So I guess the positive is that, that it makes me like really accustomed to the idea of just being
like, hey, I'm gonna, I just decided to jump on YouTube and it's, it's pretty easy for me to just
suddenly start devoting all my time to it or suddenly start devoting all my time to one thing
or another because I've never, never been constrained by, you know, the schooling method
because it's like if you do homeschooling, you can just, you can kind of crank out the work
pretty quickly. And yeah, I mean, it depends on your parents, but that's kind of how it was for me.
You know, I did a, I did a pretty mediocre to bad job with schooling, which I, if I had gone
to a public school, I would have done almost certainly the same bad job, but over a much longer
period of time stretched out over the course of every day. Whereas, you know,
at home, it was just a couple hours of feeling like I'm shitting around and being stupid.
But yeah, my point is, yeah, like the benefit that the pro is that I always felt able to just
like jump on something and just start doing it. And I've just, it's easy for me to have the focus
on things that I want to do. But the downside is there are a lot of things that you're sort of
supposed to go through as a frustration in life that I just avoid. I don't know, maybe that's,
I guess that's also a pro, but you know, it just, it just means that there are certain things that
like I never had to deal with as a child. And like part of it is having to hang out with the same
people who you hate all the time. If there were people who I hated, I could just stop hanging
out with them. But yeah, like there was, um, there was one church I went to from like ages 10,
11 through 12 that my parents went to this church and like they got bored of it and they left.
Like, I guess I get my misanthropy from my dad who always, you know, associates himself with
people and then like disconnects from them and eventually leaves. I feel like that would have
been my life if I hadn't discovered the, the, the, the pro crest and praetors people
who are people who I can like respect consistently and never get tired of,
except during ride gone to a little tiny bit. But anyway, that's beside the point.
Like anyway, in this church, like before my parents decided we should stop going there,
like, you know, they have a youth group thingy or like a tween group or whatever it was. And like,
I liked doing it because I liked being in there more than the adult church, because like it was
a small room where there was more audience participation and it was more direct to direct
to indirect. It wasn't like sitting in a giant auditorium and having a guy lecture you for three
hours, which by the way, I don't know if I remember, I remember one time I had a Catholic
friend on the internet who went to like a Baptist church one, one Sunday and he'd never realized
that like most churches that aren't Catholic, the sermons are like three hours long. I'm not
kidding. Apparently in Catholicism sermons are really short because the Catholics are like really
good at actually making their religion aesthetic and enjoyable on some level, I guess. Anyway,
yeah, so like three hours sermon with the adults and I was just like, this is terribly boring,
I hate it. But if, you know, with the youth group, I can at least feel more involved, you know, and
that's nice. But what really frustrated me is that like, like they would often be like, you know
what, we actually want the youth group to be with the adults this time because this message is important.
And I was like, okay, well, I hate this, but fair enough. But it just got to be to the point where
it was like 75% of the time, like three out of four Sundays, it honestly felt like three out of
four Sundays, they wouldn't do the tween group thing. Because because this message was just so
important. Honestly, I honestly now looking back on it, I just now had a suspicion that maybe the
guy who ran the tween group thing was just didn't want to do it most of the time and asking them
to excuse him out of it. I don't know. But that's probably not the case. They probably thought that
the messages were just that important that all the 11 year olds had to listen to it.
But anyway, what was really frustrating is that on the occasion I finally went to the
tween group thing, you know, it was more involved, but I didn't like the people there and they would
piss me off. And well, they only pissed me off twice, right? Well, no, they only pissed me off
once. Here's how it went. Like I just didn't like being there. I was just weird. I think this was,
I was going through my phase where I decided to like not wear underwear during the summer,
because I was like, my butt is sweating constantly. So I just don't wear underwear,
I won't feel it clinging to me. And then also during the winter, this was my period when I was
like, I just need to wear gloves all the time so that my hands don't get chapped. This was before
I discovered you could just put lotion on your hands and then your hands won't get chapped during
the dry season. At the time I was just like, I'm gonna wear gloves all the time. And you know,
I'm sure I'm awkward and like, it's like, I don't talk in ways that would make me seem natural,
but I do talk in ways that make me seem unnatural, you know, again, didn't really care about these
people or their opinion of me. It just made me feel like, okay, I just don't need to be here.
It just made me feel a little bit uncomfortable. Not really uncomfortable, just why am I here?
What am I doing? Right? I remember one time we were like, never mind, I won't get into like
time. There were just some times we were like, don't touch me or some kid was like, we're like,
one girl, we were like holding hands to pray and one girl was like, why do you wear gloves all the
time? And I don't remember what answer I gave. I think I think I probably just said, oh, because
my hands get chapped. So I just want to keep them warm all the time. But yeah, I probably came off
like a huge weirdo. But I don't think I was like that stand out for people to care that much,
you know, it's a bunch of 12 year olds, of course, they're all they're all probably feeling miserable
too. But like, there's one time where like, what happened, we had water cups, I just spilled the
water cup on my pants. And I was like, I'm frustrated, right? And like, you know, today, I just like,
oh, shit, I spilled water on my pants. But you know, at this time, I didn't have the maturity
to just do that. I was just like, Oh, God, I don't want anyone to see this. Like, I don't mind that
much. It's just that it stresses me out. So I went to the bathroom and I was just trying to dry it
off. And like, one of the teachers was like, Hey, what's up? Like, it was like a female girl person
woman who was like, she wasn't in the bathroom with me. But you know, like when I came out,
she's like, Is anything wrong? And like, and I was just I was just frustrated, right? I was just
frustrated at like, now I'm like spending 30 minutes just trying to dry my fucking pants off.
And instead of like, participating in whatever they're doing, which is probably going to be at
least somewhat stimulating, right? I don't want to be here anyway. And so I eventually walked back
in with the teacher lady. And like, everyone was just kind of silent for a second. And one girl
said, What's wrong? Are you constipated? And like, everyone laughed. Like, you know, the classic,
you know, laughing at the child in the classroom type of thing. And like, it didn't bother me.
It just amplified my why the fuck am I here? You know, I was just like, I don't I don't need you
people, right? Now, I must clarify that on one hand, I've never been someone who minds being
laughed at. Like for me, I was actually asked like last night, I was talking to my squiggle. And
the squiggle asked me like, what is what is like the your biggest fear? What's your biggest concern?
What's your biggest insecurity? And I said, people not finding me funny, me not being funny, that is
literally the only thing that could make me make myself image plummet into 0%. That's really the
only I could be terrible in every other way. But as long as people are laughing because of me, I'm
okay, I can live, right? And, and then like the question is raised, well, what about when people
are laughing at you? And I honestly sincerely don't mind. If if me, if my existence or my actions
causes amusement to people, then I legitimately, I legitimately appreciate it no matter what the
context is really. So like, the fact that everyone laughed at me, I don't mind. I really thought
like, huh, it is kind of, I mean, that was a funny quip. It was well timed, you know? But it just was
like, yeah, but I don't really feel welcome here. Again, I want to emphasize the laughing on its own
didn't bother me. It was just like thinking, I don't need to be here. I don't want to be here.
I was just kind of grumpy about it for like weeks. And eventually like that girl was like,
hey, sorry that I said that to you. I'm like, don't don't worry, I don't mind, you know, nice.
But then, oh God, the the like like a month later, you know, however many sessions of this later,
like we were doing a Thanksgiving thing. Hold on, Thanksgiving, that would mean that this was
like November, which would mean like a couple months prior would have been when I was still
wearing gloves during September. So maybe it was just cold all the time. Maybe my hands got
chapped all the time. Maybe it was just dry that year. I don't even know. No, no, it had to have
been cold. Maybe that maybe the kid thinking maybe the girl asked me why I wear gloves all the time
was from the last winter. And and now and this Thanksgiving story I'm about to tell was from
the the year that felt that followed afterwards. Man, I actually you know what it's starting to
trip me out. I don't remember like I'm like the dates of things are blurring together for me more
and more like I was realizing just last night I don't remember if I was 11 or 12 when I jacked
off for the first time. I literally cannot remember if it was 2005 or 2006. Like I'm pretty sure it
was 2005. But then it conflicts with other dates and timelines I have in mind. So it may have been
2006. And then there's a part of me that's like wait, was it 2007? Was I actually 13? I really,
really don't remember. And so much of the stuff that I did on the internet at the time I have
deleted long, long ago. So I won't I can't check. Anyway, this is you know the whole when you look
on back on this you'll laugh this story with this youth this tween group thing is definitely the case
with this. So it was a Thanksgiving thing. And basically the assignment is we're gonna make a
friggin. Oh, geez, it's like you're just gonna make like a card like a thing what you're oh yeah
what you're thankful for of course that's what Thanksgiving is for I don't remember that but
putting one and two together I'm sure that's what it was make a little card with arts and crafts
signifying what you're thankful for. So actually I just remember we were actually in that church
for longer than I can I remember because I was actually in the kids group before that but then
eventually I moved up to the tween group in the same church right so I was probably there for
three years or so but anyway yeah so yeah make a card of what you're thankful for and like
and they had little um okay where's those little cone shaped things for Thanksgiving where you put
like fruit in it or something and you put like stuff in it and it's Thanksgiving themed it's like a
it's like one of those bugles snacks but it's Thanksgiving and like you put stuff in it like
that's a Thanksgiving thing so part of what they were you know prompting for these cards is that
you know decorate them with one of those bugles I think they actually were literally using bugles
like the snack and you put the thing inside of them but it may have been little plastic things
and I just didn't really care that much so I was just like gluing you know you glue it to the card
and I just glue I glued the fruit outside of the bugle like I didn't like like everyone else like
I was just kind of messing around with it didn't really care but then like the other kids were like
oh you're not doing it right you know you're like like look see what we're doing like you're
gluing you're putting glue into the bugle and then you're putting the little plastic fruit ornaments
into the bugle to uh to make them stick and it looks real but I was just sticking the bugle to
the piece of paper and then sticking the fruit to the piece of paper outside of the bugle and I
didn't think of doing it the way that they were doing it but they were like legitimately like like
correcting me about it you know which is you know remember these are a bunch of 12 year old so of
course they were just like and like a couple and I was like uh no the way I'm doing it is perfectly
fine right like I'm I'm doing it I don't care you know like I think at the time I was probably
arguing oh this is more good like this is better the way I'm doing it like I don't and like and then
like when it got to the point that there was like two or three kids being like no no you're doing it
wrong you're doing it wrong I was like they weren't mad they were just trying to help me but they
were doing it in this know it all kind of attitude and so I was just like fuck this you know I didn't
say that I was just like I literally just turned around walked out of the room because you know it's
it's a church I mean for those who don't if you haven't been to a church or maybe you've gone to a
certain kind of church all the churches I've been to it's not it's pretty relaxed you can just kind
of wander around and you know whatever so but yeah the point is I wasn't doing anything like breaking
the rules I was just being kind of audacious I'm like why do I need to be here I don't need to be here
I walked out I was just like I was mad like why are they giving me shit over nothing and I walked out
the door and it was like storming down the hall and I remember specifically um like there was some
adult woman person talking to another adult woman person like what's going on oh he's having another
David's having another issue with the kids another issue like oh great this is what I am I'm the one
who has the issues right so I was just like so I never went there again I think that may have
actually spawned at the end of us going to that church like I mean I probably told my parents about
that and they were like okay let's stop going there you know because they didn't like it either they
didn't like the people there either oh god it's so funny oh so you know I remember also like much
younger at a different church we went to like a church camp thing and there was a point in time
where I just got pissed off at everybody and I just I just went into the tent and I zipped the
tent up and I was just mad and like some other kid was like man remember last year when like you
were so mad at everybody you like you zipped the tent up so that no one would get in I'm like
yeah I guess I just have I guess that's just my reputation at some point I get mad at everybody
and I just want to storm off right and I lose nothing because I have I have computers video games
and the internet eventually when I was like 13 and I started using the internet all the time
even as a kid I had the internet I just didn't use it much I you have the infinite universe
to explore I don't need I don't need useless people who are normal you know so I guess because
that's my pattern uh then when like I feel angsty towards the pcp I get paranoid like oh god am I
gonna emo out and leave because I would then legitimately be crushed you know I value this
association this affiliation way too much you know so I need to get the fuck over it man
okay um that's it I'm gonna keep this short again that was a pretty self-contained point
I have other notes but they're all things that will continue to be relevant as the weeks go on so
I don't want to squeeze this uh this my topics out too quickly uh yeah I'm planning on you know
still doing this every week probably maybe but okay on one hand I feel like if I force myself
to do one every week then I'm gonna run out and it's gonna be pointless and it would be better
if I just do it when I feel like doing it but the thing is pressuring myself to do it on a schedule
makes me want makes me like forces me to come up with ideas and to put it together in a good way
so I think I am going to commit myself to doing this you know what I'm gonna commit myself to
doing it once every other week yeah that's what I'm gonna do hopefully it's been like two weeks
since the last one yeah so yeah that that will officially be the schedule of this until further
notice the uh the voodoo hadron collider will be once every two weeks two weeks two weeks
will have lost the contract and oscorp will be dead sometimes it's gonna do things yourself