The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Oh dear god, all fucking Christ.
Welcome. If you hear some pitter pattering, that's because it's raining outside at the moment.
Hopefully that just makes it even more soothing if you can even hear it.
So...
I'd been saying on the last couple shows that I felt great.
I kept reiterating that I feel great as I've been pumping iron and eating whatever I want
or whatever.
But man, I also said on the last show that I was gonna quit smoking because it was starting
to get out of hand.
And boy, quitting smoking when you actually have started to get addicted to it, not easy.
Not an easy proposition, I gotta say.
You know, historically, this is the way I handle things when I'm scared I'm getting
addicted because I definitely have always had an addictive personality.
I take something and I make it a part of my life and it just is what I do from then on.
From when I was about 12 until I was 22 or 23 I think, I drank nothing but Mountain Dew.
I just drank Mountain Dew all day, every day.
It's all I drank.
Yeah, before that I drank mostly Sprite and other sodas.
I grew up on soda, you know, I grew up exclusively on soda pretty much.
Huge oversight on my parents' part, but they also drank soda, or did drink soda back then.
None of us were very health conscious until much later.
But yeah, I grew up drinking Mountain Dew for the better part of 10 years and, you know,
all the teeth fucking I have have cavities and fillings and shit, let me know cavities
now they're all filled, but I have asked tons of fillings, you know, I drank it obsessively
for so long and anytime I'd go without it it was like a real problem, you know, it was
definitely a hard line addiction.
I would get real upset and real depressed if I didn't have Mountain Dew for, you know,
like a day.
There was one time that my parents, you know, as we got, as the years went on they started
to realize how bad Mountain Dew was for you.
So at one point when I was like 17 I think, I think it was in my senior year of high school,
my parents decided to stop buying us Mountain Dew.
They were like, you know, we're not going to, we're not going to support you guys drinking
it anymore.
To me, Victor and Shay, because we all drank it.
Those are my two little brothers, if anyone doesn't know.
And yeah, so they stopped giving us Mountain Dew.
And so because at the time I was riding my bike to and from school every day, I would
just like not spend my lunch money, you know, I'd just like save up my lunch money for a
couple days.
I'd save up the, my mom would give me like $3 because it's like $2 for a regular lunch
and then an extra dollar to get like, you know, to get more essentially because the
lunches were pretty small.
So she would give me the extra dollar and then I would save up those extra dollars and
then every other day I would go to 7-Eleven on the way home and buy a like, you know,
a big ass Mountain Dew ball, like the biggest one I could get.
And this went on for a few months of like us not getting Mountain Dew and I, I was fucking
miserable for those three months.
Like I was, I was generally depressed anyways back in high school, but I was like real bad.
I stopped writing my anime blog entirely for those three months.
Like I think I made one post, it was, it was like, I distinctly remember that I just went
on this long unintended hiatus from everything that was going on.
I wasn't really watching anime either.
I think I, I think I just stopped everything essentially.
It was just, just feeling like shit for that whole time.
And then what finally broke it was that my parents went out of town, like they were going
out to go to like some other country or something.
And they left a bunch of money for us to buy groceries.
Now me, Victor and Shade are not the type to like, buy groceries.
Like we'll subsist off of like bread rather than actually make food, you know, for ourselves
and stuff.
Like we probably, I don't even know if we bothered.
I mean, I don't know how we would even get.
I think my parents had like, no, it wasn't that they left us money for groceries.
It was like that they had, we had bought groceries before they left and then it was like, this
is if you run out of food or if there was an emergency or something, you know, we'll
leave you with some money.
So we, as soon as my parents left, we went down to 7-Eleven and bought like 12 bottles
of Mountain Dew, two liters, you know, and it brought them all back home.
And then we, we marathoned Lucky Star.
Like that night, me and my, my friend Donsan, we sat on the couch and this was the time,
I think I've mentioned this before in a video somewhere that like we, we had Anime Suki
open and there was this thread on Anime Suki, which is an anime forum, um, which had like
goes through every single reference in Lucky Star and explains all of them.
And we were like watching the show while like pausing to look at the references and stuff
and, and you know, figure out what all the jokes mean and stuff.
It was a great time.
We marathoned the whole show in a day, 20, 24 episodes, I think, in one day, drinking
all this Mountain Dew and you know, by the time my parents got back, I guess they had
just like forgotten or they figured out that we had, you know, done this and they're just
like, fuck it.
So they started buying this Mountain Dew again.
Wasn't until I was 22 or 23 that I finally had the willpower to just do it myself to
actually quit.
So I quit completely and what I took up instead is Wawa Diet Green Tea.
Wawa is a local, um, convenience store slash like fast foodie restaurant kind of thing.
Um, and it's mostly a convenience store.
They sell food that like they, they'll make for you kind of thing.
There's nowhere to actually sit down and eat.
But anyways, they have their own tea and I don't know what it is about their tea in
particular because like, uh, growing up, I never liked tea, but then I discovered like
cold green tea and I was like, this is actually kind of drinkable and I tried a bunch of different
brands, but the Diet Wawa Green Tea is the one that like really is the only one I really
like.
So I took that up and the reason I chose Diet Green Tea is because it has no nutritional
value.
It's basically just water and fake sugar, you know, it's just like water and aspartum
and that's it.
And aspartum has a lot of people say a lot of bad stuff about aspartum.
Most of it's not actually scientifically founded.
It's mostly rumor aspartum is not actually bad for you.
And as it happens, there's been more scientific studies done on it than like anything else
in the universe because of all the bad rumors, but it's not actually bad for you.
So yeah, I have an addictive personality.
I gave up Mountain Dew and took up Diet Green Tea.
Now Diet Green Tea is a completely harmless addiction, so I don't mind that I'm addicted
to it.
I will get irritable if I don't have that like regular caffeine intake and have, you
know, something like the Diet Green Tea.
And now I can't even really stomach much soda anymore.
I can have like a soda a day kind of thing.
But I was always, you know, it's okay to be addicted to that, but I've always been afraid
of other addictions.
I try to keep everything to a minimum.
Like I love drinking alcohol, but anytime I've started to feel like maybe I'm drinking
too much alcohol, I'll put a stop to it.
I'll stop drinking for a little while.
And I've always found it's easy to do so.
Alcohol to me doesn't feel like an addiction so much as just something I really enjoy doing
and, you know, not doing it for a long period of time is just boring and it feels like
why am I not, why have I decided not to drink alcohol, you know, because it doesn't feel
like I'm dependent on it, just feels like it's something I enjoy doing.
Now cigarettes, on the other hand, it's always been this sort of tightrope balance where
I took up smoking in like 2011.
At first I was barely doing it.
At first I didn't even like it.
But then the period when I started smoking more was my mom was in the hospital with cancer
and the stress from that I was just looking for any way to relieve the stress.
So I started smoking and I would only smoke one cigarette a day, two at the most, because
by the time I finished one usually I was starting to get a head rush.
Like smoking more than you can handle will give you headaches and make you dizzy and
make you feel weird for the rest of the day.
So for a long time I couldn't even handle more than one cigarette a day, you know, and
one cigarette a day felt like this is not enough to, you know, to become a huge problem.
I'm not addicted, you know, the people who have real health risks from smoking or the
people who are smoking like two packs a fucking day, you know, not to say that there's no
health risk in smoking period, but you know, I didn't feel like it was becoming a big problem.
But for years I've been like keeping myself to any time I start to get used to smoking
more than one a day, that's when I stop.
If I get up to like two a day starting to feel normal, I could even handle three a day,
I would stop and I would just quit for like a month all the time.
I would just say like, this is getting too scary, I'm gonna quit smoking and I'd quit
for a while.
Usually what would start me back up is someone who I know who smokes would come around and
we'd have a cigarette together because having a cigarette together is super fun.
Great social, like great way to hang out with people and have a conversation is to stand
around and smoke.
It's super cool and fun and aesthetic and awesome.
But it also means that you have to go buy another pack of cigarettes and a pack of cigarettes
has 20 cigarettes in it and if you have 20, you're gonna smoke them all.
Now sometimes I would take two months to smoke 20 cigarettes, you know.
Sometimes I have one every couple of days, forget about them, leave them around, you
know, take my time.
I'd buy cigarettes so rarely that, you know, one of the problems with being addicted to
smoking is that it can be a huge drain on your wallet, you know.
It's only five and a half bucks for a pack of cigarettes here, which is pretty low compared
to how it is in some states, but nonetheless, you know, it's not expensive if you're not
doing it all the time.
If you're smoking a pack a day, it's obviously quite expensive.
So I had quit smoking for a little while and then Ben moved in and Ben also smokes when
offered.
He hadn't been before he moved in, but we started smoking together.
Well Ben was smoking a lot more than I'm used to.
He would go out three or four times a day and because I was drunk consistently for like
a week when Radcon happened, I was smoking just as much with him.
And so I got back into it and I got harder into it and I started smoking more and buying
more packs and buying more different kinds.
Well, it wasn't too bad, but then, you know, Ben loves vaping and Ben sees it as like if
you're vaping, then it's no big deal because even though like the worst thing about vaping
is that it's addictive, it's that you will, like it's still addicting to be addicted to
nicotine and you, you know, you had to spend money to fuel that addiction.
But it doesn't cause like most of the problems that cigarettes cause.
There have been cases where vaping was causing other problems, but those have been regulated
since then and like currently, I mean, it's possible that it causes problems that we don't
even know about yet because there's not enough research done on it yet, but like the way it
looks right now is that the worst thing about vaping is the fact that it's addictive, which
in itself doesn't seem like a huge problem as long as you're okay with being addicted
to something and spending money on it.
So Ben is all about vaping and he got me interested in the idea, so I bought an e-cigarette, not
a full blown vape, just like one that you can buy over the counter at 7-eleven, you know.
And what I quickly found is that because you can vape indoors and because there's no sense
of finality with a vape, where with a cigarette, you smoke it until it's done and then you
throw it away.
If you're trying to keep to one cigarette a day, that's very easy to do.
With a vape, you don't know how much is too much.
You don't know how much you're really getting.
You don't know when to start and stop every time you do it.
And so you just kind of consistently vape all day, you know, and you don't have to leave
the room to do it because it just dissolves into the atmosphere, it's gone, it's vapor.
So very quickly, I started vaping way more than I was ever smoking.
You know, it's way easier to vape all day.
But what I found with the e-cigarettes is that the stupid fucking, the little cartridges
they give you, like my cigarette came with one, you know, and then you buy them in packs
of two.
The cartridges only last like two days at the most.
Like, if you're smoking it, you know, consistently, it only lasts you about two, two and a half
days.
And a pack of two is seven dollars.
So this is way more expensive than smoking normal cigarettes would be.
Like normal cigarettes, you buy a pack for five and a half dollars and it's 20 cigarettes.
Even if I was smoking for a day, that lasts me five days and that's, you know, as long
if not longer than the seven dollars for the two fucking cartridges was gonna, you know,
was gonna run me.
So yeah, I was like, this is way more expensive.
So immediately, I switched back to cigarettes.
But now, thanks to vaping, you know, making it easy to consume nicotine all day long,
I found that suddenly I could smoke way more cigarettes.
Suddenly I can smoke five or six in a day, you know, which I couldn't, I could not do
before.
Not that I didn't do it.
I could not even do that before.
And I had, I had bought these cigarettes, I bought a couple of different specialty like
cool brands that I had heard about, you know, that I just wanted to try and got way too
into it.
So I was like, okay, this is out of hand.
That's where I was when I recorded the last podcast was like the day that I decided, okay,
let's quit again.
Now here's the important question.
Do I take up vape or do I just quit entirely?
Now the obvious answer is quit entirely, right?
Who needs another expensive smoking hobby in your life?
Why even do this stuff, right?
But the truth is that there's a reason that I've been smoking all this time and vaping
and all this stuff.
And it's because it is a stress relief and it is a simple stress relief you can do from
home.
It's something you don't have to go anywhere.
You don't have to do anything other than, you know, it's an excuse to get out of the
chair, to get up and go stand outside for five to 10 minutes and just relax and, you
know, and consume something which slightly changes your mind for a minute and helps you
to have more energy and stuff, you know.
It's kind of like an energy drink, except not completely disgusting.
It makes your stomach hurt, at least for me.
That's what they do to me.
So you know, yeah, it's like vaping, again, the worst part about it is that it's addictive
and that you have to pay for that addiction.
But am I willing to have that addiction or do I think I should just go completely, you
know, completely without it?
So my first instinct is fuck getting your vape.
I'm just gonna, you know, I'm just gonna cold turkey it as I've done so many times before.
It's never been hard before.
It was never that hard to drop cigarettes for a month.
You know, I might feel a little like, I might feel cravings for a couple days, but I didn't
feel like I needed it.
These last three days, I felt like I fucking needed it.
I felt irritable.
I felt shitty.
I didn't want to do anything.
And it doesn't help that this was compounded with another, in the last podcast I was talking
about the sort of big release that you get, the big come from posting a video up on YouTube.
And I kind of got this like one-two punch going on where I finished watching Tsukuyomi
Moonphase, which was the last thing I had to watch for the first part of this video series
I have upcoming.
And like, it was a pain to watch.
Like I did not enjoy most of the show and it really sucked to try to finish it.
But I finished it like right at the same time that DeVu was finishing up the Cool Character
Designs Gorilla Gone video and that released right at the end of the month and I got all
my affairs in order.
I had a lot of stuff kind of piled up that I had to finish and I finished all of it at
once.
And I was standing at a point where there's no half finished project that needs to get
done right now.
You know, suddenly there's nothing on the plate.
We skipped PCP this week so I didn't have a PCP to edit.
We, you know, I finished editing the commentary for the month.
Some other shit.
I mean, there are some half finished vlogs that I mentioned in the last podcast, but
like nothing that was immediately on the plate was left uneaten.
And so for like, you know, at the start of November 1st, I just kind of woke up and was
like, oh, I have no plans.
I have nothing to do.
And I also don't want to do anything.
I don't want to start anything because I have this really intense craving for nicotine
right now and I feel like shit.
And I just kind of didn't do anything for a whole day.
And then I borrowed the book Brand New World from Ben, started reading it that night, passed
out, finished reading it the next day.
That's all I did.
I read Brave New World all day.
Both of these days, I was awake for like probably only 12 hours or so.
Like I woke up before noon and passed out before midnight at some point.
But like, you know, close to those times, I just, I lost all energy.
I was completely lethargic.
I didn't want to do anything.
And then today, you know, the third, it's the fourth now, but the third is where I start
today.
Um, I was just like, fuck it, I'm going to buy a vape, like, because even if this is
a feeling that will eventually go away, even if cold turkey would eventually lead to me
not craving this, I thought there's no way I'm going the rest of my life without smoking
or vaping.
There's just, it's unreasonable to think so, you know, because again, what they provide
is something that I would want even if I wasn't addicted, just to be able to get up from my
chair, stand outside for five to 10 minutes and take some drags of something that's going
to calm me down and help me to deal with the monotony of my existence, which is a life
where I, all I, everything I do is connected to a computer chair, you know, and I look
for every excuse to get up from that chair.
And most of the excuses I have are to go get food and I can't constantly go get food,
you know.
So at some point, there has to be something else I can do and it ended up being the easiest
thing to do at home is to just go outside and have a smoke.
So I was like, I don't think I'm going to not do this ever again.
So I might as well just buy a fucking, like a real vape, you know, because it ultimately
is a lot less costly than using the e-cigarettes because even though the e-cigarettes, the
thing about a real vape, like the one I'm currently holding and have been taking hits
from as, as I record this is that the vape itself is like $45 and the liquid, I got like
a $15 bottle of liquid, which is pretty big.
And it comes with a battery, it's rechargeable, so I shouldn't need a replacement battery,
but that's something you, you know, you can get and it comes at these coils and the coils
last about two weeks before they burn out and then you have to replace them.
I have one extra one.
So about, they cost about $5.
So every two weeks, you're spending $5 on a replacement coil and every once in a while
you're buying more of the, of the shit you burn in it.
So it still costs, you know, a decent amount of money and especially it's front loaded.
You pay a lot upfront for all this shit, you know, and then you kind of maintenance it.
Whereas with the e-cigarette, it's like $10, you know, but then you immediately have to
buy cartridges.
This shit ultimately is way cheaper if you're going to be doing it for a long time compared
to the e-cigarettes.
So you know, that's a big part of it because I really didn't want to go back to the e-cigarettes
because they're way too expensive.
There's just no way I could justify spending what would probably be like $15 a fucking week
to keep that thing going.
And also doesn't hold a charge for shit.
You, you like, you know, drag on it for like five minutes and the battery's dead.
So yeah, you have to constantly have it on the charger if you're not using it, which
is a pain in the ass.
The real thing, infinitely better.
So I went for it and yeah, that's why I'm going to end up being a vapor from now on,
probably.
It's just a matter of like, what fits my lifestyle.
And I'm not saying that I would advise this to anyone else or that like my justifications
are necessarily like a good idea, but just I can't see myself as someone who would not
at all find it infinitely easier for my life for me to be able to get up and go outside
and take a drag of a vape as composed as opposed to being someone who doesn't, you know, have
to drop that little bit of money and that little bit of a, of knowing that I'm addicted
to something on the table.
You know, I have always been an extremely impressionable person.
A big part of how I end up smoking so often is that I see someone else doing it and I
immediately want to do it.
Or I just even see a cigarette or have a suggestion of their existence.
I'll want to do it.
But also when it comes to creative stuff.
I have a tendency when I see someone doing something, especially for something I think
I could do on some level that I immediately want to do it.
Any time I like, you know, consume a piece of media that really affects me in any kind
of way, I'm like, I want to recreate this.
I want to make something like that.
Now I've kind of curbed this in more recent years to mostly apply to things that I am
already in the wheelhouse of like, I no longer will watch a movie, like a great movie and
immediately think I want to go make a movie because I know what goes into making a movie
and it's not fun.
It's not stuff I want to do.
It's not really my field of expertise.
I mean, sometimes I wish, sometimes I have ideas in my head that I think would only work
as a movie, but not that often.
More often than not, the way I think has become reflective of the mediums I work in, which
are writing and YouTube videography, vlogging essentially, you know, vlogging, vlogging.
Like I mean, the stuff I do, like podcasting is not considered a vlog, but it is essentially
the same thing, you know, it's just a vlog without a face.
And while vlogging is thought of as showing your face on camera, what I do in my main
channel is just blogging, like I ran an anime blog and I write the exact same way I did
before, it's just now a video.
So it's basically vlogging, you know, all the stuff I do is vlogging essentially or writing.
And so when I see writers who are inspiring to me of any kind, like if I read a film crit
Hulk article, that's always a great inspiration for me to go make analysis videos because
he's my favorite media analyst.
And so reading his writing really, you know, gets me in that mood of like, oh, I'm going
to write a great analytical blog post, you know, but then seeing certain stuff that's
more narrative driven, that's like, that reminds me that I could be creating a narrative.
Those are the things that sort of get to me in a way that is of questionable goodness.
Because I'm not a good fiction writer, I'm not good at weaving a narrative that's anything
other than obvious or like is exactly what I am.
I'm very blunt and direct about my approach to things.
When I watch like an endless Jess video, one of his that go into like these really winding
or in depth scenarios, you know, especially something like the Horseshoe finale or its
sequel, then I have this sense of like, man, I could be doing so much more with the medium
of YouTube videography.
You know, I could be creating these meta loop holes and like really, you know, twisting
my language in such a way to set up and pay off and all that stuff and creating a more
narrative experience because I do think that people feel something more deeply when they
get that kind of narrative experience.
You know, I think I've made a lot of vlogs that people have told me are like deeply important
to them.
Once in a while, I make a podcast or a vlog and people tell me, man, this one really
resonated with me and it's my favorite one you've ever done and I'm so glad you said
this and it's been really life affirming for me and I really appreciate that.
But at the same time, I feel like with those kind of videos, you will eventually just internalize
the sentiment more so than remember the video.
You know, like if I say something like, here's what you, here's how you should treat your
life and someone says, wow, I never thought of it that way.
I'm going to treat my life that way from now on.
It's the sentiment that you'll keep remembering, not how it was delivered to you.
And with Endless Jess, what you remember is how it was delivered to you.
You know, what made Horseshoe Finale so memorable is not just the things being said, but the
fact that he was in that set with that shot, you know, in that pose, him saying it in the
way he said it.
Not to devalue what I do, but I definitely think that there's, there's a level of artistry
to what Jesse's doing, that I haven't completely tapped into yet.
And I have had moments that did it.
I think the biggest one is in the Asterisk War Sucks Part 9 with the McDonald's thing,
where I, you know, I just broke into this very evocative, artful feeling and I sort
of told this little narrative about me going to McDonald's and it really had a lot of impact.
Not just like, you know, it wasn't just about the sentiment of A1 Pictures makes things,
you know, all look the same.
It was like the way it was delivered was what's memorable about it, that, wow, he, he did this
film segment and, you know, I want to be able to make more things like that.
When I read novels, like classic literature, like I just read, you know, Brave New World,
and I was thinking how, if I wrote a story like Brave New World, my instinct would be
to just literally describe it, to just describe this world.
And a lot of the book is kind of that.
This book is very heavy on just world building and a lot less story.
And when it actually does develop a story, it gets a lot less interesting, in my opinion.
The most interesting part is the beginning where it's just establishing the setting.
But it does it in a very, you know, narrative way, with very flowery language that sort
of leads you through and has all these clever, you know, writing techniques.
It's not blunt the way my writing is, the way my talking is, where I'm just telling
you exactly what things are, you know.
There's nothing to interpret in the way I talk.
And I think that that extra little bit of having to interpret, of having to, you know,
process information, helps it to become more memorable and more ingrained in your psyche.
Where if I just tell you something, then you immediately get it.
But if you have to think about it a little bit to get it, then it sticks with you longer
and it lingers in your mind.
And that's why so many of what we consider artistic masterpieces are things that are complicated.
Because when it's simple, you don't ruminate on it for very long.
You just consume it and it's over.
But you know, if you're watching like Neon Genesis Evangelion and there's images in
that show that only mean something once you've seen the whole show twice or you've really
thought about it and you've really connected with it on this deep level, you'll remember
that for a lot longer.
And it's not necessarily that I think that those works are more valuable, but I do think
that they are more valued.
I think that people put more stock in that stuff.
I think people will talk about it for longer, they'll consider it to be a more important
part of their lives, they'll remember it forever.
And while I think I stay in people's minds because I make this consistent output that
I'm always making new videos and talking about new ideas and perspectives, I don't think
I've made a lot of stuff that if I stopped producing shit today, people would keep bringing
it up forever.
I think there's a few things that would get brought up a lot.
The asterisk war sucks, the sword online sucks.
Those will keep being mentioned for years if I stopped making stuff.
People would bring it up every once in a while in an argument, maybe a few of my other videos.
But most of it is stuff that matters in the moment.
You internalize the message and you forget the video.
And I see all the time, or some of the stuff that I consider the most important parts of
my message, people have to be reminded of it.
I'll bring up some video I made and people will be like, oh yeah, that video.
And even though they've already been using quotes from that video from then on, they
don't remember that the video itself existed.
It happens to me too.
I forget a lot of the stuff I've written.
Sometimes I go back and watch a video from two years ago that I forgot about and I'm
shocked that it makes points that I am still thinking about and forgot I made before.
I have that experience fairly regularly.
Because I haven't written a book that everyone remembers that conveys that message so perfectly
that you never forget that that's what you consumed.
So that's what I stay hung up on as a writer.
And I've kind of been worried lately and I get this worry all the time when I start
making stuff that's more specific that the further I get away from that kind of emotional
resonance, the less people are going to care about what I have to say.
Because with Shinbo in the 90s, that's a passion project for me because I love looking
at directors.
I love looking at that kind of intimate data stuff.
It's basically just data crunching.
It's just me consuming a lot of data, crunching it down and informing you of the same data.
But there's almost no emotional resonance to it.
There's no heartfelt slant, especially with Shinbo because there's so little to say about
him other than his stylistic trappings.
With Hideaki Anno, I could really get into the heart of what this creator was trying
to do and say with his work and it had a lot of emotional resonance.
Shinbo doesn't have that.
And I'm worried that if I started focusing on Shinbo, like if I made a bunch of videos
about him and made that the focus of my channel for a while, people would stop seeing me as
someone making interesting artistic points that resonate with them.
When I make a really great video, people, it resonates with people.
And if it didn't resonate with people, they wouldn't give me money on Patreon.
They wouldn't follow me on Reddit and stuff.
The kind of stuff that makes people a fan of you is the kind of stuff that touches them
on some kind of emotional level.
And I think I've done that before and I don't think I'm going to do it with Shinbo in the
90s.
I don't think anyone's going to get emotional about that.
So even though it's a great technical work of data crunching, even though it's very academic
and great as someone compared it to a Wikipedia article, and I was like, you know, it is like
a Wikipedia article, but I like Wikipedia articles.
And what's important about this one is that I'm the one writing the Wikipedia article.
I'm the one constructing all the data.
I'm the one compiling it.
I'm the one writing the article.
But it is ultimately a Wikipedia article.
And Wikipedia is a website that has so much trouble getting people to see it as more than
a utility that they always have to do these fucking huge donation funds to keep the website
running.
Because everyone uses Wikipedia, but no one wants to pay for it because no one thinks of
it as like a deep, important part of their life.
You know?
Granted, I do.
I always give money to those Wikipedia fundraisers, but you know, I don't want people to necessarily
see me that way.
I don't want people to start looking at me as just a repository for information, but
one that's not like actually giving you something meaningful and personal because I like being
able to provide those things.
So I always feel like I have to strike a balance.
And that's why I constantly feel like I have to be taking on like this multitude of projects
where there's one half of me that's like, you need to make the biggest research project
ever.
And then there's the other half that's like, you need to make the biggest emotional like
meta, you know, make people think about themselves and their lives thing ever.
And it's great when those things can come to a head.
Something like the asterisk war sucks is a lot of those things coming to a head.
Every post in it is very emotional.
It's like, you know, here's how to write a good main character.
That's very relatable, very like everyone wants to know who's the worst anime character
in history, you know, who, how do you write a bad setting?
What's what's wrong with this studio?
Whoa, this show is good and that one's bad.
Like the fucking the chivalry of a failed night comparison is like, it's poetry that
I was able to find that connection.
Like that had nothing to do with me pure luck that those two shows aired at the same time
and were so parallel and that they could have such a strong narrative together that these
two shows like that one could be so bad and one could be okay and yet be almost all the
same components.
I could not have possibly asked for something better than that.
I will never top the level of beautiful coincidence that allowed me to write that piece because
it's so narratively strong, even though it's an analysis, even though it's data crunching,
it has the strongest narrative to it and I'll never get something that, you know, that perfect
again.
But I can still string narratives out of analysis, you know, and the next thing I've written
about Shinbo does, I did write a little bit more narrative into it a little bit more here's
why you should care about this as opposed to here's just a bunch of data, you know.
And yeah, like as I read these classic novels and classic literature and stuff and I feel
like people don't like this for the data.
They like it because it's memorable because it sticks with you because the things it makes
you think about are presented in such a way where oftentimes it's just that one sentence
that one perfectly worded sentence in the middle of, you know, of a chapter where suddenly
it like clicks into place and you totally get the point and it's put so eloquently that
you'll never forget that phrasing and, you know, I want to have moments like that.
Now continuing on the subject of the previous podcast, I listened to it back and I couldn't
help but feel like, wow, I come off as arrogant to the point of borderline megalomaniacal in
this podcast.
And you know, if there's one criticism I get a lot of it's that I'm arrogant and egotistical.
That's by far the most common thing that gets brought out against me and I completely agree
with it.
But it's funny because I feel like I don't know if that's something that I could change
or if that I'd be, if I'd be better without it.
I think it's kind of a matter of there's just certain people who aren't going to like you
in this world, you know.
When people criticize me for being arrogant, all I can think is, yes, I am arrogant.
Like there's nothing I could do about that.
Like it feels weird as a criticism for me because it's not a constructive criticism.
It's basically you're explaining why you don't like me and it's totally understandable.
But to say that like, you know, he needs to be less arrogant.
It's like, I can't just do that.
It's how I am.
And it's because, and I'm sure I've explained this somewhere before, but I'm going to put
it, I'm going to put it in clear terms here and explain from the beginning.
I've mentioned before that I grew up being told that I was a genius.
My parents told me that I was a genius.
They took me to a doctor.
I was about two years old.
They actually thought, because I acted so weird, they thought I wonder if he has autism because
autism was the craze of the times, early 90s autism starting to take off as a thing that
gets diagnosed.
They take me to the doctor and the doctor says, I don't think he has autism.
I think he's a genius.
So they become convinced I'm a genius and they tell me as much my whole life.
And I learned things a little faster than other kids, you know, but I also had weird
habits and tendencies like lining up cars.
I would just take all the cars I had and line them up by size and do that obsessively all
day, make sure all the lines were perfect, you know, very sort of autistic way of acting.
And if I reflect on myself from any point up through high school, possibly even up through
my first job, and I've taken like, you know, Asperger's quizzes on lines and got like,
you know, like you definitely have Asperger's scores until I started working on YouTube
and a lot of the things that I used to do, I completely don't anymore.
And I don't think I would qualify even slightly at this point, which is weird.
But I do think it's considered a thing that you can kind of grow out of to some extent,
like it's considered something that's more amongst young people to have.
I don't know if that's just because more young people are diagnosed or what, but I don't
know, it's odd.
But in any case, I was raised being told I was a genius, so I believed it.
And all throughout school, every year, everyone, you know, people constantly ragged on me and
made fun of me and hated me for this or that reason.
And I saw it as they're all wrong about me.
I know that I'm a genius, so everyone else must be an idiot.
But then when I got into high school, it kind of flipped on its head just a little bit.
Not that I thought I was any less intelligent, but I thought that clearly it's my fault I'm
not popular, you know, to like, to flip on the Tomoko, no matter how I look at it, it's
your fault I'm not popular.
I didn't feel that way.
I felt like me being smarter than everyone else was not working to my benefit, you know,
because I think that it's sort of what separated me from like the classic idea of the fedora,
of the like the the Elliot Roger, where Elliot Roger said, you know, I'm perfect.
So if everyone else doesn't like me, it must be because they're all terrible.
But I saw it as, you know, I'm perfect, but I shouldn't be perfect.
I should be like those people, you know, clearly they're happier the way they are, and I shouldn't
be the way I am.
I probably wasn't this well thought out, you know, when I was that age.
I'm able now as a guy who's able to put things into very easy, clear terms to like put it
that way.
I would not have been able to describe it this way at that age.
But I definitely felt like I was an outsider and I was wrong for being an outsider.
This was all my fault, but I wasn't changing it, you know, I wouldn't change anything.
I was never willing to like give an inch.
I just was like hoping that one day I'd run into someone who accepted me for who I was,
you know, I always thought, you know, I'm not going to go and change myself to try to fit
other people.
I'm going to wait until someone accepts me for who I am.
But until then, I'm I'm just going to be this lonely, sad sack of shit.
And now I'm famous and everybody loves me.
So basically when I was 16, I remember coming up with this phrase, I'm sure I've repeated
this, that if I can't do what I want, then I'm going to kill myself.
Because the way I saw it is that life, normal life to me was nothing but depressing.
It was just a bad time.
Trying to act normal, trying to act like other people only made things worse.
You know, if I had tried to dress differently or act differently or get into different things
than what I liked or to get a normal job that I didn't want to do, all of those things were
only going to make me even more unhappy than I already was.
So the only way I was ever going to be happy is if I did something I wanted to do.
You know, if I did a job I wanted to do, if I worked creatively, if I got to live my passions,
if I got to act how I want to act.
And I really thought that life was not worth living otherwise.
Like what's the point of living if you're not going to be happy?
You know, if you're not going to be as happy as you can be, or as you want to be.
If I'm going to feel like I'm not achieving my full potential, my whole life, that I'm
never going to be happy about it.
So I might as well just kill myself.
Why live if your life sucks?
That was my logic.
So I went about it as let's never do anything other than what I want.
And for years I struggled with, you know, like, I mean it was a long time before I got off
my feet.
And I still did it young.
You know, I was like 23 when my YouTube career really took off.
But you know, between when I graduated high school at 17 and started taking off on YouTube
at 23, was just a whole lot of me doing things I didn't want to do.
All while thinking I'm just working towards the thing I want.
You know, in the background I'm working towards the thing I actually want to be doing.
And eventually I was doing the thing I actually wanted to be doing.
And that's when I, you know, I felt good ever since.
I felt good about life.
But I still have to maintain that.
You know, I still have to be convinced that what I'm doing is right and that I like what
I'm doing and that I like where my life is going.
Because if I wasn't convinced of those things, then laying under that just one layer deeper
is a person who thinks that if I'm not feeling that way, I might as well be dead.
That's still a person who lives down there.
You know, the guy who has attempted suicide in the past.
Someone who, you know, went to the hospital to try to have them put me on suicide watch.
The kind of person who was so anxious and so paranoid about everything that I would just
not leave my room sometimes, you know, for long periods and just, and not talk to anyone
about any problems I was having and bottle it all up.
That person's still down there.
And the only thing that I can do to keep them at bay is to constantly convince myself that
I'm doing things right and that I'm happy with where things are going.
And that's easy to do when I'm doing exactly what I always hoped I would be doing, which
is what I am doing.
But to try and speak of something else would be dishonest.
To try and say, like, to try and act humble or something.
That's not reflective of how I feel because how I feel is like I'm amazing and I'm on
top of the world and everything's perfect because if I didn't feel that way, then it
would just, it would just regress to how it was before, you know?
So to me, the arrogance and the ego is what's keeping me afloat.
And it's not a facade, it's all completely honest and I have to be honest because being
honest is the thing I always wanted to do.
It's the thing, it's the way I wanted to live my life, was do honesty.
And if I started, you know, lying about it, then it would just be dragging me back down.
Like, I would be depressed about the fact that I was lying and not doing what I want
to do, which is be honest, you know?
And being honest makes me happy, which makes me egotistical, which makes me arrogant.
It's a weird cycle.
And so, like, ultimately, sometimes I feel bad because I recognize the arrogance.
I recognize sometimes when I'm just going, like, so full tilt on the idea that I'm just
amazing and stuff.
And I do hold myself in high regard.
And not to say that I think I'm, like, the best writer or anything like that.
There's tons of people I look up to.
There's tons of people who, I mean, Film Crit Hulk is a perfect example.
I don't think I'm close to the caliber of a writer that he is in terms of being able
to convey very grand emotions in his writing and to really, like, bring this excitement
that after you're done reading one of his things, you're just so excited about what
you just read, you know?
Or on a technical level, I'm not as good as Ghost Lightning, who was, you know, the
guy who sort of trained me in how to write better.
He was just more eloquent, had better words, was better read, you know?
And over time, I will eventually be as good as Ghost Lightning.
Maybe I'll eventually be as good as Film Crit Hulk because I don't think either one of them
is an extraordinary genius who I could never hope to match.
They both are just ten years older than me, you know, and ten years more experience, ten
years more writing, ten years more reading, ten years more knowledge.
And eventually I'll have that, and I think I'll be as good as either of them.
There are some people who I'll probably never be as good as.
I don't think I'll ever be as good a writer as Andrew Hussey of Homestuck because the
way that he writes is this, like, this insane natural extension of his mind.
It's like his whole creativity goes into, yeah, goes into Homestuck and it's just so
much more sprawling and creative than anything I'll probably ever do.
I'll never write something as massive as Homestuck and as influential and as, you know, as wide
appealing or anything like that.
But, you know, he's a very special kind of genius.
But I am nonetheless going to be a great writer.
And I do think that I'm better at writing than most of my contemporaries, most people
my age, most people on YouTube, certainly all anime writers.
You know, I don't see anybody, maybe some text writers, you know, can beat me.
Some people who, I still think that text blogging is a lot ahead of YouTubeing in terms of writing
because I think the kind of people who can YouTube is maybe a different subset from people
who can write well.
You know, there is some crossover but I feel like there's a difference in priorities and
that so many people who figure out how to YouTube well by having a good voice, having
good production values, you know, have not actually figured out how to write well yet.
Some of my friends are kind of on that borderline where I think Hippo, Crit and Best Guy Ever
are both fantastic video makers, not very good writers.
Great at coming up with stuff in video form that I'd never think of, you know, both great
editors, far better editors than I have ever been.
You know, Hippo can make jokes out of the creativity of how he films things and the
creativity of how he edits things and performs things that that's half the joke, you know.
He can take a joke that is just badly written and deliver it so hilariously that it becomes
a good joke, you know, and Best Guy Ever can edit his fucking, he can edit anything.
He knows his way around the programs perfectly.
I don't have those skills but I can definitely write most people under the table and the
only person I know who is better at writing than me in the video world is Endless Jess.
He's the only person who's more clever, more, you know, more intimately connected to the
written word and that's because Jesse writes way more than he video produces.
He has like hundreds of unreleased scripts.
He writes blog posts on Patreon now.
He's written tons of shit.
I've seen his writing on Facebook where he would write these rants and stuff.
Jesse's always been more of a writer and also more of a reader than most everyone I know.
He reads a lot more books.
He's just better with the language than I am.
Mr. Betung is better with the language than I am so far.
I don't think I would have too much catching up to do to him but he's definitely better
with the language than I am.
Those are the only people I know of on YouTube who I can definitively say that about, who
I watch and I go, that guy's a better writer than me, you know.
So yes, I am arrogant but I also see myself in a place, in a place, in a gradient and
not everyone would agree with the gradient.
Not everybody would put everyone in the same places that I do but when you think of yourself
the way I do, I think for a lot of people who are looking at it from the outside, they
just see a bunch of titans.
Anyone who writes at all, anyone who's a creative, they are just these gods far above
and if they don't really like you, like, you know, if someone doesn't really like my writing
and I compare myself to a writer who they do like, they see it as like, how dare you,
this lowly plebeian, compare yourself to one of the exalted gods, you know.
When I get that, but for me as a writer, I see myself as working my way up a ladder,
a ladder of writers.
If I go up one rung, bam, I've grasped the rung that puts me above this other guy, you
know.
When I started writing video, I would have put myself on the level of errant signal and,
well, Egoraptor might have been a much better video producer than me, for sure.
But like, in terms of writing, I would have put myself around Egoraptor, errant signal
and stuff.
Now I think I'm better than them.
I do think I'm a better writer than errant signal, whose style has not progressed almost
at all in the time I've been watching him, he makes very little progress.
And Egoraptor, who just stopped writing about three or four years ago, and for whom writing
is a very laborious process as I understand it.
So you know, I'm making progress, I'm climbing the ladder, one day I'll be able to write
as well as Beton, one day unless Beton continues improving, one day I'll be able to write as
well as Ghost Lightning and Film Crit Hulk, and maybe if I'm fucking lucky, I'll be able
to write as well as Jesse, but I do think Jesse is also still improving and still hashing
out whole new ways of writing and whole new creativities.
So I think with him, I'll be chasing a moving object that might even be moving faster than
I am.
But still, as a writer, this is how you think of yourself.
I am in that world.
I am a professional.
This is my job.
Whether you think I can write well or not, the fact is that I'm a professional writer.
How do you want to measure it?
Do you want to measure it by your personal taste, or do you want to measure it by accomplishment?
I've got 250,000 subscribers.
I make a middle-class wage doing what I do.
I live happily.
I can't think of an oculod that you wouldn't ascribe to me other than something that is
very personal to you.
So yes, I'm arrogant, but I also have accomplished the things that make someone arrogant.
I've been there.
I've been to the mountain, and if you think that that's nothing special, then I agree.
I think that the arrogance is not necessary for having completed these tasks, but it is
what gets me through life.
It's how I see myself, and I see myself as I need to be this way in order to keep making
progress.
If I don't see myself as getting better, if I don't see myself as trying to climb towards
these gods, then I'll never reach those gods.
I think if you're the kind of person who's sitting around saying, like, I can't compare
myself to the greats, how can you ever hope to be like the greats?
And that's all I want, is to be the best I can possibly be, and if I can possibly be
as great as the greats, then I gotta keep climbing and keep looking at myself as someone
who's gotten better, and is good, and is doing everything to put me on that path.
I intended to go into that rant more apologetically, but I ended up coming out of it more arrogant
than ever before, so hopefully at least this seems like it's probably an interesting podcast.
This has all been one recording so far, so I'm gonna go pass out now, and maybe there'll
be more from another day.
So it's October 7th now, the day that probably this video will come out, the night rather.
I recorded the whole first hour of this all on the 4th, and it's kind of funny to think
of this as a show that, you know, because I put dates on it, and it's always like a
specific day, but it's being recorded for the whole week, so you should really think
of it as the week of November 7th, that the video comes out, or that the video represents
rather than the day.
But the reason I chose to use dates is because I find numbering everything boring, you know,
I have a lot of, I've always kind of presented numbered shows on YouTube, because it implies
that you have to watch them in a certain order, and I hate that when it's a show that you
don't have to watch in a certain order, and I just think it's a bad way to go about things,
because if you number everything, people aren't gonna go back and find number one to start
from there.
Now I have numbered some shows on After Dark, mostly because I don't take it that seriously,
those videos, or like the first one kind of explains the concept, and you might as well
watch them in order and why not kind of thing, but I generally don't like numbered series
that much.
The Procrastinators is numbered kind of unnecessarily, like you don't really have to listen to them
in order, and nobody does, so the numbers are just kind of there to keep track of how
many we've done.
But with this podcast I thought, why not just label each one with a date, so you can tell
them apart, they don't have to have unique titles, but they're not numbered.
And it kind of implies that it's a diary, you know, because it's really, it's pretty
much like if I had a diary, this is the kind of stuff I'd be putting in it, you know, and
these days I am much more liable to record something than I am to write something.
I mean like the way I treat vlogs now is how I used to treat Tumblr back in the day, like
how, you know, I'd get a random idea that wasn't quite enough for like a video, but
a little too much for a tweet, I'd make a Tumblr post about it, nowadays I would make
a vlog, or a podcast, and this podcast in particular is like super, you know, personal
diary stories, so I think it makes sense to give them dates.
In other news, I've felt better again ever since I started vaping, talked about that
earlier in this episode, that I went out, wait did I mention that I went out and bought
a vape?
I think I did in the early part, I think that was the day I had done it, and I felt great
ever since, so that problem's out of the way.
Vaping is super fun, although it is annoying because I keep doing it during podcasts and
stuff and then not realizing how loud it is until listening to those back, so I'm gonna
try to curb that habit a little bit, try to make it to, it's just that it's such an ideal
time because I'm not doing a lot of other stuff, you know, especially if I have somebody
else with me and I have to like listen to them, then you know, it's like what do I do
with my hands while listening to them?
You know, like on the pub crawl, we always drink when the other person's talking, you
know, that's how we end up getting so drunk on the show, it's just whoever's not talking
is usually drinking.
But I felt good the last few days, I've kind of become a real comic book boy in a way that
I've always wanted to and never did until now, and it's really entirely because of now
I understand how comics work, I don't remember if I mentioned this in another episode, that
like, you know, Jesse started up the panel cast and it got me looking into individual
comics and what I realized as I was reading through Gwenpool and The Vision, like shortly
after reading The Vision, it suddenly became very clear to me that comic books almost always
come out in these like one or two volume stories, like even if it's a long running comic, like
I've always been under the impression that you really have, like there's these long runners
that have been going on forever and you have to read the whole fucking thing, all 80 volumes
or the endless, the endless annals of this comic book, you know, in order to understand
it, and I think it doesn't help that I was into DC, because when I tried to get into
comics in 2012, it was because the New 52 had just started, and like, the thing about
New 52 is that it was like a complete reboot of the entire DC universe, so I thought, well
that's a really easy way for me to get into it, I mean that's exactly what they were going
for, is to get a bunch of new comic book readers to have an easy end and not feel like they
had to catch up on 80 years of continuity, you know, and so I'd read, you know, a few
of the ones that interested me, I read Batwoman, which I love, Swamp Thing was, Animal Man
was okay, and there was a couple others I read, but like, because it was so early on,
I was under the impression that like, I'm just going to be reading these forever, like
this is a, this new comic has started up, and it's going to keep going and going and
going until the end of time, you know, and it will switch artists weirdly and randomly
and I won't know what's going on sometimes. I didn't realize that the way comics really
work is more like, you know, like the comic will keep going on forever, but it's like
these little stories that are then later collected into graphic novels, or their stand-alones
and stuff like that, and there's tons of those, and a lot of them are the most interesting,
a lot of the best stories are just like these little one volume things that are meant to
be graphic novels and shit like that, and I never realized how much of comics was like
that. So, you know, now I'm looking at, like I've been reading a bunch of stuff where I
just pick some, some series, you know, some part of a series, and I just read that, and
I'm like, oh, okay, now I've completed that whole thing and I have a better understanding
of the characters and what's going on. Jesse recommended this one Silver Surfer comic with
like unbelievably gorgeous artwork. It's only four issues. It was about the death of Silver
Surfer, and it was fucking epic and cool, and now I, I understand Silver Surfer, and then,
um, you know, did the same thing with a few others, and the one that was most interesting
is just yesterday, I went out and saw Doctor Strange, and it was the first time that I
ever felt like I understood what comic book fans feel when they watch a comic book movie,
because I, I've heard stuff like Kevin Smith on his podcast where he talks about, like,
um, how he'll, he'll go out and see like Batman v Superman, and just the fact that this one
kind of character shows up was enough to justify the whole movie's existence to him. Like, even
though he admitted to all these flaws in the movie, like, the fact that that thing was
there made it interesting and worth seeing, and like, that's something I couldn't relate
to at all. But with this Doctor Strange movie, I was like, I, I went into it and I, I watched
it, it was okay, it's a, it's a decent movie, and just like any other Marvel movie, I mean,
my impression of all the Marvel movies is basically, yeah, that's a fun time, but they're
all pretty much the exact same thing, I'm, I'm very sick of the, the formula of them,
but what made it different this time was that I watched it because I was curious about Doctor
Strange, because I had just read in Gwenpool where Doctor Strange shows up and he seemed
really cool, and then he was in the Silver Surfer comic and he seemed really cool, and
I was like, man, I kind of want to read Doctor Strange, so then I go out and I see this movie,
and now I know the whole backstory of Doctor Strange, I didn't know any of it, I knew nothing
about him other than that he was like, basically a time lord, you know, that's like all I knew,
so now I know his whole backstory, and like, in the context of seeing the movie, that wouldn't
have been that exciting, it would have been like, alright, well, now I know about another
superhero guy, whatever, but where it got exciting was I came home and I immediately read the
whole current run of Doctor Strange that started last year, so 13 issues, the first 10 of which
comprise a pretty open and shut story, like, the story is still, like, the current story continues
from where that one left off, but it's like, it's a definitively different chapter, you know,
it's a new story, it's got a new artist who's not nearly as good as the other one, but like,
what was great about it was I picked up this comic and like, it takes place, you know,
pretty far into Doctor Strange's narrative, but I now know who all these characters are,
like, I completely got it, I knew who everyone was, why they were important, and I was like,
sweet, you know, all I needed to catch up on was like, the little subtle changes between the
film and comic interpretations, so yeah, it was really neat, and I got to read that comic,
and I think I appreciated it more because I'd seen the origin story, and the comic is even
better than the movie, because the movie has the problems of following, you know, the Marvel
Cinematic Universe formula too much, and being, well, very trippy for a mainstream movie, not
that trippy compared to what you would find in a comic book, whereas the comic is like,
especially trippy even for a comic book, you know, like, when I was watching that film,
I was thinking, this is kind of epic in a way that's not unlike how Silver Surfer was epic,
because Silver Surfer had these like, crazy-ass ideas, he's like, these high-minded sci-fi concepts
just thrown about, you know, and the movie kind of does that, but the comic of Doctor Strange,
like, the whole point of it is that it's just non-stop insanity, like, because Doctor Strange's
world is one of just like, you know, mind-breaking horror at all times, so yeah, I think the film
does a good job of like, broaching the subject of Doctor Strange, whereas the comic really fulfills
the promise of Doctor Strange in a way, so yeah, it was pretty cool, and I read the comic, I really
liked it, particularly the first part, the new storyline that it's now going into isn't as
interesting, but I'll keep up with it for a while, you know, probably read some other older Doctor
Strange stories that are good, you know, and check out, check out what's out there, but now I just
feel so much more acclimated to what comics are, and like, how to explore that medium, you know,
that I can read it in these little bite-sized chunks, and like, most of them involve other
characters, so I can, you know, start to feel out who they are, like, I got interested in Doctor
Strange because he was in Gwenpool and Silver Surfer, and even those characters I now only know
so much about, and I'd like to see more of them, you know, Scarlet Witch plays a big role in the
Vision comic, Scarlet Witch is also in Doctor Strange, so now I'm curious about Scarlet Witch,
I might read her thing, you know, so yeah, it's a cool way to just jump into this web,
and like, find your way around, and I think I like the Marvel stuff more than the DC stuff,
it could just be that I haven't read the best DC stories, you know, like, Batwoman, what I kind
of liked about it was that it was not super connected to everything else, and I mean, it becomes sort
of tied up in the whole Batman thing, you know, obviously it's related to Batman, but she was
pretty individual, and I didn't feel like I had to know too many other things in order to appreciate
it, but with the Marvel universe, I feel more inclined to explore all these different people
and find out about them and why they're important to one another, and I'm sure at some point it'll,
like, the whole broken continuity thing will shatter my mind to pieces, but honestly,
it doesn't bother me that much because I kind of see each individual comic as like a parallel
universe from the last one, like, I can't really, like, I read Doctor Strange, and I've read Gwenpool,
and I don't think that they necessarily, like, it doesn't make sense to have them in the same timeline,
like, I don't know at what, like, Doctor Strange is definitely the same character in both stories,
but with what's going on in the Doctor Strange story, he couldn't possibly appear as he does
in the Gwenpool story, so when does her story even take place in comparison to his?
When does any of, it's such like a temporal fuckfest, like, to even read two comics that,
for me, it's easier to just compartmentalize each of them as just a totally different comic
that happens to overlap in some ways with another one, you know, kind of like reading or watching
everything by a clamp if you're an anime fan who knows clamp, like, they had the same characters
would appear in all these different stories, but not necessarily make sense in them.
Now, what's, what it's given me to get into comics is something great, because I've long
wanted to explore every medium. I want to be someone who is cultured in every, like, you know,
main medium of art, and part of it is because I want to see all these different interesting
ideas and, you know, explore all these things and be able to have conversations about them,
but also a more selfish part is that all of it helps me to justify anime, because I explain
this in my video, like, is anything deep, where when I consume stuff in other mediums that is
considered to be deep, it never actually feels like, like, like anime is any less deep, and I
feel like there's this, this cultural idea in every medium that, like, this medium's deeper than
that one. This one's got more going on, and I think right now, the medium that's the most
pretentious is film, because even though we've got this whole, like, actually it might even be
spurned on by this whole Marvel universe thing, where there's all these big Marvel popcorn movies,
and it's really created this heavy divide in the film communities of people who, because they see
those movies, they now are, like, overcompensating on loving the, the, the so-called masterpieces,
the, like, you know, the super deep films and stuff, and the artsy stuff, and I feel like there's
this overcompensation happening to really celebrate the super deep stuff, and to present it, like,
it's this high-brow shit, whereas other mediums, I feel like there's, there's not so much of a divide
between the, the popcorn stuff and the deep stuff, that, like, stuff can bridge that gap fairly easily,
and anime bridges that gap constantly, where I really think that shows, like, Kill A Kill or
Guru on the Gone have some of the deepest stories I've ever seen, you know, in any medium, and they
can do that while still being something that can also entertain and be, be fairly normal, you know,
whereas in other mediums, like, film, and there are, there are films that do this well, Speed Racer,
great example, deep story, high intensity, fun, you know, wacky kind of presentation,
that totally works with the nature of the story, but I feel like a lot of people feel this pressure
that a film has to either be, or it has to be, you know, like, there's, there's, there's a lack of
the middle ground that should be there, that other mediums are exploring well, and the more I read,
and this is especially true when I read books and fiction, because I've been reading a little bit
more fiction the last, the last couple weeks, and as, I'm not going to say which story, because
there's some I haven't finished yet, and I don't want to jinx myself by saying that I'm reading it,
and then that'll make me never finish it, but I did finish Brave New World, which I hadn't read
before, and that was pretty great, and like, as I read fiction that is some of which is considered
to be super deep, I find that it actually has a much better approach to like, mixing high and
lowbrow kind of ideas, where like, the stories that are considered classics, the ones that are
like really heralded as high art pieces, are not pretentious about it, none of them are these like
stuffy, classy, oh, everything is the, the, the, the perfect, oh, the cinematography, the blocking,
like, it's not quite like that, most of it's actually a lot more experimental in free form,
like the books that people really celebrate are usually the ones that combine like really
heady and interesting ideas with like, this very human, like, rough and gritty kind of feeling,
you know, and, and those are the, those are the ones that are like considered masterpieces,
whereas I feel like, you know, we do get some films that are kind of like that, but then people
always want to take a step back and be like, oh, well, but you know, like, like something like
District 9 is a great example of a film that, that's very dirty and very homey, you know, and
like low budget and gritty, but also has this big message, but even with that movie, I feel like
people are so hesitant to call that a masterpiece, because of the fact that it's not like a classy
high art movie, you know, and I'm like, but that's, but it's a masterpiece, you know, like, how do you,
like, if you, if this was a book that did the same thing, had the same approach, you would
definitely say it was a masterpiece, you know, um, and anime, I feel like the people, like, people
who, who, who consume other mediums and who are kind of ashamed of anime and like its animanness
are only willing to celebrate the stuff that's like classy, you know, and I talked about that,
this is basically what my boring taste in anime video was all about, this whole idea of like,
people who, you know, only want to present themselves as, oh, well, I like, uh, Mushishi and
Legend of the Galactic Heroes and like all these, ooh, these shows that don't have a bunch of dumb
anime shit, but the anime shit is just, it's just human, it speaks to the human condition
as much as anything else, there's a reason we want to watch shows about this shit, and if you can do
that while still conveying an interesting theme and, uh, and premise, especially if it, if the, the
dumb stuff and the high-minded stuff are combined in a way that makes sense, you've knocked it out
of the park, you know, so, yeah, I really think that, uh, that help, it helps me to appreciate anime
even more, to consume deep works and other mediums, and it's really funny to me that that's the case,
because there's so many people who will tell me like, why do you waste your time and your analytical
skills on anime, you could be, you could be reading, uh, Ulysses, you know, and then I read Ulysses,
and I'm like, this is batshit crazy, like this, this, this is just as crazy as anime is, you know,
like, or people who want me to review like some highbrow film because of its deep cinematography,
and I'm like, yeah, you know, I think anime has great cinematography, I think Ava has the
best cinematography of anything I can fucking think of, you know, um, so yeah, I guess that's the
point I'm making, and it makes, it's really cool when I get to like, read comics and figure out
like, where do they relate to anime and manga, and where do, where do movies relate, where do
books relate, and then I can, uh, sort of have this greater cultural understanding of all of them,
and one day I'll have read enough books and read enough comics that I can actually talk about them
in like, a forum with other people, you know, because I feel like, uh, when I've come to realize
about why I don't do that, why I don't talk to other people about like, comics, because I went on
co, uh, the, the 4chan comics board, and I was looking at some of the impressions of like, Dr. Strange
and stuff, and the co, the conversations are very specific, and everyone's very opinionated,
these are all people with like, deeply held beliefs about these characters and stories,
and like, what they want them to be, and I'm, I realized that I'm kind of afraid of being
influenced by that, like, I don't want, even the panel cast is a little, a little scary,
because like, for instance, Jesse will tell me something like, you know, uh, Lady Thor is terrible,
right, he has all these great justifications for it, but what that creates in my mind is like,
the expectation that if I go read Lady Thor, I should expect it to be terrible, when really,
I might read it on my own, and like, because my values in comics might not end up being the same
as Jesse's, you know, maybe I'll see it in a totally different, right, light, I mean, I have no idea
if that'll be the case with Lady Thor in particular, but like, you know, there's a lot of stuff that I
want to form on my own, without having to confront other people's opinions too much until I've made
it there, and then once I have all my opinions, then I can go into that sparring match, and you
know, with a little bit more confidence, and not let myself be swayed by what everyone else is
already thinking about these shows, or these comics, you know, I'm very, I'm the type of person who,
I feel the need to know, like, to feel comfortable that I know everything about what I'm talking about,
before I talk about it, you know, not that I have to be right about everything, but that I
have to have all the information, and like, I'm so careful, even on Twitter, to even mention
having consumed something, because I don't want to have to, like, if I, I almost tweeted out the
other night, saw Doctor Strange pretty good, then read the comic very good, and what I was afraid of
is that the tweets that I would get in response would either be other people's opinions on Doctor
Strange, people telling me which Doctor Strange comics I should be reading instead of the 2015 one,
people telling me to read just some other comic, or see some other movie, or asking my opinion on
the MCU and all this shit, and I was like, I don't want any of that, I don't want any of that right
now, I want to on my own, find my way through Doctor Strange, and if one day I come to the
conclusion that yes, that comic is not as good as this old one, or maybe I thought the movie
could have done this or that differently, then fine, but you know, I'm not ready yet to have other
people sort of affecting my overall perception of comics, you know, I'm willing to let Jesse
guide me through, because I, he's a trusted tour guide, and someone who, who really wants me to
think comics are cool, you know, he wants people to like comics, so it's important to him that,
that you know, that he not try to, that he not end up ruining it for anybody.
So, so yeah, I think it's, it's, it's a fun, fun little trajectory, and I've talked about this
with The DeVoo plenty of times, that I think I am relatively close to having completed anime.
I think that day is coming in the next three years, and here's what I mean by completed anime.
Um, there is a limit to how many shows I think I need to watch, like there's, there's an end goal
to that, because you know, if you go back to anime history, it only goes so far, the first shows,
you know, the first TV shows are from like the 60s, you know, there's movies going back before
that, but not a whole lot of them. It would not take that long to consume all of the things that
I need to, that I haven't seen yet from history, you know, and then there's also a lot of stuff
that I need to rewatch, to reaffirm my opinions on, to like, you know, to figure out how I feel
about them, and lots of stuff I want to cover with regards to both. There's lots of shows I
haven't seen yet that I want to talk about, lots of big concepts, lots of creators I want to follow,
lots of, and lots of older things I've seen before that I want to cover again, and I think
that in three years, I'll have covered all of it. I think within three years, anything, anything
that exists now that I haven't talked about, that I have an idea for, I will have covered in the
next three years. Now, anime is always coming out, so it's not like I'll ever have no anime to talk
about, and this estimation could be a little short, it could be a little, it could be even, um,
maybe I'm overestimating how long it'll take, you know, because I've knocked, I've had some moments
of knocking something out that, like, for instance, music videos. I watched all of them,
you know, for the sake of that, that video, uh, the ten, ten anime music videos you should check
out. I watched all the anime music videos that are out there, you know, with the exception of, like,
some that are not, uh, professional work, or are, um, just not listed on my anime list for whatever
reason, or are a part of, like, a bigger series that I didn't cover. But I've watched pretty much
every anime music video, so that's done. I just, I don't have to worry about that until new ones
come out and I can take them individually as they come. Um, you know, I watched every shinbo show
from the 90s, that's been on my bucket list forever, you know, that's done. I don't have to watch any
of them ever again, I've already talked about them, you know, there's only a few that I'd really feel
the need to go back to if, even if I wanted to. So yeah, there's a chance that within three years,
I will, I will have finished everything I wanted to do with anime, and I'll still talk about it
forever, but at that point, I'll be ready to branch out into other mediums, and I want to have a
footing in those, you know, I want that in three years, in the same way that, like, when I was
fading out of, uh, doing MLP stuff and fading into anime, like, I started introducing anime videos
in there, and like, started, you know, mixing the pot a little bit, and then I, then at some point,
I was full-blown anime, and it was supposed to be anime and everything else, but there's nothing
else I wanted to talk about as much, but I'd love to eventually, like, bleed in other things, or maybe
there's only one anime video every couple of months, but then in the middle, oh, here's a
interesting film analysis, here's a comic book analysis, here's an analysis of a, of this or
that thing, you know, I want to be an everything guy, not just an anime guy, and, uh, and so it'll
be interesting to see if that day comes, and, like, I've been collecting all these charts, I love
collecting recommendation charts, especially from 4chan, because they make tons of them, and I've
been going to every board and just, like, checking until I find charts, and then downloading all the
charts I can find, and just crossing off anything I've consumed, and it doesn't, like, when you look
at one of those charts and you haven't seen anything on it, it looks huge, but then once you've crossed
off ten things, suddenly it doesn't look that huge, you're like, huh, well, it only took me this
long to cross off ten, how long would it take to cross off the other, you know, 60 or whatever,
well, I guess, I mean, it would just be six times what I just did, and what I just did didn't take
a year, so, what, seven years, that's, you know, a reasonable chunk of time, and that's not consuming
all at once, that's while doing everything else, so I think it's reasonable to assume that I could
eventually become cultured in every medium, and, you know, every time I read a book, every time I
read a comic, I'm one step closer, every time I watch a film, I'm one step closer, there's a
finite number of them out there, at least for the time being, a finite, if you will,
even though infinite is not infinite, well, all right, I wasn't sure if I'd have anything else
to follow up with at the end of this podcast, I'd had a few ideas over the last few days, I don't
think I covered any of them, but I don't remember what they were, so, yeah, that wraps up this,
this episode of the DigiBro decompression chamber, I hope you enjoyed it, I really
felt this was like my strongest one yet, I had a lot of fun with all these topics, so
thanks, thanks for listening, go have a nice day, and, or a nice night, as this one will probably
be released at night, daylight savings time ended, so it's like fucking dark outside, it's not even
six o'clock, have a nice night, listen to this relaxing music, and chill out.
you