The Pro Crastinators Podcast
So when Rick and Morty season 2 was first starting, episodes 1 and 2 had been leaked months beforehand.
And the night that episode 1 actually debuted on Adult Swim, the staff had this big party, which I guess is probably a pretty normal thing to do on the debut of your video, but what was unique about this one was that they live streamed it.
They did a whole thing where they had the two creators, Dan Harmon and Justin Boyland, up on a stage, drunk as shit with this interviewer guy, and they were bringing up different people who worked on the show and talking to them for a little bit.
I mean everyone, it's clear that this was primarily just a party that was happening anyways, and they just decided to impromptu do this live stream thing. They just kind of dragged people up for a couple minutes, talked to them, and they'd go back to the party.
With the exception of Dan and Justin who were just up there fucking wasted talking about stuff.
And this was one of the most eye-opening things I've ever watched as a fan. It was deeply fascinating because of the things they were saying about their staff members.
You see, they had completed making the season before it ever went to air, because that's how American cartoons are made, very different from anime which is down to the wire with each episode.
But they were talking about how a lot of their best guys had been poached by Disney, and there's nothing they could really do to stop them.
They brought up their guy who was one of the main showrunners for the season, or assistant directors, or something like that.
And they were both like, yeah, this guy is great. He's been bought up by Disney because Rick and Morty is such a good show that everybody on it is being eyeballed by other people in the industry.
But Rick and Morty itself is a relatively low budget show on Adult Swim. They can't pay these people what they could be getting paid on higher level productions.
And they were like, yeah, he's got a family, and of course he's going to take the job at Disney. They're going to pay him twice what we are, and Dan and Justin are doing this show because they want the creative freedom of being able to work on whatever they get afforded by Adult Swim, which means working for less money.
So of course this guy is going to go to Disney, but they were like, yeah, if season 3 sucks, it's because we lost him.
And I was just like, whoa.
And they were explaining that the reason that season 2 of Rick and Morty took so long to come out, because it was like a year and a half between when season 1 had come out and there was a huge gap.
They had announced season 2 like way ahead of time, and it took forever, and it's taken forever now for season 3.
I mean, we're a year and a half from season 2, and there's still no season 3 yet, even though it was announced after like episode 1 of season 2.
They'd already been greenlit for the next season, which was kind of a shame because by the time episode 1 of season 2 came out, they'd already had a bunch of their guys bought up because there was no guarantee that they were getting a season 3 of Rick and Morty.
And then by the time they had that guarantee, some of their best staff were already gone.
This is the inner workings of the industry.
But they said the reason it took so long to get season 2 is that Justin Roiland is just so talented and so integral to the show that they can't duplicate him.
They can't find someone who's able to bring as much as he is to the show, so it's just that it takes so long to...
Because he voice acts half the fucking characters, he plays the two main characters, he plays a bunch of the other minor characters.
He writes most of the show, he directs most of the show, he's deeply involved at every stage of production.
He does the character designs, I believe.
He fucking basically does everything on the show, and there's just nobody who can fill in the gaps in his workload, and that's why it takes so long for Rick and Morty season 2.
And that blew my mind, and they were saying this guy who was getting bought up was the closest thing they had to someone who could fill in the gaps in Justin Roiland, and now he's gone and they're fucked.
This is basically the way they were putting it.
And I was like, whoa.
And now, I totally relate to that.
Because, and I know this is going to sound conceited, like I'm saying I'm some kind of massive talent or something.
But like, there's a lot of times where I'm like, man, my life would be so much easier if there was just another me to cover some of this ground.
Because a lot of what I make, it's not about me making it, it's about me wanting it to exist.
A lot of the anime videos I do, I would be fine if someone else made them.
If someone else, you know, made a video where they watched every Akiyuki Shinbo show and talked about every technique he used.
I would never have had to do that video.
I would just be like, oh, you did it, cool.
And, you know, I've said this about a number of YouTube videos where I've said, like, now that that guy did it, I don't have to.
You know, people will ask my opinions on shows sometimes and I'll be like, this dude already did it.
So, like recently, someone said, are you ever going to do a video on Berserk?
And I'm like, super eyepatch wolves video on Berserk said everything I would have said about Berserk.
I mean, maybe I could do a video about, like, just the scene where Guts kills 100 guys and just flaunt over how much I like that scene.
But even that, I couldn't fill a whole video, probably.
So, yeah, it's like, it's already out there.
But the problem is that there's so many things that I want to exist and that, like, I can't rely on anyone else to make because nobody else has the time.
Like, who else has time to watch every Shinbo show and write about it, you know?
Who else?
Because no one else is making money doing this, like the way I am.
You know, I feel like I'm the only person doing, like, super in-depth anime analysis and getting paid to do it.
Most of the people doing YouTube videos are not putting out videos frequently enough to make any money.
Like, you know, best guy ever, he has a Patreon and it could become a career one day,
but he puts out videos so infrequently that he doesn't get paid enough for his videos, you know?
And he's not even doing, like, really research driven stuff.
It's more just, like, here's why this thing is amazing.
But, like, yeah, nobody else, I mean, maybe Yuyukau.
I don't know how much money he makes or anything, but, like, yeah, like, there's not a lot of people who could, who would have the time and resources to do what I do.
And there's just so many ideas I have and, like, it can be painful sometimes to, like, realize the sheer enormity of how much stuff falls on me
because there's no one else to do it.
And that really is what I connect to with the whole Justin Roiland thing.
Yeah, there's no way to say it without sounding conceited, but, again, it's not about the quality of what I'm doing.
It's just about wanting those, like, I'm not saying that the world needs a shinbo video, but, like, it's something I want to exist.
And there's too many things I want to do.
That's really the point that I'm getting at.
So Casey Neistat just happened to end his vlog mere days after I, uh, had released the previous, um, decompression chamber in which I talked about how his videos had kind of gotten stale
and how he was probably going to end the vlog soon, and then sure enough, it happened.
I mean, I got a bunch of messages about it, people like, it's your fault, what did you do?
But honestly, it was pretty obvious it was going to happen.
Um, he joked about it.
I mean, he'd said he was going to do it a number of times.
The vlog was not going to live forever.
He had a video jokingly, like, clickbaiting saying that, like, called the end of the vlog, where he was really, like, talking about the end of that vlog, that that was something special.
Um, or something like that, or maybe it was the end of the vlog for a day or some shit.
But I mean, he'd been taking more breaks from it, he'd been saying that he was trying to get more challenges, and honestly, what said to me that the vlog was going to end soon
was this whole thing where he was going to make this, um, he was going to edit this video he shot in Vietnam with his son.
And he kept saying, like, you know, I might put the vlog on hold for a couple of days or something, or like, I might do this and that, I have to edit this video.
And then, like, for the next few vlogs, he kept saying, like, you know, well, um, I'm still working on the video, you know, it's just, uh, it's just taking a little longer.
And I was like, to me, this is a sign that the vlogs are in the way, you know, that he couldn't finish this video because
what little time he has to work on video is going towards the vlog.
So, I had a feeling it was ending soon, and that's why I kind of talked about it that way.
Um, and cause nice stat works the same way I do.
He's all about challenging himself and finding new ways to do things.
Um, for me, it's more a matter of getting bored and having too many ideas and wanting to do something different all the time, as well as being afraid of getting stale.
Um, whereas for him, it's more about the personal growth of, like, doing something that's harder than what you're currently doing.
Anyways, all of that aside, just wanted to address that since it was funny.
Back when I started this podcast, a few people had said that they accidentally misread the title as Digi Bro's Depression Chamber.
Well, that's what today's episode's gonna be.
I'm not depressed right now, but, um, I'm going to go ahead and tell the whole story of when I was depressed.
Like, just everything that happened at the time, for a few reasons.
Um, mostly because I haven't told the story extensively before, and I'm always wanting to tell stories.
It's just that this one is maybe somewhat uncomfortable, you know, if not for me, then for the audience.
Uh, and also because, but I mean, that's all the more reason to do it.
And, um, on, like, the last, it must have been the last Decompression Podcast, or maybe some other video before it,
I was, like, talking about, um, like, part of my experience of being depressed,
and DeVu said, like, when I was talking about it there, it sounded much scarier than it had ever sounded before.
Like, he'd heard me talk about having been depressed, but never really, like, in-depth or anything.
And I was like, huh, that's interesting that that's, you know, because he's listened to everything I've done,
so if he hasn't really heard how scary it could be, then it means I haven't talked about it enough.
And I'm also, I'm 25 years old now, and, you know, every year that goes on, this, these stories of my teenage years become harder and harder to tell.
And it's funny because for me, I regard all of this as, like, really uninteresting.
Even though if someone else was telling the same story, I'd find it interesting,
but for me, there's, like, this weird disconnect where, like, I think of myself as the guy who's, who's been making videos for the last three years, you know?
And, like, anything before that feels like a different person to me.
But that's not at all the case, like, so much of how I act now, and so much of all of this was informed by, you know, how I was in my teenage years.
And so I think, I feel like this story has to be told before it's too late, you know, before I can't remember it in enough detail.
And maybe the fact that I have forgotten details will help to streamline this story to be consumable in podcast form.
I thought about making this its own podcast on After Dark, but, like, because I don't want to do this in video form, it would be too weird.
I have an easier time talking about things I'm less comfortable with if there's no video, because I don't want to have to see myself saying it, or, like, you know, worry about where I'm going to cut audio and stuff like that.
Not as in cut for content, but, like, just edit out silences, because I have to think about what I'm going to say, because I can, like, remember everything.
And I don't really have anything else to talk about this week. I've been playing Pokemon nonstop for two days.
I will probably continue to play Pokemon nonstop for more days until the end of the period where this podcast would be slated to come out.
So anyways, this is just going to be a depression story.
And if that sounds like it'll make you sad, then don't listen to it.
Like, for me personally, when other people talk about depressing shit, it usually, like, doesn't...
I guess back when I was a teenager I did find that kind of stuff comforting.
Like, I did enjoy listening to other people talk about, like, their problems and their depression, because it made me feel like, you know, like I could relate to it.
Nowadays, I just get sad, because I'm not sad normally.
But anyways, yeah.
So, we'll start from when I was a little kid.
And I think as a kid, I don't think I could have been, like, what you would consider, because to me, depression is, like, a long-term feeling of unease and displeasure with your life.
It's where, like, for a huge amount of time, you feel like things aren't going your way and you just want to fucking die.
That's how I think of depression.
And some people have, like, in and out of it. They'll be like, you know, oh, I felt really depressed for, like, a week, and then I was back to normal.
And I guess I still have times like that where I can get depressed for, like, a day or two.
And I guess you'd still call that being depressed in a more general sense.
But I'm talking about depression more in, like, a clinical sense.
Like, seven straight years of feeling like dog shit and wanting to die.
You know, like, that's my experience with depression.
And so, as a kid, like, it's hard to think of it as depression, because when you're a kid, you kind of just flip emotions constantly.
Like, you know, it's just however you feel in that moment is how you feel.
There's less of this, like, broader personal context, I feel like.
Like, when I think back to me being a little kid, there would be days where I felt absolutely terrible.
But then I'd wake up the next day and I wouldn't even remember the fact that I felt bad the day before.
You know, I'd just wake up the next day and whatever happens happens.
There was no sense of continuity between emotions.
So there was a lot of stuff that would make me upset as a kid, because growing up, my family moved constantly.
And I looked weird.
You know, I had big ol' glasses and I looked like a girl.
I had long hair and I was extremely effeminate.
Anybody who's seen that video on After Dark where I said proof that I was a lolly shota.
Yeah, I look like a fucking girl.
Like, there's no two ways about it.
I didn't understand that at the time.
Like, I was just mad that other people thought that.
But I didn't, like, actually think of myself as looking like a girl until, like, later.
So, you know, when I was young, I never made any friends.
Like, it wasn't so much that I got picked on until, like, a bit later.
Like, when I was, like, a little kid, it's just nobody would talk to me.
And I didn't understand how to talk to people because I never talked to anybody.
We'd moved fucking constantly.
I never made any friends, you know?
Like, I remember, I'm sure I went to more than one kindergarten.
I'm sure I went to more than one first grade.
I did stay in the same second grade the whole year I was there.
The first time my parents ever, like, settled down for more than a year in a place was in this cul-de-sac.
We moved into when I was in the first grade.
And me and my friends were sort of the outcasts among the cul-de-sac.
You know, Ed, Ed, and Nettie, we were Ed, Ed, and Nettie.
And everyone else fit the archetypes the same way that the characters in that show do.
Like, that show was like the story of my life when I was a kid.
It was super relatable to me.
With the only exception being that in Ed and Nettie, particularly for Eddie,
you feel like he kind of deserves what's coming to him and the other two wouldn't really be as hated
if not for the fact that they hang out with Eddie.
I kind of saw as it's just victims, you know, when I was a kid.
Like, I just didn't understand why anybody, like, it was so hard to communicate with people, you know?
And I mean, we knew all the kids in the cul-de-sac.
We hung out with them, you know, I hung out with all these people,
but I never felt like they liked me or understood me or, like, wanted to be friends with me with a couple of exceptions.
Just a couple of kids who were my friends.
And so I made a couple of close friends in second grade.
But then what really started me, like, feeling depression, like, understanding it, to some extent,
was when I was in third grade because I got put into this advanced placement school.
It's like a whole, it's called School for Gifted Children, ODC, no, that's the university, ODC.
And it was a, it was just like a separate school for smarter kids.
But it was this huge long bus ride away.
And, like, so at this point, even though, you know, my family up to this point is we move all the time.
I lose contact with everybody I ever knew every time we moved.
This time, I just changed schools, but that still means I'm not seeing any of my friends.
Like, the friends who live around me who I went to school with are suddenly not around me, you know?
And so, uh, so yeah, I went to this, this gifted school.
And first of all, I shouldn't have, because even though I was, like, really excelling,
like, in the second grade, I was making, like, straight A's, you know?
So they all thought, well, this kid's like a genius, you know?
But then at this other school, it was, like, constant pressure to do, like, mountains of work.
You know, it was, it's not that you necessarily have to be smarter to do the work,
it's that they give you more work.
And I was not up for more work.
And so, my grades started falling a little bit.
And this is the kind of school where, like, if you're making C's or below, you're going back to normal school.
You know, like, it's not, it's not about just passing.
It's like you have to be excelling, because that's the point of this, of this school.
And I was not excelling.
And, you know, my mom was pretty harsh about grades.
Like, she was always, like, guilt-tripping me and stuff about the fact that I wasn't, you know, making good enough grades.
She'd sit, sometimes she'd be like, you know, sit in the kitchen and don't leave until you do your homework.
And I just would, like, sit there and just, like, stare at it and not do it.
And I'd just sit there for, like, hours and just stare at my homework.
And, um...
Yeah, so I felt bad about the fact that I wasn't doing great in school.
And then I was also getting more picked on, because this was at a time when Pokémon had come and gone as a big fad.
It's, like, 98 or so...
No, 90? Hmm.
If I'm in third grade, then it's either 99 or 2000.
Pokémon is kind of waned as a fad.
And I'm still wearing Pokémon shirts and stuff to school, because I care about it.
You know, I've always been someone who cares very deeply about whatever I'm into.
And people would make fun of me for wearing Pokémon shirts.
They'd make fun of me for having long hair. They'd make fun of me for wearing glasses.
You know, it never, like, escalated into full-on bullying.
Like, the worst that would ever happen to me is that, like, someone might take my jacket and, like, pass it back and forth amongst a couple of kids, you know,
and I'd be, like, trying to get it back. And that only happened once or twice.
So, like, there wasn't a lot of physical bullying.
It was mostly just people making fun of me, mostly for looking like a girl and liking Pokémon and, you know, all that good stuff.
And I didn't know any of these kids. I didn't know how to talk to them.
I didn't know how to clear up the issue.
So I didn't make a lot of friends.
And I remember that there was one day...
I probably had gotten, like, a report card with a C on it or something.
Or it was either that or I'd been made fun of that day in class, but I was just so fed up.
And I went up, and this story is hilarious and depressing at the same time.
If you listen to a lot of my stuff, you've heard me tell it before, that I went up to my brother's shades room,
and there was this line, like, basically a string of clothespins that went all the way up the wall that had beanie babies.
Like, it's like a type of clothespin that's, like, made to hold beanie babies.
And there's, like, this huge display of beanie babies my mom had set up in my brother's shades room.
Shade was, like, probably three, no, two or three at the time.
So I go into shades room and I'm, like, crying.
Then I sit down and I'm, like, I'm gonna kill myself.
So I take a clothespin and I put one clothespin over my nose and one clothespin over my lips
with the hope that I can suffocate myself.
This obviously will not work.
Not even so much because I started gasping for air,
but because the clothespins hurt to have on my face.
And I've never been able to tolerate pain,
which is good, because that's what's kept me from self-harm over all these years,
is my incredibly low threshold for pain.
Someone there?
Thought I heard somebody.
So, but, you know, even if that was
a hilariously unsuccessful attempt,
I would still catalog that as a suicide attempt.
Because people who
have a history of attempting to commit suicide are far more likely
to commit suicide. Like, if you've thought about it, if you've tried to do it,
there's a chance that you're gonna keep trying to do it, or keep thinking
about it, you know?
And so that was kind of, I mean, I didn't know that at the time, but that's always been kind of a specter
hanging over me when I've been suicidal. It's like, you know, I kind of fit the
profile of someone who would do it.
But again, I can't really think of that as depression, because
I'm sure the next day after that, I woke up
and went about my day, and it was probably not that bad,
you know? Like, I think me being upset and sad back then
was more reactive. It's like I had a bad day, and therefore I
felt depressed. There was less of that hanging bloom.
And then when I started fourth grade at that school, that was just utterly miserable
because our teacher was like a way overblown hard ass.
From what I understand, she was fired shortly after the
year, because I left. Like halfway through fourth grade, I left that gifted
school because I just couldn't keep up. It was too much. And I was
like the third person in the class to leave, and there were like three more people who left
after me. And then that teacher, I heard she got
a hand. Just from like sheer amount of complaints
she was getting about what she does. Don't know how
that works. I don't know why she didn't have tenure or something, but I don't know.
So I go back to normal
school. And now again, I'm in fourth grade, but I don't know anybody.
I'm back to the school I was at before, but I don't know anybody. Everything's
progressed past me. I don't know all these people and what they're up to. I'm still getting
fun of, because now there's like the skater culture
thing, like Tony Hawk's pro skater, Bam Margera era starting to come
in, and there's all these skater kids who are like the cool kids, and I'm
still sitting here with fucking Pokemon. And everyone's like
what the fuck is, what's up with you? Because I never understood trends.
I never understood, I never
observe people. I'm not someone who understands what other
people are thinking easily or like tries to
look out for what everyone else is doing. I was always just doing what I
wanted to do, and I didn't understand why that was a
bad thing. I never understood what I was supposed to be doing.
And then finally, so
fifth grade rolls around, I was in a class with some of my friends again.
Eventually we finally move. We moved to Florida. That fucking
blue ass. But I don't think I was depressed.
And that's where I started doing creative things more.
Moved a few more times. I went through middle school.
But it wasn't really until I was 14, and it was sort of
in between middle school and high school that the depression
really began. And it was because
not only at school did I not really have any friends
and I wasn't really doing anything. But I was starting to become a teenager.
So I was starting to become more hormonal and starting to
understand the world around me a little bit more in a bad way.
Suddenly it's come into full focus that I'm the
weirdo. I think growing up
up until that point I had always thought everyone else is weird for thinking
that I look like a girl or that I act this or that way. Then
suddenly I realized, no, I'm the weirdo. I'm the one nobody understands.
I'm the one who's the freak here.
That suddenly became very apparent to me in the 8th grade.
It was like, oh, I'm the odd man out. I'm the one who doesn't know
what's going on. And that
kind of hit me hard. And I just like
I never made real friends. I would just kind of
hang out with kids who I could joke around with and
at the lunch table. But none of them really liked me. There was a couple kids I would hang out with
at my house. But even then I never felt like we were close.
It's just like someone to do things with. That's kind of what friends were to me.
Someone who had enough of the same interests that you could sit in the same place
and do the same thing together. But then you don't really care about them outside
of that. The only person I ever had who was a real close friend
was my cousin Boyd. He was four years older than me.
And me and him got into anime together. And we like really
hung out all the time when I was in like the 6th and 7th grade.
But then he moved away to Pennsylvania and I didn't see him for like
a few years. So during the period where I then got depressed.
So like, yeah, I didn't have any real good connections. And
my parents started fighting. And there was like a...
Not so much like violent fighting as just, there was like a lot of
it looked like they were going to split up. Like it looked like my parents were going
to divorce. You know, things were getting
like, heck, there was a point where like a brief period where
my dad just like stayed in a hotel for a few days.
You know, like to not be in the same house kind of thing.
So that was like really traumatic. Cause me and my brothers
all thought like, this is it. It's going to, they're going to fucking split up.
You know, and my parents up through this point, you know, they used
to, they used to, my parents don't fight anymore. Like these days they're just
like a fucking docile old couple essentially.
They used to fight. And we'd always be like
this is it. It's finally happening, you know.
So yeah, I was 14. I was the weird kid
in school. My parents seemed like they were going to split up. And this is really where
it just, this is where I would begin like chapter depression,
you know. And I got really,
I was really into online communities at the time. And I spent a lot of time
on these message boards. And I know there was, there was
some poster who will say it was female
for the sake of the story. I have no idea for real.
But I was like in love with this person. So
I was always on these message boards and like, you know, trying to seek out
relationships online. Like I was starting to become aware of the idea of
relationships online and friendships online. But even online I was a fucking
weirdo. Like no one understood me. And I always, I had a very
crass sense of humor, a very confrontational attitude. I
cared way too much about the things that I like and was like ready to fucking
write tooth and nail about anything I liked. You know, you're wrong
for disagreeing with me kind of attitude. I mean, if you think I come
off that way in my videos now, you have no fucking idea how toned down it is.
Like I was a, I was a fucking brat in my teens online.
And you know, most of the people on internet message boards are older.
They're in their later teens or their early 20s. That's like the main age range of people
on message boards. And those people were not having it, you know,
because I was a fucking bratty kid and I don't blame anyone for that.
But you know, that's why I was even online. I felt like an outcast
and I was depressed. So where
it all really spiraled down was my dad
who had been working in the car business for a long time. And he was
my dad's an amazingly hard worker. He had, I mean,
my parents both came from really like pretty much nothing.
You know, my dad in high school had to like steal to
eat and stuff. Like he was deathly skinny. He joined the Navy
when he was 18, dropped out of high school, joined the Navy and like just so he could
eat essentially. He said like, you know, they would give me free food if I joined. So that's why I joined.
And my mom had run away from home at like 16.
So they're both from, you know, like really low class
sort of environment. And my, like they had worked just normal
kind of jobs, but they're both really hard workers and they both would always, you know,
get to management positions quick and stuff like that. And
my dad joined the car business and
was immediately the best salesman like every month. He would always win
salesman of the month. You know, he'd always move up the ranks through the car industry.
So he'd been fairly successful at that. So we've been living, you know, the
middle class suburban life for a long time. Well
my dad was going through all this like spiritual shit. He was becoming like
a Christian and constantly reading spiritual texts
and stuff and just generally felt that the car business
was not in line with his like current, you know, state of mind and
lifestyle. And my parents were trying to make up after all this fighting
they've been doing and we were like, let's move again. And we moved into downtown
Richmond and we moved into this old ass house. It was like a
house built in like the early
1900s or something like that. And it was
huge and it was really cool, but it was like kind of, you know,
falling apart. But because it was so old and so falling apart,
it was really dirt cheap. So we got to get a huge house for dirt cheap. And my dad
became an apprentice electrician. So his wage,
you know, plummeted from what it used to be.
And we lived in this house from like September
through February, I want to say. 2004 to
2005.
No, 2005 to 2006. From September to February.
Something like that. It was six months that we lived there.
And those six months were grueling.
That was by far the worst period of my life. And I've often
said of that period that I think I might have legitimately gone insane.
Like I was losing my fucking mind. Because we moved into this
big old house and we were in the middle of
like the ghetto. We were in the ghetto
in like downtown Richmond. Me, Victor and Shade, we all,
I was in high school. Victor was in middle school. Shade was in elementary school. We went to
like all black schools. Like there was no white
kids there at all. Like maybe, I would see like five or six white kids in the whole
school. Mostly black and Latino and stuff.
And it was really hard to make any friends that way.
Because I mean, I've been an outsider among white people. You know, the school
I was going to before that was all white people. And I still felt like an outsider.
Now I'm the only fucking white kid and
I'm a fucking weird white kid. You know, so I was not able to
make any friends at this school. No one would talk to me. No one
wanted anything to do with me. I totally just looked like an outsider to their culture
and everything. It was like this kid knows nothing about what's going on
here, you know. So I felt totally
alone at this school. And
I had, you know, at this point I had
super long hair and I was growing in like this shitty ragged facial hair.
Kids would always call me Joe Dirt and
I started wearing sweatpants all the time. No fashion
sense. I looked like total shit, you know, and nobody wanted to talk to me.
This is at the period where I'm starting to like, you know, really like
want a girlfriend and stuff like that. That's not happening,
obviously. And at home
I just felt like I couldn't talk to anybody. Like no one else
understood what I was going through, you know. My parents have always been hard to
talk to about anything emotional because they just don't seem to get it
or they don't get where you're coming from. Like their mindset is kind of like
how could you possibly not be happy when you've got so much,
you know. Not that that would have been the case at this time, but like
I didn't see a lot. Jesus Christ, the fucking wind is like
rattling my house. I didn't see my family as much
as I had before, you know. And Victor just
kind of holed up in his room and played a lot of GameCube and
part of it was that like in the previous
house I'd been really into video games. Like I'd gotten
huge into gaming and like particularly
RPGs. And I'd buy tons and tons of RPGs with all the allowance money
I could get. So like probably 20 to 25 dollars a week I'd get. And I'd
go out and buy all these used games at GameStop.
So I had a decently sizable collection of PS2 RPGs that I had recently
accrued. Then my PS2 broke. Like right when we moved.
So gaming out the window. Cause all the new
games I had or was excited about were all PS2 games. Now I don't have a
PS2 and we can't afford to buy a new one. You know, the GameCube was still there
which we had had all these games from like 2001 till then.
But Victor had that and so I just wasn't playing a lot of games
and I didn't have any money to buy anything. There was no passion which I could
support here. Now I remember that it took a month
for the internet to get hooked up in this house. Like we moved
in and it was a whole month without internet so I couldn't go onto these message boards
where I'd been like living. I couldn't
do anything really. I had my
own computer but it didn't have internet access. So all I used it for was like
writing poems and listening to whatever music I had on there.
And that month just kind of broke me. It's like I had no one to
talk to. No one online. No one at school. Like
if I hadn't had Victor and Shade around I probably would have just utterly
lost it. Like if there had been literally no one to ever talk to I don't
I think I would have fucking gone completely insane. But I would just like lay around
and cry essentially. I would just lay on my bed
despondent for days.
This is where I started keeping a knife under my mattress
just in case the day finally came that I could kill myself.
I'd be ready.
And again I was super guarded about all of it. I wouldn't talk to anybody about the
idea that I was feeling bad. Anyone I was in front of they didn't get to know about
this. The internet finally did
get hooked up in this house. So I was on the message boards again. But the internet
was like the most painfully slow. Like you click
on something and it takes like up to five minutes to load a page.
So I'm on message boards like
refreshing the page and then like waiting five minutes for it to refresh and then
refreshing again until someone says something and then I immediately reply
you know and then wait all day to see if the response will come.
That was my life. Sitting on a message board waiting for people to
say something so that I can respond and then waiting more.
And then loading the page and loading the page and
if I remember correctly
I guess I had taken the speakers from my mom's
computer because she wasn't really using them and I had those in my room because my computer had a bunch of music
on it. Obviously music streaming was not a thing yet but I had
a bunch of music downloaded to my computer from my cousin having put it there
or ripped CDs I'd put on there. So
the only internet, the only computer that had internet was in my mom's office and so I would sit
in her office in silence all day reloading this fucking page
waiting for anything. I started
questioning my sexuality a lot. I definitely
thought I was bisexual for a while. For a little while I thought I might be gay.
I had like a very brief internet relationship
with a guy which turned out super weird and I bailed on.
And anytime I was always trying to seek out you know internet relationships. Basically
anyone who would pay enough attention to me to talk to me I would try to
establish a relationship with. And there was a couple people who did who in retrospect
I realized were like utterly broken people.
People with way way way worse you know stuff
going on than I have. So
you know I mean I guess I was pretty broken at the time too. So like it was me
like trying to enter like little relationships with other horribly
broken people. And then it would always get weird for me at some point
like when it started to feel real that's when it would feel weird to me
and I would break it off in the most like ass whole way
possible. Like I'd always say something like you know
you know I just I was just using you
for my own fucking gain or something and like you know I actually
don't care about you or anyone and I'm just I hate the world. You know like that's the kind
of I would just totally break off communication with people
and do it in the most dick hole way that I could think of.
So
I lived in that house for six months and I think everybody was pretty fucking depressed and upset.
I don't think anybody liked being there. My dad finally
took back up he got back into the car business
because I mean this had been the second time that he had left the car business only for
everything to go to shit because when we moved to Florida a few years prior that was the same
story. He'd left the car business we went to live with my aunt
for like three months. Then like it was such a nightmare that
they like fully paid our trip back home to rehire my dad
at a higher position because they wanted him so badly
and it just was like utter misery but again I wasn't really depressed yet at the time.
This is more like outright depression. So finally
we moved back to Virginia Beach which is the city I live in now. I've lived here a lot
like a lot of those houses were in Virginia Beach
so we moved to Virginia Beach and like a little house
I started going to this high school in the ninth grade where I ended up going
for the rest of high school.
But at this point again
like you know I'm a new kid again
still not making any friends still kind of like just a weird
guy. Now I'm depressed now I don't know what the fuck to do
with myself. So
I started collecting music but no one
to talk to about it. No one understood my fucking
taste in music. No one understood what I was going through and it just
fucking sucked and I was miserable all the time and I hated living
the end.
Eventually as high school went on
I started making friends slowly but surely
I started accruing a little stable of friends who would come over
all the time and hang out and you know that made things a little better.
And then really like for a little while what had kind of saved me
was getting back into anime because you know I'd been really into anime
in 2003 and then I kind of you know got into other stuff
video games and music and then in 07 at like the very beginning of the year
I got into anime in a much bigger way thanks to the megatocchio forums
and that's when I started my blog and like
watching anime and blogging made me really happy like that was the one
thing I had going on that made me super duper happy and
made it like way easier to deal with life. But I was still
constantly bouncing between like utter terror
especially because this was now at the time where you know I'm in high school and everyone's talking about
what are you gonna do in your future and like for me it was
always the debate of am I going to take school seriously and go all out
or am I going to leave because I sort of looked at it as an all
or nothing it's like either you're going to stick around in school and really
excel and make great grades and you know and go to a good college
or because if you don't if you don't go to a good college is no point
so you might as well just drop out and go do whatever the fuck you want.
And this was like you know I was a God
finishing up 10th grade and I was about to go into 11th when all
this is happening when I'm getting into anime and all that again
still kind of depressed and then like
I was just like constantly bouncing between like being paranoid
or just stressed out or not wanting to talk to people or just not feeling
comfortable in my own body you know.
I got really interested in like all kinds of like
BTQ stuff like I was super obsessed with that in my late teens like
just I guess I identified with that sense of like
not being sure if you are who you're supposed to be
you know like for a while
I thought that like maybe I'm
supposed to be a woman you know but I never like took it very far
in the way that people do now I think because the culture embraces it so much
that there's places like Tumblr where people are like you know you can
easily meet people who are doing stuff like that that it's so much more of like a thing
people like jump headlong into in their teens whereas for me
it was kind of like an interesting question that like every once
in a blue moon I'd hear something about
you know about like gender fluidity or something like that
and well I guess that term probably didn't even exist yet just people changing
genders and stuff and I was like whoa and I'd be like super fascinated with it
became super obsessed with Yuri
and lesbians and like that was all I cared about for a long time
was Yuri and
then like
so I remember over that summer I watched Minabi
Straight and utterly broke down because at the end of that show
it's about like the main characters graduate high school and they all sort of go their separate ways
and you see them all like one girl goes to America to continue her studies
one like goes into sports they go into
all this different stuff and Minabi herself she just
becomes a freeder as they call it where she just goes
between different part-time jobs and like doesn't stay to one place and everyone was kind of like shocked
by it but she was like yeah you know like she's free-spirited she'll be happy
wherever she goes and that just like totally broke me
because I was like fuck you know and I was trying to like
do the academic route like I was setting myself up that I was gonna do like advanced placement
English and I was gonna go to like our school had this program called ATC
where you go to like a technical school and like a
they bust you back and forth to learn more technical stuff and I was gonna try to do that
you know I was like ready to try to do this fast track thing and then I watch Minabi
and I see her like yeah you know I can be happy wherever I go and I was just like
like utterly mind broken like trying to
decide you know am I going to become a school guy or
am I gonna like like look at Minabi she could have fucking done anything
and been happy about it why can't I just go do anything
you know I became really obsessed with the idea of becoming a film director
and so 11th grade started
and I sort of got fucked
in regard because basically there was a miscommunication between
me and my guidance counselor and I ended up not being able to go to
ATC I did get the advanced placement English class but that's the only
advanced thing I had so I was no longer on this like you know like
excellent track to success and the technical courses that would have given
me the kind of knowledge that would have like allowed me to fucking do
things you know totally out the window
advanced placement English fucking sucked I hated my teacher I hated the whole style of
the class you know I love literary analysis
obviously it's what I do you know and at the time
I was like I was always happy to write analytically it's that the teacher
wanted you to read everything a certain way you know she was she
she had her idea of what the story means and you had to kind of bring
that out it was fucking horrible
I hated it and it was way too much work and so I became
the most depressed ever and you know I'd met my
friend Don Son and like we bonded over mutual
love of welcome to the NHK because that for me was the most relatable thing in the world
and I remember I would just sit in my room like paranoid
and not leave and I just talked to him about how
paranoid I was you know and he was also he was a hikikomori like a full blown one
like not even leaving his room for like years
because he had a he had a condition that kept him out of school so he would just like be
in his room all day every day and not leave and we kind of bonded over that
but you know that's that's where I was going and there was like
times where I would get so paranoid about my grades because my grades were slipping
and I didn't want my parents to know so like I'd get like a report card or a
progress report and I'd just like lock myself in my room all day
and like I would be I was I never actually did
reach this point because I'm squeamish about doing so
but like I would take bottles and be like I'm gonna piss in this bottle instead of going downstairs
to use the bathroom because I don't want my parents to see me you know
never ended up doing that I just hold it all day I'd like I would hold in peeing
for hours like waiting till I thought everyone might be
asleep or that no one would hear me come down the stairs and ask about my progress report
you know like I was so fucking paranoid
and just yeah I didn't want to see anybody I didn't want to talk to anybody
I just wanted to hold up in my room and watch anime and write my blog and post about
shit you know and I mean you can read a lot of a lot of my writing from this
era is on my blog and a lot of it's just like well there's a lot of posts
I set to private because they were just like a like nonsense of nothing to do
with the blog but like a lot of it would just be me telling stories about
how fucking sad I am you know I wrote about Manabi
straight in my reaction to it years back and I wrote about
Evangelion and how that was like a huge connector for me
when I was 14 when I first got depressed
like someone had loaned me the show and I watched all of it like just before my
15th birthday that blew my fucking mind because I related to Shinji so perfectly
everything about him was exactly how I felt
but so yeah
you know I'm just wandering through this life of being depressed and fucking
like it was never worse than 11th grade like that early part of 11th grade
when I was in advanced English and stuff and like just being overwhelmed by work and stress
I just I wanted to kill myself
badly and like I would have these
nights where I just lay in bed thinking about
like how I'm either going to run away the next day like I'd extensively plan out
how am I gonna run away where am I gonna go how am I gonna live off the land
you know and just like escape from life
or how am I gonna kill myself how can I do it
where it won't hurt or where like how can I get the materials how can I
you know but then I worry about like what are my parents you know how's it gonna affect them
like I don't want to devastate my mom you know like my mom
would fucking not be able to handle one of her kids killing themselves she would have
completely broke like she would have she would have lost
her mind if one of us killed ourselves because she cares way too much
about us you know um so yeah like
that that was a huge like factor preventing me
but then I would just think well what if I just hurt myself like if I hurt myself
sadly enough people have to notice because that's the thing I wanted someone
to notice I wanted someone to notice that I was freaking out that I was
depressed and stressed out but I wouldn't tell anybody
you know I didn't have the courage to talk about it
but I just wanted someone to figure it out and like in my mind I thought
don't I look horrible don't I look depressed like I'm scowling
all the time aren't I don't I look sad but then any time I look at myself in the
mirror I'd realize I didn't look that way I just look normal like I don't
have an emotive face I don't really show what I'm thinking
I have an amazing poker face if you will
you know I would literally think that I looked depressed and then see
myself in the mirror and realize I looked normal and I'm like this is why nobody's noticing
this is why nobody's noticing the cry for help that's only on the inside
you know the few times I had to deal with anything with my parents
I would write them notes because I was you know I was confident in my writing
so I would just like write out these like multi-page notes and leave them on the table
before school like where I was like way more honest about what I was
thinking or what I was trying to do um there was one where I was like
I want to drop out of school here's my plan you know I wrote out this whole thing
and my parents were just like what the fuck are you talking about you know uh no
so you know throughout 11th grade
I determined I was going to drop out I was going to drop out and become a film director
I was just going to start making movies um
yeah and I was really that was like where my head was at
and at this time I reconnected with my cousin Boyd and eventually
like around the time I was finishing up 11th grade and going into 12th
he moved in with me like into my room um
so I would say that that that gave me less like I had less
sit around and be paranoid and like fucking you know losing my mind
and going crazy so uh I guess that helped
though I still was you know largely depressed and we never got
anything off the ground with regards to film um you know
I was trying to I was trying to make movies that never worked I tried to write stories
I have like just the other day I was going through all my notebooks of all the story concepts
I had there's fucking like dozens and dozens of them
there's so many story ideas I tried to get off the ground that never amounted to anything
you know because for 10 years I thought I was going to be writing fiction
or uh or you know producing some kind of some kind of fictional
stories so I have tons and tons of stories that just never came to be anything
um I you know I was working on the
blog all along just because it made me happy I never thought there'd be a future in it
I never thought that was something that would take off and like
there was a period where I thought well maybe I can do this professionally by writing for
a website um there was one time I submitted a review
to anime news network and they tore me to shreds
uh because of the fact that I like spoke in first person and that it was
like it was more personal than objective which I guess they tried to go for
so-called objective reviews um so I got rejected hard
uh not that I think that review was actually good but
you know um so for a long time I was kind of under the impression
like I'll never be able to get work for a website
because the way I write is too out there like I write about myself
I write gonzo style posts and that's like I don't want to change
that like it wouldn't be fun anymore if I just wrote like articles
you know that that's not my style then it would just be a job
um
I was 16 where I had this like sort of
phrase I came up with because I've never believed in any
kind of higher power I've never believed that there's really meaning to human life in the
universe I've always had that sort of nihilistic outlook
I've never believed that there's anything more
to life than personal
personal happiness you know making your own life good
is world good but it's always going to be in small parts and like really part of
making the world good is making your own life good you know
um global happiness comes when everybody's happy and if you're not happy then
you're dragging down the global happiness you know
so to me making myself happy was the most important thing
and I had determined when I was 16 that like if I'm not
happy there's no reason to be alive like what could possibly
make it worth it like like if there's no greater
cosmic purpose to my existence then why even be alive
if I'm not happy I just that was like the the great question
at the heart of it and so to me every second that I wasn't happy with
my life was just a countdown to suicide like you know
uh if the but the the thing that kept me going is that I've always been very
optimistic and very uh like yeah in spite of all
the depression and cynicism I've always been a hardcore optimist I always
think things are gonna go okay you know and like so
what kept me going is that like I always believed that I was gonna get
out of it I always believed like eventually this will all
end and I'll become like rich and famous you know because that's always been
my goal be rich and famous particularly rich uh
you know I want I want to have enough money that I can kind of do whatever
I want with it and I want to be doing what I love I want to
be rich and famous from doing what I love and I always believed that was
gonna happen I always thought eventually I'm gonna write the story that
that breaks I'm gonna make a movie that breaks you know
something's gonna give something's gonna happen and I'm gonna succeed
and I never stopped believing that which is why I wouldn't kill myself like
even when I desperately wanted to it was like but if I do then these ideas never
come out you know the success never comes if you if you give up
so just keep fucking bashing your head against the wall
until it breaks you know it's sort of always been my mentality
just why shows like girl in the gun resonate with me so much like it's about overcoming
what appears to be impossible no matter how long it takes
and how much effort so that's sort of what kept me
going and uh but yeah
again the cries for help like the worst
one I remember the scariest thing I did was
that like I wanted to somehow hurt or
or kill myself I didn't I just you know again I'm terrified of pain
and I just put my hand on my shoulder
like just like you know like grabbing like the back of my shoulder and I just
started scratching like just up and down scratching my back
and I probably had pretty long nails
and I just kept doing it for like 25 minutes
like just like thinking about how badly I hoped that eventually
I'd you know either bleed
or something or like it would cause something just anything anything that
would make this noticeable you know and I'm just scratching this back part of my shoulder
for like 20 minutes and then finally
look at my fingers and I see that there's all this
blood caked in under my nails and I freaked out
because that's the thing I want like even though
one part of me wants there to be pain the second I register that it's
there it's suddenly terrifying you know so I go running down
to the bathroom I look and I have all these fucking you know these four trails
of blood from where I've just scratched fucking all the skin off my shoulder
and I just freaked out and I didn't tell anybody I covered it you know it was
it was all within shirt range none of it was something that would show on my body
so you know my shoulder hurt for a day or so and then
it was gone but like it was fucking terrifying to think like
to realize like I've actually done something to myself I've actually
hurt myself you know
so yeah so that's kind of the general state of mind
for most of high school just
sitting around in my room hoping to die waiting for the day I get to die
you know or that something succeeds or that I break through
it had to be one or the other it's an all or nothing scenario either I
make something so good that the world loves me or
I fucking end it all in squalor
and
the decisions I made from then on from like high school
onwards were all about sort of prolonging the inevitable
because I really thought that if I got a normal
9-5 job and eventually gave up on
creativity that's when I'd die that's when it would finally kill me
if I was unable to live doing what made me happy then
that's what's finally gonna do me in so as high
school is ending my dad's like you have to either get a job or go to college
pick one and I pick college obviously and this is when I moved
like we moved into the house I live in now right when I was right after
I graduated high school and I've lived here for 7 years so
going on 8 so long time
this is the house I've lived in by far the longest finally stopped moving around
like when I was in you know when I was in high school we moved once but it was
the same high school zone as was this house
but I was out of high school by then so
so I start college I start going to community college and I was for whatever
reason for years I was terrified of driving my mom wanted to start
college too so me and my mom went together we both went to an art college
and you know she would drive me and we would go out
and you know spend most of the day there and come back and so yeah I went to college
with my mom hilariously enough
and you know it didn't make it nothing was any
better there like I felt more okay I like college way
more than school like high school fucking blows high school is the worst experience of my life
college is fine it's just like
I didn't want to do it you know that's the worst thing about it I don't think there's
anything wrong with it like I mean there's a lot wrong with it as an institution in
terms of the fact that it costs way too much fucking money and
it's way too inconsistent with how useful it actually is you know some professors
are worthless some are okay some classes will teach
you something and some classes will teach you absolutely nothing
and there's no difference in how much those cost you know so like
I don't advise college but in terms of like a place to go
and do a thing it's not so bad it's not like high school
it's just a miserable draining fucking nightmare of an experience
it's fine I just didn't care
I didn't want to do it and I had middling grades in all
my classes and I wasn't doing all that well now
as it went on like we did one semester
with me and my mom and then my dad
convinced me and my cousin boy who was still living in my room he convinced
us like that we should try to start studying business because my dad
has always kind of had this dream of opening a family business
but he only wanted to do it if we were all going to take it seriously
and he didn't think we would he was like you know you guys have not proven that you can actually work on
anything so he said if you guys could study business and learn
how to do it and like prove to me that you understand it then we could open up a
family business and we were like well that sounds promising business classes
you can take all of them online don't ever do this
never take all online classes unless you're really confident that you can
do all the work because I signed up for like
three or four business classes all online
um this is where everything broke down
this is where it finally broke me
because I have a guilt complex about not doing
well you know like I want my parents to think that all the money they've
poured into me and all the livelihood that I've stolen from them has not gone to waste
you know I want them to be proud of me and to think I'm doing well
but I didn't like school and I was not going to do it you know and
most of my days would consist of me sitting
around thinking about how badly I need to do this schoolwork
and I wouldn't do anything else because you know
there's something else and that's distracting you from the schoolwork
but I didn't want to do the schoolwork so I would just sit around depressed
and hate myself and hate my life and hate everything I'd gotten myself into
and um there was a brief period where I tried to
turn my business studying into anime blogging
if you go through my blog you can find posts I wrote about both
Gorilla Gonnett's Serial Experiments Lane where I took chapters of the textbook
and like applied them to anime in order to
make it interesting for myself because I had realized while reading the textbook
that anime blogging and textbooks were actually fairly similar like you're
basically just describing facts about a thing
so like yeah I tried to do that didn't keep it up for very long
I probably wrote like two posts and then
there's like a deadline for when you can cancel
classes and I knew well ahead of this deadline
that I should cancel but I was too afraid to admit it
I didn't want to admit to my parents that
you know that I was going to drop out that I couldn't do it
that there was a waste of time and you know my parents kept asking me like every day
they'd ask like are you doing the work are you doing the online coursework and I'd always go
yeah like we'd be at dinner and just like mm-hmm yeah sure
I'm in the eye and say it I think they knew I was fucking lying
because why else would they ask all the time you know
I was just lying about it and then the day fucking passed
like the time passed and then I just felt
even worse because it's like well now I fucked them out of all the money
they could have got their money back before this date and because I'm too much of a fucking
coward to admit that I'm not doing the work now all that money's gone probably over
a thousand dollars is community college you know it's not it's not like I'm wasting
university dollars but which would have been absolutely
devastating but yeah I mean it was a waste of a huge
amount of money and I just I just wasn't doing it wasn't
doing the work and eventually I mean my mom
like your grades in these classes are on this online thing called
blackboard my mom has the password to my blackboard she can look at my grades
anytime she wants you know but I think my parents knew that I was
failing and they were trying to like get me to say it so it's one day
my mom starts asking me about my grades I'm like downstairs hanging out and she starts
asking and I'm just like avoiding the question she's like you know I
have your blackboard password and I just like retreat I just like ran I just
ran up to my room I closed the door I had a fucking panic
attack now if you've never had a panic attack it's
where your heart starts racing you start breathing heavily like
you're like you feel like you're like everything there's like lots of adrenaline
and feeling like you're gonna pass out at the same time like you it's just like your
heart and body are out of rhythm with one another I was just freaking the
fuck out you know and I'm just like it's over
she knows she knows she's definitely seen my grades I don't know what the fuck I'm thinking
I don't know what I'm trying to hide this was when I was like
I need help because
like I've there's this line and welcome to the NHK
that resonates with me so strongly it's in the anime
when Satou there's like this other guy who's a Hikikomori
who they meet later into the show and the guy says at one point like
you know all those shelves are lined they're in his room he's got all these bookshelves
all those shelves are lined with self-help books I've read them all I could probably
write one myself and none of it's helped and that
was that was how I felt at the time I'd read everything about
how to get yourself out of depression how to how to be a positive thinker
how to you know stop worrying and love the world
kind of thing like I'd read all this shit and I too felt I could write one
you know but it wasn't helping none of it was helping
none of it was actually getting me out of this situation none of my
personal effort none of the effort I'd put in over the last six years
because I'm 20 at this point you know six years
maybe I'm maybe I'm 19 I'm 19 at this point
so five years of trying to get out of
it and it just wasn't happening nothing was getting me out of it
nothing was working and I was like
this has got to be clinical like there's just no way there's no way I'm getting
out of this I've tried everything I could I've looked up you know my dad
has always been had the kind of attitude that like you can just get through things
you know that's that's why it was impossible for me to talk about this with my dad because he saw
it as a personal strike you know well you just got to work
hard and you know you just got to pick yourself up
and I'm like yeah I've tried that you know I can't work hard because I'm
fucking depressed because I don't want to work I don't want to do anything you know
there's no making myself want to do these things
I don't understand what you think I can do but that's not a thing I can do
so that's when I was like this must be fucking clinical
there's nothing I can do about this I've tried all that I can
and it's none of its work so let's seek help
so uh you know
I'm like I've looked into a lot of this shit online
I've been researching suicide this whole time and I'm constantly looking up stuff about suicide
stuff about depression you know I'm always trying to figure out what the fuck
is the issue or what I can do about it
so I found out that if you were to go to a hospital
and tell them I think I'm gonna kill myself then they'll like
they'll you know they'll put you in like a room and fucking look at you or whatever
uh and hold on to you until someone shows up to
and claim you or whatever so I was like alright
here's what I'm gonna do and this is what I did
I wrote out a letter to my parents because again I can only really communicate through writing
at like 2 in the morning because my dad wakes up
at 4.30 am 2 in the morning I uh
write this letter extensively explaining like I'm depressed I've failed
those classes you're not getting that money back you know I'm
I don't know what the fuck I'm doing with my life I'm never getting any better
I've tried everything I know this stuff inside and out and nothing's
gonna happen unless I fucking get help uh you know
I'm going to the hospital I've ridden my bike to the hospital
uh you know you can come find me and so
I caught on my bike in the like frigid fucking
February air I was wearing a t-shirt so I didn't
want to grab a jacket and then once I was out the door I didn't want to go back inside
so I'm fucking freezing uh writing my bike
down the fucking like like you know miles up the road
to the hospital and I show up
and I sit in the waiting room and it just so happens that the way the waiting
room is laid out and because it was so late no one could see me
no one ever noticed I was in the hospital I sat in there for probably
an hour and a half to two hours uh with
like CSI playing and I was just holding and I
I didn't have my own cell phone so I'd taken my mom's phone like I'd written the letter like
you know if you need to call me I have mom's phone um
so I had my mom's phone on me and I was just holding onto it sitting in the lobby
of this hospital for like hours no one noticed I was there
finally I get a call from my dad like are you still at the hospital and like
I'm you know shaky voice like yeah he's like you know have they
seen you yet I'm like no he's like just stay there we're gonna come get you so they
show up huge teary eyed fucking dramatic
spectacle we go back home they finally set me up with an appointment
with a psychologist so all the psychologists for a
while honestly like it's funny
because for me the value of a psychologist
was simply that I could talk to someone who actually understood what the
fuck I was talking about like I don't think I learned anything from him
I don't I don't think it was a process of like there was something I didn't know
about myself that had to be unearthed you know there was no
there was none of that and I also think he was you know
he was milking me this this dude everything everything about the place I was
at was kind of shady I think this dude kept me coming back for longer
than necessary because it was paying you know
and but like just the fact that I could talk to somebody
who actually knew where I was coming from who understood what depression is
who understood these hangups I had and where my anxiety was coming from
and why I felt that way that was enough to make it worth it to me
you know that nobody else I could talk to would understand any of that shit
and uh so I saw him for a while and then
he got me to go to the psychiatrist and the psychiatrist prescribed me
a medication called Wellbutrin now I do not recommend this
medicine to anybody because even though it did work for me lots
of people who've taken it have had utterly devastating effects
my brother Victor who turned out was also depressed
and he sort of came out about it around a year year and a half later
um he kind of went through the same thing he was depressed for a super long
time decided there was nothing he could do about it finally reached out
for help you know partly inspired because I had done it starts taking medications
Victor went through like four medications and every single one of them made him worse
and Wellbutrin was the one where he was the most
suicidal he'd ever been cried all day he he said
like the the the most heavy moment of his life is like he was sitting there
crying and listening to the song sleep forever by Portugal the man
and just thinking about suicide and my dad came in and saw him
crying and just came over and just like you know held him as he
wet that he was like that was the worst thing that's ever happened to me
um the worst I've ever felt in any case
and I yeah but for me I got
prescribed this medication uh by a guy who was like
obviously just pushing it like that dude the guy who actually prescribed me
didn't know shit about me didn't know the first fucking thing about me
and every time I'd walk in like for another appointment he would just write me up the
fucking thing and send me on my way you know he'd like ask how's it going
like how how's the medication treating you and I had a lot of concerns like
for instance that it had this horrifying side effect that made me fucking blink
constantly uh you know he'd just brush him off
he'd be like oh well you know you'll get used to it
and stuff you know eventually it'll all start making sense
that's the kind of attitude he had
so yeah I started taking this medication
and I went back to school I did
one English class and then I did another semester
of like um like general studies and shit
and maybe another semester after that but eventually
I was like at some point
I got I got a D in psychology which I had thought of as a passing
grade but then I found out that a D is too low for it to be a transferable credit
and I actually liked the class I liked psychology and that's when
I was like I can't do college there's no way I can do this if
I'm failing a class I like then this is not this is not for me
you know but what about butron did
um to me it was mostly an anxiety cure
not so much that it cured depression that it cured anxiety because my
biggest problem really was anxiety that I would get so hung up on like
you know not doing my homework or that something bad was going to happen
if I didn't do this or this or that I wasn't getting my life together like all those things made me anxious
but well butron allowed me was to stop giving a fuck
it was not that it allowed like made me work better you know it didn't
make me actually do my schoolwork it made me stop being anxious
about the fact that I wasn't doing my schoolwork so it didn't make me
any more successful or better of a person it just made me someone
who wasn't fucking anxious all the time you know who
like instead of going oh my god I'm not doing my homework
I can't watch anime but if but I also don't want to do my homework so I'm not going to do anything
I would like I would just go watch anime instead of doing my homework
so that's what it offered me
so I dropped out of college and then I spent like a straight year and a half doing
nothing you know
I got through the summer that summer I went out to
I went for a month to the Philippines and
to see my friend ghost lightning anime blogger extraordinaire
and hung out with him for a month and like the hope was that was going to instill something
that was going to become more worldly you know and I mean I feel like I did
but the results were not what my dad was hoping for you know I did not
come home and immediately get a job I came home and immediately
like interviewed for a job working for one of
the dealerships that for the BMW dealership that was under
my dad's company and they said they would hire me and I never
went back I just didn't want to do it I didn't want to work
and I spent a straight like then my mom that fall my mom got
cancer and so I spent a lot of time like being the guy who would
drive her to and from appointments and I kind of made that my excuse for not working
and then time just kept going on and I just kept not doing
anything you know I mean my parents were bugging me about it they were stressed about it
but you know they had their own shit to worry about I was just like
not doing anything then finally
it was when I found out about Egoraptor and John Tron
and when Game Grumps started and they talked about how it was actually their job
to make YouTube videos that like everything clicked and I was like I can do this
I can make YouTube videos like I have a clear well spoken voice
I understand like I write in this style already
I can make people care about this
and then I started the YouTube series Adventure Action
RPG on Modal Soul Productions which is video games analysis
that's what I thought I was going to be doing but the audio
was garbage and so I thought well I need a microphone so I went and got
a normal job at Target worked there for like four months
bought a bunch of equipment left the job became
my little pony analyst and achieved YouTube success
and I haven't really been depressed since then I would say I stopped like
again the well butrin really did cure my anxieties
which were the main source of my depression and so even though I was
still like upset with myself for the fact that I wasn't really doing anything and I was just living stagnantly
I was I never became that level of anxious and paranoid
again and I eventually stopped taking the medication like
I hated the side effects and
and I felt like well I'm already fucking I'm you know I'm not depressed anymore so fuck it
I stopped taking them and nothing you know I did not regress
I just stayed the same forever so I think whatever it
was I think I think there was just a point when I was 14
when we when when my parents were gonna split up and when
you know we were moving into the ghetto and I was going through hormonal changes
I think that I just like had I think
at some point there became a deficit in the amount
of like whatever you know chemical keeps you happy
there was a deficit in that and it never recovered
like like you know let's say it's producing at a constant rate and therefore
let's say it's like five right let's say you always have five
of this this item in your head and you know
every day you expend one and a new one comes up and then it feels like
I expended three all at once and so even though a new one kept
coming up it was never bringing me back up to five
and when I took the well butrin it brought me back up to
five and and I've stayed that way that's how it feels to me
like it was just a sudden dip and then a sudden
rise and I've been fine since you know again
not that I was like happy or anything I just wasn't depressed
and and then once I started my job and
became successful on YouTube now I've just been happy you know and I do have
times where I get depressed but it's much more in that conventional typical
every man yeah I felt depressed for a few days because
I wasn't happy with how things were going you know I haven't had a
major catastrophic I want to fucking kill myself every day
depression since then
and you know right now part of the reason I wanted to talk about this
is that my fucking friends are depressed
Ben's depressed because I don't know I don't want to get into his personal
stuff but he's depressed right now
Hippocrates seems pretty depressed Jesse's depressed because he's like
in heartache just everyone I know is depressed
and it sucks
because I hate when my friends are depressed because I want everyone to
be happy and I there's nothing I can do to change
that like there's nothing I can do to help them because they already know why
they're depressed and I can't make it not that way
and like you know the things that make me happy don't make everybody else happy
because for me it's all about like the feelings
of security and doing what I want to do
those are the two things that make me happy feeling secure and doing whatever I want
and both of those are facilitated by money like those are both basically
just straight up monetary things so to me making a lot of money
is happiness like they say money can't buy happiness I fully disagree
to me happiness has like a concrete dollar value
it's you know if I can make enough money by doing
what I want to do then I'm happy and enough money in
my definition is enough that I have
savings that if anything goes wrong I'll be ready you know that I have
money in savings so that if anything goes wrong
it won't bankrupt me having no debt
feeling like if I need to buy something I can just buy it
you know like I wanted a thousand dollar laptop I bought one
like because I wanted a laptop that wasn't gonna fucking fail on me like all my others
did and I bought that and it wasn't a financially
crippling thing to do so it was just something I could go do you know
that to me is like the most valuable thing
more so than the laptop itself the fact that I could buy it
is the most valuable thing to me that's the feeling of security
and if being able to do what I want and to be able to go out and eat everyday
and always eat stuff that I like you know and to be able to
you know just afford to have a decent lifestyle like that's
what happiness is for me and I feel that like you know
because all I really like to do is work and eat as I've said on this podcast before
the only thing I really want to do is to work I love making videos
I love doing shit and the only time that I feel stressed about it is when I feel like I'm not
getting out of the house enough and it's easy to go out and just
eat a few times a day and there I feel like I've gotten out of the house and let's get back to
work you know I've put out so far this month
as of this recording I have put out 20 videos that I was in
according to my playlist there's 20 videos have been released
that I was a part of that's not including at least
15 unreleased let's plays that I haven't edited yet
you know commentary I filmed with DeVue that I haven't edited yet
like a podcast
I recorded with Wave Motion Canon which may or may not be out by the time of this
recording I don't know when it actually releases
you know I've done it I do lots of work I'm always working and on top of that
I've watched a few complete shows I've played 24 hours of fucking
Pokemon Sun you know I've been
working out every couple of days with Ben
I've been going out to eat all the time I keep myself busy
and the only times I feel sad and upset with my life
is when I'm not busy when I don't have any ideas
for work or I'm not satisfied with any of my ideas that's the worst time
when it's like I don't actually want to do any of these ideas I have and there's nothing
else like right now I actually probably would be in
a little bit of a video creative rut if not for the fact that I'm playing
Pokemon you know like that's what's keeping me busy right now is that
Pokemon is clear and I love it and right before that
I was like you know watching all those Chris
videos and getting into like some of those ideas and like I'm always jumping
from inspiration to inspiration so that I never get bored because if I get bored I get sad
and I don't want to be sad so you know
yeah I guess that's where I'm at now and I hope you enjoyed this story I hope it wasn't
too depressing or that it was interesting I really don't know if it was interesting at all
like to me again this stuff is like almost about a different person
because that story you know
ended in 2010 like that's that's how
2011 I was 20 years old you know when
when I got the job at Target and finally kind of
that was in late 2012 and I kind of put a stop to it all you know like
well I mean I was depressed I was a little depressed when I worked at Target because I had to work but like
once I started the channel and everything kind of picked up from there I've never had
a huge the worst it's ever been is when I broke up with my girlfriend you know because
it was my first big breakup and we've been dating for six months and it was like a huge blow
but that's like the worst I've felt since then
so yeah hopefully that's
inspirational to some people if you're dealing with major depression to like
find some way and you know my brother Victor
who the medication didn't work for him he just kind of like accepted
the idea that he'd be depressed forever like that was how he got out
or not how he got out of it how he dealt with it was just to be like this is who I
am like just to self-identify as a depressed person and just live with it
but he's not depressed anymore because now he's in a really happy
relationship and that's like totally made him like a different guy
you know he's like happy all the time now used to be he was always angry
like every day that I talked to him he was angry for no reason
and now he's usually happy for no reason
so he's totally about faced just thanks to getting into a good
relationship so you know if you're depressed seek to change something
and if you can't change anything by yourself try to find somebody who can
and there's a lot of different ways to reach out I did it
through text usually you know writing a letter and just leaving it somewhere
because it's a lot easier than talking to someone you know if you can't
talk up to your parents and talk to them but you can at least write something
on a piece of paper and just leave it where you know they'll see it and then
like you know and then you're at school so you don't have to be there when they read it
that's another thing I was never around when they were going to read this stuff
then you know that's a great way to do it
so yeah enjoy your night or day
I'll talk to you next time
I'll see you next time
Music
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
you