Oh my god, I actually did it.
I actually finished all of the projects that I was working on in the last couple of weeks,
the last month probably.
Man, I gotta tell ya, first of all I have to apologize, cause I feel partially responsible
for the fact that there hasn't been any new PCP this week, and how they've been kind
of irregular lately, that there's been more of all the side projects than the main ones.
No fault of Nate who's been trying to organize PCPs all the time, the rest of us are always
busy, and Ben's been doing his Pokemon Sun playthrough, and he's been busy working on
his comic, so that's been keeping him occupied a lot.
Davoo has been working really hard on my videos, I gave him a lot of assignments, it took him
a straight week to finish the video on the one we just did, the subverting Shonen Trove's
video, and I don't know, Jesse's been, I guess, just moping around somewhere, I haven't
seen a lot of him in the last month and a half or so, but as for me, I usually see Nate's
calls to action, and I'm just like, I am busy working on all this other shit.
I gave myself too much work, I gave myself too many projects, too many ongoing projects,
where I keep having, like, I'll be thinking, alright, today I'm gonna edit this video,
but then I'll remember, oh yeah, today's PCP day, or today is Pub Crawl Day, or today
is Day I Get Called Into Random Other Podcast, I did a podcast with Mumki, just like over
a week ago, I did the Wave Motion Cannon Podcast that still isn't out, I think it's gonna come
out soon, I hope it comes out soon, because I'm giving it a shout out in my next video.
So yeah, there's just a lot of stuff that keeps pulling my attention aside, and then
I keep giving myself these really big projects, and then having them stacked on top of all
this other shit, and I was also saving a lot of stuff up, so like, the Let's Plays, you
know, I stocked up the entire Bomberman and the entire Wario Land 4 Let's Play, like,
I didn't release any of it until both of them were pretty much completed, so that was like
16 videos that were just sitting on my computer until I had time to edit all of them, upload
them all, you know, schedule them all, give them all the information, which is a process
in itself, I had these fucking, god, I, so the two big ones that were really holding
me, that were like weighing down on me, is the co-heating Cambria video and my audio
book of my novel that I wrote six years ago, both of these are pretty big projects that
I kinda jumped on while the inspiration was there, and then quickly realized they were
much too big.
Now, I'm gonna tell you about the best feeling in the world, and the worst feeling in the
world, the best feeling in the world is being way ahead of yourself, the best feeling in
the world is when I have six completed videos waiting to be uploaded, that feels great.
When there's six videos that are already uploaded to which, like, okay, let's say the Let's
Place, right, it feels great to know that in December, there will be a Let's Play video
every month, I already scheduled a whole month worth of Let's Plays, you know, all of December,
the exact length of December, because both Bomberman and Wario were 16 episodes apiece,
both their final episode will come out on the 31st, so every day of December has a Let's
Play coming out, all of those videos are fully uploaded, fully scheduled, they have all their
information in place and the files have been moved to my external hard drive, they're not
even on my computer anymore, those videos are fucking done, that feels great, that's
being ahead of yourself.
The worst feeling in the world is having unfinished videos sitting around on the desktop and knowing
that I haven't done them yet, and I have this, I like to have only one column of things on
my desktop, I have four folders that are below my wrist, you know, there's the computer,
the computer icon, the main user folder, the DigiBro folder, the recycling bin, and
there's four folders under that, the first one is a music folder for all the music projects
that I'm working on, the second one is just a general video, it's called NNB which stood
for Non Non Biori, because I made the folder when I started up the sitting around watching
series with Non Non Biori, so whenever I take files off of my camera, I throw them into
that folder, and then you know, the files stay in there until those videos are done
being edited, then I remove the files from the folder, then there is the podcasts folder
where I hold anything for this channel pretty much, stays in that folder, and then finally
there is the let's play folder which is new, I didn't have one in the old days, but I created
one because of the let's plays I was doing with both DeVue and Victor, these four folders,
the best state for them to be in is empty, now a couple of them have materials, like
for instance the NNB folder has all of the comments that I use for the board of second
chances videos, or the podcasts one has the thumbnail and the background photoshop documents
for the procrastinators videos, and the music one just has a shit ton of errant music files
in there because I have a bunch of outstanding music projects, which is itself a problem
but I don't pay as much attention to that as I do the other stuff, but aside from those
folders, I have had this technique that I've been using the whole time I've been making
videos, this is a very integral to my workflow, which is that because I'm so obsessed with
my desktop being clean, any video I'm currently working on that's not finished, if it doesn't
go in one of those four folders, it goes right on the desktop, all the project files
go straight on the desktop, and what that means is I can't get rid of them until I finish
the project, so the Coheed and Cambria video had an audio, all the videos of me talking
into the camera were all in the NNB folder because I just ripped stuff from the camera
straight to that folder, but all the project files for the Coheed music videos and their
songs and stuff and all that shit was sitting in a folder on the desktop called Coheed and
I couldn't get rid of it until I finished editing the video, which took weeks, because
I'll get into why in a second, then I did my audio book and that had to sit on the
desktop until I was done editing it, and this like, this worms its way into my mind, like
I need these things to be gone, and eventually if something sits on the desktop for long enough
and doesn't get finished, it will get thrown away, but I'm sure I've said this many times
before that for me, there's a very steep, harsh curve of my interest level in completing
a video, so there's the moment I get the idea for the video, which is a fairly high level
of excitement, depending on how quickly I think I'm going to do the idea, if it's something
that's like a vague idea that maybe I'm going to do in the future, but I'm not entirely
sure, it's a low level of excitement, I get a lot of those, almost every day, there's
some kind of idea that I'm like, maybe I can do a video about that, but I don't know exactly
how it would be, so we'll hold off on that for now, then there's the ones that I immediately
know what it's going to be, and I'm like, oh, I'm ready to do that, I can do that right
now, some of them are like, that would be a little bit too complicated, I'm not going
to do that today, that requires me to watch 10 shows, that one can get put off for a while,
but if there's an idea that's like, oh, I can do that right now, then it gets pretty
excited, now, whether it's a vlog and I'm getting in front of the camera, or if it's
a written post, the act of creating it is the highest level of excitement, if I'm writing
a post, I am super into it, particularly as I get close to the end, that's the highest
level of interest I have in this project getting made, is when I'm towards the back end of
finishing writing it, or when I'm recording the vlog, but after that, it goes straight
downhill, because if I have to start editing the video, I'm already past the part I was
excited about, which was getting the idea out there, manifesting this idea into writing,
making it concrete by putting it to paper, that's the exciting part, now I just have
to go through the process of making it presentable for an audience, which I'm not interested
in, and the more I listen back to this audio, the more I hear myself talking about this
thing, the less I care about the point I'm making, the stupider it sounds to me, the
more I feel like, was this even really worth it, why did I even make this, that's how
I start to feel as I edit, that's why DeVue edits my videos for me, because as that interest
curve goes down, the likelihood of it getting done, or it getting done well, also goes down,
and this is why a lot of my older videos reach that point where it might just be set to a
video game, like Sword Art Online and Analytical Diatribe, it's like I made this, it's an hour
long thing, you know, my interest curve peaked when I wrote that thing, it was starting to
go downhill after I had to record and edit the audio for that thing, you know, it was
still a pretty high level of excitement, but then the prospect of editing an hour of video
with relevant footage, and then knowing that it probably wouldn't get onto YouTube, because
at the time I didn't know how to get around YouTube systems, total decimation of interest
curve, let's set it to video game footage, you know, so I pay DeVue because when he gets
my videos, then he all at once hears the audio and immediately hits the top of that interest
curve, and then he edits it, you know, he edits it while he's in that state, and he's
like he stays there through the editing, and I do think it's, I think there's times where
even he, if he has to edit something for too long, it even for him it becomes like a, okay
I don't care anymore, you know, by the time he's finished, there's some videos I feel
like he, this shonen one, I felt like fairly early into editing because it was so complicated
because he had to gather so many fucking clips, I think he was starting to be like, I don't
know why I'm editing this fucking video other than that I'm getting money, you know, like,
he can correct me if I'm wrong about that, but like, it was an arduous edit, you know,
I could tell he was not as stoked about doing it because of how arduous the process was,
because Davoo's least favorite part of editing is having to just gather shit, like he's pretty
good at the plug and play of actually editing it, but the gathering part seems to stress
him out and he had to do a lot of it for this, so anyways, yeah, like, if I have to edit
for too long, the likelihood of it being finished goes down, and this is especially true for
anything that I don't see how this, like, what the impact of this is going to be, like
if it's something I don't really care about, then it goes down further and further, so
like, for instance, I got inspired when I was watching Shallow Rewards to make some
music content, like, to make a video explaining my history with a band, because like, a lot
of his videos will talk about a band's entire history, and I don't really have the kind
of knowledge that he does of like, what goes on in the industry or like, what was going
on in the minds of the bands and their personalities, but you know, with a band like Coheed and
Cambry, I've heard all their albums a thousand million times, I felt like I could talk with
some confidence about how I feel their music has changed, and maybe some of the reasons
that it's changed, but it's all very speculative and very gonzo, and I just kind of did it
unscripted and ranted, and I ranted for like an hour, and my idea with this video was I
was going to edit in music clips to try and help prove my point, that ended up being a
lot more effort than I thought it would be, and so this video that, as I'm listening to
it back, all I can find, like, all I hear is all the things, places where I use the
same word a thousand fucking times, I, everything is just sweeping and epic and huge, those
are the three words, and pathos, I say all those words a million times, and, and I just
hear myself getting facts kind of wrong, or just like, not really explaining something
and it does much depth, or like, certain places where I'm like, oh, why didn't I point this
out, that would have helped, or like, just all, because it's an unscripted mess, you
know, and I'm not really good at talking about music, and, and I was drunk and tired probably,
so like, this is, this is something that should not have had to be edited for the amount of
time that it did, you know, but it took a lot to edit it, and as I'm going, like, because
I don't really have that much enthusiasm for it, it makes it harder and harder to keep
working on it, so it sat on my desktop for like, two and a half, three weeks, you know,
like, I was just slowly plugging away at it with little energy, and then I keep taking
on all these other projects at the same time, so like, this one is just sitting around while
new shit keeps piling up, oh, we did another Let's Play with me and DeVue, oh, we did another
PCP, now I gotta, and make sure that gets out, and if that doesn't get out within a
couple of days, and the schedule's gonna get really fucking weird, you know, and like,
uh, it just becomes like a stack, a fuck shit stack, all on my desktop, and uh, so, god,
let me take a breath for a second, and these, the decompression chambers don't help either,
because I've been trying to keep these to a week, like a relatively weekly thing, and
I think I said on the last one that it, that it might be longer or whatever, uh, before
this one came out, but like, you know, when that week, when it starts getting towards
the end of the week, and it's like, oh, well, now I'm gonna do a decompression chamber,
well, that pushes, like, if I have to edit this, then I'm not editing the coheed video,
you know, and then I stacked on top of the coheed video, an even worse edit project,
which was the audio book, and I'm glad I did it, I'm actually very glad that I made this
audio book, I'm really happy with how it's come out, and the fact that it's out there,
by the way, um, I'm not making a video about it, but it's on my Reddit, on the our Digi
Bro subreddit, um, I might put a link to it in the description, if not, go find it, um,
it's called Tales from the End of the World Book 1, Scarlet City, it's a four hour audio
book, uh, and there's also like an hour and a half worth of podcasts I did about it, afterwards.
Check that out if you're interested, um, I don't really want it to be widely released,
but I do want to, like, sort of word of mouth spread it to make sure at least some of my
fans get to read it, uh, a few people have checked it out and their reactions were fairly
positive, so, uh, so far it seems to be a good time, and it's not that much of a time investment,
it's only four hours, even for the audio book, um, so, so yeah, I'm happy with how it came
out, but the editing process was such a fucking nightmare, because it was like, I got inspired
to do this all at once, and I just recorded, I just like sat down and in one sitting recorded
the entire thing, I just sat there for four hours and recorded an audio book, and then
I had four hours worth of audio that I now had to edit, which meant removing every stutter
and fuck up, and every, like, uh, tightening up spacing, that was the worst part, is that
like, you know, I wanted to make sure it flows well, because if it flows like garbage, then
it's just gonna be even worse of an experience, but it's not a good book, it's not work I'm
proud of, it's, I mean, I'm proud of it, but like, it's a six year old novel that, that
I never edited or revised at all, and like, it has tons and tons of glaring problems that
I'm well aware of, and so as I'm editing it, I just keep hearing lines that I'm like, oh
god, am I really editing this, am I really trying to make presentable, what is by all
accounts a not very good book that I know is not very good, uh, I just want it to exist,
and I'm not even releasing it widely, I'm just releasing it to like, an audience of
probably 15 people on Reddit, you know, like, why am I putting so much effort into this,
and because it's such a huge project, then even when I did like, pluck away at it a little
bit, you know, over the course of a couple days, it's just, it's so long that like, I'm
gonna have to put it on hold to go do the pub crawl or to go do something else, so yeah,
it was a nightmare to have this fucking four hour long burden over my head, and I finally
defeated it with the, the, the masterful technique that Dick Masterson came up with of the three
beers, I gotta tell you about the magic of the three beers, you see, I've always known
and I've, I've preached that editing is easier if you're a little drunk, like a little, at
least a little tipsy, you know, have a beer or two while you edit, because it, it helps
to numb the part of you that doesn't want to do it, like you, you still have enough
cognitive ability to do the job, because it's not hard, editing is not like, I don't think
editing takes a ton of thought, like you, you can pretty easily figure out what you want,
and it's rare that you come across something that's like, hard to do, that's like something
new that you haven't done before, usually you know what you're doing, and so it's just
a matter of plugging and playing, like hitting, you know, okay, this is the, I need to find
this clip for this line, I need to find this moment, I need to time it right, you know,
and all that can be pretty easily done without needing like a, like, you know, your full
brain, which your full brain is just desperately trying to rip itself away from this and do
anything else, it just wants something to stimulate it, and to not pay attention to
this editing, it wants to go to Twitter, it wants to go anywhere else, but when you numb
that part, when you numb your brain just a little bit, so that it can deal with doing
something boring and menial for hours on end, editing is way easier, and I've always known
this, but Dick Masterson came up with a formula for it, like a revelation, I mean, this man's
been a lifelong alcoholic, so he's in his late 30s, he truly has had time to perfect
this technique, but he said, three beers, he said, you know how I got through all my
emails finally, three beers, you know how I deal, like any situation that you need to,
you're like, I don't really want to do this, but I need it to get done, three beers, two
beers, not quite enough, you know, he said, you know, drink three beers, I think you can
drink three in the process, like for me, I usually start after like half of one beer,
that's enough to get my mind sort of in the game, to prep myself that like, all right,
just numb it a little bit and get it in there, you know, but the third, you can't go above
three, that's the important part, if you break over three, you're gonna get drunk and you're
gonna get, that's when you get dumb, that's when you get too dumb to actually do the thing
you're trying to do, but three beers, it has to be light beers or like relatively, you
know, not, you can't drink a strong ass beer and think that three is gonna keep you under,
you know, but you drink three relatively normal beers and you'll be good, and it's worked
wonders for me to the point that I'm now becoming an alcoholic, but I drank three beers and
made it through the entire rest of the editing and finally put that fucking chapter behind
me, all the let's plays are up, all that four hour fucking Q&A thing I did out of nowhere,
thank God I was able to edit that quickly, you know, like, because that's the thing,
I've got, oh, I'm working on this audiobook, maybe I'll do a 50k subspecial, oops, it's
four hours long, you know, what am I gonna do about this, you know, so yeah, I knocked
it all out, I got all of it done, and now I can start fresh, this isn't to say that
every single project that I have is, that I have open is complete, you know, and I closed
off a couple, I closed the finisher fail, not finisher fail, I closed off what's it called,
the board of second chances, and I closed off random ass recommendations, which I don't
know that anybody was like holding me to that anyways, because it had been like two months
since I did the first one, but I closed those off because they were kind of overkill, and
I can open them up later, but I was like, I need, there's certain series that I want
to start on that need to get started, and those ones are getting in the way, so what's
great about having like a clean slate of finishing all the old work is that I can like really
focus on, okay, now these projects that I want to get started, I can start on those,
you know, so there's a few, there's some, I have a few musical projects, I have a bunch
of musical projects that are unfinished, those ones though can kind of wait, I'm not in any
huge rush to finish my musical projects, because they're always kind of in a, there's kind
of a different mindset I approach those with, we're like when I make music, it's like getting
inspired specifically in the moment to work on it, it's not something I view as like a
project I'm continually working on, my music, you know, it's completely non-monetary and
has nothing to do with the rest of my career, it's really just something I do for fun when
I feel like it, so my musical project's not withstanding, there's only one, no, two videos
that I have footage for that are incomplete, one of them is the start of the new version
of Finish or Fail, and the other one is just this clip I took of a magazine thing that
I haven't quite decided what I'm gonna do with or if I'm gonna do it, I just have the
clip around, but all the podcasts are clear until now, now we've got this one, but that's
okay because, you know, there's nothing else there, keeping me from it, these are easy
to edit, they're not a big deal, and all the Let's Plays are done, so I can start up a
new Let's Play show, I've got an idea for a new show I want to do that I'm like, this
is one of those things where I got an inspiration the other night, like I had an idea for a
show that I suddenly was like, oh man, that's a really cool idea, I'm not gonna record anything
for it, because if I do it, it's just this audiobook's never gonna get done, this co-heat
video's never gonna get done, I just have to muscle through these fucking videos, these
shitty idiotic videos that I should never have taken on, I just have to muscle through
them, I want to become someone who finishes what I start, I never have been that guy,
it's always been a huge problem for me, it's always been so hard, and I really felt like
I got started on that road with the asterisk where it sucks, and it was very important
to me that most of it was written before any of it came out, like I wrote, I think there
were seven parts, no, there must have been at least four or five parts written before
I sent any to DeVoo, and I know there were eight parts written when the first part came
out, and then from there I continued writing it until the end of the year, and yeah, it
had to be so far along that there was no way I'd stop, that's the only way I could feel
comfortable letting it start to come out, because I'm always so worried that anything
I launch is not gonna finish, because that's how it's been in the past, if you were a follower
of my anime blog, which I don't know if anyone who listens to this was, I launched so many
projects, and they were always big, it would always be some huge thing, like, oh I'm gonna
review every single one of my favorite anime, I'm gonna review everything on my on hold
list, all 100 shows, I'm gonna randomize them out of a hat, though I built a randomizer
of show, there was one randomizer I had was I wrote the different years down on scraps
of paper, put them all in a hat, shuffled it, picked out a year, and then I had to watch
whatever show was on my on hold list from that year, now that I'm thinking about it,
this is actually a great idea, and I should do it again, because I only ever did one video
of it before, and it would be better than randomize recommendations, not one video, one text post
I mean, you know, I had this awards show, like, oh anime awards, I'll give an award
for each thing, the best show in that category, I think I wrote three of those and then gave
up on it, like, out of the 20 rewards I was supposed to give, it's just a, lots of episodes,
I'm gonna blog every episode of Utana, I got through three, you know, I'm gonna blog
every episode of Lane, I got through six, and you know, when I started doing anime videos,
that was one of my first goals was let's be someone who finishes projects, and that's
why I did Lane first, it was like, out of all the projects I had left unfinished on
my blog, that was the one I most wanted to finish, and so I did it, I mean, I completely
redid it from the ground up, but it was the same concept, and I fucking, and it almost
didn't happen, like, after the first four, I started doing like other videos, and like
they got slotted in, there was like these little vlogs that came out, I started concentrating
on other stuff, and I started to feel like, eh, the Lane videos aren't as, like, they're
not coming out as great as I wanted them to, but whatever, it got done, that was what
mattered, you know, and, and, you know, I've completed a bunch of projects since then,
I don't, I don't know that I've had any projects that had like a definitive amount that was
supposed to happen that have stopped, like, people keep asking me like, when are you gonna
do episode two of Interesting Anime Protagonists, and like, the thing is, I never had much
of a plan for that, like, I really had exactly two ideas, one of which I wasn't even that
excited about, I mostly just wanted to make that one video, and I thought that no one
would click on it if it was called like, you know, like, stoic anime characters or whatever,
like, or, or like, if I tried to give a name to that phenomena, then nobody would click
on it, but if it was just called Interesting Anime Protagonists, and then it was suggested
that this was just one type of Interesting Anime Protagonist, then people would click
on it, but I've never actually had a plan for how to continue that series, really, um,
and I still only have one other episode idea, but, um, but stuff like cool character designs
have kept coming out now, you know, um, there's a few that I need to do more of, but none
of them were that like, rigidly defined, whereas there's stuff like, there have been video
projects that have just died because I didn't get it edited in time, you know, where like,
I eventually lost interest in the concept or just thought, uh, this project's too big,
I can't actually finish it, you know, I want to become a guy who finishes things, and I've
got one really massive project that I'm kind of at the advent of, like, I'm a bit into,
you already know what I'm talking about, like, I guess I should also become someone who can
finish videos I've spoken about, because this has been a huge fear of mine, because it used
to be that any time I talked about a project, it wouldn't get done, um, this is especially
true in the pony days, every time I had a big video I would talk about, it would never
get made, um, and so I've been like terrified of that ever since, but like, right now, the
big project that I have is the shaft one, you know, and I wrote Akuki Shinro in the
early 2000s, which is like the lead-in to Dissecting Shaft, which is supposed to be like a 16-part
series about all the shaft shows, and you know, I'm gonna have to start on that at some
point, but like, I want to become the guy who can finish that, even though I've talked
about it, even though it's a huge daunting task, I want it to exist, and I need to do
it, I need to become the person who can do that, and um, I feel like I'm, I feel like
I'm getting there, you know, I've got another cool little idea, the one I talked about earlier,
which now I get to do it, like I had this great idea for a video, and I said I'm not
gonna do this until I edit the rest of the audio book, and until I finish the Kohiid
video, and I did, and it also was like a test of, you know, because another fear I have,
the reason I launch into projects on top of each other so quickly is because I'm always
scared that if I put it off, I'll lose interest, you know, I want to get these things out there
while they're fresh, but like, now I've had a couple days and it's like, yeah, this is
still a good idea for a video, I should still do it, you know, fuck it, let's fucking launch
this video idea, it'll be cool, we'll see what happens, we'll see where it goes, it
may or may not become a series, we'll find out, um, but yeah, so that's, that's where
I'm at today, I finally finished all my outstanding projects, uh, I could probably, by the time
this podcast comes out, because I think I've been recording for about 30 minutes, so this
will probably be a couple days late, because I'll have to have more things to talk about
before this gets published, but um, by the time this is out, maybe I'll have those last
videos I mentioned that are, that are like, you know, that I, that just kind of have the
early workings, maybe those will be out too, maybe even the cool idea I'm hinting at, maybe
you'll already know about it, um, so yeah, I'll see you then, and, and also in the next
part, I don't know, I'm very tired and kind of delirious, uh, from editing this fucking
co-heat video all night, um, so, yeah, whatever.
Uggghhh.
So here's a first for this, uh, podcast, I actually just listened back to the previous
part, before recording this part, just to make sure I wasn't gonna repeat myself too
much, or to remind myself exactly how I presented these concepts that I was talking about, not,
not usually something I do, I usually listen to these, um, after I've uploaded them, not
even really during the editing process, but, um, I wanted to expand on some of those things
I said, and, uh, readdress some of it, because now that I've, you know, now I've done more
projects, I, with that liberation I felt from having all my projects finished, I then immediately
launched into more projects, and it was interesting, I kept them, because of that pileup I just
experienced, I put a lot of, um, I really wanted these to each be done before the next
one started, like I kind of slotted them one after another, so, after the co-heat video
I did that Hamtaro one, the Handfuls of Zen, which may be a series, I don't know how long
of a series it'll be, or how frequent it'll be, but, um, I'm excited at the idea of it,
it's, basically the idea is that it's a Game Boy Advance show, and, um, because Game Boy
Advance is kind of, I see it as a console I'm the most connected to, it's, it's like
games that are, I don't want to say it's like my favorite console or anything, or even that
it has a lot of my favorite games, it's just that the games are very well suited to my
interests, in terms of I really love the graphical style, um, there tend to be simplistic and
short, which is helpful for me, and I've played a lot of them, like the era that I played
the most video games was probably the Game Boy Advance era in my childhood, so like I'm,
I'm very familiar with the console, and with like all the classics, you know, a lot of
consoles I had, but I didn't have the classics that everyone remembers, and I, I did for
the GBA, as well as some more obscure games, and I have an interest in obscure ones, so,
um, so I thought it'd be neat to do a Game Boy Advance show, but I don't want it to be like,
I just wanted it to be as not obvious, or, or something that, that I'm like beholden to as
possible, I wanted it to have a title that doesn't really say, this is about the Game Boy Advance,
you know, like, Handfuls of Zen, once you get it, you're like, oh, okay, because it's a handheld
console, um, and also the episode numbers, I didn't want there to be numbered episodes, because
there's something that holds you, when you have like episode one, and then episode two,
then you suddenly feel like this has to reach a certain number, like there has to be a certain
number of these, and they have to come out at a certain rate, like, because when you think episode,
you think weekly, you know, you think, oh, well, yeah, episode one, so episode two comes out next
week, or even monthly, um, as a lot of uploaders are, you know, more infrequent, at least this is
how I think, I don't know if anyone else thinks this way, but like, I, I go, I usually go way
out of my way to avoid episode numbers, unless it's a series that I really don't care about that
much, like most of my, uh, my finish or fail style things, the ones where it's like me just sitting
around watching something, and I'll give it like, you know, spin the crunchy roulette number five,
because why, there's nothing else to distinguish it, like, I'm not gonna list every show that we
watch in the title, so it's just a way to distinguish that it's not the same one you already watched,
sort of, um, but I don't really care about if those series, you know, reach a certain number of
episodes, because they're kind of like a, like a joke anyways, in the first place, um, or just
for fun anyways, so with, with handfuls of zen, rather than giving it an episode title, the number
is just the number of the game, because every Game Boy Advance game has a number, for some reason,
they all have a number between zero, zero, zero, one, and two, eight, one, zero, I believe, in, in
order, so yeah, they're all numbered, not sure why, but I've just posted the number as the episode
number, and I thought that was a really fun and cryptic way to do it, um, I've been pretty inspired,
there's one video by Shallow Rewards that was, that really wormed its way into my mind, and, and
really interested me on a deep level, because it's something I'd never completely thought about,
which was about people hiding their work, about deliberately making things that aren't meant
for mass consumption, that are meant for just the people who would care about it to see it,
and I feel like it's something I've always been interested in, and I've, I've made lots of like
alternate blogs and alternate sites that I don't connect to myself in the past, not so much anymore,
these days I really want my core fans to be able to find a lot of my stuff, but I don't, I don't
necessarily want all of it to be like widely distributed, you know, I really do want it to
just be those core fans, um, you know, back in the anime blogging days, I had my main blog, which,
when it was first made, was called Digital Boy's Anime Blogging, then its name got changed to euphoric
field after I watched F A Tale of Memories, then it got changed to Fuzakenna, once I bought a domain,
and then it got changed to my sword as unbelievably dull, once I got rid of the domain and went back
to just being a wordpress blogger, yeah, quite a trajectory, but in the meantime I also had side
blogs, some of which I was like posting just completely other alternative stuff that just
wasn't in the same style as the main blog, not that the main blog had a very defined style,
but for instance, at one point my blog was on hiatus and I deliberately decided to put it on a
three month hiatus, like I even said at the beginning, like this is how long I'm going on hiatus 4,
and I took a break from anime pretty much entirely, but I got really into manga, and so I just kind
of created this entire other persona who was a manga guy, and his blog was called Is That You
Motiliata, which is a line from a Mars Volta song called This Apparatus Must Be Unearthed,
and the tagline of the blog was this manga must be unearthed, you can still find the site,
isthatumotiliata.wordpress.com, good luck spelling that, unless you look up the Mars Volta lyric,
but the the the writer was named Se Di Se Bisante, which means is this a bison,
which is from, or this is a bison rather, yeah, this is a bison, not a buffalo is the name of the
album by Omar Rodriguez Lopez, who's the guitarist of the Mars Volta, so everything's kind of themed
around the Mars Volta and Omar in the in the titling of this of this character and site,
but on this website I was just writing about manga in, but in like a character that wasn't
like me, it was a much more like polite and upstanding figure, because my blog was always
extremely crass and in your face, and there was swearing constantly and perverted humor and stuff,
and like I just, I always had this very in your face personality, and I thought that if I tried
to write in another style, if I tried to like bring in a series that wasn't quite the same, then
people would just, I mean everyone knows it's me, so they wouldn't really see it as like another
person, they just see it as me doing a weird affectation that is clearly not how I normally write,
and that was what I was concerned about, so I made an entirely new site,
new blogger, you know I got it, there's this, I don't know that it had like any readers,
I had a few comments here and there, because there's this anime blog aggregator that people
used to use back in the day called Anime Nano, and you would try to get your, if you had like a
decent number of posts, you could get onto Anime Nano and it would just post your stuff up there,
and you could get some clicks that way, it was a decent way to get a little head start,
so I had gotten onto Anime Nano and I think I had a couple readers,
but I really was just doing it for myself, like I was just blogging manga in this very
in-depth and interesting way, the posts were all like medium length, it was always like
probably between 500 and a thousand words, not very long, but they would break down the artwork
in manga, and it was written in this very polite normal tone that was nothing like me at all,
and yeah it was just a matter of like I didn't want this to be the same crowd as my main blog,
I just wanted it to stand on its own, and if you know whoever took an interest in it would take
an interest in it, regardless of it being something I made, now eventually I gave up on the blog,
it only lasted probably like mostly it was only active during the time I was on hiatus on the
main blog, and then I posted like a couple more times there, and then eventually I imported all
those posts back onto the main blog, so they are still, they're all on my blog and on the original,
and I've had other times where I kind of compartmentalize things differently and
split things into different places, and I still do it obviously with DigiBro versus
DigiBro After Dark versus this channel versus my Reddit board, you know everything has its own
place, and this idea of deliberately, like I guess it never occurred to me, like with that
manga site, it wasn't like I was trying to not let it get popular, I still would have liked it to
be popular, I just didn't want it to be associated with the same writing style as my main blog,
and I'm sure eventually I would have revealed that it was the same guy or something, or if the
other blog got more popular I would have probably jumped ship and just become that guy, but
but like making something and then hiding it, like not wanting it to get popular, like
putting it somewhere where I don't want, I'm putting it somewhere that only people I want
to see it will see it, that was something I hadn't given too much thought to, but it makes perfect
sense to me, because so much, there's so much stuff that, that like, you know I don't want everyone
seeing certain things, like and this is the case for my audiobook, which you know this podcast
right here only has 5,000 listeners, which to some people would seem like a lot, and to me
seems like not very much, because it's you know, politically compared to my other channels,
but those 5,000 listeners, the kind of things they're listening to on this show,
they're the kind of people who can appreciate this book, who I'm okay with hearing it, you know,
or the people who are on my Reddit board, that's where I released it, is on Reddit, you know,
I'll probably link it to my patrons at the end of the month post I'm gonna do,
those are people I can let the story be heard by, because again, this is a very odd story that
was a portrait of who I was when I was 19, it's not me currently, you know, and yet it is, like
there's a lot of me in it, and you can still tell I wrote it, but, but you know, it's not polished,
it's not something that was made consumer-ready, I recorded the audio book just so that it would
get out there, even though the book itself was never finished, you know, it's got missing
chapters, it's got plot holes, it's got just stuff I would completely change,
as you can hear detailed in my podcasts, so yeah, I decided to hide it, I decided not to put it on
Digibro After Dark, because I don't want to read comments about what's wrong with this book,
because I know what's wrong with this book, it was written nine years ago and never edited,
I know exactly what's wrong with it, you know, I have no desire for it to get out there and try
to have a life of its own, and increasingly, I don't know how much, I want a lot of things to do
that, you know, for me like a post on Digibro is one that I'm trying to, like there's a reason
that so many of the videos that go up on Digibro are about like trying to change the public
conversation, like Digibro is almost like a like a rallying cry channel, like every video I post
is like me trying to affect the way that the masses talk about anime to some extent, you know,
it's it's maybe a little pretentious even, but like there's always that tone of hey I wish you
all would would talk about it this way, you know, hey why don't we stop talking about subversions
because it doesn't fucking mean what you think it means and it's obnoxious and it just shows that
you haven't read enough shonen manga, you know, like that's the tone of that video, so those things
should be out there, those things are meant for the masses, they're meant for me to they're me
trying to change the cultural tide, but not every not every little thought I have, not every little
like this podcast is not meant for the masses, this podcast is meant for whoever it would interest
and I've always had this mindset that you have to cast a wide net in order to catch
you know the fish you want, right, like let's say that there are 5000 people out there who would
enjoy my audiobook and if I only cast a net around 5000 people and 50% of those turn out to not be
people who would like my audiobook then you know I'm only getting half of what I could be getting,
so if I cast a net that's 10 times wider maybe I'll catch all 5000 of those people but I'm also
gonna catch a whole bunch of stuff that doesn't that doesn't care, you know a whole bunch of people
who don't care or who actively dislike it and like because I've always had that mindset of like I
want everyone who could possibly be interested in this thing to see it then I've never taken a step
back and gone like well I mean in the end people are gonna miss out on stuff they would enjoy,
that's just a fact of life there's too much shit out there that you would enjoy and for me as someone
who collects recommendation charts like as a fucking hobby I know this all too well I have like
hundreds of books and movies and video games and comics that I'm never gonna get to even though I'm
sure I'd like them but like you know unless unless the fucking singularity happens and I get my life
extended by a hundred years I'm not catching up on all this stuff and I shouldn't be necessarily
trying to catch every single person because I don't really need them like I'm I would like it if
everyone who would like my stuff would see it but I don't need everybody who does so to do so like I
can be satisfied with a couple thousand views and like a hundred comments on a video that's like a
great amount you know if I can make a video like uh like this mindless self-indulgence one I just put
out you know and it's a concept I've had for years I mean I even thought I did this whole spiel
in a in a halo let's play once but no one watches the halo let's plays you know no one watches the
the digi and friends let's plays um so like that whole spiel even though I'd done it before
a lot of people hadn't heard it and I wanted to make it its own like nice glossied up video
and I will say I'm glad I did the coheed one just for the experience of figuring out how it would
look like how a me talking about music would come out if I tried to throw in clips and stuff
because the MSI video was a breeze to edit I legit recorded it and then edited it all in one sitting
it was like maybe three hours four hours from concept to completion and uh that's rare you know
for for something that that's that's that heavy on editing for me to just like immediately grind
it all out but it was because I was excited about it because I thought I made my point well
there wasn't a whole fuckload of factual inaccuracies or weird shit it wasn't an hour and a half long
you know it was exactly what I wanted it to be concise and and well made and I did it and I was
like yeah that coheed video gave me the experience to figure out how this would work and it worked
really well um and just seeing you know a handful of comments that are like either wow I've liked
this band forever and I didn't know this stuff that's cool or man you really got me interested
in this band that I had never heard of before or like uh that's an interesting take on the
kind like just a few comments like that is enough I don't need it to be like seen by everybody I
don't need it to have a hundred thousand views that would be nice for making money but I have a
channel for making money you know the digi bro channel is for making money the patreon my you
know a lot of the people on patreon are people who watch like all my stuff and they're paying for
just me existing essentially you know I only really need the core audience the ones who are the
the patreon the patreon people are the people I really need you know I still make by far most
of my money on patreon not so much through ad revenue because I don't go out of my way to make
all my videos super monetizable and it's funny because I could do it I'm like I feel like I was
born and bred as the perfect youtuber in a way because uh there's this recent game theory video
about youtube's changes that they've been implementing that like everyone's been freaking out
because youtube's been changing their algorithms and stuff and game theory did a video that like
explained it in concrete terms and kind of put a lot of the rumors to rest well at least you know
attempts to but basically the way that youtube is working right now is that they're not only
rewarding retention time which is something we've known about for a couple years that youtube
rewards you for the length of time that people watch your videos but now they're also
rewarding you for coming back every day now I'm somebody who puts out hours of content
every single day I'm perfectly primed for this you know but the funny thing is that I almost
released them in a way I wouldn't say deliberately but the way I release videos does not optimize on
this ability if I had everything on one channel like just said fuck it to all these weird divisions
and all this like all this like concept of how I want these things to be released and I just put
it all on one channel and released it all at the rate I do I think it would actually like balloon
in success I think that like if all of this was just on digi bro everything I do is just on digi
bro I think it would actually maybe not everything you know keep out the rap videos and all that
weird shit that can stay on after dark but if a lot of these vlogs I've been doing we're up there
a lot of these podcasts I think it would become more successful and uh and make me more money
through ad revenue but there's also sacrifices in doing that because all those big youtubers who
are concerned about this they're the people who make their money mostly through ad revenue
like the only reason to be worried about youtube changing its ad revenue rules is if you make money
through it I don't really worry about ad revenue I don't even check it like I get the money in the
mail once a month and then I'm just like oh oh I guess I made money through ads this month you
know like I don't even think about it at all because I really just worry about the patreon
I really just worry about the the fan payments because that's not only is it the biggest
source of income those are the people I care about you know I care about the idea that I'm
making something people want to pay for more so than that I'm making something that will make money
and what those people lose out on all those big youtubers is their comment sections are garbage
you can't get any real feedback you know you've got way too many people vying for your attention
the whole internet becomes hard to deal with I've I've been there I've been in that position like
even though I was not as famous like when I was big in the brony clique it was really like
like I couldn't talk to any any bronies unless they were other video creators because they they
see you as like this celebrity guy it's a little bit this way in anime too like if I head out
if I were to head to some forum somewhere or like just talk to people casually on the internet they
come in with a huge amount of presupposition about me because they see the funny thing is that the
people who are really into my work I don't think see me as much of a celebrity like you guys anyone
listening to this podcast you probably see me less as a celebrity than people who barely know me
people who only know me as like a guy with 250 000 subscribers and they've seen like maybe one or
two of my videos they see me as like this whoa it's digi bro that famous anime youtuber you know
when I did the wave motion cannon podcast like the guy who was like uh josh he was like shocked
he was like wow I'm actually talking to you and I'm like uh yeah I'm a guy who reads anime blogs
I'm an anime blogger of course you're talking to me why like I read your fucking website read
everyone's website you know um that's the kind that's how I feel about it and I feel like the
people who engage with my content who know that you can find me in the comments you can find me on
my reddit you can find me on my patreon you know I don't respond to everything but you know I'm there
you know I'm not some like untouchable celebrity off somewhere who doesn't you know even like have
the time to engage with fans even though I don't read the comments on the main channel anymore
but that's exactly the issue that channel's too big I can't read the comments on it anymore
when a video gets over a hundred thousand views you can pretty much say goodbye to nuanced discussion
in the comments and don't get me wrong I still get lots of great comments on there in fact I'd say
more so than bad ones it's just that people have less context the more the more a video gets big
the more people are watching it who don't know me and the people listening to this show or listening
to the the the after dark show they know a lot about me they have a lot more context they know
kind of what I'm about what kind of comments I'll respond to you know like what kind of discussions
I want to have on the internet a lot more so than people who come in for just one video and and are
lacking in that context and um and that's something I value I like having a dialogue with my audience
I to me it's always been about the depth at which someone appreciates something not so much how
many people appreciate it you know I don't that's why I'm not a like a pop guy I'm always I'm boogie
pop I've said this a thousand times that like pop is all about appealing to a lot of people a little
bit whereas boogie pop is about appealing to a smaller number of people a lot and uh and that's
what I hope that I do and you know I know from my fans that I do in it so it's it's really great for
me that I was able to put out this novel that I wrote six years ago and um and a few people listen
to it I didn't even I didn't expect like the most I expected to listen to this is like at the absolute
most even after this podcast even after all the any time I mentioned this book because I'm going to
mention it probably a few times you know I'm going to mention it here maybe I'll mention it here or
there on after dark and I'll definitely mention on Patreon the absolute most people I expect to
ever listen to this book is like maybe 30 and that's including my offline friends you know Victor
has already listened to it um Ben and DeVu probably will at some point so so yeah like I I don't
expect a lot of people to listen to it but the second I had like two opinions about it I was
satisfied like it was all worth it as soon as like I was able to have a conversation with Victor
about my book that I wrote all these years ago that I've never stopped thinking about you know I got
to have a conversation about it I get to see I get to read people's reactions to this book I don't
care you know how many people see it I don't care how many like how deep these reactions are just
wanted there to be some reaction just wanted to know does anyone like this does anyone care about
this is this interesting at least you know and the responses have pretty much been yeah it was
pretty interesting all right yeah I kind of liked it you know like that's basically what all the
responses been there's been like five or six people who've commented on it on reddit and uh and
that's enough then that's enough to make it completely worthwhile and maybe there's going to be more
stuff that I kind of hide a little bit and handfuls of zen to bring this back because I'm sure you
forgot that this is what I brought this up for is like a pseudo hidden video because it's not
the Game Boy Advance show it's not a review of ham ham heartbreak you know it is handfuls of zen
it's on the digi brother dart channel the people who are going to watch that video
are mostly going to be my fans I don't want it to be I don't want it to escape into the hands of
video game fans and I mean if I have one let's say I cover like the most popular gba game you know
and I have nice things to say about it and and some some new people come in and most of them
will probably just react to that video but maybe a few of them will become fans of the show and
watch the other stuff and find it interesting that's great you know I love getting new people on board
but what I don't want is that I put out a video called Castlevania aria of sorrow review and I
make some negative comments about it and then I get a bunch of people showing up to complain
funnily enough the coheeding cambria video it has some of that like not so much in the comments
but I it some coheeding cambria fan twitter like it was like hashtag all things coheed I think was
the name of it something like that they posted it up and they were like uh see how far you can make
it into this video before closing and they tagged me in this post and then of course all these
responses come in I didn't even make it 30 seconds well this guy seems like a total asshole like
people who literally know nothing about me who know nothing about what the video is supposed to be
or the context surrounding it they just clicked on a coheed video they interpreted it as negative
and they freaked out that's why I have to hide some things you know and that video is not even
like made to be super public I mean I did give it a relevant thumbnail and title so but I even
called it a fans retrospective specifically so it wouldn't be taken that way like I originally
was gonna call it coheeding cambria what happened but then I was like that makes it sound too like
like like I'm trying to write an article or something like something more objective if you
will whereas if I put a fans retrospective it makes it more clear this is a personal story you
know and I and I try to like really in the early part try to be really fair about the idea that
like this maybe the band's not even gone to shit maybe it's just me you know I go I go on a lot
about that but you know on some level the video has to stay hidden because the video is not for
coheeding cambria fans that's not who the audience was intended to be it's just me telling a story
about a band that I that I like you know it's more about my narrative it's more for my fans to just
see something kind of fun and cool about some band they maybe have heard of or maybe not um
so yeah that's why like with this hand with the samples of zen thing it's it's it's really about
it I wanted it to be its own thing it's not the gameboy advanced show it's that video is not a
ham tarot video it's my video that uses those elements and I think that that that is kind of
what I get out of something like shallow rewards where that show has a title shallow rewards you
know it's it's not just the name of the guy making it like it is a show unto itself it has its own
style and none of the videos are just about the thing he's talking about it's about his presentation
of the thing he's talking about and the cult of personality that is his you know his writing
so that's kind of where I find the value in hiding things and um and it's really a privilege I have
because I have a main revenue stream and I think there's a I mean don't get me wrong I think there
is somewhat right now a fetish is a fetish is fetishization is that the word yeah okay it seems
like it needs more syllables there's currently a fetishization of working uh like making money off
of art like I think because there's more people who are able to do it online now than like everyone's
chasing that and I don't think that used to be like as common of a thing I think it used to be
that there were a lot more people who worked normal jobs and did art just because they enjoy it and
that it was never meant to get big and you still see this like there's lots and lots of let's say
like cover bands for instance if you ever go see like um a few of my god probably close to a year
ago me and a couple of friends went with my mom to some bar where some 80s hair band cover band
was playing and it was just like like a bunch of 40 year old guys who get together every probably
month or so and do a bunch of covers of hair metal songs because they want to and it's fun and they
get to hang out with a bunch of people at a bar and get drunk and it's a good time and I think that
maybe everyone is trying to be like their own celebrity and to make like a whole career out
of art now and they think that that's the only way to do art as opposed to just doing it on the side
because you want to which is a great way to get started and I mean if you think of my career in
terms in like a full scale that's what it was for the longest time you know my anime blog was never
intended to take off I wrote it for seven years before it got before it took off and um and now
I've been writing for over nine years close to 10 if you you know count my my anime blog as part
of it or my channel rather so yeah like I feel like people need that kind of build up time and
everyone's just trying to like launch a career out of art immediately out the gate and some people
are lucky some people can do it some people manage to get that either through having good
connections or just being incredibly talented right when they start but I think everyone
else is looking at those people and trying to be them and I think that because I've been lucky enough
that I had such a long time of build up and then I did launch a career through art and because it
manages to make enough money that I don't have to work at it constantly I actually have time to do
other projects that are just out of passion that have nothing to do with making money you know
nothing on digibro after dark is ever made to make money with the like one exception of the ghost in
the shell video because I thought it would be really funny to see if it can make 100,000 views
and it did so like nothing else on the channel is oriented around making money the procrastinators
channel is not making me any money you know this these videos these decompression chambers I can't
like I monetize them but they're they're not even on my channel you know it's connected to Nate's
account um Nate has said that he eventually wants to like split up all the pcp money amongst all of
us once it's like actually made some money and he's collected it but like you know I'm basically
just doing this for free I mean the most it would make us would be five dollars an episode for for
these decompression chambers but like you know I'm not making any money off of this I'm just doing
it because I feel like it I'm just doing it because it's something I want to do um and I wrote the
I did the audiobook you know for an audience of spend a week editing it for an audience of what
will probably at most be 30 you know 30 people I'm doing all these things that are just they're just
for me and uh and that really is a privilege because a lot of my friends are trying to become
successful you know they're trying to make a job out of it um even though some of them are just I
mean because it's not a job yet they're just doing it on the side for now but like it's because I make
enough off of those videos that it doesn't have to be a full-time career I don't have to be I don't
have to make it so I am getting out a 20 minute video every single day on a main channel just to
make a buck you know which is what like all those big youtubers who are complaining now that like
that youtube's algorithm is not working out for them you know they only have to complain about
that because of the fact that they have to make ad revenue dollars you know and I don't I I'm privileged
to not have to do that I get to have um you know my own system that works for me because my fans are
willing to pay for it so yeah I'm lucky enough that I get to do whatever the hell I want um which
is exactly what I always wanted my career to be so it's really beautiful for me
so the other benefit of having released that audio book is that I got to spend a lot of time
thinking about it and thinking about my writing uh my fiction writing that I used to do because for
a very long time that was my goal was to be a fiction writer and um sort of what incited me to go
and do that book and let me know if you find this an interesting concept which I know a bunch of
people are gonna say yes regardless because it's a video I suggested and I've never been like hey
does anyone find this interesting and had nobody say yes because someone's always gonna find everything
interesting but I had this idea that I would record a podcast just explaining all my old stories
like I was just gonna go through one by one and find every old story I'd written like every concept
I had uh and like half written first chapters and stuff and just uh explain all of them and I
thought this would be a fairly simple thing but then I started going through all my notebooks
and I realized I have a shitload of stories that I was coming up with back then like I mostly
remember a handful of like the most uh you know the ones I got the farthest with and because it's
been such a long time since I quit it never occurred to me like just how many fucking ones I had
I found like one page that's called like ongoing projects and there's 30 stories on that page
and then I like found all these other ones you know I'm just like going through these notebooks
that have all these fucking character bios all these little short synopses and stuff some of them
are like the title of a story on a page and like one line of description of what it would be
but other ones are like these whole fleshed out universes and shit and I was like holy
fuck I had so many fucking ideas um I spent so long trying to do this and um you know even
after my novel I wrote a few more things before I finally gave up on the whole novelist thing
but rereading the book really reminded me of like where my actually I won't even say reminded it
taught me where my strengths lie as a writer because back then I you know I wasn't a professional
I wasn't as good as I am now I wasn't as good of an analyst as I am now you know I can analyze
my own work just as well as I can analyze anybody else's uh but you know back then I was much younger
uh wasn't as critical didn't know as much about like what makes good storytelling or good writing
and now I can look back at that book and be like huh you know I I I have kind of a knack for
character writing and construction and like giving characters distinctive voices um and I have some
pretty pretty good dialogue some of it's corny as shit but there's moments where the dialogue is
really interesting and I of course could do it a lot better now because I have much better taste
um you know there's a lot of potential there like when you read through it you really feel like man
if this guy had kept writing he'd be great and that's my brother explicitly said that Victor
listened to it and he was like you know it's not really bad at all and he was like if you had been
writing fiction the way that you've been writing blog posts like if you had kept doing it all this
time you would be as good at fiction as you are now at analysis and I was like yeah that's true
like I would be I would actually be great at fiction if I kept doing it this whole time um I just
didn't and then but it's it's weird because it's not like I haven't been writing you know like even
though I'm writing in a different field I feel like a lot of the skills I have from this can easily
be reapplied to fiction and like now that I've kind of analyzed my story and thought about like
huh well if I just did this like if I cut out this element like you know uh I was never good
at constructing like um strong narratives I was always good at like character interactions and
more slice of lifey kind of stuff because that's more of what I was interested in at the time anyways
um I'm better at like constructing a scene that means something about a character like the the
development kind of aspect and not so good at creating a plot and uh for some reason I was always
stuck on the idea that I really needed a plot back then even though so much of what I liked
didn't really have a plot at all but now I know how to write like much smaller stories not everything
has to be like some big deep sci-fi concept like it was in that book and so uh I think I could do
it a lot better like I think I could take all the elements I was great at and construct something
new and so I'm just kind of looking at this book and looking at the reception it's getting which has
been all positive I mean it's only a handful of my closest fans who have read it so it's not like
I'm gonna get these huge negative comments but I was really shocked by how much like my brother Victor
liked it you know um who like there's a lot of there's a lot of stuff about this book that it
would be easy to hate and people didn't hate it as much as even I did like I was really harsh on it
when I first read it and I recorded a podcast about it and then I did a follow-up podcast where
it kind of softened up because I'd had more time to think about it and been like yeah I guess it
is kind of interesting now I think about it um and so all of that's kind of inspired me that I
might get back into fiction I'm I've been coming up with more like I was I came up with a story
concept I like I'm gonna maybe try to run with it and see where that takes me and see if I can get
back into fiction because I guess I was shocked by how not shit I was I expected to be more shit
and I wasn't that shit and I feel like I could improve improve quickly and I have plenty of time
like all it would take away from is probably time spent doing I don't know decompression chambers
or something or or all these fucking podcasts I mean I've even with the crazy amount of output
I have I still spend hours out of every day just kind of like laying around fucking staring at the
ceiling you know um so it's not like I am completely maximizing on my time although I will say I've
been working a fucking lot lately definitely a lot more than I ever have before these days I've been
much more of a workaholic but there's something I guess this is how I'll end this is by explaining
this last thing that like back in April um we had me and Davoo we had finished the asterisk
suck series in like January February that area um and the patreon got high enough that I could
start paying him full time where like it became his job he left his job and became just my editor
because I was able to pay him enough to make it worth it you know and so when he first joined me
as a full-time editor I wrote out a schedule for the month of April I believe it was April
and it was five videos I think there was one and a half I think that I'd written before the
month had started two of them are videos I'd conceptualized a long time before and then the
other ones were like new it was interesting anime protagonists uh the how hayami isaki
maps the setting the the one about stray little devil what else was there I think there were two
more um I think maybe what is the appeal of anime was that month and I think there was one more
but I had these five ideas oh cool character designs shimanetta I think that's the last one
and um I I not all of them were fully written I had a couple written I sent those to him and
then I was writing the rest over the course of the month but it felt so good to have a plan
because I'd never gone ahead with a plan like that I've never had a full month planned ahead
until that point um I usually was like you know coming up with a concept writing it immediately
making it and then having to come up with another concept I was very rarely working ahead of myself
so April was the first time ever that it was like here's a whole schedule and we'll make each video
has a deadline for when it's going to come out I have to have it written by a certain date and
then you have to have it published by a certain date you know and we did it we kept to the schedule
the whole month perfectly the next month we did something similar it was a more simplistic
schedule because there's only four videos which is one a week we got it done and um we didn't
keep doing that every month because eventually uh there was like a month where I only had one video
I just didn't want to do any of these concepts I had and then we did rad con and then divu moved in
and then it became like this frantic hectic schedule but then for the month of november
I won up to myself because I wrote all of the november videos in october all five of them
were written before the month even began and that was a whole new level this wasn't just
scheduling it was a whole new level of this I talked about this in a previous decompression chamber
and as a result the vu had his work cut out for him all the way up until just recently and like
I wrote the the like because we pushed back the shonen video that was supposed to come out in
october we pushed it back to december so that one um yeah we got all the november videos we
have the first december video done I really only need three this month I'm gonna do like a month
ending post on patreon so I already had the next one written back in october and now I just need
a third one for december basically what I'm saying is that I got so far ahead of myself in november
that I'm like that I'm so that like now I have there was no rush there was no rush to finish the
december work in in november and there's still no rush to finish the december work even halfway
through december because I was just that far ahead of myself and that's given me time to do
all these other projects all these other weird little things like this audiobook like handfuls
of zen and it's kind of like man I'm I'm fast enough and good enough at coming up with concepts
and I have such a wealth of ideas that I could do this forever like I can always be this far ahead
of myself and I can always keep coming up with new things and why that's so valuable why I'm
explaining that is that that is the environment in which I can write a book or write fiction or
write or make more music or learn to draw finally like those are all things that the
reason I haven't done them is because I'm scared of them taking away from my career I'm scared
that if I can't work on my main series videos then then you know that that will deteriorate
while I'm trying to work on this other shit but if I can have and this is what the this is what
I've been advertising on patreon from the beginning like it always said like the the highest goals
were always if I make this much I can do other things you know I can do bigger crazier things
and if I can continue to do something like you know what if I get two months ahead of myself
you know if I have two months where the video is written before any of them come out I can do
whatever the fuck I want for two months two months is enough time for me to finish literally
anything you know I wrote a novel in in a in a month before I wrote the asterisk war sucks in a
in a month and a half you know um I could do I could do a novel in one month and polish it the
next month I could design uh you know I could write something and then illustrate it the next month
you know like something like that I could do crazy bigger projects by getting so far ahead of myself
and always having that like that knowledge that I'm good enough to make that happen and I don't
think I would have been that good at any other time before like this is how I know I'm improving
because those five videos were all good like if I tried to write five videos in like six days which
is how I did if I tried to do that even at the start of this year they would have all come out
shit I mean if you look at the october thing where I did the video a month a day all month in 2014
most of the videos are not worth going back to there's like a small handful that are
but like most of them were just like little throwaway things that had nothing to do with
anything that were just me trying to rush through the month um if I did that today I could I mean
this is what I was trying to do at the time that I wrote the the five videos I was gonna write a whole
fucking uh 15 of them I think 15 or yeah it was supposed to be 15 but I ended up writing the ones
that I was the most interested in and then leaving the rest on hold but like they all came out as
fully fledged videos that I was completely proud of not one of them do I think though I have anything
negative to say about I loved all five of those videos they came out exactly how I envisioned
pretty much so um that's something I can only do now and I really feel like I'm reaching a point
where I can do all these things creatively that I've been dreaming of for years now
um and so maybe you'll see the fruits of that in the near future um
this is a very upbeat podcast probably uh compared to the last two I think the the last one was me
complaining about uh not having not getting laid not having a girlfriend um which incidentally
I just like after that podcast I just completely forgot about the online dating thing and went
back to what I was doing which is making videos and drinking constantly and the week before that
was the depression chamber so this is a pick me up this time yeah yeah back in the back in the
saddle the good old fun digibro saddle you know we're we're having a good time again I hope you
enjoyed this video I hope um I hope you are not one of my friends who is currently creatively
unfulfilled and is now stewing in bitter uh anger over my success I hope you're having a good time
thanks uh thanks for listening play us out jazz boys
um
you