So, when we left off on the last decompression chamber, I was, uh,
having this grand realization that I can get so far ahead of myself on work, that now I get to experiment and do other, other fun things, explore other avenues of art.
Um, not so much exploring other talents I might have, but trying to develop new talents that I don't have, such as being able to draw and create music.
And, um, do other stuff like that.
I had forgotten to list on the last part that learning Japanese should be something I do at some point in the near future, you know, with all this extra allotted time.
You hear that loud ass fucking car?
See, decompression chambers often record it during the day, unlike most of my stuff.
And I always forget that a part of why I don't record during the day is that, um, I live on a fucking major road, so there's constantly loud cars and shit.
So yeah, I was talking about developing all these other talents, and so that's what I've been working on mostly for the last week.
Um, it's really interesting, because it feels like I'm putting a lot more effort into other things, not related to my main content that you guys have been seeing.
And yet it seems impossible to slow down my main content.
Not that I'm trying to or anything, but it's amazing how I can do other things, and the other stuff will just naturally come, you know?
I mean, there's been a DigiBros video every day, um, there will be all month.
Um, I'll talk more about that in a little bit.
But, like, for up until the previous podcast, it was like this long period where I had at least two videos out every day, you know, like one DigiBros and one normal video.
And I thought that maybe that would slow down if I started working on these other projects. It hasn't slowed down at all.
Um, in part because there's just so much stuff that I get attached to, you know?
The WaveMotionCannon podcast finally fucking came out, the first half of it anyways.
I don't know why the second half is not coming out until next year, apparently, or why it takes them so long to edit them, considering he didn't really cut anything.
So, um, I have no idea why that is, but it's finally out in some capacity, you know?
Um, main channel video came out, a bunch of after dark stuff came out, and it's like, it just kind of happens.
Because, I mean, with the vlogs, it could just, you know, sometimes I just turn on a camera and rant for 20 minutes, and that's such a miniscule part of my day to do that.
You know, that it's like, oh, a 20 minute video came out, you know, without me even having to think about it, just because it came to mind, you know?
There's other stuff I've just been doing on the side, I can't even really remember what a lot of what I put out this past week was, because I've been so focused on this other stuff.
I've been practicing drawing, been drawing at least one picture a day for the last few days, just bought a tablet, so an expensive one with a screen on it, so hopefully that'll be cool.
And I learned how to fucking use Fruity Loops, the music production program that Shade uses to produce all his beats, and it's very common, it's used by a lot of people.
And it's funny, because it has a totally alien interface, so whenever I watched him working on it, I was like, I don't understand any of this, and maybe I never will.
But of course, once I installed it, you know, it took me like five hours, and I learned basically everything, so it wasn't that hard to use.
And it's interesting, because I feel like I have a head start in a lot of these categories, because of the fact not only that I analyze them professionally, so I kind of know what is supposed to happen for it to be good,
but I also have a lot of history in adjacent things.
You know, I may not have been using FL Studio or using any like professional materials, but I have been making beats for like five years now, you know, like mostly acapella or weird shit that I make in Audacity.
And it's kind of interesting how FL Studio, you know, just gives me the tools to do the same shit I've been doing much easier and with better sounds, you know, so it's not hard.
And I understand, you know, I may not know music theory, I don't know how to make a chord, for instance, or a chord progression, but there's a lot of stuff I can do with sampling and simple beat making that just comes totally natural to me.
I just get it, you know, it's not, it's, I keep thinking like, wow, this is easy, but then I think, well, maybe for a lot of people it wouldn't be who don't have any musical experience, it probably would be a lot more difficult to know what sounds right,
or, you know, something like that, but for me it feels very natural to make music, so that is really cool, and it's been fun, and I've made a bunch of songs.
Drawing, on the other hand, does not come naturally at all, but again, I do have some basic understanding. It helps, I took a lot of art classes, you know, I,
aside from just basic art in high school, I also took, like, design classes, both for traditional and digital media in college, so, you know, I understand the basics.
I know what I'm doing wrong is what I'm saying, like, you know, I can draw a shitty picture and be like, okay, well, you know, the proportions are off here and here, and I got the, you know, this isn't quite sized right, and I know what's wrong with it,
which is more than I think, it's true for a lot of people who are shitty artists, you know, it's not, I think the most important thing to getting better in any medium is understanding what your faults are,
like, that's the easiest way to help you improve is if you know what you've done wrong, and it's amazing how many people don't, how many people try to do something and then they completely don't realize what the problems are, you know,
and that makes it really hard, it's really hard to get better that way, you know, and it's why when people come to me for advice on things like writing, I've always had a really difficult time with it, I'm not good, I mean, I am good at giving advice,
I'm not good at wanting to give advice, because, you know, I'm sure you realize that I have fans constantly asking me like, you know, to check, like, check out their thing, tell them what's wrong with it or something like that,
and too often, the answer is like, some kind of fundamental misunderstanding, or just needing to change the way you think about your writing, like, there's a lot that you only pick up on with lots of experience and studying how other people write,
don't just like, listen to other people who write, but study how they write, study like, read your thing and then read their thing and then like, if you don't think yours is as good, figure out why it's not as good,
because so many people will send me something and like, what they're expecting to be wrong with it is something simple, but what's actually wrong with it is something fundamental, you know, and that is very difficult to break that news to someone,
that's why I don't like giving criticism, because no one realizes how harsh the criticism is going to be, no one realizes like, the depth on which I'm going to have to break down their stuff, where, I mean, for some people it's just not having good ideas,
for some people it's like, you know, just fundamentally not understanding how to be interesting, for some people it's not understanding just how to grammar or syntax well, or to sentence a structure in an interesting way, or to be thought provoking,
or to like, structural problems are everywhere, I mean, the biggest thing is just simplifying all the bullshit out, newbie writers put so much stuff that's completely unnecessary into their scripts, and I've talked about that in the Tips to Write Gooder video, that just like, the biggest things that bother me are erroneous details that are completely unnecessary,
but nonetheless, I think I am pretty good at recognizing my own problems, and I'll tell you about this incredibly sad story that me and Ben Saint encountered recently, and I don't want to like, slag on this person, but I just think it's a really fascinating example of what I'm talking about,
we were on Topastic, which is this comics uploading website, it's like a place for webcomics to find an audience essentially, and Ben has his comics on there, he doesn't take it very seriously because it really hasn't helped his like, a Patreon growth that much to have his stuff up there,
but one of his comics recently became like, on the hot page kind of thing of Topastic, his comic The Champion, and we were looking at other stuff on the website, and just kind of like, you know, trolling through and looking at what's what, and we stumble upon this webcomic called like, diaries of an Aspie girl or something like that,
and it's a fairly long running comic with just absolutely abysmal artwork, like the worst possible artwork that it could possibly have, it looked garish, and I mean the writing is not spectacular, it's just kind of a self, an autobiographical except not,
like you know, it's like a story about a character who was obviously the writer, like based around the writer and how she perceives herself, but we were looking at the forums, we came upon it, I don't remember if we came upon it from the comic itself or from the forums,
but she had a forum post that was like, why is my comic not more popular, and she writes like a few paragraphs about it, and her idea of why the comic's not popular is because she's not marketing it well, she was like, I know marketing's important, but you know, it seems to me like there's people who put a lot,
like you know, I'm putting so much effort into this, why is nobody reading it, it seems like there's people who are putting so much effort into, or so much less effort into their work, who are just getting really big, really fast, and then we looked through the responses, and it took a long time before we got to someone who had the balls to just say the artwork is not very good, no one was saying it,
all of them were hitting it with shallow platitudes about how like, oh well, you know, if you try to, you know, maybe strategize, people tend to like stuff that fits into what they already kind of like, you know, so maybe you have to chase what people are really, no, the artwork is unbelievably bad, that's the problem, you know, and it took a long time before somebody even suggested that,
and that's the most harmful thing that could happen to an artist is both not understanding what their problem is, and then also no one being willing to tell them what their problem is, you know, but it's rough, because I bet that she'd be resistant to it, you know, most of the time when people come to me looking for advice and I give them advice,
a lot of them are resistant, or a lot of them just kind of give up, you know, once they realize, like, that the issue is they haven't been writing for long enough, then it's like, oh well, I can't change that, you know, I can't just edit that in my script immediately, it's like, your problem is that you're young and you just started, and therefore everything you write is going to be terrible for the next five years, you know, like, that's the real issue here,
revisit this idea further down the road when you've matured as a writer, like, not easy advice to give anybody, but pretty much exactly the case, nobody's that great when they first start, and if they are, they can probably recognize their own problems and improve them more quickly, you know, or they just need one or two little hints, and then they'll be on their way, you know,
Now, my problem as an artist is that I've been doing it for five days, I'm, you know, only using other people's art as base for mine, like, I'm just copying, you know, poses and stuff, and it's going to take a long time before I'm good enough for my work to be presentable,
You'll notice that I haven't been posting any of these artworks anywhere, because they're not good, they're not presentable, they are at best charming, you know, like, and I'm drawing this character, who's part of a story that I'm working on, this fiction story, I kind of hinted that I was going to go down that road in the last podcast, and I've been trying to like nail down what this character looks like and feels like, so I've just been drawing,
the character over and over again, and will continue to do so, probably for months, you know, I will probably draw this character at least once a day, hopefully more than once a day, for like three or four months before, you know, the artwork will be of a quality that is even presentable, you know, and when this thing comes out,
because art will be important to it, I need to be able to draw for this piece of work, even when it comes out the artwork is not going to be great, the artwork is going to be mediocre, you know, it is going to be a project released with mediocre artwork of a newbie artist,
and if I continue drawing, then eventually I might release something with good artwork, but this will not be that, I understand all that, I'm not out to make something good here, you know, like conventionally, I'm not out to make something that's perfect, especially not in terms of the art, the art will probably be the least important aspect of it, or at least the least quality aspect of it, you know, it's going to have music that's okay, it's going to have music that uses all the experience I've built up as a musician,
but that's not a lot, you know, you're not going to hear super memorable chords and melodies that I invented by myself, that won't be a thing in it,
so yeah, it's not, it's not going to be amazing, and I understand that, and I wish more people had that level of self criticism to, you know, instead of asking me what's wrong with their work, just accept that they're not going to make anything good for a while, and they should not even, don't even bother asking me, you know, come to me when you've been working for five years,
and you feel like you're about to have a breakthrough, or you're on the cusp of a breakthrough, but there's just one or two things you think you need to tweak, you know, and maybe that's the kind of thing I could help a lot more with,
you know, fellow PCP member Tommy Oliver is writing a book right now, you know, he sent me a chapter of it, he's someone I could work with, because he's already got a basis of like he's pretty good, you know, he's a pretty good writer, fiction writer,
more so than being good at writing fiction, I'm much better at editing it, I'm much better at like helping people revise something that's already there, because, again, I analyze this stuff for a living, you know, like, I am good at that aspect, I could totally edit your novel, it just has to be on a certain level of like,
like, it has to be something that is basically good, it just needs to be fixed in some ways, you know, someone like Tom, I could tell him like, hey, maybe think about changing the word choice in this sentence, it actually is like that, you know, which is what I think people imagine it's going to be when they show me stuff, and it's usually not like that,
you know, really, you should be sending stuff that, well, I mean, don't send me anything, because I'm not going to look at it, but, so yeah, forget that whole line of thought, because like, this is stuff, when people ask me to look at stuff,
um, what they don't seem to understand is that editors, that's a job, that's a job that people get paid to do, that's a skill set, you know, being able to edit someone's work and look at it and understand what's wrong with it and help them to fix it, is something that most people would pay for, you know, if you're working professionally,
and aside from the fact that I'm not a professional editor and I don't have time, if I was, I would expect to get paid, you know, because I do think I could do that, I think I could be an editor, it's a career choice I've considered, if whatever I'm doing doesn't work out, the biggest problem with being an editor is that the writers hate you,
you know, like, unless they're someone who really prizes the idea of an editor, they're going to hate you, and also, I always want everything to be to my taste, you know, I'm not good at editing for what I think the audience will want most, I mean, I guess I could, I could probably do that, but like, I really like to push my own agenda when it comes to seeing other people's work, you know, that's why I don't do it that much, even for my friends.
But um, God, I don't know how I got into that tangent about editing.
Right, I was talking about this art and music I've been making, really surreal experience though, making things that nobody gets to see again, like, this is something I've, you know, I've experienced that in the past back when I wanted to be a fiction writer, I have all these stories that have never seen the light of day,
that you know I mean that fucking novel I wrote back in 2010 nobody had ever read
it until you know now now that people are listening to it and offering comments
on the subreddit which has been great it's been really fulfilling to finally
get people talking about that story and I might talk about a couple more
eventually though none of them are nearly as written as that one was God I've
considered even doing an audio version of Cyrano and purple Steve which is
highly incomplete but I really like what there is of it if you don't know what
that is you'll maybe learn eventually but yeah yeah what the fuck am I talking
about holy shit I've completely lost track of where I was going with that oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah making stuff that nobody gets to see I'm sure most people
experience this all the time like if you work on bigger projects or something
or if you're someone who you know gets an idea in your head and it doesn't get
fully realized until later then like I guess it's pretty common to to have these
things that they don't get to see be seen by anybody but I've gotten used to
this fast-paced I make something immediately release it to my audience
immediately get feedback and it's done and now I'm like I've made a bunch of
songs that are on the internet I've posted them on the internet they're
online they're just not under my name and there's a good reason for it because
they're all tied into this story I'm working on and I don't want to release
them publicly until there's more context for why they're there because if you were
to just go and listen to these right now you'd be like why you know why why this
song but if you understand the context of the story and how they're going to be
used in the story then it'll make a lot more sense so yeah those won't come out
to later but they're they're decent they're decent little songs I've
listened to them you know a number of times not just because I made them but
I think they're they're kind of neat very simple but um yeah like it's
interesting to have released content online that nobody's looking at and I
kind of would love for those songs and the account they're associated with to
like gain some some fandom by themselves without me even doing anything
it's impossible though but there's no way to grow a channel without any word of
mouth without showing it to anybody you know so yeah I have no idea if that'll
even be possible most likely nobody's gonna see these songs until the work is
complete along with anything else I do for it until then or these drawings or
anything else I'm doing so yeah it's a weird experience and and it doesn't
really show because again it hasn't taken away from anything like main
channel videos aside you know I used to be worried that like vlogs were gonna
take away from the main channel and that didn't I mean I guess that happened a
little bit back in like August when I barely made any videos just because I
wasn't up for it I was like way more into the idea of vlogging I was getting
ready for rad con I was excited about people moving in and then like that what
I what I was gonna do with vlogging I kind of lost interest in once everything
had kind of transpired but the the vlogs did not interrupt the main videos
once I got back to work on them you know they they've been coming out
consistently and then I was worried that the the art and the other stuff would
get in the way of the vlogs but that also hasn't happened because it turns
out that vlogging and getting out podcasts is something that I do so second
nature like it doesn't even occur to me that I'm doing it there's no like
preparation for any of the videos I do like I feel like other people have to
psych themselves up and get ready you know they have to like think about what
it's gonna be and prepare I barely do that like when it comes to a vlog I get
an idea I turn on a camera I rant there's there's very little like like
fully thinking out the point sometimes that could be to the detriment of the
video some of my vlogs are a little too rambly they kind of don't really make
the point as solidly as I would like but I've gotten better and better at it and
even stuff like the edited ones like the mindless self-indulgence one like you
know I I knew I knew all that stuff so I could go through it but I did not like
pre-plan everything I was gonna say I just kind of sat down turn the camera
and went and it came out really great and something like handfuls of Zen has
like some notes taken and I had to play through the whole game but aside from
that you know didn't take that much thought because I'm I'm already again
it's like automatic so these things just come out as they are and they have
they're not affected by this other artwork I'm doing which is really good
that's exactly what I wanted and it's been great I don't know exactly what I'm
doing for the next week DeVue just I guess I got it guess it's already been
two days DeVue went home to to see his parents for the holidays he's not gonna
be gone that long though he he like talked them out of making him stay too
long but I gotta have another video written for him probably by the time
he gets back and then start working on possibly building another backlog like I
did with November and just giving myself the agency to do all this stuff
because the the the story that I'm working on that I'm doing all these
drawings and music for is the story itself is very small but the project is
big if that makes sense like you know one of the fascinating things about art
is that the sort of sort of the quality of it or the like the amount of it is
not really proportional to how much effort it takes like you can make an
analysis video that's like the coolest video that you'll see all year and that
analysis video might only take like two days to make whereas a chapter of a
comic that's like the coolest chapter of a comic you saw all year probably took
at minimum a month you know probably more than a month but at minimum a month
to make so it's interesting that like the audience reaction to each of those
could be about the same takes about 15 minutes to watch the video takes about
15 minutes to read the comic chapter you know both of them have a certain level
of impact but one just by necessity of what it is took way more effort and
time and I think that's one of the most difficult things for a lot of artists
to reconcile with it it causes a lot of elitism because you know in the minds of
a lot of artists they're like I worked so much harder I deserve you know more
reward but really the quality of the final product is not all that affected
by how much work went into it you know I mean it can be sometimes what makes it
great is how much work went into it but it's not the only way to make something
good you can make something good in a million different ways you can make
something great that's spontaneous you know a lot of great music is all about
improvisation and just having a general understanding of how to perform and you
know spontaneity can be amazing for art but some of it has to take a long time
and it really just comes down to what you like doing do you like making short
form art or long form art if you like making long form art I'm sorry you know
I'm sorry for you you've trapped yourself in a hell but you know I mostly make
short form art but this one that I'm working on the nature of the project
will make it a much larger project than normal you know longer it'll take
longer to make than it would take me to make any analysis video because of the
nature of the project even though the story itself will be this really small
self-contained story that will probably be consumed consumable in like two to
four hours it will not be long but like just the number of skills that I have
to develop to even make it possible is a huge element of it so yeah
that's a fun fun paradigm to explore and it's not something I would have been
willing to do for any of the last three years you know or more because I would
have been scared that it would get in the way but now that it doesn't look like
it will I can just take my time with it I'm not I'm not in a huge rush to
develop these skills but I'd like this project to be done within the next like
six months so I'm gonna at least try to work fast and hard enough to get it done
within six months but besides that um yeah it can take its time and feels good
man alright I'm kind of just repeating what I said on the last podcast at this
point but we'll I'll cut the clip here and I'll only record if I find something
totally new and interesting to talk about between now and whenever this comes
out probably late I apologize if this podcast can get a bit repetitive at times
I mean when it's just me talking about my life and my life is kind of the same
weekend and week out a lot of the information is gonna be kind of
repetitive but I mean in a way what is storytelling if not just you know
constantly recontextualizing the same sort of basic human ideas in different
ways to unpack different nuances from them you know it's hardly surprising
that one storyteller will have a lot of commonality among their stories
especially if they put one out every fucking week it's funny because in some
ways this is my favorite show to do because it's the closest to just what's
on my mind at any given time this podcast is just like just raw digi bro
Ben said recently I came I don't remember if I told the story on here I
came downstairs and said like it was telling Ben something and then I was
like yeah I just explained it on the decompression chamber and he was like you
know listening to the decompression chamber and talking to you in person
it's like it's essentially the same experience you get a lot of like repeated
information between the two and I'm like yeah it's basically exactly the
stuff I talked to my friends about and the stuff I talk about in general which
in some ways is a sign that the decompression chamber is kind of waning
in its importance when I first started it it was around the time that Ben and
DeVue had been here for like a month because I think no I started this in late
October so around two months but I still wasn't quite I don't know I wasn't
completely you know comfortable talking to them about everything at that point
yet I wasn't like constantly sharing what was going on with me and stuff like
that Victor wasn't around for a while so you know he's the one I'd usually talk
to a lot of talk to about a lot of this stuff and what's great about the
decompression chamber is that as I explained in a previous episode it
really gives me the chance to be like unfiltered and talk in a way that is not
the same as how I talk to other people necessarily I mean there's a lot of
overlap like I just said Ben has you know said that talking to me is practically
the same thing but it's it's not me trying to put on a show and like be about
a topic that the other person can relate to let's put it that way like when we do
Digi Bros I usually try to involve Victor on some level but on this podcast it's
just me talking about my life so this is by far the closest you're getting to
what it's like the exact experience of talking to me in person especially the
lack of response from the other side need the one-sided nature of the
conversation is also is also true to life but nonetheless it is fun to do and
then that's kind of what what's keeping it going like I don't know that it's a
great show or that it has a lot of unique ideas it's just kind of fun to do
but I can't see it living too long I don't think this show is gonna be around
well into 2017 or anything I also think that probably Digi Bros is just gonna
get shut down I mean it's it seemed it seemed like an inevitability at one point
when we thought Victor was gonna move away and and like we were saying you
know Digi Bros is gonna end cuz he's gonna leave to go to college or to go
to grad school rather and that didn't end up happening so Digi Bros got to live
a little longer but then we ended up putting it on hold for like two months
because we were just busy and then we finally got back to it it doesn't really
seem like anybody cares anymore like this bomber man let's play we've been
doing the view counts are at like an all-time low comments are at an all-time
low we barely get any comments and I mean reading comments I'm sure I've said
this about all the work I do but like comments are really what let me know
that people are engaging with it you know if I don't get any comments I don't
feel like anybody really cares that much like people are just kind of throwing it
on and you know passively listening to it because it just means we weren't
necessarily engaging enough to like provoke a discussion I don't know maybe
that's just not the way people you know interact with Digi Bros but we used to
get more comments than we get now and you know I'm not watching them back I
don't think Victor's watching them either it used to be that we we both
watch a lot of them or our friends would watch them nobody I know is watching
them you know I think hippo might be but even he he's been saying that he has to
cut back on his Digi Bro content because they're so fucking much of it so yeah I
don't see Digi Bros surviving because there's not much incentive to do it and
most of the stuff like I don't I don't think our discussions have been that
great in the VAR man playthrough because at this point I run so many shows where
I get out like all the really salient things I want to talk about like when
when Digi Bros started I didn't have vlogs coming out all the time I didn't
have you know three fucking podcasts that I that I'm on and so it made sense
like I had all these backed up topics that I just bust out on the show and
now most of those are things I would make vlogs about because I do want those
those things to be out there and a vlog is just gonna perform way better like you
know on some level it's like I feel bad like you know Victor said the reason you
know the reason we have nothing to talk about is because you constantly make
podcasts and vlogs and I'm like yeah those podcast and vlogs get the way the
fuck more views you know so it's like the stuff was kind of just just exit
like we were doing what for my money is one of the best let's play shows on
YouTube like I really think Digi Bros was one of the strongest let's play
shows that's ever been it was basically just a podcast but a really fun podcast
with two brothers who you know had tons of running gags and fun things to talk
about and but it never got any attention it never grew it stayed at like this
really steady viewer base the whole way through never grew any bigger you know
when it goes away people people aren't that excited when it comes back you know
when it was gone people kept asking me about if it was gonna come back but then
it came back and no one was like oh Digi Bros finally you know it was just kind
of like oh yeah you guys are playing Bomberman that's cool you know and I'm
sure if we'd come back with like the Dark Souls 3 DLC people will be more
excited and I keep getting asked like why don't you guys why don't you guys do
in the Dark Souls 3 DLC we didn't want to do it like Victor thought it was too
hard and it's only one level and he was like let's just wait for all three of
them to come out and then we could do all three because they're gonna make three
DLCs for the game but it's like if you guys are if people only care about the
game and not actually about the show because the game is fucking completely
inconsequential on Digi Bros it's just a podcast show you know and it used to
have all these really interesting topics that to me were like these should be on
a bigger stage like this is such a good podcast show and that's why we did like
the Digi Bros Discuss Berserk video which got huge the video really took off
and that was a discussion that would have happened on Digi Bros like we were
going to talk about that and then I said why don't we just make this its own
video and people probably love it and they did you know we did the same thing
with the Ghostbusters podcast which you know was somewhat successful it was not
that great because I was a total asshole and played devil's advocate the whole
time but you know those are shows that I knew had potential to to be to to gain
some kind of you know attraction where Digi Bros was not gaining any and at
this point it's like now that I'm taking all the best stuff that like the
stuff that made Digi Bro great now that I'm taking those discussions out of
Digi Bros and putting them in other places you know Digi Bros itself is not
only worse but even less popular so there's doesn't seem like there's much
reason to keep it going I mean me and Victor the story is always the same when
it comes to just our personal lives you know I'm always making videos and he's
always struggling to find work it's always what it's going to be so at this
point it seems like there's no real reason to keep it running and there is
the Digi Bro and others show with DeVoo which DeVoo is way into the idea of
doing more Let's Plays and I think we might continue doing it if he's willing
to like edit them and stuff because for me it's just a matter of like you know
we're gonna sit down and play a game and talk for three hours and that's already
in itself like a huge time investment of time that I could be spending working
on other videos that will be relevant that will get attention that will explore
the ideas I want to explore you know and then after those three hours I have to
edit all that and break it up into chunks and post it online you know and
part of the appeal of Digi Bros was just that it was a way for me and Victor to
hang out me and DeVoo can hang out anytime we can have these discussions
anytime we want you know with him it's just a show we're doing so there's
there's even less incentive for me to keep it going but if DeVoo wants to
keep doing it I mean I can show up and play a game and talk you know that's a
huge part of why I still do the pub crawl is because I don't have to do
anything all I have to do is show up and drink and talk to my friend you know
and it's the way I keep up with Cider I don't really talk to him outside the
pub crawl except for like a few lines here and there you know each week because
I know that we'll catch up on the pub crawl and we'll have all the stuff to say
there so so like with DeVoo it's like I hang out with them every day there's not
a huge incentive for us to do a show together so yeah that's why those shows
may or may not continue and this one like a lot of what I expressed on this
show is is gonna get repetitive it's gonna end up being a lot of the same
stories it's gonna be the same thoughts about life and I could I'm not
dissatisfied with this shows view count at all I like both the nature of the
show and the the view count on it but I would you know if if if I get into other
stuff and this podcast is in the way or if this podcast waned a little bit and
viewer retention I'd just cancel it you know there's not a huge need for this
show to run forever because it will eventually wear out its welcome but
we'll see how long that takes I'm thinking maybe it'll just be a one
season thing like a 12 episode like a you know like a proper show maybe a
season that could be renewed in the future if I feel the need for it again
I mean when I started this thing it was because I really felt I needed to relax
and decompress and the best way I could think to do that with the was with the
podcast now I don't really feel I need it anymore now I'm just kind of doing it
for kicks you know and occasionally when I have a thought that I go oh that
thought would make a decent podcast let's talk about that so I had a thought
in the car on the way home from getting some pizza just now about happiness and
the nature of it and and and how it's perceived because I really think that
from an outside perspective my life must either look idyllic or crazy it's
gotta be like one of those right either you're thinking well he's living his
dreams he's making you know a good income he's doing exactly what he wants to do
what more could you want or you think that's no way to live you know being in
your room all day not talking to anyone a slave to your work you know it can look
one way or the other and it's funny because I think that for every
individual I think there's two different ways that we kind of interpret how
happy are we there's there's comparing to your own life and then comparing to the
social construct or like what you're what you think happiness is supposed to
look like so for a lot of people they have a time in their life when they were
more happy than they currently are and that kind of becomes their their
benchmark that becomes their baseline Ben Saint was just talking about this on
the latest procrastinators podcast when he the graduation one where he was
saying that his senior year of college was kind of the good old days because
that was when he was the most socially active you know was getting late all the
time was having a good time and he was like you know when I compare current
like my current self to then like there's clearly something missing in
comparison so I must not be as happy as I was then for me I've never had a time
in my life where I was happier than I am now there's nothing I there I have no
grounds for comparison that's why I always tell people that I'm happy you
know and when people ask I'm like yeah things are going great because I can't
even remember things being better than this but on the social construct level
on the what my vision is of what like my life is supposed to be I'm not there yet
because in my vision of what my life is supposed to be you know I I have I have
a girlfriend or a wife or maybe even kids you know I want to have those things
in the future I want to have a family and my own place you know a self-sustained
living which I could afford right now but to me it's like that comes later you
know like I don't think it's important for me to be self-sustained right now
but it is an eventuality I want I want to be living in a house with my wife and
kid not with a bunch of roommates you know who I work with I want them to be
able to afford their own places I want all of us to be able to afford our own
place and be stable living you know in it in a neighborhood together kind of
thing that's my vision of what it would mean to really be happy not to say that
I'm not happy now but just that like that's the thing I'm that I feel like
I'm working towards and that until I have it I will never be convinced that this
is the right way to live you know even though for all intents and purposes like
I'm doing what I want to do you know there's there's nothing there's something
bad happening to me right now there's nothing I'm like struggling with but
there's there's something I want you know and I can't feel satisfied not
having it and the the the weirdest thing about it is that the thing I don't
have is something I have no idea how to get like I think when it came to this
whole creative career for a long time I didn't know how to get it for a long time
I was just sitting around on my ass like trying to figure something out for all
those years I spent as a neat you know or in high school or college wishing I
could be the whole time I was in high school I wanted to drop out the whole
time I was in college I wanted to drop out eventually I did the whole time for a
whole year and a half after that I spent going well you dropped out you're free
you've got all the time in the world what are you doing you know where are you
where is this going man where you going with this is this gonna happen are you
gonna do whatever the thing is and then eventually I figured it out I found the
solution and then I just worked at it constantly until it until I was there and
now I'm there and I'm going okay well I see the next peak you know I see the
next thing I want and I do it's not that I don't want more success I do and I
especially want it for my friends like for DeVu DeVu needs more money if you
want to donate to my patreon and DeVu's pointed this out in the comments on these
before he said don't let Digi's complacency over money stop you from
donating because I still need money you know like DeVu makes 40% of whatever I
make on patreon so you know if you give me more money you're also paying him and
because I a you know make a little bit more and b I spend less than he does on
food oddly enough well okay not overall I spend way more on like groceries and
shit I mean on going out he spends more on groceries okay never mind I spend way
more money than he does but I make a little bit more than him on patreon and
I make ad revenue and I you know make crunchy roll stuff and I also like just
have a big savings because I I save up lots of money DeVu needs money so you
know by all means continue contributing for his sake and I can also pay more
people if I have more money but for me personally in like terms of what I want
out of my life I'm not like hugely trying to get to the next money peak if I
was you'd know because my main channel would be bursting at the seams with
content about current anime the way that it was early this year you know early
this year when I was making videos about erased and cabineri and all that shit
like and in myriad colors phantom world that was all to grow the channel you know
that was all I need more money than I have right now and then I made that much
money and I went all right let's do whatever the fuck we want now shinbo in
the 90s no one watches it don't care it's happening you know let's make it
16 videos that no one's gonna watch I don't fucking care you know it's for me
but if I wanted if I if I did want my channel to grow I know how to do that
it's easy you just talk about relevant shit you know you just make videos at a
quick rate about relevant subject matter you're done that's it you know had I
covered re-zero properly instead of as a plebe and weeb video would probably have
five times the views it has you know but I didn't want to do that I wanted to
plebe and weeb I like I wanted that show to exist it does it's funded for a
second season rad cons coming in January huge deal you know so that's not
what I'm looking for out of life right now what I want is the other things the
relationship the the the the feeling of of being on my own to some extent of
like being my own man kind of thing which I mean I basically am but I don't
want to get out there you know a little bit more and that's the that's the only
part that that like when if you ask me are you happy I'm gonna go yeah I'm
happy but I'm not satisfied you know and I don't think I ever will be I don't
think anyone ever is you get to that next peak and you're just gonna find
something else you know there's got to be something else you want but um so so
maybe I'm as happy as I ever will be and that's really the debate that I
constantly have with myself it's like I tell myself I want these other things
but I'm so convinced that once I get them it's just gonna be about chasing the
next high you know it's never going to be oh I did it I got it all now it's all
cool you know that day is never coming it's never coming for anybody so it's
just a fantasy but I have to you know clinging to that's what keeps you what
keeps you going because if I just decided well this is as happy as I'll ever be
then it's like what new things can I ever expect to be on the horizon you know
and I realize these are all kind of cliched sentiments that you've probably
heard before but but it's it's true you know and like I said a story is nothing
but sort of a re-encapsulation of the same ideas and a lot of this is what
that story that I'm working on that I talked about in the earlier part of
this podcast is dedicated to exploring not in as direct terms as I've painted it
but this I honestly think that this story I'm working on is kind of a
fictionalization of the decompression chamber it's it's it's a similar style
of presentation well not of presentation but of ideas like the
kinds of things that the story will be exploring are the same kinds of things
that I talk about on this podcast it's really going to be dedicated to how this
character the main character of the story like thinks about their life and how
exploring what is going on in their life and what that ultimately means to them
emotionally and so not like most of what happens in this story is not
particularly noteworthy it's not so much about what happens as what of what
that thing happening signifies about this person's personality you know it's
not necessarily exciting for me to say like I did this thing but when you think
of it in the greater context of like how I think about that thing I did that's
where it becomes interesting if you catch my drift how about I put it this way
if I say I watched Kill La Kill and I liked it not a very interesting sentiment
but if I say I watched Kill La Kill and I liked it because of you know how it made
me think about something else then that can be interesting that's sort of vague
but that's what the story is kind of like I don't want to give too much away
about it but I think that the audience who will be most primed to understand
this game and where it's coming from did I say game this thing and where it's
coming from they will be the people who listen to this show the people who
listen to decompression chamber will probably most readily get exactly what
this game yeah why do I keep saying game they will get exactly what this thing
is ignore the fact that I said game because that maybe a mischaracterization
um nonetheless you guys will get it I'm repeating myself I should be probably
doing something right now it's very humid in my room I feel like shit physically
by the way I'm just gonna talk about that a little bit that for the past week I
felt like garbage I've been smoking too much I need to stop again because when
when that whole thing happened with the vape where I broke the vape and then I
immediately like something clicked in my brain when I broke that vape which it's
been fixed now for a while but when I broke it something snapped and the part
of me that was like I'm vaping to quit smoking just stopped caring like that
that the whole all these years like five years of resistance to smoking full
time five years of smoking like once a day maybe twice and then quitting if I
even get close to three times that part of my brain just died when that vape
broke and I started smoking way more and even after the vape was fixed I have
continued smoking and now I like I'm smoking more than I'm vaping and it's
like it's kind of the point where now it's starting to affect the way my
brain feels and I'm like okay hold on that's that that little that little
worry guy is reforming the guy who I killed when the break the vape broke he
starting to come back to life and realize that this is a problem I should
not be smoking this much so I'm gonna quit that again that's gonna be rough
but you know especially cuz it's gonna be rougher than ever before because if
it's smoking more than ever before but it needs to stop after I finish this pack
I'm gonna go to just straight vaping and and just yeah quit smoking again
cuz it's starting to affect the way my brain feels I've also just not been
eating well me and Ben haven't worked out in like two weeks we just completely
dropped the ball on that it's been raining a lot and I get headaches when
it rains that's a fucking obnoxious thing and also the weather is all the fuck
over the place it got really cold it had got it had finally gotten like winter
cold and I was like I had considered stopping smoking then because it got so
cold the standing outside sucked so I was like well this is not fun anymore you
know I'm gonna stop doing this but then it suddenly got fucking way warm today
it's like 70 or something it's not even chilly outside and it's December so the
weather is all over the fucking place it won't stop raining it's always wet I've
always got a fucking headache yeah so I felt I have felt physically completely
off for like probably five or six days now and that fucking sucks that makes
everything else difficult I mean thankfully as I said in the first part
of this I work on such autopilot at this point that I can I can still get
things done it used to be there was a time even in my video making career where
if I felt off I could not work and that was kind of often you know like
probably at least a day out of every week I just felt not up to life I just
felt like either my stomach hurt or I had a headache or I just felt this sort of
dysphoria with my own life like not understanding who I am or why I'm here
and in that mood I'm not good at creating things but these days I'm just so
used to it that nothing can stop me I mean the last like three days all three
of those days individually I thought I'm not getting anything done today I feel
sick and I slept for most of the day and I still managed to make something
because I can't help myself like yesterday I'm like I feel like shit I
don't want to do anything I guess I'll just play sort of mana I guess I'll edit
this entire handfuls of Zen video I guess that's out and then I went and
passed out like immediately afterwards I think I passed out listening to it I
think I put it on and did not survive the whole video it was either that or
something else that I listened to in the same way I think it was that I think I
passed out listening to handfuls of Zen gross I feel terrible but you know
doesn't affect you guys you still get content and and here's another thing
please guys don't do this thing where you try to extrapolate more psycho
analysis out of the things I've said than what I've already presented because
this these shows I do this is already a psychoanalysis of myself and I've
already come to conclusions about myself and I'm presenting them here and then
I'll get people who comment things that kind of like take it a step further but
that's not how I feel like I've already taken it as far as it can go you know
this is already a full-blown examination of how I feel so extrapolating more out
of it can be bothersome and here's an example of what I mean like and I get
this in response to a lot of the issues I bring up in my life where people will
say it sounds like you're burned out it sounds like you burned yourself out like
you've been doing too many of whatever it is if I say I can't find any anime I
really love people say well it sounds like you burned out from watching too much
anime or if I say I can't find any uh like you know I'm getting stressed out
from working so much you burned you burned out if I was burned out I'd say
so I know that feeling I know what burning out feels like I know what it's
like to be sick of anime you know when I was reading all those comics I was a
little burned out on anime like that was and I said so I was like I'm kind of
burned out on watching seven out of tens I'm gonna watch or go read comics
right now I'm not burned out on anime I haven't been fucking watching any for a
little while I just want to see a new favorite you know that's just something
I want to experience that's why I said so I didn't say I'm burned out on anime
and when I talk about anytime I talk about how many projects I'm doing and
like if I say something like I feel physically sick people will say maybe
it's because of all the projects you're working on but the thing is that that's
a constant in my life at times when I feel amazing it's often attributable to
the fact that I'm working on so many things at once you know the beginning of
the decompression chamber I was talking about how like yeah man I've been
I've been making a thousand videos and working out and all this other stuff
I mean this is something this is just my lifestyle I'm just super productive
and I feel way worse when I'm not making things like in a lot of ways my happiness
and self-worth are tied to how many fucking things I can get done so the
physical illness is definitely not a result
of the working of the overworking it's a result of everything surrounding it
it's a result of a bad diet not working out anymore
uh you know frustrating climate it never is the right temperature in my room
um because when it gets cold I put on the heat
but then the heat goes stronger to my room than it does to the rest of the
house so then it just gets really hot then I
turn it off and it gets really fucking cold there's no winning with the the
heat in my house and then today because of a situation I won't even get into
where I was on hold for an hour and a half trying to call into the dick show
I uh I fucking had my window open and I because I I was stressed out because
I've been vaping for half an hour like non-stop and then I my fucking vapes
battery died so I smoked a cigarette in my room
and I had the windows open to let the smoke out which did not work
I left them open for like an hour smoke room still full of smoke
and it's humid as shit because I had the window open and it's been raining
so now I've got like maximum humidity in here so I just
that's why I feel physically wrong you know it has nothing to do with the work
it's the work environment it's how I treat myself and my body
and how the weather treats me you know those are the reasons I feel sick
so just I just don't I just I I know that people
worry about me sometimes and sometimes that's okay
worry about me for the reasons stated not for the other reasons that you've
read into it because believe me I know how to psychoanalyze
myself you know it's something I've been doing my whole
life and I've had I've been to psychologists I've
been through all the ring moral I I've studied psychology
I I think I know what's wrong with me better than anyone
you know and when I feel something's wrong I state it
I state what I think is wrong that's not to say I share absolutely everything
but you know you're not if it's something I'm not sharing you're not
going to extrapolate it from the things I've said you know
so yeah that's just something I find a little bit annoying it's not that big
a deal because I know it's well-meaning I know people just
want to help but I I do feel like when someone says
oh it sounds like you're doing this I'm like no I'm doing what I said I was
doing you know the problem is exactly as stated
and and so much of it is because people are reading in
what would be the problem for them you know it's always someone saying like
I especially get this when people like have the really far-reaching ones where
it's like a like a some kind of mental issue they think I might have where it's
always exactly the one they have you know or
like did you I know you're probably burning out because I burn out all the
time and this happened like yeah that's you
I you know I get it but it's it's it's a little annoying
anyway that's enough for that point I'll probably record one more section of
this at some point and release it later because PCP came out today I don't want
to sandwich the releases together even though this is an hour
already but you know maybe I'll have something else to talk about tomorrow
who knows
oh baby I sure am glad that I decided to hold off
on releasing this podcast because if I got a story for you guys
a fun little piece of shat and Freud for all you
fucking tech geeks out there who are going to lose
your shit hearing this little this little what I spent six hours on today
oh god so um you know in light of me trying to become
a draw boy I decided to buy a tablet and not just any tablet but a one with a
screen the the big the big boy expensive
tablets um you know I had I had a Wacom bamboo
that I bought way back in like when I back when I worked at Target it was one
of the first things I bought because when I first started making videos for
YouTube I thought I was going to teach myself to do
animations because I wanted to be ego raptor
and do sequelitis didn't really work out I didn't end up using the tablet much
and eventually it stopped working after sitting in shades room for a couple of
years and getting abused um it doesn't work anymore
so I decided I want to buy one of these ones at the screen partly because
uh fellow pcp member Tom who runs the rebel pixels channel has been doing
all these videos on Cintiq alternatives all these you know tablets with
screens that are uh that don't cost as much
so he just put out a holiday buyer's guide his mid-range one was the d13
the artisal and so I bought one uh for 500 bucks
and it showed up it's fucking massive it's way bigger than I thought it was
going to be it's beautiful uh so I decided to try and
hook it up now the artisal it has this driver you
know you have to you have to install a driver to make it work
but the driver will not install unless you don't have any other tablet drivers
on your computer so I'm trying to install this driver
and it's not working it keeps telling me that it's detecting another tablet
driver so I start going this took hours hours of
going a shit through my computer trying to find these
fucking tablet drivers because they're not in the uninstall list
they're not in my programs list I I fucking I
uninstalled drivers for like every device that had ever been plugged into my
computer that wasn't currently plugged into it you know I went found all the
hidden drivers I'm saying all this because I know
that someone someone listening who's a tech expert
is going to say well did you try this did you try that
yes I spent hours googling everything you can possibly do
and trying everything now the only thing that's anywhere in my computer that I
could find that even resembles a tablet driver is this
windows driver it's like part of a windows driver pack
and it says graphics tablet on it so I was like okay
this seems to be it but if you try to uninstall that
it's in the uninstall list but when you try to uninstall it it says that it
doesn't exist it says you don't even have this thing on your
computer I don't know why it's listed in the uninstall
list but it claims I don't even have it
and it would give me this error message you know I'm searching around I find
other people who've had the same issue but no one's really resolved it
and I'm looking at all this information about how to uninstall drivers
so what I end up doing is going into the command prompt
getting a driver's list as a text file
fucking you know control effing my way through there and finding anything that
says tablet on it and there are two different things but they're both system
32 drivers right so I go into system 32 I learn how to
change permissions on files and I go into the drivers
and I delete two of them first one nothing changed
second one nothing changes in regards to the tablet
but I now can't connect to the internet so
what I believe I did was I misread the drivers list
and uninstalled or deleted some other driver
and of course I didn't know about system restore before doing any of this
so I didn't set a restore point for my computer which would have solved this
whole problem um well this it wouldn't have solved
the the weird tablet driver problem but it wouldn't have
it would have not made it so I just uninstalled or deleted a system 32 file
that makes it so I can't connect to the internet and no one's sure why
and there's no way to replace it or anything turns out
uh manipulating system 32 files such an uncommon occurrence
that no one on the internet has helped for it uh you can't just download system
32 drivers and put them on your computer that that's
not a thing apparently I go what I start doing is
taking all the drivers from my laptop system 32 put those on a flash drive
put them all in my computer didn't help um
this is the over the course of hours by the way at this point I've got shade
helping me shades got windows 7 but even after changing permissions I can't
write any of his system files onto a flash drive for some reason it won't
give me permission eventually I remember hey wait a minute
my computer is partitioned between two different
solid state drives at the time I'd forgotten the other one the solid
state but because when my computer was built it
had a 250 gigabyte solid state drive and I later wanted to upgrade to a
terabyte one so I've been using the terabyte
there's a 250 gig one that's still in there and it still has all the
it's exactly as it was before I bought the new one you know we
didn't delete anything off of it or anything thank god because
originally I bit I was going to format it um and my tech friend was just like
let's not and you know just in case something goes wrong um
we'll wait a few weeks and then we'll we'll do it and I never did
so thank fuck I never formatted the other uh hard drive
because we also we couldn't we couldn't just boot for something like for
whatever reason my my fucking DOS has a password
and I don't know what it is and it's not the password of anything else on my
computer so couldn't get into DOS so we had to
open up the computer and fucking change the damn cords
around also that I could boot off of my old solid state drive
and I tried copying the system 32 files from the from the old solid state to
the new one that didn't work either nothing worked
so now my main my main SSD just can't connect to the internet and no one
knows why so I'm probably gonna have to reinstall
windows on that one which you know I don't want to fucking
go to the process of backing up everything and reinstalling windows
now especially if that doesn't even help the problem
because even after all of this I never solved
the tablet problem I never solved the issue
of it still thinking it has tablet drivers so finally and in the meantime a
mid-stall this happening I plugged the fucking new the tablet into my laptop
and it worked instantly you know like I got the drivers on there it's perfect
and I so I already know the thing works it works just fine
it's just something whatever reason my main SSD
has this problem so we routed to the other SSD
it works on that one um it's I fucking had to deal with
still even though the drivers installed it still took me half an hour to get the
fucking thing to detect the pen for some reason
eventually it was just like a matter of switching which usb port it was plugged
into god it was a waking
nightmare six hours it took before I got this thing working
on my computer and even still it's at the caveat of
I now am just using my old solid state drive I now just have now the one
terabyte is the partitioned one you know just I mean thank god nothing
worse happened with me fucking with system 32 files it
could have been much worse um and you know and and thankfully the
partition is is easily enough that I can just copy like you know I just had to
copy the decompression chamber from the other SSD to this one
and of course this SSD is from like you know I changed I'm like
early in the year so it's got all these like like it's missing a bunch of
programs that I now use and has all this stuff that has to be changed it
remembers all my old passwords and stuff so I have to fucking update
everything now huge fucking pain in the ass but at
least I got the damn thing working Christ
oh god I am the I am the biggest idiot in the world
I fucking immediately after I finally got it to work
I rushed out because I was just like fuming I could not contain
my rage at this point I was like I need to eat I was hungry
had you know been sitting there for six hours working on this thing
so I immediately went out to Arby's bought some big ass
shit which was disgusting I don't know why I did that then I had a cigarette
now I'm having a beer it's like somehow the fact that I had failed so badly
meant I had to continue the failure and just like make it like
if I'm if I'm this retarded I might as well go full in and just eat fast food
and smoke a cigarette and have a beer and just destroy myself I need to die now
oh god
I guess I've had worse tech problems in the past
this is the worst one in a while though anyway I hope you enjoyed that little
story I needed that I needed the decompression this was a real
this became a real decompression chamber at the very end here where I actually
needed to decompress not that that not the telling
that story like I mean it's just there for you to
laugh at me and there's no silver lining to it
but I guess I just needed to vent and now I'm remembering I can't get drunk
yet because I got to go pick up the view at the airport in like four hours so
yes I'll just drink half of this beer and then leave it around
oh see you in the next one
you