What's up motherfuckers?
Welcome to the first inaugural episode of Digibro's Compression Chamber, a podcast
about nothing in which I attempt to relax as relaxing is against my nature.
You know, I'm one of those guys, you probably hear us talk about our plight all the time,
I know I hear Jesse talk about it all the time.
I'm one of those guys who tends to make everything into a project.
Every time I get an idea in my head, it spirals out of control and becomes a thing.
And thankfully, unlike Jesse, my projects are never, they're never something that's
gonna take me a whole month to do.
It's more like I get constant ideas for little projects and I just burn through them as fast
as I possibly can.
And if I don't burn through them fast enough, they just get left by the wayside.
If a project's too big for those couple of days when I'm excited about it or if it just
takes a little bit too much mental energy, it's gonna fall by the wayside, you know.
It's so hard for me to have, to just like, to try to just do things at a normal rate
to just, you know, take a few days to get something done if it needs it or hold off
on the next idea until, until the time comes, you know, just, instead it's like this constant
like the second I come up with the next thing, the last thing has to be over so I can work
on the next thing and then I don't know where I am anymore after a little while, I'll guide
you through what this is like in a moment.
But just to explain the nature of this podcast, you know, I'm laying on the couch with a beer,
I encourage you to do the same to, to imitate me in this podcast.
And I'm just trying to decompress.
You know, I used to, I used to sort of do this on Digi Bros, which is a show, my Let's
Play show, my Let's Play channel that hasn't been very active lately because it used to
be that me and my brother Victor would get together every week or two and we'd talk about
all the stuff that was going in our lives over the course of the, you know, the time
we'd been apart.
But Victor is almost never around anymore.
Since our parents moved out at the start of September, Victor has mostly been at his girlfriend
Hope's house.
He's probably going to be moving in with their, like, you know, next year at some point.
He mostly uses our house as like a studio space.
He comes here to work on editing and stuff.
Anytime he has like a, you know, he needs to get work done or something, but he barely
ever is just hanging out here.
So I don't see him a whole lot.
And you know, we keep saying we're going to do another Digi Bros because we've had like
a month of nonstop things happening that we could talk about, but it hasn't been happening.
But you know, even then with that show, it's like there's a difference between the way
you talk about something to get it off your chest and the way you talk about something
to another person, you know, and with Victor, there's a certain security in that I've known
him my whole life and nothing I could possibly say would surprise him or would make him want
to comment on it, you know.
Victor has a very like standoffish approach to my life.
If I tell him something that's going on with me, he doesn't try to give me any advice.
He doesn't try to like analyze it in any way.
He's just like, yeah, that sure is a thing that happened, you know, and that makes him
easier to talk to in that way.
But even then, you know, it's still a person who I'm trying to present things to in like
the story like way, you know, the way I talk on DigiBros is very heightened, like I'm
trying to be entertaining or to put a spin on the story.
That's not what this podcast is about.
This podcast is being recorded in such a way that it's as though there is no audience.
I've even played with the idea of turning off comments for these videos, but I do actually
want to know how people think of the show itself, you know, if not particularly the topics
at hand.
But you know, I think that when I do a podcast with another person or even when I do a vlog,
there's a certain like level of putting on airs, there's a certain level of trying to
find the perfect words and describe everything in a way that's going to, you know, make the
most sense to the other person as opposed to just like decompressing.
I don't want to use the word venting because this isn't about being angry or like stressed
out.
I actually feel really good right now.
The reason I need to decompress is that there's just so much I'm doing and so much going on
that like I need a moment, you know, and for me, taking a moment is near impossible.
Like how can I possibly take a moment that I'm not like working on anything?
It's hard to justify to myself.
It's like when I, you know, usually I'll go for a walk or something, but those aren't
really to decompress so much as usually it's because I'm trying to think of more things
to do.
Like I'll go for a walk because I need the next video to write and I'm trying to come
up with an idea and then like while I'm out on that walk, then, you know, if at some point
I finally come up with an idea, then I'll like rush home to get it done, you know, like
I won't walk as long if I come up with something I really want to do before the walk is over.
But like I'm constantly searching for the next idea.
I'm constantly like beating over my, beating myself over the head to come up with something
as opposed to just like chilling out for a second and like, you know, maybe reveling
in what I have done, you know, I have a tendency I will do things like, you know, a video comes
out, I feel accomplished, I go out and buy something to eat to celebrate, you know, and
I do have moments like when a big thing happens that I cool off, but I think that there's
possibly some bad behavior being instigated by that and I'm going to get into why when
I describe my past week because I've all, I've kind of been building up to like why
I need to decompress.
So this past, oh my God, it's almost two weeks actually now that I'm realizing it.
The past week and a half to two weeks has been one of the most productive periods of
my entire life.
Now I'm someone who generally bounces between periods of insane productivity and periods
of eh productivity and usually those periods of eh productivity involves a lot of socializing.
Usually if I'm not getting a lot of stuff done, it's because I'm spending a lot of time
with other people or I'm trying to set up something, you know, something complicated.
Usually it's, it's because I'm doing something else other than work and I don't have enough
good ideas to drag me back to work, but as soon as those good ideas come, as soon as
I get inspired again, I come rushing back.
So here's what's been inspiring so much in the last couple weeks.
You know, me and DeVu, we were starting to work on, starting to work on videos together
towards the end of September.
We'd taken sort of a long break.
We had Radcon, you know, we had a lot of stuff going on.
We were trying to get ourselves sorted out and then we pumped out these two videos at
the end of September and I felt really good about that.
So then we got to work on the next one, which is Akiyuki Shinbo in the 90s, which is a project
that I'd had on hold for like a whole year.
I'd started it in at the end of 2015 and I thought there was no way I'd be willing to
edit it myself because I was going to edit it myself at the time and like just the thought
of how much effort it was going to take, which the kind of editing that it is, is the kind
of stuff that DeVu is just really good at.
I literally don't know how he edits these so fast.
He's most of the way through part two after about a day and a half and he keeps assuring
me, oh, don't worry, I'm almost done and stuff, I'm not worried, I can't believe you're working
this fast.
It's incredible how fast he can find all the specific examples that are needed for something.
What made it possible is that he, because the reason I wasn't going to ask him to do
it, is because there's a lot of stuff you have to watch for this and at the time that
I was working on it, he wasn't on my full-time payroll yet, but the biggest thing is that
he would have to watch all of Yu-Yu Hakusho, which is 112 episodes.
It just so happened that he ended up doing that anyway.
Him and his brother went ahead and just watched Yu-Yu Hakusho for the hell of it and then
I was like, oh my god, if you've seen all of Yu-Yu Hakusho, then you're already halfway
done with everything you need to watch, more than halfway done, for Shinbo in the 90s.
So I took the project off Hiatus and the two of us jammed it out.
I got the whole thing written, he's almost done editing it, he went on like a weird little
sabbatical for a few days because he went down what he calls a video game hole where
he, every once in a while, he remembers that he's really obsessed with video games and
then he just doesn't do anything but think about how badly he wants to make games and
then he snaps out of it when he runs out of money or something and so he gets back to
work on anime videos.
So while he was doing that though, we had come up with this idea where I was like, actually
he was talking about how in 2014 I put out a video every single day for a month, for
the month of October.
It was a challenge to myself that had a few purposes.
One was because I'd already written most of the 8 Nights of Karinokyokai series and so
I felt like I was already, I had a good foot in the door if I wanted to do it, I wanted
to do some kind of challenge video thing and I also wanted to have more anime videos on
my channel because I was concerned with the fact that, you know, in order to really have
a rapport with a reviewer, you need to really know a lot of their opinions, you can't really
get a sense of how you feel about someone's stance on things if you don't know their stance
on things.
So I wanted to review a lot of anime in a short period of time so people would get a better
sense of my tastes and just how I write and stuff like that.
So all of that sort of culminated in this thing and in order to make it happen, I made
bets with everyone I know, basically, I got everyone to put in money against me on whether
or not I could finish this in a month.
With the caveat being that each video was supposed to be of a level of quality that
it could be patroned if I wanted to, though I did not patron most of them and some of
them were definitely not of that level of quality, but nonetheless I did do it.
I did a video every day for a month in October and it was a big cool thing and it's funny
because I've never really gotten a lot of credit for it because my channel was fairly
small at the time and not so much in subscriber count, but people weren't watching my videos
because I was pretty new to anime and I didn't have a lot of followers who cared about anime
that deeply and I had a lot of stuff that I was talking about that nobody cared about
so I don't think anybody watched every video that month except probably the DeVu who at
that point had just started working for me as an editor and he got done, he got a couple
of those videos edited himself, so a couple of my biggest videos came out that month,
like back to back what is anime and what isn't and Sword Art Online sucks part one came out
that month.
Anyways, point being he wanted to try to do that again, like with him editing and me writing
which would make it twice as easy to get it done and I was like well a video every single
day might be pushing it because the quality definitely suffered in the previous attempt,
you know there's a lot of videos from that month that are not worth going back to really.
So I thought well what if we did one every other day and the concept will be a novel
worth of videos because November is coming and November is National Novel Writing Month.
Now I've been trying National Novel Writing Month every year since like 2006, I want to
say I've been doing it a straight decade now, I succeeded in 2010, I wrote a novel, I never
looked at it again after the month was over, like I wrote on the last day, the last day
I wrote 24,000 words, I wrote a thousand words an hour for 24 hours and that's how I finished
my novel because I hadn't touched it in like two weeks and it was way behind and I just
jammed it out in a day and then never looked at it again because it was such a mess, the
book was just so like full of plot holes and structural issues and bad writing that I just
didn't look at it ever again but all I cared about was that I had won Nano Remo because
I wrote 50,000 words in a month.
So then last year I wanted to do a novel in videos but I didn't have any good ideas until
like late into November when I came up with the Asterisk War Sucks series which did end
up being a novel in videos but I started writing it at like the very end of November and ended
around the end of December so I think it might have been slightly over a month and either
way it wasn't, I wasn't keeping track of it basically, I wasn't keeping track of time,
I didn't know it would be a novel length by the end but it was great that it turned out
that way.
So then this month I thought well what if we just straight up do that and so I wrote
myself out a day to day calendar like of how you know the Nano Remo thing is that you have
to write 1,667 words a day in order to hit 50,000 by the end of the month.
Now obviously you can write as much in a day as you want to play catch up if you need to.
Currently I have to catch up, I'm a few days behind but I've been doing pretty well.
Now when I came up with this I was like okay well the concept is 15 videos right?
So 15 out of 50,000 is something like 3,500 something like that I think maybe even 4,000.
It's a lot of words for one video because 15 videos that would all have to be like basically
between 15 and 20 minutes long is about the length that I would get from a 3,500 word
post.
So in order for that to happen each of these videos would have to be pretty long for it
to have to be a novel worth of videos and so I started writing these posts and very quickly
realized that they're not that long, they're probably closer to 10 minutes so I've been
doing a great job of keeping up with my daily quota of words but I also am quickly realizing
that I'm going to exceed 15 videos that I've written this month.
So whether or not DeVu ends up editing more or less I don't know, all I know is I'm stacking
up a backlog that's pretty fucking nice to look at right now.
I wrote 6 posts in 5 and a half days, I wrote 6 posts all of which I love, all 6 of them
I thought were great, I'm proud of all of them, they're all things from my bucket list.
Like basically there's certain videos I've wanted to write for a very long time and just
never like got around to it because one reason or another and then finally just like having
the pressure of like alright let's see if we can do it now and each every single day
that I've written for this I had started at like midnight like it was like 45 minutes
before I would be out of time for the day and I'm trying to catch up with the word count
you know so I'm trying to crank these things out like a thousand words to 1500 words in
an hour and they're coming out great like because of it because I'm just forcing myself
to actually fucking write this thing that I've been thinking I don't know how it's
going to be I don't know how to structure it and then like once you're in the moment
and it's like alright let's just first sentence that comes to mind fucking throw it down and
we'll go from there you know we'll structure it based on that and that's been a great idea
so I wrote six videos that I'm really into then so I'm I've got that going on and I'm
on like you know day six I'm kind of I start a video that I don't really like you know
I wrote a couple paragraphs and I was like this isn't going how I want it to go so it
kind of cool it cooling off to that you know just a little bit and then I I'm just this
is what I'm talking about with ideas that come up out of nowhere and then totally change
everything I'm doing so everyone's talking about this music video called shelter right
it's it's this little anime music video put together it's an a1 pictures thing everyone's
like like looking at me like oh do you hate this because it's a1 it's like it's like one
person made this it's like there's the director and then the animator who animated the whole
fucking thing you know and then like the the musician who made the music I don't even think
it's like to think of it as an a1 pictures thing is kind of like besides the point it's
obviously these two people's creation but nonetheless I don't really care for it I think
it's it's it's fairly trite and as much movement as there is in the animation the style of it
didn't really interest or impress me so yeah I wasn't that into it but nonetheless I saw
all these people talking about it and I thought man this is a great opportunity to talk about
anime music videos because one of the reasons that my my number of completed shows on my anime
list is so fucking high is because I watch lots of shorts I'll go through these phases we're all
just like spend a couple days like marathoning tons of music videos or other shorts and I think
they're really cool and like they're great way to see like lots of experimental different stuff
not all of it's good in fact not even most of it's good most of it's pretty middle of the road
usually it's like well that was kind of cool I guess but it was totally pointless and I'll never
think about it again it's pretty rare to get music videos that you actually like want to revisit
amazing but nonetheless I watched like all of them and so I thought what if I made a video like
10 cool anime music videos you should all check out since you're so psyched about this one here's
all these other great ones so then of course I think well if I want to do that I should make
sure I know every cool music video you know what if I make this video and I totally miss out on
like the coolest one ever so I go to my anime list and I sort you know by music video and like
you know show me all the completed music videos out there and there's 10 pages of about 50 shows
a page and I look at that and I think I bet I could do that I'm yeah 500 I mean they're only like
three to five minutes a piece so what's the big deal you know now I've been skipping I'm skipping
all the ones that that I can't find obviously those there's a there's a lot of them that I just
straight up can't find I'm skipping a lot of the ones that are tie-ins to shows because most of
those are awful it's usually like the opening theme song and they they animated a little thing and
it's always shit um the best ones would be stuff like the love live ones where they just make like
a music video but I I hate idol shows and I can't get into it at all I watched the video for um snow
halation and I was like this sure feels like an idol music video I mean it's incredibly well done
but I I don't like it you know I don't like the music I don't like idols uh so did didn't do much
for me but nonetheless um skipping most of those and any video that I'm just like I think is total
shit from the start I'll just stop watching it but nonetheless I go down this whole of music videos
and so for like you know this is an idea I've just had on a whim and then 12 hours later I've
been doing nothing but watching videos for 12 hours you know I have forgotten to eat or breathe
I'm just sitting there in a chair you know watching music videos non-stop and it's at some point I
got to the point where I'm like I'm not sure if I'm interested enough in this idea to keep going
like if this takes more than three days then I feel like the the hype from uh what's it called
we'll we'll have died down enough that like no one will be as open to this like it really felt
like something that had to happen now it had to be a flash in the pan it had to be completed all at once
so then as I'm working on this as I'm watching all these videos downstairs Davoo
is editing akuki shimbo in the 90s part one and he's finishing it up so I come downstairs you know
I think I had him wake me up I was like wake me up when it's done so he wakes me up
you know after I've slept probably eight hours after just a non-stop video music video binge all
night I come downstairs and I watch shimbo part one it's great we we you know workshop it a little
bit fix some things I upload it now as soon as I started seeing positive reactions to this
now mind you akuki shimbo in the 90s I knew from the start this is a video that's not going to get
a ton of views this is a video that not a ton of people are gonna care about some people are gonna
find it boring and stupid I will be shocked if anyone gets a lot out of it but the second there
was even one comment that was like this is the kind of stuff I come to you for or like wow such an
impressive amount of research or man I really learned to appreciate shimbo's work so much more
and I'm gonna check out some of these shows it only takes one comment like that to make me like
all right now we got to do part two you know like now we got to do the next one I mean
literal part two was already in the works of shinbo in the 90s but like shinbo in the 2000s
is a whole other animal and I was gonna hold off for a little bit because the project is gonna be
unbelievably massive I probably have to watch a hundred shows for this project like there's 70
that I definitely have to watch and those are ranging from you know two episodes to 26 at the
most so that's yeah that's like 70 shows I have to watch no matter what for this project now I don't
have to watch all of them before starting the project before any videos can come out like the
way I've been looking at it there might I might be able to like gradually put these out over like a
long course of time but nonetheless this is a titanic sized project and I was gonna just hold off
but the second I got that spark of inspiration it was like I gotta do it I gotta at least make the
preparations for it you know because there's a lot of prep work to be done I have to basically mostly
it's about organizing all of the data I have figuring out exactly what I need to watch why
who worked on it and what else they worked on that's basically the basis of it so I spend
probably six or seven hours putting together a list of every show that shinbo's been involved with
from the soul taker onwards and everyone who's worked on more than one of those shows so if
there's a name that appears in the credits of two shows that he worked on now I only went for major
credits no one who's just like a key animator or an in-between or something that would be
I mean what I'm doing is already psychotic but that would be next level psychotic I mean
that would be psychotic on a literal level like no one would do that no matter how like it's just
not even a good idea there's no point to it but um anyone who's a major staffer I made the connections
and I put together this fucking huge list and then I spent two days of just straight work
turning that into a spreadsheet I have spent two entire days turning it into a spreadsheet
and the funniest thing about it is that it was the easiest most natural thing in the world for me
to do there is nothing that comes more natural to me than making lists and just putting data
into boxes like I've often thought that if I like if if for some reason I had to get a desk job
I'm gonna go for a data entry job because that shit I don't know if I'll be as into it if it's
not about something I care about but like I am just unbelievably good at zoning out
and making a list all night long I at no point had the thought like like oh this has to get done
it was just I just did it and like the first day it was a natural progression right like I
finished making my list and so then I started making the spreadsheet and then at some point I
was too tired to go on and I passed out I woke up at 11 30 p.m or no no what stopped me working on
the spreadsheet was I had to record the pcp uh Nate was gathering everybody together he was
really I was like I was too tired I wasn't gonna do it but he he conned me into it I did the pcp
and then I read some comics and then I went to bed woke up at 11 30 p.m I sat down in my chair
the spreadsheet was open and I didn't even like ask myself do I want to do something else first
I just started working on it and I didn't stop for 12 hours that's just it I just sat down
and I worked on it for 12 hours and it was it was helped as well by the fact that like
I've been in sort of a musical slump for most of this year uh you know I'm a big music fan but
I've kind of run out of like music that I that I like that I'm not sick of I listen to the same
shit over and over and over and over again I was getting tired of all the uh all the stuff I had
and I wasn't finding anything new I was I was out there on the prowl you know I ask people for
recommendations all the time but nobody knows what I like so yeah I can never find anything
new I haven't liked much of the new stuff coming out this year um so I decided I was like I need
a revolution I need to just go out there and start downloading shit and mass and fill my computer
first of all fill it with all the stuff it's missing because most of my stuff that I have on my
computer um is new because like at some point my um my hard drive died at like the start of 2014
and I lost all the music I had and I just never got it all back like all that I had on my computer
was stuff that was on my phone so anything that was still on the phone is on the computer and
there's like certain certain albums I've gone and like re-downloaded it or re-burned it to my
computer but there's like whole discographies of bands that I love that I haven't looked into
in you know the last two years and then also there's lots of songs that I've accumulated over time
that like that are like singles by bands that I don't really like any of their albums but I really
like that single but I've never downloaded the albums I just go to YouTube every once in a blue
moon you know and and and listen to it so I thought I'll download all those discographies too so I
found a reliable Russian torrenting site and just started mass downloading music and uh that helped
a lot with the spreadsheet making because listening to a band's entire discography is hard to make
time for unless you're doing a menial task that takes all fucking day and really leaves you with
like most of your brain space open to listen to music so I listened to like countless hours of Omar
Rodriguez Lopez music that's the guitarist for the Mars Volta who puts out um he he's basically like
a light novel artist of music he puts out stuff fucking constantly for ever since like 2006 he's
had at minimum like four albums a year and then this year he's pulling a full-blown NCOE scene and
doing an album a month every month all year the man's crazy he's not as bad as Buckethead but he's
crazy so I downloaded like 30 Omar albums and I was listening to a bunch of those then I downloaded
like the whole discography of Bad Religion which is a band who has like like 10 singles that I love
that I never heard an album of theirs so I was listening to their discography and I gotta say
I was surprised that a lot of it is pretty good like I expected it to just pretty much be the
singles but there's other great songs in there those guys are masters of hooks they write the
best hooks in the world there's so many songs with memorable choruses I it's it's it's crazy
because all their songs sound exactly the same except that they all have a different awesome
memorable chorus um so I was listening to all that um AFI downloaded their discography only to
realize that the one I grew up with December Underground is probably their only good album
but it is a great album I like I mean it was partly nostalgia for me but that album is fantastic
I like didn't remember it being as good as it was when I listened to it just now and I was like whoa
finally downloaded the fucking mindless self-indulgence discography I haven't had them on my computer
since the crash two years ago and immediately I realized mindless self-indulgence might be
my actual favorite band and I just forgotten all this time because I didn't have them on my computer
but my god I love them so much and yeah if you haven't noticed I'm mostly like
downloading stuff that I listened to when I was like a teenager or uh or like a young adult
I'm in that phase in my life where uh you know all all like
concept of guilt like guilty pleasures like I mean I don't believe in guilty pleasures anyway
but like any sort of shame I might have had about something I liked before is gone I will
probably download Linkin Park's discography and give the whole thing a whirl by the end of this week
so expect to hear a lot more of me singing because there's some great Linkin Park songs
like there's some songs that come on the radio when somewhere I belong comes on or faint comes on
I still get excited so I know there's gems in that discography I just gotta dig them out you know
really the biggest difficulty of this whole process is gonna be when I have to go through
every album by all these bands and try to like weed out all the songs I absolutely hate
because more on that subject I'm also starting to try and adopt a a populist mindset as they as
they call it on on mute I don't know if it's a meme or if it's like a thing that people actually
study but like uh you know I I was recently introduced to the youtuber Todd in the shadows
I'd heard about him for fucking ever he's a he's a classic that guy with the glasses member
been around the internet for a very long time um I I can't stand that guy with the glasses
stuff so I've avoided him but now that I actually watched him he's actually really good and he
does these really interesting videos about pop music and what's most interesting to me about it
is that it's pop music and I hate pop music so like hearing someone go really in depth about
this genre that I have like no interest or experience with it's pretty interesting like
I feel like he's um giving me the opportunity to have opinions about these things or to feel
anything about uh you know a musical genre that I would typically avoid and it's really funny for
me when I watch his like top 10 and top uh bottom 10 of the year because I can't really tell the
difference that much in the musical quality I'm like it's all just shitty pop music but
nonetheless he can get me to care about it to even like root for a song or artist or something like
that you know um but in any case part of what's interesting about it is that he really goes
by song you know he's like a song reviewer he doesn't have album reviews the way that like
Anthony Fantano would and I've always been an album guy I've always been someone who sits and
listens to the whole album but in the last couple of years I've felt myself gravitating towards
like shorter and shorter albums because I don't have time to listen to whole albums all the time
you know and um part of it was also when I lost all that music because I've always kept just the
tracks I really like on my iPod you know like I'm not going to keep the slower songs on there
because if I'm driving which is why I'm listening to music on my phone then like
I'm not going to want to hear the soft songs so I just leave them all off
but like now there's a bunch of albums on my computer where I only have the songs I really
like and guess what I like those albums a lot more now you know like um Sufjan Stevens album
The Age of Odds I would consider one of my favorite albums and the album's like almost 90
minutes long it's long as shit and I don't think that it would be one of my favorite albums if I
listen to the entire thing every single time because I'm not that into the song like too much
or the song uh god even the opening track like there's a there's a few tracks from the album
that just aren't on my phone and so like I kind of forgot about them until like the other day I
was listening to the song the whole album on YouTube like to hear those extra songs and I was like
yeah I know why I cut these out because this is like an extra 20 minutes of the album that without
it the album's easier to listen to and I'm more likely to listen to it repeatedly and you know
hear the songs I do like over and over again so I'm really warming up to this idea of like listening
to singles especially because my fucking phone has it has this might sound like a lot but my phone
only has 940 songs on it and it doesn't actually take that long to end up hearing all of it you
know and because shuffle sucks and every time it restarts it just plays you every fucking song
you just heard again and even when you go through it for a while like you know a lot of those are
again whole albums so like yeah 941 songs might sound like a lot but that's really like if there's
let's say 13 tracks an album um less than 90 albums that still sounds like a lot when I put it down
but let's just say I've heard those 941 songs many many times you know I rarely update
what's on my phone I rarely take stuff off or put stuff on so I'm quite used to hearing all of it
and I drive a decent amount so yeah like I'm really in this mindset of it's time to
totally change my library let's get rid of all the songs I don't care about
let's put all the songs I like on and obviously not every song I like is one that I want to
listen to constantly but they do need to be on there you know like I don't exactly throw on
spirit they're gone spirit they vanished by uh animal collective when I'm like in the car
driving down the highway it's a very like contemplative alone at night song uh or album rather
so you know that one's going to stay on the computer but not likely make it onto the phone
but still you get what I'm saying and the reason it's called a a populist mindset is like
on mute they talk about how you know there's there's like rockists people who are into rock
music have a tendency to like really put all of their emphasis on the album um whereas people
who are into pop tend to put emphasis more on the songs and I do think that something is lost
by focusing too much on on full albums because I you know I watch Anthony Fantano's reviews
and sometimes he'll give like an eight out of ten to an album that is very consistent and very
strong in how it sounds but and maybe he feels differently than I do about this anyways but
like I'll feel like none of the songs individually stand out it's like a solid album at having the
sound it has but it's not an album I really want to hear all the time whereas there's some albums
that if you just take off a couple songs then all the rest of them are like the best song ever
you know like um acid rap by chance the rapper every song on it with the exception of smoke again
is like the greatest song ever written smoke again sucks I took smoke again off of there like
when I the album for like around when uh when I first discovered the album and uh I've never
had a problem it's always been like my favorite album I just kind of forgot that song is even
a part of it so like when you see it up on my my favorite albums list like just keep in mind
the caveat that I have forgotten that smoke again is a song on the album it's not even a terrible
song I just don't like it that much um the album lady gaga's art pop like manicure god awful song
take that off great album I originally had a few more songs off gypsy is pretty bad too take off gypsy
um but I originally had like Mary Jane Holland and uh what's the other one Donatella I originally
didn't have those on there but they worked their way back on you know it's not like I'm not open to
listening to these songs again and re reaffirming whether they belong on my list manicure is really
bad though that's an unlistenable song but nonetheless with all that stuff removed art
pops one of my favorite albums so I do think that there's something to this song based mindset
and I'd really like to get into it so aside from all that stuff that's been going on I also read
some comics yesterday uh consider this a response to Jesse's panel cast because uh Jesse started
up a podcast about reading new comics and he recommended some cool stuff and one of them was
Gwenpool which I like he was talking about it and he was showing the cover art on screen and I just
thought the character design was super adorable because it's like this just super bright pink
um very like anime-ish art style and I really liked it and then in the comments he had linked
someone he had he had linked someone a page of a batman comic but it was on this like comic
reader website and I was like oh hey a comic reader website I wonder if they have Gwenpool
oh they do oh Gwenpool only has seven chapters so far because it's a brand new comic this all the
stars are lining up just right so I read all of Gwenpool and it was really good um it has it has
these great it's a it's a comic that plays with the meta of comics in really pretty obvious ways
but effective ways where it's it's kind of all about Gwen Gwenpool like basically she she knows
she's in a comic she used to read comics and she she's like you know from our world and she's taken
into this world and it's about her constantly like well you know what I won't get too into it
because Jesse talks about it in his podcast but I will talk about what I really liked at the end
of volume one is that there's a shit gets real moment that was like really intense and what I
liked about it is that it was this villain who is sort of a goofy villain and Gwenpool doesn't
take him seriously because she's like ha you know you're you're that guy like why would I take you
seriously and then he just like vaporizes like her friend right in front of her and it was shocking
because the tone of this comic is mostly pretty light-hearted and upbeat and this is like right
at the end of chapter one and it was shocking but what was cool about it is that it's that
villain because like yeah to us who don't have to deal with the consequences of a villain a super
villain's actions they can just be goofy but like when you think about what is actually happening
in the comic that a person has been vaporized you know then it's suddenly like man even the
goofiest super villain is is murdering people you know they are actually murdering people and that
shit is rough you know and that's sort of what the lesson of the comic is it's what Gwenpool is
out there to realize is that you know shit is like for basically she sees it as this is a comic
therefore I can't take it seriously whereas what she has to realize is that for the characters in
the comic it is the real world and everything is as serious as it would be in the real world and
you know the comic is constantly drawing attention to how kind of shit it is to live in the comic
book world especially to the police force who are all just like they hate living in this town and
like why do we have to deal with this every day you know and uh that's the meta part that I really
like about it you know and I think that's really what the core of it is like there's lots of just
meta humor and jokes that aren't really that funny it's just kind of whatever you know it's just
kind of filler dialogue in a way but the actual core of the intrigue of it is really good um
and it's a lot of fun it kind of reminds me a little bit of the webcomic strong female
except the strong female protagonist is a lot more serious and a lot more like edgy
where a strong female protagonist is like a straight up watchmen thing Gwenpool is just fun
and lighthearted and like even though it has these like kind of deep biting messages it never
loses its tone of just like whimsical and fun um you know like when big things happen they tend to
happen in like pinpoint shock moments that are quickly over with as we get back to the fun um
and I like that about it it feels it makes it very easy to read and so yeah I might go and actually
buy the first graphic novel because it is out I believe um of the first six chapters
so in other news there was that Kickstarter that happened I started it probably over a week ago
it's up to seven thousand dollars an incredible amount of money um I'm extremely paranoid about it
because the Kickstarter the income of it is taxable right I I have to pay taxes on it and
everything's in my name with regard to this Kickstarter now the person who's supposed to
get most of this money is Jesse but in the process of setting because this Kickstarter
kept making more money I kept adding more goals to it and I added all these goals about uh
blue rays and like how we'll make and send blue rays and I think it's entirely possible that I
have way like grossly underestimated the shipping cost of shipping all these blue rays out and that
I also haven't really accounted for how much of this money might get taken by taxes so uh and then
like a lot of the money has to go to flying everybody down you know uh and having them all
here for a week so I don't actually know if there is enough money in the Kickstarter to fund everything
that the Kickstarter promises um so I'm concerned about that but we won't really find out until
it's all said and done like I don't know what it's gonna cost to ship all these blue rays until I
know what it cost to ship to each of these people's houses um hopefully most of them live in the
United States but you never know it's a it's a mystery to everybody you know if it turns out
all of them live in Europe then it could end up racking up quite a hefty quite a hefty fee
but it also could be that I actually allocated more money for it than I realize like I don't I
don't know it's it's a it's a confusing process I think I had initially set it so that each dvd
goal was like $500 and that most of that would be for uh for mailing but I don't know if that's
enough so yeah I'm concerned about that but at the same time hopeful because I mean the results of
it have been incredible you know that it was such a weird moment of like why didn't we think to do
this before you know because we just did radcon one um at the start of september and like radcon
getting it organized was a huge ordeal you know because it's it's six people all have to have
time at the same time we all have to travel you know everyone had to figure out how they were
going to pay for it you know hypocrite costs a thousand dollars for a round trip from fucking
england um you know we were pitching in money I paid like $120 to his ticket you know just to
help him get over here and none of us ever thought maybe our audience would just want to see this
you know maybe now I mean it would have been harder to prove to our audience what we could do
you know like what's great about the plebe and the weave is that we already had three episodes so
we could say hey here's exactly what you're getting if you pay for this you know but like
the results were so overwhelming that I really do think like maybe we could have done this for
the first radcon you know and we had all been salt like after radcon was over we were all saying like
this should not be a once a year thing you know this should definitely happen sooner we've had
too many good projects good ideas and we really want to start talking about getting everybody
into one place you know because ben and divu moved in at the time of radcon but every all of us
want to live in the in proximity to each other because we've all been saying all this time that
like if we all lived in proximity we'd get so much stuff done there'd be so many projects we could do
together you know we could really make things come to life and like the part the point of radcon
was to prove that and we did prove that we got lots of great content out of it you know we got
stuff like the potty cast live or ben's uh lecture which is ben's lecture is like a totally different
genre of video that none of us have done before or would have thought of but now that it exists
it's like this is fucking genius there needs to be more of this you know i'd love to do a classroom
thing you know as often as possible doing the plebe in the weave was something me and jesse
had been planning for years just because we were like it won't be the same if we're in different
rooms it just won't be what we're looking for you know and now that we have it it's like this is
what we've been looking for so you know jesse said pretty early on into radcon he was like i
clearly need to move down here because this is obviously the best career path you know uh like
if i want to have a successful youtube career i need to be around you people um you know
nate has wanted to get down here for as long as as long as i've known him you know but he's trapped
by um financial insecurity but he just he's finished school so he doesn't worry about staying
there for school he's just trapped at his job and as soon as he can well he's not quite finished
with school but he's almost finished with school and like once he finishes school um and then you
know has enough money that he could leave his job and he could obviously make more money if it came
down here so like radcon too is probably a lot of going to be planning for how we're gonna move
those guys down here you know and i would really love if like jesse and nate could get a place together
i don't know how soon we can even get hippo i don't know if he needs citizenship or like a work visa
or something but like you know if if we could somehow afford to have to have everybody move in
then eventually we'll be able to you know get everybody because i think someone like nate who
on his own content he spends so much time it's it's definitely hard for him to turn a profit
on the kind of content he's making where every single thing is a six month long project for a
45 minute video but he when he works with other people we get stuff out all the time and if we
were turning a profit on something like pcp which the pcp as it stands is a goofy little podcast
that's you know we we vaguely come up with a topic we all jump into a call we talk over each
other and it's a nightmare but like the amount of effort that goes into a pcp would not increase
that much if we turned it into a live show with a little bit more production you know if it was
maybe three people on a panel and we have a little set and we discuss a more concrete topic and we
do that once a month it might become something that's worth patroning you know if we had a
patreon for the pcp uh and if you know if nate had a show that he could patreon i think he'd
probably be able to be a lot more quickly successful than he's gonna get with these super long uh you
know video projects and so that's why i really want everyone living in one place because i think
we will all make a lot more money this way you know ben by all rights should be making more money
because i keep offering him uh art things to do but he keeps not doing them um but nonetheless he
does have the opportunity divu is obviously gonna make a hell of a lot more money living with me
because we can get videos done quicker i mean if he didn't live with me we would not have been
inspired for this 15 videos in a month thing of which six are already written so guaranteed
you know next month we are going to make a shitload of money like even if i don't write
any more videos after this point i've already got enough um that you know we will have a very
successful time ahead of us so yeah i think everything's coming up really well and it's kind of
it's kind of like i'm watching a bunch of plans that i've had for so long that have always felt
so far away suddenly come into sharp relief you know it's like all at once earlier this year
in around like uh the area of july to august like my channel suddenly spiked in growth and my
patreon suddenly spiked in growth and then my parents decided to move out and then we built a
studio in my house and then ben and divu decided to move in and it's like these are all things that
i always thought were going to happen eventually and then they did and it's like holy shit well now
it's time for all the other things that we've wanted to happen eventually to happen you know uh
when are we going to stop talking about getting nate down here and just get nate down here you
know when are we going to stop saying jessie needs to move out of his house and somehow find a way
for him to move out of his house you know like it could be happening soon and i feel like this
kickstarter really gave us the opportunity to start making those considerations that like
you know after radcon we were all like well i don't know when we'll be able to do this again
when will we once again have a thousand dollars to fly hippo down you know that's a crazy amount of
money but now we have it all of a sudden we have it now it's just like oh well apparently radcon
two is gonna be in january uh let's buy everybody's tickets and get down here and when we're here we
could talk about how we're going to make this happen again you know next time it doesn't need to
be a kickstarter it could just be that we have money you know maybe we're not maybe we're not
capitalizing well enough on how much like clout we have you know that that that clearly there's
some part of our audience who cares a lot about getting us you know getting to see us do things
together um and we should be taking advantage of it in a in the best way not in the uh not in the
way that that could be taken well i guess that's most of what's been on my mind i felt pretty comfy
on this couch this beer has gotten warm in my hand as i've been barely sipping it between long
sections of tirade but uh yeah this was a good way to decompress i feel it i feel
i feel like i just spent an hour on something that wasn't staring blankly at a spreadsheet
and blasting uh mid-2000s music that i used to listen to so i got done everything i wanted to get
done with this and i hope you guys enjoyed it i hope if you if you like this idea for a podcast
let me know um you know if you think this is something that you like really want to see
more of then let me know if it's more of a passive i don't really care this way or that yeah it was
fun but whatever then it probably i will be less likely to ever do it again but if it's something
that people are like holy shit this is a revelation in podcasting technology then i'll probably do
another one all right uh bottoms up have a good night of drinking and resting and uh let's play
out with some nice chilled out tunes
so
I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not
sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me,
I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I'm not sure if you can hear me, I