You know, I suspected a day was going to come when I was going to start feeling nostalgic
about things. I used to always say that I don't really get nostalgic because I think
most people, at least it seemed to me, like when people talked about things that made
them nostalgic, that nostalgia usually came from a place of wanting to go back to a time
when you were happier. Like, it seemed like so many people who were obsessed with nostalgia
properties or people who felt like their childhood was happier than their adulthood
is. And I never felt that way. I feel like everything's gotten much better. If you listen
to the previous podcast, The Depression Chamber, you know exactly why. I was pretty miserable
up until my twenties and now I feel great. But there is nostalgia is not that linear,
I don't think. And I think maybe I was just still too young to really feel nostalgia about
a lot of things. Because, you know, obviously most of the things I'm nostalgic about from
the past are the good memories I do have. You know, they're the things that helped me
get through all of those tough times. So they still have that impact of like, you know,
bringing a smile to my face to think back on how much these things meant to me back
at the time. But right now I have been in like an almost downward spiral of nostalgia.
That's maybe an over-dramatic way of putting it. But lately it's like, you know, I just
played through Pokemon Sun and Moon. And Pokemon's always a nostalgia thing, you know, because
it was a huge part of my childhood. Much more so than I think. I mean, Pokemon makes most
people nostalgic because they're like, oh yeah, I was really into that for like a year.
You know, for me, it's like that was what my life was for four years, you know, as a
kid. And it's not that it's ever completely gone away. And in fact, in recent years, it's
been even bigger because of, especially this year with Pokemon Go coming out and all these
nuzzlocks happening and stuff. And, you know, it felt kind of natural to play through Pokemon
Sun, whereas with X and Y, it was kind of like this whole return to Pokemon. But nonetheless,
it's still a nostalgia thing. You know, me and Victor have been recording Digi Bros.
I think the first episode of Bomberman will be out before this podcast. So you'll see
that, you know, we've been playing this old N64 game, which Digi Bros is usually old games.
We usually play classics, you know, but we're getting back into that. I've been listening
to a lot of old music, like music that I used to listen to when I was younger. Because this
year, I just kind of got sick of all the music I had. Because basically, I think I talked
about this a couple podcasts ago, maybe on the first decompression chamber that like,
you know, a couple years ago, I'd had a hard drive failure. So most of what is on my computer
is whatever was on my phone, which is just mostly newer stuff or stuff that I got into
in the last few years. And I've had a pretty consistent input of like new bands and new
stuff to listen to until this year. There's been barely anything I really liked this year.
It's been a real rough year for music for me. So I've been looking back a lot. I've been
downloading a lot of the old discographies, the bands I used to listen to all the time,
you know, sort of getting back into these old bands, remembering how much I liked these
records and why, even though most of it is very nostalgia, you know. And even the other
stuff I'm listening to that is stuff that I didn't listen to as a kid is still older
music. So, you know, lots of older, more nostalgic tunes going by. And then I've also been looking
more and more to my old work, like, because, you know, lately, I've entered this extreme
high productivity sort of frame of mind where I'm constantly putting out videos and vlogs
and all this other stuff and looking at all this new shit. And, and, and I feel like on
some level, I've become kind of a machine, you know, like I just kind of churn out product
and it's just ideas, ideas, ideas, here's an idea, that's a video, here's an idea, that's
a video. And there's a lot less, like, artistry to it. There's less of that open-minded creativity
of, like, expressing my, my innermost feelings and thoughts, you know, which a lot of my
older work was exceedingly personal. And I don't know whether it's a good thing or not
because, like, my current self kind of cringes at a lot of it. A lot of it's like, oh, God,
why did I have to try? Like, why did I feel like every little thing that was important
to me had to be out there, you know, even if some of it's gross or weird. But then I
kind of look at a lot of the stuff that I'm a fan of and a lot of it's like that, you
know, I guess it's only weird because it's me, but so much of what I consume is, like,
grossly personal and intense and in your face, you know. So maybe, maybe I'm missing out
on some level by, by the fact that now that I finally have an audience who could appreciate
those things, you know, those aspects of myself, I've sort of gotten that audience by not approaching
those subjects and I haven't had the desire to approach those subjects again. So it's,
it's kind of an odd, an odd sense of progression there. Like, like, I feel like my 20 year
old self would be kind of disappointed that, that my, my content now is so kind of clean
and straightforward. And I mean, not that it's totally that I'm still pretty, you know,
fairly out there, I think. I still make weird stuff every now and then, but the kind of
shit I made when I was younger was so much more like, gross. So what really brought this,
what really brought me into this is that I, I finally, and I hope this is also out on
my Reddit, I didn't want this to be a wide release, but I recorded an audio book of the
book that I wrote in 2010, which is very bad. It's not as bad as I expected, which is why
I decided to do an audio book of it. I thought the ideas were interesting, and that some
of it was kind of okay. And I really just want closure on the whole thing. I want to
finally be able to like, you know, not think about the story all the time. But the irony,
of course, is that reading through it again just reawakened all my memories about it.
It reminded me of what I was like back then, and what things I cared about, and I started
thinking about all these characters again, and who they were, and why, you know, a lot
of stuff I'd forgotten. So much of what's in this book, because I never read the book.
So much of it is stuff that was so typical of me at the time, and is not now, and it's
weird to feel that sort of dualism or dichotomy or something. I'm not sure what word I'm looking
for. But at the same time, it's kind of dragging me in. Like, it's reminding me of things that
I used to feel, and like, sort of prodding me to feel those things again. Like, hey,
didn't you care a lot about this subject, you know? But I don't now. So it's very jarring
and strange. And like, just being surrounded with so much nostalgia stuff, like my mind
is trying to rush back to this time. And if I had to over explain it, and I don't know
this is really the case, maybe it's just a coincidence. But I do feel like maybe there's
some yearning on my part to return to when I was more artistically minded, when I was
more expressive and more like, trying to feel something deeper or more romantic than what
I do now, because I've just become such a machine. I've become such a content, just,
you know, crank. Like, now it's just every day I've got some kind of vlog or some kind
of podcast. I do so many back to back podcasts that I can't even like, I can't edit them
fast enough. Like, the reason this episode is delayed is just that I was working on
so many other things that there was no room for a decompression podcast. Like, I'm finally,
as of probably when this is coming out, I've probably started releasing these Let's Plays.
I have a whole month of Let's Plays. I have, you know, 12 episodes of Bomberman, and we're
probably going to finish that game and schedule it for the rest of the month and like, 15 plus
episodes of Wario Land 4 with me and Davoo. So those are all coming out now. And I had those
sitting on my computer for a while, because I couldn't edit them because I was doing too many
other things. I have my three hour commentaries I released at the end of the month, edited one of
those, I edit the PCP, and I'm on it every week. I don't edit the Pub Crawl, but I'm on that every
week. You know, I've got this podcast now. I guest on people, I guested on Mumkey. It was like,
the last three days were, we did a Pokemon PCP, that was two hours. Then the next day,
I guested on Mumkey's thing, which was an hour. And then the next day, I guested on Pub Crawl,
which is an hour. And like, just doing those three back to back, it's like every day I had to be
prepared for, you're gonna spend an hour doing a podcast today, in between editing other podcasts
and having vlog ideas. And then I'm also working on like, this hour long video that I've been
fucking putting off constantly, because it's kind of a pain in the ass to edit. And it's not, it's
not that great. So like, it's, it's, it's like a way too big of a video for the level of quality
that it is, you know, that I just kind of don't feel like editing. And then I'm also editing the
audiobook, which is even less of high quality. It's, it's painful because it's bad, like editing,
putting so much effort into something that is bad, is painful. It's like, you know, I'm fucking
sitting there trying to make sure that I add enough gap, like, because I don't want it to be, you
know, shitty. But it's hard to like, time out how long should the gaps be between me reading each
sentence in an audiobook, what would make for a comfortable listening experience of this terrible
book, you know, like, oh God, there is no comfortable listening experience, because the story
itself makes me uncomfortable. It's such a nightmare. But just being surrounded with all this
nostalgia, while I'm in the middle of being like this, this, this mechanism of content creation is
pulling me in weird directions. And I feel like I need to take a step back sometime soon, you
know, like, because so much of this is just for the hell of it. Like, there's no reason for me to
put out this much content. It's totally like, it's totally asinine that I've gotten myself involved
in so many things, like that I stacked this podcast on top of like, you know, pub crawls every
week, which is low effort, low, low on my part, because I just show up and talk, you know, and
drink, though the drinking can be a bit of a commitment. If I get myself drunk, then I'm kind
of stuck that way. For the rest of the night. But PCP, like, you know, I'm editing them. I don't
know why I don't know why I'm on every episode, I don't need to be, you know, you've got enough
people, you can always do it without me, but I always end up showing up in doing that, and taking
all these other podcast offers and shit, and then editing this. And it's so unnecessary, and I don't
need to have a vlog out every day, and I don't need to do all this. I've been doing more and more
unpaid work, like for myself. I keep giving myself more things that are like, something I just post
on my Reddit, you know, like something that has no nothing to do with anything is just a pure passion
project. And it's like, I mean, it's cool that this is what I like doing. But I think I need to get
a girlfriend. I need it. And I started thinking, like the way I've been thinking about stuff like
that is like, like I was seriously contemplating just like buying a love doll and being like, I
don't, you know, well, if my lifestyle is going to be that I never leave the house and never talk
to any other humans, I might as well have some companionship, you know, but it's like, maybe
what needs to change is the lifestyle. Maybe I shouldn't be living a life where I do nothing
but make videos so often that I can't even talk to other people, you know, considering I've made
no effort in that regard. I haven't even tried. I have not once like attempted just talking
to someone, you know, or, or trying to date or something. And I feel like that would be a great
distraction. It's a great way to get out like, you know, I'm always saying, oh, I need some kind
of hobby other than just making videos, you know, like that would be a good hobby, something to
occupy some of that time. As long as it was a healthy relationship with which God knows how
to find one of those, you know, but again, I haven't even tried. So who knows what's out there.
Yeah, I just feel like I'm getting too wrapped up in my work. I'm doing too, doing too much as
bus driver saying about way too much and, and, and bugging myself in all this nostalgia is kind
of not helping. It's just igniting like the way it's reminding me of the artistic passions I had
when I was younger that I don't really feel anymore. But I feel like I like I'm supposed to
or something like I feel guilty for not doing more unpaid work for not doing more like a,
like, you know, speak from the soul kind of shit, which I really don't need in my life.
Like it's not something I think would be fun to do. It would just be a bunch of bullshit, you know,
and I'm editing a book I wrote fucking six years ago. That's not even good for some reason.
But hopefully when I'm done with it, that'll all be behind me and I can get back to
whatever I do. I don't know. I don't know what it like. I don't see any future for myself,
like outside of this. Like everyone else I know, I think has this mindset that, that things are going
to, things are going to change eventually, you know, like, you're going to hit a certain amount of
money that you're making or a certain amount of fame and things are going to change in some
meaningful way. Like, you know, Jesse is trying to save up enough money that he can get himself
like a nice car and move into his own place and start traveling the country. That's his dream.
He wants to see the real America travel the country. You know, Nate wants to eventually
make enough money on his art that he can become a full-time artist. Hippo wants the same thing.
Tommy Oliver wants the same thing. You know, he wants to finally release the shackles of being a
video maker and having a day, two day jobs and just become a writer. You know, they all want
something different from what they have. I'm sure DeVu, you know, even though he's comfortable
right now editing for me, I'm sure he'd eventually like to be famous on his own terms, you know,
and make stuff for himself. I know he wants to be a game developer eventually or at least to make,
he wants to make enough money one day that he can pay people to bring his game ideas to life.
You know, all those guys have all these other, all these other goals and all I ever really wanted
was to make enough money doing whatever I want that I could continue doing whatever I want.
And I'm already there. I don't know where to go from here. There's no,
there's no higher ceiling than what I've achieved. You know, I already make enough money.
I don't need any more. There's nothing I want that's so expensive that I can't afford it, you know.
There's no challenge that I've yet to undertake that I feel like, you know, like there's certain
video projects I'm working on, but I don't think they're any harder or more like more relevant
than what I did before. Like I kind of feel like I, after like the Astroscore series, like I wrote
a book in video form, that's like, that was kind of my highest echelon of what I thought could be
done with the with analysis videos and I've already hit it. So from here, it's just like, you know,
maintaining that level. So it's like, there's got to be something else I can do, you know, like,
not to say that it's kind of like with lifting, like me and Ben have been lifting, right? And
every other day, we raise our weight limit, like we, we, we lift every other day and like,
we do squats and it's like, today I'm doing 205. So the next time we do squats, I do 210, you know,
and keep pushing it further so that your muscles keep expanding. And then eventually,
when you hit your max, that's when you just start doing maintenance, when you just start
lifting the same amount just to keep the figure you currently have. And that's where I am. I'm
just doing maintenance. I'm just doing reps to keep things the way they are, you know,
my Patreon's not really going up significantly anymore. It's just kind of sat in a place,
you know, my view counts are not significantly going up. So I'm kind of like, you know, for the
last couple months, it's been like, all right, this is how much money I make, you know, this is
how many videos I can get out in a month, which is three to five, pretty much. This is the level
of quality that me and DeVu can achieve. You know, DeVu doesn't seem to be trying to like push
himself to do like bigger and better editing jobs, you know, he's, if anything, he's more
into streamlining it, you know, and trying to get more done in less time. And he's just been
spending all his off time watching tons and tons of anime. So like, yeah, I don't know, I feel
stagnant. And I don't, it's weird, I don't want to say like, I hate it, because I feel fine,
you know, everything's fine. It's just that like, it's weird to not have an image of where
things are supposed to go from here, because I always did before. I always had a, there's the
next peak, there's the next thing I have to get to. And like, the only thing I really have to be
that is money, like make more money, make significantly more money. But I don't need
any more money. I don't know what I'm going to do with that money. If I get it, my savings are
getting ridiculous right now, you know, like I have a ton of money saved up. I don't need a whole
lot more. You know, this month, this past month, November, because I'm recording this on the 30th,
like I had this goal that me and DeVoo were going to put out five videos because I was like,
yeah, we didn't, we didn't get out that many in the last couple months, you know,
so we didn't make a shit ton of money. So this month, let's try to make more money than before.
And then like, we were coming up on the end of the month and I had the fifth video that we had
planned as like a more complicated one than the other ones. And we didn't really have enough time
to do it. And at first I was like, all right, we're going to buckle down, we're just going to work
nonstop for four days, you know, but then it was like, we were already having like complications
gathering all the footage. And so I was like, all right, well, you know, let's just put it on,
let's let's just put that video on hold, I'll just write a shorter video that we can do by the
end of the month. And then I was going through like trying to come up with one that would be easy
enough to do. And then I was just like, why I don't even need to, I don't need to, I made enough
money on the four videos we've already made. There's no need to force myself to make a fifth video,
especially when I'm in the middle of editing this audio book and doing all this other shit.
So fuck it, you know, why push myself? Why am I, why am I trying so hard when it's not going to
change anything? And that's, that's a, I don't, yeah, that's the thing I don't like. Like, it's
not that I feel day to day pain, like I feel great, but I, it's, it's, you know, I'm looking at Casey
Neistat over here who just canceled his vlog and like moved in this whole, you know, different
direction just because he felt like he'd plateaued. And I'm like, that's how I feel, you know, but it's
not showing in my work, because everything I do is still unique and interesting. And, and I still
really like the videos I'm making, you know, I think everything I'm putting out is great. I think
the vlogs are, you know, are always interesting, fresh little ideas. The podcasts show at least
somewhat different angles of the same, you know, opinions and stuff. But like, I don't know, I
don't know what I'm doing. I think, I think the best solution is not right now, I don't think the
solution is take on an even bigger project, because there really is no bigger project that I
need to do. What I really need to do is find something else to do, something else to be
passionate about. So, you know, like a relationship would be the obvious answer. That's the one
that's like, yeah, that'll occupy your time. It's something that, you know, that I probably want.
But do I even for any like, why even? I don't know. It's so weird. I don't know what else I would
want to do though. There's nothing else that I'm interested in like, becoming passionate. I don't
want to play sports, you know. I don't want to just pick up some random fucking hobby to do. I don't
want a day job, because I like my sleep, I like being able to sleep and wake up whenever I want,
even though the last few days I just like straight up slept like for the majority of two days. Like,
I felt weird and shitty because I had eaten something wrong and sat in a chair for too long
recording an audiobook for fucking six hours and then I just felt like shit and just kind of passed
out for the better part of two days. So, and the idea that there's no negative consequence for that
is almost scary. So I guess that's where I'm at. I'm too comfortable. I need to find something
interesting to do with myself other than making videos. But I don't want to stop, you know,
none of this is to say I want to stop what I'm doing now. Like, unlike Casey in the vlog, I don't
think anything I'm doing has gotten dry. I don't think I need to stop doing vlogs or change the
nature of my videos. Like, all those are going fine. I just need another thing. Alright, I'm
probably repeating myself at this point, so I'll see you in the next part.
Okay, so this is me coming back a few hours later after the previous recording and I feel
at my wit's end when it comes to understanding the world and other people and my place within it.
Because I decided, you know, after I said all that stuff in the last part, the last part where
I was like, hey, you know, maybe I should seek out a relationship. Maybe I should start dating. I
was like, well, let's just get to it. Let's put my money where my mouth is. Let's go sign up for
some dating sites. So I went around and looked at a bunch of them and made some profiles. And I just
don't get it at all. Like, none of the parameters that are suggested on a dating site on any of the
ones I looked at seem like any reason that I'd want to talk to someone. You know, like,
they're like hobbies and like all this really general information and all this like boring
shit. I was just like, none of this makes me interested in a person that I'd want to talk to
them or, or, you know, like, and everyone just looks like aliens to me. I don't know what it is.
People, no one looks human to me. All of the women I was, I was looking at, I was just like,
you know, something about seeing just a photo of someone. It's like, it's not even a person.
I don't know. I feel so weird looking at like other humans, especially like just normies,
you know, everyone I looked at has this just looks like a normal person. I don't know how to
communicate with normal people. I don't like, when I see someone who looks particularly normal,
then I just feel like I would have nothing to talk to this person. Like, I have no idea how I
would communicate with a normal looking person. You know, it's, it's a bizarre feeling. I was
like, I guess I need to look at some kind of like dating site for weirdos. And then I looked into
those, but then everyone there looked weird. So I don't know what the fuck I'm looking for.
I don't know how to fill in information on these sites. Everyone that I get matched with seems to
have way more interest than I do. I have such a narrow field of interests, which I guess sounds
weird, because like all of my interests are just media consumption, which to me, like, you know,
to people who are into media, I guess that's like a broad range. Oh, you're into anime and comics
and movies and all this stuff. But like to me, that's kind of all just one umbrella. You know,
like if you're, if you're filling out stuff on a dating site, that's really just one thing. Like,
I like movies and you know, and maybe you could check video games and maybe, maybe art or music.
But there's no like, you know, that's like, that's like a drop in the bucket of all the things that
are listed as like things you could be interested in. And I have no interest in anything else,
other than eating out. One of the profiles I made, it just made it look like all I care about
is eating out, which I guess is fair. I do go out to eat a lot, but like, it just felt like that was
my only hobby in the world, because it was the only thing I listed as like something I go out to do
for fun. I don't even know what kind of human being I want to talk to. I don't know what I'm
looking for out of anybody, you know, like, because I don't need any friends. I have enough friends,
so I'm just looking for someone to date. But what the hell do I want to talk to them about?
What are the parameters? I have no idea. I went through Reddit, I went on all these different
dating subreddits where people are talking about dating, but all of their problems are totally
unrelatable to me, you know. One of my concerns is like, I mean, I'm like an internet personality
guy, you know, like, I don't know how to describe myself without talking about the fact that like,
what I do is I make videos all the time. Like, that's who I am. I don't think I have a personality.
I think I'm like, I think, I think I've reached a point in my life where I just am a thing that
appears in videos. You know, like, there's no life outside of that. There's no additional me,
you know, what I do for decompression time is make a fucking podcast. When I'm not making a podcast,
I'm making a podcast. I, there's nothing left of me. And there's no, there's no dating site for
girls who are into guys who make podcasts all the fucking time. You know, that's like a,
I don't, I don't know how to, I don't know how to be interesting or to find interest in anyone.
Um, there's certainly, I don't know any, like, uh, like, hot single girls who are into podcasting,
you know, like, seeking companionship and someone to do podcasts with, like, that's the kind of ad
that would grab my eye. Oh God, I found some hilarious dating sites. The funniest one I saw
is called Awake Dating. And it's literally for people who are like, awake to the truth. It was
like, basically woke. They could, they should have called it woke dating or stay woke dating,
because that's literally what it was about. It was, it was hilarious to realize that's a place.
Um, but then I thought, I wonder if that's, I wonder if I need a, if I need a black pilled partner.
Uh, stay woke dating. Oh God. Yeah, I don't know, I don't know who, I don't even know
who to talk to for advice about my particular problems, because who else in the world's dating
issue is I have no personality outside of the fact that I make podcasts and vlogs and that's my life.
Or, or just like looking for someone to, you know, to understand where I'm coming from when I dump
dialogue on them for 20 hours a day. I don't know.
Uh, all right. Well, continuing where I left off after about just shy of two days
of trying my hand at the misery that that is online dating where everything's weird
and nothing makes sense. And, and as a guy, you really, you, you really are fighting a losing
battle because, and I know this to be true, not just from women saying it, but from the way I
see other guys using dating apps, that women are just constantly, constantly getting likes and
messages from every guy on the planet. I mean, basically the way guys use a site like Tinder
is just hit like on absolutely everybody. And therefore with girls, they basically can just
take their time and sift through all the guys who've hit like on them and respond to which ones that,
you know, they think are attractive or, or interesting, read a bunch of articles, sort of
corroborating this as well. But yeah, that's sort of the phenomenon of, of internet dating.
So for me, it's just a matter of like every once in a while happening to stumble upon the one out
of 30 profiles that I actually think is pretty interesting. I'll be like, huh, this girl's
actually kind of cute, and she's got a decently written profile. That's cool. And then I hit like,
and then chances are that is the end of my interaction forever, you know, that they're
not going to hit like on my picture, especially because I have no good pictures of myself. There
are really none that exist. Certainly no current ones that are good. You know, I tried taking some
selfies of myself, but I don't know, I think I personally think I look like a psycho killer
in every picture I take of myself. So I'm sure others feel similarly. And, and yeah, I just feel
like there's no odds of getting that swipe back, you know, or getting that response to a message
somewhere. But I do think it's fascinating, especially Tinder. Tinder is basically a video
game, because it's just it's this it's the most simplified version version of finding people
interesting or attractive, right? It's like, you just see a picture. And so immediately you decide
based on the first thing you see, like, is this person even, you know, in my wheelhouse of what
I'm attracted to. So first, you just make that decision right out the gate. If you're unsure,
you look at a couple more pictures. And then they typically have like, a sentence to a paragraph
describing themselves, often not even sometimes they have no information. But at most they have a
sentence to a paragraph and you kind of look at it. And you decide, is this person two into dogs
or not? Because about 50% of everyone is just way into dogs, who's on these sites. And I hate
dogs. So I decided whether or not they're two into dogs, and then choose whether to hit like or
dislike on their profile. It's a little more complex than that. But, but I feel like it only
is for me, I feel like most people don't even make it as far as I do in that decision making
process. And then like, that's it, you just keep swiping, and then do that forever and then see
no results. And yeah, it's just a video game. It's like, it's like finding out both what your
tastes are exactly and how many people in your area fit them, and then doing nothing with the
information. That's basically the game that you're playing. So it's a huge waste of time. I spent
like hours swiping in different directions on Tinder. It was a bottomless fucking pit. Never
fucking hit the end. I'm pretty sure there's supposed to be a limit to how many likes you have
in a day, never hit it. It started cycling me back through people I'd already swiped on,
you know, after a few hours. And I was just like, Oh, God, this is a this is a fucking hell.
You know, looking on the online websites. It's just so weird for me to imagine myself talking to
most people. Like, the kind of people who I've spoken to in my life, there's there's very much
a type of person identifiable by sight, who I think of as like, my people, you know, like,
this is the kind of person who I see them. And I think that's the kind of person I'm used to talking
to, you know, and sometimes someone doesn't quite look like the kind of person I expect myself to
talk to. But I read their description. And I think, Okay, they seem in the wheelhouse of people
I've spoken to before, you know, or, or I think I could find an approach to talk to this person.
But it's, you know, it's weird to think that there's such a huge dichotomy between a kind of person
I'm used to talking to, which is basically nerds, you know, nerdy girls tend to look a certain way,
even if they're not even to say about like, whether they're attractive or not, just like,
I don't know, I feel like there's a certain way that people who like go to anime cons or,
or watch YouTube videos look, it's just this like, and everyone else just looks like a normie to me,
you know, and when I see the normie girls, I'm like, I can't imagine having a conversation with
someone like this. Maybe it's just a weird vein kind of like metric I'm using, but I don't know,
it feels strange. But anyways, in the midst of all this, I thought it would be interesting to talk
about, to talk about the kind of flirting that happens just from being an internet personality,
because I feel like some people who are listening to this must be thinking,
surely you have a reach of like hundreds of thousands of people who watch your videos,
many of whom are fans of you, surely some of those people are interested in you romantically. And
yeah, let me touch on that subject, because it can be interesting.
So I'd say pretty much everybody I know, who's a content creator, creator, or has been for a
long enough time, has done some kind of flirting with fans of their work or people who watch their
stuff and you know, and are interested in them romantically or sexually. I'd say everybody
is at least flirted with someone, you know, whether or not they've actually gotten into a
relationship before. And about, I mean, half of the PCP has been in relationships with people we
met through our work, you know, whether they were fans or, or just, you know, found out about us
through the work, particularly. And if you followed me for long enough, you know, that was what my
first and last relationship was like, was I was dating a girl for six months on the basis that
she was a big fan of my work. And she was in the pub crawl chat. And just like I was literally
complaining about how I don't have a I was 23 and it never had a girlfriend. And she was like,
I'll be your girlfriend. And I was like, Oh, really? But you know, here's why it's here's why
it can be weird. And I don't I don't get flirted with a lot. Not a lot of girls come out and say
anything, you know, I don't know if it's just because they think that like, because I know
there's girls who are interested. And I hear about it sometimes something like, like, Sider has told
me many times over the years that there's like girls who talk to him about how they like me,
but they never talk to me about how they like me. And I don't know if it's just because I'm, you
know, somewhat internet famous, maybe I'm hard to approach, you know, or you're just scared,
you think it won't work. But um, but yeah, I rarely rarely get approached. But even when I do,
it's super weird because I feel like, and this is what I realized this because of Tinder, because
I actually think that aside from the fact that you never get anyone responding to you on Tinder,
as a guy, I think it has the perfect information that I need to know before I'll talk to somebody,
which is what do you look like? How old are you? And where are you? Those are the those are three
pieces of information I consider to be crucial before I'm going to even consider, like, you know,
approaching you on a romantic level. Because, like, you know, if if we're trying to hook up if we're
trying to, you know, test the waters of dating or whatever, then like, it's kind of important that
we're attracted to one another, you know, and like, you already know what I look like. If someone's
messaging me, they know what I look like, I've got a thousand videos out there, but I have no
idea what you look like. And it takes a while, it takes a while of talking to somebody who's like
your fan, who's someone who knows you from online, you know, who you're trying to like kind of be
polite to because there's someone who likes your work. It takes a while to get to the point where
you're like, Hey, can I see what you look like? You know, and that's a it's a it's it's also very
weird. And it feels terrible to reach that point in the conversation to get pictures of somebody,
and then to see, Oh, I'm not attracted to this person, and then to try to get your way back out
of the conversation. Like, you know, it sounds it might sound shallow or something, but I'm sure
you all understand what that would be like, you know, to reach to reach that point, and then have
to kind of backpedal, especially to someone who you don't want to hurt their feelings, because
they like your stuff, you know. So yeah, that's the first problem is that people don't tend to just
upfront have pictures of themselves. I mean, and I can guarantee it would feel weird to send someone
pictures of yourself randomly, someone you, you know, you're a fan of and you don't know and you
just send them pictures of yourself might seem a little presumptuous, but I promise you, it would
be a huge help. If someone did that. And then also age, where I've had times where people like flirt
in my comments and stuff, you know, they'll say things like, Oh, digi, you're so sexy or something.
And I'm like, if you're like a 17 year old, then I'm not going to like hit you up, you know, like,
I've had people who seem to be like flirting in the comments that I'm like, I don't want to approach
this. If it turns out that this person's underage, you know, I mean, I probably won't even date somebody
under 21. But if you're under 18, then obviously not, you know. So like, that's the second thing
that makes it weird. And then location, because the last relationship I was in, the girl lived
in Montana at the time, you know, anytime we actually wanted to see each other, that was a $400
round trip playing ticket. So, you know, at the time I was inexperienced and didn't mind. But in
retrospect, I was like, I don't want, I don't want to be in a relationship where just actually
spending time together costs an enormous sum of money, you know, like it feels like the relationship
is tied to spending a shit ton of money just to hang out. And that's why, and then also like,
you end up like way overcompensating for the fact that you don't see each other that often in person
by constantly seeing each other online. And that's excessive, you know, I don't want relationships
where I end up in Skype conversations all day, which is what happened last time, you know. So
like, that's why, even though it seems like, you know, you'd think, well, I have a huge audience,
some of those people must be interested. But like, it's just that I don't know anything about anybody,
you know, I don't know anything about the people who, who post like one little flirtatious line,
you know, maybe hoping I'll follow up on it. But it's like, I have, you have way more information
about me than I do about you. You just constantly hear me at my most interesting, at my, at my best,
you know, doing podcasts, talking about myself, learning everything about my life and what I'm
up to and what my interests are. You don't need any icebreaker for me. But I know absolutely nothing
other than the vague sense that maybe you're not joking about being interested, you know, which
even then I have no idea when people are joking. And I get lots of attention from, from men as well,
you know, like I've had plenty of gay guys who talk about how hot I am. So I don't want to pursue
you only to find out that you're not even a woman or, or anything, you know, there's just,
there's a thousand way a troll, you could just be a troll, you know, as a, as someone who's known on
the internet, plenty of people want to troll me. It was funny too, I like, there's, there was stuff
like a, like an anime dating site. And I was like, it would be tempting to go on here because I think
it's funny that it's like a site that matches you based on your taste in anime. But I was like,
everyone on here would, would know who I am or they, or they could easily find out, you know,
people who, who know me from my videos and think of me as like a mimetic character might be on here,
you know, I might try to troll me or something and it's just a huge waste of time. So yeah, that's
why it's really weird to try and pursue these kinds of relationships. And I'm not saying,
you know, don't, I'm saying, I mean, if you want to send me messages where you actually say,
hey, I'm being completely legitimate, here's three pictures of me at my age and location,
that would be greatly appreciated. And it would be fucking hilarious if it worked, because then
it would prove that the only game I have is complaining about how I don't have any,
how I don't have a girlfriend online. That would mean that that's the only way I know how to get
relationships, which would be sad and hilarious. But I don't know, I'd be okay with it because
it's not working out any other way. Yeah. So I was giving some thought to why exactly I'm so
frustrated with all this, like with this whole online dating thing, because I mean, two days ago,
I felt totally fine about whatever I was doing. I think I did. I don't remember. But,
but once I started this, I started feeling just totally down and depressed and upset.
And I think it's just a matter of like putting effort into something that has absolutely no
tangible or evident benefit, and in which I feel completely out of my depth, which is not something
I'm used to. I'm used to things that I can do and immediately understand the benefits, right? Like
a vlog. I come up with an idea for a vlog. I record it instantly, post it online instantly, get, you
know, the reaction I want instantly. I'm used to lots of that. Like I'm, I have a very confident
approach to everything I do in my life. I know exactly what I'm going to get out of it, and how
much work it'll take to reach the finish line, you know, and, and there's always that exact like
feeling of I'm doing something I know what to do, know how to do, and, and I can do it and know
everything about it and feel the payoff. But with this, it's just like throwing,
throwing stones at a barn blindfolded and trying to hit the blind side of a barn,
uh, literally blind. I don't know how you, I don't know exactly what the blind side of a barn is.
Um, yeah, and I just don't know what I'm doing. So it's like, it's like, I have no idea if I'm
even going in the right direction with anything I'm posting. Like am I just totally off base with
the pictures I'm choosing or the descriptions I'm writing, or by even attempting this? Am I on the
completely wrong websites? You know, I've, I've been doing tons of research. Like my approach to
something like this is find every Reddit board with any information about this,
find every article about this, figure out exactly what I'm doing, and I've come to
basically no conclusions. Um, so that's what's so frustrating about it. And I was thinking about how
there would be ways to make it, like if it wasn't for the fact that all these websites and stuff
ask questions or, or base their stuff on parameters that like don't mean a lot to me,
that's kind of part of the issue. Like for instance,
these sites will always have something like, you know, what are some of your favorite books
and movies and TV shows and stuff. And like to me, that's not a very helpful question because at
best we're going to have like one or two things we both like, who boy, you know, like maybe it'll
give me something to talk about like, oh, you like Rick and Morty, I like Rick and Morty, that's cool.
But like, it doesn't really cut to the heart of the matter, which is how much do you care about
TV and movies and books, you know, like you can have a favorite book that you read five years ago,
and you don't really think about it or talk about it, you just list it when the topic of
favorite books comes up. What it should really say is like, how often do you read? How much do you
like books, you know, how much does your favorite media mean to you? Then we have an idea of where
this is going, you know, like, if I bring up that book, are you going to be like, oh my god,
someone to talk about this book with, you know, like when I when I list out this stuff, I always go
really basic because you would think, well, Digi's got a million favorites, surely he'll list all of
them, but to me, it's like, no one cares, that's the way I see it, like who would possibly care
that I like these 500 different fucking, you know, anime shows, most people never heard of any of them,
you know, so I usually just post like, I like a lot of anime, you know, like basically all anime,
I think it's what I listed on one profile, like, you know, it's, it's a huge difference between
I like this show and I care about this show, and I think a lot of the answers on these websites
could be more like that, you know, like they say like, do you like food? It's like, yeah,
everybody likes food, everybody likes going out to eat, how often do you go out to eat? How much
money do you spend when you go out to eat? These are questions I want to know, you know, because
like me and my friends go out to eat all the time, I almost as often as I can, I take somebody out
with me, but most of my friends are cheap, you know, most of my friends don't spend as much on
food as I do, so you know, that determines where we're going and what we're doing, you know, if I,
if you like to eat out every single day, probably I'm not gonna always pay for every meal we have
together, but if we eat out all the time, then that would be super cool, it'd be interesting,
like how much, not just how much money do you make, but how much do you spend on food?
Is there anybody who eats out as often as I do? Another question, what's your sleep schedule?
Now, I know that for most people, the answer will probably be the same,
but for someone like me, I'm currently recording this at three o'clock in the morning and I
like just woke up like an hour ago after a series of weird, and all I've been doing for the last
two days other than dating sites is like sleeping and jacking off intermittently, it's just been
like this nonstop back and forth, wake up, up for like an hour, jack off, fall back to sleep,
it's just been like constant ever since, ever since a few days ago, so before even this whole,
this whole thing started, it's just been the last few days for me.
So, so how, when are you awake? How often are you awake? What times are you most active?
Do you prefer to go out and hang out at noon, or do you prefer to hang out at night, or do you
prefer to hang out at three in the morning? Do you actually find things to do at three in the morning,
you know? These are all the kind of questions I want the answers to in a dating profile.
How about, how about how many times per day do you leave the house, or per week, per month,
to go do a thing? Like, do you like to go out with other people, or by yourself? Because I like
to go out every day with other people if I can, you know, me and Victor, anytime Victor's home,
we're either going to go to lunch, or we're going to go check out, like, the bookstore,
the comic store, just like, I want to get out of the house, and I don't like going out alone,
you know, so I prefer to snatch up Ben or DeVue and be like, hey, I'm going to this place,
you want to come, you know, even if it's just like a short drive, who wants to come with me?
You know, are you into that person on dating profile? How often do you leave the house with
other people? How often do you go to just, you know, frivolously spend money on food to do something
that's not sit at home, you know? Or do you have much more exciting things you go out and do
that are unbeknownst to me, that I don't even realize exist, you know? I've had a,
there's like, two people, well, only one who I actually messaged, but there were two people on
OkCupid who I had like a decent match percentage with, and one of them said, like, it said, like,
what's your typical Friday night? And she said, going to a place where I can, like, a place with
good beer and a little personality where they play good music at a volume where you can have a
conversation over it. And I was like, where the hell did she find a place like this in Virginia
Beach? I even messaged, I messaged her and said, like, hi there, where did you find a place that
has all these characteristics in Virginia Beach? Haven't gotten a response yet, but I'm legitimately
curious. I'd love to go somewhere that has beers and decent music, you know, her musical tastes
seem more similar to mine than, you know, what's typical, which is why I don't go to bars. I love
the concept of a bar, go to a place, have them serve you awesome, interesting alcoholic beverages and
hang out with other people and listen to music, sounds great, except every bar just blasts shitty
music at the highest possible volume. And you can't talk to anybody. And, and I don't want to hear
that music. Would love to know these places these people are finding that I don't know about.
One girl had a bunch of pictures of her doing rock climbing on like legit cliffs. I was like,
where the fuck are you finding these cliffs in Virginia Beach? It's a flat plane. Are you driving
out to the mountains to do this? Real curiosity. So yeah, maybe everybody else knows a much more
fun and exciting version of this town than I do. That's, that's what I'm always suspecting, you know.
I mean, Ben St moved in and he thinks this place is hell. He was like, this, there's nothing to do
here. This place is just a wasteland. It's a hellhole. And I kept assuring him like, I know
there's stuff to do here, because other people who live here do stuff. Most people who live in
Virginia Beach seem to be happy here. Just the stuff that they do is not stuff I want to do.
Most people go to the beach. I don't like the beach. Most people go to clubs and bars don't
like clubs and bars. You know, there's a million clubs and bars in this town. There's definitely
things to do. I'm just not sure, you know, what they are where and a lot of them are expensive
things to do. You know, there's lots of like little fun. You could go canoeing out on the river.
You could go paddle boarding or something. You can go fishing. There's a lot of water here. There's
a lot of water based activities. There's hiking areas. There's ultimate frisbee golf and shit.
But all that's like, you know, you have to spend money to do on the end of that shit.
Indoor trampoline gyms and indoor rock climbing, bowling everywhere, laser tag, all things you
have to pay money for. So probably not something that I think Ben's more looking for like hipster
coffee shop I can sit down at, you know, or something. But I don't know. It's not a lot.
Not a lot that is of interest to me or seemingly him around here. So whatever everybody else is
doing, I'd love to know it. Love to know where they're going and why they find it appealing.
But personally, I can't say I understand it myself.
And that really makes me think, you know, I've been talking a lot about moving all the PCP here
to Virginia Beach. And the only real reason for it to be Virginia Beach over any where anybody
else lives is that I have the most, I have personally have the most stability in my income
and in housing situation. And I, you know, I've already got Ben and DeVue living here for like
really low rent compared to what it would be if we were trying to, you know, get our own place.
You know, and of course that rent is also split between my, both of my brothers and
Shade's girlfriend. So like, you know, it makes sense because we have a good housing situation
with good rent. And, you know, DeVue works for me anyways. So he's basically best wherever I am.
And, and like no one else, like we don't want to move out to where Jesse is because he lives in
the middle of bumfuck nowhere in a town even smaller than ours. You know, Nate lives in Ohio,
but he's not really from there. So even he's not really connected there. Because he's originally
from Michigan, which both Ben and Nate are both from not Michigan, I meant Massachusetts. Ben
and Nate are from like outside Boston. And Nate, I mean, Ben kind of misses where he was from.
But I do feel like we should eventually just move this whole operation. Like,
we, we moved into this house because my parents wanted to keep the house, you know, they wanted to,
they wanted to give us our own place while simultaneously not having to give up their
house. That was sort of the whole dream with getting the, with the whole setup we have right
now is don't have to sell the house that we've been living in for seven years and done all this
work on and, you know, don't have to uproot everybody and move them around. You know,
Shade's got his girlfriend who wants to stay around. Victor's got his girlfriend who wants to
stay around. They're not trying to like move out and get into all this other shit. But eventually,
Victor's going to probably move in with, with Hope. I don't know what Shade and Amber will do,
but like, I don't know if moving like, I want everyone in one place, but this doesn't have to
be the place because it really doesn't seem like Virginia Beach has anything to offer us.
And that's becoming more and more clear to me over time. We're like, for instance,
you know, even though my lifestyle has me indoors like all the time and not really talking to
anybody, I feel like there must be in other cities, people I could actually hang out with,
communities I could be a part of, you know, like people I could see in real life
or places I could go and do things, you know, if we lived in New York City or something,
which I don't know if I'd want to live in New York City because it's, you know,
grossly overpopulated and there's just too many, I don't want to live like surrounded on all sides
by people and things and sounds and shit, you know, there's anything I've learned from Casey
Neistat vlogs is that the sound pollution is terrible. You're constantly, there's always some
weird shit going on. Probably wouldn't be a great recording environment unless I like
created a whole fucking studio. But nonetheless, like, this maybe is not the place to keep this
going. It's a great place for getting everybody in one spot, but only for us to work together.
There's nothing outside of this group, you know, which I kind of always had it in my head that
that was okay, that like, well, we're all going to be working together. So we should all be,
you know, like, who else do we possibly need to talk to other than one another. But then it's
like, yeah, but what about the all the time you're not working, you know, that's the time I've kind
of left unaccounted for. And for a really long time, I had this like romantic idea in my head
of exploring everywhere in Virginia Beach, like, because I didn't, because I kind of saw myself
as like a spokesperson for the town, like I live here, it's important to me that I am a part of
this place, I grew up here, you know, I'm going to be the guy who represents the city or something,
or be the most interesting thing to come out of this town. And so I should explore it and find
out all that's here. And now I feel like I have and there's nothing here, you know, I feel like
I've done the exploring. I'm sure there's some stuff I haven't seen yet that's interesting, but like,
on a day to day basis, there's nothing here I want to be doing, you know, I've been to all the cool
restaurants, that's over, you know, I've been to all the the comic stores have been to all the game
shops and the record stores and the bookstores and all the things that interest me. And there's
there's not a whole lot left, I don't want to hang out down at the beach strip, where it's a
25 minute drive to everything being overpriced. And there's not as much down there as I first
thought. Like when I I used to think that like there's all this stuff down at the beach, and I
just haven't really gone down there. But then like I have driven around there, not really anything,
but bars and clubs. So, you know, maybe this town just isn't meant for the the procrastinators.
Maybe we're going to end up setting up base somewhere else. And I mean, like, we don't really
know where yet. So, you know, if I don't I don't want anybody to put down on a on a lease here
or something, and then get trapped in a house for a year, and then we're all kind of stuck.
But at the same time, I don't want us to just pack up and go to some other town without thinking
about it, you know. But especially if it's going to be even more expensive, which Virginia Beach
is not a cheap place to live. But if we're trying to move somewhere even cooler, then it just means
the rent's going to be even higher, you know. So, so I don't know where we could go that we could
all live in one place, and it would still be inexpensive, and also cool. But maybe we'll find
out. I certainly would like to. Alrighty, well, I think I'll just keep this one short, kind of stuck
to one topic, or at least one train of thought through the whole thing. So, you know, might as
well keep it as it is. It's a bit late anyways, a few days late. Maybe the next one will
not be a whole week before it comes out. Who knows? Who knows how much decompression I'll
have to do between now and then. I hope you enjoy the new song choice. I know it's a real
crowd pleaser, so you'll probably all be into it. And enjoy it, and have a nice day.