Let me tell you a little story about an audience member.
The worst kind of audience member, the one that every creator fears the most.
If you're a creative, this story will be an absolute nightmare, a torturous tale from
your worst, your scariest dreams.
It's about a friend that I used to have back in high school.
We'll call him D for the sake of this story.
Now this guy, he had a really interesting taste in art, because most of what he liked
was great stuff, and yet, I could tell he had no fucking idea what was great about it,
and would completely misinterpret the intentions or just consume things in such a way that
would make someone like me very frustrated.
You know, I guess it's fair if you're enjoying yourself than whatever, but like, for some
of us, especially creative people, this is an absolute nightmare.
This guy, his favorite video game series was Metal Gear Solid.
He would skip the cutscenes.
The first time he played through Metal Gear Solid 4, the first time he played through
it, he skipped all the cutscenes.
Now Metal Gear Solid is a game that's mostly known for its story, for its cutscenes.
I mean, the gameplay is important as well, but the story is like what people really come
to it for, and the thing about it is that it's not like he was one of these guys who
says, I don't care about the story.
He would insist that he did know the story.
He would insist that he could follow the story.
He would insist that he knew everything about Metal Gear, and that he was a big fan of the
game series.
But if you ever, you know, if you asked him, like, oh, you know, have you really watched
the cutscenes in the other games, he'd say yes, but then if you were to ask him specific
details, he'd always be off, but he'd never admit he was off, he'd just be like, you'd
correct him, and he'd be like, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, that's how it was, you know.
And he seemed to have no self-awareness about this at all.
He was an absolute nightmare.
You know, he was a huge fan of Ghost in the Shell, and just based on, I mean, I know the
guy.
I know there's no way he understands half of what's good about Ghost in the Shell.
Like, he just likes it because of the aesthetic and because the major is hot, you know, and
he just likes that sort of military action kind of story.
But I'm almost certain he doesn't really get any of the deeper philosophical implications
of the show.
You can enjoy whatever you like, but this is also the kind of guy who would complain
about stories where his complaints are obviously based on misconceptions because he wasn't
paying attention.
But he would never, like, he would say something like, you know, oh, that movie was really
stupid, you know, and you'd be like, why, and you'd be like, oh, it's just dumb.
But you could tell, like, he would insist that it was a bad movie, even though if you
ever watch a movie with him, he never pays attention.
He sits there on his fucking PSP through most movies, he talks through movies, you know,
he doesn't pay any attention to movies.
But then he'll go and talk about them as though he's seen them and insist that he was paying
attention.
This guy would just insist that he followed what was going on, you know, at one point
I'd loaned him my Boogie Pop novels, and he read them, and he said he liked them, and
I told him, like, well, you know, with Boogie Pop and others, the first book, you kind of
have to read it more than once to really get the full picture, you know, because I asked
him, like, did you understand all of it?
Because you kind of have to read it again before you're going to totally understand
what's happening.
He was like, no, no, no, I understood it all, you know, I got it.
And I was just like, how do you even fucking know that if you haven't read it the second
time?
Because it's not until you read it again that you realize what you don't know.
I loaned him Boogie Pop at Phantom, the TV series, and he said that he really enjoyed
it, but he skipped one episode, and I was like, why?
And he said, I just didn't want to watch that one.
And the one he indicated when he pointed at the box was like one of the most important
episodes in terms of understanding the fucking story of Boogie Pop Phantom.
And I was just like, how can you be this way?
Now the reason I bring this up is that that guy, D, will never speak to any of the people
who created any of those things.
You know, he'll never talk to Hideo Kojima, he'll never speak to Kohei Kodono, he'll
never speak to Masamune Shiro.
You know, he's never going to talk to the creators of those things and bewilder them
with the fact that he paid so little attention.
You know, he'll never be able to criticize the shows based on false information that
is the result of his not paying attention to what he was watching.
I on the other hand, will frequently interact with everyone who watches my videos.
And I can tell when some people did not pay any fucking attention.
And then they complain on the basis of misunderstood information.
Now it's weird for me, I think it's a little weird, it comes off a little weird even to
me when I talk about my videos as art.
Because my videos feel so direct, like to people who get them, you know, you watch it
and I'm just kind of explaining a point, right?
Like how could that be, how could there be a boogie and pop skill for that?
Cause I always make that comparison that like, you know, on some level you come to the audience
and on some level the audience comes to you, right?
And it's like if the whole audience doesn't understand, it means that I didn't dumb down
the point enough.
And to a lot of my viewers, it seems like how could it be more dumbed down, you know?
But I do write with a stylistic flourish.
I like my videos to make a point in a fun and succinct way.
I like writing in this sort of cheeky, kind of pseudo collegiate intellectual way, but
not in a way that's like using big words and fancy language so much as, I like when I get
to the point in a kind of a, like an aha moment or like a gotcha almost.
So referring to my latest video, the hiding sex appeal of anime in plain sight, the first
half of the video is me like deconstructing the idea that there's a fan service in, or
presenting the idea rather, I don't know why I said deconstructing, presenting the idea
that there's fan service in Flying Witch and Amanchu, you know?
And I'm talking about how no one's really criticized it and that's interesting.
Now if you're an inattentive viewer and you don't, you haven't made it to the end of the
episode but you're already, you already think you know what the video is about, then you
start making assumptions that I'm criticizing these shows for having fan service.
But that never happens.
The whole point of it is a build up.
It's alluring you into this idea but then the point of the video is at the end of the
video.
The point of the video is when I have this sort of aha reveal that like the reason this
is interesting is because of what it says about how people think of fan service, you
know, how this is not really more mature than nudity and how that's a conversation that
I think would be interesting to have.
But if you're not paying attention to the fucking video or you don't make it to the
end or you don't consider the whole point of it all at once, then you won't get it.
And I could write the video differently.
I could write it with clarifications up the fucking ass.
I could make the whole video by the way, I'm not saying fan service is bad even though
I say that in the video, you know, but I say it in a way where I say, you know, if you
ask me to step up to bat for a show that's blatant about its fan service, I'll show up
to the plate with a road sign like Shizuo.
That sentence will go right over a lot of people's heads.
What the fuck does that mean?
Some people don't know what it means to step up to bat.
Some people don't know, I just don't get it at all.
You know, I could have dumbed it down.
I could have said every, you know, stopped every sentence and made my point very clear.
But that's not how I want to write.
I like videos that have this kind of cheeky aha nature to them.
You know, my writing style is heavily influenced by ghost lightning who wrote like that.
Like a lot of his posts were like that, you know, he loved that video and I'm not surprised
because it's the kind of thing he would have written about in the same way he would have
written about it.
It's a very ghost lightning video and granted he would have probably had less defensiveness
over fan service even than I would have or less willingness to be defensive of shows
like Seiko and No Quasar.
But yeah, like, and only because he has less reason to, he's not as interested as I am
in those shows.
But you know, that's the style I like writing in.
But then the problem is that I also like reading comments and so I kind of have damned myself
because I'm going to have to read the comments of the people who don't pay attention, you
know, and the same thing happened with the Kill La Kill video and I made a whole clarification
video after that just because it was driving me fucking crazy.
And I'm tempted to do it with the Flying Witch video.
I'm tempted to make a clarification thing, but then I have to take a step back and be
like, hold on, you know, the reason you didn't write this dumbed down is because it's not
about the audience.
It's about what I wanted the video to be, you know, it's not about the mass appeal.
That's why I'm a boogie pop guy.
You know, that's why I say that.
Even though people might look at my videos and think, well, is this really like an artistic
statement?
Like what's so, you're just like describing what's in a show.
Yeah, but you know, even then there's a level of abstraction there of, you know, writing
with the expectation that the audience will pay full attention and watch the whole video
before they come to any conclusions.
And even some people who I can tell are fans of me and, you know, and wanted to understand
the point didn't quite get it.
And I had, I had a lot of conversations like on Twitter and other places with people who
just they seem to have gotten out of it.
Like what they like, like, like at some point in the video, they thought, well, now I get
the point and then, you know, didn't listen to the whole thing.
Like my videos have to be consumed as a whole entity.
There is no like, there's nothing you can break off of it and it'll still make sense
as a whole.
You know, it's why the Astroscore sucks is so misunderstood by people who don't watch
the whole thing.
You know, people who watch like little bits and pieces of it and like, he's just trashing
some show.
It's like, yeah, there's always a greater point to why I built up to this, to this ending.
You know, the video is a complete piece of work.
It's not just a string of random ideas.
I get why people think that way because so much of what's out there, so many videos are
just formulaic, you know, strings of fucking comments on things that are all taken at face
value, that don't have a greater point they're getting to in the end, you know, and I, if
I just had written the video in such a way, like if I just reversed it, you know, if I
reversed the point, made it very explicit in the beginning, what my point is about to
be and then explained the point, then more people would have understood where I was coming
from.
But it doesn't have that same flavor to it of the fun aha moment that comes at the end
of this build up, you know, it's, it's more dramatic the way I write it because I want
it, I want it to feel cool, you know, I don't want to just fucking describe something.
I don't want a drab analysis of something.
You know, there's a reason I would never write in the style of like Matthew Matosis
and not to say that I don't like his style, it's fun to watch his videos, but they're
very much a cut and dry start from the beginning, work your way through, describe every single
thing, you know, make the point very abundantly clear from the beginning and I would never
be able to write in that style and I don't like it as much, you know, I really prefer
like a Mr. B tongue video where he deliberately strings you along and keeps like hinting at
you that maybe you're going to get to see the point, but you really got to make it through
all this other stuff, you know, and then when he finally brings it all back, it's tight
and impactful, you know, and it's a lot harder to like rewatch a Matthew Matosis video than
it is to rewatch a Mr. B tongue video or one of my videos I'd like to think, you know,
I write them in a way that's meant to be re-consumable, that they're meant to stand
alone as articles that are interesting, that you reread multiple times and that are engaging
on their own, it's not just what I'm talking about that's interesting, it's the way I'm
talking about it that's interesting.
That's why those are the videos that, you know, that I mark on Patreon that I feel proud
enough of to try to make money off of it, because to me, that's more of an artistic
video, and that's why I love writing so much, but you know, if a lot of people are going
to misunderstand it and like at some point I have to decide, do I want to, you know,
just make another fucking video, re-clarifying the points just so that the discussion will
be better, or do I want to just like ignore the discussion like a normal artist would,
you know, because most artists are not dealing with this problem, most people don't have
to hear from D, they don't have to hear him talk about their work and be just bombarded
with the knowledge that they didn't pay attention, you know, and then get so bothered by it that
they feel the need to clarify again and explain their own art, most people don't have to explain
their own art, you know, and yet somehow I keep finding myself in that position and
it doesn't help that my art is basically explaining art, you know, so it's kind of
cyclical.
There's a reason I don't send my videos to the people who make the shows, you know,
because even though I feel like I get it, I don't, you know, it's just all opinions,
it's just, it's its own thing, it's not even relative to the artist's intention and I'm
sure there's a few artists I've talked about their work who would absolutely hate me if
they had to watch one of my videos, you know, but um, yeah, that's the sort of suffering
that I feel in the comments sometimes.
And so without further ado, just to clarify, that video was not criticizing fan service
nor was it criticizing the fan service in those shows except for the fact that clingy
clothes bother me personally.
It was a criticism of the way that people talk about fan service and how people don't
seem to appreciate that these shows are blatantly featuring the most attractive characters and
putting them in the most attractive outfits because that's appealing, you know, and how
it's funny to me that that's not criticized as immature in the way that showing tits would
be even though it's basically the same thing.
That's the point of the video.
For anybody who didn't get it, who might be listening to this now, um, I doubt that's
too many of you.
Oh God, alright.
This was actually a real decompression, uh, issue, so glad this show still exists.
Maybe this whole decompression chamber podcast is gonna stick around for longer than I, uh,
just thought because man, I've gotten to a point that I almost need it.
Today I had a moment early this morning that was so powerful in making me want to talk
about it on the decompression chamber that it's had me anxious all day.
It's Christmas Day as I'm recording this.
I, um, I had planned to spend Christmas with my parents, get drunk all night and spend
the night at their house.
I ended up going a day early and doing that the day before, um, so I was there Christmas
Eve night, woke up on Christmas, you know, hung out with them, um, felt weird all morning
for reasons I'll get into later, read this comment that really set me off and I really
wanted to decompress about it, um, but I ended up being there till 10 at night, finally drove
home, um, and I'm gonna talk about it.
I don't, it's hard to know where to start with this, but I'm gonna start by explaining
something, a concept I came up with a couple of months ago.
I don't remember if I've talked about this anywhere, but if I have, I'm sorry.
It's called the good person fallacy, fallacy, if you will.
I know I say it wrong, because you know there's all these, uh, argument fallacies that people
talk about.
There's one that, that I find comes up all the time, which is the fallacy that the opponent
in your argument is trying to present themselves, present themselves as a good person.
Because that's not something I try to do.
I don't believe myself to be a great person.
I'm not a bad person, but I don't believe myself to be a great person.
I don't believe very many people to be great people.
You know, to me, being a good person is, is b- like, okay.
You know, good and bad, like, most of us are 6 out of 10 people.
Let's put it that way.
You know?
If you're a good person, you gotta be a 7 or 8.
You gotta be putting a little effort in.
You know?
You gotta be greasing the fire of the good person, you know?
And bad people are, are, you know, doing something real wrong, basically.
Fundamentally, something's broken.
I don't think I'm a good person.
I think I'm like a 6 or 7 out of 10, you know, really depending on who you ask.
In terms of moral quality.
Maybe even a 5.
I actually might be a 5 out of 10.
Or maybe lower.
It really depends on who you ask.
Uh, you know, I think to be considered a, a good or great person, you have to be a
good person.
You have to be someone who's self-sacrificing and helpful and kind and, you know, having
the qualities of a good, a good individual.
I don't have a lot of that.
You know, I have it, maybe I have it more than a lot of people.
Um, I, I have a lot of empathy.
I understand other people pretty easily.
I feel a lot for other people.
I don't do a lot for other people.
I feel a lot more than I do, you know?
I feel really bad about all the hardships in the world.
I don't do a lot to help them.
I, I've, uh, often said I have a Ruroni Kenshin policy when it comes to helping people, which
is I help the people I can see.
The ones who are right in front of me.
The ones who I understand their situation and what needs to be done to help it.
You know, I don't give to charity.
I don't try to help out on a global scale or anything like that.
And there are people out there who do those things.
Those are great people.
You know, my dad is a much better person than me.
He does a lot for charity.
He does a lot for helping people.
You know, he gives a lot of both time and energy and money and love and care.
He gives all that.
I don't give that.
I'm not a great person like my dad, you know?
And when I get into an argument with someone, I'm not trying to prove that I'm great.
I'm not trying to prove that I'm morally righteous.
I'm just trying to prove what I think, you know?
I'm just trying to state how I feel on the matter and support my claims and make you
understand how I feel.
It's not about convincing you that I'm right or good.
It's just about convincing you that I understand my own position sort of.
So this also, you know, this sounds a lot like my usual moral, my objectivity versus
subjectivity arguments.
It's very similar.
I feel the same way about morals, you know?
And I've been described as a moral relativist by some people.
I don't know how much I agree with that though.
It's not that I think, I mean, yeah, there's no objective standard of morals because that's
fucking ridiculous, that mere idea.
But you can have a pretty clear consensus on what's good and bad, right?
My version is anything that brings you closer to life is good.
Anything that brings you closer to death is bad.
If what you're doing has a net gain for humanity, it's good.
If what you're doing is a net gain for humanity, that's negative, it's bad.
And you know, you can never predict what it's actually gonna be.
There's no way to actually like predict what effect, you know, what ripple effect your actions
will have.
But on a case-by-case basis, we can say like, you shoot a guy, that's bad.
You know, you do something that endangers people, that's bad.
You do something that helps people, that's good.
I think that's pretty clear.
I think that's pretty fucking cut and dry and nobody's gonna disagree with it, you know?
So yeah, I do have a standard of what I think is good or bad morally.
I just don't hold myself to that standard.
I don't go out of my way to paint myself as a good person, nor do I think of most people
as good people.
You know, like, it's not that I think of myself as worse than most.
I think there's probably a lot of people who think they're good, who I would disagree
with them on that.
Because the way I see it, every resource we use, you know, is a resource we're not giving
to someone else.
You know, someone who needs it, doesn't have it and we're using it and we don't need it.
That's a thing that is just, that's a part of Western society right there.
If we gave up our conveniences and used those to help the impoverished, we'd have a lot
fewer impoverished and we don't do it because, and for good reason, we wouldn't be happy
if we did it.
You know, we're not raised in such a way, we don't have such a mindset to make us people
who can do that.
There are people who can do that out there.
Those are great people, but you know, they're not great because they made this unbelievable
decision to be great.
They're great because they have the state of mind to be great.
They're people who, you know, were raised in a certain way and have a certain set of
beliefs that leads them to do great things.
But that's not me and that's not most people.
I wrote about this in my song, Seeth, you know, I'd be hard pressed to name two guys
that I like unqualified or any that I find to be good, as I say, said in those lyrics.
A lot of these thoughts, a lot of these kinds of thoughts are more present in my song lyrics
than they are in any of my writing or podcasting and stuff like that because I tend to get
out more of my anger and vitriol towards humanity out in my music.
But I have to talk about this and this boils down to really my sub versus dub video I did,
my video about my stance on dubs on multiple levels.
I almost responded to this when I talked in that last section where I was talking about
comments, but I forgot to get to this because I got a certain accusation a number of times
on that video of being very biased and unfair and ignorant about the dubbing industry.
And when I got those comments, all I could think was, well, yeah, this is not a review
of the dubbing industry.
This is my stance on dubs that I somehow still haven't made a video about.
I never said my stance on dubs was not ignorant.
I never said it was fair and balanced.
I never said I'd done research.
Never said I had any investment in the dub industry.
I don't give a fuck about dubs.
I don't even like dubs or respect dubs as I said at the beginning of the video, you
know, some there are some people who said they turned off right there and I'm like fair
enough, you know, I don't like or respect dubs didn't say I was going to be fair about
it.
So that's part of the criticism.
Now I also wanted to talk about this because there's a part in the video where I say that
I hate Vic Minyona both as an actor and as a person and I got a bunch of questions like
asking why why do you hate Vic Minyona?
And I real quickly realized I can't answer all of those and this is one of the difficulties
of doing videos is that I feel like I constantly have to re clarify and explain things.
Every little thing I say I have to then make another video about or make a thousand comments
explaining it and at this point I was like, I don't like a lot of the times it's something
I don't care that much about, you know, I just said it as a one off line in a video.
I don't want to have to go and explain.
I'm not that invested in my hatred of Vic Minyona.
I just think it's really funny because I think he's a douchebag and I hate his acting,
you know, which really should be enough of a reason to hate the guy because he sucks
at acting and I don't like him.
I've hated people for less.
So I was answering people on my Reddit board who asked, you know, I explained myself.
I said, well, he's a weird Christian fundamentalist who has said at a panel before that he doesn't
think that Edward Elric is actually an atheist even though in Japanese Edward Elric literally
says I'm an atheist.
They changed that line in the dub, possibly as a result of him not being comfortable with
it.
That to me is more than enough reason to hate the guy, you know, I don't know him.
I don't care about him.
Maybe he's a nice guy.
I don't fucking care.
Still hate him.
You know, it's not about whether he's a good person or even whether he's a better person
than me.
It's just about what pisses me off.
That pisses me off.
He refused to sign a picture of his character from Free like making out with another guy.
I was like some Yaoi fan art and he wouldn't sign it because, you know, it just made him
uncomfortable, whatever.
Fuck him.
Fuck that guy.
Fuck him for being uncomfortable about some gay shit, you know.
Fuck him for being weird, a weird 50 year old guy who dresses like a teenage heartthrob.
And there's there's a thousand rumors on the internet about misconduct he's had with like
underaged fans of his.
I don't know how true any of it is.
I've been hearing these rumors for years, forever.
You know, every time someone brings up Vic Mignona, someone else brings up, oh, he might
have molested a bunch of fucking 14 year olds or something.
You know, you hear something enough times, you think it's probably true, maybe it's not
true at all, maybe it's just a bunch of bullshit that's out there on the internet.
I don't give a fuck, you know.
Don't like the guy.
I'm not out to lead a smear campaign against him.
You know, I'm not out to ruin his career, I've just made a decision about how I feel
about him.
And I think it's funny, so I keep saying it.
Now I got a comment in response to this, that pissed me off on a lot of different levels.
And it tends to be that the comments that pissed me off the most are the ones where there's
some element of it that I agree with, but it's packaged in a way that I vehemently disagree
with.
They never have those people who say like, fuck you, I hate you, your content is awful,
and then they rant about all these different reasons they don't like you and all of it's
a bunch of bullshit.
But then there's that one nugget in there that you're like, if you had just said that
and you'd said it politely, we could have had a conversation about this, you know, but
they don't.
So this guy gets mad at me because he says, you know, while I don't know Vic Minyona,
I have, you know, talked to him through emails and stuff, and he seems like an upstanding
guy in a cool chill guy or whatever, and I think all those rumors about him doing all
that misconduct is a bunch of horseshit and like a smear campaign against him.
And that part, he was obviously mad at me because I was talking shit about somebody
without having a lot of information about him, you know, without knowing the guy.
And he might be an okay guy, and maybe it's fucked up for me to sling mud at people I
don't know.
That's a fair enough argument, you know, I would have been willing to have a conversation
about that.
But it was packaged in between, oh, and you're such a good person, you think you're any morally
superior to him, you fucking, and then he goes on about like these problems he has with
me and how he thought I was, I was intellectual enough to be above all this kind of stuff,
but you know.
So obviously, that part of the argument just pissed me off, so I told him to fuck off.
Um, I said fuck off, he said I was attacking, I said I'm not attacking Vic Minyona, okay,
I'm just being a dick over here on my subreddit, you know, explaining myself, I've made a statement
that I don't like the guy, I've explained why I don't like the guy, this is not an attack,
I'm not waging an internet war against fucking Vic Minyona, you know, there's a reason I
didn't make a video about this, I don't want to go around spreading rumors about insinuations,
it's just what I've heard, and I have no reason to doubt it, I don't have any reason
to believe this guy just because he talked to him in a couple emails that he suddenly
knows what Vic fucking Minyona's like, you know, and the candor of the comment sort of
clued me in that this guy is probably also a Christian guy who probably likes Vic for
those reasons because he said that he thinks the reason that Vic gets these accusations
is from people who don't like that he's Christian and have a problem with his beliefs, then
the things he accuses me of are weirdly things that a Christian would have a problem with,
so I thought okay, this guy's probably defending Vic because he's sick of seeing Christians
get beat up on for being Christians, you know, and I get that, that's also fair, I don't
like Christians, don't like their belief system, don't like the fundamentalist mindset,
you know, I think it's a fucking willful ignorance to know scientifically why something
is untrue and to go on believing it anyways, it's like well, you know, it's one thing
if you just don't know any better, but it's a whole other thing if you've been shown
the evidence and you still keep going on believing what you want to believe just because, especially
if it affects other people, you know, when you have religious people who, you know, are
like uncomfortable with or have a problem with gay people because it goes against their
doctrine, even though their doctrine is not couched in any kind of scientific reality,
then that's just being a fucking willfully ignorant shitbag, you know, not saying that
everyone who's Christian is that, but a whole lot of them are and I don't see any reason
for the religion to exist, I don't see how it helps anybody for it to be around, so yeah,
to me, can't say I have a whole lot of respect for it, sorry if that offends you, but this
brings me to the next interesting thing about this comment and about being an internet content
creator or any content creator.
Well, I guess this is mostly true on the internet because most people wouldn't get to witnesses.
I have had these moments all throughout my career where I get to literally watch someone
become disillusioned with me as a human being.
I get to watch people go from thinking I'm good to no longer thinking I'm good, you
know, hearing something I've said that they find questionable and then deciding that they
like me less because of it and I've gotten to watch this happen a number of times and
it is a deeply fascinating and in some ways frightening experience because it's always
sad to know you've let someone down, but at the same time it's not my fault that they
are getting let down, you know, I can't control what they believed I was going to be or what
they want a person to be, you know, let's take for example, I mean, I think it's pretty
clear to most people who get into me that I drink a lot, you know, I've made that a
part of my identity, I do a show called the pub crawl, I have alcohol and all my avatars
and banners, I drink it on camera, I talk about it all the time, you know, I want it
to be clear that like, I'm a I'm a drinky guy, you know, it's a thing I do.
So I don't think there's a lot of people who come in and but I did see this before when
I first started drinking more where people started being like, you know, it makes me
uncomfortable that you drink so much because some people aren't comfortable with alcohol.
Some people aren't comfortable with this or that and it's not even always on a moral
level sometimes it's just on an experience level and I totally get it like when I was
a teenager, I was very straight laced, you know, I didn't do anything illegal.
And when other people did those things, I felt more disconnected from them.
When I heard people like talk about like all the weed they were smoking, you know, some
content creator talking about like weed and shit and like fetishizing it and talking
so much about it, it just put a little bit of distance between me and them because here
I was as someone who was deliberately not doing those things, you know, and then hearing
somebody else talk about it, it just feels alienating on some level.
And I understand that, but it's it's interesting to watch it happen because there's other
people who will be less alienated.
If I say something, if I go on here and talk about smoking weed, there's some people who
are going to be like, yes, this is exactly what I want to hear.
I love you more than ever before.
You know, please talk about this all the time.
It really makes me happy.
And there's going to be other people who are like, I'm so uncomfortable hearing you talk
about smoking weed that I, you know, it makes me want to tune out or I skip those parts
in the video.
You know, it's divisive subject matter and everything I talk about is divisive.
It's just on different levels and different different levels of people caring about it.
You know, it's one thing to be divisive about your opinions of anime, but it's a whole other
thing to be divisive on like a political or social issue that people might feel more strongly
about, you know, it invites a different level, especially when there's people who completely
agree with you on one front and then totally not on another.
You know, some people who are like, man, our taste in anime is exactly in sync, but the
way you live your life completely disgusts me, you know.
And it's funny when people equate the two.
Like this guy who left this comment, I don't know what the fuck he could have seen from
me that gave him the idea that I'm like this above conflict intellectual, like just because
I analyze anime and sound smart, I somehow am also, well, I must be like some kind of
fucking, I don't know, through through anti violence, anti being mean to anyone guy.
Not really the case, you know, I can be mean spirited.
I can be insulting.
I can be a dick.
I don't hold myself to that kind of high standard because I don't think I'm different
from most people, you know.
I'm not exactly trying to present myself as an amazing guy.
Um, again, not that I think I'm an outright supervillain or anything, but sometimes I
do feel like a bad guy, you know.
I relate to a lot of bad guys.
I relate a lot and I appreciate art from a lot of bad guys.
And that's another thing like part of the reason that I'm not willing to hide those
elements is that I respond well to those things.
I really love listening to Kanye West talk about how much of a shit person he can be,
you know, or a lot of rappers who rap about similar things.
I like, you know, I like listening to people who are outsiders who feel like they don't
agree with society, who feel out of place, you know, because I've always felt that way.
So that kind of shit resonates with me, you know, and that's the kind of stuff I want
to put out there.
I'm not out there to put on a squeaky clean image for people who want to fit in, you know,
it's not me.
So so I get to witness these things and I want to pull up this list of things that that
guy called me on my phone, because I found this to be a fascinating list of accusations
that he called me in this comment.
You can find this on my Reddit, by the way.
All right.
He says, he says, I don't see why he needs to continue to be personally attacked by degenerates,
which I never personally attacked Vic Minyona, but I find it interesting this implication
that I might be a degenerate, as if you or anyone else who attacks him is in any way
morally superior, while I certainly never claimed moral superiority to Vic Minyona.
As what qualifies one for virtue today are masturbating to porn and being a morally relativistic,
carefree libertarian who smokes the occasional blunt and voices some hate for a religious
person every now and then for good measure.
So I thought it was really interesting.
I'm not entirely sure if he's talking about me because some of that stuff just seems like
smokes the occasional blunt is such an odd out of place sentence and sentiment in here,
as is the masturbates to porn, really, because first of all, I've never had a blunt before.
I've smoked weed exactly twice in my life once a year ago and once last night, leading
into that as well, and I don't understand why that's coming up in an argument about
whether or not I'm a morally upright person because there's literally nothing wrong with
smoking weed.
But again, this is a matter of perspective.
For some people, if I talk about smoking weed, it's like, you know, like to them that's
like totally affirming, it makes me a better person, whereas others would think I'm worse.
Masturbating to porn, if you have a problem with that, I'm fucking sorry, but you're
a complete moron.
And then what was the other one?
Morally relativistic, which I already talked about, carefree libertarian.
I don't think I'm a libertarian.
I mean, I have so many socialist ideas.
I've said this before, I'm Aberdorf Linkler politically.
I completely see both sides of the issue.
If I'm libertarian, it's only to save my own ass, you know, it's just that like I think
libertarian belief systems and structures support my lifestyle better, you know, if
I was living in such a way that I thought socialism benefited me, I'd probably be more
of a socialist.
But that's all neither here nor there.
I don't consider myself a moral person.
I don't think I have to like people who are morally better than me, you know.
That is not my basis for judgment on people.
It's more about whether the things they do piss me off or not, you know.
I get a bad vibe from Vic Minyona, not a bad vibe as in he's a bad person, but a bad vibe
as in he does things I don't like personally.
So that's why I don't like him.
And maybe that's completely unfair and maybe I'm actually the asshole in that whole scenario.
I don't care if I am the asshole.
I am through with the notion that I am cool, as I say in the song Seath once again.
So I did get super duper high last night.
I started off normal high, which I hadn't been before.
It was all right.
I just ate everything.
I got the munchies super hard and ate everything in sight.
Then I just felt really chill and I was like, okay, this is probably the state of mind most
people are in who like getting high is just being chill and listening to electronic music,
you know.
Listen to Frank Jev C's volume two and then a bunch of Pogo music and it was Trill is
all fucked.
Then I got way too high and then my brain started being a thousand thoughts every second
and nonstop analysis of everything happening around me and things were too fucked up.
And then I thought it would be hilarious to watch Shrek.
I thought for the memes, I'll watch Shrek.
Well hi, that was a fucking nightmare.
I'm going to read you my Snapchat story.
If you don't follow me on Snapchat and you want to see things like this by all means
follow me on Snapchat.
My handle is digibroni after D all one word because one of my dumb ass friends made the
account.
So let me go through my story on Snapchat because I live blogged Shrek while I was watching
it.
All right, first we have feeling 840 and it happening as you can hear Smash Mouth playing.
Holy shit Shrek is the ugliest animated film ever made since Food Fight.
Every word in that sentence is spelled wrong.
This film is a waking nightmare of awful.
There is one good line in this movie.
This film is a cultural forced meme.
I am trapped in the most thorough analysis of my life.
To be fair there are some little but solid gems in here.
This scene is a Trump commentary referring to Shrek trying to build a wall around donkey.
This film is about convincing libertarians to be socialists or converting libertarians
to socialists and the nightmare is over which I should have typed ogre but you know I wasn't
in the best state of mind.
So that's my very high analysis of Shrek.
While I was high that was the worst movie I've ever seen.
The animation is like just all very stiff and shitty looking.
The character models are hideous, absolutely hideous.
Everything is very generic, low poly, it all looks like a fucking PS2 game like an early
PS2 game.
The movie just looks like dog shit as no aesthetic sensibility at all.
Everything is as standard and stock as it could possibly be.
A bunch of canned musical appearances, no cinematography at all.
The voice acting all sounds like it's recorded line by line.
Like it doesn't sound like the characters are reacting to one another.
Every line sounds like it was recorded multiple times and they chose a take or even constructed
a line from multiple takes.
And the music is generic.
The non-licensed music is generic.
So it's the worst movie ever according to me when I am feeling 840 as I put it.
So that might be a fun story for some of you and for some of you it might just sound like
an uncomfortable, self-destructive whatever.
See it's funny because I'm followed by a lot of nerdy types.
Nerdy types who often don't get into a lot of these things.
These illegal substances or substances at all.
People who don't drink.
And it's funny for me because even though I grew up super straight laced, everyone I
knew was super not.
My parents are fucking punk rock people.
My parents grew up going to shows constantly, smoking and drinking.
My dad never smoked much but he was always a big drinker when he was in his early 20s.
My mom smoked tons of weed with bands and shit.
And that's who my parents are.
I didn't really know that stuff growing up but my parents are fucking very loose people.
They swear constantly.
That's why I swear so much because my parents swear absolutely constantly.
As badly as I do.
And the people I knew in high school were all fucking stoners.
You know I was roommates with two of them at the same time.
They never smoked around me.
I never saw weed once until like last fucking Christmas the first time I even saw it.
I lived with two stoners.
They literally collected High Times Magazine.
A magazine about weed.
I guess I'd seen weed in that context.
But I'd read those magazines.
I'd sit on the toilet and read High Times or these weed books they had laying around.
I just grew up around a bunch of stoners and most of them had done other harder drugs and
drank a lot.
I didn't do any of that stuff but I was familiar with it.
So to me all that stuff is very normal.
It's all very like this is what everyone does.
I've grown up around media that represents those things.
I watch lots of movies where people do all kinds of drugs or listen to music that's about
drugs.
Most of the music I listen to is probably about drugs.
So to me that stuff all seems very natural and most of the people I know do it way more
than I do.
To people who don't drink at all I might seem like an alcoholic.
To an alcoholic I seem like a lightweight who barely drinks at all.
To people who've never smoked a cigarette I probably look like I'm addicted to cigarettes
which was true this past month or so but I'm quitting again but for years I smoked one
cigarette a day which is people who are like serious smokers.
My dad for 30 years smoked a pack to a pack and a half a day.
That's 20 in a pack by the way.
It's a world of difference.
My grandma was smoking four packs a day for most of her life.
She's still alive by the way.
She's like almost 80 and she had to quit eventually because she couldn't like she physically can't
even smoke anymore.
I did so many bad things to her lungs.
But yeah so to me that stuff all seems like babies first and again there's a divide in
the audience here.
Some people listening to this are going to go like yeah I know.
I know you don't do anything.
I know you're a fucking pussy baby and some people are going to be like yeah but you seem
like you're just a whirlwind of debauchery and nihilism which is you know I present
myself that way sometimes because I think it's funny but again I'm not I don't know
it really is a matter of perspective.
I've probably said that sentence 40 times now.
I guess to make a long story short if there's one thing I'm not interested in doing it's
policing myself publicly and I do it a lot more than it probably seems like I do given
the kind of stuff I talk talk about online just because I have very much tried to rein
myself in as a person who posts every fucking random thought I have because a lot of that
stuff is not relevant to many people and would actively make me seem like an idiot and I
try to avoid that because if you read my old like if you read my Twitter circa like 2008
or 2009 or like read my old anime blog like it was just so much unnecessary information
so much extraneous bullshit that didn't need to be there and you know it really made me
come off as like this dumb kid who was constantly shouting every thought I had and it's like
obnoxious to read that kind of shit even though a lot of the Twitters I follow do practically
the same thing you know but um so I do rein myself in because I have a lot of stupid
thoughts that that you know that I think for a second I should tweet and then I don't but
I don't want to be the kind of person who is constantly concerned about the overall
moral presentation of my character you know again I am a gonzo journalist because it's
about the experience of like what is it to be me what is it to be an otaku you know who
works online it's not about presenting that as a good thing it's not about presenting
otaku as something you want to be you know if anything I'd rather portray it more like
welcome to the NHK as kind of a living hell and waking nightmare you know that's not how
I feel my life is but it can be that and I don't want to hide those elements you know
and I guess I would feel better about it if there was a squeaky clean guy you know if
there was a version of me who who did all the same things but just was a better person
or maybe another guy well there's plenty of people who do the same thing as me but are like
you know actively more like like I see someone like endless Jess as like me with no scruples
about presenting myself that like you know I'm willing to go all out and just be you know the
monster that people want me to be in some cases now I absolutely love Jesse for that and I think
he's amazing for being so willing to put himself out there you know and and not be concerned about
trying to meet anyone's taste he does not give a fuck about your taste if anything he doesn't
respect you for the fact that your taste is not his you know and I think that's powerful and I
gravitate towards that um and on some level I because I feel like I'm such a spokesperson for
a lot of the ideas I'm talking about because of the fact that I present a lot of new analytical
ideas and I try to you know be a guy who also is talking about creators and also is trying to get
people into the media but I'm trying to be like this tour guide like that character you know gets
farther away from the gonzo element where it's like on some level I'm just trying to fucking just
introduce people to new concepts in anime that part of me can be more clean can be more polished
and doesn't have to be so gonzo but I'm not going to abandon the gonzo part and this creates a sort
of conflict of interest and I think this is part of why some of my videos go so misunderstood
because when I make a video like what is the appeal of anime or something like that is meant
to be as broad as possible it's really meant to be something everyone can appreciate and everyone
can learn from um whereas a video like flying witch uh in its fanservice is not broad it's not
for everybody it's not a video that is going to concern everyone it's almost academic it's very
like uh you know it's like a post made for other people who write about anime it's like
criticizing the way that criticism happens so it's a little too meta for for for it to be mainstream
and you know reconciling those two different elements of my work can be difficult and I kind
of wish there was somebody else who wasn't gonzo who was presenting those you know those more
cleaned up versions but then again that person would probably be boring as shit you know because
in my opinion everyone is actually biased and you know are we actually going to care what someone
who's so presentable has to say I don't know I just know that it it's um it's really it's really
weird for me when my lifestyle and moral choices have to come into conflict with my public persona
and the idea of who I am and how certain people perceive me
but it's always gratifying at least to know that there are members of my audience who
absolutely buy into everything I'm doing and saying you know not to say that they like fully
support all of it and they're like oh yeah by all means be a degenerate monster it's just that like
they get it and they see me as a human you know not as a collection of ideals or as like a moral
figurehead or or someone who's trying to present facts and you know in unbiased stances they just
see me as like yeah he's just a he's just an interesting guy you know that's all I want to be
is an interesting guy a guy who you look at and you go man that guy's lifestyle is fascinating
and and and I know that people can do that because there's so many creators who I don't
agree with on so many things but I love them you know film crit hulk one of my favorite
writers of all time you know top five easily top five most influential and favorite people for me
I adore film crit hulk but you know he has a he has a lot of political opinions that I'm just
kind of like come on dude you know he's he he can go like really hard on that like uh like social
justice kind of angle that I don't you know don't resonate with that strongly not to say that I
completely disagree with everything from that camp but sometimes he goes down that road and I
don't feel like I can follow but I don't care because he's a flawed person he's a guy you know I
don't expect him to reflect my ideologies or like my moral stance I just want to read his really
interesting writing you know um and there's so many people I feel that way about uh and it can
there can be breaking points you know there's enough that I don't respect about movie bob that I
can't really watch him anymore without just getting pissed off because it creeps into everything he
does a lot of it being production and presentation that I just have problems with uh but also is
just like fucking shoving his political beliefs down your throat constantly and generally talking
like an asshole I could get into a whole other thing about movie bob I'm sure I've ranted about
him on the pcp a few times but uh but yeah like I just hope that more people can watch me
and think of me as just as just an interesting person who they they like hearing talk and
not trying to uh view me through a moral lens because it's it's unfair in a way that I can't
refute that guy because I don't know him you know that guy who left that comment who is you know
slagging off all these things he knows about me but I don't know about that guy because I'm sure
if I had him describe as much of his life to me as I've described to him I'd find a lot of fucking
shit that I don't agree with that he's done you know but what can you do other than telling
to fuck off and ban him from my subreddit piece of shit I suppose that's about it for this one
I don't really have another thing to decompress about I've had a few ideas of of things to talk
about on this show but um they're kind of more topical and I don't know it's it's weird to just
like jump into some topic that's on my mind on this show uh at least if I haven't fully fleshed it
out and some of those are maybe things for other videos or other places I don't know I'm still
kind of finding what the decompression chamber is exactly so I guess it's probably gonna live for
longer than I previously thought like aside from the fact that it's nice to actually have it when
I do need to decompress I also am not completely sure um what stuff does or doesn't go in this
and that's always an exciting kind of feeling um likewise digi bros might not end as soon as I have
been saying it would just because there has been more interest a little bit and like once I talked
about it you know people spoke up about it and I looked through and realized that the view counts
are not actually any worse than they have typically been and a lot of people pointed out the the rather
obvious reasons that I guess I just kind of forgotten about why the show is not very popular but I'll
get into that um on the next digi bros probably so um so yeah uh that about wraps up this decompression
chamber stick around on my after dark channel for something that's kind of like a decompression
chamber because you know I kind of want to keep this to one a week I don't want to have two come
out um less than a week apart but I do want to do a big end of the year sort of summary of what
things have been like for me kind of video like you know a capping off vlog so expect that to come
and be similar to this but uh yeah that's it uh have a nice day
um