So, one of my favorite things about Jesse's podcast, especially the perfect cast, is
that he'll actually record it in segments over the course of like a week or however
long it takes to set up the podcast. It's something that had never really occurred to
me. You know, it's sort of a thing that you're, a luxury you're afforded by doing a solo podcast
as opposed to having other guests because you don't have to organize a bunch of people
to get together more than once, you know, in the course of a, of however long you can
just record segments and throw them in and it's, it's no biggie. So I wanted to do that.
This is being recorded on the 24th, right after having woken up after releasing the
previous podcast. I actually passed out listening to my own podcast. I did not make it all the
way through. I just sort of had it on and then crashed that fucking theme of, of guts
from Berserk, man. It's a, it's a real soothing track. So anyways, I wanted to continue with
thought that I like kind of cut myself off with in there where I was rambling so much
about how scatterbrained I am that I scatterbrainedly forgot what I was going to say. Because
I was saying that towards the beginning I said that when I go out to eat or something
or like celebrate after releasing a video that it creates a sort of bad habit and I said
I'd get back to it and I never did. Well, here's the explanation of that that I realized
over the last week, which is that by not having the catharsis of having accomplished something,
I think it helps to drive me to keep creating stuff like out of desperation because like
for me, you know, that moment when the video goes live and I see the first couple comments
that I sort of confirmed that it's there is like the big release, you know, it's like,
it's the coming night and day, if you will, of like finishing, you know, I've written
something that I'm proud of and I feel great about it, but it's not until it's out there
that it feels over, you know, that like the thing is done and now I can just bask in the
glory of having done it, you know. So when I put out a video, when one actually releases,
that's when I feel like the, ah, now I have done something, then I tend to, you know,
calm down and relax and do other stuff and not feel the need to, you know, stress over
the next video as much. But I think that because of the way that like I gave DeVu these two
videos to edit and I've been working on all this other stuff, then like there's been no,
like with the novel or the videos that I've been working on, there's been no sense of
release yet because all six videos are not out, you know, DeVu hasn't even, hasn't even
considered starting working on them because he's working on the previous videos and we
still have one more that we want to do before September's over that we haven't even started
on yet, not September, October. But anyways, yeah, so all these things that are piling
up, it helps to feel itself where it's like I can keep working and working because I haven't
felt that any of these projects have concluded, so it's easier to, you know, keep going through
that stuff. Which is kind of why I, like part of the reason I've slowed down vlogs a bit
because when I was doing tons and tons of vlogs, it was like this constant sensation
of getting things done, which was at some point when it was like at its most height,
like when I was just doing shit tons of vlogs, like after the summer season of anime and
I was like covering all the, or was it the spring season? The spring season. When the
spring season ended and like I covered all those shows, then there was a brief period
where I wasn't working on the main channel quite as much and part of that was because
I was, you know, building up to this whole everyone moving in thing and I really thought
I was going to like make vlogs, the central focus of my channel, which I still have plans
to make vlogs a bigger focus. Me and Victor just finally got the lighting setup done for
the studio space that we have that you've, that the plebe and the weave was filmed in.
I mean, we were using Victor's like professional lighting kit for that and we probably will
again for the plebe and the weave because that one's a little bit higher for production
value, but like with the original concept of building the studio was that I wanted there
to be lights that are just in there and that once the studio was set up, it would be very
easy to just walk in, turn everything on and start filming. You know, I wanted it to be
a setup that, that, that if I wanted to do just casual vlogs with like me and whoever
else was with me, then we could easily set it up and easily shoot it and it would look
professional enough that it could go on the main channel, but it wouldn't be like a super
high production value video, you know. So we finally got the lights set up to make that
possible and I just need to finish building the set and then, you know, I haven't been
vlogging currently because I'm working on all these huge projects, but like the fact that
I already have six videos written, like if we decided not to go through with a video
every day for all of November, I still have more than enough videos to cover November.
So like, you know, at some point when I've written so far ahead of myself that I've got
like months worth of backlog ready to go, then vlogging will be easy because I'll just
be like, wow, all my work for this month is completely done so I can just do whatever
I want, let's vlog, you know, or just keep my backlog going, just keep building it bigger
and bigger until I've got like a, you know, I've gotten way ahead of myself, which would
be great. Getting ahead of yourself is something that I think every creative wants and none
of us have pulled off, you know. Everyone I know talks about how badly they want to
have a backlog. Everyone really wants or at least to have, you know, just to have, God,
to be a couple weeks ahead of yourself, to not always feel like you're at the end of
your rope at the end of the month, like, oh my God, I have to have something come out,
you know, in the next few days, we're also not going to make any money this month, you
know, like to already have that financial guarantee allows you to go and experiment and
do other things in the meantime, which is why I wanted my Patreon to get so high and
it has gotten to that point where like I've got enough money now that I can make a few
videos and then go experiment and go do whatever I want, you know, or in the case of like the
early months of this year, me and DeVoo were like following a tight schedule where I was
like planning out all the videos that were going to happen in a month and then I'd give
him the plans and we were like editing down to a specific time frame. But yeah, we can
keep doing stuff like that now and so the vlogs will probably start coming. But yeah,
I do think that there's some value in just stockpiling stuff and never getting that sense
of like, I'm just done, oh, we put out a video, I feel so good, I don't feel like I have to
do anything else for the rest of the week, you know, it's a lot more intense and I like
it this way because like it might sound like, well, you know, that lack of gratification
must be, you know, must make it difficult. It's like, you know, it's not, it's like not
jacking off for a whole week. But you know what happens when you don't do that is that
you, at the end, when you finally do, then it's bigger and better than ever before. And
so, but the thing is that, you know, oh God, I can't stop with this jacking off metaphor
so I apologize ahead of time. But the thing is that the act of jacking off is already
the part that feels good, you know, the big after you come, then you just feel like bored
and miserable. So really, it's like I'm edging my way through all these videos and it feels
great because I'm constantly writing and writing makes me feel great or working on videos
makes me feel great. So it's like this nonstop edging and thankfully, unlike with, with masturbation,
it doesn't eventually give you blue balls and start to hurt. Although I guess my back
hurts a lot from sitting in this chair for like two weeks straight, you know, and not
moving and not doing anything. So I guess that's the blue balls of the writing world.
I apologize for how disgusting this metaphor got.
Alright, this is section two. It's around five in the morning on the 26th of October
and I just woke up, but I wanted to talk about some stuff. I'm going to talk shop for a little
bit. I'm going to talk about some of the secrets of how I do my work and how I, how I approach
trying to have a successful YouTube channel because I know some people who are really
like all about chasing the numbers, chasing success, trying to, you know, make something
that appeals to the highest number of people or is like trendy or just like, you know,
what can I cover that everyone wants to see right now? And there's other people who are
completely against even attempting to, you know, curve their content towards mass appeal
and personally, I kind of fall not so much in the middle, so much as all-encompassing.
What my goal has always been is how can I talk about whatever I want and make people care
about it? You know, how can I drive people towards my opinions and my content and the
things I want to talk about? Like, how can I make them want to engage with this? So,
you know, and I'm not saying that every project can do this. Sometimes I do stuff just because
I feel like it. Like Akiyuki Shinbo in the 90s, a video series that as I mentioned in
the last episode of this, like, I never expected it to be huge. Now, Akiyuki Shinbo is a pretty
well-known anime director, so I knew this was not going to be like a go nowhere series
in the way that it would be if, say, I had made a video called Shinichiro Kobayashi in
the ever, you know, no one knows who that is, which is why that video is called the master
in the background of 40 years of Japanese anime or whatever it's called. So, yeah, like,
with Shinbo I knew I could at least use his name, but you know, the first video it's got
a big face of Hiei from Yu Yu Hakusho because it's the most popular show that Shinbo worked
on, the one that would probably get the most people to click on it on the basis of what
character was on the thumbnail. And I don't think anyone truly appreciates how fucking
important the thumbnail and title are for a YouTube video success. No one seems to get
it. Like, I keep telling people and they're like, okay, yeah, sure, that seems right,
you know, and I keep showing them the numbers and how they correlate. They're like, okay,
I guess, you know, but no one, you don't understand. The only thing that matters if you want your
video to be successful is the title and the fucking thumbnail. That's it. That is all
that matters because no one knows what the content of your video is until they click
on it. No one has any idea, you know, they don't know how great your video is. They don't
know how genius it is. They don't know what's going on with it. In fact, they don't really
know that until it gets to a point where it's genius, you know, I think one of the biggest
reasons that endless Jess has never, you know, gotten the like a claim that he deserves is
because he takes too much of an artistic approach to his videos where his titles are always
very clever, especially if you know the video, you always are like, wow, that's a that's
a genius title, but it's not clickbait, you know, or have a great thumbnail that's like
really iconically staged, but it's not clickbait. Because what clickbait is is a close up of
someone's face. It always is that it's always a close up of someone's face. And if you like
take the YouTube tutoring shit, like where, you know, you get contacts from YouTube themselves
and like have advice with them, they tell you this, they tell you like close ups of faces.
That's what works, you know, I started doing it after Game Grumps talked about it. Like
they said that, you know, they had looked at all the big channels, all the market research
and everyone who was successful was saying, yeah, close ups of faces, because it's just
the most like intimate human connection, you can form with something instantly, you see
a bright starry face, you know, you just want to click on her or a or a gross face or someone
making a face, you know, some kind of reaction face, they always work. It's why like the
React series, the, you know, whoever reacts to whatever series is like always three pictures
of people's faces making different extreme reactions, you know, or why every big YouTuber,
you know, puts themselves edited into the thumbnails. You know, we were parodying that
with Movie News Weekly, my brother's hilarious video that's on Digibro After Dark. And like,
I understand why that could be frustrating for people. Like someone like Jesse, I don't
see him ever trying to curb himself to like have every video have a face thumbnail. He
would not do that because it would be artistically dissatisfying, you know, that instead of coming
up with these genius thumbnails that he does for every video that aren't clickbait, but
they are great thumbnails, you know, to instead try to make stuff that appeals to everybody.
Now for me, what I enjoy the most is when I get to have my cake and eat it too. When
I get to do exactly what I want to do, but also convince people that they want the same
thing. So that's why I go all out on the clickbait of the thumbnails and the titles. Because
to me, those are the least important elements of my video anyway. You know, those are an
afterthought. They have nothing to do with the actual content of the video. The job of
the title and the thumbnail is just to get people to click on the video. And especially
if I can somehow get you, if I can have a thumbnail and a title that are just dishonest
enough to get you to click on the video, but not so dishonest that you feel lied to after
you watch the video, that's the perfect sweet spot. That's what I'm always going for. It's
how can I title this in a way that, so like, you know, I just put out this video called
10 anime music videos you should check out. Now you, you already know that the clickbait
formula is top 10s. All the biggest anime channels are top 10 channels, best anime tops or like,
you know, Misty Kronexia, they do top 10s. It's just a clean number that people always
want to know. Now I didn't do top 10 anime music videos and that would have gotten even
better results probably, but I just didn't want to do that because I didn't want to put
these in order and I was making a lot more than 10 and like, it just wasn't what I wanted
to do. But 10 in itself is a great thing to have up there. You know, it's a great way
to get people to look just any kind of number, any kind of round solid number is always great.
And I didn't want it to say 15 or 20 because I actually recommend like 20 videos. If it
said 20, then it's overwhelming. It's like, oh, I don't, I don't think I'm going to have
time to watch 20 anime music videos, you know, but if it's 10, it's like, hmm, I could probably
watch all that and an hour, you know, that's anime music videos three minutes long, you
know, of course I want to know what 10 anime music videos I should watch right now, you
know, the video is 15 minutes long suggests that maybe this won't take you all day. But
of course it's a lot more than 10 recommendations. But if it said 17 or 18, it's not the same.
It's not the same as 10. But no one's going to complain that they got more than 10. No
one's going to say like, oh, you bastard, you tricked me. There were more than 10 in
this video. If anything, they're all happy about it. I mean, a bunch of people have pointed
it out. Most of them think it's funny because it is funny. It's kind of a joke. And that's
why at the end of the video, I call attention to it. I'm like, that was like 10 or so music
videos, I guess, whatever this video is long. Now let's move on, you know, like the joke
sort of is it was more than 10. And, you know, that's the kind of thing that I love doing
the most is if I can if I can give you a title that you you go, you know, and this happens
to varying degrees, people were a little bit more wary of like, how to recognize a great
anime in just one episode or how to recognize a terrible anime in just one episode, because
those titles weren't exactly what I was doing. They were, you know, close enough, in my opinion,
and I didn't really have a better title for those videos. But they were close enough to
the same thing as what I was doing that, you know, and some people did call out like this
is not actually what the video is. And I was like, yeah, that's kind of fair. But what
would you have titled this video? You know, like it's it is what it is kind of and the
title is what would be the most attention grabbing and it worked wonders. Those titles
and those thumbnails were unbelievably successful, especially the one for how to recognize a terrible
anime in just one episode, super provocative title, you know, people want to know how to
do that, people want to know why you think you can do that, you know, they're upset immediately.
And I've got this super close up of the super cute girl from gate just staring right into
the camera looking moe as fuck. Because you got to remember that even though the anime
sphere talks so much shit about cute girls, they overwhelmingly adore cute girls. There's
a reason cute girls are so fucking successful and popular, you know, it's kind of like how
even though Kaon gets shit talked all the time by people who are like, oh, this is the
death of anime, everything's cute girls, that show is super successful. Tons of people have
seen that, you know, both in Japan and the West. I mean, it wasn't as successful here
in terms of like sales figures because I mean, Bandai did a terrible job of releasing most
of the things they released in the late 2000s at way overpriced prices when everyone else
was slashing their prices down to nothing and not really advertising shows like Kaon,
at least not in the US. So it's kind of perplexing that they were like releasing it for these
high budget, you know, high budget release but not really advertising it that well. We're
like, you know, letting people know what it is or what the appeal is. But yeah, like,
I feel like, you know, people want so badly to portray this image that we're totally not
about cute girls, but they are. They are totally about cute girls by and large, you know. Maybe
those people aren't the ones leaving the comments because the people commenting about anime are
the ones who are dissatisfied. The people who are satisfied have no reason to raise hell
about how many cute girls there are, but the cute girls are the most popular. So if you
post some cute girl, if you post a hot anime girl in your picture, you know, Misty Kronexia
is like disgusting without he games the system, you know, he just straight up posts like the
most pornographic thumbnails he can get away with. And of course people click on it because
like, I mean, every time I see one, I'm like, I come very close to clicking on it. I'm like,
I want to know what this incredibly hot anime girl is from, but I know I'm not going to
get the answer because I know the formula. I know that Misty Kronexia is just putting
that thumbnail there. So you'll click on the video and then you'll have to, you know,
look at his fucking bald ass while he like talks to you about a bunch of other bullshit
that I don't care about. And I'm never going to find that thumbnail that I wanted that I
came for. So that's why, you know, and I'm not willing to go that far because I have a
brand. I have a brand that is somewhat classy, somewhat, you know, approachable, somewhat
like this guy appeal. I want to simultaneously appeal to hardcore otaku while also suggesting
to the people who are embarrassed about hardcore otaku that they can totally watch the videos
as well. You know, whereas like Misty Kronexia, I don't, I think a lot of people would be
embarrassed to say that they liked him, you know, whereas the people who just don't care,
especially younger people who just don't give a fuck are going to watch all the videos.
So, you know, I want to hit that middle ground. But again, for me, it's all about these middle
grounds. It's all about maximum viewer engagement. But like in terms of getting the most views
possible while still making what I wanted to make. And it can never be lazy, because
like I don't want to make lazy videos. I don't want to make videos that are just about getting
clicks. I want people to click on a video that I thought was great. And I'm going to
make them think it's great. So with the anime music videos thing, like for me, what was the
in what made that video fulfilling is that this video comes out for the song called Shelter.
Like it's super big. Everyone's talking about it. And I think, A, I can capitalize on the
success of Shelter to talk about a part of the medium that I'm a big fan of that people
don't talk about enough. You know, I love anime music videos. I get this is now a platform
being afforded to me to share ones that I like. I also want to have seen them all and
to be able to suggest all the good ones I can think of. Now we'll say, um, god damn,
there's a lot of people who are commenting with like, why not this show? Why not that
one? Why didn't you include this? A lot of them are ones I just haven't seen because
in spite of the fact that I see, I said I've seen them all. There's some that are not really
because I watched everything that's considered a music video by my anime list. So anything
that's not professionally released, you know, I didn't watch some of the animator expo shorts
that I still haven't seen yet were music videos, which I fucking tried to look into that. I
like looked up, you know, which ones are music videos. I didn't get like any results that were
helpful. So that's why I didn't include more animator expo ones because I wasn't sure which
one are music videos and I haven't seen all of the animator expo yet. But I can probably
just do a video about the animator expo at a later date. But you know, there's there's
a few I didn't include said and seen him some because I just didn't care for them and stuff.
But like, you know, ultimately the point of the video was to just share a bunch of them.
It wasn't about like, here's a comprehensive list, nor was it about here's a top list.
A lot of people seem to think this was a top 10, which was not at all the case, but you
know, whatever. So but the idea was like, let's have seen all the music videos that
I that I can and let's share all these cool ones and like get people to watch something
that they wouldn't have watched otherwise that they would never have known existed.
So, you know, the amount of research I put into this vastly outweighs what anyone else
would put into a 10 list of any kind, you know, because that's my style. I want to overwhelm
with how much research I do. I want to be that guy who went that far, you know, not
only because it's cool, it makes me look cool, but also because I just that's the kind of
content I want to see. I wish everyone was doing this much research into a top 10 list,
you know, and if I can do that much research for something and pour that much heart and
energy into it and yet still have it managed to be successful, that will be the perfect
thing, you know. So the title and the thumbnail are entirely in service of that and I I capitalized
so hard on shelter for this. Like I just took, you know, I showed clips from it at the start.
I mentioned it. I never mentioned my opinion of it, which is just kind of meh, you know,
I just say, hey, shelter's really popular. Here's a bunch of other anime music videos,
you know, I'm not here to start a fight. I'm not here to make people talk about shelter.
I'm here to make people watch these videos using shelter as the springboard. And of course
I use shelter as the thumbnail. And I would have liked a different thumbnail. I didn't
want it to be the exact same one that the fucking video itself uses. I did crop it to
be a better fit for my style, which is like hyper close up with with blue in the background.
That's the thing. The thumbnail was too perfect, like, because it's super close up of a cute
girl's face and it's got a bright blue sky. And for whatever reason, bright blue does really
well for me. I don't know if this is true of everybody. I don't know if there's any science
behind this. And I have some thumbnails that are on big videos that aren't all blue, but
almost all of my biggest videos are all blue thumbnails. Sword Art Online sucks part one,
blue thumbnail. Why good anime is hard to make? Blue thumbnail. How to recognize a terrible
anime in just one episode? Blue thumbnail. Why one piece works so well? Blue thumbnail.
So and most of them are blue either because of hair or because of the sky. So blue just
seems to be a really attention grabbing thumbnail for whatever kind of audience watches my video.
So I definitely gravitate to and I like them too. I love like blue how it pops off of the
screen and stuff. So, you know, that's why I chose blue hié for that shinbo thing, why
I chose blue sky behind the girl from Shelter. But like, yeah, everything about this video
is meant to say, hey, you like Shelter? Here's more. And like, if I can perfectly capitalize
on the success of Shelter to get people to watch something that is totally my thing and
something they did not at all anticipate getting, then that's perfect. You know, just getting
people to say like, to suggest to the audience that they're going to get the kind of trashy
bullshit they want. You know, they want the top 10. They want the cute girls. They want
the reminder of the thing they already care about like Shelter. They want to just watch
a video about something they already have opinions about and just want reaffirmation
that someone else cares about the thing they care about. So yeah, it looks like it's just
a video about Shelter, but it's not. It's the opposite. It's about a bunch of obscure
shit that no one cares about except me. And I'm now forcing you to care about it if I
can, you know. So yeah, that's sort of my that's that's that's the trick of the trade.
That's what my goal is. Be the most myself possible and get the most people to care about
it possible as opposed to trying to, you know, go to my audience because I don't want to
do that. I don't want to go to them. And when I whenever I try, I regret it, you know, like
when I not to say that I don't like these videos, but I mean, I've made it clear in
the past that like every once in a while I cover a popular show just so that I can have,
you know, something new or current or popular to talk about, you know, usually it's when
I just don't have any other ideas. I'll be like, All right, let's make a video about
what to motay people like what to motay. And that video is huge. Let's make a video about
erased and myriad colors phantom world. Those videos are huge. Cabin airy debt videos huge,
you know, it's a very easy way to to reach success. And I only do it if I have something
to say mob Psycho 100 huge, huge video. All those were the most popular anime of the season
that they were airing. I found something to say about them. So I made a video about it.
And, you know, but the the main thrust of why this show, why cover this show is because it's
the biggest show of the season and people will come to me for it. And, you know, if I was, I
feel like if I was a normal YouTuber, if I was someone like a gig or something, that would be
all I do. I just find the most popular shows and not gig, I meant glass reflection. The gig
is similar. They, you know, they go after what's the talking point? What are people talking about
right now? And they respond to it. And they, you know, they just whip up the audience reaction
they want. Whereas for me, it's like the opposite point. Get people invested, even though they
didn't think they'd care. Use Re Zero as a platform to talk about something else, you know,
which I almost wish that, you know, the, that Planetarian and Re Zero had been reversed,
where we could have had re like use the Re Zero video to tell people to watch Planetarian,
because unfortunately, as expected, my Re Zero, Plebe and the Weeb, it has three times the view
counts of the Planetarian Plebe and the Weeb, you know, so, which is to be expected. But if we
could have diverted people there, that would have been nice. But, you know, the reason Re Zero,
we even covered it on Plebe and the Weeb was to get more attention to Plebe and the Weeb,
a show that people would not have watched. It was, you know, a two guys talking show that
is totally different from my normal content. Nobody really knows who Jesse is. The title is
not Click Beaty, you know, the Plebe and the Weeb is the name of a show. It's not a Click
Beat title that will get like, you know, if I had been trying to make those just Click Beaty,
it would have just been like Re Zero, best or worst show on television or something, you know,
like, because who cares? It doesn't matter what the title of the video is. But with the Plebe and the
Weeb, we want it to be a series and we want it to be recognized as such. But covering Re Zero at
all is a huge boost to the series. You know, if we hadn't covered that show, then there's a good
chance or covered anything popular, you know, like we covered your name because it was new and it
was making waves and Re Zero because it was a huge deal. You know, Planetarian is more of the
kind of show that me and Jesse would be more inclined to watch and more inclined to talk about.
But that video has way fewer views and it would not have gotten Plebe and the Weeb off the ground
and it would have just sank down my channel, you know, though I am impressed by how many views it
did get at least, you know, I think 21k was a pretty healthy amount. Even if that's like,
for my current self, that's like the lowest I'm likely to get at all, you know, like it used to
be that I had videos that, that if it was like no one cared about it, it was below 10k. But now
I'm big enough that like 20k is kind of like the rock bottom I can hit. But nonetheless, I'm glad
that that's the rock bottom I can hit because that's a lot of people and that's a lot of heads
to go watch Planetarian, you know, in go watch Jesse's content. But yeah, and I mean, even with
the thumbnails for Plebe and the Weeb, like, I was going to make the thumbnail for, like, Jesse
made all the thumbnails for it and I would have had your name would have been the image of her
groping her own tits from the start of the movie because we do talk about that scene. I would have
had the Re Zero One would have just been a close-up of Rem and Ram, like as close as I could get
into their faces, but at least they were in there for Jesse's thumbnail. And then with Planetarian,
just, you know, close-up of cute girl's face, like, that's close-up of face. It's, it is a one-way
ticket to your video getting views. And it's so satisfying when you do it and it works, like,
when you put the, like, with the anime is how to recognize a terrible anime in just one episode.
I knew what the thumbnail was going to be immediately when I was watching Gate because,
like, the second that girl's face popped up on camera and it just hogged the whole frame
and it was just this perfect shot of this girl's face, I was like, that's the thumbnail. You know,
like, I figured that out before I was done writing the fucking script and I was so fucking excited
to use it and that video has over a million views. It's my second most viewed, no, yeah,
my second most viewed video of all time. People, the title and the thumbnail. And, like,
I told this to Mother's Basement and he's totally changed the way he does titles and thumbnails
as a result, but he's still not doing it right because he'll put, like, a kind of okay thumbnail
but then he puts his stupid animated avatar over it, which is cartoon guy, which is totally
antithetical to making a good thumbnail and unnecessary and I don't know why he does that.
I keep telling him to stop, but he keeps doing it. It's terrible. It's like, it's cancelling
out the effect of the thumbnail, you know, but he's gotten better with the clickbait titles.
He stopped, you know, it used to be like, what's in an OP? X show and then now it's called like,
how strong is one punch man's punch? What's in an OP? You know, personally, I would cut out
the extra part entirely. I would just make it what it is because there's no reason to have
a series title. It doesn't, the only people who care that it's a part of the series are people
who watch all your videos, you know? Like, if you can come up with a series title that's also
clickbait, like cool character designs is a good clickbaity title for the kind of videos those are.
Like, that's what the video is, is about cool character designs, but it also is eye catching.
Oh, I want to hear about cool character designs, you know? So that's a good clickbait series,
but if it's a series title that doesn't really mean anything to the audience, you know, like in a
major way, like what's in an OP is okay, but it doesn't make me like rush to click in the way
that just saying like, here's what's cool about this show's OP, you know, gets you in.
Um, but, you know, I know Jeff likes to keep things as part of a series and he kind of has
like an older YouTuber mindset because it used to be that, you know, people really wanted things
to be a part of the series so that people like knew that there was more and they knew to go find
more of it. But nowadays, if people want more of your content, they subscribe. Like, YouTube is a
subscriber culture now. It wasn't like that before, you know, back in the day there was, there was
not this push for subscriptions. And when YouTube redesigned the whole website back in like 2013,
they did it around subscriptions. They built it around how do we make people get drawn to the
subscribe button. That's why the subscribe button is dead center in your channel on the page, you
know, like they want to drive people towards subscribing to channels because they realize
that that was the best way for content creators to, you know, keep their audience and keep making
revenue. So yeah, like you really want subscriptions and the people who are subscribed to your
channel, it doesn't matter that it's a series. They get it, you know. Now you can codify your
thumbnails and titles in a way. I think the best way to handle doing a series is color-coded thumbnails.
You know, guys like Chaseface do this well, where, uh, you know, if it's part of one series, then it
all has the same color of thumbnail, but the title and thumbnail can be something clickbaity,
you know. If you want to have, or Glass Reflections does this well too, where he's got like, you
know, if it's a proper review, then it's like a close-up of a character's face and like a blue,
like, techno-y background. And it's like, you know, this anime review. But then if he does like the
impressions, then it's like a gray background. And it's close-up of a face on a gray background.
This is an impressions video. And you can instantly tell looking at his channel like, okay,
there's several different series here, which one am I interested in. Canapa Effect does something
similar. He uses like, blue text for all of his, you know, creator spotlight videos, and then other
kinds of text for other stuff. That's a good method of doing it, because it doesn't take away from
your ability to make things clickbaity, while also notifying it as a series. So, you know.
But anyways, everyone needs to pay more attention to their titles and thumbnails. They're the only
things that matter. The only things that matter for views. The only things. Because you just have
to get them to click the video. That's all that matters. Like, once they're there, they will
find out that it's a genius video and they'll reshare it. You know, if you're making, if you're
making good content, then, then it's going to, you know, it's going to get, um, going to get
reshared once people find it. Once they find out it's good. But they have to find out it's good
first, you know, and they're not going to find out it's good if they're not going to find it.
And if you're not going to click on it in the first place, if it's got a weird title and a
weird thumbnail and people don't understand what the appeal of it is, they're not going to click
on it. Um, so you just got to get your fucking hooks in people and drag them kicking and screaming
over to what you want to do. Alright, that's it for this segment. She's opened up a beer.
So as an addendum to the stuff I was saying like four days ago or for you like one minute ago,
um, advice for YouTubers, tag yourself on all your videos. Your tags have to do with what shows up
in the related videos on the side. And for my whole YouTube career, the overwhelming majority
of hits that I get that aren't from subscribers are from related videos. And if you tag yourself
all the time, it means your own videos are more likely to show up in the related videos.
So always tag your own name, write your own name into the tags. On the PCP, all the tags are pretty
much just the names of all the PCP members. I don't know how well that works, but um,
it's a, you know, it's worth doing. So I got to talk about one of the big things going on with
me right now, which is that I am turning into a fucking monster. This is going to contradict
everything I was saying on the fat fuckery podcast. We were talking about lifting and I was like,
oh, lifting sucks. It just leaves you exhausted all day, blah, blah, blah, and all that shit. Well,
you know, at the start of that podcast, we hadn't finished building the squat rack,
the one that Ben brought with him. We told a whole story about that, but we did like within a couple
days of that podcast. And so me and Ben started lifting. And what I quickly realized is that
lifting is fucking awesome. Now, yes, it does have the negative consequence of being exhausting.
And your muscles feel sore all the time, at least so far mine have, you know, they've never,
because we keep pushing ourselves to higher and higher weights every time we do it. We've never
just been maintenance lifting. It's all strength lifting, all in increasing the amount we lift
every other day. So, you know, it's been a fairly brutal workout schedule, but I feel strong.
And every time, like right after working out, it's just like, you just feel the pump and it's
just like, yes, I can do anything. I am a God, you know, and definitely gives me more of like a
strut and like more just, I don't know, I feel good about whatever I'm doing. And it's funny,
because, you know, so much of my time is spent sitting around and just like, when I'm not sitting
around and probably eating, I say this all the time, how I pretty much just leave the house to go get
food. And, you know, that can make me feel like I'm not doing enough physical activity, like I'm
not getting out enough and stuff like that. But lifting, which only takes like half an hour,
with the lifting, you know, the schedule me and Ben have been doing, is like, it feels like it
meets that need completely. It's like, you know, working yourself to such physical exhaustion
that it's like, yes, I have done my physicality for the day, you know, and now I can feel good
about just sitting down for eight hours doing work, you know, or just getting up to go eat
and stuff like that. I don't feel like I'm hugely missing out on the rest of the world
or just on doing anything physical. And it's, I mean, it's been fun. Me and Ben have been,
you know, doing the workouts together. It's just a fun time to just pump out some iron,
you know, see what we can see how high we can raise our, our fucking lifting amounts and stuff,
feel the gains flowing through us. But here's what's, here's why it's turned me into a monster.
Because ever since we started, started lifting, I can't stop eating. I've been eating constantly in
larger and larger portions. Like I've always been kind of a small eater. There's only been a couple
of times in my life where I've been able to eat like more than normal. And it's usually like,
like, it's like the kind of thing where once you start eating big, you can continue to eat big.
But if you typically don't, then it's like you feel capped out at a lower level, you know,
I'm the type of guy who often doesn't get the side dish with my order, you know,
go, go to a, go to a fast food restaurant. I don't need the fries. I don't need the combo,
you know, buy one, get one free. I might eat half of the second thing, you know,
I've never been someone who eats like a huge portion or even like a normal portion. But
like now ever since I started lifting, it's just been like, I will eat everything in sight.
It doesn't matter. Give me the biggest thing on the menu. I'll fucking put it down. Give me the
two. I need the two. I also need the large drink, you know, I usually can't even finish a fucking
medium sized drink of like soda, you know, with my meal. Now I'm just chugging down these fucking
big ass drinks. I went to Hardee's yesterday. I had like they had a steak, egg and cheese
biscuit, buy one, get one free. I got two. The guy said, do you want a dollar drink? And I'm
like, what the fuck is a dollar drink? And he said, it's cheaper than the small or yeah,
because I think I asked for small, but then he gives me the dollar drink and it's a fucking huge
cup. It's like an extra large drink. And I'm like, I don't know why that's a dollar, but sure, I'll
take it, drink the whole fucking thing, you know, along with eating both steak, egg, and cheese
biscuits, which I am certain I wouldn't have been able to do two weeks ago. It's just given me such
a fucking appetite. And I know that the way I'm eating, because, you know, you're supposed to
eat big to get big. If you're lifting big, you got to eat big, but you got to eat right. You know,
the key is to maximize on protein, but not to eat a bunch of fat and a bunch of sugar,
because if you do, you're going to get, you know, your muscles will get bigger,
but you're also going to get fat. But I, I don't care. Like it feels so gratifying to like pump,
you know, to just lift heavy weight and then be just, and then just go eat everything that I want.
It doesn't matter what I just, I want it. It's going in my mouth. There's no hesitation. There's
no looking at the labels. There's no nothing. I have been eating like a fucking pig, and I know
I'm going to get fat, but I'm going to get strong fat. And I feel like, I feel like I like that.
I want to, I want to be a mosh pit guy. That's what that's the body I think I'm going for is the guy
in the mosh pit at metal shows, which I've been to a considerable number of metal shows. I've been
in a few mosh pits. I'm usually the guy who gets pushed around pretty hard. I usually walk out pretty
bruised, you know, because there's usually at least one guy in there who's some big fat buff
motherfucker with huge muscle, huge chest, huge arms, but you know, like a beer, beer gut.
I see myself being that guy, because honestly, for me, like, I feel like vices
are like, I don't, I don't get the point of life without them to some extent. I guess if you, if
you get really into something like running and it makes you feel like your life has been affirmed
or something like that, like you don't need any vices because you have running, which needs to
be the way that runners act, you know, like a, like a Casey Neistat or even my dad, like my dad
used to smoke and drink all the time. You know, he was like a pack of day smoker. He drank a lot
at parties and shit, completely quit both of those, took up running. That's what he does now.
And maybe that'll be me one day. Maybe in my 30s or so, I'll eventually, you know, my dad started
late. He didn't really start running till it was like late, late 30s, early 40s, I think. But uh,
you know, maybe that'll be me one day. But right now, it's hard for me to go very long without
advice because I start to wonder why am I even alive for this? You know, like why, why be a person
who has to eat healthy and watch what you eat and not drink too much and not smoke? Because those are
the things that make life fun. Those are the things that make it easy to do, to do work all the time.
You know, like to not, I live a lifestyle where all I really want to do is work. That's all I want
to do. All I want to do is watch anime and make videos about anime and make blogs and make podcasts
and, and, you know, collaborate with other creative people. That's like the only desire I really have,
other than like, you know, having interesting conversations. I like doing that, you know,
I take breaks from work to go hang out and talk to people both in real life and online,
you know, offline and online. I don't know why I still say in real life. I hate that being
equated with something different, but it's just such an ingrained phrase. But anyway, yeah, you know,
having interesting conversations is great, making stuff is great, and there's nothing else I really
like to do. I don't really like to leave the house except to eat, you know, that's the only reason I
want to leave. I've done the whole go out and do things stuff. Things aren't interesting. The beach
is not that fun. Mount Trashmore is not that fun. Maybe once a month it's fun to go out and do
something somewhere, you know, gatherings all week. I don't care. I just want to stay home and work.
And all I want to do other than that is stuff that will make me feel like I have not sat in one spot
for eight hours. And there's a few easy ways to not feel that way. One is to get up and go have a
smoke. It's such an easy way to like, I've been working for an hour. I kind of want to just stand
up and have a break. You go outside, you smoke a cigarette, you come back in, you feel ready to
take on the next hour of work. Or I'm about to do a huge editing job that I don't want to do.
Let's have some beers. It'll make this easier, you know, like the other day, what was this, two days
ago, I had, okay, so everything I talked about in the previous podcast is not happening the way I
described it, which is good. And because that leaves me the opportunity now to not describe this
stuff that I am doing in too much detail so that it can still happen. But I'll go into at least
this much, because this is already guaranteed, because I described that I had written six videos
for a month-long project in November to make a ton of videos all at once. I ended up canceling that
project because it was financially retarded to make 15 videos in one month. I obviously can't
Patreon all of them, and I already had got those six ideas that I had that were so good that I like
wrote instantly. Those were all the like ideas I had that I really wanted to do, and all the other
ones I'm looking at like, eh, this, eh, you know, I don't want to write this video. But I have another
project that I am excited about, and I'm just going to get straight to work on that as opposed to
the whole novel of videos in November. So I'm already working on the next big project. But
instead, I now have, you know, six videos that DeVu can make at his own pace over the course of,
one will come out by the end of this month, and the other five will come out over the course of
November. And so, like, I'm looking at it like, that's five videos that are already written. All
I have to do is voice them, and then the rest of it's DeVu, you know, like, I mean, there's a few
that I have to make some more notes for. But basically, I can have all my work for November
done as soon as these are all voiced. So two days ago, I just sat in my closet and voiced all five
scripts one after another for like, probably two and a half hours or something, and just sat in
the closet, voiced every single one of them, then I came out of the closet, and I edited all of them.
And so, you know, editing audio is not horribly difficult or time consuming, it's just kind of
a grind, because it's just remove all the spaces and bad takes, and then add in new spaces anywhere
that there's not enough space between words, which basically means listen to the same 15-minute
script like three times in the process of editing it to sound coherent. It's kind of boring, especially
to do on five videos at once. So had a few beers, made it easier, you know, by the time I was done,
I was feeling pretty drunk, and was ready to pass out, great day of productivity. That's now five
videos that I have done my whole part for, and so the entire month of November, if I really wanted to,
I could fucking sleep, you know, but of course, because all I like to do is work, I'm already
started on the next big project that'll probably start coming out in December, and I've, you know,
I'm planning all these other things that I want to do, we've got planning for the plebe and the
weave to worry about, we're trying to figure out the situation with getting Jesse and Nate down here,
I've been guesting on podcasts, putting together my own podcast like this one, my own vlogs, I have
a bunch of, I have like five vlog series, five vlog videos that are like halfway done, or even less,
like okay, I started up all these new vlog series that are related to like watching a show, there's
like the second chances board, and what happened with that was I, you know, I selected the next show,
I watched the first episode while I was drunk, and it was, it was kind of too difficult
to comprehend, like there's too much going on for my drunk mind to process, so I decided to
wait till I was sober to watch any more of it, and I just haven't gotten around to it, because I'm
not that, like, I didn't want to drop the show based on that first episode, but I'm also not excited
to watch more of it, and I probably will drop it before the end, but like, I don't know, and then
there was the, the exact same story with random ass recommendations, I shot the dart at the screen,
got the next show, watched the first episode of it, and like, I didn't dislike it, but I also
wasn't so enthusiastic about continuing that I would watch the rest immediately, then I started up
another thing that I won't describe too much, which is another Select a Show thing, I selected
a show, watched the first four episodes, really loved them, but got busy with other stuff, and
haven't gotten around to watching the rest of the show, which is horribly ironic, considering the
nature of this particular show, which you'll see eventually, and then, and then there's also
Finish or Fail for 2016 shows, which of course, the entire fucking summer season ended, so now
there's like 30 fucking shows that I had on hold that I now have to try to watch, so all of that
is waiting, and in the meantime, I'm working on this other huge series that I just, you know,
got excited about and launched right into, so there's just too many have finished and unfinished
projects going on, I have to edit this commentary for the for the for the Patreon before like tomorrow,
and meanwhile, I'm trying to figure out how I'm gonna start promoting the PCP guys, because like,
I'm trying to get all everyone on the PCP more popular and more famous, because all of us are
trying to do this as careers, and I'm the only one other than Jeff, who's like really succeeding at
it right now, Jesse is too, but like Jesse has a lot of stuff that's siphoning his money away,
other than just the fact that he spends it haphazardly, but like, we want to get Jesse and
Nate living down here, and Hippo eventually, and we want everybody to be like, satisfyingly able to
make careers off their arc, and so I'm trying to figure out how I'm gonna help promote these guys,
how I'm gonna like, you know, help them to find content that they can produce that'll
that'll make it easier to have a career doing this stuff, you know, that's that's kind of the
the thing we're all chasing is to have everybody as a group be able to, you know, sustain ourselves
off of this shit, and right now my my Patreon, I'm actually kind of, I wouldn't say I'm like
losing money or anything, but my Patreon is like kind of just floating around a number that it's
just kind of stable at, and I'm not gaining a ton of views on my new videos because I've chosen to
work on stuff that's not topical and not like big stat cow stuff, which I mean is deliberate,
I just want to do what I want to do, but you know, there's a reason I do those stat cow videos
sometimes, it's because I want the growth that comes with it, and that's not coming right now
because I'm doing weird shit like Akiyuki Shinbo in the 90s and stuff like that, that and plebe in
the weave, that's not going to draw the numbers the way that a, you know, clickbaity title on a
current show is going to do. So point being, I've got all this stuff going on, vices are a great way
to help me through it, all I want to do is do all these vlogging projects, all these
podcasts, all these fucking videos from my main channel, all these huge research projects that
I keep getting myself into, and the project, it really is reaching the point, I'm reaching the
promised point, I used to always say that like if I hit this amount on Patreon, I'll be able to do
bigger and bigger projects, I kept saying that like guys, if you get me up to a thousand dollars of
video, and I only need to make two videos a month, and those videos can be as big as I want them to
be, they can be these huge weeks long research projects that are just like, you know, deep and
involving, and that's exactly what I'm now doing. Stuff like Shinbo in the 90s, you know, is a project
where it just takes that long to watch all those shows and do all that research for it, and it's,
I'm so glad, like this is what I've always wanted to be doing, is these huge projects, and now that's
exactly where things are going, but um, but in the meantime, it's like, I just want to have a couple
of beers, a couple of cigarettes, and eat whatever I want, because eating makes me happy, eating things
I like makes me happy, eating things I don't like doesn't make me happy, you know, like eating healthier
food, you do get that sense of like, wow, I feel physically better, but there's no satisfaction
in it, there's no sense of reward, there's no sense of like, I just worked for three hours,
and I want something to take the edge off, you know, when you just eat something that's just
good for you, it just feels like, well, I am now sustaining myself, like, yes, I can now continue
to live, I guess I'm not hungry anymore, but there's no sense of like, yeah, all right, I did something,
now back to work, at least not for me, I know it's different for some people, the DeVoo has been on a
big health food kick, and it's really working out for him, but for me, I take so much satisfaction
from eating, it's such a huge thing, you know, it's a huge element of what I like, and from drinking,
and from smoking, which I'm gonna try to cut out the smoking, because that's gotten out of hand,
vaping only made it worse, and I've been smoking too many cigarettes, but only because I was like
experimenting with different types, because I bought a pack of blacks, which is a clove cigarette
that I've always wanted to try, I mean, I've tried one before, but I've always wanted to try and buy
one, and I like, hunted them down and bought a pack, and that was pretty cool, but those things take
too long to smoke, and you know, by the end of it, I've got a headache, so went through that pack,
then this is kind of its own story, but I was watching The Dick Show, which if you're a patron
of The Dick Show, you get to see video feeds of the episodes, and Asterios Cocanos, who is a
fantastic comedian who I love, was finally on the show after a long period of trying to get him on
there, and it was a fucking great show, and Asterios was just smoking cigarettes constantly through
the whole show, and it was really funny, and I am extremely suggestible, so when I saw him smoking,
I immediately wanted some, and what he was smoking was a cigarette brand called Dunhills,
which had this really interesting package, and I was like, okay, I want to try those, so I hunted
them down, and now I'm smoking a pack at Dunhills, but once that's over, I will hopefully stop
for at least a little while, because I've been burning through this pack at a rate that is
completely beyond anything I've ever been doing before, so it's not a good look in terms of getting
addicted, but you know, cigarettes notwithstanding, I do love drinking, which I am good at doing in
moderation, I've never gotten to the point of alcoholism or any kind of addiction with that,
it's purely a casual thing, cigarettes, it's starting to feel very not casual, which is why
I'm worried about it, but yeah, that stuff just gets me through, man, that's what makes it so
five days of nonstop work doesn't feel exhausting, I don't feel like, oh my god, I haven't done
anything, I feel like wow, I've accomplished so much, and I've felt good the whole time, and all of
it's possible because of the lifting, because the lifting is so satisfying, and so like, physically
engaging, and it makes me feel so like good afterwards, like my body feels good, and I look
at myself in the mirror, and I feel good, because I see this like, I see the confidence running
through me, I see my body slowly becoming more, you know, like able to stand upright, and you know,
and have a posture to it, that it's like, yeah, I don't even care if I'm fat, because who do I
need to be skinny for, I don't know, I don't care, I'm not even like, it's not like if I like lost
a bunch of weight, and got like really good looking, that I would suddenly go out on the town, and start
like, hooking up with girls or something, like that's not gonna happen, you know, even if I
completely lost weight, and I look fantastic and beautiful, it's still gonna be me sitting around
on the computer, editing your, you know, writing videos for days on end, so it's like, as long as
I feel good, it doesn't matter what I look like, I just want to feel good physically, and what makes
me feel good physically is pumping fucking iron, and feeling strong, you know, and as long as I feel
strong, no amount of eating makes me feel completely gross, no amount of drinking makes me feel
completely gross, and so I'm just totally indulging, I am completely breaking bad, and going off the
deep end, and it feels great, and I don't know if I recommend that to anybody else, if that would
work with anyone else's lifestyle, but um, yeah, I just physically feel, for the last like two and
a half weeks, I felt great, and I mentioned at the start of the last Digi Bro's decompression
chamber, I was like, you know, even though I need to decompress just because there's too much going
on, I feel good, like I don't feel bad at all, everything in my life feels really great right
now, and that's entirely because of the lifting, the strictly regimented lifting just every other day,
me and Ben lift, you know, and then I feel, I feel incrementally stronger, I feel confident,
and I can just eat whatever I want, and not give a single fuck about anything, and I have been
picking out on a scale that I have never done before, and uh, and probably spending too much
money, but I mean, I don't really spend money on anything else, so my budget is so hard to exhaust,
because it like, it like, the amount I spend on food looks like too much, but then there's nothing
else taking it away, so I always look at my bank, and there's still money there, and I'm like, well,
as long as there's still money there, I guess it doesn't matter, but we'll see, we'll see what happens
when tax day comes, and it all comes crashing down around me, and I have to fucking make an LLC,
and I gotta fucking register DeVue probably as an employee, because I'm sure he's made
ten grand this year, uh, uh, I don't want to do any of that, I need to, I looked up the rates for
hiring an accountant, they were too high, uh, I gotta figure out how to do it all myself,
no money, no problems,
all right, this is either the end of this episode, or there's gonna be another segment that I record
tomorrow before I post this, so look forward to that, and uh, see you then. You know, all week long,
I had fully intended on finishing and editing and uploading this thing on the 30th, and the 30th came
around, sat around all day, kept thinking I was gonna do it, but putting it, putting it off for
this reason or another, and now it's already the next day, but I wanted to talk a little bit about
why this is on the PCP channel, because some people were saying that this seems like a very
after-dark kind of, uh, kind of show, and I get where they're coming from, the explanation is
something that I think anyone will understand who's an artist, and probably a lot of other people
will too, which is just basically about the different ways that you compartmentalize
your thoughts, and your works, and just what you do, and there's sort of the reason that I have so
many channels, and I think this applies to everyone I know who has multiple channels,
is that each one has a very distinctive voice and purpose. You know, some people,
back in the day, we started up multiple channels because we thought, well, you know,
this channel's for anime, this one will be for this, this one will be for that, but uh,
over time it's come to be more of like the character of the content that's on it, so
my main channel is meant specifically for like, you know, highly edited videos that have a concrete
point, but it's not just that, it's also that they're kind of individual, like each one,
while I do expect that people, you know, watch more than one video on the channel that they want
to fully get, like, where I'm coming from with my videos, because I think there's a sort of
ongoing narrative of the way I talk about shows, um, I don't expect that people who watch the channel
will know me that well. I don't expect them to know, like, everything I've ever done, I don't
expect them to know who I know, who I talk to, you know, uh, so if I make a video on the main
channel where I'm just openly making reference to, like, the PCP, or to any of my friends, or to,
like, more personal aspects that I don't expect most of those people to have heard of, or like,
to get where I'm coming from, then I think it would, it would be weird, you know, so it's like,
each, each video on there is more about, here's a subject I'm dissecting, and you can go from
this video to any of the others, and it'll, it'll continually make sense, it's that kind of body
of work, whereas on other channels, like After Dark, I have more of an expectation that if you're
watching After Dark, it's because you're invested in me, not so much that you're invested in anime,
or in analysis, per se, you're just invested in what's DigiBro up to, and that channel is intentionally
random, it's just whatever comes to mind is up there, it could be a vlog, it could be a music
video, it could be anything, you know, I don't market it in such a way that, uh, that I expect
people to, you know, subscribe for one kind of content. Now I know that, I mean, that's not,
in terms of marketability, it's probably a terrible idea, I mean, there's lots of stuff on After Dark
that if the channel was just that, it would probably get bigger, and if I, you know, if I
changed the thumbnails and stuff to be more accessible, but I don't want it to be that,
it's meant to be just anything goes, uh, take it or leave it, you know, it's the DigiBro experience.
Now, the PCP channel, though, is a little bit different, because PCP channel is about regularity,
it's about shows that come out on something resembling a schedule, you know, each show is a
once a week schedule, with the exception of some of the specials that we do, like, you know, the
draw cast or rowdy fuckers cop killers, but even those are a series, there's a definitive style
to it, there's not a lot of videos on this channel that are just totally out of nowhere,
there's the 360 classroom, which we do intend to do more of, so that's a series as well,
and the Great Dark Souls race is probably like the most, just like, this is just a thing we did
with all of us in it, um, kind of thing, but like, the idea of the channel is weekly shows that are
usually pretty long, they're always like at least an hour, they're mostly podcasts, there's not a lot
of visual element to this channel, um, and when there is, another part of it is that it's, it's
all of us, and even if we're not all in the video, or even if it's a one person podcast, you know,
there's still a lot of reference being made to the PCP, to other people involved, and so,
so, you know, I think for that reason, this show kind of belongs here, where if I, if I constantly
talk about my online friends on Digibro After Dark, I don't know that all of my audience knows or
cares about them, you know, like, if you're watching the PCP channel, it means that you know who all
of us are, probably, as opposed to on After Dark, which has its own distinct audience that's about
me, so, yeah, I agree that this is the kind of content you would kind of expect from Digibro After
Dark, but it's very formulated, and I wanted it to be that way, it's a weekly show-ish, it's, uh,
you know, it's got this certain visual presentation, the certain style of audio, it's got music,
which is unusual for my content, you know, so, yeah, that's why I think it's more of a
procrastinator's channel show, and we wanted, uh, Jesse especially wants each of us to have
our own show, or for each combination of us to have our own show, so like, we'd love it for the PCP
channel to be like a bunch of different podcasts, uh, each of which have their own formula, their
own regular intervals of output, and uh, yeah, I think that's cool, and it's kind of, in a way,
it's a lot like the Red Letter Media way of doing things, you know, where their channel is like,
there's the best of the worst, there's half in the bag, there's review, and they're all
sort of different, different takes on the same concept of two guys sit down and talk about
a movie, um, in a way, The Plebe and the Weave would have been a good fit for this channel too,
but that show is, um, just, we wanted it to be big, like, I wanted to see how big of a deal
The Plebe and the Weave could get to be, so that's why we put it on my main channel,
because I have the most subs out of everybody's channel, so, you know, I didn't want it to sort
of languish in obscurity on something like the PCP channel, which is growing, but not huge,
you know, at this point, but yeah, um, that's why it's here, and I think it's, I think it's good
for it to be here, I like it being here, and I like the idea of the podcast in general.
By the way, I thought I'd mention, if you guys haven't been listening to Jesse's panel cast,
you should be, because it's great, um, so far, it's two for two on getting me to read a comic
that, uh, that I would have never heard of, or ever read, and both of them I loved. I liked
Gwenpool last week, and this week I read All of the Vision, which is actually a complete run,
it's 12 issues, and it's finished, and it was, it was great, um, once again, I went out to try and
buy it, but they didn't have it at Barnes and Noble, so, um, one day I'll read a comic that
is available, but yeah, uh, it's a good time, you should read that comic, and you should listen to
the panel cast, and I guess that's about it. I don't, I don't want to talk too much on this
podcast about the specifics of, like, what I've been up to, because usually those are things
that will be represented in a video. It was one thing to talk about, like, the spreadsheets and
stuff before, because that's an element of my work that doesn't actually appear on camera,
but like, I've been watching, uh, Tsukuyomi Moonphase for the last few days, and it's like,
everything I have to say about it, it's gonna be in the, the video about it, you know, and about
Shinbo, though I guess what I could talk about is the fact that because the show is pretty boring,
and I kind of lost interest in it about eight episodes in, I've just had it on on my second
monitor, and I've been like, really struggling to pay enough attention to it, you know, to, to get
what I need, because I'm just watching it for research, I, I don't care about the story at all,
and it has elements that I really, really like, the character designs are incredible, um, there's
just great facial expressions, a lot of the characters are likable, and the show is good
when it's just like a light-hearted, fun comedy, but it, it's rarely that, it's usually this really
boring, plot-driven show where the story is fucking generic and garbage, uh, so that's what
I've been struggling through, just smoked the last cigarette that I had in my pack, and I'm gonna
quit now, um, because that's getting to be a dangerous hobby, so getting out of that,
it's Halloween today, I've got a video coming out, kind of regret that I didn't, um, I meant to post a
like, a Patreon post of three months worth of vlogs and unpatron videos, I still might,
I always feel bad when I load multiple Patreon posts into the very end of the month, because I
feel like, you know, it suddenly hits people with multiple things to pay for right at the very end,
um, which feels like a transparent money grab, but it just so happens that because,
you know, we get paid by the month, we always have a plan to like, this video has to be out on
this week, this one on this week, and this one by the end of the month, and so like, you know,
I both want to post this like, hey, here's three months of, uh, three months of content that hadn't
been patroned yet, and then also this new video, and part of the reason that I don't want to do it,
um, like, I don't want to do my post first, because I pay DeVoo 40% of whatever I make on Patreon,
uh, for the videos that he edits, so anytime I make a Patreon post for something that wasn't edited
by the DeVoo, and you know, with each post you make exponentially less money, like, the first of the
month is where I make what it actually says on Patreon, and then each one after that is way, way
less, because most people have a monthly cap on how much they'll pay, so, you know, each video is
basically worth more the earlier into the month it's posted, and so if I post up like, um, you know,
my, just like, here's three months worth of vlogs that never got patroned, then that will make more
than the video that DeVoo's editing, and that means that DeVoo gets paid a smaller amount,
than he would, uh, you know, if his video came out before my post, so, you know, I know DeVoo needs
the money right now, so I'm kind of hoping his video comes out first, I mean, I could just pay
him 40% of the other one instead, but yeah, because of all that, I was hesitating on posting it,
but now it's the last day of the month, so if I post both on the very last day, then it, I don't
know, it feels weird to me, I don't know if it feels weird to the audience, no one's ever complained
about me doing it that way, no one ever complains that, like, at the very end of every month is when
a ton more content comes out than normal, you know, like, when we had Kurokono Basket and
Mob Psycho in, like, the same day, and then also at the end of the month is when the commentaries
come out, so there's like a four-hour commentary, and then, like, you know, all this other stuff,
I don't know if people treat that more as like a wow, I'm getting so much content all at once,
or if it's like a wow, you've completely, you know, charged me all this shit I wasn't expecting
right at the end of the month, but, I mean, everyone has their monthly limit set in place, so,
you know, as long as, as long as you have that monthly limit, then you know, you know what
you're in for with how much can be spent by you by the end of the month, I don't know, Patreon's
weird. I'm thinking about doing some kind of really long vlog, or maybe even podcast about
the weird nature of living in a world where people fund you, and the nature of the cult of
personality that's forming, and how I get scared for people sometimes when they have to start up
a Patreon or something, especially if they're starting it on the back of something controversial,
because you kind of become like someone who's not just doing your job, but who's trying to
convince people that you are worth spending money on, you know, and a lot more of like
stuff that's not connected directly to your work becomes a part of it, where like, you know,
if I said something that deeply offended a contingent of my audience, or I got involved in some kind
of drama, then that could affect my, you know, like my Patreon, whereas, I mean, that would happen
with other stuff, and that's partly also what I'd want to get into into this podcast. In fact,
I should just stop talking about this now, because I'm gonna have a whole thing about it. It's an
interesting sort of conundrum, and I've been in a unique position to observe it as an early adopter
of Patreon, who's been using it for God, three years? Holy shit, that's a lot. Well, yeah,
that's about it for this episode. I just wanted to do one last segment before, before wrapping it up.
So, I'll see you next week, and have a good time. Have a nice night, and listen to this soothing music.