All right, so on this week's show I'm going to do something a little, I'm going to try
something a little different and if I don't like it or if it seems if it comes off as weird and
inauthentic then I'm going to stop you know before I get too far into this podcast. You know I've
been listening, I always listen back to the decompression chamber after I post it and the last
episode I enjoyed it, I enjoyed getting to decompress and like make all these points about myself and
but you know I feel like I've been on on the defensive a lot on this show and just in general
this show is it's always one of two things it's always either me talking about how great things
are going and all these like amazing plans I have or how awesome my life is or defending myself
or the way I've done something from either someone or I don't know from the world at large
I always feel like this this show is kind of self aggrandizing and you know I've the biggest
accusation I get all the time like the biggest criticism people have of me is that I have a
giant ego or that I'm uh or I'm arrogant and stuff like that and I it's it's weird for me hearing
those complaints because I don't really think of that as a problem like and I explained this on a
on a previous episode you know on the the decompression chamber how like that egos kind of
what keeps me afloat and what helps me to get through um and I don't really understand how ego
is a problem it's like I'm doing something I like and I'm enjoying myself and uh you know
like where where does it become bad for me I understand how it can be bad for for someone
else for the audience like I can understand how it could it could piss you off to listen to someone
be so like kind of smug and self-satisfied and enjoying themselves too much maybe um especially
if you feel like you're not enjoying yourself in the same way I get that I get it as a reason not
to like me but as a criticism like as a constructive criticism it's not helpful because the ego
is not damaging me at all it's not hurting me it's not hurting uh you know what I'm doing
so I want to talk about I want to criticize myself on this episode I don't know how well this is
gonna go I'm not good at it not because I'm so egotistical that I can't see my flaws but because
a for me when people talk about their problems um I don't know there's always something weird
about it it always comes off as kind of kind of fake and half-hearted it's like well you obviously
well you obviously you know I don't know how to fucking phrase this I'm bad at even talking about
the concept of talking bad about myself it's like these are these are thoughts that are kind of
internal to me you know it's like if I talk about a problem I have with myself then the question
becomes why am I not fixing it you know like if if it's something I recognize as an issue
then either people are going to tell me how to fix it or I already know how to fix it but I'm not
for some reason and it's like to me those this kind of things should are things you internalize
because you know as soon as you admit it you feel like you have to work on it or something and um
maybe that's like maybe that's what I'm getting at here maybe I'm afraid to work on these issues
or I feel like it's wrong to to brag about your problems you know to like to to be like huh I'm
so shitty you know it just comes off I was like well dude then fucking fix it you know if it's such
a big problem then why the fuck are you complaining about it on the internet as opposed to fixing it
but but at the same time I don't necessarily feel that way when other people complain about themselves
I do sometimes especially if people complain about themselves all the time that I'm just like
at some point I just kind of think well if all you if all you ever do is have this issue why are
you not putting everything you have into resolving this issue you know especially for people who have
more issues than not like if your life is nothing but you know self-criticism and and constantly
worrying about like how shit you are then how is your entire focus not trying to fix those elements
you know but but nonetheless I have I have things about myself that I like look I look at me and I
think god I fucking hate you for that you know I hate that you do that um and some of them some of
these things are not even things that I that I so much hate about myself because I enjoy doing them
like I enjoy being shitty in some ways I just know that it's it's bad of me or for me to do these
things so for instance one that comes to mind immediately uh because I experience this all the
time especially on procrastinators like either on the show or in the chat which is that I am
incredibly full of shit I am just absolutely full of shit um in like most arguments I get into
because I don't have many convictions I don't really like have a stance like a concrete stance
in the world that I'm like fighting for or arguing for I will just argue whatever side of an issue
is currently interesting to me you know or like if someone phrases something in a way that I find
questionable then I'll take the opposite stance you know just because I find what they said
questionable even if I don't even really care or I'm not really on that side this comes up a lot
when I argue with Nate where I'm not really arguing with Nate because I disagree with him
but because I don't like how he's framed his argument you know and you you'll hear this on
procrastinators all the time and it happens in the chat where we'll get into these long arguments
and then at some point he realizes that I don't actually disagree with like the overall point
he's trying to make I just hate how he's argued it and therefore at that point it all just like the
the discussion breaks down and it just becomes why the fuck are we arguing you know because I'll
argue all day because I don't mind arguing you know I'll keep I I just want I guess I have
more of a problem with language than I do with ideas you know like any idea can be presented
in a way that I'll end up agreeing with it if you if you word it correctly you know if if
if I understand where you're coming from and I and I think that the way you've presented the
idea makes sense which is why again I have that abradolph linkler mindset of just every every idea
makes sense to me it's just a matter of of putting it in the right terms you know there's very few
arguments that I like really have a hard line stance on like the idea that there is no objectivity
in art like that's one of the few things that I have always taken the same stance and will always
argue the same way but when it comes to social issues political issues just general discussions
especially discussions like about words and language I'll just play whatever side of the field
I find most entertaining to me at the moment you know and sort of derail things so here's an example
from today where I was sort of pseudo arguing with mumke in the pcp chat because mumke is now
officially a part of the pcp and um I think this was today it was over the fact that everyone in
the pcp has started showing interest in like uh making games in one form or another not not
literally everybody but a bunch of members like a bunch of people have been talking about uh game
ideas that they have going into 2017 and I was joking that 2017 is the year that we all start
making games and then Nate was talking about how you know he's made a game before and how it's
incredibly difficult and the all this stuff and I was like uh you know well the game I'm
positing uh is is you know incredibly simple like the whole idea of it is that it's simple
you play it with one button because it's not really a game and uh and like you know someone
asked like what's the gameplay and I said there is no gameplay and mumke was like it's not a
fucking game then and he came in with this argument about how it's like you know uh you've all heard
the game what is a game what isn't a game debate and like I have no stake in it I don't care either
way and the way I put it to mumke was like I argued with them for a little bit and I was literally
arguing both angles at the same time like I will simultaneously agreeing with him that it's not a
game but also disagreeing that the the definition of a game should be so limiting because I'm so
uninvested in it that I just I just want the argument to be presented in a sensical way like I
like to me giving a shit about whether like what is considered a game is like completely
retarded like I don't I think like even having that argument is like I could not possibly care
less about anything in the world and I don't think anything matters less in the universe
than like the label of what is or isn't a game who fucking cares because I'm very anti labels in
general I hate that everything is so like sequestered into mediums and genres and stuff when so much of
the best stuff out there is stuff that breaks those conventions and is like stuff that that is not
easily classifiable into you know into um categories like that I just generally hate labels and
categories but at the same time I do agree that it's not really a game like by standard definitions
of like like what is a game it shouldn't be called a game the thing I'm talking about so like
yeah I see it both ways and I can argue both ways and I'm only arguing because I think it's funny
and I'm totally full of shit so so I'm like literally arguing both sides of the field against
him and he was just like what like he was just like you know like fuck you you're a fucking idiot and
I'm like yeah I know like I know I'm being an idiot like I just I'm this happens all the time on
PCP like when I said something like uh how do you even know that I'm uh that I'm trying to speak
English in my videos you know like stuff like that where yeah of course I'm speaking English in my
videos but I'm just like I'm I'm broadening it out to like such a philosophical level just to
like win the argument and by for my like for me winning an argument doesn't mean proving I'm right
it just means like proving that being right doesn't matter that neither like like that that if you
argue something hard enough if you argue it to like a broad enough scale then it's all meaningless
you know that's like why I was such like a nihilistic mindset about everything because
you can kind of win every argument that way just like it only matters if you care and if
you don't if you if you bring the argument to a point where you make it apparent that you don't care
then it's all meaningless it all it all means it all just goes out the window and that's the way I
argue because I have no convictions I don't care about any side in any argument I don't care about
being right I don't care about like you know actually progressing the conversation I just care
about playing these little lingual games and you know and saying fuck it all and having any
stances lame like that's kind of how I end up spiraling my conversations
now I enjoy doing it so that's why it's a problem that like I don't know what the solution is
because I do think it makes me a total douchebag and it makes me impossible to talk to it's like
when you get to that point in the argument you're just frustrated and especially because
you know it always makes me look like the winner even if I'm not even if like you know in any
conventional sense of a debate I'm just making an ass of myself but there's never a sense of me
like admitting that I've lost you never get to a point where I'm like okay you've out argued me
because all I do is take the argument to such an extreme and broad place that there's no way to win
it's just over like you all I've done is removed the game out from under you you know um I've just
made myself above it all and even if you see me as like obviously wrong and and just a dick you know
it doesn't affect me it never makes me feel like I lost or feel like the bad guy you know and that's
why something like the pokemon race where you know the real drama is ben versus Nate in that race
right like Nate they both tried they tried really hard and they had a sincere you know dedication
the reason that that video is entertaining is because Nate tried so fucking hard that when he
lost it had a real gravitas to it but no one likes competing against me because I won't take it
seriously because if I did win I would of course lord it over everyone I would brag to the end of
the earth and I'd be like I'm the greatest guy ever but if I lose it doesn't matter because nothing
matters and I don't care about anything and I have no stakes in anything and and uh and it's all meaningless
so yeah I guess it's kind of like Nate was talking about how one of his in the in the
pokemon sun and moon podcast how he really hates the rival how because every time you beat how he
just goes like wow that sure was a fun match you know like we sure are buddy buddy pals and he's
like there's no sensation of victory from from like beating someone like that and that's me
that's who I am is that guy who when I lose it's like well you know playing games is for idiots
but when I win it's ha fuck you you lost um yeah and I think that just I think it makes me a total
douchebag and uh you know it's hard it's a hard thing to call someone out on so I think that's why
I've never quite been you know people get frustrated with me in the moment in things like that but it's
hard to express the overall problem of like why what like what is what is it that I'm doing that
you can sense I'm being a dick but you're not sure why this is why it's because I have this
affectation that nothing matters to me and and like and it's just a defense mechanism it's a way
to make it so you never have to feel aggravated or a sense of loss you know I never feel like
I've lost anything because I refuse to take anything seriously um but it also means that
you know when I taste victory it's only like it's always backhanded I mean I always feel
like a dick even when I win at something just because you know I only celebrate victories
that I was like bound to win anyways so I don't know uh yeah that's that point I guess that was
fun to talk about I think I rambled and repeated myself a lot but maybe you'll hear more about me
talking about why I'm a total dick in this uh the compression chamber
okay
all right I guess we'll mix this up a little we'll we'll jump back and forth between different types
of stuff in this this podcast this time it's gonna be more about a certain a certain fear of mine
I don't know if I'll call this a character weakness because it makes me sound like the
good guy in this scenario um whereas the last one was just me being a dick but uh it is a
it is sort of a weakness of character I guess um you know you often see this trope in media of the
character who um tries way too hard to be strong like someone who tries to take on the weight of
everything on themselves and to never crack and to always look like you know to try to be the rock
the person who never sheds a tear in front of anybody or shows any fear you know in front of
their crew so to speak because they're trying to hold everyone else together you know and there's
always this sort of this the sense of almost fear um that that person is one day going to
snap under the pressure that they're not that like all that all that strength and resolve you know
they eventually the hardships they're facing will eat away at them and it'll just break them
you know and sometimes these characters are presented as heroes and as the strongest people
sometimes are the ones who you're the most concerned about and usually there's you know what
what holds these people together is that there's someone that they find that they can show their
real insecurity to that they can break down in front of you know I'm thinking the first thing
that comes to mind when I think of this you know it's not quite a perfect example because this
character kind of flies off the handle would be in arreca seven when you have uh uh what's his name
you have talho and the guy the guy who holland who uh you know both of them are sort of inauthentic
around everyone else but you know like because because holland's always putting on this this
character of being this like larger than life figure but when he's with talho he can emote
and have those moments where he just kind of breaks down and um you know there's a lot of
characters like that in media and I'm always afraid that I might be one of those people
and I realize that because I'm comparing myself to a heroic trait then this sounds like you know
this sounds like egotistical self aggrandizement but I I don't know that it's that the people around
me are weak or that I just perceive everyone is weak you know because I'm so egotistical I feel
like I'm supposed to be stronger that I'm supposed to present myself as someone who is flippant and
doesn't care and is is unaffected it doesn't get emotional and never feels you know hardship
because everyone around me seems to be dealing with worse you know and I always feel like I have to
be the one person who is not complaining you know the one person who is doing okay so that
everyone else feels comfortable like like you know we're not all on a sinking ship someone
steering it upward you know and I want to look like that guy I don't even know how much I do
look like that guy you know and I I do know that like for for the pcp you know Nate has often said
for instance that he sees me as sort of like you know a beacon of of hope that this group is going
to do well because I'm succeeding so much and I seem to be having such a good life that it's like
we can all do it you know um and I want that I want to look that way but there are lots of things
that you know that bother me that are that are that go wrong or that I just feel emotional so
there's oftentimes you know several days in a row where I just feel like total dog shit and just
and don't even want to you know deal with anything and this decompression chamber is helpful for that
and that's kind of part of why it started because again as I've said in previous episodes um you
know the sort of incentive to have a show where it's just me is that there is no none of the
putting on airs that comes from talking to another person there's none of the turning myself into
someone else and it's not that I'm always completely vulnerable to my audience but um and it's it's
it's funny too because I know that most of the people I'm talking about who I try to be strong
in front of listen to this show anyways you know um so this is kind of an admittance to everyone
in those people probably again I don't think anyone sees themselves as relying on me or possibly
is relying on me you know maybe no one is you know it's just how I feel like I have to be
and part of it I would say this this sort of mindset originated from my teen years because
of the fact that I am the eldest of three brothers and my dad is exceedingly strong
he like me puts on that character of like everything will work out and part of the reason
for that is that my mom you know while she is a very you know tough person she is comparatively
in terms of like emotions she's very emotional you know she will be worried very intensely
worried she's very pessimistic she's very um you know if things are going wrong she expects them to
go very wrong and my dad has always been someone who's constantly reassuring her he's always playing
the oh it's not that bad it's gonna be okay I know what I'm doing I know how we can get out of this
you know my dad always has that optimistic mindset just to counterbalance my mom's pessimism
and when I reached a certain age I realized that I too have to do that for my mom you know because
she will become concerned if me or victor or shade you know if it seems like things aren't
going well for us or if we're concerned about something you know it it becomes almost a bigger
concern for her than it ever was for me you know so I won't talk about hardships my mom even though
I know she wants me to I know she would want me to and she would want to help but I feel like
things that I can deal with that like are that aren't that big a deal to me become a bigger deal
both for me and her if I tell her you know so I won't say anything I'd rather come to my dad who
is you know who will who will be able to deal with it you know but even him the problem with my dad
is that there's just too many problems he has a difficulty understanding and he has his like you
know he's the type of person to like give advice and it kind of expect you to take that advice even
if you know to me it's like well I know what I'm doing you know I'm just here to vent I don't I
don't I don't know I don't have an easy time venting to my parents I've never been able to
tell them about anything going like wrong with me um not because they're not you know they're
totally there for me I just personally would rather keep it to myself you know because I don't feel
like um like worrying them will help me more I feel like I should deal with it you know and then
I've also got two little brothers who you know I wanted to be a role model for who I wanted to be
strong for so I you know again have always put on that face of like being a leader I've always been
the leader of my brothers you know they've they've followed me through whatever I've been doing all
these years you know um we're always very close they're always right right behind me and I've
always been sort of a leader amongst you know friends I have and stuff like that I've always
been someone who constantly reassures everyone and and unlike my dad who does it with this sort of
brazen manly confidence my dad's just like you know he's a man of the house kind of guy he's the
kind of guy who's like you know this is what we're gonna do and it's gonna work and we're gonna do
it and he's very confident I on the other hand approach everything in a much more sarcastic way
where to me it's more about my dad suggests like believe in me because I know what I'm doing and
I will get it done for me it's more like um you're silly to be thinking of like this is a problem
like I constantly make people like I make people out to be overreacting anytime they're they're uh
they're complaining about something I always make it out like of course things are gonna work out
you know like yeah no shit everything like everything's good everything always goes well
you know if you just give it time everything always goes well like that's the way I present
things as if that's a given and like I think DeVu is the person who's called me out on this the most
because the fact that I like you know he is often like has problems with things that I'll just be
like eh you know if you just give it like five minutes it'll work and then like it doesn't work
and he's like you always say that's gonna work it you know you're like you're wrong like half the time
but like because I I I approach everything in this way that I'm just like eh you know everything
always works everything's good the world makes sense you know um that's just my way of reassuring
people like trying to make them feel like uh like nothing's nothing's ever that big a deal
whatever thing you think is a big deal it's actually not a big deal and everything makes
sense and it's all gonna work you know um that's just kind of my approach to life and
to to bring that back a little bit to like you know what I was initially talking about just
I feel like I constantly have like I'm constantly putting on this persona of like
everything goes perfectly for me everything makes sense and flows in a logical manner and um
you know I I know that like DeVu really likes in spite of the fact that he calls me out on the
way I approach you know uh the other thing like he's he's very much about the idea that like if you
exude confidence then the confidence will come you know like if you're if you're always thinking
that you're doing things right then you'll end up doing things right and uh and I kind of act the
same way but I have I have doubts about it you know like things aren't always perfect for me
things aren't always great things aren't always working out sometimes I just I'm just like I
don't know what the fuck I'm doing you know I have no idea what I'm doing with my life or
I'm just I'm just angry or anxious or bored or like just upset about something and I never feel like
there's someone I can talk to about it because if I do then it breaks the charade it breaks the
image it breaks the idea that you know that there is someone who's doing it all right and that like
you know I I sort of want to be this symbol of like what you're all hoping life can be
you're all hoping you can live your dreams and you can do art and make money and be happy
you know and I don't want to suggest to you that even after all that effort and all that work
it's still gonna be shit like half the time because you're just a fundamentally broken person
who has you know problems with addiction and you're not satisfied with your body and you never
leave the house and you you know you never get laid at all for years on end and you know
and you sit around and drink alone and sometimes stare into space all day and the only sense of
accomplishment that you ever feel is when you throw together random 10 minute vlogs
and you're so self-satisfied about your own content that you'll put something out you know
every single day and feel like you're getting something done when all of it is just like
pennies in the ocean of actually accomplishing something when you could be if you put your
mind to it like putting out you know like more mainstream content that you know everybody
wants and you know you could make and it would make you more money and it would help out you
and all your people and you'd be moving way faster towards anything you wanted more money better
place you know getting all your fucking friends down here but because you're so stuck in this
this mood driven mindset where all you do is you just I'm just talking about myself by the way
I don't know why I'm still in the second person but like maybe it was just easier to rant about
that if I'm talking if I if I pretend it's not me but you know I I'm so governed by moods I'm so
impulsive I just want to do whatever is interesting to me right now and I never want to do anything
that's like takes setup or time or work or effort you know the reason I put out videos every day
is not because I have an amazing work ethic in fact it's pretty much the opposite the reason I
put out videos every day is because I just attach myself to every flight of fancy that I have and I
just want to do that and that works decently for me because people do watch those videos and enjoy
them and that's great but I could be if I set my mind to it making stuff that everyone would enjoy
all the time you know I could be having a video every third day on the digi bro channel you know
with a hundred thousand to five hundred thousand views and that would be growing at such an exponential
rate if I had videos coming out that frequently of that level of quality so many people would start
tuning in that I'd have way more ad revenue way more patreon money devout get a raise devout would
have a car you know my friends would be able to we'd all be fucking moved in somewhere you know
and doing these things that we've been talking about that we've been slowly making progress
towards for years but because none of us just buckles down and just does the fucking thing
you know we we all kind of like slowly get it done while we pussyfoot around and procrastinate and
you know worry about other shit that we haven't just like just buckled down and made the thing
because we're all flawed people who can't just do that you know none of us has the mindset to just
become a purely engine of success and I keep painting myself like one I keep making it look like
hey you know someone's at least got their stuff together enough that they're they're still rising
through the ranks you know I'm making I'm doing it but I could be doing so much better and you know
and of course I agonize about it every day every day that I you know when I fucking spend a week
what the fuck have I done this week I don't know and I know it's because it's a holiday season but
this is why vacations freak me out and I shouldn't take them anytime I'm like I'm just gonna not do
work for a week then at the end of that week it doesn't matter what the reason is that I didn't
do work for that week it doesn't matter that I was hanging out with family or that I was like
trying to take a sabbatical or that's like oh we have enough work done there's no reason to do more
except that there's always a reason to do more because if you do more then more will come out of
it that's why Casey Neistat has the do more tattoo on his hand and the work harder tattoo on his arm
because he sees those and he goes you're right I should just work it doesn't matter that I don't
have to you know complacency will kill you it killed him he talks about that you know how there
was a two-year period where he didn't do shit because he had two million dollars from selling
his show to HBO and it made his life miserable it was the worst he felt because he wasn't working
you know and every time I take a week off and I don't work and I look back at it I'm just like
what the fuck am I doing why am I why I don't care about the fucking holidays why am I sitting
around for five days drinking and fucking making vlogs about my dream anime stuff that comes into
my head like out of nowhere and I make a vlog and then I feel satisfied well I made a video
today so what does it matter yeah I could I could I could be done with the next part of
shaft uh studies you haven't even started on the next video yet I could be done with it I could be
probably I think I could be done with it yeah I could be done with that if I've been working
on it this whole time since finishing writing shinbo in the 2000s um you know I could be started
on the next thing I could be using this this last week of the year to write uh you know videos for
all of january to have ready for devu so he has work so he knows what he's doing you know
um so we don't start january with this whole clusterfuck of the goddamn plebe in the weave and
then who knows what my channel ends up being for the rest of the month oh god
that was too much decompression you unzipped me me
this might end up being a longer decompression chamber because I'm still in the same night
and I'm already on a third recording so uh you know I don't know how long this might go on for
but I want to expand a little bit on the idea of complacency and also to share one of the
the pieces of advice I've gotten that stuck with me the most out of anything I've ever heard
you know sometimes you have those those things that someone says to you or I mean I don't know
if you have this but I've I've had a few of these instances where someone said something that like
just has replayed in my mind forever and this one by far the most um so just because it's
remained true over all the years which is that I was talking to ghost lightning once my friend who
I've often described as my mentor fellow anime blogger who um who I visited for a time in the
Philippines in 2011 and uh we were talking about probably some project I was trying to do like
some you know I was probably telling him about some idea I had that I wanted to get off the ground
but that I was like probably bitching about how I wasn't doing it and um honestly sometimes I'm
shocked by the level of patience that ghost lightning had with me because it's a level of
patience that I wouldn't have had like that current me would not have for a like 18 year old
complaining about the things that I would complain about um you know with the lack of
self-awareness but I I'm sure I was bitching about something and I about how I was not in the mood
to do it and he like like really hit me hard with his line he was like you always let yourself
be controlled by these moods and like you need to stop that like I don't remember exactly the
phrasing but the advice was to stop letting myself be controlled by my mood and it was like mind
blowing to me because I never thought about that that that's like a thing that you have to fight
like that like what it means to me in many ways what it means to be an adult or to be like mature
and to be able to like handle your scandal as the phrase goes um is the ability to work through
what you don't feel like doing you know to do it anyways even though you don't feel like it because
it's necessary or it's the right thing to do or it will you know benefit you that to me is like
that's the entire definition of what it means to be like you know uh to be um to be an adult who
gets things done because I mean that's entirely what work is you know work is when you do a thing
you don't want to do because you understand the long-term benefits of it and uh you and you know
can make progress and you know in the time since then I mean it was a while before I that that advice
like haunted me but I did not beat that for a long time you know I did not get past that problem of
having you know just letting my mood completely control me because I would if you know I would
only do things I was in the mood for and like I would be in certain moods for days on end or just
like very rarely actually be in the mood to get something done so you know it was a big problem
that I would let myself be so controlled by whatever mood I was in and I've I've learned how
to beat that I now know how to put like to say to override my mood and just fucking do something
and the funny thing about moods easy to change it's it's it's actually like you know you can
be in a mood you can be in like a rut you can be think like I'm bored and upset or something and
you can stay that way all day but if you actually flip the switch in your mind where you realize
like I can change this then it's it's pretty easy to do for me it's often a matter of just
throwing on the right music and like getting out of my chair you know I've had days where I'm like
sitting there for hours just like just kind of you know ruminating on something negative and
just being in a shit mood and then like I realize I'm listening to depressing music and sitting in
a chair and you know and eating cheese balls all day and then like at some point I go wait let's
stop this and I just like throw on some onomatoguchi and get up and like do some push-ups or go for a
walk or go eat something and I come back and I feel completely different you know you can do things
to affect your mood and oftentimes just working through it will make you feel better just like
for me actually getting something done always feels good it doesn't matter like sometimes
I get something done and I feel great and then I immediately going back to feel like shit as soon
as I'm not working again but like working on something always feels good it's always a pick
me up you know I'm never sad when I'm doing a decompression chamber because I'm recording
you know I'm having fun making a recording so you know that at least an hour out of my week
that I'm recording this podcast is a time I'm feeling pretty fine you know and sometimes
the result of that can change how I felt from before especially if I've just made something
that's actually like really beneficial like anytime I write a digi bro video I feel great
afterwards because it's like um sometimes they come out of nowhere it's it's you know I feel
like shit all day and then suddenly I finally get an idea that I really want to do and I do it and
it's like this has made my whole month because you know I only really have to have a video every week
and if even if I spend like two days completely agonizing over getting the video like you're
coming up with an idea that I want to do and it's like just sucks those two days are grueling
and then I write that video on the third day then that weight is gone it's like oh now I've
saved the week and the rest of the week is fine I don't feel that pressure anymore you know like
accomplishing things and working can be so you know can really get me out of those moods and um
so I still am someone who lets myself be governed by moods a lot but I know how to fight it but the
problem is that I face now is complacency and I really do think that like when people talk about
complacency it sounds so phony right to hear someone who's like successful say that like
that success can be a problem but it really can because hunger and like desire for more
is such a huge motivating factor to like it really pumps you up and like makes you want to keep
working and again working is the best feeling I have you know it's the thing I want to do the most
I feel lazy when I'm not working I feel shitty when I'm not working I feel like I'm not going
anywhere like my life is stagnating and nothing's really happening you know it's only when I'm
accomplishing more than I have already done that I feel you know reignited either in the form of
making more money or feeling like I'm making creative progress like I'm getting better you know
those are the best feelings but when you're complacent it's when you realize that yeah you could be
getting better you could be making more money but you don't have to that's the danger that success
can bring is when you don't have to so you you just you think well it doesn't matter if I just do
whatever I'm in the mood for it doesn't matter if I spend all day you know being a shit because I
know by the end of the month I'll get those videos written you know at some point this month I've
got to have a huge burst of creativity where I write four videos in a short span of time and
that's all I really need you know it's enough to make the money to keep the channel growing to keep
me but it's not progress it's stagnation and when these periods happen when I have like
times where I don't really care about what's going on it tends to even though the same amount of
stuff is coming out you know I don't feel like it's getting better and it's not necessarily the money's
not going up you know you can tell at times when I'm very passionate when I'm like really getting
things done it seems like I make more money even though there's no real logical reason for that to
be the case and maybe I'm wrong maybe it's just the way I look at the statistics depending on my
mood just feels that way you know and it feels like like I'm not getting anything done when I let
myself be lazy when I let myself go uh you know I already wrote the videos for this month so rather
than writing the ones for next month or rather than writing something even bigger and better rather
than getting a new thing done and expanding on my creativity I'm just gonna sit around you know
because I can why not but that's the thing sitting around makes you feel like garbage
these meat makes me feel like garbage makes me feel like nothing's happening makes me feel like
I'm not doing anything like I'm just stagnating like I'm getting worse as a person or or remaining
the same you know um this is what happens to me with like diet and weight loss and and quitting
things like the reason I keep going back to smoking um you know I bought a pack of cigarettes
yesterday just because I had a like what always happens is I think why do I have to stop like
nothing is making me stop the only reason to stop is this vague sense that I'll be better if I do it
you know but there's no there's no actual pressure to there's no pressure to stop eating out so much
there's no pressure to eat better to to look better to feel better you know all logically I should
just want those things but because I'm already like I'm already meeting my own demands for success
I don't feel like I have to do any of that who cares why do I need to look better why I need to
feel but then you know but then at the end of the day I'm sitting on my couch for hours at a time
going like I have no social life I feel kind of sickly and fat you know I'm not eating well
I feel wrong I feel imbalanced my head hurts because I've been smoking too much you know
and all of that is what puts me into the mindset of like well you know I gotta numb this somehow
let's either you know take a couple Advil or take drink as many beers as I can you know and then
and then drinking feels great but then there's that moment when you're drunk and then you can't
get anything done and you're like well now I'm useless so I guess I'll just go to bed and then
sleep for you know 12 hours every fucking day complacency is dangerous and you know I think a
lot of people view their vision of what success is is like you reach this level and then it's a
plateau from then on of happiness but there is none of that because if you plateau you become
unhappy the second you stop fighting is when you lose your drive to become better and to to keep
being good it's when you you you kind of realize the bare minimum you have to do and you just decide
to do that and that's when you stagnate and I'm not saying this is all happening to me because
the only reason I feel any of this stagnation is that my life is so open-ended and I work so fast
that's the only reason this happens because if you look at like the content I'm putting out you're
like well wait you're trying new things all the time you've got like all these new series you keep
opening up you know after dark so it's doing new things you've got all these you know new things
going on in digi bro where's where's the stagnation well the problem is that all that stuff only takes
up a small part of my day you know the amount of time I spend working on these videos and stuff
that's like a few hours the day is 24 hours long every day is a long day you know I sleep probably
10 to 12 hours of those so like you know it's not not as long but the time that I'm not making these
videos or consuming anime for these videos or like doing research is time I'm not doing anything
that's the stagnation time I do not monopolize my time well you know and like Casey Neistat with his
do more and work harder if you watch that guy's video about his fucking schedule he's never not
doing something never you know he's always either working or making movies or spending time with his
family or uh or you know traveling or doing whatever and he he works even when he travels
like on planes and stuff he only sleeps like four hours a night uh he's always you know he
works out every day he runs consistently he's always happy healthy and working harder and getting
better all hours of day you know so even though yes I still work enough to innovate I still do
enough to make progress because I can work so fast and I get things done so quickly
because I'm like a fucking engine I'm just a machine that cranks out stuff
nonetheless there's a lot of every day that is just sitting around feeling wrong you know
and that's the part of me that I have a problem with that's harder to communicate to people
and it's harder to be like to make people understand that like
being satisfied with with with my career does not mean that I'm satisfied with my life because I
know I could be doing more and doing better and not letting my mood control me you know fucking 10
hours out of the day well it's been almost a month since I recorded the first 50 minutes that you
just listened to of this podcast I recorded it at the end of December and I spent a lot of time
really deliberating about whether or not I was going to release it whether I was going to continue
the episode a big part of me just wanted to delete it not let it see the light of day
because I just I feel so weird about talking about these things and you know
listening to it back I couldn't help but feel like somehow I came off as even more arrogant
and self aggrandizing when complaining about myself than I ever do when bragging about myself
it's quite incredible but I ended up deciding I wanted to post this particularly when I came
up with this last section I wanted to record this for the last like week or so and I finally have
time now that rad cons fully over and I've had a day to sleep and do stuff so I want to talk about
the hedgehog's dilemma as described in Neon Genesis Evangelion something that connected
with me very strongly back when I watched the show and which still does which is the idea that
you know when two hedgehogs try to get close to one another they end up stabbing each other
with their pins and the closer they get the more it hurts and so they just try to avoid people
altogether I think this is generally true of human relationships the closer you get to someone
the more it's going to hurt you and I feel like the more aware of that you are the scarier it
becomes I think most people are able to form relationships because they mostly see and focus
on the good you know even though they might fight with someone or or have problems with them
they really you know internalize the idea that they they love the person or they're close to them
and I try to do that as best I can but I always have this the sensation when it comes to
you know with with other people of like I I kind of how about I put it this way I feel
the pins going into me and I don't make any sound I don't scream you know I don't tell them
that it hurts I just let them get closer and I feel the pain and I don't say anything I just
eventually turn and go the other way I just eventually leave all at once and um you know
this is a big problem in my life in general and what I'm trying to rectify and that was an extreme
example of of me taking this kind of action but let me let me break it down in a in a more simplistic
way I have some friends who when you let's say get into a fight with them or if there's something
they disagree with you on fundamentally some of my friends will just let it roll off of them
they might form a general opinion of you like you know if you repeatedly piss them off
then they generally think that guy pisses me off but they don't think about the individual reasons
why I want to say that Nate is like this you know he doesn't ever seem to bring up like hey when you
did this that pissed me off he can if pressed but he will more have a general idea of like you've
pissed me off in this way a bunch of times you know but but not really focus on the specifics too much
then I have friends who will get pissed off about very specific things and will let you know
they will tell you they will hold it against you then is a good example of this you know you'll
have heard it on the pcp he will hold a grudge about specific things and he will keep reminding you
of that thing until you've done something to rectify it or to placate him now I I don't know how
many other people are like this I'm sure everyone is on some level but this is generally how I operate
is that I get mad about specific things and I stay mad about them but I don't say anything
I just bottle it all up I just can because I don't want to me the best way to deal with it is to just
let it go right if we keep arguing about it we're just going to keep getting more heated
but at the same time what I'm failing to realize is that you know some things can actually be resolved
sometimes an infraction can be talked through and reach a conclusion and that's what I'm trying to
do more of I'm trying to you know bring up when I have an issue because I have this tendency to
just sit back and accumulate all these different little incidents or someone's making me mad
and I don't tell them just how mad those incidents have made me it just builds up and builds up and
I've got this this list and I'll tell other people you know I'll be like I can't believe what this
guy said to me today you know and tell them the story but I don't bring it up to people's faces
this is true of absolutely everyone if you're listening to this and you're thinking he's
talking about me I am because I'm talking about everyone I know anyone who does anything that
makes me mad I keep tally I've got them all in my mind and I've told other people about the things
that you've done that made me mad but I probably haven't told you and you'll know if I have
because again I'm trying to rectify this I'm trying to become someone who lets you know
you know when I've got a problem and tries to resolve it and tries to come to terms with it
because I've been so bad at that in the past and what I basically have done with some people
in my life is just let all those little things accumulate until I just cut ties you'll remember
on a previous podcast I talked about my friend D I just called him D this was a guy who was a part
of my circle of friends and over time everyone developed a problem with him everyone I knew
had an issue with D because just he would constantly do things that made everyone pissed off
it was just like a never-ending cycle every time we saw him he would do something to make someone
mad and it got to a point where me and my friends would literally just sit around and shit talk D
all day it was like the number one thing we did as a group was to talk about how much this guy
pissed us off and the reason we did that is because D was the kind of person who you could not
like make realize his faults you know and if you did if you brought something up if you
made him realize that he defended you he would apologize and he would try to do something for
you but I don't I don't want that I don't want people trying to do things for me I just want
you to recognize that you've done something wrong and then to not do it again but D's not like that
he would do it again you know he would he would never recognize what the mistake was he would
think he fucked up in that instance and try to rectify that instance without realizing that he's
just doing the same mistake over and over again now obviously D is someone who you know I'm probably
better off without having him in my life but so long went by that I just didn't even confront him
and I would just sit back and cowardly wait for someone to do it I just wanted someone to finally
snap on him and give me an excuse to ride that wave and just you know have him out of my life
for a while we thought it was gonna be my mom of all people because you know all my friends hung
out at my house and D had done enough things that pissed off even my parents that my mom had straight
up said like if he does one more thing that pisses me off I'm kicking him out and I literally
hoped that it would happen I spent like days just thinking God I hope he fucking does something
that pisses off my mom so she'll kick him out and I won't have to you know because I wouldn't I was
I just couldn't bring myself to do it myself I'd rather just let these things wither away I'd rather
let people who I don't you know who I don't want to talk to anymore I'd rather just ignore them
until they go away and eventually D actually did piss off my brother Victor badly enough
that he excised him from the group he flew off the handle on D you know and uh and I just
like you know I let it happen and I rode the wave and I just never talked to him again like I didn't
even really make it clear that I also had a problem with him but the fact that I never tried to contact
him I think he you know got it and he kind the way the way it went down it was kind of like he
had done an infraction on our whole household you know he'd been kicked out of the house and uh
I haven't spoken to him since it's been like two and a half years maybe no about two years I guess
so you know that's the way I deal with problems ignore them until they go away until someone
deals with it until you know I can just burn the bridge break the ties or just they they stop
trying to contact me you know this is how I've avoided a lot of people online when there's a
lot of people who I you know was friends with for a little while then decided I wasn't really getting
out of anything out of the relationship or that it was just annoying or that I didn't want to
participate anymore so I just stopped talking to them stopped responding to their messages you know
they'd message me here and there I'd never respond you know I don't tell people hey I don't want to
be friends with you anymore I just let it let it go but there are some relationships I do want to
protect there are some people like everyone in the pcp who you know I want us to to continue to
work together to continue to be friends to continue to have things to do and so I think it's dangerous
when you know if some if I get mad at someone like that someone who I I actually care about
and I just hold on to that anger and don't say anything and let it fester and build because
what happens when you do that when you don't confront the issue is that it just builds on itself
because there's been no resolution so all I can do is think about that thing over and over again
and just keep thinking like you know and then if something like that happens again that it just
builds on to the pile and I haven't let the person know that it bothers me you know I haven't told
them hey you have to stop doing this or else you know eventually you know I'm gonna it's gonna
feel like the cons of knowing you outweigh the pros and I have to let people know that and I hope
I can do that you know and I know it's like it's kind of a selfish way of thinking in the first
place even that like I'm the gatekeeper to our friendship but I do feel like you know this is a
horrible thing to say but I feel like I treat relationships in the same way that I treat
watching anime that every episode that we go through together I take stock of is this worth
continuing you know should I keep keep you know interacting with this show or should I drop it
and I feel the same way about people like you know if I feel like I'm net gaining from knowing you
from having your relationship with you then I'll keep it going and as soon as I start to feel like
you're a drain on me you're you know you're taking more energy than giving then I just drop it
and uh and I've dropped a lot of connections there's a lot of people there's a lot of
unresponded to mail in my inboxes on every social media site you know there's lots of people who I
just stopped talking to and then that last mail they sent trying to reconnect came and I just didn't
bother responding and uh you know I've probably lost a lot of connections I that I you know that
that are worthwhile that way but it's just I have such a hard time facing people facing the issues I
have you know and part of it is that I'm a harsh critic you know I am a harsh mean person who will
tell you exactly what I think is the problem in no uncertain terms you know if I have to
if it comes down to it and I'm going to tell you like what I think it's going to be brutal and harsh
and there's a lot of people I don't think can take that and I will say that one of the great
things about the pcp members in particular is that we can all take it you know we harshly
criticize each other all the time we criticize each other right on the show sometimes and there are
some criticisms that some of us can't take and we'll get mad about you know there are certain
things that I would avoid saying to certain members of the pcp but if it was something
that it came down to like this is a make or break for our friendship you need to know I have this
problem with you what allows me to be friends with those people is that they can hear that and
understand it you know and if they couldn't then that would be the end that's what I really value
out of people to give an example of a case where that you know it wasn't that way my ex-girlfriend
the whole time I was dating her like six months I had an endless litany of issues with her you
know there were so many things she did that made me mad that made me think I want this over but I
would never bring any of them up because I didn't think she could take it because her mindset would
not have been to hear those things and to say okay I'll try to you know to change or I'll try to
make this work instead what she would have said is well I guess I'm just a terrible person and
you know I guess you hate me and I guess we should break up and I didn't want to break up in spite
of all those issues you know but when we finally did break up then it was like well you know all
I had to think about was all the problems you know she she is another person who later tried to
contact me and I just ignored it I just didn't respond I didn't you know I just said well I've
already excised you from my life you are already gone to me you know so you know I really want to
cherish the connections I have with people who can take it who can you know hear that they've
done something that that makes me mad and then think you know to weigh the consequences to say
how much do I value my friendship with digi and if the answer is enough to change something to or
to rectify this problem then you know then to go through with it and I hope that I can change
for other people too you know again I'm I'm a very selfish person I do view these at a very one
sided lens it's like if you make me mad then it's then it's over if I make you mad then you know
I don't know how you'll take it I don't know if there's people who like I've never had the sense
that I've ever pissed anyone off enough that they stopped being my friend and that's what makes me
wonder if I'm just like a shit person you know for for thinking and acting this way because I
don't know anyone who's done this to me I've never had anyone just stop talking to me seemingly
out of frustration with me I've never had anyone at least not in my adult life maybe in high school
but even then I can't really remember you know I can't remember a time when someone was just like
ignoring me clearly out of the fact that they you know didn't want to talk to me anymore I don't
even know if people interpret me ignoring them that way I'm sure some have I'm sure to some people
it's been very clear you know um but you know I feel like I'm just an asshole and that I look at
people in a different and perhaps wrong way and I kind of resent myself for it
this whole fucking podcast has been very heavy for me it's I mean I don't feel like these things
would probably be as heavy to other people because a lot of this probably sounds like
either relatable or you know maybe maybe it doesn't sound like a big issue to someone else
because you're not experiencing these things they might just sound interesting you know it might
like I doubt anyone heard what I just said and thought wow you're a monster they probably thought
huh what a different way of looking at the world or actually that's exactly how I think
but for me it's like you know I'm literally describing to you things that I absolutely
hate about myself that's what this whole podcast has been you know trudging up the elements of me
that I most hate and explaining them I really hate that I have such a tendency to just abandon people
to leave people at the wayside to not talk about my problems to hole up in my you know in my room
in my space you know that's what I do when I'm when I when I don't want to face a problem I just
sit in my room you know I don't leave when I don't want to like go out into the world when I don't
want to speak to someone I just fucking I just become a hermit and that's what I always return to
I feel like I've been in this state for much of my life I feel like I've been retreating from society
for most of my life hiding you know hiding in this this safe cozy room surrounded by all this
cutesy imagery and cute anime girls trying to like pacify and distract me trying to give me
something to look at other than myself and the world outside and all the things that I fear
you know and this isn't even getting into my broad paranoias you know these are problems I have just
with with myself that are very specific but on a on a more broad scale I'm also extremely paranoid
about everything and I hate that about myself too but it's it's in so many different forms
like I have an utter paranoia that everyone in the world is constantly judging me or wants me dead
or that society is ultimately going to side against me at some point you know I have I guess
sort of a persecution complex like I spent I've spent a lot of time thinking about like
how I would explain myself uh in in like court or to a police officer for for any number of
reasons involving society changing like I always feel like you know one day I'm gonna be the the
main character in 1984 or something you know like the the the person who has broken society's
rules in such a way that I'm going to have to stand trial and that in spite of my perfect logic
and arguments the system will fail me you know I'm always afraid that that everyone's out to get me
that nothing's really on my side and you know I have I have a really hard time talking to people
about my problems talking to people about what's stressing me out you know at the very least
you know it's nice to have friends I can bitch to bitch and complain to and at least I have had
that I've pretty much always had you know someone around that I can just talk to in isolation
and complain about things you know I'm glad I've got friends living with me you know like Ben and
DeVue and my brother Victor who I can talk to and like share some of this stress and they can go
yeah I I get why that's a problem you know but at the same time living with other people you know
is exactly what causes these stresses and I'm there's there's parts of me that's constantly going like
should I just fucking run away and be by myself would I be happier by myself or by forging
new connections or by embracing the ones I have more you know we just did Radcon 2 and from the
outside Radcon 2 probably looks like a big party where we all just have fun and make stuff but
Radcon is incredibly stressful it is it it's just a powder keg of stress and fucking you know
intensity and everyone was feeling it I think I mean the amount of times that we were all just
standing around going oh god I want to die I wish I was dead you know I mean we joke about those
kind of things all the time whenever we're stressed out but like we always mean it you know when
someone is standing around saying I want to die even as a joke it means they're stressed out it means
that they do want to die on some level you know I don't think that phrase is ever completely a joke
I don't think anyone ever says the phrase I want to die and doesn't mean it on some level
and we were just standing around parroting it back and forth at each other for days
because what Radcon is is not just hanging out with your friends it's living with nine
extreme personalities who all have their own ways of living their own desires and are thrust into an
ultimately uncomfortable situation of living in a house with a bunch of other guys for fucking a
week you know sleeping in the open in on couches you know five people in one room and I don't even
have a lot of that problem I slept you know in my room by myself a lot of the time but I had to
organize all of it I have to drive everyone around you know figure out what everyone is eating what
everyone can afford you know everyone's got different levels of income different interests
different you know ways of life and we've got one car and and there are two cars me and Victor's
you know and different sleep schedules you know I want to be up all night Ben is always up all
night Nate wakes up early you know we're trying to we're just trying to force all these people who
live very different lives to live enough of the same life for a week to get a bunch of stuff done
and I've said this before that the best to me the best possible future for the pcp
is for us all to live in the same area not in the same house because living with other people
is kind of a nightmare you know every single every little difference between your lifestyles
is is monumental and sometimes it's not that big a deal you know um like me and Ben live on
opposite sides of the house and we rarely interact because Ben almost never wants to go out for any
reason he doesn't want to you know he stays in his room he doesn't want to do anything so that's fine
but like DeVu he needs food all the time DeVu eat like just goes through tons of fresh food so
you know I end up driving him around and we'll go to like the store or something
we'll drag Ben along sometimes and it's just like that little tiny incongruence in our lifestyles
that I only need to grocery shop every two weeks or so but he needs to every like five days to a
week is a problem you know because it means that either I have to get in my car when I don't want
to and drive from the grocery store or he has to go a few days without food you know waiting for me
to be willing to take him it's such a small thing but it causes stress for both of us you know
and I'm think you know DeVu tells me I need groceries and I'm thinking about that in the
back of my mind well I'm trying to get all this other stuff done and he's you know sitting around
hungry for a couple extra days living with other people is just a non-stop source of issues unless
you're trying to live together you know you're trying to do one thing like when you get married
and you have a family then it's like you are unified in your goals you are trying to mold your
lives around one another but I'm not trying to do that with the PCP I want to work with them I don't
want to live with them or like them you know and when you put us all in one place together like that
then it's not just us working together it's us living together and it is stressful you know it's
not like we got into a bunch of big fights I mean we did get into some pretty heated arguments
you know uh those of you who've listened to the apescape video will hear a part where like me
and DeVu get into an argument and I straight up leave the room because I was so heated you know
um sometimes stuff like that happens it's and it's kind of just a powder keg it's it's a bunch
of heated personalities you know and it was even more stressful because we had the only way to make
radcon happen was to base it around work you know and like I've talked a lot about how I love working
and I love working with these guys but man I would much rather I would much rather if we had just
spent a week hanging out you know if it was just a week of us hanging out not having cameras not
working on stuff that would have been great but we couldn't have afforded that we could not afford
you know four months after the previous radcon to have everyone pay for flights again to come down
here and do this thing for a week you know what made us able to do it was the Kickstarter and the
Kickstarter needed a product we can't just run a Kickstarter for us hanging out I don't think
I don't I don't think we'd that would work out maybe I should have tried
but it's such a shame you know it's a shame we didn't just hang out it's a shame we put ourselves
into an even more stressful situation where we had to get certain videos done on certain days
videos that involved watching stuff with each other you know we and so many people had so many
projects they wanted to get done and everyone wanted to be a part of everything so you've got
you know what should be like two person let's plays that are just fun and relaxing turn into
nine person chaotic nightmares where everyone's screaming over each other you know it's just
not a good way to live you should not live with with eight other extreme personalities
and and little resources you know with everyone living in the same space and and not having enough
cars to go around and it really made me like you know realize like yeah I the ideal way to live
would be all of us in the same area but I do not want to live with these guys I don't want us to
all share a roof I don't want and the problem is that that's the only reason that we're doing that
with me and Ben and DeVue is just simply that we can't afford it you know we can't afford we don't
have the money to all live in the same area if we did we'd just be doing that you know the only
reason we all live in this house is that we were able to split the rent extremely cheap
and um you know Ben would not be able to afford his own place definitely not DeVue could probably
not you know I don't pay him enough I don't make enough to pay him enough and really the only
reason I can't afford my own place is because I pay DeVue like I would have enough money to get my
own place but because I hire him because I want to have him employed by me you know I am putting
myself in his position where I have to split rent and have to live with him and Ben so you know
it's it's a very weird position to be in and I just want us to be as fast as possible I want
us to be in a situation where we can all have our own places and we can live near each other and just
you know work together and hang out because those are the things that that friends and business
partners should do you should work together and you should hang out those are fun things hanging
out is fun you know I had a lot more fun in the later half of Radcon when it was just Jesse here
because even though I love all those guys you know I would love to hang out with Hippo every other day
you know I he's so much fun to hang out with I love hanging out with Nate you know I love hanging
out with Munchie he was super fun I did I had never really had a chance to hang out with Munchie
until now and he was really you know he was great to have around but having him around along with
everyone else was hellish you know and I'd love it if we all just kind of lived in a space in a
in a in a play in one city you know and I could go hey let's go to lunch on Monday you know and
catch up and hang out and have a good time hey let's go play a video game we don't even have to
record it if we don't want to you know when we were uh when Jesse when Jesse was the only one
left we spent a lot of time playing video games me and him and Ben spent one whole night recording
let's plays it was really fun um and then we did a bunch with Victor we were playing through all the
tony hot games and Jesse was getting really stressed out about the fact that like you know
he's trying to beat these games but he keeps failing at certain challenges and just getting mad
and being like I just want to rush through this game because of the fact that we didn't have enough
to talk about to keep the podcast interesting you know because it's we were recording it so
there was this kind of need to be entertaining and Jesse feels that even more strongly than I do
like I was perfectly willing to just like kick back and relax and let it be like a goofy video
that wasn't really meant to be something all that serious but I've noticed watching Jesse that when
you turn a camera on him he transforms you know Jesse cannot stand not being an entertainer
when when there's when there's something recording at least that's how it seems to me
so you know I could see him getting stressed out and I was it's on some level I was like I just
want to watch you play tony hawk you know I don't care about the lens play I don't care about this
whole conceit that we have to be you know working on something I'm just enjoying sitting here
reading comics and watching Jesse play tony hawk and I'd love to be able to do that and for that
not to require a seven thousand dollar Kickstarter and living in the same house and you know if if
I'm hungry I better take Jesse because we're we're you know he's not going to be able to eat otherwise
but then he's you know like does he want to he has to eat it whenever I'm hungry you know because
he's kind of stuck with me you know that's I guess most people probably know about these things I mean
I had a lot of issues living with my family you know and living with Ben and DeVue has ultimately
been less stressful than living with my family was on some levels because while I didn't have to
worry about them too much you know my parents there was one of the biggest stresses in our lives
was that we all ate dinner together and I'm not even sure why we did it for so long I guess just
because shade was still growing up we all just felt like you know like it was something we had to
connect with as a family or something but just for the longest time and also because I was cheap
and Victor was poor so like the idea that we got a free meal every day was a was definitely a plus
but the most stressful thing in our family is that none of us have the same taste
uh you know my mom's a vegetarian my dad quit red meat at some point now he's a vegan they're
both vegan now now that they live together alone um you know and me Victor and shade all of different
tastes we're all picky and we would like just spend like almost an hour like every day trying to
figure out what to make for dinner like arguing about what to make or deciding and like none of
us could really cook well and everything we made turned out kind of mediocre and it was just like
and and we go to the grocery store and argue so much about like what we were gonna get and it was
just it was just this huge amount of stress that's only caused by the fact that we live together
and have decided to do this thing together and as soon as I started buying my own groceries that
all went away that whole thing went away that huge source of stress went away you know and like the
stresses I have now living with Ben DeVu Victor and shade are comparatively minor um but I still
can't help but think man if we each had our own place it would be such a weight off of our shoulders
you know like I feel like DeVu would really thrive on his own you know and he's like because he has
a huge problem with the cleanliness of the house me and Ben are fucking slobs you know we don't do
anything and I could tell it really bothers DeVu and he doesn't want to have to be the only person
cleaning because it sucks you know because he's the only person who cares so obviously we're not
gonna do it because we don't care but it sucks for him because why should he have to do it all
just because we're slobs you know so like you I would love for him to be able to have his own
place I think he'd be happier that way you know and I'd be happier we'd all be happier
and so we've all been talking about this whole idea of where are we all gonna move like where
are we gonna go are we still gonna have a place together are we all gonna move into separate
houses in some other town there's no reason to stay in Virginia Beach this place is kind of blows
and as we've been talking about it I've kind of come to the realization like I don't know how much
I care about whether we all you know live in the same place in the same house you know like
I would prefer we had our own places as soon as possible and I know not everybody can afford it
but at the same time the level of compromise that we have to go through to to be in the same place
like um you know the two main cities we've been looking at moving to are Austin and Portland
and I personally would love to go to Austin because that has a lot more to offer me personally
it's a much more music-centric city and I'm a big music guy it's got lots of events you know
and Portland is fun and cool and I mean it has those things it has music it has events but it's
just not quite the same level and Austin just seems more attractive to me overall but like
if we are sharing a place then it's kind of everyone's decision you know if we're all if
me and Ben and DeVue have to share a play a room or whatever uh or whoever else we bring you know
Ben would rather go to Portland and some of the other PCP guys would rather go to Portland and
I'm sitting here thinking like am I going to keep compromising in order to have us all you
know live together or should I just go fucking live in Austin by myself you know I could do that
if I wanted to and I don't know I don't know the answer yet but I know that there is one clear
solution that will make all of these problems go away and that's making a lot more money if we all
made a lot more money none of this would be an issue you know if each of us could afford our own
place in the same city done there's no problem there's no issue you know if I could afford to both
live by myself and pay DeVue enough that he could live by himself no issue so that's
that's the that's where I'm going after this you know this whole podcast has been mired and
what are my current issues and the solution to a lot of my problems to the problem of stagnation
to the problem of complacency that I talked about earlier to the problem of not wanting to
live with other people but you know still wanting to maintain relationships with those people you
know with the least strain possible the problems all the problems I've talked about if I just make
a lot more money those problems go away whoever said money can't buy happiness is a fucking idiot
peace out
you
You