You all thought Digibro's decompression chamber was cancelled, didn't you?
Well it is.
I stopped doing them.
This is the special edition, yay!
Special depressing podcast, just for you guys.
And to see, I love this idea that the PCP is becoming this mishmash of hilarious comedy
shows and then just utterly, gutturally depressing solo podcasts.
So this one is going to get extra meta, because this is kind of a response to the second episode
of Tom's hyperbolic wine chamber.
And if you didn't listen to that one to summarize it, essentially it's Tom, as usual, being
very hard on himself and talking about his need to earn his keep in The Pro Crastinators
by feeling like he's under-talented and not doing enough, I don't know why he thinks
he has to earn his keep, no one's ever said anything of the sort, but you know, Tom's
always pretty down on himself.
Personally, I think Tom will always be in the PCP because I like Tom, I like having
him around, I hope he keeps living, um, might be selfish of me to say so, but uh, but anyways,
I want to respond to it, because in it, Tom has some admiration for me and Jesse and
Monkey Jones.
And this is not just about Tom, this is also about a lot of The Pro Crastinators fans,
a lot of my fans in general, a lot of people who look up to us, um, you know, even within
our own group, I mean, just as Tom looks at, you know, looks at us and feels like he's
not doing enough or isn't, isn't talented enough, I've always felt the same way looking
at Jesse, I've always felt Jesse was exponentially more talented than me, and you know, I really
struggle with the idea that the videos I make aren't really doing anything artistically
in comparison to what Jesse's doing, you know, and I mean, I have a lot more self-confidence
and I enjoy my own content a lot more than I think Tom enjoys his own content.
So like I'm able to find a reason for it to exist, uh, but you know, I still feel it
pales in comparison to Jesse, but I think the difference I have in mindset here and
that like the perspective I want everyone to keep, everybody, everybody in our audience,
Tom, myself, everyone, is that nothing about this is admirable, nothing about what any
of us is doing is admirable, and none of us is really happy doing this.
I need, I need to stress this.
If you look up to us because you want your life to be like us, what you're going to
get is not going to be a life of satisfaction and happiness.
You're not going, if you're trying to pursue, I want to have the exact same career that
those guys have or the same art that they have, like none of us is someone who sits
around being satisfied with our lives and, and is like, and is like super okay with the
way things stand or the way they are, you know, and maybe you think it'll be different
for you, maybe you think it's not going to turn out the same way, but I just want you
to like before you go looking up to what we do, just remember that we're doing this largely
out of being broken people who can't function normally in society, either because of the
circumstances surrounding us, or just because I don't know, I don't know what's wrong
with us.
I mean, Monkey Jones has a channel called Monkey's Countdown to Suicide in which he
is constantly reassuring everyone of the fact that he will kill himself.
He hates being alive.
He is a depressed suicidal man.
You know, it's cool that he got a book written, like I know that's what Tom was admiring
about him is that Tom, you know, also wants to write a book and he read Monkeys and he
really admired Monkeys writing, but writing that book has not made Monkey not suicidal.
And all he's gotten out of it is that it paid his rent for one month.
You know, it's sold incredibly well for a self-published book, which is to say it made
like $600, you know, and paid his rent for one month at a crucial moment when he was
in between moving and, you know, needed that money because he couldn't get a job during
that month.
So it's not like he's got spending money as a result of the book.
It just covered his living expense.
You know, his Patreon's not super successful or anything.
He's not living off of it.
He hopes to be possibly, but I'm pretty sure when he moves to North Carolina, he's going
to get a normal job, you know, writing that book.
That book will never be publishable.
He knows it himself.
The book has an 11-year-old rubbing cum all over her body.
Spoilers.
He doesn't like it when I tell people that.
So that's, you know, being Monkey Jones, you might see it as artistically fulfilling
because you admire his art more than your own, but Monkey Jones himself is not happy
with it.
Like if you were in his shoes, you wouldn't be happy.
He's not a happy person.
If you were Endless Jess, Endless Jess, his art comes almost exclusively through adversity,
through just the horrible things that are happening to him constantly.
This is a man who was already depressed and didn't want to fly across the country to make
a bunch of videos at the time that he, you know, that we did a Kickstarter, so he kind
of had to, but he flies down here, you know, works through his crushing depression for
just long enough to finish these videos, goes home, and his fucking house is flooded and
everything's ruined.
And he's sick and he's just like, you know, sifting through the ashes of his dead life,
trying to harness nuggets of art out of that just to make money to live.
Jesse doesn't want to be doing YouTube videos.
He's doing it because he's broke and he has no other choice, you know?
I just, he's not happy with it.
He doesn't like his work that much.
He's usually dissatisfied with his videos.
He's looking back at them, you know, like, as much as we look up to it, as much as we
look at it and go, wow, Jesse, the stuff you're doing is so amazing, I admire you so much.
None of that matters to him because where that art is coming from is a, you know, it's
a place that's, it's a dark place.
And this is sort of the subject of this song that me and Jesse made called Paradise recently,
because a while back, me and Jesse made this song called Get Action.
And the point of this song was to shit on everybody who wasn't putting in as much work
as we were, but it was not necessarily meant to inspire people, which is what it did.
And we both saw it as kind of ironic and maybe even dangerous.
I mean, I do say in the song, you know, you have to get action, you got to put your life
on the line, you got to go all out if you want to be as good as us.
But it wasn't my intention to suggest that you want to be as good as us.
I was merely like, like the anger of that song is in people looking at me like I don't
know what I'm doing.
You know, like the point of it was to say, I am amazing at this, I'm built for this,
I've done nothing but practice this, this is my life.
So don't, don't try to say, like don't even look at me for advice unless you're willing
to put this level of insane effort in.
But it's not me saying that you should put this level of insane effort in, that you
should become this person.
Because when I look at what I am, I spend 50% of all my time sitting around wondering
what the fuck am I doing with my life.
You know, I sleep for ridiculous amounts of my day.
I sleep through as much of the day as possible and the only way that I manage to get through
because of the fact that there's nothing happening in my life.
The reason I'm so productive is not because I have a great work ethic, in fact I don't
even think I have a good work ethic because actual work, like work that, like if I wanted
to be making money and doing like the right kind of videos and like putting out stuff
that's gonna advance my career and stuff like that or like sometimes I write, I have a main
series video that needs to get done and I put it off for days to just go make a bunch
of bullshit and I'm not making the bullshit because I think it's good work, I'm doing
it because I'm fucking bored and I don't know what else to do with myself, I don't
know how to live a normal life, I don't know how to do anything other than make YouTube
videos, I'm just a machine built for this.
It's not admirable, it produces fun art for all of you but like wanting to be like me,
I don't think you should and keep in mind because in everyone else's case I can say
like they're throwing themselves against a brick wall with maybe seemingly no reward,
no matter how much Jesse works he can't get himself out of that shitty house, no matter
how much Tom works he can't get himself out of his shitty house, no matter how much
Monkey works, well we don't know, Monkey's kind of up in the air because he's about
to move, Hippo just wants to have a breakthrough, he's making all these videos, just trying
to have one of them get big enough that his channel can actually sustain, Hippo's talking
all the time about how he's not sure if he should keep doing YouTube forever because
it just hasn't fucking broken through, it's been three years you know and for all of them
there's that aspect but that's not true of me, I am successful, I made $50,000 last year,
I made more than a lot of your parents probably made, you know I made a lot of money, I had
a successful year, this is a career, this is a real career for me, that hasn't made
it happy, it's given me lots of perks, it's given me great ways to get through this crushing
nihilistic depression, you know, I'm able to survive and to come off as like you know enjoying
myself because I constantly distract myself, I constantly make videos because when I'm
not making videos I'm just sitting around with myself and the only ways that I know
how to escape that are to just go and eat, you know I go out to a restaurant and I try
to waste as much time as I can, I go out you know I fucking drive across town, go to some
far flung restaurant and I have a nice meal and I enjoy myself, yeah that's cool, it's
a perk that I get for having so much money and being successful on YouTube but it's just
there to make me not think about what I'm doing at home, you know I've developed a shopping
addiction because every day I want to go out and go somewhere and be not at home for as
long as possible so I feel like I'm doing anything with my life so I'll go out to just some store
and just wander around until I buy something, you know just to just to have that thrill of
purchasing a thing and taking it home, you know, I'll, I drink all the time, you know I get bored,
I can't stand being alone with my thoughts so I just start drinking, you know, or I make another
video, just do anything to distract me from the fact that I'm not doing anything and I don't know
how to do anything, making all this money hasn't taught me how to do that, it hasn't taught me
how to get out of the house, how to how to meet new people, how to like make connections, how to
figure out what's wrong because this is not how I envisioned my life was going to be when I was
growing up, you know, like I always thought that the road towards success was going to be from
escaping this, like I thought when, because this is what I've been doing since I was a teenager,
I've been locked in my room, you know, sitting on the internet talking about anime for over 10 years
now, this is all I've ever been doing and back then when it didn't seem like there was a career
to be made out of this, when it seemed like this was just this was just throwing shit into the void
that no one would ever care about, you know, which is how it was for over five years, may I remind
everyone, I have only been successful for as long as I was doing this completely unsuccessfully
to an audience of no one, you know, I started anime writing in 2007, I spent five years before I even
had a YouTube channel, you know, and even then another year before it was successful enough to
consider a job, you know, and another two years after that before it was a job that that was
above minimum wage, but like in all that time, I always thought that the road to being successful
would mean getting out of the house, going out and finding something to do out in the world,
and so the fact that I found work here that I was able to be successful without changing anything,
what that feels like it's telling me is that I won't ever change anything, like why
why would I change if I can be successful just staying here, but this kind of success,
this doesn't feel right to me, like I'm not happy with the idea that I'm a guy who just
lives in his room all the time, I want to be someone who goes out and does things and has
stories to tell, who meets people, who goes places, like I really admire and look up to people who
have like a storied life, you know, and I don't have that, all I have is, I mean I do all these
fucking podcasts and let's plays where always the story is, well I watched a lot of anime this week
and I made a whole bunch of videos, that's what I was up to, you know, like I can't tell stories
about what's happened in my life, because nothing's happening, and like there's a huge part of me that
always thought things would be different, and I'm standing here like, but how do I even justify it,
how do I even justify leaving the house, you know, and it's not like I want to do something else,
because I love doing this job, but I could, like I just don't know how to branch out, I don't know
where to go, because I'm just broken, I'm broken in the mind, the reason I'm able to have such
an amazing work ethic is because I am broken in the mind, so before you go looking up to me
and what I do, take a step back and ask yourself, do you actually want this life,
because this is what it will cost you, you'll have to spend five plus years working in complete
obscurity just to hone your skills, that's what it took, I've been doing this non-stop for 10 years,
I started my anime blog in 2007, I was writing, there were times in 2009, I had a post out every
day, sometimes three posts a day, you know, I had 59 posts in the month of February 2009,
I remember that, no one read any of those, I was just grinding material, and then finally it got good
enough and I figured out a platform where people would actually watch the shit, and then another
five years to get actually successful, you know, I've got 10,000 hours in this shit, that's why
I'm good at it, so first you gotta be willing to just waste years of your life, and I got lucky
in that I got to waste those years young, you know, if you're already my age, get ready to
waste the next 10, I mean you probably have a leg up on 15 year old me who was just garbage
at writing, you know, it had no worldview whatsoever because I was so young, you've got a leg up on
that, but expect to take some time, you know, now the next thing you have to be ready for is to lose
all social connections in all of your friends, I used to have a group of friends who was at my
house all the time, none of them are here anymore, I don't talk to any of them because we have nothing
in common, because all I do is work, this is my whole life, I don't relate to anybody, the only
people I relate to are other people doing the same thing, which is why I'm in the PCP and why
those are my only fucking friends, so you have to be ready to burn away your social connections,
to spend all your time on this, to burn away your health, because in the process of trying
to make videos constantly, you will sit in a chair for, you know, dozens of hours a day,
I know there's only two dozen in a day, but you know, I sit in this chair 12 hours a day,
that's a fair statement, you know, assuming I'm awake for that long out of a day, I am always
here working and I just don't, you know, I don't really find time for health and upkeep and personal
fucking like grooming or anything, like that stuff doesn't come naturally to me, all of my teeth
are falling out of my fucking skull, I keep getting fatter, I've become an alcoholic, I was addicted
to cigarettes for a little while, you know, I'm trying to keep away from that, but I'm fairly
certain I'm gonna end up smoking again before too very long, because it just looks too cool not to do
it, like, you know, I quit smoking and I quit caffeine for the last few weeks, because of the
fact that I started having anxiety attacks and, you know, I looked up what causes anxiety and it
was a lot of the things I was doing, so I cut those things out and I have stopped having anxiety
problems since doing that, it's just made me incredibly lethargic and I've just been laying
around staring at the ceiling all day, you know, like, I'm always bouncing between those two extremes,
it's always either I don't want to do anything or I want to do everything and it's driving me insane
and why do I still live here and why am I still acting this way and am I ever going to be normal
because even when I find myself in situations where I should be able to talk to people,
I completely fail at it, you know, I just, I don't want people to look at me and think that
because I'm making videos all the time and I'm making lots of money that you want that life,
because what that life comes with is just this constant feeling that you're doing something wrong,
that this wasn't what you were supposed to be doing, that like this isn't what the world,
you know, told you you were meant to be doing growing up, you know, and it's not that I don't
like this job because I do and this job is what's keeping me from being completely depressed because
anytime I try to just say I'm going to put distance between myself and this job,
I just do nothing, you know, I don't know how to do anything else, this job is the only thing I
have, but I don't think it's something to seek out, you know, if you have the opportunity to go
do something interesting and normal, I would encourage that, you know, normalcy is not a
bad thing to pursue, it's stability, it's like the idea of normal is that there's nothing wrong
with you, you know, like to do this kind of job you have to have something wrong with you,
something kind of broken, you know, and I mean not to say that it can't be fun, it can be and
if you do get really successful, like I totally encourage best guy ever to keep going on the
path he's going to eventually get successful at YouTube and to, you know, make enough money
out because he's going to treat it like he treats his job anyways, you know, it's just going to be
a more creatively fulfilling version of what he was doing and I kind of almost admire all these
YouTubers who do just like treat it like work, you know, these guys who are just doing it as a
job because the way people consume it doesn't change if you do it as a job versus doing it as
art, you know, and I worry that guys like us are just inspiring a whole a whole fucking group of
people who are setting themselves up for disappointment because either you're going to go down the
road of constantly straining yourself trying to become an artist and failing and getting depressed
over it or actually becoming an artist and realizing that it doesn't bring you any more
happiness than what you already had, you know, except in the the mere pride that you can eke
out of the fact that you did what you wanted to do, which I guess is what keeps us all going in the
long run. Anyway, yeah, that's that, I guess.
Nice.
Give me an mentor to all who admire me. I know it fired me if I had ever hired me.
And I mean by firing squad. I'm gayer than God and deserve to be deader than a door now.
That's love but I quit smoking so I won't be choking on anything other than dick for a while.
Never been in style. They didn't like something of a prick in its wild or some punk to act like
I stabbed someone just because I gave a one to their favorite show. Do you even know what is
an opinion? Objectivity doesn't exist. I told you a million times. There is no rule to write no
design. Only what you decide you like at this time and I hate myself. So don't emulate me unless
you're better with self-help.
Trillion fans ain't worth a damn. They ain't worth one friend. I can't call my man.
Ambition is living how others won't floor a vision and a mission. Getting what others don't but
that's missing the mark. Given every spark makes your heart dark because ambition is a prison.
Not a walk in the park. I've had best friends tell me that they envy me and look with jealousy
like I'm the enemy, like I'm a rival. But when you ain't a rival to me, I'm rival. My survival
two miles of trials would be tragedy if not for the fact that I'm getting back to my family.
Nothing else helps or is held to have you mad at me because I'm broken. I don't know how long
you've spent. Since I've seen the sun or put my lungs with oxygen, I'm too far gone. I take
norminess over this. Gotta check the pulse of my wrist to know I exist.
I go wild, I go wild, I go wild.