The Pro Crastinators Podcast is a non-commercial podcast that is based on a non-commercial topic.
It is a non-commercial podcast that is based on a non-commercial topic.
That goddamn vape. I had that vape for four days and I broke it.
It has a cap that you're supposed to be able to screw off, but for whatever reason the screw off cap was super tight.
And I couldn't get it off. And in my attempt to get it off I broke the glass that contains the fluid.
And none of the vape stores in town had replacement glass, so I had to order it online for the specific model of vape that I have.
So now I'm smoking again until my glass comes in for the vape, which of course the only place that sold it was only standard shipping at a three to four weeks rate.
You know, it's like it's not coming till December.
So yeah, bought a vape, broke it immediately, even though I was loving it.
I was totally in love with this vape and I managed to break it so quickly, just trying to get this fucking cap off.
Anyways, so this past week I've been doing practically nothing but reading comics.
I've been talking about comics at the end of each of these decompression chambers briefly.
And of course this was all inspired by Jesse having his panel cast, which I don't know if episode three of that will be out by the time this comes out,
but I did a little guest spot on it towards the very end where we talked about the new issue of Gwenpool since that's sort of what started this whole thing.
And rather than talk about the specific comics I've been reading, I want to talk about why this is happening.
Why am I so into comics right now?
And you know, I've always had an interest in different mediums besides anime.
Obviously I take a lot of interest in film, TV shows, comic books, music, which I am pretty diehard into.
I'd say I know quite a lot about music.
Just every form of art essentially I have some interest in, especially the mediums that really get discussed and the stuff that people analyze and talk about and cherish and collect, all that kind of stuff.
And with comics I talked about sort of how I got an in with comics in the last podcast, like how I sort of figured out what they're like and that made it easier to start reading them.
But as for why I'm so intensely into it right now, it's that as an anime fan, I've kind of talked about in the last podcast so I feel like I'm reaching the end of anime.
Like that I've watched so much of the good stuff and there's only so much of it left.
There's only so much left that I need to consume before I can kind of move on from anime.
I mean, I'll still be watching it forever and there'll always be new stuff coming out.
But for instance, this year, 2016, in fact let's just take the first half of this year, because I have completed everything I intended to from the first half of this year.
I watched all the winter and all of the summer shows with a couple of exceptions in the process of my Finish or Fail series.
And not one thing that I watched, did I score a 9 out of 10 or above.
Not one single thing that came out in the first half of this year was that amazing that I would give it a 9 or above.
I mean, it's not so much that this is a complaint about this being a week year, which I haven't even watched any of the summer or fall shows.
So I might have said summer early, I meant winter and spring are the ones I've completed.
I'm sure there's probably something that's better than what I've watched so far and if not, it's not terrible to have a year where nothing is outright amazing.
But I feel like I've gotten to the point where it is a struggle for me to find an anime I haven't seen that's a 9 out of 10 or above.
Like, you know, if you get into a medium and you watch all the classics, then what's left?
You know, all that's left after the classics is the stuff that's just kinda good.
And for me, so much of what so many of the anime that I finish now, so often when I go out and do a marathon, when I do finish or fail and just, you know, watch a whole bunch of shows in one big clump,
or when I do board of second chances or something, or any of the stuff I do to marathon shows.
Like, I'm really getting this baseline 7 out of 10 experience. That's most of what I'm gonna see.
Most of the shows I haven't watched already are gonna be the 7 out of 10 shows because if it's something really amazing, then chances are I found out about it already, you know?
And the reason I have to scour everything is just on that chance, on the chance that I stumble upon something that, you know, no one else thought was a 10 and I did.
Cause like, you know, if I only watched Consensus Masterpieces, I probably would never have seen, like, Log Horizon.
You know, a show that I think is extremely underrated, that for me is one of my favorite shows of all time and has so much going for it that I never saw talked about, and I still haven't really seen talked about to a great extent, you know?
I think there's so many shows like that that I'd be at risk of missing if I didn't try to seek out every good show.
But at the same time, like, you know, it takes a lot of effort now. It takes going through all this searching, and in the meantime I end up watching so many 7 out of 10s.
And what's great about being able to dive into comics is that I've got, you know, I know, I have a list, sort of, not like a real list, but in my mind, from having consumed so many charts and favorites list and heard so many recommendations,
I know a concrete list of, like, what are considered the classic comics, and I haven't read any of them.
So almost everything I read is going to be great. It's either going to be the best comic ever, or at least something really cool and interesting.
And even if it's not, I'm so new to it that even the, like, 7 out of 10 stuff is, like, something that I have never seen before, where, like, with anime I've seen everything, you know?
If there's some new cute girls doing cute things show that's not bad, but it's not not noteworthy or, like, memorable, you know, then it's not going to be anything extra for me.
I've seen them all. I know exactly what I'm getting myself into. But, like, with a comic, if I read something that's, like, it doesn't blow my mind, but it's just interesting enough, and I haven't really seen anything like it before, then it's still interesting.
So that's sort of what I've been experiencing this past week. It's just every single comic I've read has automatically been, like, a new fresh experience that adds to my overall understanding and appreciation of the medium, and that's kind of magical.
And I've always wanted that to happen, and I kind of wanted that to happen when I tried to get into comics back in 2012, which I read a whole bunch back then, but I never had this sense of, like, finding something complete to read.
Like, I didn't understand how comics worked, you know? I thought that it was all just giant series that go on forever, and, you know, there was very few that I read that I really got interested in, and none of them were over yet at the time where I didn't read the whole thing,
so it was just kind of this confusing, like, you know, haze of reading comics. Now I've already put down a few, like, full series that I'm like, that was great.
You know, I read The Vision Run. That was great. Silver Surfer Requiem wasn't amazing, but the artwork was so fucking good, and it was a complete story in, like, four chapters, and I was like, cool, I now know a thing.
I know an event in the timeline of The Silver Surfer. I know this thing that happened, and I've been reading Sandman, which is fucking amazing.
I'm about a little less than halfway through the whole series, and it's just been all kinds of cool-ass shit happening, and, yeah, it's been great, and it's something I can't get from anime right now.
And not to say that there's not plenty of good anime I haven't seen. I mean, my on-hold list stretches towards Infinity, and a lot of that is legitimately great stuff.
There's plenty of, like, classics that I still haven't watched, especially older ones, and I'd love to get to them at some point, but, like, it's so easy with comics right now to just, in one day, read, like, five comics that are all solid.
Today, I read, I woke up, I read, like, a whole arc of the Sandman, which was awesome, and then I read the first two volumes of The New 52 Wonder Woman, because I had bought, I read Volume 1 back in 2012, and I thought it was cool, and so I bought Volume 2, and I never read it.
And so today I read both volumes 1 and 2, and they were pretty good. And then I also read all of this series called Aries the God of War, just because I saw it on a recommendation chart.
That one wasn't very good. It was only five chapters. It was a pretty generic, like, basically taken, except with Aries and God's fighting, as opposed to Liam Neeson, but it was kind of corny, and I wasn't that into it.
But then, you know, I followed that up with, started reading Animal Man, and, unlike, ten chapters into Animal Man, that's pretty cool. So, yeah, like, all at once, you can just bowl through a bunch of comics, and have a great time with it.
Whereas with anime, you know, there's like a, there's a serious time investment if you want to watch even a short show. You know, like, a 13 episode show is four hours, and it's a lot more taxing, because you have to pay full attention.
You know, it takes up all of your senses. Whereas with a comic, I can listen to my own music, and, you know, and take a break whenever I want, kind of thing. A chapter is just a few, maybe ten minutes, as opposed to twenty-two, you know? So, yeah, it's just very easy to sit around and read comics forever.
So, I definitely have taken a huge interest in that medium, and it's even making me think about, like, man, I want to get into all the mediums this way. I want it to be like this for all of them. I just want that easy end.
I want that moment of realization, like, to happen for literature or for film, where I don't know what it is about movies, because obviously I've seen, like, fucking 750 movies in my lifetime, according to my Letterbox account, which is pretty complete.
So, it's not like I haven't seen a ton of movies. It's just weird to try to, like, get into them in a big way, I guess, just because movies are almost always short, and I'm not that into, like, that super short form media.
You know, even though I'm saying that comics are short, but, like, comics tend to have a lot of shit happen in those short spans of time. They're just really fast and constant, like, crazy fucking things are going on.
In comparison to the way movies are more of a, like, a slow build to making one point, whereas a comic will just make a thousand points by the time it's over. At least the ones I've been reading have been kind of like that.
But, you know, maybe one day I'll find the time to get into that as well. I definitely think that I'm just more interested in drawings in general than I am in, you know, live action.
I have much more of a predilection towards things that couldn't exist in reality than I do to things that could exist in reality, you know?
I'm much more interested in the fantastical and the mythological, just to an extent, like, with The Sandman.
Like, The Sandman could not be anything other than a comic. I don't even think it could be an animated series, really.
I think it's, like, perfect as it is, and I could not see it being adapted into anything else, which is probably why it hasn't been, really.
And, um, it's, yeah, it's just so imaginative and so out there. I guess it could be a book.
The only thing it could imagine as would be a novel, so even less information would be helpful for it.
But then you'd lose out on the awesome character designs.
So, yeah, and the reason I haven't started talking about comics is what allows me the time to do this is that, you know,
November is a month that I already, I did all my work for November before the month started, gave it all to DeVoo, he's been editing,
you know, we've been working on a couple little things here and there.
He wants me to do more, like, blogs and stuff, but honestly, I just haven't had any ideas for things to put him in.
So, in the meantime, I've, you know, I've got, like, a video or two planned for next month, but, like, I have a lot of time to read comics,
and you might be thinking, why not make videos about comics if you're so into it, why not do some reviews, why not talk about it,
and it's just a matter of the way that I like to do my content, which is to come at it from a very broad perspective.
I like, for me, every anime video I make is from the perspective of someone who has seen all the anime, you know,
like, it's kind of imperative to the way I write, where I talk about a series for what makes it unique as opposed to what it is,
like, something like Mob Psycho 100 that I did recently, where, like, I really just zeroed in on this one aspect of it
that was not something that is in any other anime I can think of, you know, in the exact way that it is in that show.
And so, to me, that's the most interesting way to write about something.
And when I think of a comic book, like, if I wrote about what's interesting to me about some of these comics I've read,
then I really run the risk of comic book fans being like, yeah, no shit, you know.
I mean, and I know some people are happy just to hear someone talking about something they like, no matter how basic,
but for me personally, the style I like to go for has that broad perspective.
So maybe eventually I will write about comics, but I feel like it's not something I could do until I've read, you know,
enough that I wouldn't be easily torn down by comic book fans if I said something wrong, you know.
I want to have a good enough grasp of the overall canon and the way that comics have moved over the years,
like what they've been up to, like, I'm slowly getting this sense that in the 80s and early 90s
they started like using lots of old superheroes as canon fodder.
Like, it seems like there's a lot of like individual chapters of stuff like Animal Man and the Sandman
where it'll be like, introduce some old DC characters so we can kill them.
Like just to have a really dark scene in a chapter which fits in with that, you know, this is the era when the Watchmen
and Vertigo took off and like, you know, it's a deconstructive era of comics when comics got serious and adult and stuff.
So yeah, it'd be interesting to, you know, study up on stuff like that.
But yeah, that's all I have to say about that for now.
I have this great fear with regards to what I do because I've seen so many other people fall into this sort of trap
and I'm afraid it'll happen to me.
See, I hear all the time people giving the advice that you shouldn't make your art your job
because then you'll grow to hate doing it.
I think it's weird that people give that advice because obviously most of the artists you know and are a fan of have made art their job.
You know, anyone who's ever made a movie or written a comic with any degree of mainstream success,
anyone who's made an anime, they're making their job their art.
And for many of us, that's the only way we can justify doing our art.
I mean, it's nice when you get to do art as a pastime, but like for some of us doing a normal job is soul-crushing
and we feel like that's keeping us from doing our art that we should be doing.
No, I've never had a problem with that.
The idea of making my art my job is totally cool with me and if anything, it makes the art even more satisfying.
When I get to make something and then it makes money, that's like the pinnacle of making the art for me.
My fear is a different one.
What I've observed is when you make your art your life, then your art runs the risk of becoming boring.
And here's what I mean.
I'm talking kind of about this modern phenomenon of like daily vloggers, people who do stuff daily, who do stuff all the time,
who are constantly making things about themselves.
Because what inevitably happens is that who you are becomes a guy who makes things about himself.
And that narrative is always going to just kind of eat its own tail, you know?
You see where I'm going with this, like for instance, I love Casey Neistat.
I love his vlogs.
But I got into him, you know, and started watching the daily vlogs and I watched like over a hundred of them.
And inevitably, they all start bleeding into each other.
I mean, if you watch one now, nothing's going to be in it you haven't seen before.
Very rarely will he do something really innovative in one of his vlogs.
And so it kind of becomes where the story of Casey Neistat is the story of a guy who makes a daily vlog, you know?
Not that that's really what he's doing.
I mean, his vlog takes up, you know, only so much of his day.
He always says, you know, what you're seeing is ten minutes of a 24-hour day in which I'm busy for those whole 24 hours.
And sure, he works on other things. He keeps himself busy.
But when you're watching just the daily vlog, it's like inevitably, it's just going to be like what it is.
It's repetitive.
You're always either watching him flying somewhere or watching him skateboarding around New York
or flying drones around New York, you know, or hanging out with one of the same couple of people
or doing some kind of speech somewhere.
Like, you're going to see those same things over and over and over and over again.
And he's not even the worst example.
And this is kind of why I don't follow Game Grumps anymore.
And Game Grumps has this channel called Grump Out,
which is like for a bunch of side things that they do that are not relevant to the main channel.
Even though I unfollowed Game Grumps like towards the beginning of this year, I still follow Grump Out.
So I still kind of see little bits and pieces of them.
And they just started up this interview series that's very similar to the PCP interviews,
except ours are three hours long and there's only 45 minutes.
But it's one of the Grumps who will interview one of the other Grumps for 45 minutes about what their life was
up until joining the Game Grumps.
And funnily enough, the least interesting interview that I've heard so far is the one where Aaron interviews Dan.
Now Dan is my favorite member of the Game Grumps.
He's a super cool guy. He's super nice and lovable.
And listening to him talk is relaxing and fun.
And it's what's made Game Grumps such a great show since he came on.
But what killed Game Grumps for me ultimately is that Dan only has so many stories.
Dan doesn't have a great memory.
He's not generally someone who, A, has a whole ton of memories.
And B will remember whether or not he's told the same stories before.
So listening to his interview was just kind of a reminder of all the problems I have with Game Grumps now,
which is that they just talk about the same shit.
Because, you know, their lives up until Game Grumps, once those stories are exhausted, there's nothing left to go on.
But their story now is they make Game Grumps.
But when they talk about what they've been up to, it's always the same thing.
It's, well, you know what we've been up to. We make Game Grumps, you know?
Like, of course, it's gonna be the same stuff.
And again, it's not that they record every single thing that they're up to in the day,
but the exciting things happening in their lives are all relative to the show you're already watching.
And I have long been worried about falling into this exact trap.
You know, and you hear this on the Digi Bros. show, where me and Victor would get together,
and I usually let Victor tell all the stories because Victor is doing film.
And like, he's not a YouTuber. His daily life is not explained anywhere.
So when he comes on the show, he's telling all these stories about all these things that I don't know about.
It'll be some film he was working on, and the film has nothing to do with the process of having made the film.
Whereas, like, this podcast that you're listening to right now, there is no, like, story to it
beyond the fact that it is about my life. You know, the process of its creation is the same thing as what it is.
So if you were to watch one of Victor's films that he's worked on, you won't learn about what he was doing on the film.
That is a story best explained on Digi Bros.
But me, I don't have a lot of that. And you'd hear this all the time, right?
You'd be like, well, I was working on this video that came out on my main channel, you know?
There's nothing more to it. It's like, the story of me making Shinbo in the 90s is that I watched all the Shinbo shows,
and I wrote a video, and DeVue edited it. There's nothing more complex to it.
So I'm always worried that I am going to inevitably become a boring person,
because, like, my pool of things to talk about is pretty much self-explanatory.
And that's why sometimes, that's why I constantly try to innovate with things.
Like, with the Digi Bro After Dark, I did, like, a huge amount of vlogs,
and then I've kind of calmed down with them a bit, and now I've started this podcast.
And, like, this podcast might seem like it's pretty much the same thing as After Dark,
but it's different in enough ways that it keeps things fresh, that it's not the exact same thing as Digi Bros.
Where, you know, as I explained in episode one of this, on Digi Bros., it's more of a conversation.
It's more of, like, me presenting myself to another person.
On After Dark, it's more idea-focused. Each video is about a certain idea.
This podcast is just free-form thought-dumping about what's going on with me right now, you know?
So, it's somewhat different. It's a different approach, and there's different nuances and different little flavors
you can get out of it that you might not get out of the other things I'm doing.
And I feel like it's imperative to keep innovating that way, because when you watch enough Game Grumps,
eventually it's just the same thing every episode.
Dan tells the same stories, Aaron cracks the same jokes. We already know their lives.
We already know the Game Grumps experience, and it just, it kind of all at once just got so dull
right around when, I would say, right at the end of last year.
Like, when they were wrapping up, dead-rising, and when Mario Maker just went on a little bit too long.
And now I have seen, and I haven't watched these videos yet, but I've seen that Grumps have been doing a few new things.
Like, they just did a playthrough of just Aaron playing Mega Man X, and I totally want to watch that.
Because that's new. You know, whoa, it's just one of them. What will that be like? What will the dynamic be?
You know, and that kind of little innovation is enough to perk my interest again.
And Casey Neistat has talked about how he's going to stop the daily vlog at some point, and I'm kind of excited for that.
I want him to go back to just, you know, I want to see just his films, his little short films that he likes making.
I want to know what it's going to be like to go back to those, or to see what kind of innovations he'll think of
if he has more time, and isn't, you know, instead of putting those ten minutes a day, or whatever, you know,
which is obviously he works on for hours on the editing of the videos.
So it's not like it's literally just ten minutes a day going into the vlogs.
But I want to know what it'll be like when he decides to open it up and do something a little bit more experimental,
as opposed to the same things he's been doing.
And yeah, that's why I have to keep innovating.
And like this podcast is only going to go as long as I think it's interesting,
as long as I keep thinking that I have these unstructured ideas.
And it works really well for right now because of the fact that I haven't been having these single topic ideas like I was
when I was doing the really intense vlogs, and I was vlogging like every day as I was for, you know, most of the summer of this year.
Because at that time it was just, man, I've had so many random topical thoughts that I need to get out there.
And right now I haven't been having those.
I've been more having a, like my life has been this kind of hazy miasma of moving between things,
of this weird experience of being way ahead of myself in work, and way ahead of myself in planning.
You know, I have things planned for a fairly large amount of time ahead of me, which is unusual.
I've got, you know, all these new interests like comics that I don't really want to talk about in videos that I'm like exploring.
So there's just this whole world of new things happening that I'm not used to.
And this is the right, this podcast is the right vehicle for exploring that.
But as soon as it stops being that way, this podcast will probably end.
I'm really predicting this to have maybe, maybe it'll go for a season, you know, like an anime season.
I kind of started it at a, when did I start this?
Midway through October? No, late into October.
So I could see it going until maybe the end of the year.
Maybe until Radcon 2, that would probably be a stopping point.
Which, when that happens, you know, me and Jesse are going to make the plebe in the weeb.
That's going to be 10 whole videos on its own, so that's a whole different experimental thing.
We're going to be working more on trying to move Jesse and Nate down here.
So that's going to be a whole thing.
So yeah, like, there's just going to be, there's going to be a lot of changes going forward.
And for each stage, I want, I want everything to evolve.
I don't ever want to be boring. I don't ever want people to watch my videos and be like,
this is the exact same thing I heard last time.
And I know that I repeat myself a lot. I know I come from a very certain place.
And that I'm not always presenting new ideas.
But I do think that the rate at which I present new ideas is kind of staggering.
I don't know anybody else who's, who puts out as much content as I do
and for as many of the ideas to be unique.
And as I watch other people, I've come to realize that like,
a lot of people are more just kind of known for holding one position.
You know, they're not really, especially like politicians.
I remember having this interesting moment where I was kind of like watching a few different things
that Bernie Sanders had been saying back when he was trying to run, you know, for president.
And it was weird to realize that they all say the exact same thing.
He has a strict platform and everywhere he goes, he just presents his platform.
And you know, a lot of comedians in the old days before, you know,
before now everybody kind of has to change their set
if they want to keep making specials for the internet age.
But like, stand-up comedy is usually you go to a bunch of places, you tell the same jokes.
And there are certain YouTubers who are kind of like that.
Or if you watch Jimquisition or something, it's not so much about him constantly coming up with new ideas
as it is him applying the ideas he always applies to a variety of different subjects.
And I think that's what standard reviews are like.
I think most reviewers are like saying,
hey, you all know what my opinions in general are.
Here's how this show worked with my general stance.
And I've never really done that.
I've always been more of like every video, everything I do has to have something new.
It has to say something I haven't said before because I often take this stance that like,
if you know how I feel about things, then you can apply it to everything else.
Like you can take what I've said about this show and you can then apply it to every other show you've seen.
But I actually think maybe I've been somewhat misguided in that.
Like when I think of reviews as entertainment or even as just giving people information,
I think it could be helpful if I took on like every show in kind of the same way because nobody else is watching all of it.
You know, nobody else has the time to sort through every single show and tell you how they all relate.
And speaking personally, as someone who's been watching video game analysis for four fucking years now,
while playing very few video games,
like I am deeply invested in the narrative of video game evolution even though I'm not following it at all.
You know, I'm just following these analysts who are like sort of guiding me through what games are doing,
but I don't even play the games for the most part.
So I feel like there's probably people who, and this would be a great way,
if I ever just want to like buckle down and get out a lot of videos and expand my audience,
I would probably do something a bit more like that, just like make more reviews of things
and just like go through a ton of anime and just express opinions on them and sort of get people invested in the narrative.
It's just that with anime in particular, there's so much foundation I felt like I had to build.
Like that no one was talking about the things I wanted them to talk about with anime
and there's so many ideas I have to present and so much groundwork I have to lay before I can even consider
just like jumping on to each individual show, you know.
And over time, as I've kept doing this, I've seen some of the ideas I've presented
start to permeate through, you know, other people and the way they talk about shows.
So that's been cool to see, but I want to take it even further.
Anyway, hopefully that helps you to understand why I never have anything happen consistently
and I know that can be kind of weird for my followers who might get really into one way that I've been doing things
and then have it kind of disappear.
You know, Digi Bros. will be back, I know it seems dead right now because we haven't been doing anything for it
but I still like that format and I like the idea of it coming out consistently over time.
But things like, you know, when I start up some new video series and it seems like,
this content is going to go in this direction and then it just like hard right veers somewhere else
or anything like that, you know.
It's understandably, I can see how that could throw people for a loop and make it so it's harder to follow me in a way
but it's just how I like doing things.
I want to always be new, I want to always be fresh.
I don't ever want you to like wake up one morning and put on one of my videos and feel like,
God, it's just Digi saying the same old shit, you know.
I don't ever want you to feel like you can just skip half my videos which is how I feel about like,
nice stat or game grumps that I don't have to watch them.
Like a new video comes out and I'm just like, eh, I know what I'm going to get myself into, you know,
I can watch it at a later date.
I want, when one of mine comes out, you're like, what is it going to be this time?
What's he going to tell me?
What new thing am I going to learn?
You know, I hope it's felt that way.
Anyway, continued in the next part.
So, in the process of reading all these comics and books and all that other stuff I've been reading,
there's one dangerous thought that keeps popping back into my mind.
It's sort of an itch that I get every once in a while,
and I know this is relatable for some other people who do the kind of work I do,
which is that itch to make original stories.
Even though I don't really like writing original stories or constructing them in any way,
but there's all these characters and plots that I came up with ages ago
that like, when it bubbles up to the surface, it's like, God,
maybe I should finally make that story.
Maybe it's time to bring these characters to life,
even though most of the stories and characters that I have are just by-products
of things I was interested in long ago,
that like, the current me has no relationship with the spark
that generated these characters and ideas.
I feel like me now couldn't possibly bring them to life
in the way that me then wanted them to be brought to life.
But I was thinking about why this keeps happening.
Why do I keep getting this inspiration specifically from reading comics
and books to a lesser extent, but comics especially?
And it's because it's my language.
Like, obviously I watch anime with subtitles and stuff.
I read manga that's translated and everything.
But Japanese has a very specific way of communicating.
The way their language is, the way that their writing sounds.
Like, I'm very used to hearing it.
I know exactly what it's like.
And I could not recreate it.
Like, there's no way I could write an anime-style story using English words.
Because to me, those stories are communicated through Japanese.
Like, the way the language is is integral to the way that characters communicate
in anime and manga.
And if I knew Japanese well enough, I'd almost be tempted to write,
you know, an anime-style story.
Because, like, just the way I think about them is so integrally tied to that.
But now when I read, like, books and comics, it's like, whoa!
These are my words!
These are sentences I would come up with.
These are stories that seem like something I would have invented, you know?
And it's been especially true with these comics that, uh...
God, comics have such a willingness to go so big and so audacious
and so, like, out there with their ideas.
And to do it quickly.
Like, with no hesitation.
Just to bowl through all these high concepts.
Um, you know, and obviously this isn't true of all comics, but...
You know, there's the crazy ones, like the Sandman,
and I've been reading Grant Morrison's Animal Man,
which are just, like, nothing but mind-destroying, high-concept shit all the time.
But even, like...
Like, even normal stuff.
Like, I mean, in comics, comparing characters to gods is, like, a mainstay feature of comics.
Like, in an average comic, someone will be a god.
There will be a battle between gods.
The universe will be at stake.
Alternate dimensions and realities are a constant, you know?
It's kinda like...
It's funny for me because, like, when I watched Rick and Morty,
I thought, wow, this show goes so far beyond the insane with, like, you know,
uh, with going to all these different dimensions and universes and stuff,
and it's so flippant about it.
And that's kinda what I love about Rick and Morty, is that it's so flippant,
and it's all just kind of a big joke to that story.
But in comics, they also do kinda do that.
Like, it's not as flippant about it, but it's so sudden.
Like, we're aliens from another dimension,
we'll show up and be like, oh, we created your reality, you know?
And that just happens in a comic book.
It's kinda taken as a given that crazy-ass shit will happen.
And, uh, I feel like that...
Like, when I'm reading these things,
it feels like the kinds of stories that I used to come up with back when I was trying to be a writer, you know?
Most of the stories that I had thought up involved some kind of super-super-humans,
super-powers, like, uh, concepts as characters.
I mean, for fuck's sake, in, uh, The Sandman, in that comic series,
there's these seven things called the Endless, which are personifications of concepts.
Uh, they are dream, death, destiny, uh, destruction, I think,
uh, pshh, desire, um, delirium, and...
Nah, I'm forgetting one.
But, you know, it's seven personifications of concepts.
And, like, in my story that I was writing called, uh, uh, Tales from the End of the World,
then it was, like, I had seven concepts personifi-
It was, like, the seven gods who ruled over this city, um,
who were all, like, personifications of concepts.
There was the chaos, the end, the, uh, something else.
I don't remember them right now.
It's been a long time. The chaos was the one that, like, mattered to the story.
But, um, you know, that's the kind of stuff I used to do.
And there's just so many little things when I'm reading The Sandman
where I'm like, fuck, I would have written this.
And I never even read this story. Like, I wasn't influenced by this.
Funnily enough, I was more influenced by anime and stuff like that.
But somehow, I still got these concepts that are so comic book.
Reading these comics, I wonder if I would have felt more at home in, in this.
Like, if I'd grown up with these. You know, if I'd grown up with comics like The Sandman,
which is, ironically, The Sandman has been around me my whole life,
because my mom is a hardcore collector of The Sandman.
She owns all the comics, she has tons of statues,
she's been, like, a lifelong fan, and I've never actually read any of it.
So, like, you know, it's, it's this weird irony to pick it up now and be like,
this is exactly the kind of thing that I've always been looking for, you know?
And it just makes me wonder if I would have become more incensed to write
if I had, you know, seen these things before, to create my own stories.
And even though I still like a lot of the concepts I had before,
it's just, a lot of them are just not me.
Like, I don't have that same kind of, like, I don't know.
It used to be that I loved edgy shit.
I loved to write this crazy off-the-wall edgy shit, you know?
And now, the idea of writing something more abstracted than reality,
just like, I can't even do it.
I, I try, I, uh, because of Nano Remo,
which is, you know, every November is Nano Remo,
and I, I had done, I was working on this video project,
I kind of canceled that.
And then I thought, like, four or five days into November,
I was like, what if I just try to write an actual novel?
Let's just go for it.
And I wrote, like, four pages of something,
and most of what I wrote was more, like, diary style.
It was like, I was just writing everything that came into my head
as it came into my head.
And, uh, and I just wrote out, like, four pages of stuff
that kind of works as maybe an intro to a story.
And then I, like, at the end of those four pages,
I was like, all right, now let's launch into an actual story,
like a fiction story.
And I just couldn't do it.
It's like that, that just isn't my style to make stuff something up
as opposed to just saying things that are on my mind.
And I'm, I think I'm good at that.
I think I'm good at writing nonfiction.
And maybe I could write a whole book worth of just thoughts
that come into my head.
You know, I don't think a book is really the best outlet for it.
I think these kinds of podcasts and vlogs are great.
And even if I did something written,
I'd prefer it to be more like a series of journal entries or something.
Just, I don't, I don't like writing non-real things.
And as time has gone on, I've gotten worse and worse at it.
So it's weird, because I feel like I should.
I feel like when I read these comics, I feel like I should do this.
But then I'm like, who even wants it?
Who wants me to do that?
Like, it might not even, it probably won't be good for me
and not good for anyone else compared to what I'm already doing.
You know?
But it's this odd compulsion.
And I know this is something that other people get.
I know because DeVu had, had like a, like a month ago,
he went into what he called like a game hole
where he just suddenly remembered like that,
like a trigger in his mind that like,
because for so long he wanted to design games.
And he has designed games.
He has made actual games before.
You know, very minor little self-made ones that took him forever.
But like, there's a huge part of his brain that still thinks of him as a games guy.
Like his destiny is supposed to be to make games.
And like, even though he's happy with what he's doing now,
and he loves being an editor and he loves, you know, working on analysis videos,
there's still this, this little thing in his mind that gets switched every once in a while
and he becomes obsessed with making a video game.
And then he remembers that he, that it's not the time yet.
And he dials it back.
He grabs the dial and he dials it back.
Oh God, I'm like, I've got my hand on my head
and I'm grabbing like a dial on the side of my head,
like Stein from Frankenstein in Soul Eater.
Imagine that.
Cranking that dial.
But, but for me, it's even more torturous
because I feel like I'm at a place in my career where I, I totally have time.
Like if I wanted to start writing now, I have time now.
You know, I, my dream when I started up Patreon and everything,
even when I first started making videos,
like I've always wanted it to be where I could get so far ahead of myself
that I'd have time to work on other things.
And I've said this a thousand times, I must have.
Like, that me giving all this work to DeVue ahead of time is meant to free me up
to do whatever I want.
And I have been doing other things in my main videos,
but like, you know, it's all been kind of related.
It's all more things that utilize those same kinds of talents,
the, the speaking, the vlogging, the video editing,
the making, making content for YouTube, you know,
occasionally writing a little bit of, you know, nonfiction stuff here and there.
But that, that itch for prose writing, it just creeps up and it grabs me
and it makes me feel like, you have time, you can do it.
But then it's like, what do I actually want to write?
I just, I'm just so in love with the idea that I could do it,
that I could be a writer, that I could be creating these kinds of stories.
But do I actually want to?
Do I actually want to sit down and try to write prose, which I hate?
The answer is probably no, but it's torturous,
because so much of my life was about that up until, you know, I found this.
Like, arguably, even though, even though it's something no one's seen,
even though no one knows or cares about that aspect, you know,
I was 10 when I wrote my first story,
and I was about 20 when I gave up on writing stories.
I mean, I was 20 when I, no, I guess I was 20 when I actually wrote the book,
the nano-remote book, the one that I succeeded at.
So, you know, 10 years I was writing stories,
and then in the next couple of years,
I mean, the last thing I wrote was Ciano and Purple Steve in 2011.
So, you know, it's 11 years of stories.
Nobody read any of them.
None of them are worthy of digging back up, really.
But that's a huge part of my identity,
and it's still there, needling at me in the back of my mind.
And who knows, maybe one day I'll give into it.
In the meantime, I think I might just release those four pages of that book that I, you know,
just those four pages just to see how people feel about my style of writing,
because I don't really think that story is worth continuing,
but it would be interesting to see how people feel about reading that kind of thing.
So that's all.
Oh, boy.
For this last section, I'm gonna be sitting in my desk chair as opposed to the couch.
I mean, I don't know if anybody, like, processes how relaxed I am anyways in these,
but, you know, this one's a...this bit's gonna be decompression more in the sense,
not so much in the relaxing sense, as the God I need to get the thoughts out of my head sense.
I feel like shit right now.
I've made the...
I don't know why I do this to myself, mistake of eating fast food twice today.
All I've eaten today is fast food, and not just any fast food,
but both Wendy's and Arby's.
And every time I eat Arby's, I feel like total garbage.
The only reason at all to go to Arby's is that it's right next to my house.
So, like, you know, I can walk there.
But, God, it makes me feel terrible.
I don't know why I ever eat at Arby's.
It's such a bad idea.
So I feel like garbage doesn't help that I'm back to cigarettes because of my vape breaking and shit,
and, like, I've been getting head rushes because I fucking bought 100s like an idiot.
Oh, God, I feel like a fucking mishmash whirlwind of shit.
And the main reason, aside from all the physical stuff,
is that I have way too much power and way too much responsibility for me to deal with at this point in my life.
I am too big. I have too much pull. I have too big of a voice.
And my vision outstrips my ability to deal with the things I say.
My God, I put out two videos the other day that, I mean, these are not big videos.
They're on After Dark. They've got, you know, 5,000 views apiece.
It's amazing how much I can just, like, suggest something and cause, you know, after effects to ripple out from it.
So one of the videos was to make a recommendations community on Reddit.
And it's the kind of thing where, for whatever reason in my head, it's like, alright, I'm posting up three recommendations.
Maybe this will have, like, I'll make a video about it, you know, suggesting it to people.
I'll post, like, 20 or so recommendations. I'll go through them. It'll be slow forever.
No, of course it's not like that. I post that video and there's fucking several hundred recommendations on the board already.
And immediately I'm like, well, I can't moderate this.
Like, I don't have time to go through this and moderate this and, you know, like, check out absolutely all of it.
I mean, I have been actually consuming a lot of it.
Immediately it paid off in a huge way, because in one of the first recommendations someone posted this series by a music guy called Nick Ott,
I think that's his name, Chris Ott, I don't know why I thought Nick, Chris Ott, OTT, who did this series called Shallow Rewards,
which is just a series of this guy, like, just basically vlogging in much the same style as Digibro After Dark,
which is just like his face and he's talking about stuff, about music, usually about music history and just interesting stuff,
and it's fucking great, because the way he talks is insane.
He talks like he's writing an article in speech, and I don't just mean like a straightforward article.
He talks like prose, almost, and just makes all these connections and references to things at a blistering speed,
where, you know, I don't completely, I don't know a lot of the stuff he's saying, and yet I can draw the connections and I can kind of get it and I can follow it,
and just everything he talks about is fascinating, because he just has this unfucking believable wealth of knowledge about music and its history,
you know, and he's a former journalist, but he formerly worked for like a pitchfork and stuff,
and he has all these opinions about the way, the state of the industry and stuff,
and what got to me the most about the way he talks is that he's very serious.
There's not a whole lot, I mean, he swears and stuff, and it's sort of loose and personal and gonzo,
but there's no sense of like making fun of himself in the way that like I do, where I come out with the fucking sunglasses and the robe and everything,
and I try to make like a big joke of it so that, so I don't come off as like a, you know, a douchebag or whatever.
This guy doesn't care, he's just like, he's upfront about how much he cares about the shit he's talking about, you know,
and he's very dramatic about it, but in a good way, and I really enjoy it, and I'm watching these,
and what got to me the most is how he name drops things, you know, he constantly is, you know, making reference to specific musicians,
specific points in time, specific people in the industry and people in his line of work, you know, fellow journalists and stuff like that,
and it fascinated me because I've had this problem with how I think there's a lot of great journalism happening in the anime community right now,
and no communication happening between the people doing it. I mean, some of them are friends with each other on Twitter and stuff,
but there's no like cross-referencing, there's no people saying like, or like joining of information, you know,
like I'm writing this series on Akiyuki Shinbo, and I'm reading Wave Motion Canon, which is blogging about Akiyuki Shinbo,
and I'm reading, you know, this and that person talking about this stuff, why aren't we all talking about it together?
Why is there no coalition of information, you know, if we're all doing the same research, why are we not sort of in the same field together?
You know, it's odd that we're all kind of reading each other, but not mentioning it to our audience,
no one's like, by the way, check out Digi Bro, check out Wave Motion Canon, you know, we're not doing the back and forth,
and that's including me, I'm not doing enough back and forth, you know, so I decided when I was watching these Chris Ott videos,
I was like, I gotta fucking get something out there like that, so I made a video like that, you know, a mere hour after I had just put out the video
about the recommendations thing on Digi Bro After Dark, you know, so I just launched this Reddit board that is already spiraling out of my control,
and then an hour later, I launched another video that's like where I name drop eight different people who by morning have all seen this video
and have all commented on it on Twitter, and I'm trying to like fucking, you know, figure out what to do with the can of worms I just opened,
and now suddenly I have all this responsibility because I'm the one calling people out, so now I have to do it, I have to follow up, I have to follow through, you know,
I have to go and make reference to all these people and try to make these connections and start talking to people,
and you know, I just showed like eight important guys, hey, I want to start a dialogue between us, you know, and that's where I am now,
and that's just, it's so weird because the way I go about creating things, it's all about that video,
and this happens to me all the time, where I make a video that has a ripple effect, that has this follow up, but I've already moved on,
like when I publish a video, I have mentally moved on to the next thing, you know, sure, I will incorporate elements of what I've said,
I'll start moving in that direction, but like, you know, I feel like the kinds of calls to action that I do on like a weekly basis are the kind of things that most people save for once a year,
once every six months, you know, like every so often someone's like, hey, why don't we all do this, and everyone else is like,
oh, that's an interesting thought, and I do that like constantly, and then I'm always like, you know, it backfires on me partly because I have no skills of delegation,
and I don't talk to anybody, you know, my biggest problem is I'm not talking to enough people, I am very, I'm a hermit, you know, I talk to the PCP,
those are my friends, I like almost exclusively talk to the members of the procrastinator's podcast, that's it, I really don't talk to anybody else,
except for like, you know, a few ancillary people like Munky or Munchy who are basically PCP members as it is,
and you know, some of my other friends like Neil X, who I even him, I can barely ever get around to talking to, you know, it's like,
it's really the close people who I have a narrative with that I keep talking to, so, you know, when I open these cans of worms,
it's like, I don't know what to do with it, who can I possibly appoint to be the moderator of this recommendation subreddit, I don't know who anybody is,
you know, everyone posting there, you know, they're now, you know, possibly committed to being a part of this community,
but I have no idea who I could pick out, you know, after like a year, I appointed Lachlan still the moderator of the Digibro subreddit,
you know, the one that I have for myself, maybe it hasn't been up for a year, I have no idea, but after a long period of time,
you know, I saw that Lachlan was, he reads everything on there and responds to everything, and I was like, well, this guy cares more about my subreddit than I do,
and even then, I still do most of the moderation work myself, because something is caught in the fucking filter or something, and I'm the one who ends up taking it down,
so, yeah, just because I'm on there all the time, not like to take a thing away from Lachlan, like I just kind of get to stuff faster,
and I understand why he'd rather have me make executive decisions than, you know, try to decide for me what goes on my Reddit board,
but that's the problem, I don't know how to like delegate tasks to people and like handpower over and not try to be a part of every single fucking thing that I open up,
and then as a result, so much of what I start goes unfinished, so many of the things that like, I opened up this huge big idea to the world,
and everyone's like, whoa, that's a cool idea, and then, you know, I lose interest and the whole thing dies, because I don't leave anybody in charge,
I don't know who to leave in charge, you know, I wish I was better at that, I wish I could have the mindset of someone like, you know,
I watch Casey Neistat and he's going around talking to all these different kinds of people, and like, he starts up something like Beam,
and it's like, he started it, but the guy who like fucking Coke founded Tumblr is the guy who runs it, you know,
and I wish I knew people like that, who I could delegate to these things, but the problem is it's all unpaid, like these are all passion projects, you know,
I can't pay somebody to mod the fucking reccomendations board, what is it, reccompendium, I can't like, pay someone to do it,
it's just like, hey, who's interested in like, taking this idea that I had out of nowhere, and now you're suddenly in charge of it, you know,
like I haven't even peppered anybody up and gotten excited, I just launched this fucking thing the second I had the idea for it,
but that's me, I just kind of go and go and go, and I don't stop, and then, you know, I blast past the things that I've left in my wake,
and it's a sad thing, and it's not that I don't think I have time to like, even do some of this stuff, it's just that I like moving on,
you know, I'm so into getting into the next idea, and when I have an idea, it's always a big idea, and I guess it is that I don't have time,
like, how am I meant to, you know, launch a community, and like, for most people, that's then what they're doing, you know,
for most people who are like, a moderator of a forum, that's like, when they get off work, that's what they do with their day,
you know, they moderate the forum for a few hours, like, that's their kind of thing they do as a creative outlet,
and for me, it's like, I just launched a community, and now I'm gonna go watch 200 fucking shaft shows, so I can write about them, or something,
you know, like, I have some huge project I have to go do that will totally absorb everything, and I will not have time for this forum,
so, yeah, that's the kind of nightmare I live in, and then, you know, I know that some of the comments on here,
like, there's probably gonna be somebody who's like, hey, what about me, I'd like to delegate your forum, and the other problem is that,
like, again, I don't know people, and I don't trust anybody I don't know, like, and I don't go and meet people, so I never meet anybody who I can trust,
you know, not that I don't think that you guys can probably do a good job, just that, like, the way I am, I don't tend to, like, contact people unless I already know them for something,
you know, like, for me, before I ever, like, follow someone, or befriend them, or, like, get their fucking discord information,
it's always, like, someone who I've been watching for a while, who I know their content, and I'm like, oh, I'm comfortable with this person,
and those aren't the people you can hand something over to, because those are the people who are already running their own channel, you know,
I already felt, like, kind of bad that I saddled, like, I know Lachlan wants to do it, but I felt funny about saddling him with the moderating of DigiBro,
and it's like, his attention's obviously not gonna be here, he's got his own fucking YouTube channel, you know, he probably hopes that one day he'll have his own subreddit,
you know, uh, dedicated to his work, um, that he can fucking find somebody to delegate it to,
but, yeah, so that's the place I'm in right now, and it's kind of dramatic, and I just never have my ideas just don't fucking stop,
and especially when I'm watching something like these Chris Ott videos, and just, like, every single one makes me want to go do something,
I started up so many videos yesterday, like, aside from those two that I already released, I filmed a fucking hour-long thing that I'm working on,
uh, that's got, like, full editing and stuff, and if it's successful, it might launch a whole other series, you know,
I did, in fact, post on my Reddit the story I was talking about in the last part of this podcast, um, that I had written, like, five pages of,
and, you know, let that out there, and people were like, yeah, this is kind of not bad, I can see you reading more of your prose,
and I'm like, don't tell me that, tell me it's awful, tell me to stop, don't tell me I can do this, cause that's fucking scary,
you know, and every time I read some, like, God, I'm so envious of the people on Twitter who, like, post screenshots of every show they fucking watch,
and like, make web-ems of every cool piece of animation, and I feel like that's a real service that I could be doing, you know, that I could be going through,
I tried to do this, uh, like, a week ago, two weeks ago, when I was watching Moonphase, and like, I capped out this little segment that I was like,
this seems like it's probably one of Shin Onuma's, like, first defining moments, and I kind of posted it, but then I didn't feel anything afterwards,
I can't even tell when I've made a tweet, people, like, really care about, cause everything I fucking post gets a thousand likes and retweets,
I know I'm making that sound like, oh, whoa is me, everything gets so many likes, but it really does, like, make it so you don't even really know that you've had an impact,
unless it's like, way over the top, you know, like, the number of likes and retweets you get, um, it's like, I don't even know if it's helping anybody,
who just, did anybody care that Shin Onuma had a thing in some show you probably never fucking watched or cared about, cause it's 12 years old,
and who the hell is Shin Onuma, I haven't even made a video about him yet to make anybody care about him, um, you know, but then I see those people,
and every time I'm like, man, is what I'm doing really helping people, you know, am I really, like, helping the anime community,
could, would I be more helpful if I was like, I don't know, type setting, scantilations or something, and of course I can't make money doing that,
so I'm gonna be, you know, I can't do as much if I'm doing something that doesn't make me any money, cause I have to get a regular job,
and I can only do whatever it is on the side, you know, um, which is in its own way kind of sad, and obviously I'm not very self-sacrificing about all this,
um, but Jesus, I wish I could fucking, I need to learn Japanese, cause I could do so much more, and I do feel bad, I feel like I, you know,
I consider myself a journalist, and I say Gonzo journalist, and that's both a defense and a warning, like the reason I'm Gonzo is because,
you know, it lets you know, hey, I cannot necessarily be held to be, like, presenting accurate facts, this is just my interpretations,
and that's, you know, some people might see it as, well, you're just using an excuse to not do more research, and I'm like, sure, fine,
you can accuse me of that, I certainly don't do as much research as I could, but it's also to warn you, like, hey, I haven't done my due diligence,
this is not facts, this is just how I'm interpreting the things that I see, you know, the data that I see, so, be aware that that's what you're getting yourselves into,
um, and, yeah, but I do feel bad that I'm not doing more of it, but like, you can't really fucking research this stuff if you don't know Japanese,
it's fucking impossible, there's just not enough, you know, information in English, and what there is is trickling out in a, like, a, you know, wave motion cannon,
I love what they're doing, where they're translating interviews with Japanese creators right now, and it's all like, you know, hot, important people who people care about,
but it's like, this is one interview about, like, one cut from one show kind of thing, you know, like, sometimes a year old, and I'm like, I need to be able to fucking,
a journalist is someone who calls up the office of the fucking place, and, you know, gets the interview, which, in fairness, Wave Motion Cannon did this interview with Lan from the 2B Hero show,
that was great, that's some real journalism there, that they could reach out to him, and like, get this guy who, you know, is fucking just now being heard of, just like, breaking out,
and having this like, moment, and it's like, this monumentous occasion for Chinese animation and stuff, and even then, like, as excited as Lan is to the fact that,
like, in American cares about his work at all, you know, on the flip side, how many people even read Wave Motion Cannon, you know, like, disinformation needs to be out there,
and that's when I feel like, well, I've got the platform, I've got the 250 subscribers, or 50,000 subscribers rather, but do they care?
You know, like, if I become this, like, if I became a full-blown journal, it's like, yeah, I'm doing better work, but no one wants it, you know, people want the pop shit,
there's a reason that my biggest videos are like, reviews of, you know, shows I don't like, and stuff, it's, people aren't clamoring for the information,
they want the stories, and of course, the best journalists can spin the story, you know, can spin the info into a story, and, yeah, like, I feel like that's what I'm,
that's what I'd like to be able to do, but without knowing Japanese, it's so much harder, and being the, you know, insular, self-obsessed guy that I am,
being the guy who doesn't spend a month on a video, I spend a day on a video, I spend, you know, and I don't just mean, like, main-series videos,
I mean, like, I'm constantly making shit, I always have something going on, I have three Let's Plays that I'm in the middle of editing.
Let's Plays, like, nobody even cares, nobody even fucking cares about my Let's Plays, except for, like, this, his handful of people who are, like, hardcore fans,
but, you know, that's the kind of work I'm saddling myself with that's taking away from time I could be learning Japanese,
but, you know, doing Let's Plays fun and learning Japanese fucking blows, but it's something I hope I eventually do, you know,
I don't know if I'm gonna get any more mature than I am now, so that's, I can't say, like, maybe when I'm grown up, that time has come and is here.
This is what I'm talking about, like, you know, I went on that whole rant, not thinking about the fact that this will come out before,
and then people will just link this to that guy, so, you know, that's the kind of thing that's gonna happen,
and I'd rather talk to him about it in person, so now I'm just gonna have to scrub 15 minutes out of this podcast that I don't even want to do that.
Well, God, that's probably the end, this might be a shorter one, I thought I was actually gonna rant for, like, 40 minutes about this,
but I seem to have gotten all the ideas that were at the surface of my head out in a concentrated burst, so that might be the end,
and we'll leave it in case I remember something.
So this video is gonna be coming out a little late, like, an extra day rather than at the end of the week.
I know because it's already the 15th, as I'm recording this, like, about 45 minutes ago it became that.
In any case, just some parting thoughts, you know, I got a moderator for Ret Compendium,
gave it to rival Steven, who moderates the subreddit for the Procrastinators channel,
that we don't talk about all that much, but it's always in the descriptions,
and, you know, after yesterday I felt like total shit until I did this recording, and then I went and got Ben.
We worked out, I felt much better after working out and eating something that wasn't fucking fast food for the first time in the day.
I spent all night watching Chris Ott videos and all day today doing the same, and, yeah.
You know, I find that for me, a bad mood is usually attributable to, like, it's usually more physiological.
Like, whatever I'm mad about, I'm mad about it because of other reasons.
Like, it's not really because it's that bad, like, there's a lot of things I can shrug off when I'm generally feeling good
that will make me feel shitty if I'm generally feeling shitty, so it's kind of funny in that way.
But, man, I've just been reeling from the realization when I did the last part of this recording
that, like, I can't say anything anymore that has no repercussions.
Like, I have too much of an audience now that knows my stuff too well, like, too many people who follow everything I do.
And it's kind of funny, like, it used to be that the things I said didn't matter.
Like, I could say fucking anything, and it just didn't matter because, uh, you know, I was nobody.
And now that I'm, um, you know, someone popular, then it's like everything I say, like, has some kind of repercussion.
Not that I'm saying, like, I'm gonna watch my words from now on.
Like, I'm not that type of person.
I'm always just gonna be, like, off the handle, but it's just, it's really interesting to sort of enter that world where, um, you know,
if I name drop somebody for any reason, that person's probably gonna hear about it because it wasn't just some guy who said it.
It was DigiBro, who has 250,000 subscribers and who, you know, has fans who will send my stuff to the people I'm talking about.
Um, or even not fans, just people who want to start something, you know, if I'm talking shit about somebody.
Uh, and vice versa, like, anything anyone says about me, I hear about it.
It's, it's really funny to me when people are, like, shocked that I turn up somewhere, when people are like,
wow, you watch that YouTube channel or wow, you do that?
Yeah, of course I do. All I do is fucking watch YouTube.
All I do is consume stuff, you know?
Like, I'm, whoever, if you're someone who sits at your computer all day and, like, you know, watches my videos,
like, I promise I sit at my computer more than you do and watch even more videos than you do.
You know, like, all I do is sit around and watch stuff.
So, like, yeah, anytime someone mentions me, it gets sent to me.
You know, someone's gonna fucking post it on my Reddit or something and I'm gonna watch it.
I'm always around.
Um, so, yeah, it's, it's kind of funny when people are like, oh my god, did you watch this channel?
I watch every channel, um, if it's relevant to, like, the kind of stuff I'm doing, you know?
I'm gonna get sent it eventually.
So, yeah, that's funny to me just because I guess, I guess it's like people see it as if you have a big following,
you must just be busy all the time.
Like, you know, somehow you're spending all your time doing something.
I don't know what, you know, I don't know.
I mean, I guess that's, like, there's a lot of big channels who they don't, you know, they don't respond to comments,
they don't seem to watch a lot of YouTube videos and stuff,
but the reason for that isn't because they're big, it's because it's just not what they do.
You know, like, if you're someone who normally spends a lot of time, like, let's say you have a family,
you know, if you spend all your time with your family, no, you're not reading YouTube comments,
you know, you're not out there watching everybody else's videos and stuff,
but like, uh, that's not a consequence of having a big channel.
Um, I, that's, you know, that's what I, I, I live my life just the way that probably most of my viewers do,
which is probably why so many of them connect with me, you know, because it's like, hey, this guy is exactly like me,
just articulate and, uh, and, uh, you know, and interesting in the way he thinks about things,
but yeah, I find that kind of funny.
But anyways, that about wraps up this, uh, this Decompression podcast.
It was a very, a very necessary one, I guess, for me this week.
Um, but this podcast is, it's funny because its purpose is kind of to get stuff out there and relieve stress,
but it can be stressful in itself just because it is a thing I have to make, you know, and I've got so much going on.
And like right now, the consequence of me making this is that I'm not editing the new PCP that we just recorded, you know,
and like now those are going to come out weirdly back to back.
And, uh, the whole schedule of this channel is kind of fucked,
but it's because the person who cares the most is Nate, and Nate has the least time to deal with any of it.
Like Nate is the one who by far puts the most effort into organizing the PCP and making sure it comes out,
you know, and like making sure everybody's on top of their game, but he personally can't work on it.
You know, he doesn't have time to edit these videos and to make it all correct.
And like, uh, and I'm the only one who's kind of reliable enough to expect that it'll actually come out like reasonably on time
because I edit fast and I don't put things off, um, the way everybody else will.
Like in the early days of PCP, we were all editing.
Like we would exchange editors and you can see that in most of the early videos.
Like there's a credit for editor and like, you know, if Jesse edits one, he's going to put more effort in,
but it's going to take an extra fucking week before it comes out.
Um, so, you know, it just kind of falls on me, which is funny because I'm doing a million things.
So, you know, I'll put it off for a couple of days because I want to do the decompression chamber.
I want to do this, uh, did you watch a dark video, you know?
But anyway, so that's it for now.
I hope you enjoyed.
Stay tuned.
The next one will probably be out in a week, but maybe it'll be a day late like this one.
You know, it's not a strict format.
Um, enjoy the music and have a nice day.
Oh,