Hello, everybody, and welcome to yet another Pro Crastinators Podcast interview series.
I am here with the one and only Hippocrit.
Yep, he is.
Hippo, um...
I'm curious about the fact that a lot of the time on the show, people call you Gibbon.
Why is this?
That is because it used to be our secret brony names. We all have them. That's our secret identity.
That's my one. I'm a Gibbon.
It's just my old channels. Gibbontake.youtube.com.
Yeah, that's really all it is. It's a nicer name to say than Hippo, so some people couldn't get into the habit of saying Hippo all the time.
Yeah, it's that we called you Gibbon for so long, and then you changed to Hippocrit.
But because you've always kept both channels active, it's kind of like how with Jesse, we all call him Jess, or we called him drowning in footwear for a long time, even though he had other channels that were even bigger.
Well, we called him Jesse Wood most of the time.
Right. But with you, it was like, because we've never called you by just your name, which if you want to let the audience know what it is, then...
There's other places where they can find out.
Oh yeah? You're going to leave it mysterious?
Yeah. I mean, I'm sure people know already. They can put it on that quiz.
Oh, was it?
That procrastinators quiz.
So yeah, we have the hardest time deciding. I usually say Hippo. Nate usually says Gibbon.
I think Ben usually says Hippo.
It really doesn't matter. People know that I'm being addressed.
I just wonder if it's confusing for anybody who doesn't know about your old channel, you know?
Yeah. Well, that's it. It's give and take. On that channel, you'll find my Brony stuff, and a huge amount of weird, crazy nonsense that may or may not be entertaining.
Surely you've done more weird vlogs than you have Brony content by now, right?
I have. I think by now it's mostly just weird shit.
Which is usually great. In fact, it's always great.
I don't know about always, but yeah, it's very experimental. I like it.
So how did you get your start on YouTube?
Well, my very start on YouTube, I think I made in like 2007 or 2008.
And I had Windows Movie Maker, and I made a video about putting Google images set to a Beatles song.
And I thought it was really cool, and my dad liked it. I don't know why I made it, but I made it, and I made a YouTube account because it was a thing.
And I put it on there. And that was the very beginning.
After that, I did a few stop motion things, and then when I really started doing stuff with the pony fandom, with all the stuff,
I tried doing YouTube poops at first because I was really into that.
They weren't that good, but I kind of laughed once.
And after that, I got into doing compilations, which...
The first compilation was like... I don't know where I came up with the idea, but it was like a summer after school,
and I wasn't doing anything, and I was really bored, and I was into the pony fandom, so I thought,
I'll just make a video of all the times every pony says no.
And it was a huge undertaking because they say it a lot of times, and it took a long time, and I made it,
and I got like thousands of subscribers within a few hours, days, and it was overwhelming.
And after that, I just felt like I had to continue, and I did.
So, when you made these compilations, every single one you made, you had to watch the entire show, right?
Yes. Well, I didn't have to watch the entire show. What I did...
I'm trying to think...
The way I went about it changed over time. At first, I was just going through, and I had a little notepad open,
like a digital notepad, and every time I'd have all the characters' names, or I would...
No, what I did, I went to the scripts, the online transcripts of the episodes, and I would control F for the word,
and then I would go to that point in the episode by memory, like when they say this line,
oh, I kind of know where that is, that's like five minutes in. I go in there, and then I see them say it,
and I pause, I tally one on the thing, and I just keep going.
And, yeah, it's really retarded and autistic when I think about it, but it was kind of fun.
I've always wondered how ridiculously familiar you got with the show through doing that.
Did you watch the episodes like a hundred times?
It sort of waded me out to... It made a very big difference in how I view or think about those episodes compared to the ones
that came after I stopped doing the compilations, like Season 4, because Season 4 was when I started doing the analysis,
and that carries its own sort of like... I remember those for having to watch them twice and think about them,
and the other ones I just know lots and lots of little parts of them all over the place,
and it's a very big disconnect from each, like Season 3 to Season 4 and then beyond.
Season 5 is actually the first season I feel like I watched as a guy watching the show, because of all that nonsense.
So, those compilations, I remember it, because I saw them from fairly early on to them being created,
because they would get promoted really heavily on Equestria Daily. They'd get a whole post to themselves.
I guess they were seen as something very valuable because of the effort that they took, or just the sheer weirdness of their existence.
I think what I... I was pretty happy with the fact that I had come up with this idea, because the amount of work put in,
I felt like nobody would go to the trouble of actually trying to compete with me, so I could just have all those posts to myself,
so I would just do all the words I could think of and get a billion subscribers, and it kind of worked.
I had like 15,000... No, that was later. I think I got to like 9,000 or something through that alone.
So, you actually... Among the procrastinators, you had one of the bigger pony channels, like other than me and Tom,
you were probably the biggest out of everybody, right?
At that point, yeah, I mean, T-Bap I think overtook me at one point.
I plateaued at... During the analysis stuff, I plateaued around 16K, or maybe 15K, and they went further.
So, you would do all these videos with the show, but then what really brought you to my attention was when you did the same thing
with actual analysis videos for the word analysis. How long did that take?
Oh, well, that started because I did that one compilation of all the analysis people.
Like, I found... It was ridiculous, because that was the biggest one, but nobody cares about it.
It's the one where I went through all of your videos, all of Tom's videos, all of...
Basically, like a hundred different people, maybe. I looked into all of their videos and watched all of them,
and since there wasn't any transcripts, I had to literally watch every single video.
I think I'd tell you... I can't remember how long it was, but it was... Maybe not thousands of hours.
Hundreds of hours of watching these shitty videos, and after that, I did the analysis assemblage thing.
So, I already knew about a lot of these people, so I could just sort of go,
uh, okay, I guess I'll get all the opinions of everybody together, because usually people say the same thing over and over,
and if I can get the unique parts of everybody's conversation, it could be an interesting thing.
It kind of was, but probably not really that much.
Well, I was first referring to the one that was just analysis, analysis, analysis, the compilation,
where it was every time anyone used the word analysis in an analysis video, and you compiled them all,
and I had like 150-something uses or something like that, like some ridiculous number, right?
Yeah.
Like I said it fucking constantly, and it was really funny, and I remember taking it
and setting it to like this insane, like, noise song that like me and Victor had put together,
and just like put that over it, and it was like, did you put it after dark?
I remember seeing that, I remember seeing that and being really, really happy that you had enjoyed it that much.
Yeah, it was great.
And then, yeah, and then after that you started, it was with season four, right, that you did the analysis assemblage,
where it was like taking everyone's, a new episode would come out, everyone would release a video,
and then you would assemble all the best points they made into a video, right?
Is that how you'd put it?
Assembling all the different points, like if people were arguing with each other, I would bring up each other's topics,
but really they're not very, the people coming up with things is like, there's only so many ways you can view a certain episode,
and it's, yeah, I got bored of it pretty quickly.
So then you decided to throw your hat into doing it yourself, doing analysis videos.
Yeah, which was much more fun, because it was me, and I'm important, and I'm cool.
And the way I remember the trajectory going was that at first you were trying more to be like an analysis guy,
and then very quickly you seemed to stop caring about that angle and wanted to just do jokes,
and they became much more comedy oriented.
Yeah, I think it was the Christmas one or something, like it was over Christmas,
and I hadn't done the video because it was Christmas time and stuff was happening,
so I was like, ugh, I don't know, blah blah blah, and it was hilarious, and I really liked it, and everyone really liked it,
so I just thought I'd be more funny instead of caring too much about reviewing the show.
And then Jesse, I found Jesse's videos, and he introduced me to all different types of ways of being a brony
and enjoying the show and hating everyone, and that was cool.
So that sort of became the second wave, and then I died.
What was it?
I know that I knew about you, but how did Jesse find out about you,
because I assume you would have said something about him at some point to draw his attention.
I think Jesse had seen that I had mentioned him in one of my first analysis assemblage videos,
so he noticed that. I don't think he had talked to me then, but I think I talked to you.
I remember when I first became Skype friends with you, we were playing that MMO, the Pony MMO, what Legends of Equestria,
and I saw you in the game, and I was like, holy shit, it's him, so I'll see if I can be friends,
and I jumped onto a video you were making, and then after that...
For anyone, I don't expect anyone to track this down, but me and this dude, DJ Calcos, had done...
It was like, did you and Calcos do Equestria? We were playing the betas of this, or alpha rather, of this Pony MMO that they were making,
and the second video we did, we just happened to run into give and take, but you didn't have a mic, so we were just kind of like,
just showing you in the video.
I think I did have a mic.
Did you? I don't remember you saying anything in the video.
I didn't say much, that was the thing, I was like really nervous, like holy shit, he's an internet celebrity,
and I'm being with him, it's cool, and I'm scared.
But I do remember that, that was probably the first thing we had that was like a collaboration in any way.
Yeah, and then what happened after that? I think, Jesse, I think I talked to you about making the Faggot compilation,
because I found out about Jesse through you, and I looked at all these videos, I thought this guy's great,
I'll do a compilation to get his attention, and I told you about it, and I told you not to tell him, because I knew you were friends with him,
and then I made it, and he saw it, and it was cool, and I think I added him on Skype somehow.
That's still up, right on, give and take?
Yeah.
Yeah, go to give and take and look up the Faggot Faggot compilation, every time Jesse says Faggot in any of his videos.
That was great, and you even, how did you get his older stuff, because you had the Tucker Todd Ferguson character,
you had the stuff from videos that are no longer on his channel.
I think, I went to his Blip channel, actually, and I found, like his old Final Fantasy 7 Let's Play,
and I battled Toads and Double Dragon Let's Play, and I looked through all those, and the old school podcast with,
No, what was it?
There's a Johnny Old School, and his friends, those games, that podcast.
Aiden, and Cinemascist.
Yeah, I listened to those, and I basically just, I actually went on his Facebook account,
I typed in his name, I found him on Facebook, and I got an image that I used for the thumbnail.
So I really, I basically stalked everything I could find of Jesse, just so I could make that video.
Yeah.
It was cool.
And it was good.
So yeah, I guess that's probably when we all started talking, because at some point we all did a horse cast together,
where we brought you, or first it was that you and him did one because I was gone,
and he wanted to do a podcast, and then the three of us did one together before we brought in T-Bap,
and became the horseshoe crew.
So, yeah.
And then, I think that first podcast with me and Jesse was really awkward.
It was pretty bad.
I remember listening to it, because I was at my girlfriend's house at the time, and that's why I couldn't be on.
And it came out, and I listened to it at some point, and I was just like, what the fuck are they talking about?
It was like 40 minutes and lots of pauses, and like a long period of time between dialogue.
See, I didn't expect that, because I didn't think of Jesse as like a quiet person like me,
but if you think about how we act in the procrastinators' podcasts, we are the guys who say nothing for a long time,
and then chip in with a little thing.
I've always said that.
Only us in a podcast is a fucking nightmare.
Yeah, I mean if you listen to it, if you listen to any of the old horse casts,
I was always talking way more than Jesse.
I would just go on and on and on, and then he would come up with a big point,
and it's like the stuff he says is more memorable, but if you actually listen to it, it's like mostly me.
And I really don't think it was until the blue glow that I ever felt like Jesse could just go on by himself, you know?
And like the early blue glows have way more editing, where like he has to cut a lot more,
and now he's gotten better at just like stream of consciousness talking,
so I definitely think it's a skill he's developed, but at the time, not so much.
Stream of consciousness talking is fun.
Yeah.
It's hard to get going.
I can occasionally do it on my own gaming channel that I have, but I haven't been using it recently.
Yeah, GivenGaming.org.
I very much enjoyed your Dark Souls 2 videos on Given Gaming.
It's just the most spiteful, angry, even more so than mine, because mine are more bitchy.
Yours are just like, I hate the world.
It feels so raw and real.
Yeah, what was I doing?
I was killing what I didn't realize was like the second to last boss of the game,
and I was just running back down through that dark cavern and going insane because they were annoying.
That's a good video, even though it's kind of shitty looking.
The one I remember more is the Aldi is Keep one where you're just like,
you hadn't realized yet that you were playing with the covenant that makes the game three times harder,
and you're just so mad, and I was watching you like, this looks like,
just getting my blood boiling, this game is so fucking bad.
It was a direct result of those videos of yours that I ended up trying to do my own Dark Souls 2 videos,
because it reignited my hatred for that game, and I was like,
somebody's got to do it, someone's got to kill it, but then my videos were stupid.
Just so people know, I did beat the game on that difficulty setting, because I was like, fuck it,
I've gone this far, I don't care anymore, and I killed them.
At level 180, I want to say, that you beat the game at.
And you're generally great at Dark Souls, like Dark Souls 1, right?
Yeah, I am infamous among a few people that I killed Onstein and Smo, and Manus,
no, not Manus, Artorias on my first try through the game,
and my brother can vouch for that because he was watching me, and he was like, holy shit, you did it.
Because you leveled your endurance to a comically high degree, right?
You did insane grinding or something like that?
I don't know whether I leveled my endurance so much, I think I was just using fat rolls and wearing really strong armor,
and had a lot of health, but yeah, there was a point in fighting Artorias for the first time,
he hit me with one of his charging attacks, and I was drinking Maestus, and I didn't get knocked down,
and I thought that was worth mentioning to you guys.
And you were like, what?
I blew my mind into a thousand tiny pieces, and now you do challenge runs all the time, right?
Oh yeah, I did a challenge run of endurance by leveling just endurance,
which is actually not that difficult because it makes sure that you can roll all the time,
and you have really good shield usage, so you could, at the end of the game with 99 endurance,
I could wear the entire Giants set plus 5, and I could do fast rolls, and it was really cool.
That is fucking intense.
Yeah, and after that I started doing a Faith one, which I leveled only Faith to 99,
which actually was also not so bad after I got to level 70 in Faith,
because then I got this thing, the Wrath of the Gods, which is like an area of effect,
blasts that damages things, and so I could run into that little place in the painted world of Ariamis with all the slime guys,
and I could blow them up, and kill them all at once, and then run back, and just grind like that.
That sounds beautiful.
It was.
It sounds like a, like a, like a, I don't know, what's a phrase that means really good thing?
A true complete mental play.
So, um.
It's Sublime.
So Hippo, you are a man of many interesting talents.
I am.
Besides being a funny man, a punmeister for sure,
someone whose Twitter is nothing but weird puns and fucking bizarre jokes,
and general comedic guy, YouTuber, but you're also a musician, yeah?
Yeah.
I've never been in a sort of a professional band sort of thing,
but I play guitar, and I can play bass and drums, and stuff.
I very rarely play keyboards, but I can.
But guitar is my main thing, and I'm pretty good at it.
Haven't you played at a few live shows, like with your dad?
Oh yeah, I played with, my dad's a drummer, my dad's cool.
He's a drummer, and he drums in a band, two bands.
There's a band that he formed with dads from my old school,
and they called it Dad's Own, and then there's a band that he had with this jazz band he was in.
I don't know whether he's in that anymore, but yeah.
And he had like two pretty good bands that I've been listening to recently, actually,
because he's got all these old cassettes of his, like, studio recordings and stuff,
and I've been going through them, and recording them onto, you know, big...
I've got this, like, cassette to a USB thing, so I can download them and make them digital for them.
And yeah.
Cool.
So yeah, I've played in a few live bands.
I'm actually going to be playing in a live rock concert at Aguna Re, which is a whole other thing.
Aguna Re is this camp for disabled kids, where I volunteer and help and stuff.
And this year, we've organized a rock concert, and I'm going to be playing a bunch of rock songs for them.
And that's cool.
Nice.
So yeah.
You can play a lot of classic dad rock.
Yeah, I like all that sort of stuff.
Whenever we talk music in the PCP, Hippo has very specific tastes.
You like the Beatles, Led Zeppelin, Pink Floyd.
What are some others?
Queen, David Bowie.
I mean, there's loads.
Whenever I think of, like, a list of bands, I forget all of them.
ACDC is a pretty good one.
But anything that's cool.
Yeah, cool.
And from the 70s or early 80s or 60s, I guess.
I like rock from any time period.
I mean, Muse is one of my favorite bands, and they're still going strong.
They're one of the biggest bands in the world at the moment.
But I'm not very much into weird indie shit like you are, I guess.
You seem to like guitar-driven rock, stuff where the guitars are prominent.
And generally, it usually is massively popular just by happenstance.
Right.
In the procrastinator's discord room, we have our PCP channel,
and then we have the musical corner.
And every so often, Hippo will just pop into the musical corner
and start playing a bunch of, like, Beatles and Led Zeppelin songs on his acoustic guitar.
And we'll just come in and listen to him.
And it's like, it's the most relaxing possible experience in the world.
I'm glad you like it.
I didn't expect that to be cool, but I guess it is.
Yeah.
I made that corner, I don't know why, really.
I guess I was just, like, imagining me playing for you guys or something over the internet.
But I assumed the internet would make it all annoying to listen to, like with lag and stuff.
I mean, it sounds like shit, but it's still fun to listen to.
It's kind of like, I mean, I mean, I listen to a lot of shitty sounding music, you know?
Like, I listen to a lot of black metal, which is deliberately recorded badly for the atmosphere.
So to me, it kind of has this atmosphere of, like, it sounds like if you were outside,
next to a babbling brook, and someone about 30 feet away was playing acoustic guitar,
and you're just hearing the acoustic guitar mixed in with all the other atmospheric noise,
then that's kind of what it sounds like.
But with, like, weird digital pop in and pop out.
So it's like all of that, but it's inside the internet.
It's like a cyberpunk future thing.
It's an electronic babbling brook.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's nice.
There's going to be a VR future where we can actually make that exact scenario I described happen.
So what would you say is your outright favorite band, Beatles or Led Zeppelin, or something else?
It's usually Led Zeppelin, but I don't really like having a favorites.
I like having a ton of favorites.
I don't like choosing one out of all of them, because it depends on what I feel like listening to,
and how long it's been since I've listened to my quote-unquote favorite.
Do you have a favorite song to play?
I have quite a lot of songs I've learned to play, and I can't remember my favorite one.
I guess at the moment it's back in black by AC DC, because that riff is really cool.
That's the one that's like...
You saw them recently with Axl Rose as the lead singer?
Yeah, the guy, what's his name?
I've only gotten into AC DC recently.
I knew they were cool, but I only started listening to them recently, so I don't know the guy's name.
It was sick, and Axl Rose was singing for him, and I went to see him live at the London Olympic Stadium.
Well, the beginning of the month.
It was really good. They had cannons and a giant fat inflatable lady, and a giant cool bell that was tolling.
It was the hell's bells it was. It was great.
What were the cannons shooting?
Blanks, hopefully.
I saw a Coldplay show once, and they had cannons that shot confetti out over the audience.
That's a fake cannon. These were real cannons, because they were actually super loud.
Oh, full-sized cannons.
There were like nine of them, and that was the finale.
For those about to rock, we salute you. Boom!
It's like, whoa! It's the coolest thing I've ever seen.
That's fucking intense. That's awesome.
So, yeah, your dad performed in these bands. You are a musician.
Both of your brothers are musicians, too, right, on some level?
Yeah, well, my brother, Henry, is kind of a budding bassist, but he hasn't really been getting into it as much as my other brother, Charlie,
who got really into ragtime music, you know, all that sort of stuff you see in, like, YouTube videos where they're trying to be old-timey, and they stock ragtime music.
He actually knows how to play all that on the piano, which is really cool.
And then he got into a lot of Motown and stuff, Stevie Wonder and David Bowie, and he knows a lot of cool shit, and he's good.
He's really good at it. He's good at piano, he's good at bass.
He's going to be playing with me in that rock concert.
To ask you more, like, who are your brothers? How old are they, and what do they do?
Because they're fairly interesting as well.
They are. Well, fairly. Henry's two years old, younger than me, so he'd be 20, I think, and Charlie is my youngest brother.
He's the piano guy, and he is 19, I guess. I can't remember.
I mean, I don't pay too much attention to their literal age, I just know when their birthday is.
But yeah, Henry's actually kind of a neat at the moment, but he's cool.
I mean, he's not depressed or anything. He's got his new room and stuff.
He's just not doing shit.
Yeah, he's not doing much, but it's okay. I believe in him.
One of them has a YouTube channel, right?
That's Henry. He's got a little YouTube channel. He puts some confessional sort of things, not too in-depth,
but it's interesting to listen to from my perspective, because it's the sort of thing he doesn't say to me directly all that much.
And some other weird stuff.
And he's worked on some of your weird-ass give-and-take videos, like holding the camera.
Yeah, he's usually the cameraman when I need one. He's up for all that sort of stuff.
He likes my channel. He likes all the procrastinators.
I've actually gotten him into the PCP procrastinated podcast has allowed him to get into everybody who, you know,
into Jesse, into you, into Davoo, into all the other guys. He likes them all.
And through Nate, he's actually started watching anime, starting with Gurren Lagann.
And he's the one who dressed up as Bloodborne, right?
Yeah, he likes buying really cool outfits that he never wears, because he never goes anywhere.
The fucking Bloodborne thing came out of no ways.
You just came into my room dressed like that, and you said, oh, and I was like, oh, shit, I'll get a bit of fullness.
Whenever I see you guys' videos, I feel like you communicate largely through laughs.
We do. You know, it's weird, because it's hard to explain an example.
But say, for example, there's dinner is coming, dinner time. Mom calls up the stairs and only I hear it.
So I go to the door, I open it, and I go, yeah, and then they know exactly what to do.
They just come out. It's not like, yeah, is the word.
It's just the fact that I came to the door and didn't say anything of worth means that it's dinner time.
I know exactly what you're talking about, because I'll go into Victor or Shadesbury would just be like,
just peek open the door, and I was like, yeah.
And they'll be like, yeah, and I'm like, yeah.
And they're like, what do you want?
Oh, there's food. That often happens. I know.
That's cool.
Oh, man. Little brothers. It's fun that we're both, me, you, and DeVoo are all the eldest of three siblings.
Oh, yeah. I think Ben is too.
I meant to ask Nate this when I finally get to his interview, because I'm pretty sure they have a sister that Ben just never brought up in his interview.
Yeah, I don't know why they don't talk about it at all.
Yeah, we never mention her. I don't know the first thing about her.
Apparently she's a tattoo artist.
Oh, yeah, I do know that because Nate said it on Twitter the other day.
But enough about them. This is your fucking interview.
So do you have any plans with your musical career?
You have a band camp, which probably not a lot of people know about, but it has some great songs like Chicken and a Basketball.
That's a fan favorite.
Yeah, Ben loves that fucking song and he always brings it up.
You recently did a rap song about being sick, and that was fucking...
I did a whole album about being sick. I was sick.
And for seven days or so, I think I recorded a song in whatever state I was, and I got worse over the course of the album, and then I got better by the end, and it was really cool.
And it just so happened to end on the day Homestuck ended.
Which has nothing to do with it, but it's cool.
It was completely disgusting, but great in that way.
It was the kind of thing where I was listening to it and I was like, oh no, yeah.
What is the band camp's URL anyways?
I think it's just a hypocrite, like one word, band camp slash hypocrite, I don't know.
You can find it, not too hard. I think I've got it linked on one of my channels.
But yeah, go check that out. There's not too many songs and some of them are pretty good.
I think from the sick album, I'm a piece of shit, it was pretty good. A lot of people like that.
So then, aside from music and YouTube, you also are an animator.
That's what you actually just finished college for, right? You got your degree?
Yeah, I got my degree in animation. I'm an animator. I make things removed.
Is that an associate bachelor's degree, right?
Bachelor's, yeah.
And you made this great student film, Spiders or People 2, which is currently up on Gibb and Take, I think.
Everyone watched that. It's fucking great. I watched it again and I liked it just as much as the first time.
Yeah, I like all the student films I've made. I'm pretty proud of them.
I'm not sure about animation in general, though. I'm good at it, but I'm not a fucking fine artist when it comes to animation.
I can make them and they're fun, but they take a long time.
I'm going to be doing more animation, I think. I've got a potential documentary thing I'm doing.
My parents are probably going to be looking for work for me, which is nice of them, but I don't know.
I think in the case of your animation, personally, I'm less impressed with the animation as I am with the directing of the animation, where your comedic timing is always perfect.
Yeah, everybody has always said that. My comedic timing in editing is my strongest point, and it's true. I know when to start a joke.
And also just knowing the storyboarding element. I don't know if you actually storyboard them, but they're very coherent and easy to follow in a way that I think is incredible.
It's amazing to me that you did everything on Spiders of People, too, because a lot of skillsets went into that. Even the sound effects are great.
Yeah, I guess I'm good at sound design as well. I don't know how. I picked it up and I'm good at noticing when a shot is good and using it in my own stuff, but I don't really go over the storyboards too many times to get them perfect.
Let's do it from over the shoulder, or behind the thing, or from a weird wide angle, I don't know. And it usually works out really well, so I guess I just have a knack for that as well. It's good. I'm good at it.
I agree.
So I would say that this also applies to the live-action segments of your videos. I always find them to be highly inventive and entertaining, and you do lots of little stop-motion stuff.
I think when I look at your videos versus, like, let's say John Tron, whom I know you're in my camp of thinking he's totally gone to shit.
John Tron?
Yeah, right?
Oh, sorry, you cut out while you said John Tron. I thought you didn't say his name.
I was saying that you're in my camp of thinking John Tron's gone to shit, right?
Yeah, yeah.
But he was a huge influence on you.
He was a very huge influence. I mean, the idea that he had started in 2010, and at the time, like, everybody who was big had started, like, as soon as YouTube had started.
And he started in 2010, and he got that big. I was like, whoa, you can still just start whenever you need to, and if you're good, you'll make it.
So, yeah. And he was, like, the best I had seen, aside from AVGN, and I really wanted to...
It rekindled my desire to be one of those guys, because I always thought I wanted to, but I sort of fell out of the idea once I realized how difficult it would be to begin at this stage.
Yeah.
But, I mean, I'm still beginning, kind of, but I'm doing okay. I'll get there.
So, the reason I brought John Tron up is that, like, he's got these videos now where you can take one look at it at any shot, and you'd be like, oh, this is shot on a nice camera.
The sets look expensive. You know, it's, like, quote-unquote, high effort.
But I think the writing and delivery of the jokes is always just kind of, like, whatever.
And when I think of, like, a great use of effort, I think of the Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone opening, where there's a part where, like,
like a hooded cape, like, stop motion animates onto your body.
It looks amazing.
That wasn't stop motion. That was just me filming it in reverse. Well, I filmed it falling off me, and then I did it in reverse.
Oh, okay.
It looked like it was just flying up into me.
Yeah.
It looks hilarious, though. And, like, you've done a lot of tricks like that where you really just do something inventive with the camera.
Lots of green screen, especially all the weird shit on Give and Take.
Like, most of those videos is, like, you had one idea of a cool thing to do with a camera and base the whole video around that, and it's...
I'm always like, man, that's fucking ingenious. Why didn't I think of doing something like that, you know?
Yeah. Really, Give and Take is my experimental grounds, and if something really works, then I'll try and use it in a Hippocrite video.
Yeah.
Yeah, I like doing weird shit with the camera.
It's funny, because all that sort of skit stuff, I never really plan it.
I sort of just say, alright, I know what the voiceover is going to be in the script, and I have ideas for, like, what the slapstick will be in the skit.
But I don't know how I'm going to film it until I'm there, and I tell my brother, alright, stand here, and sort of zoom in as I say this, and then he does.
And then we look at it, and it's like, yeah, that's good, alright, let's make the next thing.
And then I go into the editing thing, and everything looks pretty good.
And even when it doesn't, I can sort of make it look good with, you know, fast cuts and stuff.
Right.
It's fun.
The whole Sly Cooper live-action skit where you break into, like, the, what was it, a museum, that felt so real.
Because it was just your brother who was dressed up as a guard, right?
But he had, like, a legit, is that one of the random outfits he buys?
Like, did he just have that?
I think he just had some cool black gloves, and that made him look official, and some, like, combat, like, black combat trousers.
And he had this weird hook that came off of wardrobe, and he stuck it in his pocket, and on the hook, we put these iron, wrought iron keys that I bought, like, at a souvenir at a castle once.
And it just looked, it was just perfect.
I had this walking stick as a hook, as a cane, and I got him.
Apparently, people went up to him thinking that he was a real bodyguard, and just saying, no, it's just, it's nothing, I'm no one.
That's fantastic.
Like, I really appreciate that kind of stuff, because, you know, I made all those old Project Awesomeness videos, as you've seen, where we really would just, like, take whatever was lying around.
Whatever was lying around the house, and, like, that's our props.
And if you can use those, and make it still look good, and communicate the point, then to me it's even funnier than, like, having the real thing, you know?
Yeah.
It's that sort of, like, homemade quality that, you know, Jon Tron's lacking at the moment.
He's got all this cool stuff, and it's like, okay, you know, it would have been funnier if...
You cut out.
I can't hear you anymore.
Oh no, you're cutting out.
Cut out what happened.
My computer's weird.
So you have this strong fixation on the PlayStation 2, it seems.
What's up with that?
Yeah, it's my, it's my favorite console of all time.
All the best games are on it.
And it, it's the best, it's the best one.
All, all, all of them suck except that one.
Was that your first console, or did you have one before it?
No, I had a PS, PlayStation 1, but I didn't have many, very many games for it.
The PlayStation 2 was when it all sort of got knocked into 12th gear.
And I got all my favorite games were on that.
And then the real reason I think I like the PlayStation 2 so much, or rather that I base my channel off of it,
is because not many people make PS2-based videos, and if they do, they're not very good.
Like there's not a Jon Tron off the PS2 area.
So I am that guy.
Yeah.
Which is odd to think about, but it's, it's true.
Like there's a lot of, like when I got into those, those people like Jon Tron and AVGN,
like I had never played those old games.
So to me it was like, they're talking about a forgotten era.
Like it didn't even occur to me that those were games they actually grew up with.
It's like, I thought they were going back to like before they're even their own time.
Because for me, like PS2 would be, like your videos are like,
gonna take me back to the past.
Like that's how I feel.
Watching Ratchet and Clank.
I'm like, oh Ratchet and Clank, that's, I remember, I was a lad, you know.
Um.
Yeah.
So.
I like, I like all that nostalgic stuff.
Yeah.
And also the PS3 sucks.
That's another thing.
I wanted you to get into that because what is it about everything after the PS2
that you hate besides the Souls games?
Well, what, oh yeah, the Souls games are great.
But I think it was mostly, it was a lot of things.
One of the things was that all my favorite franchises had either been dropped
or replaced with something that sucked, like Uncharted.
Jack was better than Uncharted.
But there's other things like the new Ratchet and Clank game on PS3 wasn't that good
and it ended on a cliffhanger that annoyed me.
And in general, AAA gaming at that time felt more like,
let's see how realistic we can make everything,
rather than let's have a fun, cool world where you can do things.
Right.
Like, I don't know.
It just felt like all my favorite things about the PS2, the colors, the stuff,
the cool characters, the wacky worlds, that was seen as childish.
And now we've got to be making lens flares and shadows that look really pixely
when you look at them, but they're sort of moving, so it's cool.
It's all about the lighting effects and the rendering, and I didn't care for it.
And I just sort of grew out of playing games for a long time.
Yeah.
And since then, you've sort of, like, what games have you liked since the PS2 era?
I've liked plenty of games since the PS2 era.
I think after I got annoyed with the PS3, I sort of went to the DS,
and I played DS games and stuff.
But in console games, it was really just been Dark Souls, Bloodborne, Demon Souls.
I really have had, like, a lot.
They're cool things.
And it's been a long time had it in my head that, to me, the DS was, by far,
the best console for games over the last generation.
Because it really did follow up with the PS2.
The PS2 had an unbelievably huge library of tons of totally unique games,
and the DS had the same.
It had this unbelievably large library of great games.
It's like the best-selling console of all time, but no one talks about it.
It's got Phoenix Wright.
It's got Professor Layden.
Yeah.
Goddamn.
Goddamn things on it.
I think it's a combination of no one knowing how to capture from the DS.
I think that's really hamstrung it from being talked about in games media.
It's so hard to take footage from it and talk about it.
I feel like whenever someone talks about Phoenix Wright,
I know tons of Phoenix Wright fans, but I've seen no Phoenix Wright analysis videos,
with the exception of the one you did on Professor Layton versus Phoenix Wright.
How the fuck did you capture footage for that?
Did you steal it all?
Well, I stole it all.
I either filmed my DS with a camera, or I stole it,
because that's the easiest way to do things.
I don't want to ruin my DS just so I can capture footage.
And even if you get a DS emulator, you still have to fill half the screen with the text box,
and it's weird to put on a YouTube video.
Yeah.
It really works.
It's terrible for filming.
But I do think it had a fuckload of great games,
but they're on the DS, and it pisses me off that they're not all on the Wii U.
If I were the president of Nintendo, I would have said,
hey, we just made a console with two screens, and one's a touchscreen.
Let's make the entire library of the DS available on it,
and it would be worth owning a Wii U just for that,
just to have all the DS games available,
because that's the biggest fucking library of great games of the last 10 years.
I would buy that, even if it was like $200.
Yeah.
What's more than $200?
It's probably $300, but it's worth it.
I bought a PS4, and there were no games for it,
and yet I managed to buy a bunch of games.
I bought a PS4.
I bought a Bloodborne machine, too.
Yeah.
I think I talked you into it, right?
Like, I goaded you and Jesse into it.
I think I just wanted to play Bloodborne in general, but yeah.
Have you used it for anything other than Bloodborne?
Oh, wait, no.
The one reason that I actually went over and bought things other than Bloodborne
is that I learned that Dark Cloud was coming onto it as an HD,
and I bought the HD Dark Cloud, and it's great.
I love it.
The only thing that's wrong with that port or version of Dark Cloud
is that the main theme that plays, for some reason,
I don't know how they fucked it up, but there's like one drum in the beat.
I guess it's like a MIDI track or something,
but there's one drum that's just out of time with the rest of the thing,
and it keeps getting faster and slower, and it's like,
no, guy, you're ruining it.
You're ruining the song.
It's supposed to be the cool bit, because it plays at the title screen,
and then later, like in the last bus, where you're in the Sun Giant,
and you're fighting the Dark Genie in space,
and it plays, and it's just fucking awful, and I cried.
Oh, that's a sad story.
But yeah, aside from that, you should buy a PS4 for Dark Cloud.
I haven't on my PS4.
I have not played more than 45 minutes for that one Let's Play when I was sick.
That's it.
Oh, yeah.
And I'm determined to beat it before I buy Dark Cloud 2, because it's also on there.
Yeah, I don't know whether you should play the whole of Dark Cloud before Dark Cloud 2.
I mean, I love it, but I know that the sequel is more streamlined and a better game in general,
and it has very little, if anything, to do with the first in terms of story.
And a lot of people played the sequel first.
So, you know, I don't blame people for liking that one over the original,
but I still like the original a lot.
Well, I want to play the original anyways, just because it's a classic action RPG,
and that's kind of my thing, is that whole genre.
And it's interesting, if nothing else.
I didn't even, like, I mean, I'd played it as a kid, but never gotten very far in it,
and then, like, your video, when you're like,
oh, there's like five different characters you get to play as.
I'm like, what the fuck?
I didn't even know there were other characters you got at all.
That was a great video, incidentally.
I've said this before, I said this before to you,
but your videos have the highest rate of making me want to play the games immediately.
Like, I actually went out, like, I spent a while trying to track down Dark Cloud for the PS2,
like, because I had seen it one time at a local game store,
and then, like, as soon as your video came out, I went back and tried to find it,
and they didn't have it, and then I would just, like, hunt for it at game stores,
because I didn't want to buy it online, because, ugh.
And then, once it hit the PS4, I was like, oh, yeah, immediately buy that.
And I also bought Professor Layton vs. Phoenix Wright because of your video, like, immediately,
and then never played it for more than 30 minutes.
I'm good at making people spend their money, but not by having fun.
I mean, and I also really wanted to play Jak and Daxter after your video,
but I remember that the exact reason I didn't, and this is probably true of all of them,
but it was because it's always been hard for me to justify playing a game
if I'm not going to make a video about it, and you had already just made a video about it.
So, like, that's always the catch-22 with video game videos,
is it's like, oh, cool, that analysis really made me want to play that game,
but now I can't make an analysis of the game because it already exists,
so I can't play the game.
I totally know how you feel about not feeling right playing a game
when I'm not going to make a video about it,
because that's the whole reason I started the Let's Plays,
aside from the fact that I thought Let's Plays might be fun
and I could maybe get better at talking through them.
I just wanted to play these old games, like I played Rayman 2, which was great,
and I actually beat it for the first time in the Let's Play,
but I would have never played it again,
even though I owned it through digital download or whatever.
I would have never played it if I didn't have a video planned for it,
so that was why I did all those Let's Plays, and then I got bored.
And now I'm doing, like, GRPJ, which is my excuse to play games,
really long games, and not have to record any of the things in them,
so it's more fun.
Good reason to play GRPJ.
It is a very good reason to play GRPJ.
That's, like, for me, when me and Victor started Digi Bros.
The biggest problem I've had with it the whole time
is that Victor will only do it if he gets to play the games,
so I would love to be able to finally play all these video games
and make Let's Plays out of them and make that my excuse,
but I can't do it because Victor won't watch me play video games.
So it never happens.
But I have tried to do that myself.
Like, I really wanted to just play a game,
and I'm like, okay, we're just going to turn on a recording.
And, like, Dark Souls 3, I was convinced I would write something about it,
and I never did.
But I'm finally getting over it, and maybe you can too.
Like, with Doom, that was the moment.
I finally just played a game because I liked it,
with no intentions of writing about it,
and it was a really good time.
Yeah, I mean, I've been playing Twilight Princess today
because I got a TV, and that's cool.
And I have no intention of ever making a video about that
unless, you know, I really feel like it.
But, you know, Zelda games are so well documented,
it's kind of pointless.
What console are you playing it on?
On the Wii.
I got the games.
Wii RectaPray!
Yeah, I would, thank you.
I would let you into my house.
I, uh...
I hate the Wii.
You hate it?
How do you feel about the Wii?
I actually...
I mean, because the PlayStation 3 annoyed me,
and I never cared for the Xbox,
the Wii was my favorite of that generation,
purely by, you know, being the other one.
And I did kind of like Wii Fit,
because it actually made me a jog on the spot,
which I never did, and I have never done since,
because I stopped playing that game.
Not that you need to lose weight or anything,
since you're like 90 pounds.
No, but I don't exercise at all.
Yeah, I'm very small.
I don't eat food.
But I don't go out of my way to go get something.
I just eat what's put in front of my plate.
Or on my plate, rather.
So, uh...
You've covered mostly on your channel
like your favorite games, right?
Yeah.
You sort of make a point to like highlight games
that you really loved from your childhood,
or that still hold up today.
Yeah, it's...
I kind of don't like the whole,
oh, fuck all these shitty games, am I right?
Because, I mean, it's funny to be mad at something,
but it's more interesting when you're mad
at something that fucking tore your soul apart.
Like the Banjo-Kazooie nuts and bolts video.
Like, I don't have something of that equivalent.
Or maybe I do. I don't know.
I'll figure it out if I do.
I mean, if Dark Souls 2 wasn't so well covered,
I'd probably be a good candidate.
Yeah, I would.
But I like just making videos about stuff
that I like with the intent
that I can tell people about it.
Because with all those other sort of games
that people talk about, like Zelda,
I know that those are massively popular
and everybody, oh, is it not recording?
Am I not recording? What's going on?
I had to kick Nate out,
because he made your internet so bad
that I couldn't hear you anymore.
Okay, what was I saying?
Oh yeah, I wanted to make videos about good games,
because other games like Zelda,
they get massive coverage,
and I know loads of people love them.
I don't need to make a video about why Zelda is good.
But I do feel like I need to make a video about
why Wretched and Clank is good,
because I don't hear as many people talk about Wretched and Clank,
or, you know, some more obscure games
like the Professor Layton vs. Phoenix Wright,
which I heard nobody talk about ever.
And it's fucking brilliant.
I saw all these cool things I want to talk about Okami.
People haven't made a really good Okami video.
I'm sure there is one or two.
Well, you know, I've always thought that was fucking weird,
because I loved Wretched and Clank back in the day,
and even back then, I knew,
I've always known that the games sell really well.
Obviously, they keep making more of them.
They've always been considered like a mascot for Sony.
And they get really well critically reviewed.
The three were both like, especially three,
was like hugely well reviewed.
I would see them on...
Yeah, three is great.
I'd see them on TV.
You know, they had like mainstream advertising.
And like, if you go into like a character poll
or a best game ever poll,
then like, they usually do okay.
But yet, no one talks about them.
And I've never understood it.
Like, I've never known anybody in person
who knew Wretched and Clank
until like, you know, some of my friends that I met,
like, later on.
And like, they get no critical analysis.
Nobody ever talks about them
when they're talking about their favorite games.
I'm like, what the fuck?
Like, why does no one talk about these games that are great?
And then you finally came along.
I think, it just feels like
the market of video game reviews
is dominated by early Nintendo fags.
They just like all those early games.
They were there before,
and they were big and good and stuff.
It's like, everything is either...
No one cares about the new stuff.
I think the reason that that era gets glossed over
is that like, everyone wants to talk about new stuff
because it's relevant to everybody.
And then people like to talk about the first classics
because they said a lot of the rules of what stuff came after.
And also, I think they're just easier to talk about.
Like, it's pretty simple to blast through a 30-minute NES game
and deconstruct what makes it great.
Whereas like, I think the PS2 is right in that era
where it wasn't like new ideas.
It was just perfecting ideas, you know?
But I mean, I guess we have like Devil May Cry games
for some reason get like, really well covered by everybody.
So it's not like all PS2 games go by the wayside that way.
Yeah, I think it's mostly the goofy platform of things
because I feel like a lot of people
see Ratchet and Clank and Jack and Dax or anything.
Banjo-Kazoo is better, you know?
They did the mascot animal thing first.
Not at all true.
Not at all.
I mean, I haven't played all of Banjo-Kazoo.
Banjo-Kazoo has the clunkiest fucking controls
and the worst live system ever.
I don't think it's a bad game,
but that game does not hold up with the ease
that like Ratchet and Clank 2 holds up.
Like, you could still play Ratchet and Clank 2 or 3 today
and you'd still have a good time.
Banjo-Kazoo has a lot of antiquated things that like...
I can't help it, I'm sorry.
It's a nightmare.
Hmm?
It...
What? Hippo?
Don't mean to make you cry.
You're popping in and out, fading.
And you sound like a ghost on the shelf.
Carry on, carry on.
I just hear every...
every so many seconds I hear...
I forgot the next lyric.
Am I a scrub or what?
Hey everyone, welcome to the...
Hippo, come back!
...podcast, podcast with me.
What?
Oh, you came back.
Oh, you're there.
That whole last minute or so you've been cut out
and I've been singing.
Yeah, all I heard was just you going like...
Every once in a while I was like,
oh god, he's a ghost.
Yeah, what were you saying?
I don't even know.
Well, I'll just let that be a clusterfuck
for the people to listen to.
Yeah, I'll probably edit some of that out.
I know you won't because it's like an hour in
and you won't find it.
I edited the one I did with Jesse
to remove a bunch of fuckups like that, so...
So, are there any games that you definitely want to cover
on your show that you haven't yet?
I have a list.
I can't find it at the moment,
but I know I want to do Okami.
I want to do the other Wretched and Clank games.
I want to do the other Jack and Dexter games.
I want to do...
What else do I want to do?
There's lots.
Wait, I can look at my...
I can't look at my thing.
My shelf.
My shelf is blocked by a cupboard
and if I move it, it'll be loud.
Here we go, though.
I'm just going to move my cupboard.
Here we go.
It wasn't that loud.
You know what?
I can't see them because they're behind other games,
but forget it.
I have a lot of...
I have a list.
I have a list of cool games to talk about.
It's not just the action platform of mascot things.
It's cool games from the PS2 era.
All the RPGs.
All of them.
Every single one.
I'm going to do all the GRPGs.
I'm going to play all the cool games.
So...
Oh, Ape Escape.
That was a one.
Ape Escape 2.
We were going to do a thing with Jesse, weren't we?
Oh, yeah.
Because Jesse loves Ape Escape
and you love Ape Escape 2.
And then you found out...
Well, I love all the Ape Escapes.
But one of the Ape Escapes had a girl protagonist
and you were like,
Digi, you can do that one
and we can all cover Ape Escape.
That is a great idea.
I totally forgot about that.
I got it out, sir.
But yeah, are you still there?
I'm going to have to pull a plug.
He's a goner.
And I'm the guy with the plug.
See, this is the thing.
My internet's terrible.
Okay, don't worry about it.
It's just terrible
and I can't speak and I can't talk
and he can't hear him.
And I'm sorry.
I didn't mean for this to happen.
Technical difficulties.
Hello?
Is there anybody in there?
Just nod if you can hear me.
Well, if you nod,
I can't see anything really.
So don't nod.
Make a sound if you can hear me.
Hello?
Oh, I was back for a second.
Hey!
Hello?
All I've been hearing is...
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Every couple of minutes.
Oh, this is a train.
But it's not wrecked yet.
We've got it still on the rails.
It's a crazy train.
It's going off the rails.
How much of what I was saying...
It's just gone again.
It's just...
Immediately it's gone.
See, this is what I have to deal with
the latest engines.
I just...
You're looking at me
for internet advice.
Don't.
It's bad.
I don't know how to fix it.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Goodness gracious.
Are you back?
I'm back.
Is someone doing something on your computer right now?
On one of them or something?
Making it worse?
No, I just have terrible internet.
I could ask my brothers to turn their computers off.
I don't know if it'll help.
If they're not actually doing anything on them.
They might be.
I was describing the apescape thing
when you cut out...
And I think it's a good idea
that we should still do at some point.
Yes.
Oh god, I don't remember my follow-up question.
Oh.
G-RPG.
How'd it happen?
Yeah.
Well, I like RPGs.
And there are tons of RPGs I haven't played.
And I wanted to...
You know, it's like before with the Let's Plays.
It's an excuse to play a whole one of them
and make a video about it.
But I didn't want to record the whole RPG
because I know from Spoonie's videos
he's made reviews of Final Fantasy VII and stuff
and Final Fantasy VIII, I mean.
And they take up huge amounts of hard drive space recording
and then you have to look through it
and that idea is terrible.
I don't like that idea.
So I just thought I would steal footage from YouTube
and then talk about it on camera
in a sort of unscripted but kind of scripted way.
And that's why they exist.
Do they actually...
Do they actually take way less effort than a normal video?
Because they end up being long as fuck
and you usually do put in relevant footage.
So...
They're pretty intensive,
but compared to making a full review of an entire RPG
there's not even close to the amount of effort I would have had to put in.
So it's preferable, definitely.
I like putting in relevant footage
just so people get a...
If there's like a cutscene I'm talking about
you can see it.
Because one thing I hate is when...
It's when somebody's talking about something
and the thing that's on screen is just the clip
that's been playing for the last five minutes
and it's actually got nothing to do with what they're saying
and I can't visualize what they're talking about
because they're not showing it.
10 minutes ago and I'm like...
Well, I can't go back.
Can you just show it now?
I just hate that sort of stuff.
With your last GRPJ
Victor was watching it and he was complaining
because you had the laptop right in the middle of the screen
and he was like,
I can't ever tell what the fuck's happening in the cutscenes
because giving slaps tops are the way it.
I was like, well, I don't know if you're really supposed to pay attention to what's on screen.
Why did he edit it to be all relevant footage?
That is the one thing that I'm stupid about.
I don't know, man.
I thought of doing a weird green screen thing as the first thing
and now that's going to be the thing.
I'm going to have a weird green screen.
Partially because I don't want to get copyrighted in just in case
and also because it's hilarious.
But I guess I could just let things...
I can't help it though.
I see the editing thing and I'm like,
well, now I'm going to talk... I'm talking about this.
I'll just show some footage of whatever.
And now I'm talking about a specific thing.
Oh, I got to get that scene.
I mean, I got to get it.
I don't think it would be a problem if not for the giant laptop sitting in front of the screen.
I'll try and figure out a way to make it better for the next one, I guess.
Yeah.
I enjoyed those though.
I hadn't actually watched the Final Fantasy 7 one when it came out
and then after the Kingdom Hearts one I went back and watched the Final Fantasy 7 one
because the FF7 one came out at a time before I just watched every random long ass video.
And I was like, well, I haven't played Final Fantasy 7
so I'm not going to understand or care about any of this.
And then I went back and I was like, oh, this is actually good.
You actually edited this video.
Yeah.
But I definitely want to...
It's disguised as a ramble but it isn't really.
I want to copy the format myself.
Actually, really, that might have been the direct inspiration for the laying around videos that I've been doing this month
where it's like laying around watching Non-Nun Biori until I like it
where I'll watch an episode of the show and then just turn on the camera and ramble at it
because I like this idea of covering the entire thing
just every random thought you had about it through playing
and then just throwing that all out there.
And it's not something that's super reshareable and revisitable the way that a main video is
but if people just want to hear someone talk about Kingdom Hearts, then that could be interesting
which I thought it was interesting and I haven't played that game in fucking 11 years.
Yeah.
A lot of people found it interesting.
I've been getting like a lot of comments from people who are clearly not subscribed.
They just found it.
I guess it's been shared among Kingdom Hearts fans
and people are agreeing with my points even though they still think it's a good game
despite its flaws and I don't know, it's nice.
It's nice that something like this conversational sort of like just talking about a thing
not really with a big point can still get across to a lot of people and they can enjoy it.
I mean what I came to realize over time is that like the amount of effort you put into your video
has nothing to do with how many people will watch it or how much they'll care about it.
It's what the subject matter is.
Like I'm sure that the Kingdom Hearts video probably has as many views as most of the other videos on your channel, right?
Yeah.
So it's like even though it's a lower effort in terms of like being a big cool comedy thing,
I don't imagine people would like patron you as much for those kind of videos,
but people will still watch it and enjoy it and get something out of it
and that's why I've sort of turned to doing like a lot of these 45 minute long vlogs about anime
where it's like people just want to hear me talk about anime.
It doesn't really matter if I have something interesting like or like profound to say.
It's just, hey, what did you think of that show?
Well, let me tell you everything I thought of that show.
So yeah, GRPJ is pretty cool.
I'm copying it wholesale for myself and I'd love it as a GRPJ for myself
because I need a good reason to play these fucking JRPGs.
You could steal the formula if you credit me at the beginning of everything.
Oh, I certainly would.
I don't know if I'd steal your categories or anything.
I would probably just fucking unscripted rant about them or something,
but I would love a GRPJ.
I'm jealous of the fact that you found a GRPJ
because like in the mid-2000s, I was obsessed with JRPGs.
I never beat any of them.
Actually, I think I made a pact with myself that I would finish Persona 3 before the year was over.
Which year?
This year.
Like, I've been putting it off for 10 years and I think I said,
oh, you know what it was?
It was that I have to try to beat Persona 3 and 4 before Persona 5 comes out, I think, was my deal,
which is like this October, probably.
Good luck.
All right, Hippo.
Do you have anything to say about video games other than what I've been asking you
for this interview?
I like shitty graphics.
I like low-resolution things.
Really big pixelated textures like PS1 sort of stuff.
It's really, really cool.
I like the aesthetic more than I like actually good-looking, realistic stuff.
You know, those PS1 games, what bothers me the most is the wobbly thing.
I love the wobbly thing.
It makes me feel dizzy and sick.
I tried to play a vagrant story.
You should put that on your GRPJ list because that's a great JRPG.
It's supposed to have one of the deepest stories in an RPG,
but it's got that wobbly effect to such an extreme that it really makes me want to die.
Even though the aesthetic of the game is great other than that.
I don't know.
I think that I just love, I don't know what it is about the wobbly thing.
It's just like you turn the camera and it moves a little and you like you can see
like things popping in and out of being like correct and wrong.
I don't know.
Something about this just really...
It's like a glitch in the Matrix.
Yeah, I don't know what it is.
I can't explain it.
It's just cool.
Well, I guess for me it's weird because I didn't grow up with it
because I had an N64 which did not have that same thing.
Yes, it's weird.
I guess it's the same generation, so it's not really an upgrade,
but N64 looks much better in general.
Yeah, well it had...
It was the problem with the N64 was that it had better graphical power,
but it had less space because they kept cartridges
and discs could hold more and you could have more of them.
So Final Fantasy VII would never have fit onto an N64 cartridge
because it was four fucking discs or three fucking discs.
So that's why there were no RPGs on the N64 except for Quest 64
which everyone thinks is fucking garbage,
but otherwise it was not a single RPG because they were too fucking big.
Nintendo and their fucking weird decisions.
They never seemed to...
Ever since the N64, I feel like they never have the developer's best interest in mind
when they make their systems.
I don't know.
I think the Wii U is pretty good,
but I don't think people were on board for developing for it because of the Wii.
They thought it was just another gimmick thing.
Well, the Wii U obviously has much higher graphical capabilities and stuff,
but you still can't do...
You couldn't run uncharted on there or something, you know?
I mean, I'm sure that there's a lot of games that would have been cross-platform to the Wii U,
but can't be.
But I don't know.
I don't know to what extent that goes.
Hippo, how about you tell me some stuff about your life?
My history.
Your backstory.
Where does Hippo come from?
You live in London.
You're not even in the United States.
That's true.
I mean, I don't know whether people could tell that I'm English from my accent,
but I am.
I would hope so.
I've had a lot of people over the years, I guess it is now, years,
be surprised when they learn that I'm English instead of like a weird Australian something or other.
That's because most people hear Australians and think they're fucking British.
That is true also.
No one can apparently tell the difference.
But yeah.
And I think it's that a lot of people think Yatzee is Australian because he lives in Australia,
and so people get those accents confused.
And people think Anthony C is...
No, wait.
Anthony C is British, but he lives...
He's British Australian.
Yeah, that's the combo.
No, I live in England, London Place, and that's about that.
I don't know what to say about my backstory.
I went to school.
I didn't like it.
I wanted to be on the school podcast, but I think I was either asleep or the internet didn't work.
But there's school things.
I went and did a lot of art.
I liked art until they kicked me out for drawing.
Not drawing, but like writing.
I want to kill everybody in my art book.
That was the story I wanted to bring onto the school podcast.
Is that I got kicked out of school.
I'd go ahead and tell it here.
Okay.
Well, one day, I was an angry depressed teenager boy, and I wrote my art book.
Fucking, I hate everybody.
Kill, die, murder, or whatever.
Exactly what I said, and I was feeling a bit nervous about it because I knew they would see it,
but I kind of wanted them to see it and read it and be like, oh my goodness.
And they did, but they did more than I thought they would, and they banned me from school.
They said, you can't come in.
And the reason which was hilarious to me and my parents was that I'm a danger to myself and fellow classmates
because they thought I was either suicidal or homicidal from those few words I wrote in my art book.
So I just came into the school the next day.
They didn't even phone me or anything.
They just said, excuse me, you're not allowed in.
You have to go home.
I said, well, I can't.
My mom dropped me off.
I was like, oh, we'll call your mom.
So I just had to sit there being like, what the fuck?
And then they sent me away from home and they said they needed a written doctor's note saying that I was sane or whatever.
Jesus fucking Christ.
It's it was the most overreaction thing that I've ever experienced at school.
And I just fucking, it made me angry.
It made me more angry and more, you know, liable to actually attack people.
And if they had just, you know, given me detention or something, because it was so presumptive.
I don't know.
That's my school story.
It doesn't work.
Although I did have, I did have a lot of fun at doing art in school.
I made a lot of, I did fine art in GCSE, which is good.
I made a lot of sculptures and paintings and I made a man out of tape and he lived in a giant tube out of tape, like black gaffer tape.
And it was all shiny and black and he was shiny and black.
And I made, no, the man was made out of a suit of tape that I made that I could wear and I can still wear because I'm really small.
And it's really weird.
But yeah, art's cool.
And then I went on to college to do a foundation degree because I wasn't sure what I wanted to do.
I was kind of feeling interested in animation, but I didn't feel ready for it.
So I did a foundation year in college and that was fun.
I met a few friends that I now don't talk to, but whatever.
And then I went to, oh, are you going to say someone?
No, you can continue.
And then I went to uni and I did my three year animation degree and I met friends that are really cool.
And I'm keeping in touch with them, which is cool.
We played D&D on, well, we played one session of D&D and I got an animation degree and that's my school career, I guess.
My school journey.
Yeah.
You kind of left unresolved.
After you got expelled from that school, did you get back in or what?
Oh, yeah.
Well, it was just like, I was out for a couple of weeks or maybe a month or something.
And we asked the doctor and they said, we need a fucking note to say that I'm sane.
And they're like, what?
The doctor was like, the fuck?
So she just wrote a note and she said, just let him in.
Like he's fucking, he wrote a little thing in his art book, who cares?
And then the school was like, okay.
And I felt like the reason, no, it was the reason, the reason they sent me home was not so much because they were afraid of me attacking students.
But they didn't want to be responsible for me attacking anybody.
So like if I attacked somebody at school, they didn't want to be seen as the reason.
So like if I was going to a kill myself, they wanted it to be at home.
So that they didn't get in trouble, which was fucking really, I hate them.
I hate them all.
School sucks.
I gotta say, that's the first time I've ever felt lucky about my story that it didn't get to that point.
You heard mine right in the school podcast.
I haven't listened to it yet, but I might have heard it before, but I'll listen to it.
So how did that month treat you?
I mean, it sounds like it was awesome.
You got to not go to school for like a month.
It was kind of awesome.
But at the same time, I think it wasn't GCSE.
I think it was in A level.
So in A level, you choose three subjects and I would chose art, art and photography, I think, and physics.
But I dropped physics.
So it was basically fun times all the times because I liked art and I liked the art department
and I liked sitting in the art department doing whatever I was doing and not going and talking to anyone.
So staying at home was not actually that fun because the only things I could do was play games
and the only game I had at the time that I was trying to be good at playing was Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2
because all the people at school were playing it.
And I felt like I needed to be into a game that everybody was into in order to be popular,
which was what I was trying to do, but I was playing that so much and I got so angry at it that I nearly broke it.
I nearly broke my controller and everything.
So I hate Call of Duty.
Jesus.
It wasn't a good time.
I felt really sad.
So what does the future hold for the hippo man if everything goes according to plan?
The future.
Well, I want to make a bunch of videos by the end of the year and then after that,
well, I'm going to Radcon, your house, the Radconference.
Yes.
And that is somewhat of a test out, a try out for potentially me living either with you or near you
in the future to be able to do more collaborative things with the rest of the PC, the TCP, TPCPC members.
Yeah, that's essentially the purpose of Radcon is.
Yeah.
So let's do things together and see what we can do together and see if like logistically how we could possibly all live together in the future.
So after that, you're the hardest one to move in though because you're in another country and currently no income.
Yeah, not really.
I mean, a Patreon is tiny.
It's like $50, $60 a month, which is not good enough, guys.
Come on, give me some more.
That's my Patreon plug.
There it is.
That's all I got to say about it.
But I want to be making videos so that after Radcon, if I've decided that I want to go to America and it's like seems like a good idea possible to do,
I will try to make as many videos that will get me Patreon money and AdSense money and get growing big channel, big, big money, big, get money, get big money and I want to get big money
so that I can move out safely.
I don't want to go to America and then die in the streets because that's probably what would happen if I went now.
Probably because of the plane ticket alone to get there and then, you know, buying a house, I mean, I don't know, renting an apartment.
It would feel weird and also I'd have to get like a visa or a change the nationality.
I don't know how any of that stuff works.
It's a scary idea to go and live in America forever.
So I want to make sure I'm getting a decent income because it doesn't matter where I do my YouTube videos.
It just matters that I do YouTube videos and I can make money.
Well, that's kind of where I live.
The whole basis of us all moving in together is like that it doesn't matter where you do YouTube from.
So like all of us, like the only people who who like absolutely we know can't just pick up and leave are you because you can't leave England that easily and you don't have any income.
And then Nate because he has a real job and for anyone else it's like the sky is the limit.
Like it doesn't matter where we are.
You can do YouTube from anywhere as long as you have a decent internet connection, which is why Davoo particularly wants to get out of where he is to get a better internet connection.
And Jesse where we don't know about because he takes care of his family and everything.
But yeah, that's pretty much the idea is hey, if we could do it from anywhere, why not do it from right next to each other where we could do way more shit.
It just seems like a good idea.
It'll be really cool, especially having Victor do all our skits.
Yeah, if he's still around, which who knows.
I mean, I haven't seen that motherfucker in like a month because he's been constantly working.
I actually saw him for a brief glimpse like two days ago.
He came in and he was all like, I'm going to Hope's house and then left.
That was it.
That was all I saw of him all week.
I'm not even joking.
That's exactly what he did.
Oh God, he's got a lot of hope in the future.
So you actually you're you're closer to Davoo on the scale of watching all the shit I make.
At least you watch all the Digi Bros.
Yeah.
Yeah, I watch all the Digi Bros.
I watch the Digi Bro.
I watch as much as I can.
I haven't been watching your After Dark vlogs recently because my internet's been so poor.
I have to really pick and choose which videos I let buffer all day.
So I haven't been watching those.
What the fuck is the deal with your internet right now?
What is this nightmare that you've been living in?
All right, hopefully by the time this podcast comes up, it will be sorted.
Although I don't know how long you're going to take to make it to put it up.
Next Tuesday, so six days from now.
All right, probably won't be sorted by then.
But the idea is we had an internet service provider and they went bust.
And then we got shoved into this other one, which was like it consumed it.
I don't really know the specifics.
I just heard this from my parents that they had an internet service provider and it died.
And then we have been swept all the way into this other one, which is absolute garbage.
And it's very difficult to get out because of a weird thing with my dad's company who pays the phone bill.
And it's confusing and I don't get it.
And all it means is that the internet is absolutely abysmal.
So long as there are more than two people using a computer at once in the house.
And there usually is.
That all sounds like it should be illegal.
Yeah.
I don't like it.
I'm sad.
I made a single rage tweet on Twitter about it.
And a guy said, if your internet is so bad, how come you're on Twitter, you idiot?
Or whatever.
You use those arrows, the 4chan arrows.
Twitter is like the easiest fucking site to load in the universe.
It doesn't take a huge load on your internet.
Fuck that guy.
I did.
Fuck your listening. Fuck you, guy.
I mean, I don't really hate him.
It's just in the moment.
And after I responded to him, I said, fucking, I explained that I didn't say all of my internet.
I said, some of my internet, fuck you, guy.
And then he replied with salt.
And then I blocked him because fuck that guy.
That's a very good reaction.
Anyone who uses the word salt deserves to be blocked.
Salt and pepper.
Pepper's okay. Say pepper instead.
Say paprika, anything.
Let's go through some words I know you hate.
Salt, cringe, get good.
Well, you actually enjoy cringe, though.
I enjoy cringe.
It's fun.
It's hilarious.
I know you have a problem with people who try to be dismissive by acting cool.
Like, your opinion doesn't matter because I'm cooler.
You need to get good and stuff like that.
Oh, get good.
Yeah, well, that's the specific term get good is annoying because it exemplifies that.
I guess I just don't like people assuming much of me based on the small things that I say.
And when they look down on me, I'm like, who the hell are you, bitch?
Don't you get angry ever?
You were cut out through half of that sentence, but it's okay because you said the whole thing and it'll be on the recording.
Yep.
How do you spend your time on the internet?
How would you say it's divided between?
Well, a lot of it is YouTube.
A lot of the time, I'm just either watching a YouTube video.
Like, it's very rare that I have no YouTube videos ready to watch.
There's usually I watch Creparion, which is a Hearthstone YouTuber, and he makes two videos a day and they're always interesting to watch because Hearthstone is just fun to watch for me.
And then there's all the stuff the TPC members do.
And I've cut out all of my podcasts.
The only podcast I listen to is the procrastinators podcast if I wasn't on it.
And I think the sleepycast, yeah, those are the only two podcasts I listen to.
I used to listen to a bunch more.
I made a whole ramble about it on my Give and Take channel about how I need to cut out all this stuff because YouTube has taken up so much of my time in general.
I just needed to stop it.
Aside from YouTube, I usually check Twitter a lot and I check Tumblr somewhat, but not really that much anymore.
Because it's generally just kind of...
It's not really a thing you go back to check an update because none of the notifications I get or asks I get are interesting.
I actually don't get asks anymore.
So Twitter is my main sort of let's see what's happening thing and then other than that it's YouTube and I don't think anything else.
I don't do... I don't like streams at all.
Well, you were cut out for me for like the last two minutes and it sounds like you just kept talking.
So that's great.
Did I cut out again or did you cut out?
Jesus Christ.
Damn it.
Hey darkness, my old friend, come in, have a cup of tea.
You don't like tea? You like coffee? Black? Sure.
You are? Darkness? My old friend.
Hey, how's the thing? How's your wife? She's dead? Good. I don't care for her either.
We're halfway there.
Living on a prayer.
Take my hand and make it out there.
Is it? No? No? You made a little noise. You made a little it and that's it. Also, I could hear.
Oh dear.
I can't wait to hear the entire secret other podcast you've been doing with yourself.
All these times that you've cut out.
It's gonna be interesting.
Are you actually here this time?
Yeah, oh.
Hippo.
As soon as you say something.
Hippo!
Fucking gun, you're dead. I'm dead, we're dead. This is the dead podcast.
Hey, you know what? I like murder.
I like murdering internet service providers.
That's fun. You go to their house, they say, excuse me, who are you?
And I just stab you in the brain.
Woo, in the brain. Right there.
I bypass the skin. I bypass the skull.
I stab you directly in the brain with my brain knife.
It cuts only your brain.
I made it especially for you. You sick fuck.
Why do you do this to me?
Why do you do this to this podcast?
I mean, it's probably interesting. Probably hilarious.
Seeing both of us flounder.
Okay, you're back.
Are you back, though?
Okay, you are back. You are actually back.
We are actually back.
For another all too brief period.
Let's see how long that lasts.
It's already over, isn't it?
Are you gone?
Oh.
It's already over.
It's already over! It's already over!
Hippo!
Come back to me.
Ladies and gentlemen,
do you understand the implications of this?
I forgot the rest of that.
Oh, Aaron Hansen.
You don't even try, dude.
Don't even try.
This is the two-way podcast.
Streams.
We're on two different universes now.
Both of us sailing along on the Milky Way.
Individual.
All individually.
And that's the way the cookie rumbles.
That's the way...
That's the way it's meant to be.
That's the way it ought to stay.
You know what?
Wait right there, everyone.
Here we go.
Let's start with a good old...
This...
Oh, fuck.
I did it wrong.
Let's do it again.
Blackbird singing in the dead of night.
Three deep broken wings and learned to climb.
All your life.
You were only waiting for this moment to arrive.
I hate it.
It sucks.
Internet.
Here's a solo.
But I've been...
Are we here?
You spoke too soon, you fool.
Oh, you fool.
You spoke too soon.
Fuck this shit, I'm dead.
Very good at improved guitars.
But here's one from the ages.
Oh no, we're not here.
You're silly, Digi.
You think it's okay.
It's not.
You're gay.
We're in the thing.
The thing that which...
I can't think of the word.
You know what?
It's like the limbo?
That's a bad word.
Limbo.
You were in the limbo.
The limbo of the limbo.
On the window of the windowsill.
It's bad here.
I don't like it very much.
It's got graham on the side.
It's a bad game.
It's not a game.
I'm not talking about a game.
Here's another classic.
You know, I'm not actually very good at that.
Let's click the knuckles.
Alright.
I can't...
Alright, I can.
That's the way you look at the world.
I can.
That's out of tune.
That's why it sounds bad.
It's not me.
Let's do a whole fucking...
I'm tuning my fucking guitar while Digi is like...
Oh, I wish the podcast was working.
But you know what?
Maybe he'll cut his own bit out and this will just be me.
Me and you.
You like TPC?
I like it.
I don't listen to it.
Because I'm usually there.
But when I'm not there, I try to listen to it.
It's fun.
It's nice.
I like being these guys' friends.
They're all my best friends.
They're soul to best times.
I love you all.
I'm burping.
Alright.
You all know the words to this one.
I don't.
I could finish the song, but I messed up.
I'm sorry.
Oh, you heard it.
Oh, he heard it.
He heard some of it.
He was trying to sing along.
I should finish it for him.
I skipped to the other bit.
I don't know what to do.
So, Hippo, give me a state of the Hippo address.
How do you feel about how your life is going right now?
The address?
State?
I feel my life is okay.
I feel my life is actually pretty great.
I'm at home with my parents, but my parents are cool,
so that's not an issue.
They love me, and I love them.
I've got a room.
The construction at my house is finished.
They've got an extension.
So now the house is really cool and new,
and I have a new room, and I have a new TV,
because it's my birthday,
and everything's looking up, really.
All I've got now is to focus on my career,
my money making,
and really, that's going well as well.
Actually, I can't complain.
Aside from the internet,
that'll be fixed within a month, probably.
So, my life's great.
How was yours?
What kind of frequency can we expect
new Hippo Crit videos with?
I'm trying to get them out to a month,
like one every two weeks.
That would be beautiful.
That would be a reality I want to live in.
Yeah.
I've got a follow-up to the miniclip games video coming,
but I don't know whether I'm already too late for that
to become two weeks later.
I don't think so.
I think either it's this week or next week,
well, obviously, it's this week or next week,
but it might be next this week.
I mean, the upload time alone
might make it come out a week later.
That's true.
I actually don't think the upload is that bad.
It's just staying connected.
Like, the connection is just wobbly in it.
It's like, okay, and then it's suddenly gone completely,
and then it's okay, and then it's gone completely.
I guess you could just hear.
It was like that just then.
So, I don't know how much you can say about this,
but there's also some contract work you've been doing, yeah?
Yeah.
I don't think it's, like, it's secret,
but I've written a pilot for a...
not necessarily ever going to be made TV show for teenagers,
a cartoon, animation cartoon,
because a person came to me and said,
I think your animations are funny.
Would you like to help us write a comedy script?
And I did.
I went and talked to them.
I helped design the characters and the idea of the show,
and I helped write the pilot.
I did write the pilot the script, and I sent that in,
and now they're using that in their animation studio
to pitch to a bunch of different studios' channels,
that is, to get them green lit and stuff.
That's all that's going on with that.
So, I don't know whether that will become anything,
but I'm sure I'll work with them in the future.
So, that's cool.
I had been under the impression it was a children's show you guys were making.
It was like a pre-bubescent children's,
sort of like 13, 12, sort of,
because it's for kids, but it's kind of dark,
because it's about death.
It's a train of ghosts.
It wasn't really a train of ghosts.
It started off as a train of ghosts,
and it was going to be spirited away.
That's the idea that I had in my head of what it would look like.
But like a show set on a train,
filled with mythical beasts and creatures and witches
and cool things like that.
Creatures of Greek myths and stuff,
you know, death, the grim reaper himself would be a character,
and he would be cool.
He would be all reserved and read the newspaper and stuff.
Just, you know, sit in the corner and not talk to anybody.
Be really shy. That was the thing with death.
He's really shy.
He doesn't like talking to people,
because, you know, he kills them eventually.
So, it's just sort of like, oh, no, no, that's fine.
I'll just sit here.
But yeah, the point of the show is there's a little girl
and she's an orphan,
and the orphanage is horrible and evil and despicable,
and the person there is evil, and she runs away
and she finds a magic train, she jumps on,
and before she thinks about where the train would be going.
And it turns out it's a ghost train with ghosts,
and it's cool, and she has adventures on the train.
I think in the scripts that I wrote,
she meets the spider girl, which is basically Muffet,
but a little girl Muffet from Undertale,
which is adorable to me,
especially the character design they based off of that.
I don't know whether I can show anybody the character designs,
but I don't think there's much point to it,
seeing as the show may never be made,
but it's cool.
Specifically, the person who brought you on to do this
was Anna Esther Volos, right?
That's how you pronounce her name.
Yeah, I don't know either, but Anna Esther Volos,
she's great, she's cool, you're cool,
you might be listening to this.
The longest time and highest paying patron
of a lot of the PCP.
Yeah, it's kind of impressive.
She was my biggest patron for a very, very long time,
but she also has her own YouTube channel
called Anna Stays At Home,
where she did a couple of really short anime analysis,
one for Ava and one for Utana,
specifically the ending of Utana,
like the last episode,
and a part of End of Ava as well,
and then this long-ass Rambley vlog about Dragon Age.
Which one had the Madagascar comparison?
That's the Ava one.
I always think of that one as the Madagascar one.
It's such a cool comparison to make.
Yeah, I never would have imagined someone
using Madagascar to analyze Ava.
I feel like there's not a lot of crossover
in people who have even seen both of those.
I certainly haven't seen Madagascar.
That's a good show.
I think Nate, for some reason,
doesn't like the idea of Dreamworks at all,
so he hasn't watched any of those things.
Kung Fu Panda and Madagascar are a great series of trilogies.
You should watch them if you like kids films.
I just heard that Madagascar was shit,
so that's why I never watched it.
It's not the best thing ever,
but Kung Fu Panda is fucking amazing.
Kung Fu Panda is the new Shrek.
Shrek is good,
and then Kung Fu Panda is the next one up.
Madagascar is kind of worse than both of them,
but it's still alright.
I really want to watch Shrek,
because I've gotten the impression
people don't look back fondly on Shrek.
It's become like a meme,
and it seems like people really hate that movie,
and I remember loving it as a kid.
I watched it a lot of times.
What I think is people remember it as a kid,
and then they look back at it,
and they're like,
whoa, all this is weird,
and then they made a meme out of it because of that,
but then, you know, as memes stewed,
they just became...
I really hate Shrek.
Well, they're dumb.
It's got great comedy.
Some animation fans, you know?
Yeah, I mean, it was a fun movie.
I don't remember anything about it that I'd be like,
oh, fucking Shrek is garbage.
I remember being pretty okay.
Shrek is great. Shrek 1 is great.
Shrek 2 is brilliant,
and then Shrek 3 and 4 is just sort of like,
yeah, I guess.
That's how they went,
but nobody can argue that Shrek and Shrek 2
are terrible or bad.
They're stupid if they do.
Yeah.
Ooh, what are some of your favorite movies, Hippo?
Are you into movies?
I'm not actually into movies that much,
mostly because I don't like sitting down
and not being able to just leave.
Like, with a TV show...
Yeah, that's a big part of why I didn't get into movies
for a long time.
There was the last hour, maybe,
or 30 minutes or something,
and if you don't want to watch another one,
it's easy to just stop.
But the movie, it doesn't feel right to pause a movie
and then come back to it,
especially since DVDs, the early DVDs,
they didn't save your place.
They used to. They now do,
but they didn't use to,
and you couldn't really just leave it
until another day.
Yeah, movies.
I like Reservoir Dogs.
I like A Terminator.
I like...
I don't know. I like Alien 1.
I haven't seen that many,
but I have seen a lot of good classics.
A lot of animated movies.
I like a lot of Disney stuff.
What's your favorite Disney?
Ooh.
The favorite.
I like Lilo and Stitch.
Oh, that is a good one.
Yeah, I think...
It's hard,
because every time I think of my favorite,
I forget...
I did mention this before.
I forget all the other ones.
I can only think of Hercules because
I just listened to the Munchie podcast
and he said he liked Hercules.
I also like Hercules a lot.
I like Hercules a lot more,
but I can't remember.
But I think my favorite animated movie
is The Brave Little Toaster,
which I know Jesse is a fan of.
Oh, yeah, you mentioned this.
You're a huge fan of The Brave Little Toaster.
Yeah, Brave Little Toaster 2 and 3
were...
Disney took the sequel,
the rest of the sequels,
which are not even slightly as good.
Brave Little Toaster 1
is like a super amazing adventure
and you definitely see it.
It's the grace...
Yeah.
It's like a meatloaf song
in the middle of the movie.
It's awesome.
Have you seen it?
Yeah, I saw the first one probably
like three or four times,
and then I know I saw the second and third
and I remember even as a kid being like,
these suck!
They just kind of did the same thing again,
but with none of the emotions.
Yeah.
And the music, I think...
I'm not sure,
but I think the music in Brave Little Toaster
made me interested in becoming a musician
down the line.
Because I just love those songs so much.
I had the old VHS tape
and I would go to the songs part,
any of the songs,
apart from the first one, which is sort of a sing-song thing.
But like the techno one at the end
with all the high-tech computers,
I would get to that point
and rewind and listen to it again,
and I would dance all the time.
This is my favorite song ever.
I love that fucking movie.
Yeah, oh man.
I'm just looking at the soundtrack.
I was trying to see
if anyone...
They have the spooky one in the middle.
Yeah.
I just remember how much,
like, Worthless is like a legit
classic rock song.
It's like a full-on,
full-on or something.
It's great. Good music.
Cool movie.
So, recently...
I guess not too recently
at this point, but
you kind of got into anime
through the PCP, yeah?
Yeah.
Before I met
you and Nate and all that,
I had watched a few anime, I think.
Well, I've watched Naruto Bleach in One Piece
and Lucky Star
and that's about it.
I think I watched
On a Guy Teacher or something weird
as well.
But I've never really
gotten into it
aside from liking One Piece so much
that it's my favorite thing.
But you're a huge manga guy, though, right?
Or much bigger of a manga guy.
Only because
I stopped watching the anime because
the manga was coming out quicker.
I don't just mean of One Piece,
but you seem to have read a lot
of the long-running
great manga. You've read Bakumon
in I-Shield 21 and...
Once I started reading the manga
of One Piece and stuff
and Naruto and Bleach,
I think I...
I didn't read the manga of Death Note.
I was a fan of Death Note as well, anime.
But on those sites,
I saw all these things. I was like,
I'm bored. I'll read I-Shield 21
and it just so happened to be the fucking
thing I've ever seen in terms of sports
manga. And then there's
there's a...
What did you say, Bakumon?
I think it was just because those ones were like
high up on the popular
list next to One Piece.
At a certain time, I was like, oh cool,
I'll check it out. I actually
read Kimi Nii Torokai
as well because that was up there for a while.
How did it... did it frustrate
you to no end while reading it?
That the two never fucking
hooked up for so fucking long?
I think I actually
gave up of reading it, but it was kind of
cute.
There's quite a lot of
manga I kind of forget about that I've
read. Like Ichigo 100%.
I think I was into
that sort of romance sort of stuff for a while.
That was cool, except
it wasn't because it took too long
for anything to happen.
Did you ever get into like Negima
or Love Hina or any of those?
Love Hina, I got into the dating
sim that was around. The Flash
dating sim of Love Hina. I didn't know what Love Hina
was, but it was a dating sim
and it was like, ugh,
the girls, you date them.
Like a fan made pornographic dating
sim, right?
I don't think I ever got to the porn part
if there was.
But yeah, it was probably fan made. I didn't know
anything about it, but it was really shitty
looking and it was a really shitty sort of flash
game with gradients everywhere.
You know, the sort of flash gradients.
Yeah. So what
animes are you into now?
I'm going to go ahead and guess the same ones
the rest of the PCP are into, which is
all the Gainax shows.
Yeah, there's Cowboy Bebop,
Space Dandy, Killer Kill,
Gurren Lagann, Gurren Lagoon,
Neon Genesis
Ava, and
what else?
It's basically just stuff that I've heard you say
is considered
really a classic.
And I felt like I wanted to get into all the classics
because they're at least guaranteed to be
good. Like I didn't want to go into
experimenting.
I think it's something to do
with the kinds of people
we all are and the kinds of shows
that Gainax makes, that
there's definitely a correlation there
because we all love Gainax shows.
Like we all love Ava, we all love
Killer Kill and Gurren Lagoon.
I guess Nate doesn't love Killer Kill that much, but like
he's been a weirdo
about that. He clearly
would like it. He just feels that Gurren Lagoon
is my baby and it's similar.
Fuck it. Stupid.
Well, what did you think of, did you see
Fully Coolie?
Oh yeah, I saw Fully Coolie as well. That was good.
I didn't get it, but I like it.
Something about
those shows, it's just
like that studio
the way they make shows
because I mean those are all popular, but they're not like
you know, everyone
loves them and yet within our chat
everyone loves them.
Like there's no dissenting opinion
about Gainax shows
in our chat. And like there's kind of a
period at the start of
where like
we all simultaneously
watched like a bunch of them
because it was like you and Jesse
both watched Killer Kill at like
the same time.
I think it was, I don't know
whether it was me.
I feel like my decision, oh yeah
I watched Gun Buster and Die Buster
as well and K-On, I forgot.
Yeah, well because K-On was
like I definitely remember that
I got you to start watching K-On
and then Jesse started watching K-On
and then
I as a result of that
made my K-On video
like because you guys were watching it
it got me watching it again
whenever any of us
are like revisiting something and talking about it
in the chat you get all hyped about it
like if you or anyone
were playing a game that I had made a review on
and you'd never played it before
and you were talking about it and be like yeah cool
it's this
sort of thing because like I remember I was watching
Ava and talking about it in the chat and Jesse
was like oh shit Ava's so cool and then
I feel like that prompted him to go
on his crazy Ava binge
and start writing fan sexy stuff.
That did happen. Yeah it was
all like early
2014, early 2015
there was this period where we were all kind of
watching the same anime like you watched
Kill La Kill, Jesse watched it and then
as a result of you guys watching it
I watched it again and then
that also inspired my
Guru on the Gun vs. Kill La because then you watched Guru on the Gun
and so I watched both shows back to back
and wrote that video
comparing them and then
you started watching Ava and I started
doing my Ava videos not long after that
so like pretty much whatever
you were watching we all
ended up watching at the same time
and that sort of
spawned some of those old videos
it was great
it was a great time and then
it kind of stopped I guess because
we watched all the...
the run out of cool anime
I guess because of the fact that
those are all shows that both Nate and Jesse
also know about then
it's easier for me to be like
we all kind of like Ava so of course
you had to watch it or Cowboy Bebop
it was like me because I was
the new but I was new to it
and you were like you were all
feeling my new good
vibes about it
and not too long later like
DeVoo watched all those shows once he joined the chat
because like we kept talking about all of them
you know
well I don't know I guess he'd already seen Kill La Kill
and Girl in the Gaunt but he definitely watched
Cowboy Bebop and Ava like once he started
hanging out with us and shit
but yeah like
I guess that's like the TPC canon
is like all the guy next shows
and Cowboy Bebop and Space Dandy
have you not watched Samurai Shampoo yet?
I have not
but you should probably
watch that one because it's the
it's like the third
in the trilogy of Cowboy Bebop and Space Dandy
and Samurai Shampoo
or it's the one in the middle
which me and Jesse are both long time fans of
though Jesse
has said he can't watch Samurai Shampoo
the one that Jesse really likes
the ninja one
there's a ninja one
that Jesse really likes
I forget it
a ninja
oh ninja scroll
yeah the movie
oh is it a movie? well I'll watch it
it's like a movie from the
mid 90's that's just like nothing but violence
and kicking gas
it's great and tits
tits violence and kicking gas
um
yeah
it's harder for me to like
get you to watch
other anime that I like
because
it's hard to get
everyone into something
I feel like I'm the only guy
in the PCP who
people say this thing is good
and I immediately want to check it out
everyone else seems to really need to have
their arm twisted
in order to get into something
yeah me more than most
I feel like my time is
precious even though I don't do much with it
a lot of the time
I have so many other things to
get into that I already know that I want to
get into why would I get into this new thing
you know
I mean I totally get it
with like you say
berserk is great and you would really like it
I'm like sure
yeah we got you to read berserk I forgot
then I eventually did and it's the greatest
fucking thing ever
well that was one that like
I very deliberately wanted you
to read berserk because
knowing your taste I felt like it was perfect
for you
because it's got like you know
it's fantasy with skeletons
and it's got this dark plot
and this like really strong main character
and you like shows like Breaking Bad
and stuff like that and I felt like it's along those
lines in a way
so I felt like
you needed to read berserk
and I was not going to stop
talking about it until you did it
yeah there are actually quite a lot of like
really
saddening moments like not saddening but like
like you just feel like shit after
like that bit where there's like
that how do you explain it
it's like a big sack of
ooze and they throw the women in it
and they get
raped through the ooze and then they
spawn demon babies
and that's just a fucking
and it's like oh
disgusting but I kind of like it
there's definitely a period
like I guess it's like right around when shirk
showed up and like
it was kind of becoming like a little too
magical girly and then I think maybe
he wanted to like throw it back in the other direction
and just made like a lot of rapes happen
like in a row and it was like
this has gotten exponentially
rapier
um yeah
there's a lot of rape in berserk
I remember reading this like
one of my first exposures to berserk was this like
4chan copypasta was just
this guy going on a rant about how he was like
every single fucking
chapter I see some new kind of dick
it's like mirage just sits around dreaming up
new kinds of demon dicks I've seen every
kind of dick imaginable raping
every kind of human imaginable
and I was like yeah that's
that's pretty accurate that's what berserk
is
myriad colors phantom dicks
uh
so I guess that's
all the animes
what's your favorite anime
what's the best one I guess one piece
well I don't know what yeah the manga
the manga is the best one ever I don't know about the anime
I mean I watched like
I don't know how many episodes there are
I guess 300 I watched
400 I don't know a lot of
episodes of that anime because I didn't know
like anime could be more than just
what that show was which was kind of
limited like it it looked like
the manga but it wasn't as
well produced as
other anime that I've seen since
um so I don't know whether I'd like
that the most but I think
it's either Gurren Lagann
plus the movie the second
movie with the giant guy
giant Kamina space Kamina
that's important you need that I don't know
why that didn't know why that wasn't wasn't
in the show because I kept saying I kept
seeing that that scene
of him you know
be a huge Kamina and he wasn't
in the show and I was like oh what
happened um
so it's either that or
uh K-On I think
yeah
I'm not I'm not sure probably
both together
I gotta talk about this in this podcast
because I don't know when else I'd get the opportunity
the
like the specific
instance that caused me to rewatch
K-On and write about it and actually
I think this instance is what made K-On
into my number one favorite anime and it's all
because of you because
of Otacon
2014 because
I mean not Otacon uh BronyCon
2014 because that's the year you didn't get to go
and you went to
uh that camp
thing you were talking about where you take care of disabled kids
um
and there's a
two-part episode of K-On
in season two it's episodes four and five
where in episode four
um all the older girls
go on this trip to
oh what was it Kyoto I think
yeah um
yeah they go on a trip to Kyoto and they all hang out
and like
you know they're telling all these stories to each other
and like they come up with these
memes with within themselves
like where they all just up at night saying skull
and lycopene
for some reason and uh
it's just it's
it's really adorable but like uh
Azusa the youngest member
didn't get to go um
cause she was in you know another grade
so then in the next episode we see what
she was doing like at home
with the with her other two friends
and like you know like she keeps getting
texts from the other girls and she's like
totally jealous that she didn't get to go
but uh you know she has her own little adventure
and like
the parallel between the
horseshoe crew and and you
not getting to go and you being the youngest
member and you having to do something else
it was like spot on
how accurate it was you know
we came back with our memes are
the lord of shit mountain meme
that we were all saying and stuff and
and then I literally
just thinking about this like once I
realized cause I had already been
thinking that our adventure
reminded me of episode four like when we
were up all night like saying these things and giggling
I was like oh this is just like that scene from K-On
and then once I realized
that you were Azunyan I remember like screaming
in the chat about it like oh my god
Gibbons Azunyan and
I just started fucking crying
like I just started losing my shit
all over the place over the fact
that I had just lived out a
K-On arc and like
that legitimately was like such a powerful
feeling that I was like K-On might be
the best anime ever
and then I watched it again
and I cried during those episodes
just thinking about it like I actually
cried a lot at the like
I was a little like
I think I was on painkillers at the time cause
I had broken my foot I don't know if that made me
more emotional but I like consistently
kept crying while watching K-On
and thinking about you
and how you were Azunyan and I kept
messaging you like as I was watching the show I was like
everything about Azunyan is what you are
she's into Dad Rock
her parents are musicians
yeah I was gonna say like
she made a reference to Jimi Hendrix
and no she made a difference
a reference to Jimi Page which is the lead
guitarist of Led Zipna it was like
whoa nobody does that everybody talks about Hendrix
nobody talks about Page she's the coolest
I like her so yeah
even on that level
as a character I identify
with her more than the others
I had said out that I thought
um
Jesse
I think I said Jesse was Yui
and that cause the way he
acted around you was like Yui and Azunyan
where Jesse always like acted
very like protective of you and like you were
his little brother and like you're his favorite
kind of thing
and it just really reminded me of Yui and Azusa
and like Nate is obviously
fuckin
Ritsu and Ben would be
Mio but that's not really a good
comparison and then I think I had myself
as Sumugi
and Tom
as Notoka
and I guess now we have Jeff so he has to be
like
Jun-chan I guess
I don't know
I don't know who he would be I guess uh
Mage can be Yui
why not I just
I had to go through all of them but yeah
it was just really striking
and I kept that was what got you to watch
Kaon I think was that I kept saying
uh like I kept saying
you're just like Azusa and then you decided
to watch it on that basis and then we
kind of like finished it up around the
same time and uh
and you got to the movie which was in London and it was
like literally your hometown
yeah the place
where they play on the big grass thing
is actually a place that I know
so there was a few places like that
but I just like oh I know that I know
that sign I know that corner they obviously
went to London to get reference
images which is really cool
yeah it's a perfect show
it's a
it's a 10 out of 10
it's the best anime ever
makes me uh makes my
makes my pee pee go poo poo
I guess
that's a good thing
yeah
that's a good question hippo
what makes your pee pee go poo poo
uh
a titi
that's a perfect answer
tell me about your waifus
oh yeah
um
I talked about this a bit in the waifus cast I think
I can't remember
I have a bunch
yeah that's like the second one
yeah
um there's a vriska
who is my number one I think
yeah vriska from homestuck
diamond tiara from my little pony
I try to collect one from each thing I like
a lot um
I think uh
who else is there
it's Marceline from Adventure Time
uh
uh and Undyne from
Undyne from Undertale
and Raven from Teen Titans
you I think you
you did mention at one point that I
I tend towards gray girls
and it just so happens that I did love
Raven as well
so yeah all of them are either like
other than diamond tiara they are all
literally gray skinned
how the fuck does that happen
that's like the oldest coincidence
I mean they all like
they'll have similarities in their
personality that even if they weren't
gray you would understand why you liked
all of them but the point
stands that they are all gray skinned
uh with the exception of
the pink pony
yeah who just so happens
to have a gray skin
counterpart that I'm not into
as much
a weird missed opportunity there
but I guess the exception proves the rule
yeah so my wife who's
if you know those characters
you can tell that they're all bitches
they're all bitchy they're all
powerful strong independent women
they boss
people around and I guess
I like that in a woman I'm not sure
oh my god have you seen
panty and stocking with garter belt
I know I didn't
oh I think you would really like that show
I think you will like all the girls in that
show
all bitchy powerful crazy women
I can't
think of which one will be your favorite because I don't
I don't know if it'd be panty or stocking
it'd probably be one of the demon girls
scanty and knee socks
because they're more of like the domineering
type they both believe in like
absolute order
but they're like the bad guys
because the main characters are all about anarchy
but they're the good guys
it's great you will love that fucking show
okay I
definitely guarantee it's the same director as
girl in the gun and kill I kill
and uh
Davoo's a big fan Jesse hated it
but he only watched the first two episodes and he watched
them dubbed and he really
hated that the girls
swear constantly and it sounds
terrible
it does sound terrible dubbed I looked at it
um well because of the swearing
yeah that's the funny thing about it
is that like people constantly say that
you like that's one of those shows that everyone's like
oh you have to watch it dubbed because the swearing
is so funny and I'm like no the swearing
sounds gross in English
because what makes it funny in Japanese
is that they use English
swear words randomly
in their sentences and it's really
fucking hilarious because they'll say like
oh do that
you know and it's really fucking funny
one of my favorite things in anime
is Japanese voice actors
saying English words
yeah I just love that so much
they do it constantly and it's mostly bitch
they'll say
bitch
like what the fuck
happens a lot
it's great I find that way funnier
than some like
American girl just going what the fuck
you fucking bitch
and I'm just like oh come on
that's tacky
you know
yeah
I should watch that then that's one on the list
yes it's
pretty short so you could probably do it in like a day
but it's got that
old school cartoon
episode setup where each episode is
like two 15 minute parts
that have like an opening title
card type thing like Ed and Nettie used to
have and stuff like that
it's pretty cool
people always talk about it's very influenced by
western cartoons but not to the extent
that people make it out like it is
people make it out like that's all the show is
is like a reference to western cartoons
but it is it's definitely
heavily influenced by them and it's
a good
yeah
yeah I'm still here
that's where you might have cut out again cause DeVoo
joined in and I'm like oh no
it's gonna be just like when Nate joined in
it feels stable
we can keep going
we've been going strong for a good little while
so
you have made the remark
that you think that you're not a good
drawer
yeah
yeah I mean
the draw costs
both of them I'm ashamed of
because the first one I was being like haha
I'm bad but then
they were all so good it was like
why did I do that why didn't I try
like even if I tried my best
it wouldn't have been as good as them
at least I would have looked not terrible bad
and then the second one I thought
I'll try really good but then everyone was
like hilarious and interesting
and I was like damn
I should have been hilarious and interesting for this one
I just fucked up both times
so people don't know
unless they see my deviant art
what I'm good at drawing at
I don't know I'm not
like I used to be really good
I mean I could draw like a
really good life drawing of a person
I have lots of good
drawings that I've done
but when it comes to a tablet
I'm generally just sort of
fucking I'm bad I'm worse
I gotta learn
how to use a tablet better
even though I've made three animated films with it
but you said
that's why you like animation because it hides
how bad you are at drawing
yeah yeah you can
you can draw some like
my first film the fish at the door one
the reason all the frames wobble
so much is because I drew the first guy
I was like
it doesn't look right
it doesn't look good I can't keep him on
screen for more than one second
but I gotta so I just drew the same frame
over again and made it loop
so that it was deliberately wobbly
and then it was cool
yeah it was adorable
yeah people liked it
yeah yeah
huge
I don't know why I keep
lapsing into gudra these days
I think a gudra bit me
and I've just been like
like wear gudraing
got a weird gooey rash on your back
yeah oh god
oh gudra
that's disgusting
oh my god it's like a
ren and stimpy image in my head now
oh no
uh
I always liked your art style
I still think your drawings are good
I liked your gudra
I liked the face on it
I described it as a gormless expression
I think
yeah I mean I don't think
I'm bad at drawing I just
like in comparison to people
like Ben even
people like Ben I mean Tom and major
like they can draw like pro
fashionals and Ben's like really
got a unique style that's very
Ben and it works and it's
cool and then I've got mine which is
like it's a style
but it's very easily
replicatable I think
because it's simple I don't know I could
tell your style immediately when I see it
like every time you ever drew
like a pony character
I would know that you had drawn it
oh well yeah now that you say that I guess
that is true my pony Osea was
very different from everyone else's
because I drew it myself
and it was good
both you and Ben had that
like that kind of style where like
because me and Jesse got like you've drawn
both mine and Jesse's
ponies I think in your style
for like use in different
things and
I draw your guy
once for the analysis
compilation and then I made a bunch
of poses for Jesse for a horseshoe
finale when he wanted to act
like me which was cool
yeah
I had to stop myself before I
go full goo
you
you're trying
your main career goal
is to be a YouTuber right like that's the
one you want to pursue the most
yeah
I
I mean I'm
it's kind of weird because like the
communities I have I could become
an actual animator or
a writer or a musician if I just
went in one direction or the other
I was already a pretty good musician by the time
I was considering going for an animation
degree
and it was like what do I do do I do
music do I go on the road or become
a band guy or do I do animation and do
all that I don't know whether I like
animation so I had to make a decision
then I chose animation and now
after doing three years of it I'm not sure
I would like to do that for my entire life although
I could I just and then
YouTube became a possibility
that I was getting better at and I made
a few videos and they were good and I really like
them and I think I could be better I could be
one of those 900k
sub weirdos
in the gaming community
like if I try this like
I have opportunities and there's too
many good ones to pick and it's kind of hard
to decide but I guess YouTube right
now I'm doing YouTube
while I wait for
potential other things
but I want YouTube to
if it if while I'm
waiting to do other things my YouTube grows
to a point where I can say okay
that's what I'm gonna do and that's what
I'll do
well I think what's great
about YouTube is that it's
pretty easy to imagine how
all of those talents can be used
in YouTube videos
like you know you can
pretty easily like incorporate
animations and music and all that
into a video we all just
saw I mean Nate didn't make
the music itself but what he did with
that Kenny Logan song and his
new video was like yeah we should
be this is a good idea like
this is a good way to make a funny YouTube
video is to like
if you can sing then sing in a
video you know if you can play guitar
find a way to get guitar in there
or like Yotam Perrell where
he does like his animations
with songs and shit and
and then just makes like whole albums out
of nowhere really the
YouTube is most likely
the best
like out of the best decision
to go for but
it's been slow so I don't know I just
I just need to be making more videos
more quickly and putting
them on the internet yeah I think
that's like the the big fear
that I have like with or not fear
so much is like what I need to see with you
and Nate is like
we all kind of are
under this mindset of like we're never
gonna know for sure if you would be
successful until you get fast
because like if you
do put out like 30 videos
in a year and
you still don't get big
then it'll be like okay maybe
maybe it's not happening you know
but what it's only like two videos
a year like you did in the last year
that it's like well we can't really say
for sure until you know
we get a better read on the same with Nate
where it's like his channel is growing really slow
because he's putting out videos
really slow
and like
he's got more subs than me though that fuck
yeah
but then you've got like Jesse over there who's
puts out videos constantly and doesn't grow
but he has a huge
Patreon so like you know maybe
that maybe you guys will end up like that like it's really
hard to say but until you have enough
videos I don't think any
I just don't think we can judge it you know
that's why I'm trying to do
two per month until the end of the year to see what happens
yeah
I really gotta buckle down
yeah I'm looking forward to it
because
number one thing I want
in the world is
more best guy ever more
hypocrite
and more of my Japanese anime
as opposed to
more edless chess blogs
in blue glows
not that I don't enjoy those
but god damn it
I need to see everybody on top
of the world
not just me and Jeff
Jeff with his fucking
like 10 avenues of income
that he has now that son of a bitch
fucking Jeff
who is he
I don't know I can
I don't know him
we talked once about
about playing Game Boy Advance in bed
and that's it
that's true you haven't really talked to him
much at all
he makes too much money
and therefore he's
piece of shit
who are your favorite YouTubers
currently and of all time
currently
I don't know I really
I'm only really watching the
procrastinators plus
the Sleepycast
and
that Hosto and Guy Creparion
and Creparion's fun
but he's not like a really great YouTuber
right
yeah I don't know
I forget all of the ones that I like
all of the ones
I know you like
yeah go ahead
you said Yotam Peril
is a girl animator
yeah
he's cool I like his stuff I like
Hot Diggity Demon as well
really great animations like
ridiculously good for YouTube
he doesn't get paid enough
he puts way too much work
into his animations
they come out very
very rarely and I often
feel like
the quality of the writing
does not deserve the level of
animation he puts into them
I don't often find them that funny
I'm just like blown away
by how much effort he put into something
that is sometimes just weird
not even really funny
I guess
you commissioned an art piece from him
of Riska
I did he was doing commissions
and he never does those
so I paid him
a bunch of money
for Riska with a hippo
with a little hat
and that's cute and I love it
he's
I think it's just his art style and his animation skill
that I really like so much
um
in terms of favorite you oh
ABGM is probably my favorite YouTuber
because
he's got such a great
background
he's really charming and I love him
and he's still not shit
yeah
there was a portion
of ABGM
in episodes during which he was
filming his movie
that were sort of
I don't know but then afterwards
there was only like four or five of those
that were just sort of okay
but they were never bad
they always were decent enough
you know better than most
it's amazing that he's
gone so far I mean he's
clearly a genius
clearly got the
power
I know you used to be a big
total biscuit fan right
oh yeah I like total biscuit
he doesn't really make
he's never really made um
single videos that have like blown me away
I just really respect him as like a
journalist or not really a journalist
but like a commentator
like he has a lot of correct opinions
about lots of issues about gaming
news and stuff
I always love his content patch
I used to love listening to him
on the podcast because that was fun
but the podcast takes too long
and it's not that fun
not fun enough to waste like
three hours every week
right
but I like him he's really good
at the news thing
you used to be a big
Game Grumps fan right
oh yeah
yeah John Grumps is my favorite let's play
series of all time
I recently rewatched
basically all of it
which was kind of you know
I tried to watch from the very beginning
in order of playlists
um
and I got like
I got quite close to the end
I think I was like at Mario
for something
something that I didn't remember really
watching the first time
and then I got bored
but yeah that's like
a huge amount of my favorite comedy
comes from John Era Grumps
Dan Era Grumps is also great
but it feels different and
well you know actually now I think about it
that's also got a huge amount of hilarious moments
yeah
but we all kind of like Grumps is great
there was like a huge
mass exodus of TPC
members from watching Game Grumps
like at the start of this year
yeah they just
they were doing the fucking Mario Maker
thing and they got
they finished Bloodborne they did Mario Maker
and some of the game
that nobody cares about and they just kept doing
Mario Maker and it was boring
and we all gave up
and quit and I don't think any of us
have really gone back except to
occasionally look at the weird celebrity guests
that you've been getting
like that what's the guy
Stevo
I ended up listening to that
fucking Sanchez I don't want to get into that again
my Digi Rose fans are fucking
sick of hearing about that
but yeah
what happened I don't understand
yes it's weird
I mean
so much of that early
not early YouTube stuff but like
I think it was mostly the pony era
where
John Trun was amazing and Game Grumps was also
amazing and it was that really cool
and we were all like
you know that's why I used that banana
the banana shoe song at the end of the
brony con videos that I made
it was like oh yeah that's sort of
that's sort of a thing
that's sort of a pony thing
almost
banana shoes it's great
it's a classic
it takes you back to a bygone era
and really like
it's like yeah
times were once good
John Trun used to be great
Aaron used to be great
hell that he wasn't in that song
but Dan used to be great too
now they're all washed up
has been
although did you see that new video that Barry
made about Skyward Sword
that was pretty good
it's got a lot of that Barry
almost funny humor but it
it works I liked it
it was the best thing to come out of
the Game Grumps all year probably
yeah
but the whole Game Grumps
and John Trun being shit
it's sort of
changed the way I view
YouTube and it's less about
being a consumer of
stuff I mean I still watch a lot of
YouTube but like I feel less like
a consumer on YouTube
and more like a creator
where I'm probably the best guy I know
at what I do
aside from James Rolfe
I would definitely say that
it seems like for you and Nate
especially since you were both such big
John Trun fans like
him turning to shit in some ways
did more good than harm
because it like made it so there were shoes
that everyone kind of wanted to fill
you know
John Trun sucks now that means we can
we can now be
the new one you know like
he needs to be replaced we need to kick him
off his throne let's get
up there
would you say that it inspired you
in that way
I'm not sure whether it would
like it was a direct inspiration I think
it was just sad but I felt good about
myself in general
at the same time I don't know whether it's directly
related but I feel better
about my own videos
in general because I'm like yeah
because people like you
and Victor have said you know I'm better
than John Trun now and I'm like
you know what you're right I am
I am better than he is
and that's weird and cool
oh John
you bastard what happened
you're so beautiful
for a time
really Ethan
is like the new funny guy
I watch H3H3
I forgot to mention him
I uh
I watch all the H3H3
and Ethan and Ela videos but they're never like
great
you know it's usually just like
yeah alright that was pleasant
every once in a while you get one that's like
memorable but you know
I think the stuff he does in public
where he's being a weirdo is like
yeah
it's like
for the fact that the jokes aren't that great
it's just like the spectacle of him
making an ass of himself in public
is like whoa cool
yeah and he does it in a
not douche baggy way
whereas some I think a lot of those
people like you know
because he's it's funny because he's so
close to being the stuff he makes
fun of like the prank bros
and everything but it's just like the important
difference is that he's just not an ass
while doing it you know
those people are those people are like
damaging and
scary and why are they out
in public doing that whereas with Ethan
he's always the butt of the joke
yeah
I mean I think he was saying
you're done with filthy frank or someone
was done with filthy frank maybe Jesse
because he was doing all those things
both me and Jesse
like he was doing these things that are
just as bad as all the prank bro things
because he's just being a weirdo at people
and he's not making any attempt
to make it like charming it's just
as weird as possible
I'm like yeah that like when he's had
that ravioli in his pocket
I was that I forget what that was
I don't know it was weird
he's going around to people with it
yeah
well
like I have a lot of like the
reason I followed filthy frank for a long
time is just I have a lot of respect for
like the physical comedy
like when like I mean with Ethan
too that it's that he'll
like when he did the fucking boy band thing
and it's like he really changed
his whole fucking appearance just for this
video you know you know like shave
off his head and fucking spray paint
himself with tanning spray and just
become this monster for often
like days
or weeks on end you know
like going through this physical transformation
for the comedy and I really appreciate
that and like filthy frank will do
stuff like there's one video where he
like just like
falls out of a car door while it's
moving it just like
like rolls on the pavement
it was just like oh my god that looked
painful as shit
but I do think that filthy frank
stuff has gotten to the point where like
it's
it's just kind of crass and I mean I know
that's the point but it's
it's not quite tongue in cheek enough
for me to think that he's not just
being a dick you know
and he's not really being a funny
dick nest like there's way I think it
would be possible to just be a total
asshole and for that to also be hilarious
if it was so over the top
but it's not it's like he's afraid
of crossing that line and so he doesn't
quite become like a total dick
that would be funny to watch you know
voyeuristically
but uh
that's just what I thought of off the top
of my head
that could all be
totally unsubstantiated
and uh just
me wanting to not like filthy frank
I
hate the whole
circle jerk between Frank, John
Trott and Ethan I just
I'm not impressed by it and now
potentially donkey as well
yeah donkey seems to be like
on the fringes of it
just because it's I mean we
don't circle jerk a lot but
but all of our content
is good and we don't circle
jerk any like what bothers me about
it is that like they're all
putting each other in their main videos
just to have them there
yeah somewhere else like that it'll be
like they're watching a John Trott video
then suddenly Ethan's there and he's not there
to like serve I mean it was funny in the
Kool-Aid Man one but like
when they went to that like karate dojo
it was like why these two why is
this happening this is just
it's just for the sake of having them both on screen
in the same video you know
I don't think it enhanced
anything to have them both there which is like
all of us TPC members have been
since the pony days pretty strict
about not doing frivolous
collaborations it went
pretty poorly when me and you did it
yeah I was gonna say
we I tried
to make it it was weird as well because
we weren't even we
hadn't really talked even that much
right but I was I asked
you for a color I can't remember why we
did it but we did it
I came to you about it because
oh yeah that's why I didn't want to talk
like oh my god it's didgy
right it was just that I didn't want
to cover the episode myself because I
that was at the point in season
four where I was like doing weird shit
and I was busy with other stuff and I
was just like this episode fucking blows
and I don't want to talk about it so I'll just
jump in on somebody else's
video and I'll jump in on you because
you were one of the people I respected
so you know I always had this
mindset of like I wanted to collect
the people who I like the most
so like if I thought your videos
were great then I wanted some way to
associate us so that it would like you know
help you out in a way
so I was like yeah I'll be in a hippo
video and that'll draw more attention to
hippo and I don't have to make a video about
it and then it was we didn't
put a lot of effort into making it like
work it just kind of sucked
like particularly the the collaborative
bit of it was just like awkward and
terrible
probably my fault because I'm not funny
well I think we just didn't really try
on the script like you wrote what you
were going to say about the thing and then I wrote a sentence
and then that was it we didn't go over it
again
yeah I'm just really all I
wanted to do was I wanted to avoid
the the the classic
that guy with the glasses whoa
what are you doing here so
I just said oh you're here
and then we talked
but yeah it was it didn't make up for the
fact that we didn't really have anything to do with each other
in the video
right I really want us to do
more like the best
I think best guy ever is monster musume
is the best collaboration that we
have ever done as a group
like it was so because that's
the only way to like he integrated all
of us but it didn't matter that it was
us it just mattered that it was
some guy doing something
weird with a monster character
you know like
it could have been anybody really
so it wasn't about like oh hey
my friends are all in the video it was
like that was a bonus to the fact that it also
made sense in the context of the video
and that's what I want collabs to be
I don't I don't want to just put Jesse
in the video because he's Jesse it has to
be that he serves a function
you know
yeah
that was that one other
collab thing where you asked me and Jesse
just to do to do some like
yeah at the end of your video and that one went
well because it was
that it was the leap of faith
video
and it's like 15 minutes long and it's a part
basically the script was really
depressing and I was
worried that it was like too
depressing and edgy sounding
so I was like what if
I like drew attention to this fact
by having jokes in there but
the joke is that like I tell you guys
to lighten up the mood and you make nothing
but cancer jokes
in a video where I was talking
about my mom having had cancer
I think like I think I bring that up in
the video so it was like
you know
like no one could say oh you can't
cancer jokes because like I just talked about
like dealing with it like personally
so
the joke is I'm like give in tell a
joke and you're like
then you just like
I fucked up I didn't
do it
it was great
yeah
you should rewatch that
sometime just for the ending bit because
like both both of
you sent me like too much
but it was all good
so I put like a little bit of it
in the middle and then I like left in
all the other jokes you made at the end
and there's like two minutes of you just
like rambling
incoherently about clouds
having silver lining but then you get
like diseases from the silver
or something like that
it's classic
everyone should go look it up
you won't find it it's in a playlist somewhere
on my channel
my little pony episode
yeah it's a good
I watched it recently and I laughed
a bunch
and then I died
I killed myself
so
how do you feel about the whole pony
era of videos
and about the show itself like in retrospect
well the way
I mean I like it the pony era
because it's how I started
getting into youtube and making
things frequently
and getting better and that's sort of what
allowed me to get the courage
to begin hypocrite really
was that I was making videos and people liked them
and I was like whoa I could really
do what I really want of video games
um as for the
show though I don't know
I liked a few
episodes it was the most recent
season six is it six now
yeah
yeah I watched a few of those
the first three were terrible
and after that it's pretty great
so I think I still like the show
I'm just not too invested in
anything to do with the fandom at all
right
I think we all kind of concluded that we
didn't want to be involved with the fandom
yeah I mean really
there isn't much to the fandom anymore
it's just you know all the musicians
I just sort of
tired of it all the artists
I just sort of doing the same thing
and the analysis crew is
they're all just in it for the money
and the analysis people
are fucking cancer so
they are awful you had
a lot of experience with those people
like you were in that chat for a lot longer
and you talked to them for longer
the bro analysis
Skype chat
where I think
were you even invited to that
yeah I was there at first
and I left after like a month or so
yeah
it's weird because at the top I think Skype
usually says who used to be in the thing
and who's left or maybe no
maybe it's just the people who just never
talked yeah because I saw
Tommy Oliver was in there but he never said anything
but all those people in there
I don't really
want to get into it because it's sort of
wrong a lot of stuff to say
but just they suck
most of them suck
I'm glad to have left it
there's a good reason that none of us
are going to BronyCon again
because uh
I mean I don't know I like the con kind of
but it is weird I would rather
go to a different con
if I could
but instead you're going to a
conference
in Virginia Beach Virginia
I almost said my address
for some reason
yeah don't do that
I almost went through my entire address
and I was like wait a minute
why am I doing that
not that my address is probably hard to find
or anything
I do want to open a PO box soon
so have you thought about
expanding and doing videos
about anything other than video games
um
perhaps
I was thinking maybe
I could try an analysis of an anime
just so that you know
because you always want one from people
you want more anime analysis
and I guess I could analyze
one piece anime but I don't know
I don't know
there's nothing
well yeah after Nate's done his
but then you'd probably say everything
I
I could analyze movies really
I just want to talk about stuff I like
so if it just happens to be something that isn't a video game
then I'll talk about it anyway
it's a very nostalgia based channel
I mean that's like
theoretically
my channel has never been
an anime channel
it's just that I only talk about anime
like it's
it's never been like
this is just the only thing I care about
because I've done like a couple
video game videos in there and like a couple
film analysis but it's like
I don't care about anything other
than anime so
it's clear that your fans like
they know
that you're smart enough to talk about things
like Dark Souls because everybody loved that video
well that video
I think that video hit it big
outside of my main audience
because it has a
fuckload of comments and most of them are from people I don't recognize
so I really think
it just got big in like the gaming circle
and the Bloodborne fandom
or Dark Souls fandom like as opposed to
my main audience for the most part
I guess
but uh
yeah I'm definitely seen as an anime
YouTuber I mean which is completely fair
it's all I cover but like I it's never
been technically an anime channel
um
but Hippocrite so far
has been exclusively video games
and I guess skeletons
yeah
what is it with you and skeletons
what's the deal with that
oh finish what I'm going to say first
I forgot what I was going to say
and now I want to talk about skeletons
skeletons are cool
because
they don't need to say any words
they just swing their sword I think I mentioned
I actually didn't really go into much depth
in the skeletons video
but I love skeletons because of the
cauldron skeletons which are really creepy
and spooky and cool and dangerous
and
the skeletons from Dark Cloud
because I don't know I love Dark Cloud
and skeletons in that
I think there's just something about
the way a skull it looks
like a face because it's obviously a human
skull
but it's like it's got this innate
spooky quality
because the eyes are black
and if you know anything about you know
shitty deviant art
creepypasta stuff everybody always makes
the eyes black to make it scary
if you got like a cursed Mario game
that's why everybody's afraid of black people
yeah well
badum tish
badum shh
that's why people are scared of you because you wear
black glasses
sunglasses
but yeah I don't know
I could go into the analysis
of why a skeleton is
a symbol of death
and death is really cool
I don't know
I don't know why I like skeletons
I think I like the fact that
they're a symbol of death but they can be really goofy
because they can't talk
and they're just like uh
fall apart
yeah
I guess it's like
there's something moe about skeletons
in that like they simultaneously
are imposing but also very fragile
yeah I actually had this idea
it was really weird
and it would
I don't know whether it ever
exist
in any form but there's
idea for an anime where the main girl
main girl character
gets turned into a skeleton
and it's like oh no my chest
is flatter than that other girl now
or something
which would be one of the things
but the main thing is obviously trying to fit in
because she doesn't have any skin
so she's got to wear clothing all over herself
and people are like what's wrong
why don't you show me your face
why don't you speak
I don't have a voice box anymore
and she has to learn sign language
and she becomes
friends with the death kid
that nobody likes
this would make an amazing one shot
you really need to make a one shot out
it's like 45 pages
it's just the idea of having
like a cute girl but she's a skeleton
and that's
I don't think that's been done before
I could totally see that working
it being
like a weird
offbeat magazine in Japan
because it, frank and fran
you might like the manga frank and fran
I just bought the first two
omnibus volumes of it today but it's a
it's sort of
that combination of like
like cuteness
but mostly gruesomeness
it's like a
it's about a girl named fran who
was like
she's basically a frank and sign monster person
but she's also like a doctor
and she lives out in this mansion in the middle of nowhere
and like she'll repair people
but she always turns them
into like some kind of Kafka-esque nightmare
so like
someone will come in and they'll be like I broke my leg
and she's like I can fix it
I have to mutate it with this other
animal and then like
she'll turn them into some kind of freakish monster
and like it'll alter their personality in some way
and it's fucking great
I think you might enjoy it
and fran is adorable
so uh
there's lots of cute girls
I've just realized one thing about skeletons
which is the reason I don't like some skeletons
is that they can't have an expression
like if a skeleton were
to just be a guy and you call him over
and he turns around he'd just have that completely
blank face because he doesn't have any face
muscles and he'd just be looking at you
you couldn't tell what he was thinking
like when the people
have skeletons and they give them angry skeleton
eye holes it's like
silly
the way you would do it with the anime or
manga version is that you use
just all those like manga
like blush and stuff
yeah somehow
sweat drops and stuff like that
yeah
cause they're usually like drawn over the face
more so than on it anyways
so I think it would work
I think it's a great idea
I want to read it back like I have a picture in my head
of what it would look like and it seems really good
and I really want to read it
and I could totally see it
being a chapter of Frank and Fran
hilariously enough
oh shit
David Boney I'm afraid of a skeletons
one of my
one of my favorite music videos on the internet
on the Hippocrite channel
which I heard
that long before I actually
tried to find the actual song
and I don't like the actual song
nearly as much
cause the version you used is like this
it was like a weird karaoke version
you found I guess
and I just kinda like the instrumental
in that better than the actual song
and you mumbling about
skeletons over it
it's really funny
it's the best
I'm afraid of skeletons
I'm afraid of the world
yeah I'm proud of that
the way I
filmed that was I got
my dad has these
rotating like
colored lights that he uses
for like a stage performances
and stuff
and they were just in the
the room so I was like
let's plug them in and get all the halloween
decorations and just go nuts
and it was me and both of my brothers
were just having a fucking
blast being idiots
and yeah
I asked Henry to film
me singing and then I filmed
them doing everything else
and I just filmed it over and over until I had
a bunch of weird shots and then it put it together
and it worked
it's great
it's definitely one of the most fun
things that has ever happened
like it's just pure enjoyment
every time I watch it I'm like
yeah this is great
um
we're actually gonna be part of the
the 20 skeletons video
but I made it a separate thing
cause I felt like people would wanna rewatch
the cool music video and not have to go through
all the bullshit so
yeah I'm glad you made that decision cause I have watched it a bunch of times
so we're
getting towards the end here
do you have anything you really wanted to say
on this podcast that you haven't had a chance to
uh
not really
I mean I
probably will remember something like
two hours from now like fuck
but right now I can't think much
else that I wanna say I think I've talked
about myself
I talked about what I like and what I do
uh
go subscribe to Hippocrite
YouTube
and it's spelt like Hippo as in
Hippopotamus and Crit as in Critic
there will be a link in the description
I know but
I know but Google still
changes it to Hippocrite
and it's wrong
Hippocrite is the real world
and I don't like it
I invented Hippocrite
it's mine
alright everybody
well thanks for listening
and we'll see you in the
next one
see ya