It is 11.25pm on Wednesday, January 4th, 2017.
I just got back from my 5k run. I did my nightly pull ups and I am glowing like a god. I feel
great. I feel really great. This is Nate's isolation training. Maybe I'll go with Guy's
isolation training. I don't know. I'm flip flopping between those two a lot. I haven't
really gotten comfortable calling myself Guy, even though I came up with it. Guys like Digi
and Gibb the whole time I've known them. I've called them that one name. Now it's kind of
funny to like Gibb change his name to Hippocrit with his new channel. It's been tough for
me to sort of shift with that and call him Hippo with his new name. And it's even harder
for me to start calling myself the new name I gave myself because I've known myself for
so long. So I don't know what I'll end up naming this exactly, but we'll see. Recently,
as I'm sure a lot of people know, I've had some things in my life that have wrapped up.
There have been some big changes. And now feels like a really good time to decompress,
you know, especially after the holidays. When I got to go home, see my folks hang out with
my family and see some friends from home, check in on what everybody's doing. And you know,
it kind of feels like it's a shift to a new chapter in my life, which, you know, if you
follow along with the things I say in PCP and whatnot, I'm sure that you're aware of
this. You know, it's kind of like, it's kind of like in my favorite game of all time, Final
Fantasy 15. It's like I've entered a new chapter. And the old one is getting left behind, going
to a new chapter, new things are happening, just like that perfect game. So I do a lot
of exercising. And actually, you know, we did the fat fuckery podcast recently. And I really
enjoyed doing that and getting to talk about, you know, my relationship with exercise and
dieting and that kind of stuff. I never intended to come across really as well, I probably
did intend to come across as like a real hardcore expert or someone who's who's incredibly
good at sticking to the advice that intellectually he knows is the right way to operate. Because
I have faults in that as well, you know, all of one, not all of, but actually the last year,
like, like the end of 2015 and 2016, when I moved out to Ohio for my new job. And that
was also the time that I was really starting to crank out heavy duty work on on my big
videos on best guy ever. That was a time when exercise and, you know, like health consciousness
definitely decreased in priority in my life, because I was so dedicated to getting those
videos done in all in in all my spare time was devoted to that in addition to, you know,
having to go to school and working full time. And then, you know, as you know, I finished
school, which is fantastic just a couple weeks ago. But during that time, my exercise
routine suffered. And there's no way around it. I gained some weight. And I lost some
muscle, you know, it's it's just true. I was at a peak of my life, probably around two
years ago, you know, before I started doing all the stuff intensely, health and fitness
peak of my life. It was awesome. It was wonderful. And I am definitely not at a p at that peak
right now. Now is the time where I'm now that I've got more time, I'm working on getting
back to that point, and surpassing it. But, you know, this is a lower point than that.
I'm no longer in a valley. I'm not at a nadir, as opposed to a zenith for you English majors
out there. I'm not at the lowest point. I'm currently on a rise, which feels great. But
you know, my point is just that I'm not perfect at this stuff, you know. And but but all this
is just a preface for something I wanted to talk about, which was that a guy I know, someone
who watches who watch this podcast, the fat fuckery podcast, somebody reached out to me
who had watched it. And I won't say who it is, just to protect privacy, even though,
I mean, I mean, if I were them, I would want this screen from the rooftops, because it's
so awesome. But this one guy messaged me and told me that that podcast, and specifically
the things I was talking about in it, were so resonated with him so strongly that he
was able to, I mean, I don't know if it was immediate or not, but was able to from that
point on, and I don't know how many months ago that was now, was able to make a change
in his life. And I think it was mostly dietary. And I believe he said he lost around, I don't
want to exaggerate, but I honestly think he said 100 pounds. I believe it was about 100
pounds that he lost. It might have been 50. I feel bad not remembering the exact amount.
But this is a math, even 50 pounds, like holy shit. And this was in the span of like, it
was less than six months. Let's just be conservative and say he lost 50 pounds in six months. That's
insane. That's fantastic. And this guy came to me and said, you know, Nate guy, whatever,
you really inspired me to make this change in my life. And I think he said thank you
or something. And you know, you know what that made me think? That made me think for
once in my life. I got to be the role model. I got to be, you know, the Kamina, who was
inspiring somebody else to be, you know, to live up to their potential, to do something
that they didn't necessarily know they could do. And God, Jesus Christ, I just don't know
if there's anything that would ever feel better than that, than to help to make a positive
change in someone's life like that. And obviously I'm not trying to take full credit. This,
this, this hero fucking did it himself. But to be a part of the process for that, you
know, to advocate what I would consider generally positive changes people can make in their
lives and to see someone follow through and succeed and be grateful and happy and better
and healthier for it. There's just nothing better than that. So, you know, I was just
out running middle of the fucking night. I got home from work, you know, had had shit
to do. It's fucking, it's, I should have gone to bed half an hour ago. Instead went for
a run. Because, you know, when it's the time of day to do your exercise, there ain't nothing
to it, but to do it, you know, just, just a really validating story. You know, I don't
even mean to talk about me. I'm just talking about the principle of, of applying yourself
and God, it's just, it just, it feels so good to be able to help other people to make a
positive change. Because that is really what my entire YouTube presence is about, at least
on Best Guy Ever. You know, every video I post on there, well, aside from the shit posts,
which there are plenty of, to be fair. All, I mean, all of like the scripted videos I
write, I like to think they all have a central message. And, you know, I like to cite Huey's
Law as I call it, the rule from the Christmas episode of the Boondocks, one of my favorite
shows when Huey's like, if people want to see my vision, nobody's going to give a fuck.
You got to dress it up with special effects and flair and songs and Hollywood movie stars.
You got to dress up. You got to, you got to put candy around the medicine if you want
people to swallow it. But I do think that there is that medicine, at least in my opinion,
contained in my videos that I want people to get. Because I do, I'm a really strong
advocate for humanism. I mean, I don't really like to attach myself to any particular movement,
but I just mean for, I value human life. And I want humanity to succeed and foster itself
and grow. And I like to think the messages that I put in my shit, you know, have that
effect. I mean, one of the big reasons that I wanted to do this today was because I just
finished my Lucifer and the Biscuit Hammer video, which I was really secretive about
and I didn't tell anybody about until it was just about done, except Mr. Donut the Donut,
big shout out to him, who inspired the way that the video was edited. I wouldn't have
done it if I hadn't seen his Jojo videos, which I love, especially his white snake, fuckin'
white snake. Here I go again on my own, going down the only road I've ever known.
Fuckin' Enrico Pucci is my fuckin' nigga. I love that dude. Way to go, Donut, you killed
it. I wanted to decompress about how intense the editing process was for that. I mean,
there's a couple things I wanted to talk about it. Before I get into that, I've noticed that
I'm a really extreme guy when it comes to the way I attune myself to things, and that
once I'm focused on a particular task, it's really hard for me to multitask, if you know
what I mean, in the sense of, like, when I was getting close to finishing that video,
and for me, that video took about two and a half months of straight working every single
night editing. To be fair, Christmas vacation, I was away, so I didn't work every single
night, but worked many, many hours on that project. Towards the end, I'm so focused on
just getting it done, getting it done, gotta get it out, gotta move on to the next project.
Time is ticking, you have to finish it, you have to finish it, that I sort of give up
things like cooking myself healthy meals, because I think, no, I can't spend the time
doing that, I need to be editing right now, I can't waste time, I'll just fuckin' order
up whatever. Fuckin' Crangoonz. That's Crab Rangoonz, there was a Chinese food menu
at my house that said Crangoonz on it, I've always loved that. Fuckin' Crangoonz, dawg!
Have you ever seen me buy me some Crangoonz? I'll love you forever. Yeah, like why would
I spend time cooking myself a fuckin' healthy meal, making my delicious protein shake, that'll
take up two whole minutes of my life, I could be editing, just fuckin' order something, or
spend an hour exercising, really, when I could spend that hour, you know, photoshopping fucking
two panels from this fuckin' massive project I'm doing right now, I can't justify that
time, I need to be editing right now, you know, like that's the way my mind goes, and
I've noticed this pattern, you know, I talked before about how my exercise routine has suffered,
you know, for a while it's suffered, you know, it's better now, but it's suffered because
I would trick myself sort of, my mind would play tricks on itself to make me think that
oh, I can't exercise today, I need to fucking be editing right now, you know, my ability
to divide up my time in a healthy way diminishes as my urgency to complete a project increases,
you know what I mean? I've noticed that, you know, ever since, even since the first
Guren Logan video, Guren Logan part one, you know how I edited that thing, I would, I was
using my old laptop for that, and I went to the library where my parents wouldn't bug
me, because I was living at home and I was making it on my shitty fucking laptop, and
I would go to the library and sit down there all night and just edit clips together on
that piece of shit laptop that barely even worked, you know, I didn't even know that
Vegas, I was watching clips in like full resolution, and I didn't turn down the, like the little
preview window to like quarter resolution, which allows you to actually play it properly,
so I was just fucking like, I would have to render a clip and then watch it to see if
the timing worked, it's fucking whatever. The point is, like, all my time was just spent
at that fucking library editing, that's what I did, and my, my, you know, exercise routine
suffered, and then once that project was done, oh, I was free, and you know, I could start
preparing to work on part two, and then, you know, my exercise routine got way better,
got much better again, and you know, that was just the start of this, but now I've been
doing these intensive editing projects straight for almost two years, like a year and a half,
or so, and it's, it's not a good cycle of, of like managing the important things I need
to do in my life, you know, I, I've given up a lot of other things to focus on editing,
and I'm aware that it's having negative effects in other aspects of my life in various ways,
but those are all acceptable to me, but the exercise one is not acceptable to me, and
that's why I, I need to make some changes in the way that I, that I structure my time,
you know, I really feel like The Procrastinators is the perfect channel for me, because I have
never met anyone, you can talk to my friends, I have never met anyone who is a worst procrastinator
in the sense that you get things done generally, but at the absolute last possible second,
are you aware, of course you're not aware, I've never, I don't talk about this, but
I finished all my assignments this last semester as a fucking, you know, super senior guy finishing
my degree in my last class here, every single assignment was turned in the hour it was due
or later, or later than the due date, and luckily, like in this particular class they
didn't mind, but I've had classes where people did mind, and then, you know, then you have
to play the whole dance of like, oh I'm so sorry, like, oh I thought it was due late,
like I've been a real shitty, you know, time management guy as long as I can remember,
and it's my biggest flaw personally, and it stretches into other ways, you know, like,
I think that it's the same problem that I have with my ability to, you know, like budget
when I get close to the end of an editing project, like how much time I need to be editing,
and then, you know, Nate, take the fucking hour to go exercise, you know, I think that
these are all a manifestation of the same, same kind of weakness of, you know, an ability
to structure a schedule effectively, I'm really a one track kind of guy, which by the way
makes me a great editor, as everybody can see, because I so autistically focus in on
whatever I've decided is the thing that I have to do, and when it's done, generally
pretty fucking good, but, you know, it comes at a cost, you know, other shit gets neglected,
I really am a, you know, an artist in the sense that I need a rich, gay, Italian lover
slash patron to, to be my patron as an artist, so we can have gay sex, you know, like I'm
referencing Michelangelo, if you're not getting the reference here, and the Pope, I think
they were gay lovers, right, that's fact that's confirmed, yeah, I'm pretty sure that's confirmed.
You know, if I can just focus on the thing that I want to do, I'm pretty darn good at
it, if I, if I do say so myself, hey quick aside, when I was out on my run today, I found
not one, but two potatoes on the ground, and I'm holding them in my hands, they are completely
frozen solid, how's that for focus, fuck boys, where's I going with that, whatever, not important,
oh yeah, I'm just decompressing about the whole, my whole experience of YouTubeing and
making the Biscuit Hammer video, you know, it's really, it's revealing to me more and
more the way that I operate on YouTube, and the ways that that isn't optimal, you know,
I've talked about this many times, I think in various PCP episodes, so I'm, I don't
need to dwell on it too much, but that project was a vast sinkhole of time, two and a half
months, that, you know, just isn't the most efficient way to spend your time on YouTube,
not to mention, it's a niche thing, like it's a, it's a fucking AMV, you know, an MMV
I guess, Manga Music Video, for a series that's not particularly popular, but you know, I,
I just really identify with it, hey you know what sucks about that, that I want everyone
to die, who says this, everyone who fucking comments on that video, wow, great video dude,
or even, or it just skips that part and gets straight to, you guys should read Spirit Circle,
Spirit Circle is the latest manga by Satoshi Mizukami, the guy who made Lucifer and the
Biscuit Hammer, we're not here to talk about fucking Spirit Circle, you fucking idiots,
we're here to talk about Lucifer and the fucking Biscuit Hammer, everyone who fucking commented
about Spirit Circle, shut the fuck up and die, I hate you guys, I don't hate you guys,
I just wish you would focus on the matter at hand, I didn't make a fucking video about
Spirit Circle, okay, I made a video about Lucifer and the Biscuit Hammer, because it's one
of my favorite manga, and Spirit Circle, I've read about half of it, okay, it does not focus,
it's not like these things are interchangeable, like oh if you like, if you like Lucifer and
the Biscuit Hammer, just read Spirit Circle, like it's, it's, it's the new one, so it
just replaces it, no, that's fucking not how it works, Lucifer and the Biscuit Hammer
is fucking great, and I wish you fucking people talking about Spirit Circle, we just make
your own fucking Spirit Circle video, and then comment all your shit on that, okay,
just keep it off of my shit, god damn it, god, Lucifer and the Biscuit Hammer is too
good to be ignored by discussions about fucking the new work by the guy, okay, I like Spirit
Circle, it's, it's, it's good, I haven't finished it, I can't say that it's great, because
I haven't gotten, I don't know, I don't feel like it's really earned, it's, it's, it's
weight yet, as like, you know, because I love this series, I don't feel like it's reached
that bar with the place I got to, I don't, I don't know how far I got into it, I'm lying,
I didn't get halfway, I just, I read like, I don't know, 20 chapters or something, just
everybody chill out about Spirit Circle, okay, can we please, you know, the biggest disappointment
for me about that, about that video is that there isn't more, and you know, to be fair,
I get it, I understand why, because it's the nature of the video, it's kind of just a,
a really quick, emotional dive into Lucifer and the Biscuit Hammer, as opposed to like,
what I, what I'm tempted to do, because I'm not getting enough of this, but like a, you
know, like my Tengentubba girl log in part two, I would, I'd like to do a, someday I
probably won't, but maybe I will, Lucifer and the Biscuit Hammer, part two video, where
I like, really talk in depth about the themes of the, of the manga, and what it means, and
why it's so important to me as a person, because that is a very important series to me as
a person, really, oh god, it, it doesn't really come across that much in the, in the video
that I made, there's, there's so much about that series that I couldn't capture, that
oh, it, you know, you know, it's like, no matter what AMV you make of any show, or any manga,
you're never going to capture everything that you love about it.
And just one of the things I couldn't capture about that series was, in the video, you do
see Amamiya's, or Yuhi's transformation from like his self-hating, you know, kind of an
asshole weirdo creeper who wouldn't mind if the world got destroyed into, you know, like
a guy who lives for his lady, has real genuine friendships with people, you know, has father
figures that come and go, and is able to make a positive contribution to the world emotionally
and practically, by fucking, you know, saving the fucking world, fuck yeah, Lizard Knight,
but it's, there's this other part about him, there, there's a lot of physical training
that goes on in that series, I was fucking out running today, Amamiya Yuhi goes out running
every single morning with the princess, every day, in Lucifer and the Biscayne Hammer, they
go for a fucking run, alright, and it's to build up their stamina, because their, their
ring power is the domain control, psychic power, ball things that you don't see much
of in my video, those, the more stamina you have, the more endurance you have, like the
stronger your domain is, like the longer you can use it, and also, later on in the series,
he gets, I wish I really tried to include this, there just wasn't enough space, Yuhi
gets really into digging holes, like he just, out of the blue, out of the fucking blue,
he develops the habit of digging trap holes all over this fucking mountain, and he starts
doing it, and he gets fucking ripped, just he goes out every day, and he digs fucking
holes, just like, you know, like the movie holes, only he covers them up, and it's used
for fucking like emotional payoffs, as well as gags, like the idea is that he'll dig holes
to, you know, get stronger, it's his form of exercise, as well as, it's a meditative
thing, it's an exercise thing, and it's also a practical, you know, like trap hole, like
when they're fighting the golems, maybe one will step in one, and it'll, you know, help
them in the fight somehow, and God, I fucking love it, but, but it's the training that Yuhi
goes through, oh God, I just love, you know, you know, guys, I want me at Yuhi, he starts
that series, the weakest fuck, right, me, I started running seriously about four or five
months ago, I think after, I had gone for a long time, I'd still been working out sparingly,
but I got, I got really into running again, and now I'm doing 5Ks pretty frequently, and
I'm going for 10K, just like, even though that's, even if a 5K is not that impressive,
but, well, let me put it in context, when I started running a couple months ago, like
my ankles, and I had never felt this before, because I used to run a lot, but my ankles
were so weak, they were like the limiting factor when I tried to go for a run, like
as I would be out running, I wouldn't get exhausted, my ankles would specifically give
out, like when you're doing curls, and your bicep gives out, and you just can't do another
fucking curl, my ankles would just, I couldn't lift my leg to, or, you know, to move my fucking
foot to run anymore, that was the limiting factor on them, it was, it was weird, I had
never felt that before, but now, several months later, no problems, my ankles are totally
fine, and that was like a real problem for like a month when I was running, but God,
it feels so good to set yourself a goal like that, and to achieve it, to get past it, which
is why I fucking love exercising, I feel so good, every time I exercise when I'm doing
it, it's hard, doesn't, don't really love the actual doing of it, but afterward, feels
fantastic, and you know what, I do love doing it, like every set is a struggle, obviously,
but once you put the set down, and you can just bask in what you've just accomplished,
ugh, it's great, everyone, I hope everyone feels it, ugh, boy, a little bit rambly, hope
you forgive me, I feel like everything here is fairly related, more or less, you know,
in the same ballpark here, is there anything else I wanted to say about my fucking video
there, no, no, I guess I'm a little disappointed with the views, I mean, you know, my channel
is not that big, I understand, I knew from the get-go that that video wasn't, you know,
it's not like I was making a drama video, now that's what I need to do to get the views,
it's a little art piece, you know, I think that my patrons probably appreciate it a lot,
because it's the, I feel like it's new content for me, and it's a whole new fucking art form
that I've never done before, and I really loved it, thanks again Mr. Donut for inspiring
it, yeah, I don't know, I just think that my particular brand on Best Guy Ever is gonna
grow as time goes on fairly, I mean, if I kept doing what I had been doing, it'd be slow,
but I think I'm gonna make a couple changes, hopefully it'll go faster, we'll see, hopefully
the quality will remain high, I mean, it's me, come on son, you know I'm gonna be high
quality, yeah, I guess there's one other thing I kind of wanted to talk about that relates
to some of the stuff I've been saying here, I was just thinking about the kind of characters
I gravitate to a lot, I don't know how much, I know I've talked about this to some extent
in PCPs, but you know, I was just thinking about Kill Bill, the bride, you know, the
snake boys, that whole bunch, nah, but really I was thinking about Bill, Bill himself, there's
a line in Kill Bill, it's not really a line, it's just a concept about the character Bill
that someone says, I think Esteban, whatever, the Spanish dude, Mexican, I don't know, the
guy that is in Kill Bill part two, who tells the bride where Bill is finally, what's her
name, Beatrix Kiddo, that's right, when Kiddo goes to meet this guy, he was like a mentor
of Bill's growing up, and I don't really know exactly what their relationship was, but they
hung out, you know, and he says something interesting about Bill that's really stuck
with me over the years, and it was that, I think he said that Bill and his brother Bud
were orphans, I think he said that, but I know he definitely said, Bill collected father
figures, ever since I heard that line, I just felt such a strong kinship with that, you
know, I don't know if everybody gets that, but I know exactly what that means, and I
mean maybe Bill didn't have a father, and that's why he, you know, quote unquote collected
father figures, but I really feel like that sort of idea is why I'm so into anime, and
the specific things that I gravitate towards, you know, I of course have a dad, and he is
a wonderful dad, and I love him with all my heart, but he's not perfect, you know, no
dad is, my dad is a very emotionally, I don't know, I don't want to paint him in the wrong
way, you know, like a lot of the time, mothers are the more emotional person, I think between
two parents, at least it seemed to me, and fathers are a little bit more, I mean not
even that they're more disciplined, but they're more, they're more like a teacher, you know,
as opposed to a friend, you know what I mean, a little more strict, you know, and my dad,
you know, was kind of strict, I guess, but my dad was definitely the more emotional one,
I hope I'm not fucking going too deep right now, too real, but whatever, I don't think
I'm going to say anything that's going to hurt anybody's feelings, my dad was definitely
the more emotionally connected of my two parents, you know, my dad's a psychologist, so I'm
sure empathy is his fucking business, you know, it's his deal to connect emotionally
and do that shit, and my mom is just, you know, I don't even, I don't want to say emotionally
distant, that sounds negative, I just mean that she was a little more, you know, private
of a person, and she was always there for me when I was real sad, and when I needed somebody,
but it's just not really in her nature to, like, what I'm trying to illustrate here is
just that I think when I was growing up, and this has a point, this relates to anime, your
favorite thing viewer, so hang in there, I think when I was growing up, like, I didn't
have anybody who was like really cool in my life, you know, like I don't think I had a
strong positive male role model in the sense of like a badass, you know, like my dad was
a wonderful father, a fantastic person, but I wouldn't exactly call him a badass, and
actually it's really funny, as I've gotten older, and I learn more about his history,
and I see him spend more time with like his brothers, because he's got a whole bunch of
brothers, and I see him do things that I don't think he would have showed when I was younger,
I see like the badass part of my dad come out more and more, which is kind of ironic,
as he gets older, he gets more of a badass, at least in my eyes, but like there wasn't
as much of that when I was young, and I'm not trying to complain, I'm just describing
reality for me, this is not a complaint, but when I look back at the guy that I am now,
and why I am this way, I do think that I didn't have someone in my life who I could emulate
to be cool, you know, and being cool is so important to me, and it's not that I choose
that I want that for myself, it's kind of just instinct, and it's not even that I really
think that I am that cool, it's that I want to be cool, and so I project that I think
I am cool, oh god we're getting deep here, this is a little more than I bargained for,
fuck it, fuck it, so what I'm trying to say is, I think I filled that hole in myself,
and hey for all I know, everyone in the world feels exactly the same, you know, maybe everyone
can relate to this, I'm not trying to say I'm the only one who felt like this, because
I had a great life growing up, but everyone's got things that are deficient, you know, excesses
of some things, deficiencies of others, in my case, I think I could have used some more
like positive male role models, because I had my brother around, but he's not cool, you
know Ben was cool, but I don't know, I think we were too much alike, oh man I don't even
know what Ben's place in my life was, we hung out a lot, I don't know, I can't even comment
on it, I just gotta skip over that and just say what I'm actually trying to fucking get
to, which is that I think anime, cartoons, Goku filled that role model for me, filled
that hole in my life, of like, I didn't have a person in my life like a dad or an uncle
who would fucking talk to me about like, oh man, you wanna look at all those sexy girls,
you know, or like, hey let's go hunting, let's go kill things, let's go be beasts, let's
go be animals for a while, you know, I wasn't in touch with my reptilian brain very much
when I was younger, I don't think, I don't think I was really like aware that it's okay
to just be a fucking animal sometimes, you know, and I think I have tried to make up
for that in other ways, but that's why I think I feel so attracted to characters like, like
when I was young, Goku man, Goku was my dude, he's why I started exercising all those years
ago and I've been doing it ever since with varying degrees of success, man you should
see some of my pictures at my sexiest, oh it was a fucking god, but give me a couple
months, I'll be back in top shape, I just need to do a little more running, anyway when
I was young, Goku was my hero, it's funny because think about it now, really Vegeta
is the guy that I relate to way more, like fucking Vegeta dude, like prince of all sayings
right, fucking planet gets blown up, alright, his kingdom gone, his people gone, like who's
gonna be sadder about a fucking planet being destroyed, like Goku, some fuckboy who doesn't
even know that other fucking Kakaradians exist, other fucking sayings exist, or the fucking
prince of all sayings who was gonna rule over his people and they all fucking died, right,
bam, sadder backstory, trains so hard all the time to be the best, and still, fucking power
friendship Goku just beats him every god damn time, and of course like being fucking crushed
under the superior alphaness of Frieza his whole life, the guy who killed his dad until
you know fucking Goku saves him, the man who defeated him, god and he can still never surpass
Goku, why is Goku the legendary Super Saiyan, why not me, I'm the fucking prince, I'm just
trying to describe how hard Vegeta worked, right, and how what a raw deal he fucking got his whole
life, until he finally found peace and settled down with a top shelf babe like Bulma, had a
kick ass son like Future Trunks, holy shit, fuck yeah, love Trunks, love Vegeta, love Bulma,
perfect family, 10 out of 10, man, but anyway when I was a kid I didn't understand that,
I didn't know what a real nigga Vegeta was, I was into Goku, because Goku's still trained hard,
you know, he worked hard and he played hard, oh god I've gone too far
but Goku was the hero right, Goku was the dude who fucking saved the day, he was the strongest,
he was the coolest, everything revolved around him, he was the most important character,
everyone respected him, everyone loved him, I wanted to be him, I wanted to be him so bad,
I wanted to be him more than anything else in the world, and I think at the time I worked out
specifically to be like Goku, to be a hero is why I worked out, I think that I can say that
with some confidence, that is why I started working out when I was a little kid, I mean I
wasn't that little at that point, I mean I was probably like, I don't even fucking know, long
time ago, yeah I wanted to be Goku, and I see that pattern in different ways, as I got older,
you know, like the whole girl thing became more relevant, because when I was young, man, brother,
brothers and sisters, I was uncomfortable with the ladies, let me tell you, I had opportunities man,
I had him, goofed him up, goofed him up, and that's why I was so attracted to characters like,
you know, like Kamina, my favorite character, the women loved him, and the men wanted to be him,
and I was one of them, he had Yoko, he would have had his pick of the litter, you know,
he was a hero, he was a leader, that is the exact kind of person I wanted to be, and
you know, I definitely was not, I definitely was not that guy, for a long time,
and I wanted to be more than anything, and you know, I think I'm closer than I've ever been
to being like a Kamina, I mean hey, I fucking, right, my story earlier, inspiring someone to
exercise, work out, and get some real change in their life, that's what it's all about man,
it really, it really touches me that I could, I could do that, I could have that kind of positive
change in somebody's life, so you know what, I mean things are looking up right, things are
looking up, I'm just talking about how I relate to that line in fucking Kill Bill, you know,
he collected father figures, I collected father figures too, I think, and I, it's guys like
Vash the Stampede, who just go above and beyond the fucking call of duty to protect people,
and their superior, and their gods, you know, like Vash is a fucking god, and he uses his
power to connect with humanity, to have a good life, you know, fucking fuck sluts, like a real guy,
and though he's actually, he's a sensitive soul, he would never take advantage of a woman like that,
because he doesn't want them to see his fucked up body, because he spends all day
helping, protecting people, guys like, I mean to some extent, Rance from Sengoku Rance,
and the whole, the whole Rance series, love, love him, big admirer of his work,
go look up Sengoku Rance if you don't know what it is, play that fucking game, it's awesome,
story aside, the gameplay is hard as fuck, love that game, love that game, I don't know, I think
I just wanted to talk about why I'm into anime at all, you know, I'm not like, I'm not like a lot
of the other guys on YouTube who talk about anime, who really give a shit about anime as a medium,
for me, anime is just sort of the medium that life led me to, that happened to most appeal
to the things I'm into, like, there aren't a lot of communas outside anime, you know what I mean?
You don't see a lot of that shit these days, strong, positive male role models are a big thing
that I like to see, you know, I love good dads, you know, I say that sometimes, I really love
good dads, infection, I don't know man, I'm gonna have to listen back to this and see if this is
even worthy of being shipped out, this may have gotten too real, too fast, and too furious for you,
and for public consumption, anyway, I think that's about everything I've got to say,
I might delete this, might upload the whole thing, might edit some shit out,
maybe I'll add another piece, I don't know, we'll see, but hey everybody out there, before you go,
just remember, go do cool shit that's hard, but you want to do anyway, because if you do it,
because I told you to, and then you tell me about it, I'll feel really good about that,
and so go do that, so I can feel good about myself, all right, I demand you make positive
changes in your life, so that I can feel better about myself, all right, there you go, there's
your ultimatum, don't do that or I'll, I don't know, your mother will die under sleep tonight,
all right, thanks for listening everybody, I'll see you later.