Hello everybody and welcome to another solo podcast on The Pro Crastinators Channel.
I am The Hippocrit and I've never really been that good at doing solos, but I feel, you know, practice makes good.
So I'm gonna make one and the first solo I want to talk about is Led Zeppelins, something or other.
I think Celebration Day is the song, I forget the name, but it sort of goes like this.
So that's the solo, it's quite short and it's quite difficult.
Obviously that wasn't the first take, I'm not that good.
But yeah, I really like this song, it's very upbeat, it's very bouncy, it's very quick and fast, and it's fun to play.
The reason I like Led Zeppelin so much is because their guitar bits are just, you know, really cool to listen to, but so fun to play.
Like getting down a solo from Led Zeppelins, like the coolest feeling in the world.
And not even just like the guitar solos, Led Zeppelin and all the musicians, their solos are great and they're fun to play.
And that's the thing, the thesis behind a lot of Led Zeppelin songs at least.
It feels like they're just always having a good time trying to do as much cool shit as possible.
And it's like, yeah, yeah, 20 minutes solo that just keeps going and it's cool and it's fast and it's energetic and it's great.
And that's the only one I can really do.
There's, you know, there's Stairway to Heaven, which I never really figured out.
It's probably not as difficult as that one that I just played, but it's like, what does it go like?
I need to turn the distortion off for this, hang on.
A lot of the time I can't remember what a song goes like and how it leads into things without playing it.
And then it does the...
...
Yeah, it's uh...
I mean, it's fun to to to imagine the solo. It's not it sounds terrible when you say it with your mouth
But I I've never figured that out
But soloing is like it's it's cool. It's great and I love solos and there's lots of solos I like but I I don't know many
Yeah, I guess this really was a pointless podcast if I had more solos to show off
That would be cool. I
Can make up things in like a in a thing let me turn distortion back on
Oh
You
See that's not really a solo, but it is a riff I could do a podcast on riffs. I love riffs too fucking guitars are cool
Um
Yes
Yeah, I like guitar that the entire joke was I was gonna say I it's a solo podcast and then it's a
literal about music
solos
When you really you would think oh, it's just a one person in a podcast and that that was the joke
But now I'm standing here with a guitar and I just want to place things
I'm gonna play some things and tell you what I like. I like things. I like stuff
I like
Let's think of distortion stuff like what's good right like like really what's good like
That's that's a powerful chunky little chunky little power sound, you know all of those
I'm trying to think of like
Oh
Never really quite get that bit I always forget it says who's one of those things, you know
Yeah, jeez. How's this? How's this gonna work?
I'm gonna have to compress this to fuck if I'm gonna make my voice sound like it's you know
The right volume level compared to all the stuff I'm doing
What else is cool? Um I
Can't play back in black even though I really want to because I don't know
Some of you might know that I played back black in back in black
Just with an acoustic guitar by myself in a video on Gibbentate channel
And he got taken down for content ID
They know those chords and they fucking took it down. It was annoying
Let's just make up a solo let's go all the way up here and then it's just
Oh, yeah, I'm playing a song this goes
I'm gay essay is a fucking stupid song and then it's like oh, yeah, and then you go all the way up here and it's like
I
I'm not good at solos, but I can I tried my best. That's not good
I know what I've just remembered this is one
I
Was a cool little bit I was like that. What do you call it a lick? Do you call that a lick?
Don't know how that goes. I don't know a lot of songs
I know some parts of lots of songs. I don't know whole songs, you know
I get I get tired of looking up tabs tabs suck. Fuck tabs. They're gay. I can't read them
I mean I can but I don't like them. It's like it takes like 40 minutes to read a tab
I probably would take longer for me to read notes because I don't know how to read those at all
I just listen I listen and figure it out. I guess
Oh, I'm I'm gay
Oh
Wow
I can't sing I hate that the reason I haven't made any music is because whenever it comes to singing and lyrics
I fail. I'm just bad at it. I don't know what to do
Text to speech maybe
Oh
And I'm here
Now I'm there
It's just
I
This podcast is not even real. I'm gonna cut out everything
Really I don't know what I'm doing here
I guess I'm showing off, but I'm not really good at that because I don't prepare for anything. I don't I don't plan
For like what I could talk about. I don't have anything up on the screen to reference
It's really a shit show and I never do it. I never plan. I never do any planning for anything
Every podcast I go on to every PCP. I just jump in and have try to think of something while everyone else is talking
And then I say it and if I don't have anything to say then it's nothing's coming out
Even on the podcast like I read the chapter once
Nate reads it like a million times and he takes notes and then he comes in and does the thing and he has like stuff to say
I'm just like
I'm I'm a lazy
I'm uh
It wouldn't be cool if I knew lazy by deep purple and then transitioned into that
That would be a great fucking thing, but I don't know how to play it. Oh, I fucking hate
This this this almost talent this almost skill
Like it's pretty good. I admit. I know how to do some things
But gosh darn it. It's not always great. It's not always the sort of thing that would make somebody say wow
You know you say wow because oh, I didn't know he had guitar talent not oh wow
His guitar talent is really good and I would like to hear music from him
Like I'm I'm just mediocre enough
To be uh, whatever
I try to do things, but I don't work out
I'm really annoyed with my current output
It doesn't seem to get better only seems to get worse
Soon I'll be in a hearse
I
Don't like you you smell like poop
See that's what I mean when I fucking can't lyrics
I know you're not supposed to come up with them off the cuff
But I can't come up with lyrics and then put them on a song that I already made because I can't really make a song without lyrics
To to structure it and I don't know fucking how to do any of this
I hate music and I wish I could make an album and it's hard and I don't know how to do it
I don't really know what to do
I can't stay on beat with myself
I tried like playing guitar and then playing bass and it wasn't the same speed
So what would you fucking everybody just has to do it in fruity loops and make not real instrument noises
But I don't like using a computer when I'm making music. I hate music editing
It's the worst thing in the world just sitting there with hunched over
Trying to like sit on a chair with a guitar so that it's close enough to the microphone
Fucking it's it's fucking the worst. I mean and now I have a microphone arm
So I can stand up and play like right now, which is it's great
I could probably make an album now just because I have a microphone arm
So I don't have to sit down while playing anything, but it's just I fucking hate it
I fucking hate everything about music production
I hate the sitting with the the headphones listening to something and then trying to play along
With another instrument. It's impossible. It's impossible and no one has ever done it and no one will ever do it ever
It sucks. I hate fruity loops because it's entirely that you don't have anything in your hands
You're just clicking you're just clicking and putting notes in various places and then listening to it
And yeah, it's you know, it's cool, but I hate it. I hate that process of making things
Digitally
It doesn't appeal to me as a person who plays guitar
Because the whole reason I like playing guitar is because I'm holding something and I'm going
You know, I'm going dilly dilly dilly with my fingers and it's great. That's fun
It's like the difference of like shooting a gun in a game and shooting a gun for real
Like I've never shot a gun, but I can imagine people who actually play, you know
Own guns and go to gun ranges and shoot
Like stuff
They they know the difference and it's very, you know, it's it's a different sort of feeling
I'm not saying that digital music is bad. Obviously. It's great
It's just I can't do it and it's so difficult as a single person to make a music without
Fucking using extensive digital
shit
I don't know what to do about it. It sucks
God damn it
Damn it god
Like I wish it was as easy as just like walking up to a thing going boom boom boom on the drum
And then switching over to the guitar and going. Oh, yeah, I'm listening to the it's just difficult
I wish I was in a band, but I don't know any human beings. I don't know anyone. No one is in a band that I know
No one is even playing music. I don't know anybody. There's no one in the world that I know
That lives nearby nearby at all
I don't know any human beings in my country
Because I just you know school friends fucking drift it apart
I don't keep up with them. It will be weird to just say. Hey, is anybody in a fucking you need a guitarist
I don't fucking know. Well, how do you meet band people just go to places
It's fucking
I don't get it
I don't get it at all. I hate I hate everything
I
The city of no one nobody knows me and that's all my fault
I try to be cool
I try to be awesome, but on the internet
Fuck you these lyrics
Wait, am I trying to be like
Suddenly like oh poetic at the end
I don't know how to play this song. It's bad. It's it was no bad song. I'm bad at it
Hey
Oops
And I hate me baby
And I hate me
And I hate it
Yeah
I made a mistake
Everybody's gay everybody's really gay
Maybe even me everybody's super gay. That's the way it's gonna stay
And then they go I forget how it goes to this
Oh
And she's buying
A siggy stardust
In walmart
I don't know not a fucking walmart. I don't have walmart. What am I?
What am I an american now?
Yeah, that's what playing red hutch silly peppers does to you makes you go american
Makes you a american boy
American boy
I love no one
It's all gay
And that's okay
American boy
I'm really gay
I don't like anybody's anything. That's all I say. I'm gay
I'm american
I'm american boy american boy
I'm gay
I'm american
I don't like you and I don't like me
American boy american boy american boy
American boy
I don't like you. You don't like me. I've got nothing else to say. I'm really gay
I'm gay american boy
I'm really
Yeah, I clicked the clip the mic quite a little bit. Uh, well, uh, that's how it's gonna end