Hello everybody and welcome to another episode of the Hyperbolic Wine Chamber where I train
my ability to complain. I'm Tom Oliver and today I'm going to be drinking Fireball Cinnamon
Whiskey. That is today's wine. It was provided for me by the best guy ever two years ago when
he came to my house. It's been sitting here ever since and I figured fuck it. I'm down
here. It's right there. Might as well fucking put an end to this Fireball Whiskey. As usual
if you'd like to donate to the Wine Fund to provide wine for the Hyperbolic Wine Chamber
you can do so in the link in the description to my paypal. If you donate of course I will
mention your name in the beginning of the show and we'll give a link to your social
media in the description of the podcast. So today we're going to be talking about being
untalented and how much it fucking blows. So my channel RebelPixels is kind of all about
that idea of being untalented and trying to scavenge some small amount of success with
your lack of ability nonwithstanding. God I'm afraid it has some of those whiskeys who
are sitting here forever but we're just going to fucking go for it my friends. I feel like
I'm going to need some for this. Yep. Yeah so being untalented is something I'm familiar
with. It fucking is not. Okay let me back up for a little bit and let's start with why
I'm talking about this to begin with. For the last hour or so I've been sitting here
working on an illustration for a review of the new tablet that I got in from XPpen. I
know thrilling stuff for anybody who's a PCP regular fucking tablet reviews but I'm doing
a drawing just kind of to record some footage of how the thing works so I usually have to
sit down and do an illustration even though I don't really do illustration much anymore.
Looks on me I suppose for starting a channel about drawing and then immediately getting
out of drawing. So I'm sitting here doing an illustration and I did a sketch on paper.
I always start my illustrations on paper even though I have all these fucking digital shit.
It looked pretty good. I mean it wasn't like amazing nothing I've ever drawn has been amazing
but in terms of like my scale it looked pretty good. So I brought it in to Manga Studio and
started inking it and now it looks like fucking garbage. And I don't know why. It's a kind
of a meme among artists and people who create that sometimes you draw a sketch it looks
pretty dope and then you try and ink it and it completely falls apart. And it's the worst
because you never really quite know why it's happening and usually the only solution is
to scrap your inks and start all over again. But that just kind of like started the whole
kind of snowball effect of like oh these inks looks like shit oh it's because you're a shitty
artist though it's because you have no talent and blah blah blah. It's tough being in the
PCP and drawing and not being good because you know we got Ben we got Mage we're both
really good. I'm not so good and that kind of fucking sucks because it feels like constantly
you got to like prove you have a purpose for being there. And I don't know I definitely
feel like I'm still struggling to find my niche which is weird because all throughout
high school and college and shit I always figured like oh drawing is absolutely what
I wanted to do. I always thought it was kind of laughable that people didn't know what
they wanted to do with their lives or didn't kind of have their thing figured out because
I figured my thing out so early in life like art duh clearly. But that was before the fucking
internet and then you get the internet and you're like holy shit I'm so fucking bad at
this thing that I thought it was actually kind of good at because like this might not
make any sense for you young people who grew up with the internet but back in the day you
only had your immediate surroundings to compare yourself to in terms of ability relative to
your age and your time spent on your craft and in my tiny little pre-internet bubble
I was doing okay. It was pretty you know locally and live in a small town there's like five
other people who draw so the fact they could even draw at all seemed fucking amazing when
considered in a vacuum the personal little vacuum. I said vacuum a lot in the last episode
too what the fuck. Small aside I have this weird tendency with my vocabulary to get stuck
on certain words for a while days weeks months. Vacuum seems to be one of the ones I'm using
right now. Sucks. Whatever. In this tiny little bubble of where I live I seemed like I knew
what I was doing comparatively but then you get high speed internet connection you go on
DVNR and you realize you're fucking garbage and despite the effort I've put in I've been
drawing now for oh my god. I started getting serious in eighth grade eighth ninth grade
something like that freshman year of high school so that would be 12 years of work and
you would never know it by what I create. To put that into perspective Ben has been drawing
for I think three or four years. I mean I don't really even see anything more than that
it's self-explanatory. So I've constantly had I've kind of just had to like realize
you know from I want to say like the middle of high school to today that I don't have
any talent. Looking back at what I've done and where I've been and how far I've come
it's it's it's kind of amazing that I can even do what I do now. All things considered
considering how fucking terrible I was and I like I have a little sister who's 15 right
now and she can draw better than I can today at 15. So it's just like a joke and then my
other sister who's younger than me but older than that sister was consistently better than
me at drawing growing up. So I've never known what it's like to actually have an ability
that actually I seemed like I was proficient at was obviously in the PCP I'd have no no
drawing skill compared to Ben and Mage. I don't have analysis or video making skill compared
to Momkey or Nate or Digi or your analysis skill compared to Digi or personality charisma
compared to Jesse and Momkey. So it's like it's like what do I do. What do I bring to
the table. I was kind of going to say this topic for another time but I guess I guess
we're going straight into it. I feel like in order to be part of something you need to
justify your being there. I don't know what I provide to this group and that really bothers
me because I have this desire and I think we all do. I think we all have the desire and
the want to feel useful to feel like we're providing something. That's a big reason of
why I create things in the first place is because I feel like the ability to create and make
things whether it be you know something as frivolous as art or something as utilitarian
is like you know construction or architecture or things like that. The ability to create
things is what separates us from from other animals. Right. Like we have this ability
to like be cognizant and like create tools and express higher thoughts and creativity
and stuff like that. So I feel like human beings we almost have like an obligation to
use that. That's like that's that's to be human is to express ourselves in some way
to to take advantage of our higher cognitive abilities and whatever direction we find most
resonant with our personalities I suppose. All of that's that's just mandatory and I
really not to get fucking divisive again but I really hate when people have abilities and
squander them or when they don't ever try and kind of explore some sort of higher higher
even the right word but like embrace their humanity you know like do something like so
many people are just passive consumers and it's it's so easy to fall into because our
society is designed to enable passive consumption because that's kind of what keeps the cogs
of everything going is you know we live in this weird kind of structure where if people
stopped buying things for a day the entire fucking system would just fall apart. You
know it's it's necessitating constant consumption which is a whole other you know fucking can
of worms we could open up in terms of like problems but human beings are are capable
of more than consumption you know because what what is it that animals do animals consume
that's it you know they go around they look for food and they fuck and they try not to
die and that's all an animal does they're they're they're they're they're blatant rampant consumers
and nature kind of has a way of providing checks and balances to make sure nothing kind
of gets out of whack and that's that's what life really is like we want to get down to
the nitty-gritty of like like the the state of nature is like consuming and doing your
best not to be consumed so when human beings are given more cognitive tools to do more
than merely consume but then we've created a culture that kind of incentivizes being
animals it's kind of sad and I'm going way off on a tangent but I think we all have a
responsibility to be more than animals to take the the gifts we've been given as human
beings and apply them as effectively as we can in a way that's most complimentary to
our skill sets I am trying to do that to the best of my ability and ever since finding
the internet and realizing that I'm not good at drawing like I thought I was as a kid and
realizing that there are so many people better and that for the amount of time I've put in
over a decade of work and not getting anywhere near as far as I should I've still improved
leaps and bounds but like when you start from such a huge deficit that's not saying a lot
I'm trying to find something else and I've been working on that you know like videos
were the first thing like okay I guess I'm gonna I'm gonna try making videos cuz people
seem to like these even though I've never had any interest in it and that was a huge
flop more whiskey oh fuck a little bit just got into the cut on my lip out okay whatever
um videos didn't really work out for me not my thing and didn't work out long term then I did
writing and I'm still kind of in the midst of writing writing seems a bit better but the
problem is like with writing twofold problem number one with writing is that not a lot of
people care and I am so bad at real life I can't hold down a job I can't work a real job I can
barely get hired for a real job it's a miracle that I got the fucking security guard job that I
got and it's cuz I had connections I would never would have been able to land it on my own I need
to be an internet man because I have no other really possible career path at this point it's
this or like die in the streets and that's it so I gotta make that work and writing is very
difficult to do that I've done so much research on like how people make money being authors other
than just like you know becoming published and get super fucking successful and famous and shit
like that and like so it seems to be like you need to create like classes on how to write and how
to like get an email list and how to promote your stuff and like I could do that I have the
technical ability to do that I just don't I don't have enough experience so in order to like get
to the point where I can make money writing is actually not making money writing it's making
money teaching other people who want to write how to write effectively and I can't really teach
that if I haven't done it myself yet so it's just like oh that's that's it's like years of
grind before I can really get to that point so writing just seems like a fiscal dead end despite
having some passion for it but then the other problem with writing is that now we have fucking
monkey coming in who's way better at writing and has a book deal and is getting all that shit done
and then I guess Jesse's writing and Jesse's a fucking genius so he's great at writing so just
like alright this is just drawing all over again once I'm exposed to other you know writers it's
like oh well I don't really have the chops there that I thought I did either so that's that's a
fucking fail and I'm gonna stop you right there viewer who's thinking Tom you're a fucking idiot
you shouldn't be comparing yourself to other people because I hear that line all the time and
it fucking pisses me off and I'll tell you why the pisses me off because you have to okay in the
magical fairyland of dreams and like magic where where nothing fucking matters of course you don't
compare yourself to other people you just sit down and you do your thing and everything's great
you have a good time but unfortunately we live on planet earth where everything's fucking terrible
and on planet fucking miserable shit whole rock land okay you have to compare yourself to other
people because life is a competition you exist to crush other people under your heel and be better
than them everything that you gain in life is at the expense of somebody else every product you
ever bought everything you've ever consumed everything you've ever you know watched or read or
done was at the expense of someone else's time money and effort so you have to compete life is
competition and the only way you can kind of like gauge where you're at with certain things is to look
out into the world and understand where you fall in the hierarchy I can sit here and draw by myself
and ignore everybody else like I'm just gonna draw for me but I'm never gonna get anywhere
because if I don't know where I fall and where I need to improve and where I need to get better
or just like be like hey Tom guess what you don't you're not cut out for this shit you know
you're never you're never gonna know you're never gonna be able to be successful because you
have to be cognizant of your comparative value in whatever you're doing like I could sit here
in my room I just like I'm gonna do fucking physics I want to do physics but I don't know
shit about physics so if I just sat here it's like yeah I'm just gonna do my thing I'd never get
anywhere with it like you have to look out into the world and understand where you fall in the
pecking order to understand okay am I any good at this where do I need to improve what am I doing
wrong and is this even viable because it's not just about being happy it's about being happy
while having enough money so they don't fucking die when you're born into this world your life is
a burden okay that's what oh god I'm gonna get political that's what capitalism is about and I'm
not I don't hate capitalism but I definitely think that it kind of sucks that everybody
who's ever been born and ever will be born until we fucking become starfleet uh is
instantly at risk of death of of of just self-inflicted death and that you in order to subsist
you have to constantly be producing something of value in a vacuum did it again that's kind of a
good idea like motivating people to constantly be uh doing something valuable but the problem is what
you think is valuable isn't necessarily valuable I think working on source was lost and writing
is valuable I find it valuable nobody else finds it valuable I only find it valuable so the things
I have to do things that have objective value that have social value that have social
practical purposes and that means walking around an abandoned building for 40 hours a week I have
no interest in doing that has no value to me in terms of like interest but the value it provides
me is currency and the it helps whoever owns the fucking building that's the social value
it's fucking dumb so you need to compare yourself with your skills and your talents and
your interests in order to understand will this provide value because drawing people want drawings
people want art there are people out there who patron artists so drawing as a medium has value
has potential value but if you're so far down the rungs of the the hierarchy and there are so many
people above you you inevitably there's a fall off the lower you go down the rungs the less your
talent becomes valuable because there are people who can do it better and if you have the choice
between a and b and a is better than b you're gonna go with a because a is superior so the
worst you are the less value you have in the world so I'm at the point where it's just like okay my
drawing is is borderline valueless because it's just so much worse than the people around me
compared to the time I've put into it and and I'm hitting this kind of glass ceiling in terms
of just like the amount of time it would take to become valuable in this skill is so gargantuan
and so massive and such like a steep ascent to get to that it almost becomes a worthless endeavor
because by the time it becomes valuable I'm like five years dead in the streets because I haven't
done anything else it's bullshit and it sucks so I can't draw my videos aren't as good as anybody
else's in the pcp I don't really have any charisma or charismatic personality that can carry anything
I do you know right now I'm getting slowly buzzed off of my not wine and I'm sure I sound like a
raving lunatic so what do I have to offer right if everything is about value and you come here
to listen to podcasts and be entertained by the people in this group because they're providing
some entertainment value to you if I'm not providing anything in that sphere why am I here
you know I want to earn my seat at the table but I feel like I'm ill-equipped in terms of skill set
to provide anything that isn't overlapping and underdeveloped compared to other people I don't
draw better than Ben I don't write better than monkey I don't make better videos than digi and
I don't have a better personality than Jesse I'm a knockoff shittier version of everybody else
so what's the fucking point like what do I provide here other than complaining anybody can
complain this isn't a skill this is just an outlet for frustration you know my channel rebel pixels
people like it because they're like you're such a failure I resonate with your failure and that's
why I'm attracted to some of your videos because I can understand and sympathize with your feelings
of inadequacy if my most valuable thing is providing comfort for other failures why the
fuck would I even bother like that's that's so fucking demoralizing it's like yeah you draw
yeah you write yeah you do this but the fact that you fail the way I do is what really attracts me
to you misery loves company so I'm gonna hang out with you like like that's grounds for fucking
blowing my brains out right there like fuck that like oh god so shitty I fucking hate it oh so what
what do I do what do I do I don't know what I do what was this podcast even about it's about
not having talent so I guess I guess we're still semi-on topic I don't have an ego I don't have
confidence I would like to I think it's valuable I don't know how to do it but I do have ego at
the same time it's weird I don't really know how to describe it maybe maybe you guys are familiar
with this in that like you have an ego but it's repressed like you can't express it because it
makes you angry or something I don't really know because like if I just sit down and ask myself like
do I want to be better than all these people in the pcp of course I do I think that's not rude to
say like why would I not want to be more successful than people around me again if everything's a
comparison and everything's a competition then in order to thrive you have to win I want to win
clearly because I don't want to be fucking dead I mean that pendulum swing in the other way with
every day but we're still we're still on live live land right now so if I'm going to be alive I want
to win and I want to be the best guy clearly I think everybody wants to be the best guy if they're
being honest with themselves like who doesn't want to be the best guy right I'm gonna be the best you
can be well if the best you can be fucking blows what if it's like like like the lowest tier that's
the best you can be nobody wants to be the best they can be if it's fucking shitty still everybody
wants to be the best guy so I want to be the best guy I want to be the best writer I want to be the
best artist I want to be the best video maker I want to be the best of everything but I can't be
the best of everything I can barely be competent at anything I don't know what I bring to the table
that isn't done better by somebody else so sometimes I just ask myself why I'm even here
like why bother like should I just leave should I just let let these guys do their thing and and
not fucking weigh them down with like this excess baggage of like yeah we got Ben he's a good
artist we got made she's a good artist we got monkey he's he's got a book deal going and and
we got like all these guys doing great videos with like really charismatic personalities
and sweet editing and really analytical points and then Tom well we've known him for a while he just
he kind of does this thing if I had met these guys now and not back during the horse days
none of them would give a fuck about me and I'm so fucking aware of this and it's not spoken but
I'm saying it now it's so fucking obvious that the only reason I'm still here is because of the
history we have nothing I'm doing in the moment has any value or any interest to anybody else on
this fucking channel oh you review graphics tablets who fucking cares I barely fucking care
it was an accident that it even happened what else you do oh you talk about how depressed you are
and how creativity is hard no fucking shit we all know that we're all doing it none of them would pay
rebel pixels any mind they barely do now which I don't blame them because it did fuck who cares
I barely care and I make the damn things none of it matters it's unimportant and it's unimpressive
I have no reason to be in this group and I'm desperate to to earn my seat again
back in the day when we first met and we were all doing gay horse faggot shit
I earned my seat I was the second biggest guy after digi
and I built that from nothing granted it was off the back of a fandom which kind of invalidates
all of the accomplishments but it was mine and I did it and I felt like I had earned my seat there
at the table of the horseshoe crew I belonged I I was there for a reason you know I was doing
something now I don't I don't do anything of value I don't do anything worth doing and everything
that I can do is done better by somebody else we're friends we're all friends but we definitely
are very aware of our creativity and and the things that we make and we prescribe a lot of value
to ourselves and everybody else based on what they make and I know my social currency and my
social credit in this group is is dwindling rapidly nobody wants to say it but I can see the
writing on the wall I'm not providing anything I just want to be good at something I don't know
if that's like it must be nice maybe I'm just too fucking depressed and full of self-hatred to
recognize my own skills but again skills in isolation don't mean anything it has to be
you have to look out into the world and compare favorably and even if I could come to terms with
the fact that oh I do good things in isolation it doesn't matter because in the real world compared
to other people none of it's any good so I either need to get really fucking good at something
or do something new that nobody else in the group does and say that's my thing
he's the guy who does that and that's why he's here
because right now I don't do shit and it's just only a matter of time before I just
get kicked out because he's not doing anything I think I already would have been kicked out
if I didn't have history with these guys I don't I don't do anything hi I'm I'm done
there's been hyperbolic wine chamber lots of whining today let me know if you want me to get
a specific one donate in the link and I'll get it next time