Good evening everybody and welcome to the first episode of the Hyperbolic Wine Chamber
where I train my ability to complain. I am Tom Oliver and today I'm going to be drinking
Red Bull because I'm at work and that's the best wine I can have here. The Red Bull was
donated by myself or technically by the wonderful taxpayers of Massachusetts because I got it
with my EBT card because I am that poor. If you would like to donate to the Wine Fund,
the link is in the description to my PayPal and by all means request a specific wine in
the text field and I'll do my best to track that wine down and drink during an episode
of the Wine Chamber and of course I will mention you in the show notes. So today we are going
to be talking about Art vs Critique and I guess this is a bit of a follow up to the recent
as of this recording Procrastinator's podcast episode I don't fucking care because it's
late, it's currently 12.37am and I'm only half an hour into my shift at work. I've got
a long night ahead of me and this is how I've decided to pass the time is to do the first
recorded but probably not the first aired episode of the Hyperbolic Wine Chamber. So
we're going to talk about Art vs Critique and a couple other kind of retorts and rebuttals
and points talking about the latest episode of the Procrastinator's podcast. I will link
it in the description if you have not watched it. I suggest you watch first but you don't
have to but of course if you're watching this you probably already have seen it so for like
you know most people it's fucking fine. I wanted to start with my definition of Art because
the podcast kind of was centered around art mediums that we don't respect or art mediums
we think are lesser like the tierless or hierarchy of artistic mediums and the conversation kind
of had its ups and downs and there were points that everyone was making that I was kind of
agreeing and disagreeing with so I'm going to try and kind of go into that a little bit
but first I just want to kind of lay the foundation with my definition of Art and I kind of have
two definitions sort of there's like the literal definition of Art and then my personal definition
of Art and I will try to explain what that means as well. So in terms of if you were
going to like say like Tom what is Art like if that's your question I would use Scott
McLeod's definition of Art ever since I stumbled upon it I think it's well I may not like personally
sit down and describe everything within its context to my personal beliefs of what Art
is I think like when soup comes to nuts I can't disagree with it so I'm going to say
that like literally everything for the falls and sides is definition of Art and his definition
of Art is anything that isn't done for survival or procreation counts as Art and that's a
super fucking wide huge gamut but I think if anything YouTube and just the internet
in general and things that have become monetizable and become art forms I think the definition
really holds true that things that you know even like 20 years ago that we probably never
would have considered artistic or a pursuit that had artistic merit have been proven wrong
even if I don't personally agree that some of these things I would consider as artistic
I think are still art so there was a great it's in I think it's in understanding comics
the book that Scott McLeod drew because like understanding comics and making comics and
reinventing comics or trilogy of books that he made that are comic books that deconstruct
comics as a medium they're really good even if you don't read comics or don't care about
comics too much I was just kind of thumbing through them anyway because they're really
interesting but at one point he has this kind of these panels that describe what he believes
Art to be and it's his caveman running around and he's saying the caveman has like three
main goals is is procreation finding a woman because it's a guy a woman to procreate and
have a child with because that's like kind of programmed into his primitive brain seek shelter
from the elements and acquire food and drink to sustain his body those are the three things
that like instinctually drive all living creatures and his ability his desire to survive and he's
being chased by a saber-tooth tiger or something to that effect and he's running and running he's
like you know he's trying to survive this encounter so he he runs to the edge of a cliff
and then he jumps up on like a tree branch that's overhanging the cliff that the tiger
leaps at him and falls off the cliff and it's like this was an entirely an exercise in this
man's desire to survive there's no art in here so what does he do next does he find more food
does he seek more shelters you find trying to court a woman again but instead he kind of like
does sticks his tongue out at the dead corpse it's off off uh i guess off camera but not really
camera and then it's just the next panel just says art something as simple as that it had no
practical application in this person's life uh but it was a self-expression uh devoid of necessity
that is art so i would say as a baseline kind of like anything that isn't done under survival
can technically be considered art so even if i don't personally deem it worthy of artistic
consideration by my own personal standards i would say that that is a true enough kind of
like factual objective definition of art now in my personal opinion which i consider art
you know that's much more nebulous it's kind of much on a kind of uh
case by case basis like you present me with something and like do i find it worthy of my
own personal artistic consideration um it's more nebulous i guess to really define now that i'm
trying to actually sit down and like kind of spin it into a sentence or two i don't think i can uh
it really is just there there are definitely certain things it's tough because like to go back
into the main idea of what the podcast was talking about like what is art and what are my tears i
definitely have a personal tier list of things that i respect more in terms of their artistic
merits versus other things however something that was done consistently on the podcast that i don't
know if i really understand uh and this is a podcast that i really wish i was in on but i was
at work so i couldn't really do it um is that there there were these tier lists are being
mentioned by some people but i don't know if they were like trying to present them as objective
fact or if this was just personal opinion being confused with it because ben was saying some stuff
um i think hippo made mentioned a couple things um
but those those are personal opinions like i i could i could give you a list a tier list of like
things that i appreciate more than anything i think animation is probably at the top uh
then then it'd probably be books then comic books then video games and and and things like like uh
modern art and and abstract art and and uh you know like analysis and things would be at the
bottom in terms of things that have artistic merit but but that's just my that's not a tier
it's not like an objective tier list that's not something like these are worthy this is just my
interpretation my appreciation of these mediums in terms of ascribing them personal artistic
uh values objectively it doesn't mean anything and that's i guess that's kind of like the problem
right because like where does subjectivity end and objectivity begin or does it ever begin or end
i need to actually have some of my wine my quote unquote red bull wine
here we go so
where does one begin and another end and another thing that um that jesse said that i agree with
very much and i would have i was itching to bring up sitting there listening to podcast until he
brought it up was that um pieces of work are not necessarily confined to the slot that they reside
in and what i mean by that is like let's say i think personally that i feel that animation is a
more powerful and more artistically uh impressive to me medium than uh video games undertale is
still way more impressive artistically than a lot of animation i've seen you know like you're
they're not nothing is is bound by its tier list it's not like every the worst animation is still
more artistically valuable to me than the best video game there's definitely some overlap there
and that's why i think that the tiering doesn't really mean much um it just kind of says to me
that like you know if you mentioned the medium off hand like i have a certain amount of respect for
it just from my personal experience um as someone who's written books as someone who's attempted
animations as someone who's attempted and failed miserably at making games and as somebody who's
done illustration and podcasting i'm like i'm dabbled in a bunch of different things there's
subtle nuances to each medium that need to be understood and appreciated in order to do them
effectively and i'm not even going to begin to pretend that i'm a master at any of the fields
i've ever attempted to do uh even this podcast i'm probably doing a mediocre job at best but
there's there's mastery in every field even in things that i particularly revile or not even
reviles too hard word things that i don't find much particular personal interest in things like
abstract art you know like the jackson pollocks and the cubism and and shit like that that is
fine boring and uninteresting and vapid personally uh aren't some boring or vapid to other people
and aren't boring and vapid objectively at least i don't think so like what does the objective uh
value of art really mean and like going back to a specific example from the podcast itself with
pornography is a lot of porn empty and baseless well sure like it's kind of manufactured to be
low hanging fruit because it's appealing it's art that's made for the primitive mind instead of the
intellectual mind and that sounds really like fucking pompous when i say it out loud but it's
true right like like sexual desire isn't really a refined uh intelligent aspect of humanity it's
very like going back to the caveman example of how i defined art it's something that's been there
since the inception of mankind and to appeal to that you require very little you know because
it's not a very complicated emotion uh you want to fuck somebody so to make art that that stimulates
that part of the mind doesn't really require a lot of intellectual depth a lot of creative
endeavor you know like you you see something someone hot you want to have sex with them you
know it's kind of like that initial and emotional kind of visceral reaction so pornography to be
an effective form of art doesn't really need to be all of that uh crazy complexity like like it's
more complicated to to stimulate your intellectual desire or intellectual appreciation of like a
love story having two characters fall in love with each other and i'm sympathizing with their kind
of emotional play that's a much more complicated thing to do than to stimulate the primitive
mind of like i have an erection and i want to fuck something i can jerk off to this
it's it's a simpler desire so pornography i guess as a result is a much simpler art form
um is it still art for my technical definition yes uh from my personal definition i think it's
probably lower rung if i was going to rank it in terms of things i appreciate artistically but i'm
never going to deny that it's not art there is pornography in any medium is still uh a sub
section of the medium itself so like if someone's drawing like a pornographic image it's still a
drawing and has all of the artistic merits of drawing as a medium same with as a film same
with as a comic book same with any of that stuff like it's all using the same techniques that if
you replace those drawings of fucking with drawings of anything else would still be an art form so
well the the so it's not really the structure of pornography that makes it less desirable
uh or less valid as an art form i think it's the goal that turns a lot of people off ironically by
just existing to turn them on um because it doesn't aspire to much more than that right like you
know the typical plot of a porn the the the stereotypical you know uh pizza delivery guy
comes i can't before the pizza can i pay with something else like you know that's about as
complicated as porn plots tend to get but then again just to make a good example with alan
war's lost girls taking pornography to a whole other level that was done intentionally so it's
like how much of pornography being unexplored as an art form is because of culture because culture
really is still kind of on the fritz when it comes to to to porn and and human sexuality in
journal is still something that's very private i think probably with good reason for the most part
um i don't think we need to be super puritan about it but sex is a private thing uh you know
just by nature of what it is do i think there's more room in social uh commentary to to to address
it more to be more open about it of course um i think we've made large strides in the last like
even like 10 years of of kind of normalizing this talk and just understanding of sexuality
because it's a huge part of humanity and again it's very ingrained in the human mind so i think uh
artistically there's definitely more room for pornography to become to kind of like move beyond
its its stigma i don't think it needs to be as stigmatized as it is uh but i think like i said
because it's it's it's it's trying to stimulate a very primitive part of the human mind it doesn't
have to be very complicated in order to be effective uh so that's what i got on pornography i got a
whole notes what else was i going to talk about um oh i uh another thing i wanted to talk about
was analysis because analysis is kind of glazed over i got a lot to fucking say about analysis as
someone who did analysis for two years um like i mentioned earlier analysis is pretty low on my
rung of like things i have a lot of appreciation for i kind of get where ben was coming from where
he was saying that analysis can never uh surpass the work it was based on um i don't think surpassed
was probably the right word i think what ben was trying to say or at least what i was taking from
him because it was something that i kind of agree with is that analysis is always contingent upon
other art to exist it can't exist in a vacuum right you can't analyze nothing so in order
to analyze something something else has to pre predate it i guess was a word something something
needs to exist first in order to be analyzed um so it's always a reactive medium it always has
to be a reaction to something else and that inherently makes it a response and never an
initiation of creativity if that kind of makes sense um i don't know if that's exactly the best
way to to word it but there always it always has to come after something else and i think that's
what ben was trying to get at um the the the the red letter media thing he was kind of referencing
when saying star wars is a good example of uh the the analysis getting more kind of critical
recognition than the work itself uh though depending on the social circle you ran uh the
prequels are well loved by certain fanboys but something i wanted to bring up when i was listening
to that was the idea of analysis and cultural catharsis uh red letter media is a great example
of that how much of the the the reaction to uh that video was was catharsis right because there
was a long build there was a big gap between the phantom menace in 1999 and the red letter media
video which i think was like 2009 2010 something it was it wasn't very recent it was it was a couple
years ago but there was a huge at least i think a 10 year gap between phantom menace and the video
so there was 10 years of this like cultural buildup of like animosity toward this video like the
initially came out um i was like in fourth grade at the time so i loved it because i was a stupid
little kid but i'm assuming at the time there were adults who were kids watching the original
star wars watched it and felt betrayed by it felt that it was a letdown um obviously people feel
that way nowadays i'm assuming at the time there probably was a group of people who were too
so there was a decade of just like built up animosity towards this trilogy and how it let them
down and how it was just just a different approach to the franchise than the original movies so how
much of the appreciation for the star wars reviews and by extension analysis in general
is for the catharsis of having your your note your ideas um given a bigger outlet than just your
mind versus for the art itself um because as someone who did analysis and someone who's from
the bunch of people who do analysis and reviews and critique and stuff i can appreciate the red
letter media reviews on a technical level for what they're doing with the medium of analysis
even though i don't appreciate it as much as an art form but i'm sure a ton of people don't think
about that at all they're just like yeah they're sticking into these movies that i hate so i think
a lot of the love that eclipses the prequels probably comes from this just like jonesing for
the the fucking like verbal assault that they gave the prequels does that really count i guess
is my question maybe it does um but it seems like a lot of that comes from um the catharsis and the
feeling of oh i understand that and that's how i feel and and he's saying exactly what i want to
say and it kind of almost feels like uh you're appreciating it because you're seeing yourself
in it and therefore you're kind of like you're kind of pushing your ego into the piece because
it's saying something that you wanted to say and something you already believe versus your
appreciation for the piece itself um maybe another way of examining this point is talking
about um four panel comics that are prevalent on tumblr where they're like hashtags so relatable
you know when there's a character in like their pet and then life or some sort of life struggle
is personified and and shits on them or something and like all the reblogs like ha ha this is me
hashtag me and like people seem to there's like a huge backlash against those now especially
against owl turds comics on tumblr as of late just because they're so redundant and done over
and over again and they appeal to a very kind of base uh concept of like i'm going to point out
something in life that is common and affects a lot of people and you're going to look at it and
you're not going to really see the work itself you're going to project yourself into it like ha ha
this is me i like it because i see myself not because i appreciate the work and i feel like
analysis uh sometimes can do that as well where it's appreciated because of catharsis
and not because of what it is okay that went on a bit longer than i want i got five minutes left
to wrap this up before i gotta do my next round at work fuck um analysis and dependency uh critics
and laziness what am i even talking about with this bullet point um i don't remember
critics and laziness fuck i'm gonna have to cut this whole part out i don't even remember what
i was talking about these bullet points i wrote them like three hours ago fuck okay so i this is
like an hour and a half two hours later i'm cutting this in because i remember what i meant by critics
and laziness okay so this is probably gonna get me a ton of flak but i don't fucking care because
i think it's true and whatever i think critics too many critics fall back to criticism because
they're too lazy or feel they're too untalented to do the thing they're actually passionate about
that they criticize for example i think a lot of people who do video game reviews and shit on
probably really love video games and would make video games but you think it's too hard
or they're not talented or they just don't want to put in the effort to learn how to make games
because that's really difficult but they want to express their love for video games so instead
they talk about video games and i think because analysis is such a big thing and critique and
reviews and it's easy and you can make money doing it and it's become this big thing because of youtube
i think we're being deprived of a lot of people who make things because it's easier and more
rewarding short term to talk about things that other people have already made i think that's a
huge fucking problem and it's one of the reasons why i don't really do much reviews of media anymore
because i would rather spend the time that i spent making reviews making things
you know this is something that i guess this is kind of a personal tick that really
resonates with me is that when sometimes there are some people there are people who are legitimate
critics people who like actually want to be that and that's what they want and nothing else i think
digi is a great example just off the top man to somebody who actually legitimately likes
and wants to be an analyst i don't think if given the knowledge and the tool set to make anime he
would stop reviewing anime i think that's that that's his thing and that's what he wants to do but
there are a ton of people who aren't like that and for me personally that's what was kind of pissing
me off is that i'm talking about tv shows and i'm talking about movies and i'm talking about games
but i'm only doing it because i'm too lazy to get off my ass actually make the things i'm talking
about and that's what i was doing before i got into youtube was that i was putting my money
where my mouth was and where my passion was and trying to make the things i don't want to talk
about things that are cool i want to be talked about is one of the things that are cool that's
what i'm really interested in and i really hate how there are so many people who are doing analysis
because they're too lazy to put in the legwork to make the thing that they're actually passionate
about i think there are so many people out there who would be making movies who would be making games
who would be writing books who would be making tv shows who would be doing all these things but
it's just too hard so they don't and then they see people talking about the stuff on youtube like
oh that's easy i can just point a camera and talk about it and look the guy's a million subscribers
and makes a hundred thousand dollars i'm gonna do that and then they do that and we've lost another
creator to the simple easy returns of analysis and critique and i really hate me all you want
but i really think that because of youtube has made analysis and review and critique and commentary
way too big and has pulled people away from legitimate creation i think youtube is unfairly
it's almost too easy to make money with youtube and now too hard to make things doing things that
actually require effort it's like this reward effort is unbalanced right now you should make
more money quicker and and and more significantly when you do the hard work than the easy work but
that's not the way the system set up right now and i think that combined with like just lack of
confidence or lack of desire in people you know i actually want to make things and it's still
fucking hard and i still haven't done anything of any significance yet so i can't even imagine
someone who like doesn't really have that drive they're kind of sitting on the fence like it's
so fucking difficult but like the tantalizing prospect of being the next nostalgia critic a black
nerd or red led or media whatever just like like like just sitting there and talking about
shit and getting all these acolytes i just think if put in a vacuum and asked what would you want
to do if the effort and the money and the time was no object and you could just snap your fingers
and you would do one of these fields i think a lot of people who are involved in criticism would
say like like if it was no object of course i would make a movie instead of talk about movies
of course i would make a book instead of talking about books of course i would make a comic instead
of talking about comics and that's what's frustrating that's what i think so much analysis
comes from laziness too lazy to put in the time to be what you admire instead you're just kind of
talking about it that's what i meant that's just a huge problem with analysis and that's kind of
why for me personally i put it so low in terms of where i think it is artistically because i think
so many people do it for the wrong reasons and fuck that i want to talk about books because
munchie kind of tried to go on this fucking rampage about books i'm happy that jesse and ben
both shut him down because he's so fucking stupid saying that books are shit books are definitely
not shit um but this is kind of like i don't want to say a new revelation but something i was reminded
of by getting back into books in the last couple months um i used to read a lot in high school
and middle not even high school i used to read a lot in middle school and elementary school
by high school i was reading mostly comics because i think i had the same mentality that a lot of
people do and kind of maybe what munchie sounded like saying that like pictures are better than
words and that's kind of why i started gravitating towards comic books and manga away from uh
books when i was a little kid because i liked drawing i liked words but i also like pictures
and i liked pictures more so like this has words and pictures this has just words i'm going to go
with words and pictures um but reading again in the last like two or three years as i've slowly
started getting back into reading novels um there is a specific cadence and a specific tone and a
specific way of storytelling that books have that cannot be replicated in other mediums um
um books aren't just movies without a budget it's something that i think a lot of people don't
realize or don't fully appreciate is that a book is a very unique form of storytelling
because it allows a couple different things that i really appreciate the first is that you
can really get into a character's head in a way that you can't do in movies as much um because
movies have show don't tell uh books have show don't tell as well but you have to show by telling
which is kind of weird because all a book really is is telling it's it's like 300 pages of telling
but it's the way that you tell that makes it feel more like showing
it so you can get into a character's head and really understand their thought process and get
into their their their thoughts and their inner kind of workings as they go through situations
that you can't do uh in a way that isn't heavy-handed in film you can imply a lot of things
with cinematography uh to a character's inner plights and stuff but in terms of like a very
like direct line into a character's thought process books can do this more efficiently
because they're nothing but writing so you can like stop as you're describing something you can
describe the the emotions and the thought process going through character's head in between statements
because time flows a little bit differently right you're reading the book and and a book can have
like a page that goes through like you know five minutes of stuff or another page it goes to like
half a second as they think through uh a decision um you can't really do that with a movie because
a movie's running in real time consistently like time can flow differently but you as a passive
viewer are experiencing it in real physical time obviously because you're sitting watching the movie
so like if a character is sitting there uh think about something for a minute it's happening in a
minute of real time um and the movie's kind of happening in that time as well but if you're
reading a book um it it doesn't it it just it feels different um you're still experiencing it in
real time but the book allows for some reason allows that time to feel less uh disjointed i
guess um i guess also because like a book is right at your own pace it doesn't really have a limit of
like two hours approximately to really worry about it can kind of meander a bit more uh because page
counts are much less consistent than movie times uh but regardless you can get into character's head
just can examine situations and and really break things down more than you can in movies and another
thing that i really like is you can engage all of the senses more specifically than you can
in any other medium uh ironically because there's less sense there's less visual engagement like
describing things in books like visual medium is very difficult to do in books compared to any
other medium because there are no visuals like you have to sit there and describe things as opposed
to just showing it in any other medium and i would say that's books biggest weakness is that it can
also be considered a strength um from a certain perspective that like you can envision the world
however you want it kind of stimulates your imagination a bit more and i'd say that's a
useful thing but in terms of like like uh objective like strength versus weaknesses in terms of like
me as an author trying to tell you what something looks like by me having to describe it with words
i can never be as accurate as it would be if i could just show you a picture of what it was
so that's a weakness of books but on the flip side every other sense can be stimulated uh second hand
just as eloquently whereas something visually has to kind of go out of its way to kind of
tell you about it so for example if i was going to sit here and describe the room i'm in i could
describe how it looked like uh the room had a very ominous cadence because i'm sitting in an
abandoned building with nothing else in here one lighted room looking outwards through two windows
into a vast sea of blackness sparsely lit by a small light scattered throughout the large room
the the ticking of the clock kind of punctuates every minute of my time being wasted in here
not being able to do the things i actually want to do the smell of the air smells of oil and dust
and makes me cough it's so i can jump between visual stimuli and and like you know how something
smells and how something feels and then how i think i can do that all in the same kind of rhythm
without ever breaking the flow of how a book works whereas if a film wants to describe how
something smells a character usually has to say oh man it stinks you know and and very clearly like
kind of stop whatever else is going on and say this is what this send this this uh this sense
is being stimulated in this world because all you can do is see it um but if i showed you a picture
of the of the room that i'm sitting in i can much more clearly give you the visual information than
me describing it because every one of you listening to this saw a different version of the room and
none of them were exactly the same as the one i'm actually sitting in whereas if i gave you a picture
everyone's perception would be the same so books have strengths and weaknesses but the point i'm
trying to make here is that books are the are in work of art or a medium of art that is unique
they do things that know where the medium can and they're not just like shittier versions of books
or comics um that's all i got for this episode i was going to make some other points but i'm out
of time already late for my next round so this has been the hyperbolic wine chamber i've been
drinking not wine but if you want to give me wine for the next one link is in the paypal tell me
what you want me to drink and i'll go drink it if you have suggestions for the podcast let me know
till next time i'm tom oliver and i'll be whining forever because i hate my life i don't know how to
end these yet that's that's all i got