Hello everybody and welcome to another fantastic episode of the Hyperbolic Wine Chamber. April
Fools, it's probably gonna be pathetic. Today, we are drinking Magner's Irish Pair Cider.
Imported since 1935. I don't know anything about this, but I just got it. Today's wine
has been funded by Michael Perrin at Crackkissie on Twitter. So if you want to go say thank you
for the wine, go to at K-R-A-K-I-S-S-I on Twitter. They're cool. They provided some money for the
wine fund and this was the first acquisition of that that fundage. I actually didn't even realize
this was there. I was digging through and just noticed it and I was like, oh, why did PayPal
not email me about this? You fucking bastards. Alright, so today we're going to be talking about
God and religion. Oh boy. I hesitated whether I wanted to talk about this, but I do. And I do
because I feel like I have a perspective that is at least I haven't seen voiced very often. And
because of that, I kind of wanted to give my two cents. Before we do that, I'm going to
get to take a first sip of the Pair Irish Cider and see how it is. Smells nice.
It's very, very sweet and barely tastes the alcohol at all.
Interesting. I actually kind of like this one.
Okay, so I don't want to even start this. Oh my God. So I guess maybe some background
would probably be appropriate to kind of explain where my current position is on like
God and stuff. So I was raised, I was raised Catholic, I was raised Roman Catholic.
I went to church every Sunday and every holy day from when I was,
assumingly from when I was born until I was 16 years old. And at least four of those 16 years,
I was being forced to church against my will because I was not a fan of it.
Roman Catholicism, at least a brand that was taught in this house,
never really appeared much, appealed much to me, I should say. It was always kind of like the doom
and gloom fire and brimstone. You're gonna burn in hell if you don't follow everything like completely
100% by the book, you know, the book. My mom, who was the super religious one in the house,
would consistently say when we were kids that she loved us but loved God more and things like that.
My big problem as a kid, I first started really not being into the whole God thing because when
I was a little kid, I never really considered it much. It was just something we did, you know,
I never kind of sat down and examined the spiritual and philosophical nuances of the Catholic doctrine.
I don't think much 8 to 10 year olds really do that. I just kind of, you know, went to Sunday
school, went to CCD, went to church, knelt, stood, bowed, whatever we were supposed to,
had a little way for thingy and then, but I got donuts after the fact. We always get donuts
after the church would provide them or we'd go down the street to dunks and get a big fucking
donut and then I'd be happy happy. The problem is that it's on a Sunday and that's 50% of my weekend
as a kid when you're going to school and I don't want to wake up, I want to sleep in late, you know,
because I've already got up early the day before because I gotta fucking watch Saturday morning
cartoons, you know, fucking Pokemon and Spider-Man and I'm gonna mute my computer. But I just found
church to be an annoyance is really where my initial disdain for going to Mass came from. I just,
I didn't want to go because I was too busy playing video games, I wanted to sleep in and it was just,
it was annoying. It was an hourth long thing and my mom's like a parish hopper, at least she was
back when I was going to church. So we would go to different parishes all the time. There was a
small window of time where we went to Mass in Latin, which was really weird. So the whole Mass
was in Latin. Nobody had any idea it was being said. We just listened to a priest and the priest,
I guess when this is like, super hardcore is when you have the Mass in Latin is the priest
isn't even allowed to look at you like he has to look at the tabernacle and tabernacles where like,
you know, the Eucharist, like the holy like the body, but the little way for things are. So
didn't even get the eye contact, he would be saying the Mass to Latin away from us,
you would see wouldn't hear him very well, which didn't really matter because he was speaking Latin.
That was like an hour away. The Mass was an hour and a half. So you're burning three hours there
an hour and an hour and a half there and an hour back. Near the tail end, we would go a couple
towns over. So it would be like a half an hour there. Mass then half an hour back and because
my mom was super religious, we'd have to say a rosary in the car on the way in and back. So it
was it was it was like two hours of like prayer. And and we just was me and my sister at the time.
We neither of us were into it. Just just we didn't either of us. We were annoyed by it. It wasn't
it wasn't really ever sit down like I have issues with the doctrine. I just didn't like it. And
eventually at 16, my father, who used to be religious, got out of it and kind of has like
his own sort of like kind of like weird personal kind of pseudo spirituality. I approached him
because I had to go get confirmed and confirmation is like when you become an adult in the church
or whatever and the Christian or at least a Catholic thing, but you have to stay at church
like overnight. You got to like go in, do a bunch of prayer stuff, a bunch of like Jesus
activities and you got to stay overnight and you do something the next day and then you're
confirmed. I'm just like, No, no, I can't I can't do a whole weekend of church. And the problem was
like, you have to this is what the confirmation was when I first started to really kind of think
about the doctrine itself. I didn't just sit there and go through the motions because like they made
a big deal out of the fact that like the priests and the people who were talking about confirmation
are still going to CCD and crap at the time. They made a big deal about how like, this is a big
deal in this faith, you know, if to be confirmed means like you're you believe in all of this,
this is something really important to you and you're kind of like making a contract with God
like with your soul and all that stuff. And and that was my first way to call like, wait a minute,
none of this jives with me. I'm just going through the motions I'm being told to, you know,
and and it was the first time I really realized that like faith was a choice because I didn't
have a choice in my house and have a choice to go to church. I had even though I'd expressed the
fact that I wasn't really interested in it. It was always like a firm no, like you have to go
like this is this is you have to do this, you know, and I don't really blame my mom for that
because if she she's knee deep in the whole thing. And so she was worried about my eternal soul.
So I don't blame her for being adamant about it. But then you'd go to the priest and the church
and stuff and they would tell you that like, this is your choice. And if you don't want to do it,
you shouldn't do it. So that's when I started to sit back and really like think about things like,
wait a minute, none of this really resonates with me, you know, I've never it's never been
something that like I've been gung ho about, like I know the rules, I know the ins and outs,
like I've been to CCD and I've been to mass, I know all the stuff to achieve, you know, at least
at a basic level. But I don't know if I really believe it, I can recite it, but I don't know
if it resonates with me. And now you want me to go through this like really big, like, ritual,
that's a huge deal in this faith. And literally, it's to confirm your belief. And I have no faith
to confirm. So it felt really wrong to me just from a moral standpoint. I didn't because like
none of these people in church that I knew and I knew a couple people of this one and the pastor
at this church who went to was actually a really nice guy. I just felt bad going up there lying
to him, because he was a good guy. And it was just like, I don't I don't feel like this is right.
So I approached my dad, because he was the only one I could talk to about this and be like, Dad,
I don't really want to do this. Like this is an overnight thing. And they're trying to
fucking confirm. And I don't I don't think I can confirm without lying, like, should I lie in a
space of God, like that seems that seems wrong, even by their rules, you know, like this, I don't know.
Long story short, there's a huge fucking fight between me, my mom, my dad. I eventually got out
of going to confirmation. Stop going to church at 16. Big riff between me and my mom for a while,
kind of at this point, we've patched up. She's really not even as religious as used to be anymore.
It used to be bad, like I couldn't read Harry Potter, because it was the devil, I couldn't play
Magic the Gathering, because that was the devil. So she would guilt me into giving up my cards that
I'd like saved up my allowance to buy. And my Harry Potter books disappeared. And I never got to
read past the prisoner of Azkaban. So happened to this day. Very, very religious. So I got out of
it. And then when I was when I was no longer like in it, I started really kind of reflecting on all
the things that they were talking about. And it's like, I don't really think this is true, you know,
and it really it affected me for a long time. You know, my first relationship, my first girlfriend
suffered because like, I always felt guilty about having sex and stuff, because like, you know,
in the Christian faith, like, no sex before marriage and all this things. And it took a while
to kind of like, let myself forgive myself for it. And even to this day, there's always like
thoughts of just like, you know, like, what if I'm going to burn in hell? Like, I've been a very
bad Catholic, you know, I think I've been a good person from kind of like a universal morality
kind of standpoint, but in terms of like following the Catholic doctrine, I'm way off the fucking
beaten path. But my history, I could go into more detail. But that's not really the point of this
podcast. I'm already like 10 minutes in, I've kind of just barely set the stage. I want to talk more
about not any specific faiths. I want to talk about like more like, like, not heady, but basic
concepts. God in general, right now, I'm not really a big fan of labels for anything. But if
you want it to kind of like understand my perspective in like a few words, I guess the best description
right now would be an agnostic atheist. I don't believe in a God. I don't think there is a God
just just based on just my observations. And I know that's the complete opposite of God like
God is faith. So God defies observation. But the problem with that for me is that everything else
in the entire world is based on science and observable phenomena. And the fact that there is
like this big ruling kind of energy and system in place in Judeo Christian faith, and then you
have to take it on faith, it just seems so convenient that there's a loophole for everything. And this
was really the first thing that I really honed in on with Catholicism, especially because I was
most familiar with it, that really rubbed me the wrong way, is that it was so interesting how the
faith had a way to skirt any sort of questions you would have. There was no arguing it. It was
always some sort of weird kind of sidestep, faint dodge to any questions you had, you know,
that he works in mysterious ways line. And at the same time, it was always interesting to me to
consider how archaic religions were kind of seen as a joke and nothing more than entertainment.
And it was always a bizarre concept to think of like, well, you know, we look at like the Egyptian
gods like Horus and the Greek gods like like Zeus and stuff and their characters, their fictional
characters, we they're the same thing as like, you know, Harry Potter, or, or like Luke Skywalker
stuff, they're their fictional characters that can be like repurposed and reinterpreted and
used in fiction all the time. But Jesus Christ isn't Muhammad isn't you know, these characters
these these characters aren't characters, they're historical figures and all this stuff is true.
And it always just felt really odd like why is this we're so sure that this is bullshit,
but this isn't bullshit, but they both have just as much like realistic viability. The only difference
is that one is accepted as spirituality, and one has long been rejected. So it's 2000 years from
now is Jesus going to be you know, parodied and like, you know, you're going to have like
fucking like a God of war video game and VR where you fight Jesus or something instead of like the
Greek gods, like, like who knows like, like, that's the whole thing. It just it just seems
the faith seems very convenient. And it always it feels like Catholicism and its kind of current
incarnation was developed back in medieval times to control people. And to siphon wealth off of
people, you know, like you have to live in poverty, because that's going to make you yours is the
kingdom of heaven, the meek shall inherit the earth and all that stuff. So give us all your money,
give your money to the church, give it to God, and by extension, give it to us the clergy,
and you live in an abject poverty, but that's a good thing. And you'll be rewarded when you die,
you know, but who fucking knows? Because once you're dead, it doesn't fucking matter anymore. It's
just it just seems really convenient, you know, like, how can you and people make these I don't
want to like get too bogged down this because again, I'm still just kind of setting the groundwork
of of the Vatican is a great example of like, almost the hypocrisy of the faith, you know,
like how can you have a city like the Vatican, but your tenants say you have to live in poverty.
And I know the current Pope is kind of like, in fact, I am aware of that hypocrisy. But it's
just like the whole thing just collapses upon inspection. The point I really wanted to make
with this, though, is that I'm not an atheist. I'm an agnostic atheist. And I wonder if there are
anybody listening or anybody in general, I'm sure there is, but like, I've never really talked to
anybody who kind of thinks about God the way I do. And so much that I'm not an aggressive atheist,
you know, you kind of go online and you and you and you look up atheism. And there are these people
just like, fuck God, God is bullshit. God is stupid. God is a terrible idea. And you're invisible
man in the sky. And if you believe in God, you're an idiot. Science is all that matters. God is
nothing but fairy tales. And you're a dumb ass. And the atheist community quote unquote, or just
atheism, the most vocal atheists are people like that. And then you know, I'm there's probably
the every man atheists who just like, Yeah, I don't really believe in that. And they kind of go on
with their day. The reason I use a term agnostic atheist is because I don't think there's a God,
but I can't prove it. There's just as much proof that there isn't God, that there is God.
Because that's the whole thing that's kind of going back to the loophole thing I was talking
about God by definition is unprovable. So any any sort of tangible evidence we can have that would
prove God would just be dismissed by the religious as not God. It's like, Oh, we found we we figured
out the the existence like the the the existence of the the big bag we proved it we have proof.
And like this is what it is. And like this is what God was. And then just like but that's not God,
you know, like even even the fact that like someone could like, God could come down to earth,
have a physical embodiment, and not be any of the faiths that we've ever had, like, you know,
like, because who the fuck do we know what God is, if God is like this big immortal thing.
But let's say, let's say God is real, and God comes down to earth in a physical body,
and says, I'm God, I'm going to do all this crazy shit. And yeah, I'm God, like now you know,
you know, all you people been asking for proof of God, here I am. I think the atheists would still
be like, fuck you, you're not really God, you're just an imposter. And then the religious would be
like, no, God is this God is God is our faith. And then whatever you are, you're not true, you're
like, you're like the devil trying to trying to trick us, or, or you're not God, you're something
else, you know, by the fact that you're here physically, disproves that you're God, you know,
even I think the super religious who believe in things like the rapture, and like the second
coming itself, I think of the second coming actually happened, they probably wouldn't believe it was
the second coming, kind of got sidetracked. But that was a point I did want to make. My perspective
is that I'm an atheist under duress. And what I mean by that is that I don't hate God. I actually
would prefer if there was a God, I just can't find any reason in my heart of hearts to truly
believe that I would I because because if there is a God, everything has a purpose. I have a purpose.
My pain has a purpose. My suffering has a purpose. The suffering I see around me has a
everything is happening for a reason. Everything that's chaos instantly becomes order.
Everything is going completely according to plan. Nothing is wrong. Everything that's happening is
just this huge big like supernatural chess game that my tiny little mortal head can't understand.
But everything's fine. So I don't have to worry about it anymore. I just got to do me to the best
I can and know that I'm being guided subconsciously by a divine entity that's going to lead me to
exactly the right place I need to go. That would be great. I would prefer that even if it would kind
of give up a bit of my autonomy almost, but the the idea that everything's good, that everything's
fine, that there's nothing wrong. I find that very appealing. I would love there to be. I'm
envious of people who have faith because they must be so much more sound of mind, so much more calm,
so much more collected because they believe, truly believe that there's a guy up there making
sure everything's okay. I would love that. But to go back to what I said about how faith seems so
convenient and how all these old dead faiths are just jokes now and that everything that
throughout human history that was once attributed to God has been shown to be a natural understandable
phenomenon. It just, I can't believe because it seems ridiculous given the circumstances
to continue to have belief. I would love to, but God itself, religion as a concept seems like
a desperate ploy by humanity to have something bigger, to have that control. I think everybody
wants what I just described to know that everything's okay. The difference between
the religious and myself is that they can find a way to buy into it. And as much as I want to buy
into it, I can't. So I'm an atheist under duress. I don't want to be an atheist. I just have no choice.
I don't know if other people feel like that. I don't know. I've never talked to anybody about
faith really all that much, but like even just in casual conversation, all the atheists are always
just like, fuck God. And I just, I can't get mad at religious people. Like they do some stupid
shit sometimes when they bring their, their, their faith into like politics and into like,
you know, people's lifestyle and shit like that. But just like when they're doing their own thing,
go for it. Like you're definitely more mentally healthy than I am. I'm on antidepressants seeing
a therapist suicidal because my life's falling apart. And I don't think I can't bring myself to
believe that there's any greater purpose than just some crazy bullshit genetic fucking cocktail
random chance fucking destroyed doomed universe around us. And there's nothing to live for. And
I have to build my own fucking destiny and my own fucking purpose with my own bare hands.
And every day I don't do it, just another day closer to my own death when I turn into nothing.
And that's it. The universe is big and vast. And I am pointless and have no purpose. And I
just have to sit here and try and forge my own purpose in this tiny little speck of existence
I have before I'm dead and everything is forgotten and no longer exists. There's no afterlife.
This is all I have. And right now it's really shitty. That's terrifying. I would love to have
the comfort of faith. I'm envious of people who have the comfort of faith, but I can't do it.
I don't know if I even want to, if I could, because I'm so kind of, I don't want to say logically,
but just like observationally grounded. But I can see the appeal. I can understand the appeal.
I'm envious of the appeal. So that's my thing on God. That was the big point I wanted to make.
This is a very ranty video. I would love to believe in God. Because I think there would be this kind
of like a placebo effect. There would be a placebo effect of if I was truly confident
that I was being guided by God or I had God on my side and that everything was happening for a
reason, I would probably self actualize better than I do now. Because the stresses and the
depression and the anxiety that I have right now would be at least partially lifted because of that
faith. So even if there was no God, just the belief in it would probably allow me to function on a
higher level than I am right now. Because my mind would be less burdened with all these heavy,
fucking crazy, deep philosophical ideas and the horribly bleak outlooks that my scientific
based perspective leads to with those questions. I don't know. That's really all I got. I kind
of want to talk about this for a while. Not exactly the most welds put together podcast,
very rambly. But there you go. Wanted to find about God? Wanted about God? Let me know in the
comments if you hated it. I'm Tommy Oliver. Thanks again to Michael for the wine. It was actually
a good choice. I like it. So if you want something really sweet that barely tastes like alcohol,
Magner's Irish Parasiter. Not a bad choice. Take it easy, guys.