Hello everybody and welcome to another episode of the Hyperbolic Wine Chamber where I train
my ability to complain. I am Tom Oliver and today I am recording much earlier than I usually
do these episodes. Usually I record these around 11.30 at night but today we are recording
at 11.30 in the morning. So I thought it was a perfect time to try out a new wine that
I picked up. Fourth star brewing company, Maple Breakfast Stout, brewed with real maple
syrup. One pint in a can. Maple C Series, 6.5% alcohol per volume. Another Vermont small
brewery. We seem to get a lot of those here in Massachusetts because we are pretty close
by and there's a big brewing scene over there in Vermont. So this seems like an early morning
beer for an early morning kind of podcast. So let's see what we got going on here. Yeah,
it tastes like beer. There's a little bit of a hint of maple syrup but I fucking hate
beer man. I don't know why I buy beer. Every time I'm just like maybe I'll enjoy this one,
maybe I'll enjoy this one. I don't, I don't like the taste of beer. People give Coors
Light and Budweiser a bunch of shit because it tastes like water but like at least water
tastes good. You know what I mean? It's probably blasphemy to like lots of beer enthusiasts.
The maple syrup, it's very very subtle. It's very subtle but it does a little bit to kind
of like take the edge off that like piss and barf taste that is beer. So yeah, I'll give
it, I'll give it that. I will give it that. It is a beer but it's one of the less offensive
stronger beers that I've had. What can I say? I'm a Roman vodka guy. Wait, shit. I forgot.
I'm gonna like insert this into the beginning. Reminder to self. Insert this before I start
talking. If you want to help support the Wine Fund you can go to the PayPal link in the description
and donate wine, money for wine. You can tell me what to talk about and what wine you would
like me to drink. I will do my best to find it. I have a local liquor store up the road
for me. They have a pretty decent selection but I am in the middle of nowhere so if not
I'll do, I'll get the closest to what I can because the guy there is pretty good and he
knows I don't know shit about wine so if I have questions he usually just takes pity
on me. So that's, then do that. Suggestions are cool otherwise you just get noodley videos
like the one I just made that you're about to listen to. Okay. So today we're gonna be
talking about, I don't know, I guess we're gonna be talking about making shit. Making
shit online and why I'm frustrated with it and just venting some of my personal frustrations
and thought processes behind making stuff in terms of just my personal development trying
to build a personal brand and also intermixing my personal brand with the PCP and the effects
that it has had and how I feel it's working and it's not working. So that's what we're
gonna dive into today. So I don't think a lot of people who are listening to this, who
listen to the PCP either know that I make things or give a shit and that's not an accusation,
it's just an observation. It's something I've always been very curious about and not just
me. One of the interesting things that I've always tried to observe from behind the scenes
about doing the PCP is like where do these people come from? What are they interested
in? Why are they here? And what happens when like a DigiBro fan finds the PCP? What do
they do from that point? Do they look into everybody else? Do they just kind of listen
to the podcast and that's it? Do they even stay on the podcast in general or do they
just listen to ones with Digi in it? And the same thing with anybody else, like if I bring
someone to the PCP, are they just gonna listen to episodes that I'm in? Are they gonna ignore
it all together or are they gonna explore the other members? You know, because there's
this core group of people in the PCP who listen to it that have been following all of us since
the horseshoe days. And I think that makes up the core audience, but we've been growing
substantially since the beginning. For the most part, there's been a general upward trend
since the start. So there has to be at some point since no one's doing horse shit anymore,
that there's an audience trickling in that has no idea about any of our backgrounds.
I would assume the bulk of them are probably coming from firstly Digi. There was a phase
where there was monkey and Nate's getting pretty big now too. So there's definitely
and since Nate's the showrunner, the frontrunner of the PCP, I'm assuming a lot of the PCB
audience has to be coming from him. But where do they come from? Where do they go? Where
do the fans go, bro? That's always something that's intrigued me. And there's really no
way to track it. There's no hard data on it. There's no way to really know. Because none
of us really make posts that say, hey, here's a new PCP episode, go check it out. So we can
go into the YouTube analytics and track where viewership is coming from. It just kind of
happens. And that's something that's always intrigued me. So I've always wondered, like,
what do people see? Like, how am I perceived externally? Right? That's kind of interesting.
Because I have, obviously, we all have limited perspective on ourselves. We're not going
to have some more maple stout. Hold on a second. I want to say it's grown on me, but it really
is. How am I perceived externally? What is my persona being projected outward? Because
I can observe the persona and the image of everybody else in the group, but I can't
observe my own, because I'm too connected to it, you know? And the reason I'm interested
in that other than just general curiosity, because like, the internet in general fascinates
me and how it grows and things of all that stuff like that. But also, I want obviously
like one of the benefits of doing the PCP, there's like three benefits, right? The first
is like I get to hang out with people that like that's that's the first one. The second
one is I make some money, which is also very important. And the third one is that it can
help bolster my personal projects, right? So that's like the three benefits to everybody,
like we all get to hang out because we don't get to do that much otherwise. We all make
a bit of coin, which is handy and brings us to our long term goal of not having to be
slaves to the man. And then also like we can use each other's audiences that we bring in
to build our own brands. My personal brand kind of sucks. And I feel like because it's
constantly been in this amorphous shifting thing, whereas everybody else is very much
kind of concretely decided what their personal brand is going to be, that my personal brand
and my brand recognition and even people understanding what I do and if I do anything
has been lost. And I don't blame anybody but myself for that because I've been in a long
transitional period because everybody in the PCP, the exception maybe of of of of Gibb,
and then obviously Mage, because Mage doesn't do much with YouTube other than posting her
animations and like Gibb kind of like, does you want to be the art boy who wants to be
the YouTube? Everybody else is very firmly in the YouTuber camp. And you know what, I even,
I take that back. It goes there very much in the YouTuber camp, like at this point.
So everybody kind of like settled on, I'm going to be the YouTuber. I'm going to do this gimmick.
You know, Nate had the best guy ever. Digi is Digi and pivoted to anime. You know,
so everybody kind of did their shit. They've been locked in their shit. And even Ben,
who's not really on YouTube, was locked into shit. He's doing the Vapors and Champion.
I have been floating around in space for ever since 2015 when I stopped doing MLP. I was like,
what am I going to do? I'm going to try writing. Guess not. I'm going to try drawing and comicking.
Guess not. I'm going to try doing this Rebel Pixels thing and try and like review art things and
talk about art just because I like being an artist and that whole field interests me and like
entrepreneurship. Maybe I'll try starting an email marketing business. I don't really think this is
as hype as all the people making money off of selling courses or online email marketing is
really selling out to me. So now I'm in 3D and I don't think anybody even really knows on the PCP
that I do 3D because I just looked at like some of the past PCP episodes and they're all linking to
my old channel that's dead and I don't even use anymore. And there are people in the comments
saying like, well, the only reason Tom's on the PCP is because like he knows these people.
And if he didn't already know them, like they wouldn't give him the time of day and they're
right. I don't care what anybody says. They're right. But what I want to do is I want to understand
what how my personal brand is being perceived and then fix it so I can more accurately explain
who I am, what I do and why anyone should care. And I guess maybe that's partially the point of
doing this episode on this topic is to be like, Hey guys, for all like 300 people who listen to this
that care about my personality enough, ironically, probably the 300 people who already know exactly
where I'm at what I'm doing. But just in case there's a little bit of a little bit of dipping in a
little bit of crossing over a little bit of influx, you know, whatever. I'm a 3d boy now.
I've been that since last year. And the beginning of the last year around February is when I started
really focusing solely on doing 3d. I run a blog, polystation2.com, like PlayStation 2,
but Polly's because Polly gods, that's the idea. And the just behind the blog and the website
go to polystation2.com I bought the domain is that it's trying to like capture the aesthetic
of like PlayStation two games, and like, mostly doing fan art stuff right now to kind of build
the brand and like get people interested in it. But that's what I do. Like a lot of people, I guess,
I don't want to say a lot of people, but like, I look through all the comments on the PCP,
I try and respond because I think this will probably be a topic in a future wide chamber. I
think we're pretty bad at interacting with audience a lot of the times. I think that's a huge
problem with the PCP in general, is that this kind of meme of like cometer rules is like somehow
amorphed and evolved into like actual disdain for the audience. So I think it's a huge mistake.
That'll be next week's wide chamber. I'll probably get more into that. But because of that,
I try and like, be someone who tries to interact with audience and stuff just because I enjoy
doing that. Probably more than anybody else. Maybe don't quote me on that. I never talked
to anybody about it. But I feel like I try and be a little bit more active and try and talk to
people and definitely respond to questions and stuff when people have them. Because why the
fuck not? I don't mind. So I forgot what my main point was. I want my personal brand to be understood.
And that's why I was trying to do this podcast. So maybe people who don't understand who I am
and why I'm still here can understand what I'm trying to do and they can decide for themselves
whether it's interesting or not. So that's what I'm doing. I'm doing low poly, PlayStation 2 style,
3D models. Right now, I'm definitely still learning this. I've only been doing it for a
little over a year, probably like 13 months now. No, it's, no, it's, it's beginning March,
just 13 months, 13 months. And that's, that's really my big thing, you know, like Ben has his
comics, Mage has her animation memes, and I'm doing the 3D. But the interesting thing is that,
like, in addition to the 3D models, I've been trying to, like, talk about 3D in an analytical
fashion on my YouTube channel on Tommy Oliver. So if you go to youtube.com slash C slash Tommy
Oliver, link to all is in the description, if I remember. I have, like, analytical videos breaking
down 3D as a medium, because there's a lot of people who talk shit about, like, 3D anime and
stuff, but they don't understand how 3D works. And they're like, Oh, 3D anime looks like garbage,
but they don't know why. They just say it looks wrong. But now that I like know about 3D, I can
explain why it looks wrong, like the technical reasons that things look different. In addition,
I just like exploring the medium of 3D because I'm in learning mode right now, trying to absorb a
bunch of information and figure out how all these things work. So I want to like, explain that to
people. So that's another thing that I do. But the growth has been bad, trying to do that. It
seems that every time I put out one of those videos, I lose subs, I lose, like, 100 to 300
subscribers every time I upload a video. And then if I don't upload for a week, I'll slowly gain
back, like, 50 or so people that upload another video, and then it plummets again. So, like,
it's almost like YouTube is a bad idea. I really like Instagram. I just started using Instagram.
And I know it's like kind of like not cool, like, because we're all like, PCP, art, faggy, kind of
like counter-cultury things. And like Instagram and Facebook are really gay. I don't know anything
about Facebook, but I really like Instagram as a concept, because it lets you separate
your content. Like the interesting thing is like, you know, how Digi has Digibrow. And then you
have Digibrow After Dark, which is like the more casual vlogging kind of content. And then Digibrow,
the main channel is like, this is where all like the serious analytical shit is. Instagram is set up,
even though it's much shorter form content, it's not a replacement for YouTube. But in terms of
like organization, you don't have to make another thing to like vlog about your niche in addition
to doing like main content, because you have Instagram, like the main Instagram, where you post
your photos and your videos and whatnot. And then you have Instagram Stories, which is kind of like
Snapchat. They expire in like a day. And you can like pin like some of the best moments to your
profile, but these don't show up on your main feed. They're separated. So you can do all your
vlog and casual stuff at Instagram Stories. So you can have one account and you can like
document making stuff without cluttering your main feed of content, which I just think is fucking
dope as shit. And I wish everyone did that. Like Patreon just rolled out like I think called Lens,
which is basically Snapchat built into Patreon, which I think is true. But I think Patreon should
be a social networking platform at all. It should be a payment service. And that's it. The whole
social thing makes no sense to me. I've never had anyone really network with me on Patreon. It just
seems like such a dumb idea. They should just focus on their strengths, which is like taking
people's money and giving it to me, or whatever. YouTube has a community tab thing now, which
kind of works in the same way. You can't upload vlogs and stuff. What you could do is you could
upload vlogs on listed and then post them on the community tab. So they show up in your community
tab for people who want to look at it, but they're not going to be in your main feed with all your
like actual content. So I like this idea, especially on Instagram, because like YouTube
community tab is great, but like it's not integrated very well, like nobody really gets
notifications for it. They kind of show up sporadically, whereas Instagram Stories is like
very much a strong understood part of Instagram now. So you could use stories like people get it,
whereas on YouTube, it's not so much with the community tab. It's still a new feature.
My whole thing is like, I want to communicate my brand effectively. And now that I like have a
direction and like 3d is like, this is what we're doing. This is this is the hill we're dying on.
I'm growing slowly, but growing on Instagram. I'm growing on Twitter. I'm growing on Tumblr,
not growing on YouTube. And the YouTube videos, the analytical videos are a technically still kind
of off brand, because I do like tutorials, which is fine. And then I do these anal analysis videos,
which aren't really the same thing. They're tangentially related to the topic of making 3d,
but they're not really the same thing. Like one's a creative thing and one's a commentary thing.
So they feel off brand. And every time I post them, they hurt my channel, not help it. And even
more damningly is that I hate doing the work because I hate video editing. So I'm like,
maybe I should just stop making YouTube videos for the time being and just focus on Instagram,
Tumblr and Twitter where I'm actually growing. I'm actually making progress and I'm actually
able to do work on those platforms that I actually enjoy doing because like I try and take Saturdays
to do video stuff because that's whenever we record PCP. So I'm like, well, I'm already going to not
have I'm going to have a block of time or I'm going to have to record PCP. So I might as well take
this entire day and just shotgun as many videos and stuff that I can, but I never get a lot of
stuff done because making videos sucks. It sucks so bad. Like whether it's technical problems,
whether it's things not working or it's just me being miserable, usually all three things just go
really slowly. And so it never just takes that one day, it takes two days or three days. And then
like half my week is dedicated to doing things that aren't helping my brand grow and make me upset.
Seems kind of stupid. I definitely feel like a pressure to be a YouTuber because everybody
I'm friends with is a YouTuber and YouTube is like the big platform and it's helping everybody
else like become rich, become famous, become successful and like building a really strong
brand and like you listen to anybody who talks about marketing and they're all like,
you've got to be on YouTube. There's no reason not to be on YouTube.
But if YouTube's not working for me, like should I still do it? I don't know. I like Instagram a
lot. I like Twitter a lot, a lot. Twitter is like my favorite social media platform.
Super fucking fun. I don't really know why I like it so much. I just do.
I was thinking maybe taking all these vlog ideas and video essay ideas and just making them regular
essays on medium like maybe I don't know. My whole thing is like personal brand dude. That's
what this episode is going to be. I was actually going to talk about just art, but it's turning
into a branding thing. Personal brand. My personal brand. I want to grow. I want to be a personality.
But that's the interesting thing. And I talked with Mage about this at one point
when we were talking about just PCP stuff in general, because we're both the artists. Ben is
too, but Ben's a bit better at this than me and Mage are. I feel like me and Mage definitely
related to this is that we don't have bombastic personas. We want our artwork to do the speaking
for us. Like I'd rather be behind the scenes making cool shit and the cool shit sells me
instead of me, you know? And like Ben has an interesting personality. So even though he's
doing like the champion and the vapors and they're fucking amazing, like he can he has an
interesting personality just naturally. So like when he talks, like you can get vibes with him
and like he gels off other people really well. Me and Mage less so. Like like I think Mage has
a good personality, but I think she has to like try to like do it. It doesn't come naturally.
Same with me. I have to like sit down like on a pcb episode and like try and project myself and
like try and be a presence and not just fade into the background because that's just my natural state
is like I'd rather just sit down do the work and let what I do define me and not like who I'm acting
like. So I try and do these podcasts to help build a personality because now I don't have any
I'm not competing with anybody else on wide chamber. It's just me. So I don't have like a Nate
Bestman salesman voice that can like hype up anything. I'm just like mumbling and rambling
and getting progressively more buzzed. But I just try and be as real as possible like straight up.
If I have something I want to talk about, even if it's weird or uncomfortable or makes me sound
stupid, I'm just going to let it out anyway because that's the best I know how to communicate
who I am and how I be. So yeah, I just want I want anybody who comes to the PCP from outside
even if they don't like what I do. I want to at least make it clear what it is I do so they can
make that decision for themselves. You know, it's becoming very obvious as I dig through comments
and stuff that nobody knows what I do. I'm not communicating it clearly enough. And obviously
just because I've been jumping back and forth but like I think we're set. We're going we're going
into this year on a year. This is like the longest I've actually sat down actually worked on something
consistently. Medium wise in the last couple years 3D seems to be the thing that's clicking for me.
I enjoy it. I like it. I want to keep doing it. So I want that personal brand to to to become
something that is clearly understood. But it's difficult because I'm not a guy commentating
right. So like if you listen to Nate bitch about stuff on on the PCP like you're basically getting
a little preview of what he does because all he does on best guy ever is bitch about shit or hype
shit up. So when you listen to like Digi or you listen to Gibb or you listen to Nate like you're
just getting a preview of what they do on their channel full time. You listen to me bitch. It has
nothing to do with the content that I actually give a fuck about it. It's like I'm not a part of it.
I'm just a guy behind the scenes pushing vertices and making textures and like saying here don't
look at me. Look at this. Whereas you know Digi Bro is like look at me. I am the product. Whereas
I'm like don't I'm not important. This is look at that. Tell me you like that. Don't tell me you
like me. So and I feel like a lot of the the interest in the PCP is like it's this cult of personality
and people are more interested in in it for the personalities and they don't care as much
for consuming art. They want to consume the personalities like
I think a lot of people are into anime because they like watching the discussion around anime almost
more than they like watching the anime themselves. I think it's I think that is it's not a lot of
people. I think there is like a very dedicated group of people who consider themselves like critics
or pseudo-intellectuals or whatever not to not to disparage anybody because you can like whatever
you want. But I'm saying there is like a group of people I think who watch anime as a prerequisite
to be a part of the discussion of the criticism of anime. And I don't know if that's the PCP
audience because I don't know what anybody does. I don't have enough time to like invest in everyone's
personal profiles or whatever to figure it out. It's kind of creepy if I did.
I uh I don't know. I make 3D models. Please pay attention to me. That's that's like the underpinning
cry for attention at this podcast really is. It's that I feel like I get lost in the shuffle
because I've been so disparate and lacking focus and now that I have it it's like too late
for people to understand. It's like I gotta go back to like all 90 something episodes of PCP
and change all the links probably like to my Instagram or my Twitter so people can see the
artwork I'm doing as opposed to like a YouTube channel that doesn't communicate it very effectively
and I don't think is my best work anyway. Oh oh god oh building things online is hard when you're
not an extroverted confident person. It's very hard guys let me let me tell you. Keeping up
keeping up with these guys who who who feel like their shit is the shit when you feel like your
shit is shit. Oh boy it's it's tough it's it's a tricky. There's definitely jostling in every
PCP episode like man I gotta be able to say my fucking piece. I gotta be able to say something
witty but I'm not a funny guy. I don't my jokes are very reactionary. You can tell me sit down
and be like Tom tell a joke. I'd be like fuck not funny. I'm not entertaining. 99% of my life
is like sitting behind a laptop screen clicking and that's what I do and I hope the fruits of those
clickings take me somewhere and give me something. Oh what was the point? I don't remember what the
point was. Let me drink more beer. I had so much fucking rum last night and I didn't even get bugs.
I was so upset. I just wanted the pain of editing to go away and it did.
Um this is like the worst wine chamber yet I feel. Usually when I do a wine chamber I have
like a one specific point I want to hammer away at and then I'm good. This one felt way more all over
the place because I'm talking about myself and again this kind of goes back into what I was just
saying. I don't have that extroverted personality so when I have to talk about myself I fall apart
because like I'm boring. I don't care. I don't care about me. Just just go to instagram.com
slash polystation 2. You'll understand more about me just by looking through those videos than
then you will listen to all these episodes combined. Like that's what I care about.
That's what I want to be known for. I changed patreon.com slash save me. It's patreon.com
slash polystation 2 because I'm sick of my only person. My personality on the pcp has devolved
into this guy has a miserable shitty life and he's a joke. I don't want to be a miserable shitty joke.
I I freely admit that my situation is not the best but I don't feel sorry for myself. I joke
about being sorry for myself but I think the joke has become my primary defining characteristic.
Let me fucking tell you I don't feel sorry for myself. I made mistakes. I have suffered and
fucked myself over because I don't have confidence in myself and I've let other people make decisions
for me and I fucking put myself in this position but it's my responsibility and my interest in
digging myself out of the shithole and becoming the best person on this podcast becoming the most
successful person making more money than everybody on here because despite the fact that I self
depreciate all the time I think the work that I do is way more interesting than when everybody else
on this fucking podcast does because criticism is gay and making things is by default more valuable
and commentating on things so despite the fact that I kind of mope around and have become this
caricature of myself saying oh woe is me patreon.com so I save me I'm poor and fucked up I still think
that my shit's more interesting and more valuable than anything anybody else does in this goddamn
fucking channel except for mage and ben because they're both doing art too so they're excluded from
that rant but that's the whole thing and munchy investigator come on munchy you promised me you
let me see whips like fucking a month ago and I still haven't seen him I still haven't seen him
okay fuck I don't know why I'm getting more like buzz off of this stout than I did on like
shotgunning rom yesterday maybe I'm just still really tired I don't fucking know dude
I don't want to be I want to have a personal brand I want to like have a good personality and I want
to be known for like my artwork and I'm sick of being a fucking uh sad sorry I don't want anyone
to be sorry for me fuck you if you're sorry for me I don't I don't want to be sorry for me I don't
want anyone else to be sorry for me if you donate to my patreon I want you to be like man patreon.com
slash save me like this guy's got a shitty life I'm gonna give him a dollar because he needs it
more than me no I want you to be like patreon.com slash polystation too this guy is totally zeroing
in on my nostalgia the fucking fos from Hoseki no Kuni designed to look like a PlayStation 2
character straight out of like Xeno Saga that's fucking dope like I'll give you five dollars
you're the coolest that's what I want that's what I want my personal brand to be I don't want to be
the sorry parody of myself fuck that
sometimes I feel shitty because Nate and Digi have more money and more patrons and more all
that shit and more subscribers but I would hate to have subscribers and money for the work that
they do why because I did when I did my little pony and I was miserable and it felt disgusting so
fuck that I don't I don't want to do reviews and there's also why maybe I shouldn't do these analysis
videos on youtube even though I feel like they're more valuable because at least I'm interested
in the subject matter but even if they took off like let's say why 3d anime sucks got like 10
million views today like while I'm recording this and I got a million subscribers all those people
they wouldn't care about polystation 2 they wouldn't care about the animation and the 3d graphics
I'm doing they just want more analysis they probably just want more analysis on anime in general
and I I know so no
I think I think this podcast is over I feel like I'm just rambling now but that
go check out my work that matters understand if you've been confused about my personal brand I
am a 3d artist I'm gonna do lots of cool 3d shit and my personal belief is that the worst piece of
art is more inherently valuable than the best analytical video ever made by by context of the
medium it's in fight me if you want if you want more description on that let me know maybe I'll
do a wine chamber on that opinion but no I don't feel sorry for myself don't feel sorry for me
okay good good bye