Oh my god! We did it! We're back! Max Revive Hyperbolic 1 Chamber! We did it guys! It's
only been fucking 10 million months, but we're back. We did it! Max Revive Tommy Oliver TV.
Go check out the link in the description. I put out six, seven videos in two weeks. Fucking
amazing! Did that and now we're back here for the Hyperbolic Wine Chamber to bitch about
shit! Yes! Today we have a new wine on the wine chamber we haven't had yet. Tis the season
for this wine. We're going basic bitch and basic bro at the same time. Today we are drinking
Captain Morgan's Jackoblast Pumpkin Spiced Rum. Mixed with a little bit of Coca-Cola for
good measure. It's fucking gay and I love it. If you would like to donate to the wine
funds so I can try more wines on the Hyperbolic Wine Chamber, link to my PayPal is in the
description down below. I've also decided to try and make the show more frequent since
I don't know what to bitch about all the time. You can, in addition to sending some money
and suggesting a wine, you can also suggest a topic for me to bitch about. So if there's
something you want to vicariously get off your chest, let me know, send some money, suggest
a wine, suggest a topic and I'll fucking tear it a new asshole. So with that out of the
way, I have no one to recommend or thank for donating this wine. I bought it myself. However,
I still need to give a shout out to someone for this episode and that is going to be Matt
on Twitter at Techtonic Improv because they messaged me about five or so days ago saying
that they were still waiting for my defense of Dungeons and Dragons because if you remember,
resident shitfucker Ben Sainte has constantly shit on Dungeons and Dragons and told everybody
that it's not fun and it's impossible to have fun playing Dungeons and Dragons. When you
know what? He's fucking wrong. D&D is a fantastic game. Tabletop is a fantastic medium and it
shouldn't be shit on by this contrarian motherfucker. It's good shit with an asterisk because Dungeons
and Dragons' biggest strength is also its greatest weakness. It requires people, those
motherfucking shitstains that everybody hates. Yes, people is the key to D&D's appeal and also
the chink in its armor because it makes it difficult to have the game be in an optimal
condition because you have to understand what makes Dungeons and Dragons a good or a bad experience
is entirely dependent upon the people you are playing with. D&D's rulesets, D&D's lore,
D&D's mechanics on its own, not very interesting. Everything is dependent upon the people you're
playing with and how they play the game and most importantly the Dungeon Master and how creative
and interesting they are. Finding a good DM is incredibly difficult, especially in this age
where everyone is fucking used to instant gratification and shit. You got to have somebody
with a little bit, a little bit going on upstairs if you get what I mean. They got to be smart,
they got to be quick, they got to be creative, they got to be able to make shit up on the fly
because the Dungeon Master, despite being probably the biggest barrier to playing something like
D&D as opposed to any other tabletop or board game where you have a bunch of people like,
hey, I want to play the game. You want to play the game? Let's play the game. We sit down at the
table, we open up the box, everybody picks their dude and you start playing the game. You know,
I got a bunch of games like that sitting on my chauffeur behind me like Mage Wars,
portrayal of the house on the hill, even something more simple like Bunchkin. All you got to do,
sit down, play the game. The game basically runs itself and you just do the player part of
the interaction. However, Dungeons & Dragons requires a human on the opposite side of the
spectrum as well. You need someone to be playing the game itself. You know, the game doesn't run
on autopilot and the players just have their interactions. You need the opposition, the
challenge to have a human involved as well. And this makes it very difficult to get into D&D
because finding people want to play D&D is easy. Finding people who want to actually run the campaign
is very difficult. It requires a lot more. However, when you find a good DM, that's where
the magic happens, okay? Because the biggest strength of Dungeons & Dragons and other pen
and paper role playing games is that they break free of the biggest restraint of games in general.
And that is the mechanics and the boundaries of the game itself. Video games are an amazing medium.
Board games are an amazing medium. Games in general is an amazing medium. However,
the biggest problem with things like games is that they limit the tool set available at your
disposal in order to get things done. When you play a video game, you are limited to interacting
with the game to how your character has been pre-assigned to do so. You have a limited move set.
You can only do certain techniques in the game that the developers have given you to use. When
you want to interact with characters in story segments and something like a role playing game,
you have pre-assigned statements that you can use and pre-assigned actions you can take. And
everything has to be done within the boundaries, within the sandbox that the developers have
designed for you because you're interacting with a machine with a scripted preset of options.
And you cannot go beyond those options without breaking the game in some way. If you go beyond
the options, that's usually a glitch. That's usually a mistake. It's something the developers
actively want to prevent you from doing. And the most successful games that feel the most immersive
are when they give you all the options that you can possibly think of wanting to do
because that makes you feel like you have a ton of options available to you. There's two ways
that a traditional game can attack this problem. You want to A, have a world that gives players
options, but at the same time you want to mentally railroad your players as well. You want to put them
in a situation where they feel as if all the options that they would think of are available to
them. And so you put them in a situation where the things they would think of doing are very limited
and then you give them those options. A game type that people never complain like, oh, it feels
limited is something like a fighting game. Because a fighting game is a one-on-one combat system.
And the only thing that you want to do when you sit down and play a fighting game is beat
the shit out of the guy on the other side of the screen. And the game gives you tons of ways of
doing that. So you never really feel like you're starved for options in a fighting game because
the entire game is crafted to only make you want to do one thing. You never play a fighting game
or like, man, I wish I could like talk it out because it's not an option. You know, when you're
in an RPG or something, there are times when you're just like, man, I wish I could have just like
tried a diplomatic option talking to this character. But if the game doesn't give you the option for
diplomacy, you have to engage in combat or you have to do certain things. Or it's like, man,
I wish I could have done a specific moveset, but I can't do any moves with my character
outside of these five or six different branching combo systems that I can earn through the game.
Games are limited. And that's the biggest problem with them. You have to work within their
mechanics. But what makes D&D so amazing, what makes D&D so fantastic is because it is not
constrained in the same way because of the Dungeon Master. The Dungeon Master is a human being.
So because it's not a pre-programmed system, the DM can respond in real time to anything you
can think up. And this is the strength, the magic of D&D and pen and paper role playing,
is that the rules are not set in stone. The mechanics of the game are just a set of suggestions
and you are able to interact with the person. There's an actual person controlling the mechanisms
of the game. And so anything you can think up and do, they can respond to and assign that task
and push that specific idea you have and implement it into the rule structure of the game, because
everything's done around the D20 dice system. So anything you can think up can be assigned a
difficulty on a D20 role or some sort of variation thereof. So you can do anything you want in D&D.
You are not limited by a moveset. You're not limited by mechanics. You're not limited by
anything because you have a human being on the other side working the mechanics of the game
in charge of the system itself, because the system itself has just as much human power
and creativity behind it as the players playing the game, anything can happen. And this is why
the people you play D&D with are essential for having good time. I've played D&D with dumb
motherfuckers and all they want to do is kill shit. All they want to do is run into a dungeon,
roll dice, and slash things. And I'm just asking myself the entire time, why the fuck are we playing
D&D and not something like Dark Souls if you just want to run in a dungeon and slash things?
There's nothing more fun about rolling a dice and slashing something in D&D than there is
slashing something in a video game. A video game is designed to do that, to be a visceral
combat simulation. There's so many games that let you do that. D&D is so much more than that,
and that's why you need good people. You need players who are willing to think outside the box
and treat D&D as a pen and paper game where they can creatively solve problems as opposed to treating
it like a video game on a table where, oh, I'm just going to use my sword because it has plus
three strength and I'm going to roll. And that's what I'm going to do. That's boring. If you're
playing D&D like that, if you're playing D&D with a bunch of people who just want to play a fucking
video game, that's going to suck. And if you're playing with a DM that treats everything very basic,
that's going to suck. To play D&D and have a great time, you need to play with people who
understand the strengths of pen and paper and leverage it by never doing things just by the
book and trying to roll dice and approaching everything boring. You want people who really,
who want to literally role play, who want to become this character, think creatively in situations
and always be trying to do different and interesting things. They never just want to swing a sword or
cast magic missile. No, no, no, no. The people who are going to have a ton of fun playing D&D with
are people who want to start shit just to start shit. All right, I've said this story a couple
times on social media, but my favorite thing I've ever done in D&D is when I played a dragonborn
paladin who was a pacifist. He refused to fight anything because it was at a front to his god.
So I put all of his stats into charisma and diplomacy. All he would do was talk to people
and I gave him all of his beats. I just gave him a fuck ton of languages. And so we're on this
pirate ship or we're on a merchant ship and get attacked by pirates. And so everybody's upstairs
fighting the fucking pirates because that's what the DM wanted us to do. All right. And this is why
you need a good D&D DM as well so they can handle these situations that the person who's DMing can
respond to these creative things. So I said, I don't want to fight them. My guy would never fight.
He's going down into the cargo hold of the ship. He's going to pray. He's going to pray that the
conflict is resolved. And everyone's like pissing me like, what the fuck dude? You're like a big
fucking giant half dragon guy. Come help us fight. I don't have any weapons. I'm just going downstairs
and my guy's going to pray. So he goes down and he starts praying to his god. So the DM gets mad
at me and wants to force my hand into combat. So it's like the pirates breach the hull of the ship
and the cargo hold and a bunch of giant alligators that are in the water around us enter the cargo
hold. They're trying to kill you. They're trying to eat you. They're giant. They can actually eat you.
So if I just approach this as a video game, I'm like, I'm going to get out. I'll bear hand combat
them or I'll, you know, I'll do a perception check to see if I can find a sword or something down
here in the cargo hold. But no, I was like, hmm, I tried to fudge it. I tried to like, how can I
creatively think of a situation out of this that is going to keep me in character? My guy is a diplomat.
He likes to talk. He has an incredibly high charisma bonus and a stupidly high diplomacy check
and he knows a fuck ton of languages and he's part, he's part reptiles. So I'm like, I want to,
I want to, I want to talk to the alligators and they're like, are you fucking retarded? The DM's
like, looks at me like I'm idiot. Like you want to talk to the alligators. I'm like, yeah,
I want to try and talk to them. I know Draconic. I know a bunch of other weird primitive languages.
I'm going to try talking to them and I roll a natural 20 on it. And while everyone flees the
sinking ship on boats, I surf out on a giant fucking alligator who's not my best friend.
That is why D&D is the best fucking game of all time because you could never do something like that
in any other kind of medium. Pen and paper is magical when you have people who think creatively
and you have a dungeon master who is able to entertain those out of the box thoughts and
not only entertains them, but actively encourages them and wants to think creatively too. D&D
is so fucking good when people actually want to have fun with it. When they recognize and
appreciate the strength of pen and paper, the ability to adapt any idea into a gameplay
mechanic and you're not limited by prescripted tools and explore that to the best of your
abilities. Dungeons and Dragons is amazing if you play with the right people and it's so
fucking boring when you play with dumbasses who only treat it like a fucking video game
with no graphics. So find some people who are fun, play D&D, have a good time, drink some Captain
Morgan's Jackoblast, hyperbolic mindchamber out bitch!