Hello there and welcome to another episode of the Hyperbolic Wine Chamber where I train
my ability to complain. I am Tom Oliver and today we are drinking Citizen Cider Unified
Press Traditional Semi-Sweet Apple Cider. This is made locally in Vermont which is pretty
close to where I am here in MassachusettsCitizenCider.com. It's pretty good. I've had a few cans
of it so far. I'm a big fan of hard cider in general. The reason I bought this actually
wasn't because I was in the mood for cider or anything. It was because the graphic design
on the can is really nice. Really good type setting. Yeah, that's what happens when you
go to school for graphic design kids. That's where your purchase influences come from. Good
typography gets you a purchase from me. So yeah, not too sweet, just enough tart to be
pleasant. Good interaction with the palate. I like it. I like it a lot. CitizenCider.com.
If you would like to donate to the Wine Fund and suggest a wine to drink on the show, as
well as a topic to bitch about on the wine chamber, there's a link in the description
to my paypal. I'll also link to my coffee, which is a new thing I have now. So if you
want to buy me a coffee, buy me a drink, you can do that as well. They both have a note
feature so you can drop in what I should look for and what I should talk about. Now, before
we go any further, I wanted to make a quick mention because someone a couple months ago
sent me a wine suggestion and a topic suggestion and I'm not doing them right now. The reason
for that is I don't know if the payment got declined or it was cancelled or something,
it's weird. So I'm not going to use any names, but the guy said to get some passion
pump and if not, just get some box wine and wanted to complain about Windows updates,
which actually I could say a lot about because I had a bunch of problems with Windows updates,
but the status is money received cancelled. So I don't know if it never went through,
the payment never went through or like paypal did something or it's just like you've taken
like 3 months to get to my wine chamber topic, I'm taking my money back, totally understandable,
but just wanted to throw that out there. You know who you are if you're listening to this.
There was a weird issue with that and that's why I haven't gotten the passion pop. Also
the joke of the show is that it's called the wine chamber and I drink everything but wine.
So I'm more than willing to sell myself out and kill the joke entirely for money, but
I'm just letting you know that that's kind of the gist of the show is that it's a play
on words with wine because I'm whining while drinking not wine. There you go. I've explained
the joke, it's no longer a joke, so I guess I can do whatever I want now. But today on
the wine chamber, we're drinking Citizen Cider and we're talking about, I really didn't have
a good way of phrasing this like snappy, maybe I've come up with something better by the
time this goes up and I have a title for this episode, but for now it's going to be diametrically
opposed advice that is convincing on both sides. So I don't know a snappy way to put
that yet, I'm going to workshop it a bit between now and when this gets posted. But the idea
basically is that when we're growing up, we learn things and usually as we grow up, we
kind of internalize the building blocks of like how to actually function in society and
be a semi competent human being and kind of build the baseline skills you need to be actually
functional. There's usually a pretty straightforward path on how to do that. You know, and if
someone tries to deviate you from the path, once you have some general context, it's pretty
self evident that deviating from the path is a bad idea. Let's say you're a little kid
and your parents tell you, don't touch the stove, it'll burn you. I'm not going to touch
the stove. If someone then comes along and says, Hey, touch the stove, it builds character.
Not a very convincing argument. You really don't want to scald your hands. You're going
to be like, No, I'm good on that, dude. Not going to touch the stove. And if you do, you're
going to learn pretty quickly that advice kind of sucked. Like the character doesn't help
your hand heal over the next like two or three weeks. Simple example, but you get the general
idea. There's like a very linear sort of singular progression to building the basic building
blocks you need in order to be a functional human being. But at some point around adolescence,
things start to get kind of convoluted. Multiple paths open up, you can spec into different
options as you were. If you want to get some lead gamer terms in here, right, you can go
in different directions. And that's where things start to get a little bit murky. You
get to specialize, you know, your hobbies, your education, your, your dreams and ambitions
in life. There's tons of different options. I think it gets even worse though, when you're
done with education, because when you're when you're educating yourself and you're going
through the high school system, the college system, the trades school, anything like that,
there is an underlying structure, right? That's why you're paying money, you're putting the
time and that's why the accreditation you earn has merit because there is some sort
of underlying structure that you're working within and the people outside judging you based
on your your acquisition of your diploma or scale or whatever, they know that you were
able to function within the boundaries of those constraints and perform accordingly.
That's kind of where the value of a degree or whatever comes from. But when you try and
decide your life after that when you try and make more abstract decisions, lots of people
offer tons of conflicting advice that all seem basically as good and as relevant as
the next one and they all make compelling arguments. And now it's up to you, someone who has been
on a single trajectory, for the most part, a very structured way of learning a very structured
way of progressing your life and acquiring new skills to discern with no kind of guidance
whatsoever on how the best way is to operate your life. And perhaps this is just me as
someone who is like cursed with analysis paralysis constantly overthinking everything. But the
more I try and learn about how I should function as a human being and how I want to function
as a human being the skills I want to acquire the ways I want to live my life the values
I want to uphold. There are tons of conflicting information out there. And none of them seem
less compelling than the next they all make good cases. And it's up to me to try and figure
out which way I want to go and the only way to really kind of come to a proper conclusion
it seems is trial and error. And that's a pain in the ass. Let me give you an example.
This is probably the most relevant example to me personally in my life that continually
comes up in some way or another because it's a broad subject that can be attacked from different
angles but it really boils down to the same thing. Ambition versus complacency. And that
sounds much more derogatory really when I say it that way than what I mean. To kind
of delve into it a bit more. I am the kind of person that reads self help books. I know
it's kind of sad but that's just kind of where I am in my life and I like reading books
and like listening to audiobooks and that stuff mostly because I have an audible account
and I can't stand listening to fiction in audiobooks. But also because there's a lot
of interesting people. Usually what happens is I'll find someone on YouTube just kind
of browsing YouTube and I get a suggestion and I like find a person who seems really
interesting as a speaker like Gary Vaynerchuk is a good example. And so I read his book
and I bought his book and I'm like oh this is cool. So that's kind of how I find a lot
of these audiobooks that I end up purchasing because I have like these tokens every month
and I'm like what the fuck else am I going to do with it. I'm not going to listen to
Lord of the Rings and have some weird British guy try and voice you know every character.
But I digress. The self help books kind of there's two different schools. There's kind
of like the western business self help of like pulling you up yourself up by your bootstraps
and like attacking everything head on create big goals always be striving to grow more
more more be the biggest best you can be figure out what your goal is and then make it a hundred
times bigger and go for that. There's that one aspect of like constant self improvement
constant growth and constant just like expanding of your abilities and never being satisfied
with where you are. And then on the other hand you have the minimalist kind of Zen I don't
want to say Eastern but I kind of like the Buddhist kind of more like calm Zen mentality
of just like you know get your shit sorted. Understand that nothing is as important as
it's all being told to you to be and kind of try and find some inner tranquility imbalance
carve out a small little niche for yourself. Master that and then learn to be complacent
and maybe I'm complacent but satisfied. It's really being hungry for more versus being
grateful for what you already have and both sides of this equation make really good arguments
right because on the one hand this kind of like growth mentality is avoiding stagnation
and it's about not letting any of your potential go to waste. It's realizing that the human
potential in everybody is massive and you just have to learn to tap into it and be comfortable
going to places you haven't been before being vulnerable and weak and unskilled and powering
through that to reach new heights. And I guess as someone who's entrepreneurially minded
and why I'm doing all the YouTube stuff like I want to tap into that more because I feel
like that's definitely something that's holding me back from getting to a Digibro level of
a success is like really focusing like picking one skill and hammering away that hardcore
over and over and over again and not accepting anything less than the best that I can do
and beyond that and really planning huge and going far beyond anything I've never attempted
to do before and really push hard on that. But on the other hand you know the gratitude
mentality would say that that mentality is dangerous because you're never satisfied.
Even when you accomplish your goals it's short lived and you're just going to keep chasing
the next high for the rest of your life and you'll be chasing these empty accomplishments
where if you come at it from an angle of gratitude you can be thankful for what you have. And when
you grow it's always on top of a stable base like the growth isn't to give your life meaning
it's just something on top of meaning you've already derived from something internal. But
the downside to that is that you're limiting your potential because you're not working
as hard you might have more inner peace you might have more like mental tranquility but
you're inevitably not going to push yourself as hard or go as far as you would if you were
hungry. So it's this kind of mentality I've always struggled with because because I've
been raised in like a Western culture you know in America the first method of like constant
growth and the hunger mentality dominates our culture it's everything in America is bigger
better faster stronger all that shit. So that's the kind of mentality that I've always adopted
and I definitely feel like because of my like mental deficiencies you know my clinical depression
and things like that it makes it very difficult to achieve that because you need to be confident
in yourself you need to be able to take hits and keep going and because I'm just very mentally
up unstable being able to power through things like that is very difficult and that leads
to a lot of my problems that I've had in the last couple years trying to make it as a content
creator. So the allure of trying to like go inward and find this gratitude and this inner
peace of this other sort of mentality is very appealing but I just feel that it would it
would be counterintuitive to what I want to achieve long term I want to be big and this
is the thing like even my idea of being big is like I'd like 100,000 subscribers or something
like that an audience big enough to sustain me financially so I can do what I want to
do but the the growth minded mentality would say that that's thinking too small I need
to be like the biggest youtuber of all time I gotta make millions of dollars I gotta grow
bigger bigger bigger and like I gotta take my 100,000 no no times about 100 you need
10 million 100 million like that's what you need to shoot for and it's just this like
I don't want to say greed but you're tap dancing on the line between ambition and greed by going
for this hardcore and it really needs you to have an ego and I definitely don't have
one so this is just one example but there's tons of other examples in life of like arguments
being made that both seem equally cogent and it really comes down to personal preference
and the problem is when you're somebody who's looking for answers which is how you're going
to run into all these kind of things in the first place you are looking for answers so
when you're presented with multiple choices you're not really in the mindset of like trying
to sift through all these things you're looking for someone to tell you what you need to do
because the whole problem is you don't know what to do so when you're presented with multiple
options that seem good you're kind of just giving yourself a new set of problems as
opposed to finding the solution you were looking for so this is something that's always bothered
me because I'm I have a pension already to be analysis paralysis of just like being overloaded
by choice and they're not making any choice I'm very susceptible to falling into this
trap of being like this is a good idea but this is a good idea but this is a good idea
too so which idea do I want to do and it seems like the only thing I can do is just play musical
chairs with them essentially and keep trying one out and seeing if it works for me or not
but even then like I'm always trying to look for the objective truth and it's arguable
that there is no objective truth but I think in the confines of our reality I think there
are definitely choices that have more merit than others like even if I said you know what
I'm just going to be a gratitude minded like in the back of my head I'm always going to
be like but you could be doing better you could be doing more you could be bigger and vice versa
the other way like if I'm constantly hungry and keep climbing the ladder I'm just like
you could just calm down you know you could take a moment and just kind of like clear
your head a little bit and not be so voracious all the time like just chill so I don't know
that's that's really all I want to say is a short episode but that's what I'm bitching
about is that I just I wish things were simpler I wish maybe if things can't be simpler I wish
we were given more tools growing up to face things like this there because in our inner
education system it feels like to be at least in my experience is that it's very much one answer
you know they give you the answer they prep you for that answer and there's there's a linear
progression in learning things and you know especially in school there's never multiple ways
of doing things it's always like this is the one way regurgitate what we've told you you can't
really come to differing conclusions for the most part and college sometimes you can but even then
it depends on who's teaching the material so in light of not being able to simplify a complicated
world I wish we were better prepared to make complicated choices at least me so that's all
I got for this episode of the hyperbolic wine chamber it's good to be back check the links
below if you want to donate to the wine fund if you want to support me and all my other content
in the long term you go to patreon.com slash save me a dollar a month gets you a bunch of extra
stuff including cool art things and you can rant at me about how dumb I am or whatever so until
next time Tom Oliver this has been the hyperbolic wine chamber have a good one