Greetings, everyone, to a PCP Mini. This is an impulsive, spur-of-the-moments topic that we came up with because we were talking about it so much in the chat and I felt it needed to be hashed out verbally between at least a couple of us.
The subject is, is analysis worth existing? Should we even be doing it? This isn't like a highfalutin, what is the value of the medium like that one podcast we had which was utterly miserably terrible.
This one is specifically about us and whether or not it's something worthwhile for us to pursue in our lives, whether as consumers or as creators of the subject of analysis.
Now if you look at Urban Dictionary, the definition is, uh, anal says that's it. There's no Urban Dictionary on the word analysis, let's move on.
Oh yeah, with me is Nate and Mumkey and Ben and me, The View. No introductions. So anyway, here we go.
Nate, you start with your opinion of analysis. Okay, well, first I'm going to give some context as to why we were having this discussion.
Yeah, okay. It's because our good buddy, Nate, just put up probably the best video of all time where he's doing analysis. According to Reddit, according to Reddit, it's the greatest video.
Nate, is the number one post on r slash anime as of, I guess, last night and this morning?
As of this morning, it had fallen, it's fallen a little bit down now, but it got over 3,200 upboats, so not bad.
And you got like 2,000 subs overnight, which is fucking phenomenal.
I got over 2,000 subs and it's got like around 40,000 views now or so.
So our good buddy, Nate, you know, we're all proud of him because he made a successful analysis video and it's blowing up. But then, oh brother, my brother, gets who comes in to pull the rug out from under.
You know, I felt bad griping, but now that I know how successful it's been, I don't care anymore and I don't feel bad anymore.
You know, you say that, but I feel like if this, I feel like everyone's really jumping the gun on my breakout success a little bit.
This is like one video with like, it's probably, maybe it'll climb to like 50,000 views. That is like not even that good.
Nate, this is Ben, class warfare saint you're talking to. I don't think he's gonna give you much lenience.
Yeah, okay. I shouldn't complain. I'm happy that it's getting the attention that it does.
Well, yeah, so I mean, I'm glad about that. I've got my own feelings about that video in particular, but I'm more interested in, you know, the general subject in hand.
So, like David was saying, when it comes to analysis videos, there are really two ways to think about it from our side of the spectrum.
The autism spectrum. And so there's like the, first of all, like the, I guess like the value as art pieces, or I would call like the societal value of like creating something like that to begin with.
And then there's just like the commercial value, like if you're, if you're gonna be able to survive making that kind of thing.
And there's, there's always going to be a balance between those two things. And so like this video, for example, I feel like it's the funny thing about it is it's very similar to other videos I've made.
Like it really reminds me of the one punch man one, and that video did did pretty well actually.
But like the way that I branded this one was different and was like a little bit more skewed to like what I've come to understand as like the YouTube success formula, which is just like thumbnail, just a big picture of Galco's face.
It's like my favorite frame from the whole thing. And then the name of the thing, you know, the name is like, it's like a thought like understand, I'm forgetting what it was like something about defying, defying stereotypes.
Yes, in oh shit, the Galco Chan. Yeah, that that's right.
So the love progressive shit like that.
They do, even though it's really not a very progressive message, I guess it kind of is whatever. It doesn't matter.
But the point is, like, there is no more intellectual content. If you put like that more kind of marketing angle to it, like my instinct would have been just to call it like best anime ever.
Oh shit, a Galco Chan, because I think about doing these things as like episodes in my like TV show that is best anime ever or like, you know, the best blank ever, whatever the series.
That's how I think about it. But like with the way things are going, that just doesn't work right now.
So in this particular case, I didn't have to actually like really think about how to like change the content of the video so as to like, you know, be most rewarded on YouTube.
You can always put it out there with a YouTubey name, let it get that initial view surge and then just change it later.
That's true. I mean, I've actually been pretty comfortable with the way this is named. I don't really mind it at all.
I kind of like leading with like, I like leading with the idea that's going to be presented in there and you know, that's totally fine.
But I do feel resistance like going back and changing old video names, like the one punch man change to Saitama's a big fuckboy. I don't know, it doesn't matter.
Yeah.
Well, it's not wrong.
But you know, but like I do think that when I, because you know, like to me, the most important thing about making a video is like having the idea of what you're going to make in the first place.
And really, that's where like, you know, that's where like the big decisions are made, at least for me.
So I mean, I was happy to make this Galco video because it is like perfectly fit for YouTube. It's just over 10 minutes long, which means I could put an ad at the end of the video.
So I was totally aware of that fact while making it.
And you know, like the fact that I made this and didn't work on one of the many other projects that I've got, you know, just like written and waiting to go, you know, like the, it's, it's just like,
it's the framing, it's that, you know, like the commercialization and the ability to survive and to make money.
Like that did control to some extent, like what I chose to make as this current product, as opposed to, you know, like another, like I'd love to make like a big analysis of, you know, like Lucifer and the Biscuit Hammer, you know, like as like a sequel to the thing.
But I'm not going to do that anytime soon, because it's not as viable.
I don't, I don't my, my interest in the concept of an analysis or even a review is at like an all time low right now.
Maybe not all time, but certainly has gone down consistently for like the last six months after like me being really obsessed with it for like two years.
And now my default reaction to any analysis is just who cares, you know, like, like any video that is a review, it's like a steep uphill battle on its part to get me to go and wow, this is valid.
You know, I've, you know, I've become very like burned out.
And I feel like I've heard of all the things, you know, like, yeah.
Do you think that you're burned out because you spend hours each week editing these types of videos for digital?
Yeah, I do believe that isn't, you know, the insiderness of it is absolutely that, you know, I'm in the looking at my sub feed right now.
It's like, do stories ruin spoilers?
Super bunny high patch wolf.
I'm just like, like, I don't know, do I want to know?
Maybe it would be best if I just never, if I just go the rest of my life, never know.
You know what that video is going to be before you even watch it.
It's going to be him.
It's going to, he's going to go on a long thing.
Most of it will be superfluous.
Maybe there'll be some jokes or something.
And the point will be that you can enjoy a thing even if you're spoiled on it, uh, rewatches, uh, da, da, da, da.
It's all, it's all shit we've heard before.
I'm right with you, I'm right with you, Davoo.
I feel like, I feel like I've heard everything and I feel like it's so fucking rare.
It's so fucking rare for someone on YouTube to say a thing that I've never heard before and it just makes me feel, just makes me feel like what's the point, you know?
Okay, let me, let me, I, I've got to watch videos anymore.
This is something I've been thinking about for a while now and it's that, uh, that we are in fact no longer the target audience for YouTube, including the content we make.
Indeed.
The target audience is like, people new to analysis and new to YouTube.
Like, at this point, like, I, I'm not going to say the name, but I'm, I'm reading a book that is about a lot of the stuff that I think about, like as a consequence of all the anime I've consumed.
The fountain.
And I, no, that one, that one's in the can, my friend.
Um, no, uh.
The autism spectrum diagnosis booklet.
Basically, yeah.
The Triflors by Monkey Jones.
Yeah, you guessed it buddy, you guessed it.
That is literally sitting on my desk right in front of me right now.
Um.
Do you use it as a poster?
Actually, it is a, it is my little cloud from Kingdom Hearts.
Uh, he's sitting on it.
So it's his little table.
Oh, that's cute.
Isn't that cute?
He loves, he loves that thing.
I'm glad it was put to some use in the, in the Nate household.
It's there to remind me to read it as soon as I have a free moment.
Now you already bought it.
I don't care if you read it.
Exactly.
I just wanted to do five bucks.
You got it, dude.
Uh, where was I going with that?
Oh, like, yeah.
I was just saying that I feel like for guys like us, we're kind of, yeah.
Like, like Ben was saying, I also feel like I am, I basically learned everything there
was to learn.
Like what did these YouTubers, like what is their skill set that they have like delved
into and like cultivated on YouTube?
Like, you know, right?
That is the thing.
There's nothing.
There's literally nothing separating a YouTuber from, from me.
There's nothing there.
There's one thing Ben, there's one crucial thing and it is editing ability.
It is editing ability.
That's the only thing.
Well, that's what puts, that's what puts people like Captain Christian over the top.
Captain Christian is the absolute fucking nadir of human civilization.
Oh, well, he's just, he's just very...
Captain Christian just fucking typifies everything that is wrong.
Yeah.
Which is that you can just regurgitate, you can just regurgitate information, dress it
up in like a pleasing way, just tell people what they already know they want to hear.
And fucking put a little fucking editing stank on it.
And they will, and, and the people will think it's genius.
The people will think it's genius because they're being validated.
They'll think you're a fucking prophet because, oh my God.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
That's true too, man.
Why'd you have to bring up Captain Christian?
That, that's what he had to.
I'm already fucking angry enough already.
Yeah.
I, yeah.
I, I, I hate his success.
I am angry how, how successful he is.
Well, okay.
So, you know, my, my whole time on the internet over the past many years, you know, has been
discovering different practices, different disciplines, different mediums, right?
So around the mid-2000s, that's when I sort of discovered the idea of reviews as this
thing, you know, like, like, I see a review and I'm like, wow, you're, you're looking
at a piece of work and then you're talking about it and summarizing it.
And that concept alone fascinated me for a number of years, right?
Then slowly over the course of time, I start to understand this idea of analysis as distinct
from a review, which is a critical thought exercise.
So finally, for the first time in a number of years, I was, I was revitalized in a new
practice, a new, a new, a new technique, a new skill to try to develop.
And that was like five years ago now.
It would have been like 2012 when I first got introduced to this idea of analysis as
distinct from reviews.
And I feel like once you basically like dwell and meditate on Mr. B tongue for like a straight
six months as I once did, you've basically hit maximum critical, you've hit critical
mass with critical thoughts.
And so from then, what I've been pursuing since then is just people who have different
life experiences and different, different banks of information to go to, you know,
which is what has made a Digi's content still pretty valuable is by having this wealth
of shit that he's watched.
But then, but then recently I was walking around the streets of Atlanta with Digi and
some old commenter of his who I believe has seen more anime than he does than he ever
has, just shitting on all of Digi's opinions constantly by inciting just like every single
time he wanted to justify any opinion, he just name drops like 17 old robot shows to back
up his argument.
And I'm like, this guy needs to make videos.
This guy has a totally different world view.
Me and Digi are both like, dude, please make videos.
And he's like, I don't want to make videos.
That would be a waste of life.
And I'm like, what, what, what, no, no.
That guy knows exactly what's up.
That guy, I'm way on board with that guy.
I think he does.
Let's, I'm going to fucking, I'm going to date that boy.
We both looked at each other.
Me and Digi and we were like, wait, there's something you could do with your life other
than make analysis videos.
Yeah.
So I've been like in a weirdly unique position with analysis and that I've gotten to like
be on the receiving end of producing it without having to actually write any of it, which is
sort of the easiest possible way.
So, you know, and I still get the satisfaction of transmitting analytical ideas because I
kind of have to like reinterpret them in order to create a visual, you know, a visual of
it.
Right.
But without having to actually like go set on a rock for five days as Digi does to come
up with ideas.
Because coming up with ideas is fucking impossible.
DeVoo, I think last month you made a video that has stuck with me and I've been thinking
about it a lot called YouTube is stomach acid.
I think is what you called it.
Yeah.
And it's very relevant to what we're saying because I think your main idea there was that
on YouTube there aren't really any original things.
Nobody's really making original content.
They're just talking about other content that already exists.
And that's a problem with reviews and analysis.
Guys, what if Mario was racist?
Just imagine.
Okay.
Several levels below like analytical critique there is game theory, which is what you're
talking about there.
Well, yeah.
I don't know.
I think there's something to the idea of like presenting an alternate interpretation.
Right.
That can be food for thought.
I suppose that's true.
I don't think Jesse's Mario was the one though.
Maybe not.
Ben, isn't that what Nate did in his newest video that you were kind of...
No.
I don't think it is.
I feel like what was explained in that video is all explicit to the text of Galcochan.
Okay.
Here's the feeling that I got watching that video and it's a feeling that I've had with
lots of other videos is that like the...
What's good about that video is that it just like...
I don't know.
What's good about Galcochan and just like kind of packages all the like the positive
message or whatever and like delivers it in this kind of nugget without earning it.
Like they had to earn it by making the fucking show in the first place.
Oh man, that reminds me of Digi's video.
Digi's video.
He has a vlog from like I think two years ago where he's comparing analysis to vapor
wave where you literally just take exactly what you're basing yourself off of and then
just slow it down and then loop it and then add the Windows 95 startup sound effect.
I will happily admit that my favorite thing about that video by far...
I like that it is spreading awareness about Galcochan.
Which is a show I really, really like.
That's good.
I would feel better if I thought that people were going to watch that video and be like
hey, sounds like a cool show that I'll like and then go watch it.
But I don't get that.
A bunch of people did.
I got a bunch of people saying that.
I get the feeling that the video is appreciated on its own merits and here I fucking go.
Here's my point.
Like the video's merits are not its own.
They're merits of the show.
I will happily admit that my favorite thing about that video, which was always the same
before, is that I got to recreate the final pointing scene from The Breakfast Club, which
is the whole point.
That's what I wanted to do.
That commenter who asked that, yes, you're right.
That was my goal and I did it.
I know you were sending me footage and screenshots and asking me about, I know you were really
putting effort into replicating it perfectly.
Can I just take this moment to tell the tale since the topic has come up.
I worked for literally weeks to get that shot right because I work alone because I have
no friends and I had to set up the camera by myself.
I had to figure out the right camera placement.
Turns out it's got to be really low to the ground and even mine wasn't low enough.
And your viewfinder doesn't flip around either.
My viewfinder does not flip around.
So I had to do takes and I couldn't even review the footage because the resolution is too bad.
I can't tell if it's in focus or not.
I had to do my takes, go home and review the footage, find out if I focused right.
And then the sun had to be in the right position.
Oh, it was a big thing.
It took me four separate trips to that fucking field.
So Ben.
In addition to scouting around four locations at which to film it.
This is a big thing.
But Ben.
I have a way to phrase I think what you're getting at and I think I feel exactly the same
way is that analysis videos often serve as a cheat to get the themes and morals of a
story without having to consume the actual work.
It's like reading cliff notes and it gives you the sensation of watching these experiences.
But we're moving like the nutrition of them.
You know what I'm saying?
And like the moment where this finally started to sink in for me was when I saw fucking reaction
videos on crunchy roll, like crunchy roll on its front page where it has a little flip
through the main featured articles thing or main featured shows.
Half of them are episodes, you know, like watch fucking Super Whale God know everybody
that buddy episode five, but then also watch some white blonde woman react to some other
episode of something else.
I'm like, wait a second, why are reaction videos on the website that's supposed to have
the thing that you react to?
And it's because no one wants to watch anything anymore.
No one wants to have the attention span.
Yeah, I mean, I mean, that's a bit of an overstate.
It's not that there's not enough people.
I know that there's people that watch an analysis video of a show will digest it, feel that they
have like understood the show and then not watch it because I do that all the time.
And I don't like that about myself, but I can't fucking go watch everything.
Damn shame that YouTube gets so many more views because it's YouTube and it's so easy
to watch where it's like actual art takes more time and patience.
And I feel like if all the analysis in the universe just disappeared forever and was disallowed
from returning, then, you know, a bunch of people would just take more time out of their
day to find stuff.
Okay, guys, well, let me let me ask you this and I'm serious about this.
Nate, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to beat up on you.
I don't want it to come across as too mean spirited.
No, I don't feel like you're being that way.
Yeah, I think it's really, Bennett, it was distasteful that you would be so aggressive
towards another PCP member and always talk shit about them.
I don't know why you would do that.
It was unforgivable and I will pitch myself off of the nearest bridge.
I'm sorry.
So you're talking about you're talking about like distilling down.
No, I won't.
I won't apologize.
I'll just kill myself.
That's acceptable.
So you're talking about distilling like the core, I guess, ideas behind a show and, you
know, presenting them in an analysis video as kind of, you know, like cheating to get
the, the nuggety center out and not having to like put in the work to consume the piece
of art.
But okay, now this is going to sound a little crazy, but maybe that's better.
Like it's a more efficient way to consume the idea of, you know, like the work in question.
So what are you losing?
What is being lost?
I'm not saying that it has that there's no merit to it at all.
I just, it's just, it's just cheap, you know, it's just cheap.
I think it's helpful because like DeVu brought up Cliff Notes.
I was an English major in college and I mean in high school as well.
I use Spark Notes for most of my assignments.
I'm not, I don't have time to read all that shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's extremely valuable in a case of videos that I've watched in my life.
Old, shitty, terrible games are the best example.
Like when you watch, I recently watched Aqua Lung Game Reviews, the Chuck Norris game on
Atari 2600.
The fascinating mechanics on that thing would have been a miserable weekend if I tried to
find that out for myself.
So yeah, definitely.
If you Cliff Note responsibly, it could do you great.
Like I think, like, I guess I think that like discussing art is a worthwhile thing to do,
I guess.
And like an analysis video is just like a form of discussion of a work of art.
And I think that that is all fine and dandy.
But I do think, I mean, I guess I will say that like, I don't know, people build their
careers and their fucking internet presences around like talking about other art and it's
just like, you know, it's just fan art and it just feels like, it just feels like they're,
you know, they're just kind of stepping into that other things limelight and grabbing it,
grabbing as much of a piece as they can.
The metaphor that Mumki was referring to that I came up with, YouTube is stomach acid.
The idea is that all the stuff you watch and read is like food and then the analysis you
watch of it and the discussions you have about it is like digesting it, which is very important,
you know, to come to an understanding of what you've consumed.
But what I'm concerned about is when people get stuck in a loop of just digesting and
digesting and then they become malnutritioned and die.
And that's what I'm concerned about on behalf of like, whenever I see people who are like
PCP fans and seem to keep up with everyone in the PCP, I'm like, how do you have time
for anything else?
Yeah.
That's a good point.
We put out a lot of shit.
Yeah.
So, you know, I feel like, I feel like, I feel like a lot of this comes down for me to
to goals and plans and how they've shifted over time because I became...
Let me touch on that PCP thing.
Yeah.
Like the PCP is a great example.
Like, you know, we have a small but really like dedicated kind of like cult fan base
and for them, for a lot of them, it's like...
It's not inaccurate.
Like we're making art.
Some of our art is about other art, whatever.
That's all fine.
But like, to a lot of them, the...
To a lot of them, like the PCP, like the object of interest is the PCP itself.
But like, we're not here.
We're not here like, you know, like what we're doing, like we're trying to make other stuff.
But like that...
I feel like to a lot of people, this is getting into my fucking shit right now.
To a lot of people, like the stuff that the PCP makes is less important than the PCP
itself and that is like a real ugly thing and it makes me feel bad.
It leaves a real bad taste in my mouth.
I don't...
I haven't been keeping up with anybody's...
Anybody's work, including Digi.
Like pretty much the only Digi stuff I consistently watch is the stuff I work on now.
Yeah, I can't...
I can't follow like anyone, I don't know, I'll watch like occasional stuff.
Well, just to...
I mean, what the PCP is, is...
I mean, and it's kind of been talked about this way the whole time.
You know, it's like a bunch of friends talking about stuff, like debating, you know, ideas
or whatever.
Yeah, I certainly hope that what people would primarily do is like discuss the ideas that
are presented, but like, you know, a lot of it is comedy and joke it around and it's only
natural that like the personalities of the people involved would be a primary focus of
what people discuss.
Well, you know, my favorite podcast is the Digi...
It's not a philosophy show specifically, like where we're like, okay, today we're bringing
in like this idea, we're going to talk about it specifically, like it is a comedy show
at its heart.
My favorite podcast is the Digi show and I love his personality and I love the personality
of Sean and a couple of other of his regular guests and I love that show.
But when he talks about the fans and the viewership and like the communities of sprung up around
him, it's just like the whole PCP community stuff, but like significantly larger.
There's the Facebook group and the Reddit group and there's like drama going on within
the different groups of the fandom of this show where the whole concept is just one guy
and a couple of friends and I'm like, I get the impression there's a lot of people for
whom their whole life is being fans of that show, whereas it should only be the host's
full-time life.
Dustin Isanova, that is definitely his whole life.
And I just like, I have a, you know, for me, it's like this, the world is like a giant
game of Minecraft, the world of art, right?
The media out there, especially after the internet, is infinite resources.
You could just find some random niche that is a subset of a subset of a subset of some
other niche and spend your entire life dedicating yourself to the study and honing of that tiny
little corner of the world, of culture, right?
And there are so many stories that you can tell.
You basically can weave your own narrative of life about what you experience, right?
The favorite one I've heard in a while is Munchy explaining his story with Parkour
Dude91, where it's like, this is an incredible little, tiny little, weird little story that
Munchy happened to be there to witness all of, and he got to relate that to others.
And that for me is like a divine, beautiful thing that he experienced.
And for me, I feel like I have a responsibility, especially as someone with a microphone that
a few people will listen to, you know, just a humble little content creator like myself
that people are gonna like, you know, take some inspiration from maybe, that I should have
an interesting story of like, hey guys, today I went to this random website and discovered
this random little thing.
I don't like the idea of like just sort of being carried along by the current of like
whatever feels convenient to click on from day to day.
I don't like it when I hear from people who spend 75% of their time just experiencing
what happens to be in their Facebook feed, right?
Where they're just carried along by the current, by the tide of wherever things take them,
rather than like trying to go out and find their own.
You're never gonna watch everything.
You're never gonna consume even the tiniest fraction of anything.
And when I feel like people are just stuck in some sort of full time routine that isn't interesting,
I feel sad and offended for them.
I feel like they're wasting their life.
And I feel like this is a problem.
Man, I agree.
I agree.
I feel that because I've been in that loop before.
I've been in that fucking cycle.
And yeah, it's terrible.
This reminds me of something.
Just to go back a little bit to what Ben had said before about, you know,
I think it was Ben, about people being obsessed and like fixating on the people
and like in the PCP, they're more focused on us as opposed to the ideas.
Like as I said, I'm a little bit more excusing of that.
But what I hate in general is the focus on like the people on YouTube at large.
Like the fixation on characters.
Yeah.
You know, I...
What do you mean?
Well, it's this idea, right?
It's this Eleanor Roosevelt quote that I always think about that everybody should know.
Great minds discuss ideas.
Average minds discuss events.
Small minds discuss people.
And I feel like YouTube is far too much of small minds discussing people.
Indeed.
I feel like it's just such a waste of brain power.
That's what YouTube drama is all about.
It's just talking about people.
Yeah, you know what I don't like about YouTube, I guess, is that I always have it in my mind.
I'm always conscious of this hierarchy.
Like I always know that there are people out there with 10 million subscribers
who are like affecting more people.
And I don't like the way it feels like a...
Like it feels like this hierarchy, right?
One thing I liked at first when I got into YouTube was anytime someone commented,
I wish you deserve more subscribers.
And I still like those kinds of comments.
But I felt a little cheated upon when I started seeing in other people's comment sections
who had hundreds of thousands of subs.
I'm like, how do you need more subscribers?
It's because the people who comment that are subbed to people with 10 million subscribers.
True.
And we're all sort of...
We're sort of judged as though we're on like the same plane of existence.
Whereas for me, they're really not.
And I feel like old YouTube, you know, as early as...
It's late as 2007, it still felt like...
It still felt like a bunch of blogs in a way.
It felt more like blog spot.
When you're on like a blog, when you're on WordPress,
you're not conscious of comparing the view counts of this WordPress
to the most famous WordPress, PewDiePres, you could say, right?
But on YouTube, you're always...
Because YouTube is so interconnected,
YouTube always feels like you're on an intersection.
And every four directions, there's another video.
You always know who the popular guys are.
And so it feels like...
It feels more like...
I think just the fact that the view counts is the most prominently displayed statistic.
It always makes you think, oh, but how can you get more popular?
And it makes everyone fixated on how to get more popular and more popular
rather than being content with 125,365 subscribers.
I'm done, you know?
And this ties in, of course, to the whole, you know, like the sort of...
What's the word I'm looking for?
Like the bleaching of content on YouTube.
Like they're trying to clean up their act, you know?
To appeal more to like large...
Yeah, YouTube wants to encourage it.
YouTube is encouraging.
YouTube wants the most viewed videos.
It's all pushing things towards this kind of sanitized...
That's the word I was looking for, sanitized.
Sanitized, you know, like a kind of content
that's sort of further and further away from the kind of like individualized
things that you might have seen, you know, back in the day.
And there's some advantages to that, like the larger reach that you can get
as YouTube gets more and more popular.
But there's disadvantages too.
Yeah.
So, okay.
See, the ultimate thing I wanted to say about analysis is I feel like
it just depends on different needs and plans I have
at different times as years go on.
And this is why I was talking about getting out of loops, right?
Where it used to be the given that I would watch every video
by every analysis channel that I kind of liked, right?
And now I'm so insistent on getting myself out of that loop
that I feel the need to record a whole podcast
just to say that that's what I'm going to do
so that I feel accountable to myself to actually do it.
And I have been doing a good job.
I've barely been watching videos.
I've barely been watching Digi's videos.
I feel like I basically...
It's not like I'm done with analysis forever more.
It's just that I've spent enough time.
I feel like it was like being a monk out in the mountains
and meditating to find my center in regards to the creation of art.
You know, I tried to make a video game back in 2014 and 2013
and I failed miserably.
And so I've spent like three years watching analysis videos
trying to like give it another shot
so I can fail slightly less miserably next time.
And now that I'm basically doing that,
I feel like, okay, I'm basically taking my entire viewership
of Extra Credits and Mr. B-Tongue and internalizing it.
And I'm going to try and use that wisdom as much as possible
and make a video game.
And then when it's done, I'll see how bad it is
and then whoever is the new cool kid in town,
I'll fucking watch his videos and how wrong I was
to make the game that way.
And I'll repeat the cycle anew.
So this really, this video is a PSA for everyone, including me,
to not just be in training all the time.
If you are an artist, I feel like analysis is like training
or it's like finding your center and you just can't do it 24-7.
I strongly, strongly disagree with that sentiment.
Because, I don't know.
Okay, people make, shit tons of people make fucking game
and story analysis and stuff.
And do you find that it comes that so much of what they say
ends up getting repeated,
so much of what they say is shared between them
and they all coalesce into this hive mind
that all has the same opinions about what makes good art,
what makes good games or whatever.
Yeah, that's why you should then stop.
I don't see how that's different from what I said earlier.
I don't see how it's like contradictory.
Oh, Ben, fuck you.
I just don't, I don't think, I don't know,
I don't think you should listen to anyone
about like what your art should be.
I have a question for Davoo and Ben,
since you guys are more on the negative side
of analysis existing as a format.
If somebody in the audience wants to make analysis videos,
would you give them any advice or would you say don't do it?
Is there a right way to do it?
Honestly, unless they had some incredible gimmick
that I'd never heard before, I would say don't do it.
I would say don't do it, yeah.
So would you both tell Digi, like hey,
quit your main channel, let's just do Digi after dark?
No.
No, don't say it, I fucking, that's my job too.
I'm thinking about that one, I'm thinking real hard.
Ben's not the biggest fan of Digi's main content as I recall.
I watch Digi's main content, I don't know, it's fine, whatever.
I mean to be honest, I kind of feel the same way about it.
But if it disappeared, would I cry? No.
Well, I would financially, but like in terms of,
this is what it is, right?
Analysis Digi's channel has become for me like a day job
but in a really, really good way.
Where I get just enough satisfaction out of it
to where when I'm done with it, I'm like man,
that was really worth my time.
But it's not like I'm discovering all new planes of thought,
it's not like I'm like having to radically evolve myself,
which is good because it means that
it doesn't actually take that much of my time to like think about.
I don't have to spend any time meditating trying to figure it out.
Which leaves me with so much space in between
to fulfill my other ideas, which is to make a video game
which takes a whole lot of time.
So basically I'm considering the analysis to be funding
my other artistic ambitions you see.
And when it comes to the fact that I'm...
So for me it's worth it, I think I honestly wonder
how much it's becoming like that for Digi too
because he just dropped a rap music video where I'm like
if he like lost everything and he had to pursue a rap career
he'd probably not have the worst odds at this point
because he's pretty close to like professional now.
So yeah, I don't know.
I mean I think it's a little...
I mean I think whether or not you can fund yourself on your art
is kind of aside from the point of like
whether it's worthwhile as art in the first place.
Like of course all these YouTubers that are all getting sanitized
because that's what gets the clicks.
Like of course they're all doing it that way
because that's what makes the money.
But that's the problem is that it makes it all fucking the same and shitty.
I mean just think about the fact that like all the old animators
nobody makes animations of the level that we used to see
because it just doesn't pay anymore.
That shit is gone by the wayside.
You know what really used to happen on YouTube is
is people... is a paid content on YouTube needs to become regular
and people need to like get used to the idea
that they're gonna drop like 15 cents every time they go on YouTube.
That way animation can come back. That's my theory.
Like I think I am not against...
I'm not against the idea of a creator doing what is popular
or I'm not against the idea of someone doing
working in like a format because that's what works
at that time and place.
I don't think Charles Dickens is a piece of shit
because he wrote fucking serialized shit in like newspaper or whatever.
I don't hold that against him.
That format is what worked at the time
and it's the reason why his stories are the way they are and whatever.
That's all well and good.
But I do take issue with the idea of like deliberately making your content.
When you're not doing it because it's what works
or because it's what you wanted.
It's when you're just making it like everyone else
to like fit into this crowd.
Because when everyone is doing that, then nobody is any good ever.
I don't fucking know.
I like... in 100 years is anyone gonna look back
at any of this analysis content and be impressed?
Is anyone gonna give a shit?
Have we gained anything?
That's a great question and I don't know.
I don't think so.
I mean, not unless it's somehow relevant to some...
Are there any works of criticism that are like really famous historically?
In-defensive policy is pretty up there, but otherwise I can't think of many.
There are some.
The Ghost in the Machine is like a response to Descartes' theories about Cartesian dualism.
It's basically an analysis piece on Descartes.
I guess so.
Here's another way of...
Because every time we formulate what is the problem here,
each one is equally true and also not true.
Here's another reformulation.
It's sort of a huge simultaneous everyone's getting old and running out of ideas effect.
You see a dynamic new pop star or new rocker fucking person
or some other genre of music you like.
Then they make three albums and then they make two albums that aren't as inspired
and then they put out one album that's completely uninspired.
This is sort of happening to a bunch of people simultaneously
because the whole scene was invented sort of around the early 2010s or so.
I'm looking at Mr. Betung's channel right now.
His first video was five years ago.
That video obviously came out about...
He had an idea, he really wanted to explain it
so much that it was worth all the pain in the ass of figuring out
how to use Windows Movie Maker for him.
Back in 2012, that's what basically all of them were for the most part.
It was always like, man, I have these ideas I really want to explain
and so I'm going to make these videos to get my thoughts out there
because otherwise it's going to bug the shit out of me.
The thing about Mr. Betung is that he's the only one I know
who remains exactly that.
He only makes a video when it's something he really wants to bitch at people about
and has never started doing it for the sake of justifying itself.
Which I know is a trap that Tom fell into immediately
with the pony analysis thing where he dropped a couple that he cared about
and now he's like, oh, well, now I need the money
so I'm going to force myself to care about it.
It's the same as a band's first sellout album.
Where they're just doing it for the sake of doing itself.
That's kind of what gets me when the analysis becomes...
Yeah, when it exists just for its own sake.
Or when a channel exists for its own sake.
Or when an artist, when a fucking YouTuber is just putting out shit
and it's just there because you want to see this guy
and it doesn't even matter what he says.
I really hate the whole idea of a cult of personality
that just exists for its own sake
and that's why I've been really resistant to the dick show
and even though I liked him on Biggest Problem
I don't want to fucking watch the dick show
because I don't want to tune in every week
to hear a commercial for how cool dick is.
That's exactly how I felt too,
even though I haven't watched all of Biggest Problem.
It just sounded like that to me.
But there is good news.
I have the solution to this problem
and I don't have the materials on hand just yet
but the solution to all this shit you're talking about
is post-scarcity
because once nobody needs to make any money
like do you think that fucking...
God, I don't know.
Whoever.
Do you think anyone is going to make a shitty YouTube channel
where they review something once they're bored with it?
Honestly?
If they don't need money anymore?
Yes, because if there's no money
people would just do it for the popularity.
Yeah, they'll crave the attention.
But no one will...
I think post-scarcity will get lots of like
suicide on YouTube.
Let me work out the kinks on that.
People will just like upload...
There'll be mass suicide
and people will just upload it onto YouTube
and YouTube won't even take it down
because death doesn't scare anyone anymore.
Hey, you know what?
If there's mass suicide at that point, that's great
because the only people left will be the people
strong enough to survive in that kind of environment
and they'll breed the superior race.
I can't wait for that to happen.
Yup.
Alright, well I guess that's basically the end of that point.
This is a mini episode after all
so we should end at 42 minutes.
Yes?
How...
Can I make one last point before we end?
Absolutely.
Alright.
Okay, and it was just...
You guys...
You, Davoo, we're saying something about...
Like you were talking about music, for example,
and like something about them being...
Like, you know, a band makes an album
and it's inspired.
And then they make another album
And then they make another one
and it's not inspired.
What I wanted to ask about is, like,
what do you mean by inspired?
Like, what...
What is the utility of an inspired album
versus a non-inspired one?
What's the difference there?
Um, is it better?
Why is it better?
Well, it depends on the bands.
Um, but like even...
Just think of any one.
Any example you want.
Even with bands where a lot of their albums
or even if almost all their albums are good.
I mean, like, Steeley Dan is the first example I think of
because I've listened to all their albums a bunch of times.
Well, they're a bad example if they're all good.
Well, the thing is, is that the first album
I do enjoy slightly differently
because each song, like, feels more unique
from every other song in that particular track listing.
Whereas all their other albums,
many of which I might even like more than the first one,
it feels more like they're like this cohesive thing.
Um...
Okay, well hang on.
I understand what you're saying
and that's perfectly fine.
But that's not really what I wanted to ask about.
What I'm sort of asking at is,
like, what is the purpose of a band
that makes a good album?
What is the world's gain?
Finding good music to listen to.
Yeah, what does that do for us?
The music is the point.
So, like, people listen to it and enjoy it and then what?
They live their life better?
Is that it?
No.
No, they just enjoy it.
That's all.
Nate, this is what you're saying is,
this line of reasoning is reductionism
by making it too big of scale.
I don't know.
I think Nate might have a good point.
What if people just enjoy
hearing their opinions regurgitated in an analysis?
Isn't that as valuable as a good album of music?
That's kind of the comparison I wanted to make.
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
God.
Yeah, shit.
Ben, people can like things that you don't like.
Is that the point?
No, no.
I'm saying, oh, no,
because I don't think I can argue against that point.
I finally have one of these.
If you can see that music is valuable
because it makes people happy,
I think you also have to concede that analysis
that makes people happy is equally valuable.
God.
No.
Oh, no.
Unless you're like me,
and you don't see value in music,
and you think the only purpose of that
should be to educate people on better ways
to improve human society.
Well, you know what?
Okay, here.
Objective value.
I do have an analogy.
Parallel to...
Yeah, I just lost.
I need a sporty pig with this.
You can't fucking argue.
That's all, folks.
You can't argue against fun.
You can't argue against what do people like.
Now it just comes down to,
I like it and you don't.
Yeah.
But I really don't like it, though.
Well, we should defer to Ben on this matter.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here's my parallel.
I think about what is the most, you know,
like derivative analysis,
and I think what's the most like derivative music
that I like and why that would be a future funk.
You can just put on the whole playlist.
It doesn't really matter which.
It's all the same,
but I like it always entirely
because it's good to jack off
while playing in the background.
So the question is,
who can I jack off while it plays in the background?
Monkey Jones.
I can't jack off.
So there you go.
That's the ultimate answer.
I don't actually...
I think I missed something.
Okay.
All right.
Hey, let's end this so I can go pee.
That sounds good.
Is there anything else?
Is there anything else to say?
That is all to say.
I'm good.
I feel like we've accomplished nothing here.
Yeah.
Of course we did.
There was no hope.
I honestly think there's going to be a lot of people.
My goal is that there are some people,
some TPC viewers,
who to whom that exact armchair diagnosis I came up with
completely applies to them,
and that this would be something they haven't thought of.
The whole being stuck in a loop
of just watching analysis.
Oh, yeah.
I am so young.
And there are people talking about how they used to...
Even it's been around like a year,
but they used to love the PCP,
but they feel kind of done with it.
Like they've gotten out of it all that they're going to,
and I think that's kind of similar to what you're talking about.
That's like half the members right now.
Are you talking about the members
or are you talking about the audience?
No, no.
I'm talking about the audience.
I'm talking about the audience here,
the members too.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
Well, I think sometimes these things,
these podcasts kind of seem formatted
like we're trying to win,
but that's not it.
Like we're not trying to find the solution.
I think we just had a discussion,
and hopefully we generate more discussion
from the audience in the comments.
We're not here to find the answer,
so I think this was a worthwhile podcast.
The goal is don't get bored.
Don't get bored.
That is the goal.
Sure.
That's the goal of our life.
That's our goal.
And that's your goal viewer.
But why not get bored?
No.
Okay, I'm done.
What's the purpose of...
Nate, this is Nate, Colin.
What's the purpose of boredom?
Starfleet, like everything else.
Starfleet.
It all comes back to Starfleet.
Will there be any boredom post-scarcity?
All roads lead to Starfleet.
Yes.
There will be no boredom post-scarcity.
There will be nothing but boredom post-scarcity.
That's what you think.
That's what half the post-scarcity stories are like.
Humanity will change.
Humanity will change and adapt.
Okay.
We'll get there another day.
For the PCP Mini,
I've been Momkey Jones.
Ben Sane.
Best guy ever, Nate.
Davoo.
Out.
We're...
Goodbye.
So long.
Bye.