Question for our audience. Is the PCP in crowdfunding jail? I'm joined with Best Guy Ever.
Hello everyone.
To discuss whether or not the PCP is in crowdfunding jail. I'm very curious as to what our audience is going to have to say about this, but we're basically going to be presenting a case based on an argument you and I were having all morning.
Yes we were, yes we were. And I really, yeah, honestly what it comes down to is what the people out there think. So we could argue all day, but this is a much better idea to put it out there and let the people judge.
So for starters, what is your concern about the idea that we might be in crowdfunding jail?
Okay, now not to shit on anybody in particular, but so here's the basic concern that some of us have here. And it's that so since the Pleeve and the Weeb was, you know, it was a Digi and Jesse project, of course, obviously, from the start.
But as time went along, the rest of us got involved with it to the degree of, we were basically, we were part of the Kickstarter, you know, there were reward tiers added to get us flown out.
And we each, you know, took the amount of money proportional to what it cost for us to attend. We didn't make any money on top of that and produced content regardless, but we were there and we were involved.
And most of us were on episodes of the Pleeve and the Weeb and maybe people don't even know that, I'm not really sure, but we were involved on that front and eventually when the episodes come out, the people will see that we were involved.
And the concern that we have is that so considering the fact that it's no secret that the Pleeve and the Weeb is taken quite a while to be released and it's, you know, it's been nine months.
Beyond what was anticipated by people.
Yes.
Like, it would be fine if it just took a long time to come out if that was what had been established from the beginning.
Of course.
But the sort of projected schedule was that it would take some six months or so to release the first season.
And it's taken some nine months or so to release one episode.
That's right.
And from what we hear, the next one's around the corner, not too far, but you know, we're not really sure.
We're not really sure.
And so the concern that I and my PCB brothers have is we've been thinking about future possible Kickstarter projects.
You know, we've got a couple of things kicking around.
Redcon 3.
You know, we've got a couple of ideas for things we want to do for that and other stuff.
And, you know, we were just mulling around the idea and then we thought, like, OK, what if we made a Kickstarter and then, you know, it occurred to us that, oh, you know, now that we think about it, the last sort of PCP related Kickstarter has not really delivered what, you know, it's not done.
You know, it hasn't been finished yet.
And so based on that, we were like, is it really, do people really want to hear that the PCP boys are doing another Kickstarter type thing or an Indiegogo or whatever the fuck before that's done?
And so you and I had a disagreement and there's a couple of factors at play as to, you know, if that's true, where the responsibility is, what, you know, different individuals, members owe to the audience and what we can expect people to say.
So what do you think?
What do you think?
Well, I think the way to explore this is, first of all, is the plebe and the weeb Kickstarter a failed Kickstarter?
OK.
If so, to what extent and how to to what extent is that true for the PCP and how much responsibility does the PCP even have?
Right.
The interesting thing is that if you look at it from the lens of the PCP's involvement in the plebe and the weeb, I actually think it comes out like startlingly great because the plebe and the weeb was a Kickstarter.
Like the idea of the Kickstarter was 10 episodes season one, 10 episodes season two of this show.
That is, me and Jesse do a talk show about anime and it's a jokey funny thing. Jesse edits it and posts it and like the real humor of it is basically Jesse's editing.
Like the actual content of the show is just like a pretty shitty review of a show made funny in post editing.
But we wanted to have a Radcon 2.
Radcon 1 was just where all of us flew out to my house and we made a bunch of shit and just so happened that plebe and the weeb was one of the things we made because it was an idea we'd had for years.
With Radcon 2, it was sort of funded by the plebe and the weeb, but we did not just use it for that.
We ended up using Radcon 2 to produce assloads of content.
Very true.
That was completely not even related to the Kickstarter, but made possible by the Kickstarter.
So I think from the perspective of what did PCP fans get out of the plebe and the weeb?
They got a lot without even anticipating it.
That's true.
They got shitload, like hours and hours and hours of let's plays, a lot of which haven't even come out yet.
Several big lecture videos that have been some of the most popular content we've ever made.
If not for the plebe and the weeb Kickstarter, you don't get the Munchy lecture on Parkour due 91.
You don't get the Kingdom Hearts lecture.
You don't get Ben's Sadachu lecture, of course.
That was from the first Radcon.
Oh, was it? Oh, fuck.
Okay, never mind.
But from Radcon 2, yours and Munchy's lectures, we get the Ape Escape playthrough five hours long.
You get the Hanboy Winter War, the PCP wrestling, and then just all the weird shit like Jesse is Digi and hippos, Jesse and all that shit.
Stuff people love.
So you also have all of the background content from the Kickstarter.
If you were a backer of it, you got all the videos of us watching the shows, all the videos.
Now, I realize at this point, I'm starting to sound like I'm defending the lack of the Kickstarter, the actual product.
No, it's still a bad thing.
It's a very bad thing that the product is not out.
However, I'm thinking of this in terms of what it means for the PCP because the plebe and the weeb is a me and Jesse project.
So are me and Jesse in Kickstarter jail?
Definitely.
Okay.
All right.
There you have it, folks.
Is Jesse super in Kickstarter jail?
Absolutely.
Well, don't throw Jesse under the bus.
Well, okay.
I know it's his responsibility.
It's his editing project.
That's true.
I mean, it's my fault, though.
Everything about the plebe and the weeb Kickstarter is my fault because I started it and I managed it.
True.
Though I would argue that everyone is complicit who shared in its warm glow.
There's a lot of reasons that the show hasn't come out yet.
I would say that the biggest reason, sort of at the core of it all, is that I don't think Jesse even knew what I meant.
I said, let's kickstart it.
And he said, that sounds like a good idea.
And then I immediately launched a Kickstarter, which he thought I meant, let's do it eventually someday.
But I was like, I want to get moving on this because we all wanted Radcon 2 to happen sooner than Radcon 1.
Damn right.
So it was basically an excuse to fund Radcon 2 as fast as possible without really considering the amount of work that it was going to be to do the plebe in the weeb season 2.
The fact that all of it was going to end up on him to edit and then like a bunch of disasters happen in his life immediately afterwards.
So it was like a really badly timed thing.
And so it's really my fault for putting it on him in the first place.
It also, in spite of having been a successful Kickstarter, there's not that much money in it.
Most of the money went to the production.
Everybody else, all the PCP members were just flown out.
That's all you guys got out of it.
And the rest of the money, anything that wasn't used for the project.
I'm still holding on to the money that's supposed to be used to ship all these fucking Blu-rays out.
But other than that, all the money was for Jesse for editing.
So I gave it all to him so that he could, because he's fucking his life is in dire straits and he needs the help.
So I was like, here, have all this money to help with his moving shit.
So there's ultimately not much money in it for anybody else.
And the way I see it is I produced this project.
I came in and I essentially hired a director, which is Jesse.
Director slash editor.
And I hired a bunch of actors, which is the rest of the PCP.
And the responsibility of the project being finished is on me for having orchestrated that.
I'm the one who picked everybody involved.
I'm the one who set up a situation that was not ideal for getting this finished in a timely fashion.
Now, the Cleveland the Weeb Kickstarter is not canceled, by the way.
If I'm making it sound that way, we're still working on the Cleveland the Weeb.
Jesse just seems to be working on it at like he he's given up on it coming out in a timely fashion.
He's editing it at his pace, which leaves the question of how does this affect the rest of the PCP?
Does anybody else not get to do a Kickstarter?
Or even as a group like funding a Radcon 3 when the Kickstarter for the last one was pretty clearly a Radcon 2 Kickstarter?
Does this look does this bode poorly for the rest of the PCP?
That's the question.
I would argue it does.
I would argue that it does.
And I think it's because we have a different idea and we're just exploring the issue, right?
Like it would be in my best interest to deny this and to go against it.
But we're explorers of intellectual content.
So here we are, folks.
To me, it seems like when I think about myself, okay, I would never give money to anyone under any circumstances.
But if I was forced to, I was part of a Kickstarter.
Okay, so you raised a couple issues there.
One of the things is that despite the fact that the Kickstarter, you know, the actual product at the core of it all, at the center of the Kickstarter was not delivered,
there's all this other content that came as a result of it.
I couldn't agree more and that's all great and wonderful.
But it is not the thing that was delivered or the thing that was promised.
And it harkens me back to my favorite YouTuber, Anita Sarkeesian, and all the grief that she got for, you know,
back from her original Kickstarter or whatever it was, she developed a presence and made tons of content.
But a lot of people shout on her because they hate women, but also because she was not delivering specifically the product that was promised.
And she distinctly got a lot of flack for it.
You know, whether her true fans were the ones doing that or not, the fact remains that bad press was generated for her
based on that situation.
And I can't help but feel that it's a similar sort of situation in a case like this.
And so the thing that could vindicate us, I think, the PCP as a group, is indeed the fact.
And one of the missions that I feel you are here to do is to separate you and Jesse as the culpable parties responsible for getting it done.
And the rest of us, I mean, we have offered many times to help.
And it's not that we're not wanted, but that's not what the show is, so we can't.
We cannot help.
Well, that's the thing.
That's the way I see it is that the purpose of The Pleeve and the Weeb is that it's me and Jesse's show.
It's a show that I organize and that he edits and sort of makes watchable.
Right.
And the only reason everybody else was involved was because we wanted Radcon 2.
We wanted everybody to be there.
And so the only way that made set like the way I saw it was like, all right, we're raising all this money for the Kickstarter.
We want this Kickstarter to fund everybody to come to one place.
So the only way to justifiably fly them is to say, well, they'll be in an episode.
So everybody who's there is going to be in an episode because that justifies flying them down here for this event.
Whose main purpose is to generate as much content as possible, not just to generate The Pleeve and the Weeb,
but to create all kinds of shit that we can only do in person because, you know, it's just, it's content that can't exist over the Internet.
Without a doubt.
Or would not be as good, you know.
So the way I see it is like the core product is the me and Jesse show.
Everyone else is just kind of incidentally involved as part of something else.
As part of, and I think a lot of the people who backed the Kickstarter just wanted Radcon 2.
I saw that expressed by a lot of people at the time.
I agree.
I know a lot of people who are satisfied with the stuff that's come out or just don't care because we all put out tons of shit anyways.
And it's not like The Pleeve and the Weeb is radically better than all the other stuff we put out.
Well, yeah.
Like the specific product, yes, it is missing and that's a shame, but it's not like we've all gone quiet.
It's not like Spoonie who promised he was going to make a movie and then has literally done nothing.
Like, I think Spoonie would be in better condition if he had promised a movie but was still doing his regular content.
He'd still have a lot of patrons.
I agree.
But, you know, we're in a situation where post-Pleeve and the Weeb, you know, recording is all of us entering our most prolific phases ever.
You've done me a Mephava, we Agua, I've been the human content machine.
Of course.
The only person who's really slowed down has been Jesse because he's not in a good position to make videos right now.
You know, he's just, and like, to me, that's kind of like an act of God preventing this Kickstarter from being completed.
Like, I don't think it's just Jesse.
Like, it's just the circumstances surrounding him.
Like, you can say, like on some level, sure, it's like he could have done more by now, but like, it's not really just as simple as he hasn't done it.
It's also like things are, you know, things are not in a place where he can do it easily.
Let me throw this at you.
So we can, I feel like it's appropriate to, we can remove Jesse from the situation and we can just look at the fact that, you know, nine months, one video.
You know, and maybe a second one soon, who knows.
But based on just those facts on the ground alone, considering that this is a Kickstarter with, you know, promised rewards and it's a fairly official thing, even though you don't have to do your Kickstarter stuff, you can't just blow it off, I think.
There's no legal repercussions.
But we're not, it's not about legal, it's about goodwill.
But like, considering that you're in that situation, it reminds me of basically what happened to Hussey when he was trying to make HiveSwap.
And he basically had a situation where, not to compare the two, but like, he had like a scummy developer just basically steal his money and, you know, run off.
As I understand it, I don't know, I don't know the odd gentleman or whatever the names are that well, but that's how I understood it to be.
Or in some way, the money was lost due to that bullshit.
And I absolutely put the blame there on Hussey specifically, or if not him, whoever was in charge of the project, if it wasn't like specifically him, but I feel like he's the guy.
Because of his managerial accountability, and it's his responsibility to deliver.
That's why you shouldn't put this on the PCV, you should put it on me.
I'm the manager.
I organized everything. I bought everybody's playing tickets, you know, or gave them the money to buy the playing tickets.
I fucking did all this. I did everything for this. At a loss, I might add.
I didn't make any money off the plea of the week Kickstarter, and in fact, I lost a lot of money off of it.
I'm sure.
From driving everybody around and fucking buying food for people and just everything I did involved.
I've only lost money from it, but I'm okay with that because I wanted the product.
Also, Radcon 2 was like the worst week of my entire life because it was just a stressful nightmare.
But I look back on it so fondly, but I wasn't in your position.
No, I mean, I'm happy with all the products that came out of it. It was just a really trying time.
Having 10 insane people in my house and I'm trying to organize a show with a guy who doesn't want to be working on the show at all.
That's really the, that's the issue right there, isn't it?
I'm sorry, Jesse. I love you. You're my brother. I don't want to show you at all.
I want to help. Let me help. Let me help make the show happen. What can I do? Tell me what I could do.
I, okay.
I just don't think it, I mean, we've talked about having you edit a certain episode before,
like even when we first recorded it, we just haven't gotten to that episode yet.
Right, that's way down the pipe anyway.
The thing is that Jesse has extensively planned this, like he has a whole narrative for the plebeian, the weeb season.
I think that's why he doesn't want to give it up.
It's because like, he has like a clear vision of what the narrative across it's going to be.
And we've even started, like we started recording season three, or season two, however you want to look at it,
with the idea that it takes place after that narrative.
So it kind of has to happen a certain way, you know, which is why we're not just, why I haven't just wrestled,
all the files, if I wanted to just give them to somebody else, I could.
But like, I want Jesse's product.
So do I.
I see it as, it doesn't entirely matter how long it takes to come out.
Like, it's a shame if it takes a really long time, but like, it will come out.
And I'd rather it come out than have to change it just to rush it out the door.
And I think a lot of the people who would back it would agree, like they backed this because they wanted the show that Jesse edits.
They don't just want the plebe and the weeb just in name only.
That's how we get Mighty No. 9, you know?
Like, yeah, Mighty No. 9 came out, but it looks nothing like the fucking game that was promised, and that's why everybody's mad about it.
Nobody's happy that it's just out, you know?
So if the plebe and the weeb came out and it's not the show Jesse wanted to make, people are going to be like,
well, why the fuck did I back it if you're not going to give me the show I want?
Okay, okay, but to play Devil's Advocate, you know, Hiveswap, for example, went through multiple changes, you know,
the whole big fuck up.
And the product that's delivered now is nothing like the original, and yet people like Hippo are pretty happy with it.
They seem to like the product, though he wasn't a backer or anything.
And to a certain extent, like my opinion isn't really like the right one to be like voicing on this issue.
Like I'm coming in from a certain angle of like involvement with the project as opposed to...
But I'm trying to like speak for the backers because that's where my concern lies.
I want to, you know, my interest is making sure that people feel satisfied with like any obligations that I personally owe them.
And I want to make good on that.
That's the thing.
What I want, if there is to be a Kickstarter or something for Radcon 3, me and Jesse's name should not be on it,
and we should not have any managerial duties on it.
It should be best guy ever's Kickstarter where he runs the show.
Because I think you through, even if it's just guilt, will get it done.
I have no doubt I will get it done.
I have no doubt.
You will get whatever it is done.
The Plebe and the Weeb as a specific show is a me and Jesse show.
And it's just a show that like the nature of it has led to this situation.
If it was your show, it would be done by now because that's the way you work.
That's true.
I remember when it was a twinkle in y'all's eye.
I remember those days so well.
It was a dream.
It was a dream to do Plebe and the Weeb.
Yes.
And it just was done at the wrong time.
It was just badly planned in terms of timing and then stomped on by an act of God immediately afterwards
where Jesse's house flooded and everything he owned was destroyed.
True.
Like literally while we were filming it.
So there's a lot of reasons that hasn't come out.
But that's me and Jesse's project.
Best guy ever's project?
I mean look at all the stuff that came out of Radcon 2 that did come out.
Everyone else's projects are out.
Hippo made like 30 videos.
You made one of your biggest videos, Kingdom Hearts Lecture.
Yeah.
It's a real winner.
Which you edited to a video that if I had made it would have just been posted exactly as is
without the enormous list of time codes in the description.
So many fucking time codes.
Because I wouldn't have watched it back to do that.
Right?
Yeah.
I don't blame you.
And I spent a lot of time meticulously color correcting.
So yeah.
I give a shit everybody.
There you go.
So I'm just saying that the way I see it, if we tried to say kickstart the next plebe
in the weave or the next Digi and Jesse show, then yes, it would be a bad idea and everybody
would shit on us for it.
But if we kickstart the best guy ever show by the guy who knows what he's doing and will
make sure it happens.
Right.
And it might be more necessary to do crowdfunding for Radcon 3 because we don't even really
have a venue.
Yeah.
That's what comes to mind that situation.
There's no place, none of us have a big enough house at this point that can host it.
So maybe we'll have to rent a space for Radcon 3.
I don't know what it'll have to be or we'll have to go somewhere specific.
So yeah, that's kind of why it's a question.
Like it might have to be crowdfunded if there's a Radcon 3.
But like, you know, I'm sure we can come up with a project to tie into it that is not,
maybe the project is just Radcon 3.
That's what I was thinking.
Which everyone knows can produce content.
All we have to do is link them the playlist of Radcon 2 content that I put as the card
in every single PCP episode that comes out so that people see the real shit that we
do for the sake of future Radcons.
Because I know it's going to happen.
And yeah, I wish that we had somehow included a little bit more.
It's all about framing and marketing really.
If I just felt personally that the content that was produced from this Kickstarter was
a little bit more entwined with just all that shit.
And it kind of was.
The $5,000 Kickstarter limit where Best Guy Ever and Hippocrite are coming to Radcon 2
says, if we're going to make this much money, we might as well bring the other guys down
too, yeah.
This amount will pay for Hippocrite and Best Guy Ever to fly down once more.
And even to guest in at least one episode of The Pleeve in the weeb season one, this
will also propagate more wacky Rad content from everyone involved.
That should be the main focus with maybe some like, some core project that just like we
gather around and then make shit other than that.
That's what I want.
The thing about The Pleeve in the weeb is that like the reason I went so hard on like
making it this big extravagant project is I thought it would be necessary to do that
to fund it.
Like I thought nobody will pay for The Pleeve in the weeb unless it sounds like really huge
and crazy and expensive.
When the reality is we hit the initial goal like immediately.
You only ask for a 1200 fucking bucks.
That's like nothing.
Yeah, because it wasn't originally going to have everybody involved.
It was going to be just me and Jesse.
But we said, well, if we add in people with stretch goals, maybe we'll make a lot more
and be able to fly everybody down.
Again, it's originally me and Jesse project.
Nobody else was even involved at the start.
That's right.
They're all just actors I hired on.
So the way I see it, if we just are funding Radcon 3, maybe people see it differently.
But that's why we're doing this on, that's why we're airing this out on the channel.
Because we had this entire discussion this morning at great length in which I concluded
I think we could definitely do it.
I think that as long as everybody understands that it's not going to be in my managerial hands
or Jesse's editing hands.
It's going to be projects that everybody wants to do, that everybody knows how to do
and is going to be on time because the people running it will make sure that's the case.
Indeed, we will.
And I think if people understand that they might be reticent to it.
I don't even think that many people see the plebe in the weed Kickstarter as a failure,
which again, it's not canceled.
It is still in the works.
But the question is like if we do another one before it's over, does that look bad for the PCP?
And again, I won't even be involved.
If the PCP, if a requirement for this Kickstarter is it can't fund Digi's trip,
I'll pay for my own trip to Redcon 3.
I'm willing to throw myself completely under the bus for the rest of the PCP to be able to do this
because I really don't think it should be any of your responsibility what happened with,
or what is happening with the plebe in the weed.
Which incidentally, a lot of current PCP fans probably weren't even around for.
Channels twice as big as it was when we did it.
And a lot of those people are probably just fucking confused what we're talking about.
I'm sure that's true.
You know, I just...
I don't want anything...
Okay, the reason why I...
Here's a little psychology of myself.
The reason that I'm so meticulous and I try to stay on top of everything so much,
and not like, this is a new thing.
I never fucking did this in school.
I was a complete fuck up.
But the reason why I do it like my pursuits now is because I don't want there to be any problems
that stop me from doing the things I want to do.
And even the fact...
Okay, I'm not saying this at all.
But what if this got to a situation where it was so bad, something happened,
and then you and Jesse, your project just got so fucked up,
people didn't even want us to be involved with you.
Or you couldn't be a part of the Radcon thing.
That's just my nightmare scenario.
And it worries me, which is why I want to help if I can.
I know I can't in this particular situation.
And as you've said, I do think you've made a pretty strong case that I hope the people will be the judge
that was your project, was your project, and the rest of us more than delivered upon the requirements,
which were zero.
We did it all for fun.
And we got a free trip.
That's true.
Cop to that.
But we did it all the shit because we wanted to, and we want to make more.
And we want to continue to grow and continue to work together on stuff.
So here's my pitch, everybody.
Radcon 3.
It's coming.
One day, to your fucking face, you better brace for it.
And there might be a Kickstarter thing involved, and I'm telling you, I'm running this shit now.
All right?
This shit is sailing straight.
Straight into your mom's pussy.
The juiciest location there is, and you better get fucking ready for it.
And you can trust me.
They trust a tight ship.
The PCP has been a tight-run ship ever since you started taking manager fees.
It's been a tight-run ship.
And you can get...
I mean, you know what content can come out of Radcon 3.
There's a lot of shit that we've put out from the last two, you know?
More lectures, people.
God, everyone loves the lectures, right?
You want the more lectures.
I know you want the lectures.
You fucking plebes out there.
That's Radcon 3.
That's it.
And maybe we can...
Maybe if we can raise enough money, maybe we can get a better space for it.
And if it's not tied to something that is basically a me and Jesse project,
like, we can market it much better as well.
Like, everyone's channels can advertise the fucking thing.
Absolutely.
Like, because last time it was just me, because that was the only one with the real audience.
Now we've got, like, you've got 50K, you know?
Like, we've got...
Everyone's kind of growing now.
So there's more room for us to try to do something a little bit more.
Not ambitious in terms of the videos getting made,
because Plebe and the Weeb was too ambitious of a project, just by sheer size.
Like, honestly, it should have been crowdfunding three episodes.
I agree.
It should have been a crowdfunding for three episodes of the Plebe and the Weeb.
It should not have been 20 episodes.
That was fucking stupid on my part.
People, it probably would have made the same fucking amount of money for three episodes.
That's why I keep emphasizing that I don't think the backers are, like, that broken up about it.
Because already episode one is twice the length of what anybody expected the episodes to be.
You know, I do want to say...
And there was a shit load of bonus background content, you know?
Yeah, like, that's all, like, done.
Isn't that, like, all out?
It's all completed?
Yeah, everything's...
Basically, everything from Radcon 2 is out, except for the Plebe and the Weeb,
and a few more Blue Glows that Jesse still has.
Actually, all the Blue Glows from Radcon might be out as well.
I think that might be the case.
Oh, yeah? Okay.
Well, to me, it's honestly baffling how chill everybody is
that just, like, the Plebe and the Weeb is not fully out yet.
Because it wasn't that much money.
Like...
That's true.
Like, when you look at it in terms of, it's a Kickstarter...
Like, everyone's so afraid of, like, the ghost of failed Kickstarter.
But, like, most of the famous failed Kickstarter's were a huge amount of money.
And the thing is that the people who complain about them are usually not so much the backers
as people looking at it from the outside and saying,
you made that much money and you failed, you fuck up.
But the thing is that Kickstarter is investment.
And if you're participating, you're an investor.
Investors are used to failure.
You're basically hoping this thing will work.
Maybe you'll get something out of it.
Maybe you won't, you know?
But, like, I think that for the people who backed it,
most of them probably paid $15, $30.
And they got a lot of shit out of it, you know?
That's for sure.
And there's still a promise that they will get what they actually paid for, you know?
Like, if I came out and said it's canceled and there's none left,
like, this is all we're releasing, I could understand being more angry.
But, like, this show will come out, you know?
Like, one way or another, it will come out.
Okay, last point, just on that specific thing,
again, to play Devil's Addict there,
do you feel it all the sense that, like, if it takes that long,
it's almost like it never came out?
You know, like, if it really does take at this pace,
if it takes, like, four years for every episode to come out,
like, will people even care, you know?
I don't know how many people will care.
I think there's lots of shows that have done things that way,
shows that just take forever to come out, you know?
Mr. Plinkett still has an audience,
and though he releases one Plinkett every year,
but it's always a big deal when it comes out, you know?
Again, I don't think The Plebe and the Weeb was ever, like,
the highest class of content that we make,
so I don't know if it'll be missed the way a Mr. Plinkett video would be missed, you know?
But, like, for me, I think of everything in the long term anyways.
Like, I have video series that people think I've killed
and then I bring it back a year later
and everyone's excited that it's back, you know?
Like, I think people think of this in a very impatient short-term way,
but, like, part of investment is the long haul.
Like, Kickstarter usually takes years to finish.
Like, the vast majority of them take two or three years.
Well, I think the only problem here is just that, you know,
you did give a time frame, and that's really the issue at hand.
The thing is, I gave a time frame that was absolutely ridiculous
because I was imagining if I was editing it, you know?
Because I work insanely fast.
If the plebeine that we've had been something I was editing,
it might have been, like, a fifth as good,
but it would have been out in a month, you know?
Like, all of it would have been out in a month.
Because that's how I work.
I do want to give Jesse all the credit in the world
for the obvious love and dedication he puts into it,
which is why when I think about, you know,
the discussion about, like, me editing one of the episodes,
like, I don't want to because I know I can't do it as well as Jesse can.
Jesse just, he's got the spark.
And by Christ, I want it back.
Jesse, make more content. Please, come back to us.
I miss you so much.
I miss him, too.
But, like, the, there is an episode that, like,
would make more sense if you edited it.
Yeah.
But see, I want Jesse.
I want, I want to be enveloped by Jesse's, by his panache.
By his fucking, yes, that's what I want.
I don't want my interpretation of that.
That'd be fucking bullshit.
That's exactly why I don't want to take it from him.
Like, I think, I think the project, I think the people funding the project
will ultimately be happier to get the product they wanted
as opposed to getting a product fast, you know?
I hope so.
Like, if you can't have, like, it would be nice if you could have both,
but you can't have both because the way to get the product you want
is to milk it out of the most talented man in the world
who needs to be away from the internet for the next however long he wants to be.
You know?
Like, that's the nature of, of what's going on.
So, like, yeah.
But I don't think that should affect the rest of the PCP.
And I think we should be able to, like, I think if people,
I don't think people will have any fear about it getting done
if you're the one running it, you know?
I agree.
Like, even if they were completely disappointed in the other Kickstarter,
you can look at this one and say, well, Nate's running it,
so I know we're going to get over it.
The whole thing would start.
The whole thing would start with a careful analysis of what is actually
a reasonable expectation for what we can actually get done at a radical.
It would all be framed around that to begin with.
And that's really, that's the most important step when it comes to this shit.
Um, yeah.
And, you know, there's one other point I did want to make in here,
and, uh, and it's, okay, it sounds a little odd,
but is it cruel to Jesse to keep him under the yoke of this?
Like, as a fellow creator, if I had, like, nine episodes,
like 20 episodes or whatever of a show just, like, hanging above me,
like a fucking sword of Damocles every day as, like, this is, I have to do this.
It, it seems nightmarish.
It seems horrible.
I mean, if it, if it was that way, we've all offered to take it off his hands.
Like, everyone's offered that.
So if he doesn't want to do it, he can pass it up.
But, like, I think he wants to do it because he has a vision of it.
And he likes the series.
He likes the idea, you know?
It's just, like, again, it's just bad timing.
Like, maybe next year, maybe, like, February 2018,
something clicks in his head and he finishes the rest of the show in a week.
You know?
Like, I've seen him do that before.
I've seen the way this man works.
Horse Shoe Finale was in production for a fucking year.
You know?
And he disappeared for six months of that year.
There was a long period with no new Jesse uploads.
Then there was a thousand of them.
You know?
I'm not saying that's gonna happen.
Don't expect your hopes up.
Well, let's just, but it has happened before.
Let's just think for a second about the worst case scenario,
where Jesse just thinks, yeah, fuck it.
And he leaves.
And he never makes it.
He gives me it.
You know?
I take all the, I take the, I have all the files.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
So that's the, that's the critical mass points.
Everything's, everything's in my head.
Like, the second, the second I get the text from Jesse that says,
I fucking hate the plebe of the weave.
I don't want to edit it anymore.
I go, all right.
Hippo, Nate, how much do I have to pay per episode?
You know?
Cause I know if I edit, it's going to be garbage.
So.
I'll have to get creative.
Yeah.
I wouldn't, I would love a Ghib edited episode.
I know that boy could do some good things.
Yeah.
I think Hippo could do it well.
I think it wouldn't be the same, but he could edit.
Yeah.
And it would be funny.
Of course.
DeVoo could probably edit one.
We got a lot of editors in our midst.
We do.
But there's only one who's a, who's, who's got a specific brand of genius mania.
You know?
Yeah.
There's only one Tarzan boy out there.
He's just waiting for him to come home.
Jungle nights, far away from nowhere.
I'm getting nostalgic.
Yeah.
I know, right?
All right.
Well, so down in the comments.
Let us know, everybody.
Way in.
Yeah.
Be our judge and jury.
Beneath, right after you're done with your comment, ripping on me for defending my failed
Kickstarter, go ahead and leave a comment about whether or not you think the PCP can do
a Kickstarter.
Just let us know.
Would you fund Radcon three with the promise that it's going to have for sure all the things
that Radcon two had besides the plea in the weeb, as well as potentially new projects
that we haven't even dreamed up yet.
I think it is almost guaranteed the people will want that.
That is what I think.
And if we, if we firm it that way.
Yeah.
Sounds good to me.
Here you go, folks.
Digi has taken full responsibility.
All right.
No blame on this side of the fence, everybody.
No accountability whatsoever.
There you go.
So there it is.
I'm, you know, I think this is good.
I think people will be happy to hear us talking about it.
You voicing an opinion on it and just, just giving an update, giving an update to this
whole situation.
I think it's good.
Yeah.
That's what I would want to hear if I were them.
Alrighty.
Suck my dick.
Fuck my ass.
Bye, everybody.
I love you.