Hello everybody and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm Digibro and I am doing yet another interview this time with the Endless One himself, Mr. Endless Jess.
The people demanded it. They were barreling down the doors for an interview with yours truly.
Let's talk about right off the bat how butthurt, Ben and Nate are. How butthurt they are right now as we speak, still being butthurt, talking amongst themselves, screaming and whining like petulant babies in the chat as we're talking.
Oh my god. I'm Ben. I'm the best guy ever and everyone just wants to hear from Endless Jess.
What's so great about him? Well you know I'm sorry guys. Maybe you should put in the work to become the most entertaining motherfucker on the face of the earth in the entire history of humanity every day of your life.
It's that simple. Just get good. The people will want to hear more from you if you just get good, faggots. That's why they want me.
That's why they call out for a savior, for Endless Jess to come down from my throne in Valhalla and bring a little brightness into their lives with that special gift of gab that only I have.
Not you, me. Only I. That's why they want me. That's why they love me. That's why they don't love you. That's why they beg for me when you're on screen.
I knew that rant was coming at the start of this.
So Jesse, you and I have been friends for a good, what, god, three years now?
Yeah, it's about three years. It's gotta be.
Holy shit. That's a long fucking time. Other than Tom, if you were a woman, I'd have thrown you to the curb by now. I would have gotten sick of you after two weeks.
I think other than Tom, you're probably the longest still active friendship I have on the internet.
My oldest friend. The good old old school fool with that old school cool. The Endless one.
So to start with, I want to ask you some stuff about your backstory.
Particularly where your persona and comedy, not so much persona, but you have this very self-aggrandizing attitude.
You're definitely a big fan of your own work and you think you're better than everybody else.
And I want to know how that came to be.
Because some people say that. Some people say that he's arrogant or egotistical or too much of a fan of himself.
But then at the exact same time, other people go, oh, he's too self-deprecating. He's just too down in himself and mopey and whiny.
Well, which is it, you stupid motherfuckers?
Gee, maybe I'm not egotistical or depressed. Maybe I'm just a normal, actual fucking human who's confident in the work that I have put in the effort to know for a fact is good.
Maybe I'm not egotistical. Maybe I just know what I'm good at.
Yeah, I think the impression I've always gotten is sort of that you're self-aware enough to see your own flaws.
But I think that you still seem to think that the net positive is higher than anyone else's net positive.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Like, we're all flawed. We all have our strengths and weaknesses, but you have more strengths than anybody else.
That seems to be how you present yourself.
That, and I don't think that anybody on the internet has a right to assume that they know what my flaws are.
Right.
Like, I'm the only fucking person who can criticize me, maybe me and some people who know me in real life, like some girlfriends that I've been dicks to or friends.
You know, anyone who actually knows me, fine, go ahead and say that Jesse, that he smells bad 60% of the time or that he says nigger too much.
If you know me in real life, those are totally valid complaints.
Wait, are you sure you're talking about yourself and not me?
Those are two complaints a lot of people have about me.
I think we are kindred spirits in many ways.
That's probably why we've been hanging out for so long.
I don't know, I just think that, yeah, that's kind of how I feel about criticism on the whole is just that I think that nobody really has the right to criticize art except for the person who made it, because they're the only one who really knows.
I mean, yeah, if you pay to go see a movie, you have a right to say that was a shitty movie, but as far as like, I don't know.
Telling them what they did.
Yeah.
We talked about this in the commenter rules how it's like, or in the authorial intent podcast, so you weren't there for that, I think, but that the only person who really knows what they were trying to do is the author.
And it's like, you can criticize how well it appealed to you, but you can't really criticize what the author was trying to do unless you completely understand what they were trying to do.
So a complaint like, or a complaint like he is an egomaniac or he has too much of an ego.
Well, how the fuck do you know that? You don't know anything except what you see on a fucking YouTube video that is designed first and foremost to be hilarious and to make me laugh.
Right.
I hate everybody.
I'm already sweating. I'm already at that level.
What I want to know, though, is where your like sort of personality comes from in your past.
Oh, yeah, that was the question we got. I already got way off on something.
If there is any specific point, I guess to lead into it because for me, you know, I've been I've been watching you for a long time and what's unique about our relationship is that we're not just friends, but I'm also a really big fan of your work.
And one of my general favorite content for everyone that I talk to, I don't I have a real problem taking people seriously as human beings if I'm not a big fan of their work.
Right.
I feel pretty similar. It's hard. It's a lot harder for me to like keep up communications with someone if they're not making things because so much of my life is making things.
That's what I want to talk about.
It's the world that I inhabit and I can't it's hard to relate to someone who doesn't inhabit that same world.
Right. And I think that's, you know, I'm probably I'm willing to say more than anyone I am the most invested in your work other than yourself because I watch all of it and I talk to you about it while it's being made.
And so that's good that you are because you're one of the only people that I trust besides myself to articulate my work to anyone.
Because I feel like everybody else in the world explains my videos wrong and it just adds to the growing frustration of nobody getting it.
Like whenever whenever some commenter tries to defend me in the comments, like some guy will be like this guy, he's not funny.
And then like immediately some commenter will rush to my defense.
But instead of just saying, no, fuck you, he's funny.
You're like a comedy subjective or like some normal sounding defense of me, they'll launch right into you don't understand the artistic intent of Jesse's master plan.
This web that he weaves goes beyond what any of us mere mortals can possibly comprehend just from watching a single YouTube video.
It's like, okay, that's just making me sound worse.
That's not helping.
Yeah.
It's true, but it's not helping.
Well, along the line, there was a point towards, I guess, the back end of 2014, where you started up the drowning in kayfave channel.
And you started talking about wrestling and describing like these hours long vlogs describing wrestling history.
And it all kind of culminated in the horseshoe finale.
And it was interesting because I'd known you for a long time by then and I didn't know anything about wrestling.
And then once you explained all of it to me, that's when like your persona finally clicked and I understood what you were trying to do.
Like, I think you're someone who the more you understand where like your influences and where you're coming from, the easier it is to parse what your channel is.
Yeah.
And I.
What?
Yeah.
Oh, sorry.
I think some of the difficulty in that for a lot of people who find the channel is that like, you know, a lot like my little pony fans, for instance, like, where are they coming from?
They're like these high schoolers watching a, you know, a little girls show, maybe didn't grow up with wrestling and don't understand like that this is a type of thing that has existed before.
Because I think if you just stumble upon endless jests with no idea like those kinds of influences, then it's like, why is this man screaming at me?
You know, what did I do wrong?
He seems so angry.
He seems so violent.
But then if you're familiar with something like wrestling where that's the whole entertainment of it is a bunch of violent, crazy people screaming at each other.
Then it's like, okay, I get that this is a form of entertainment that has existed long before you did it, you know, even if you're, you know, obviously putting your own unique spin on it.
Yeah, fuck them.
And you.
That's what you were getting at, right?
Yes, fuck them.
They're all stupid.
Yeah, of course.
They should all burn in a garbage can.
Yeah.
Yeah, I want to know.
So you, you have a lot of influences from like outside YouTube.
Yeah, like, yeah, mostly.
Yeah, I think very few of my influences are within the YouTube sphere.
I mean, I consider James Ralph an influence, but that's about it.
As far as YouTube goes, I come from like, how did you end up on YouTube is what I want to know.
It's just, it was, I don't know, I just kind of fell into, it's just the most convenient platform to get my stuff out, because I don't really, like, I'm a big fan of stand-up comedy and I'm a big fan of doing stand-up comedy.
I've only done it a few times, but every time I did it, I felt really good.
I was like, hyped and amped for like a week afterwards.
It was like, yeah, that felt really like stand-up comedy, like being on a stage in front of real people in like a, in like a little club or some, any place with a microphone.
It just feels to me more legitimate than YouTube.
And I know that we disagree about that because you always say that YouTubers should take YouTube more seriously as its own thing.
And I agree with that to a point.
But for me, something about YouTube, it just feels like a website for talentless assholes.
And I deeply resent everything about it.
I resent YouTube culture.
I hate reviewers and critics.
They're all fucking smarmy, sarcastic twats.
I hate every fucking agenda pushing blow hard, trying to scream his opinion on politics or the societal ills affecting our generation.
Like, who gives a fuck?
You're all asshats.
You all belong in the trash.
I just, I can't stand it.
To me, it just feels like a big fucking circle jerk.
It's a treehouse for babies is what YouTube is.
It's a sewer full of poop floating around poop.
I definitely think it's lowered the overall standard of what you have to be to be good.
Because old media or stand-up comedy, only the absolute most popular people make it anywhere.
The overwhelming majority of stand-up comedians are still in dive bars in their 30s and not making any progress.
Whereas on YouTube, you can just, like, not even be that talented, but because you're talking about video games, people find you, you know?
Or because you're talking about, like, a certain thing, you can be found.
Not to say that everyone does get found.
Just, like, there's plenty of talented people, like yourself, who, in spite of covering a lot of popular stuff, have never really taken off in that big, viral way.
But you are making a career off of it, even in spite of that.
Which has always impressed me that you have, like, you make an amount of money that no, I don't think anyone would expect from someone with your audience.
I mentioned that in Horseshoe Finale. It was one of my many acrimoniously spewed points.
It's not spewed. Spewed implies a lack of articulation.
But I mean, it was one of the many things that I launched at people.
It's true. Because you don't, to me, Patreon is a better measure of success than, like, YouTube subscribers.
Because the patrons will fucking leave if they don't like what you're doing anymore.
And to anyone can attract viewers, but to attract people who think, I care about this person as an artist.
I care about them being able to continue their work. So I'm going to give them some of my money every month.
That, to me, is a far better measure that I'm connecting or accomplishing something good.
I definitely think that, like, it's a direct response to quality and to, you know, like, with the fucking Asterisk War videos.
Like, when the last episode of that came out, my Patreon jumped unbelievably.
Like, it had never done before. And it wasn't that I was getting any more views than normal.
It was just people were so excited about that particular video series that it, like, struck such a chord with them that they threw all their money at me.
And every once in a while, like, the last video I did, like, ten best things happening in anime this decade,
like, a video like that that just makes people feel something will definitely cause them to patron.
And so, even though you've got, like, well, I mean, I make a crazy amount of money now, but for a very long time,
I had ten times your subscribers and was making, like, the same amount, you know?
Just because you had people who cared so deeply about the stuff you were making.
Yeah. And a lot of it was, you know, being drowning in horseshoes was such a consistent gimmick.
Like, people knew that they were getting my little pony reviews.
And I knew that after I did Horseshoe Finale and I stopped doing Horseshoe reviews, I knew that it would go down substantially for a long while.
But I was prepared to make that sacrifice because I knew that eventually I would be able to get it back up with my other content.
And I have. It slowly trickled back up to almost where it was.
But that's a source of pride for me, that I was fully aware that it would go down, and it did, and I did it anyways.
Yeah. So, to explain sort of why the two of us know each other, because we've told the story before,
but a lot of our old podcasts are gone now, because we did these old horse casts together, which you took down eventually.
Which is probably for the best, because a lot of the information would be out of date.
I don't like anything that I see, like, more than one year ago is like, I don't consider it me anymore.
Right. I have very similar feelings.
I feel like I'm always a different person than I was a year ago, and I feel like people should be always changing.
I like having all that stuff up from my past so that people can look at it and see that I'm so different,
because I think it's encouraging for new artists who don't know that you have to practice and that you have to evolve.
And you can point to, like, if a 17-year-old tells me, like, how do I get better at writing?
I can link them a post I wrote when I was 17, and they'll be like, wow, this is fucking garbage.
And I'll be like, I know, now you have to practice for 10 years, catch up to me, you know.
But yeah, we had those podcasts before that have since been removed.
But basically, we met because you were one of my first subscribers when I started as Digi Baroni,
and you were the, for a long time, you were the biggest channel that was subscribed to me,
even though you only had, like, 2,500 subs, which to me was a lot, so I was like, oh, this guy's bigger, you know.
And you, like, messaged me, you messaged me once, and I thought that your channel was literally about footwear,
because it was called Drowning in Footwear, I thought it was a shoe review channel,
because I've known some people who are, like, obsessed with shoes, so I just thought, okay, he must be a shoe guy.
And then you messaged me again later when my channel started taking off, and I went and watched your Sin City video
and the Hello Kitty video, and I was like, this guy's a fucking genius.
And I've been evangelizing you ever since.
Yeah, and that's good, because somebody should be.
I often think of you as my ambassador to the world.
I might as well be.
Because I don't like explaining things about myself.
It feels like, like a part of me feels like, first of all, nobody fucking deserves me to explain my work.
Like, yeah.
Like, I just, a couple days ago on June 6th, which was the one-year anniversary of Horseshoe Finale,
I finally sat down and I recorded the one-year anniversary video of it, and I talked about what went into the making of it,
and I talked about a lot of what the video means.
And even though I explained it, a part of me feels like, you people don't fucking deserve this.
It feels like a betrayal, almost, to explain my work.
And also, it's just hard for me.
It's hard to articulate in the moment what I really mean with my art.
It's like you have said before on Digi Bros. about Hideo Kiano.
You know, the medium is the message, and he's clearly so uncomfortable whenever someone tells him to describe Ava
and what it means, like, and I know what Ava is about.
You know what it's about.
If you're, if you're reasonably intelligent, it's not that fucking hard to understand,
but nobody is reasonably intelligent.
That's the one constant about this universe.
So everybody watches it and, you know, slack-jawed with drool rolling down their chin and going,
What happened?
Doesn't make any sense.
And so they ask him about it.
He's like, I don't fucking know what to explain.
It's right there. Just fucking watch it.
Like, the best way that I can explain Horseshoe Finale to me is to point at it and go fucking pay attention, you slime.
And it feels really obnoxious and aggravating that I even have to explain these things.
And it's not like I expect everybody to watch Horseshoe Finale and understand every little tiny word or phrase or reference
or thing in the background 100%.
That would probably be completely impossible unless you were actually me.
But I do expect people to at least get the themes.
Like, nothing makes me madder than the fact that to this day people will watch that video and go,
Oh, this is, he hates bronies. He's mad at bronies. He's leaving the fandom.
That's what this video is about.
That makes me sick. It makes me sick to my fucking stomach.
I want to, I'm, I'm kind of repeating everything that I'm about to be saying in the video that I'm releasing
because this is basically the same rant that I went on.
All right, well, I'll just cut you off then.
Wait, shit. Now I lost track of what I wanted to say.
Oh, yeah. You know, I, I've been planning.
But what I was saying, wait, let me go back.
Anyways, what I was saying is that it's aggravating and frustrating for me to in the moment be put on the spot
and have to explain my things because I can do it if I sit down and I write it out.
But it's hard to figure out because, you know, I put so much of it into the medium is the message.
And you're a lot better than me, I think at, at vloggy type off the cuff explanation
because we both do vlogs and I think we're both good at it.
But like we're, we approach it differently in that I'm a, I'm a performer.
I'm, you're informative and I'm performance driven.
Like when I turn on a vlog, my instinct is to be energetic and funny and say funny things.
And that's what I'm good at. You're better at actually giving out information.
And I hate doing vlogs in general because every time that I do a vlog, I watch it back
and I feel like I could have just written it out and I could have said it a million times better.
This is just going to confuse people more.
But the problem is that when I write it out, it becomes a project and a project takes a lot longer to make
and then it piles on.
That's exactly why I've gotten into vlogging.
Yeah, it's so much easier to just like rant.
It's easier to, it's so much easier and quicker to do a vlog,
but I am always left with the feeling that I've articulated myself like an animal would after I do a vlog.
I feel the same way where I, all of my vlogs definitely have more comments from people who don't understand
than a typical video would, but some of those ideas aren't worth a whole project.
You know, like talking about the two anime I just did where I was laying on the couch.
Like I don't want to write a video about those.
It's okay if some people don't get it.
I just wanted my thoughts out there.
And that's why I almost think of you as my ambassador a lot of the time or like the ambassador to my art
because I feel like when you're in a position where you have to explain what the hell I'm doing,
you're usually better at explaining it than I am.
Yeah.
Well, I thank you first of all and I like doing that for a lot of people.
Like I do that for anyone I encounter who can't explain themselves.
I like to be able to try and explain what they're trying to say,
which is why I've always said that I think I'm good at creative intent,
like getting it because I really search for it more than I think most people do.
Yeah.
Definitely.
And I think more people should.
That's like a big hang up of mine, really, that more people should.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't think it's the only way, like I think you can make interesting points about something
without caring about, you know, while doing the whole death of the author thing.
But I think that for me, most often the author's thoughts are the most interesting, you know,
like nothing's cooler than what the guy was trying to say.
That usually is what gives you the most meaning.
I think that, um, I think that like nobody uses 10 scores right.
I think you did a video on this very topic, but our opinions are,
I think are like directly opposite.
I don't remember exactly what you said.
Yeah.
You're very like everything's a 10 or a, or not a 10.
Well, like to me, I just think that like intent is kind of what I look for most
when I dole out my number scores.
Like I think that not enough people pay attention to intent.
And if you're a, if you consider yourself a critic or a reviewer,
I think you have a responsibility to try to understand what they were going for
and not just look at it through like this narrow,
like when people complain about the cut scenes in Uncharted,
have you played a fucking Uncharted game before?
Did you not know it?
You put in the fucking PlayStation 4?
Did you not know what you were getting into?
They didn't like Uncharted 4 does not have a lot of cut scenes by accident.
They, they wanted to make a game with a bunch of cut scenes.
So you have to judge it as that.
If you don't like cut scenes, that's fine,
but you can't fucking sit there like a petulant baby and go,
there's too many cut scenes in this game.
It's the game is supposed to have cut scenes.
You idiot.
Yeah.
I would agree with that, uh, that sentiment.
Ooh.
So I have been for a very long time trying to like,
literally be an ambassador for you and, and write a video.
There was a time back in the horseshoe days where I completely wrote out a script
and I'd sent it to you that was like explaining why Jesse is cool.
Um, and I just never got around to making it.
And then now I've been inspired that I want to literally rip off
Nerdwriters understanding art formula and do an understanding art on Endless Jest.
And the reason is that like, because I keep saying that I think YouTube is so important as like a medium and everything
and I want to see it advancing is that like, you're my favorite YouTuber.
And I think I probably take YouTube more seriously than anybody else.
I watch way more of it than anybody I know.
Um, like, I, I, I care a lot about like where it's going.
And, um, in the process.
It's funny because when I think about like what I tried to do,
and in my mind I accomplished completely 110% what I tried to do because I'm a genius.
But when I think about, um, the horseshoe saga and leading in the horseshoe finale,
um, I really think that I did my part to elevate YouTube as an artistic medium.
And I don't think people are ever going to really recognize that.
I don't, or if they do, it's going to be a long time before anyone looks at it and thinks that.
But I think I did.
And it's funny to me that I would think that of myself because I'm the guy who probably hates YouTube the most
and respects it the least as a medium in the first place.
But I tried, dammit, I tried to save you all.
Well, the way I want to start this video, because you, the very first video on your channel, on Endless Jest,
if anybody goes there now, it wasn't the first YouTube video you ever did.
There's been removed ones.
But the first one that's up, it starts in such a perfect way for revealing what the point of Endless Jest is.
Because the first scene is you going, yeah, it's you going,
fuck, this game's too hard.
And then you put the controller down and you go, you idiots don't even realize.
I'm not even in the game right now.
I'm not playing a game.
I'm not even in the TV room.
And that was the first official drowning of footwear video.
So even like the first five seconds of my YouTube career was already subverting what was popular at the time.
Subverting video game reviews.
It's all about just sort of pulling back.
And that's all that I do.
And I hate that people don't understand satire.
I hate that people don't get subversion.
Like, I still get it because really I still do it.
Like all my videos in some way are meant to be a subversion or a parody or a satire or something.
Like, for example, that series of videos that I did, the best review.
Fuck, in Batman v Superman, the best review.
And best is in all caps, like it's clickbait and stuff.
Like, the whole point of those videos, like the joke is that it says the best review.
And then you click on it and it's a two hour irreverent vlog that makes no sense and is completely retarded.
And people in the comments go, this is stupid.
It's just a two hour irreverent vlog that makes no sense and is retarded.
That's the joke, dummies.
Congratulations.
Get out of my fucking YouTube.
You're stinking up the joint.
Uh, that's, yeah, that's also kind of what the joke is with, um, with Victor's movie news where it's like.
Which I love, by the way.
I said that, I said that that was the best video you've ever made.
And then you said, well, actually, Victor pretty much was in charge of all of it.
Yeah.
No, Victor wrote, directed, staged, did everything.
It was his, his debut on YouTube.
And it is supposed to be a weekly series.
So expect more of that.
That was though.
That like your performance in it though was like the perfect, like the essence of DigiBro.
Like that's what I want the world to see DigiBro as.
Me too.
Um, but yeah, like the idea of it was that it looks like this click bait.
Like, you know, here's the hit new movies and then it's just like this weird dry Eric Andre show ripoff.
Um, but yeah, like I feel like all of your videos are sort of about taking what, uh, what YouTube is and playing with the meta of it.
You know, in a lot of ways you're like the house of leaves of YouTube.
And I know you haven't read that book, but the way it's structured and written is that it's essentially like Ben and my Amazon cart for two years because you keep talking about it.
I mean, if we ever, uh, when we do this whole rad con that we're planning, uh, you could just, uh, read it.
I'll loan it to you or something as I have it.
Um, but I don't know.
I could see you getting pissed off with it because the way you have to read it is so confusing.
Um, but it's a lot like your videos.
How dare anybody challenge me but me?
How dare any other creator think that they're clever?
Well, this is coming from a guy who, uh, tried to read Homestuck without reading the chat logs.
Yeah, we don't need to get into that.
I don't get Homestuck, man.
Yeah, we're not going to talk about Homestuck.
We should just do the, we should just do the Homestuck fucking, the people versus endless Jess for Homestuck podcast.
Because it's not going to go well.
I know it's not going to go well.
That's what, that's what annoys me is because every time we talk about Homestuck, it turns into a huge, screaming, intense argument and nobody ever hears it because it's never being recorded.
It's literally just us legitimately fighting amongst ourselves and it's going to waste every time.
Yeah.
I'm glad that's the kind of content you want from us.
It's just us all fighting and getting legitimately pissed off.
Mostly Ben.
Ben gets legit mad.
It's like he can't, like, you know, I got real mad the first time we argued about it.
But ever since then, I'm just like, well, whatever, Jesse hasn't read it.
He doesn't get it.
I don't care, you know, but like somehow Ben can't not get mad when you talk about Homestuck.
Like, it's not even that I hate it.
Like, I don't think I hate it.
I just, I hate it.
I haven't read it.
I just hate it.
Yeah.
Instinctively.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, it's pretty similar to your work, though, in that regard of being like something complex and meta.
It's because three years ago, I got into a Facebook flame war with a fucking Vriska cosplayer.
And from that point forward, I deemed that Homestuck was the gayest thing ever because this guy was the most annoying person.
But you somehow can still enjoy my little pony in spite of having met all the bronies.
Yeah, well, I'm the best bronie, so I guess it balances out.
I'm as good as the rest of the bronies are terrible.
That's what makes me still able to enjoy the show.
Yeah, I guess we should, I was talking to Ben during my interview with him about how, like, did you listen to that, by the way?
I think I'm like 40 minutes into it and I pause to go fuck around or whatever.
Okay, you might have heard this part, I'm not sure.
I was saying that, like, what makes me sad with Ben is that, like, the T-Bap is, like, the most content that him and Nate did.
And it has so many creative ideas and, like, if I was trying to explain to someone, here's why I think Ben and Nate are, like, great artists.
Then I can't show them T-Bap because it's a fucking weekly My Little Pony review show and it will make no sense.
T-Bap needs to come back and it needs to expand beyond My Little Pony because nobody has chemistry like Ben and Nate have.
No, it's amazing.
They're great together.
And you, though, I have the same problem with, which is that horse shoe finale is your masterpiece and there's just no way I can introduce new people to it.
Because it's such, it's not just the matter of that it's an MLP thing because, like, I honestly think that the horse shoe reviews are mostly, like, the early ones would be the hardest part where it's, like, more legitimately an analysis of the show.
But, like, I feel like the horse shoe reviews get so out there that you could appreciate them without having seen the show, but not having seen the show will make it so confusing.
And the fact that the channel's not even called the horse shoe journey to horseshoes anymore, you know?
I fucked that up so bad.
I did it so backwards because fucking cold corona went off and started horseshoe heaven because I turned drowning in horseshoes into Man Child Incorporated.
I got it totally backwards.
I should have turned drowning in horseshoes into horseshoe heaven and Man Child Incorporated should have been an entirely new channel.
But for some reason I was like, well, I don't want to sacrifice these 10,000 subs, so I should just change, but I did it, I fucked it up so bad.
And now I can never go back.
That's true.
The idea was that that channel had the most subs, so that was the one that had to go corporate and just become a shill channel.
Which I loved the idea of that, but it did make it so you can't go back.
It's a great joke in the moment, but now that I can't go back and I can't rectify it, it was a terrible mistake.
I think that's the biggest issue with all the pony content.
It's not just that it's my little pony, but that we all wrote in such an in-the-moment way.
It's impossible to look back on any of it, even my own work.
The problem with Man Child Incorporated is that the whole joke is that it's soulless and it's like a sell-out channel.
And that's funny, but because it's a sell-out channel, I feel the least investment towards it.
So I never do Man Child Incorporated videos.
It had its point for about a month, and then it completely was like, well, alright, I guess that joke's over.
It was meant to be like the Man Child Incorporated saga.
It has another name, but I can't reveal the other name yet, because if I reveal the other name, I'll spoil it.
It was supposed to be like the semi-sequel slash criticism of the Horseshoe Saga, and it was supposed to culminate right around about Nowish.
But I'm just so I can't fucking, I don't know, it's annoying to fucking make videos on Man Child Incorporated, so it's taking a lot longer than it should.
Well, for what it's worth, I think Horseshoe Finale came out like a year after it was supposed to come out.
Horseshoe Finale, well, the Horseshoe Saga grew so much in the telling, because the original plan, when I made that first Horseshoe review for Princess Twilight Sparkle or whatever,
the idea was this is going to be a dramatization of how I grew as a person during the two years of drowning in footwear.
So, and it's going to, I'm going to make these reviews, and they're going to be really sincere and easy to make at first, and sort of, you know, to get people watching.
And then their reviews are going to slowly become more and more insane and resentful and bitter, and it's going to culminate in CM Punk's pipe bomb.
And I'm going to sit cross-legged, and I'm going to, you know, essentially cut the exact same six minute promo that he cut in 2011 on wrestling.
But change the words so that it would be about bronies, and then drop the mic and end it with that.
And that is still an elemental Horseshoe Finale.
There's six minutes in there where I'm just doing CM Punk's pipe bomb, but all the rest of it.
It's sprinkled about 90 minutes of other stuff.
Yeah, it just grew so much in the, like, and it became so much more than just what I set out to make it.
It became like my artistic footprint of everything that I am and everything that I've ever thought or felt.
And, like, and I'm very protective of it for that reason because, like, that video is me.
I put every fucking part of my soul into that video.
And so, yeah, it became something special unexpectedly, and that's always how it happens.
Everything good sort of happens on its own unexpectedly in the telling.
And I want to note that, like, I knew all this from the beginning.
You told me.
Like, I think I was probably the only one who was around for, like, the plans because this all started in 2013.
Me and you sort of became friends that summer.
Yeah.
And, you know, this was before the Horseshoe Crew was a thing because it really sprung out of all this, where the way you had described it to me was that you saw that there was this,
because I had started working for Equestria Daily.
All these new people were coming out with all these analysis videos and shit.
And you were like, man, I know I can do this better than anyone else.
And it'll be a way to make really easy videos and make a shitload of money and subscribers.
Because, like, at the time you were, you only had the one channel, right?
Drowning in footwear.
Yeah.
Yeah, just drowning in footwear.
And you didn't want to flood it with pony content, but it looked like that was a very quick way to success.
And then you could transform it from there.
And it totally worked.
Like, maybe you didn't get super famous, but it did blow up as a much bigger channel.
Yeah, it blew up at first until my videos started getting more Jess.
Right.
My videos took a very quick nosedive into the boogie realm very quickly.
Because for those first four months, when they were more like, you know, actual typical pony reviews, that's where, like, all the subs came from immediately.
And then once the video started getting more intricate, and I guess weird, for lack of a better term, that's when people stopped subbing.
And I became like this weird underground thing.
Yeah.
I don't know if it's that they stopped or that you were constantly losing and gaining them at the same rate, you know?
Yeah, yeah, that's also possible.
But then it's worth noting that of everyone in the procrastinators, you have the video with by far the most views.
Yeah.
Which is-
And I always will.
Of course two of you bats.
It's got a picture of Fluttershy's ass as the thumbnail and like four million views, I think.
Yeah, four million fucking- I don't know why, I don't know how.
Oh, and by the way, everybody who's listening to this, four million views on that video has never been mine.
Has never been monetized, ever.
Yeah.
Because it very quickly got copyright ID'd as soon as I posted it.
So that's, I mean, what is four million views?
That's gotta be like four thousand dollars, right?
Yes.
That belongs to me that I never received and never will.
Thanks, YouTube.
Yeah.
And unfortunately back then we didn't know as much about fighting content ID's because I'm willing to bet that-
I don't know if you could have at the time, but I think now you could definitely beat that.
Yeah, if it had happened now I probably could have fought it, but...
We didn't know about that shit back then, man.
We would delete videos sometimes just because they got matched, like not even taken down.
We'd just be like, I don't want this to get worse.
Yeah, now what I do is I upload everything on private first and if it gets ID'd, I either change it or I say fuck it.
No one deserves this video when I throw it in trash.
Yeah, I fight everything now.
Now that I realize how easy it is to win, I'm like, oh, hell no, you're not taking my videos.
Yeah.
I'm recutting my PsychoPass video into a full two and a half hour thing and I know it's gonna get a strike
and I don't care because I'm gonna fight it and win and I want this fucking video to exist.
But yeah, man, you have the video with the most views incredibly.
And I mean, everyone's review of bats had more views than normal.
I don't know what it was about that episode because, like, that was my biggest video too,
but mine was like not even 100,000 views and yours was like crazy.
But that's because of the horseshoe, because the procrastinators was originally the horseshoe crew
and it was all because of you because me and you were watching all these new guys,
all these newcomers into the fold and we found Gibb and Take
and we both thought he was hilarious and he did like these videos where he would supercut
like everyone who did analysis videos and he put both me and you in there, I think.
And so we knew that he was like a fan of you on some level.
And then the TBAP had started making these funny videos and they did a Q&A where they like specifically,
they didn't just name drop you, but they name dropped Butchugger.
And you were like, oh my God, they know Butchugger because no one had listened to that.
The true forgotten masterpiece of endless Jess's catalog.
And I gotta say, you know, back then, because, you know, we were friends and I was a fan,
but I didn't, back then I didn't get into all your weirder shit.
Like I just thought it was all too much.
So like I hadn't even heard Butchugger and then like I want to say over a year later,
I finally listened to it and I was like, oh my God, this is fucking masterpiece.
This is amazing.
Highly recommended to all of our listeners, if you haven't heard Butchugger,
it's a six minute ballad that you wrote this epic, would you consider it a hip hop song?
I'm not sure.
Yeah, yeah, I guess it's sort of a rap opera word.
It's a rap opera.
Yeah, that's a good way to put it.
It's about Cody LaRue the Butchugger.
My actual real life friend Cody LaRue who's a comedian and also has a channel called Flint Rant Films
where he is currently working on his ongoing series, Regular Dudes,
which I may one day have a part in.
I haven't yet because I'm very lazy and I'm misanthropic and I don't hang out with people when I say I will.
But it's always a possibility.
Cody LaRue has a hilarious Twitter as well.
Yeah, Cody LaRue is an expert at Twitter.
Yeah, he makes...
I was really shocked that I actually, because I don't follow a lot of people on Twitter,
so when I read how funny his shit was, I was like,
wow, I'm going to follow this totally unknown friend of Jesse's just because he's funny as shit.
He's the Butchugger.
I mean, I'm not sure where this came from, but it must have been like four or five years ago.
He mentioned that he was the Butchugger.
And now if you mention it to him, he staunchly denies it.
He denies that it was ever a thing, that he ever said it.
It's true. He's the Butchugger. Never let him forget.
He can't outrun his past. I won't let him.
The song is there for all time.
Yeah.
Cody LaRue's the Butchugger. He's going to make you his Butchug brother.
His Butchug brother.
Man, I get so hyped for that song and I can't get my friends into it.
It makes me really sad.
This is why I need to abandon all my friends and just adopt you guys.
You all need to come here so I can hang out with you and sing about Butchugging.
Yeah, we all have...
I'm not sure it's worth having friends who don't know the Butchugger.
It seems like we all have our crosses to bear and mine is my family and yours is your friends, your IRL friends.
Yeah. Well, I don't think my friends are nearly as big a problem as your family is.
I don't know if you want to talk about that on here at all.
I don't know. I'm really protective about it, I guess, that aspect of my life because I don't want to seem like I'm whining.
It's that thing where I can say whatever the hell I want about my family, but as soon as somebody else tries to say something bad about them,
I get really protective and I want to beat people up because they don't fucking know.
It's the same way I approach my family.
You would say you don't hate your family, they just cause you most of the problems in your life.
Unnecessary grief.
My youngest sister is literally Zephyr Breeze for anyone who saw the newest My Little Pony episode.
I related so hard to that episode. It was so cool. I was so into it.
Eh, fuck them all.
But that's sort of, so you do live in a basement, right?
Yeah.
It is the basement of your mom's house, so much more literally than Jeff.
I think it's more accurate to say that she lives in my attic because I really fucking hate that.
I get that all the time.
He's in his mom's basement. This guy's the fucking basement. He lives at home.
Like, this fucking living at home stigma, I want to do a video about this so bad because it's a rant that needs to be spoken.
It's the most insane, illogical fucking stigma that we have in society. It makes me fucking sick of my stomach.
As Americans, specifically. It's weird.
Yeah.
Because the rest of the world usually lives with their parents.
Like, if you live in like an Asian country or something, typically you take over your parents' house and you just start paying for it.
Even people our age who don't live with their parents, they have fucking roommates. They have significant others.
They're all splitting the bills and the rent. Nobody is actually living on their own.
So it's such a fucking, like, pot con the kettle black to anyone who fucking looks down at you for living at home.
And by the way, I just want to throw this out there since we're on this topic.
The reason that I live at home, and I don't say this publicly because I like to keep my shit private,
but I'll go ahead and say it. I live at home because I support my entire fucking family.
So suck my ass.
You know, there's this, people say, living at home and it comes attached to this idea that you're a fucking,
that you're just laying around, that you're a freeloader, that they're supporting you.
Most, a lot of us support our families, okay?
I make the most money if anyone in my family because I'm fucking ambitious and the hardest worker I've ever known in my life
and I built the fucking empire on my own as an entertainer and an artist.
And I'm talented enough and charismatic enough to make a living off my art so that I can support my fucking family
and it really, really gets under my skin when I get that living at home stigma shit thrown at me.
It's one of my biggest pet peeves. In fact, as George Carlin would say, I don't have pet peeves.
I have psychotic fucking hatreds and that's one of them.
When people fucking say that to me, I want to lose my mind.
Fuck them.
I completely get where you're coming from, man.
Fake niggaz all looking at me like I don't know what I'm doing.
When I've been pulling salary for creativity since 2013 and I mean, when you see me, what do you think?
That guy's just crazy. He doesn't count. He's an outlier. Anomaly. Surely got lucky somehow.
Now, I'll be the first to admit, I've had some privileges, but I'm seeing all these kids like I ain't done shit.
You're just plugging your own EP right now.
You're gonna be on this song.
Look forward to me and Jess on the album Bedroom Bedrock coming sometime.
By the way, I made an entire album the other night when I got really fucking hammered.
Oh God. It's not like the hymn album, is it?
No, it's better than that. It's like an artistic statement almost.
Okay.
Because the other night I drank an entire bottle of Malibu rum.
I got excessively drunk. I was up all night.
And I did a freestyle rap. Then I did another one. Then I did another one.
I just got some beats offline off of some YouTube channels that make beats.
I did like four complete freestyle raps and these were legitimate freestyles.
Not one fucking second of it was written or rehearsed.
Just read all off the cuff and they're all incredible and hilarious.
I did them one after the other while I was completely fucking totally drunk.
And then to cap it off, I jotted down, still drunk mind you, still completely drunk off my ass.
I jotted down a guitar song and that closes out the album.
And it became weirdly emotional but also like movingly artistic.
I almost said autistic, but I said artistic. That's a very important distinction.
They mean the same thing.
It's not autism. It's artism that I suffer from.
We're all on the spectrum, man.
Yeah, the autism spectrum.
Yeah, I made a whole album the other night while I was drunk.
And then I did a drunk Let's Play.
And then I woke up the next morning and I had the worst hangover of my entire life.
And I vowed to never drink again for the rest of my life. It was horrible.
It was like...
Oh man.
You just reminded me of...
I don't know. Sometimes I feel like you have so many ideas that half of them I remember and you don't even.
So tell me if you remember this one, which was...
You wanted to make a talk show called What's Your Tism?
Yeah, I remember that. Now that you mentioned it, I remember it.
I thought that was the best fucking idea ever.
Yeah, where the point of the talk show was just that all the guests would come in
and everyone would talk about the thing that they are completely neurotic and autistic about.
Because everybody has that one thing.
Yeah.
I definitely think we're all somewhere.
That's a good idea. That's definitely something that we should still do someday.
Yeah, that would be cool.
One of the many ideas in The Endless just vaults that maybe someday we'll get made, but who knows.
If I'm not too busy making chair videos...
A lot of collab ideas that we're just like...
Well, we live too far away because the biggest one is The Plebe and The Weeb.
Which is a show that we wanted to do that's half in the bag but for anime.
But more aggressive and over the top, probably.
Yeah, and I want to go all out with it.
I want to build a set that is like a line down the middle of the room with different sets on each side.
Yeah.
That would be easy enough to do if we lived anywhere near each other.
Then the other idea was that after I started listening to Biggest Problem I had this idea,
the fans should vote at the end of every episode who was The Plebe and who was The Weeb.
Yeah, that's a great idea!
Oh!
I don't know if it would be a good idea to do this,
but on YouTube you can have it like hit like for this guy and dislike for the other guy.
I mean it would give us crazy dislike bars.
Yeah, I'd keep it in the comments I think because I get like a sick feeling seeing the red on that like bar.
Well, the gray.
Oh, is it gray now? God damn it.
They keep changing it.
It's been gray for quite a while now actually.
Well, I don't know because I never get any downvotes because all my videos are masterpieces.
Oh, man.
Well, to go back to the point we were making before I distracted us with that rap verse about living at home,
like yeah, I think there's like this weird idea that existed like 30 years ago of like, you know,
back when everyone left home at 18 and like maybe if you were still at home at 30 it was because like you...
And by the way, the reason they left, the reason everybody left home at 18 was because they got drafted into Vietnam
and then came back and didn't have a fucking home.
It had to fucking go hitchhiking down the freeway like Rambo with all their friends dying from age and orange cancer.
Like, you know, each of my parents kept like a, you know, they're like really surprised that me, Victor and Shay like didn't want to move out.
But like, because they both left home really early, but they were both from like dirt, poor, shitty...
Like my dad had to steal the eat and stuff when he was 18.
He joined the military literally for food and my mom was from a family of like six brothers and sisters with a single mom
and no moral compass whatsoever.
So she just like moved out when she was 16 and, you know, started living with other people.
And it's like, of course, if you raise like a loving family at a good home and you have a well-paying job, why the fuck would your kids want to leave?
Like you guys didn't leave because you were 18, you left because your lives were terrible, you know?
And it's like everybody I know who's my age lives at home and they're not unsuccessful, they're not unmotivated.
I have a friend who's a fucking published writer who's currently in grad school lives at home.
I have a friend who's a professional guitar teacher who fucking went to college for music shit and has a degree in shit lives at home.
You know, these are not fucking, these are not freeloaders. These are fucking adults.
These are motivated adults carving their own path in the world.
They just so happen to live at home because that's the smart thing to fucking do.
Yeah. I mean, I personally, I'm paying $500 a month for rent, mostly just as a sign, like, you know, of the fact that I'm doing work and contributing something to the house.
But the funny thing is, I mean, there's a lot of legitimate reasons to leave home.
If you don't like your parents and you fight all the time, get out of there, you know?
But like if you're supporting them and putting them up, it's a good reason to be there.
And the funny thing is my parents are now planning to leave the house to me and they're moving out.
So, so it's like, I would doubt like I'm who lives at home now, motherfucker.
Right. I want you freeloading parents out of my home.
Oh, they won't be freeloading. They'll probably still be helping me with the running it.
But they they're like, yeah, we know you guys have no reason to leave.
But, you know, we just want to go somewhere quiet and be alone kind of thing.
And like, but yeah, um, yeah, I don't I don't blame you at all, especially because I know that you, you know, you're helping to to pay for your family.
So it's like, it's like they're more reliant on you than you are on them.
So that's why you're there. And I know a lot of people like that. So I don't think it's weird.
But you do technically live in a basement. But it's a cool basement.
Yeah, that's the other thing. My basement fucking rules. Why would anyone not want to live in my basement?
Have you seen this fucking place? I got posters. I got a fucking TV. I got a fucking, I got pirate flags.
I got a couple Oscar statues. This place is a fucking paradise.
Yeah. And it just happens to be a weirdly amazing set for vlogs.
Because there's so every different angle of the room looks different because there's so many like chest high shelves and like weird bookcases and stuff and different poster arrangements.
And it's like every time you film it from a different angle, it feels like a totally different place.
And then you also change up the posters and that just makes it like dizzying sometimes.
It's like me and DeVue were always saying how we couldn't.
It really, the moment I finally got a good sense of the layout of your room was that vlog of you just squeegeeing water while the girl was recording you.
And that was the first time I like completely understood it. And I was like, oh, it's okay.
There's a separate room where the bookcase is. That's like a weird closet room or something.
And to go off on a weird tangent, because I just now reminded this, of all the sets in my room because I sort of have decorated my room for like, it's sort of segmented into sets for my different channels.
And there's like an anime corner. There's a wonderful waifu wall. There's a fucking man child incorporated corner.
And there's the bookcase in the other room with the fucking.
My favorite of the sets, which I haven't used in like years, is the set, the part of the corner where I filmed the like the Sim City and the Hello Kitty vlogs with that like sort of chest high shelf.
And the reason that I haven't filmed there is because I started filming in front of the bookcase for like some horse shoe review at some point, I think.
I think I started in the Grand Theft Auto review, but I started changing the posters around in there and I could never fuck.
It's that poster Tetris. I want to, I want to make a video about this topic too, because my entire life is poster Tetris, figuring out what goes where.
And for two fucking years, I haven't been able to get that corner the way that I wanted to.
And I just recently finally got exactly the right size poster, exactly what I want to fit in that little spot.
And right now the corner looks great. I'm just waiting for the right video to fucking go back to my corner and reveal it.
Because I hate the fucking bookshelf. Every video of me that I'm in front of that bookshelf, it just inherently feels pretentious and stupid to me.
It's my worst set, but it's like, it's just where I naturally tend to stand because it's where the shelf is like level for the camera to sit it on when I'm in a hurry.
So I end up making videos there. I hate that fucking bookshelf set.
I both agree and understand like the bookshelf is definitely my least favorite just because it's so like collapsing in on itself and just looks uneven and weird.
And that corner is my favorite one too because it's got two different shelves that are at different heights and it just makes it look really complicated.
And the worst part is they're right across from each other. So when I'm filming vlogs in the bookshelf, I'm looking at the cool corner and I'm fucking feeling I'm missing it.
And I'm feeling this longing for it, which just makes me so fucking angry and just adds fuel to the fire.
And that's why my vlogs are always so acrimonious. That's why everybody thinks I'm such an angry person.
I just feel a sense of loss for my corner.
See, I tried to do something similar when when I redesigned my room because like because DeVu told me at some point that he finds my room almost as confusing as yours just because I'll film from so many different angles.
So I was planning to do this thing where I was going to make like all these different micro sets and then film in front of all of them and like really make people wonder how big my room was.
Of course, I burst that bubble because I started doing all these vlogs and just showing the whole room.
But like what I the problem is they're too small. Like I put together a shelf of anime DVDs, but then when I sit in front of it, I block the whole shelf.
So like I have no one spot where there's a good wide angle to see like a bunch of shit. It just looks chaotic and random.
But like I just end up going with whatever is the easiest place to like, you know, oh, this shelf is convenient.
I'll throw a chair in front of it and put up a tripod and I'm done, you know.
So yeah, I get the bookcase thing.
How many like how much do you spend on the posters?
A lot. I think most of what I spend is because I I don't know like hmm.
I don't know trying to do the math. Can we just generally talk about your your buying habits which seem to be go out and just drop hundreds of dollars on whatever you see.
Here's the thing like because my family is such a drain on my finances, mostly from my sister, she has an illness that requires a lot of money all the time.
That's how I'll put it. So I just get a lot of my money drained. I like I constantly have to pay the rent.
I constantly have to pay the bills and shit, mainly because so much money goes to her.
So I've gotten into the habit over time of if I spend all of my money, nobody can take it from me.
Right. So it's just like my instinct, like it's like a paranoid because if I save my money, someone's going to get their paws on it eventually.
But if I go out and I see a bunch of like if I go if I like walk into a comic book store, you know, I go, well, I shouldn't spend all this money on comics.
But if I don't, I'm going to lose it anyways. Someone's going to take it from me.
So yeah, so it's my I might as well just, you know, I might as well blow all my money on comics.
And then when my family needs to borrow money, they can fucking borrow it from somebody else because I don't have the fucking money anymore.
I just have comics. Do you want to pay the rent with my comics? You can't do it. Can you motherfucker? I win. Checkmate.
Yeah, it's basically like an investment, except that you'll never get a return on it.
Yeah. But I don't know, I think it's like I understand the plan and I think it's a good idea, even though it sounds insane.
Like I get why you're doing that and I think it works.
Well, the upside to it is that because of what our job is, everything is a write off.
Yeah, that's the best part.
So I just I just go through life.
My my philosophy is I don't have to pay taxes.
I don't know if that's true, but I don't.
It's definitely not true.
Well, I believe that it's true.
Because I I mean, I don't know if I spend as much as you did on stuff I could write off last year, but I still had to pay a thousand dollars,
even after writing as much off as I could.
But yeah, no, I do the same thing.
We're like, I justify every purchase by like, well, this will be in the background of my video.
So this is part of my set.
So, you know, it's it's all justified like like that light novels video I did.
I went to Barnes and Noble and spent like $110 and then I came home and made a vlog about all the stuff I just bought just so I could write it off.
I have a I have a robot in my corner that I bought six months ago because I came up with a robot character for my videos.
And I haven't used it yet, but I'm going to someday.
And that's why she's a write off.
My robot.
I, uh, yeah, I've always loved that, though, that you spend so much and like on your like a lot of it on improving the videos or like,
because you'll buy a ton of new posters, not just because you want them, but because the video will be better by having those posters like,
like, um, and of course, horseshoe finale is like 18 different sets all built around like different characters and themes and stuff like that.
A normal person would spend $30 one time on a green screen and put whatever they want on it.
But I am no normal person.
Yeah, I like practical effects, practical sets.
Yeah, same here.
I mean, I've emulated that like the reason my walls are all covered in posters was like directly based on you,
because I loved so much that you had all these different like, you know, specific topic poster corners.
Unfortunately, all my posters are anime, so there's no way to make it feel particularly like that.
But I did like, for instance, near my bed is like all like girls in swimsuits.
And then like on the wall behind my couch is all like really dignified looking posters, like, you know, cool action show type stuff like that looks all serious.
And then there's like one corner that's like just Pokemon and Yu-Gi-Oh and like childish stuff, which is supposed to be like, I haven't really used that one,
but it's supposed to be like the infantilism corner essentially.
That's the baby bro corner.
Yeah, well, because it was going to be where I was going to have a shelf of My Little Pony and a shelf of Pokemon,
but I can never bring myself to actually put the My Little Pony shelf together as I talked about in the Insomnia Analysis 2 video,
just because like I feel I have such like mixed and mostly negative feelings about like the pony experience that I just don't even want to think about it anymore.
But like, yeah, I totally copied your idea of spend all my money on posters, put them everywhere, and it'll make my sets look cooler.
Because personally, I think green screen sets are lame and they're also hard to use. You have to really like those things.
Yeah, if you do green screen badly, everybody can tell.
Right, and me and you both live in rooms that are like too big to light.
They're just black holes. They're fucking, all our videos look dark. There's no way around it.
Yeah, so, all right, I got to think of more questions for you.
So, all right, the channel that you've been saying that you want to put focus on the most is My Japanese Animes.
Yeah.
How did that channel happen? Like, where did it come from?
Oh, fuck. Okay, I believe the first My Japanese Animes was in January of 2015 and it was the Bleacher View.
I think the dandy videos were out before that though.
Yeah, but it was during that time of November 2014 to June 2015 when I was working on Horseshoe Finale.
And in the meantime, between Magical Mystery Cure and Horseshoe Finale, I couldn't very well make more pony videos because that would have fucking ruined it.
But I had to make money somehow, so I had to find ways to keep making videos while also making Horseshoe Finale and one of the ways was to make My Japanese Animes and just have an anime channel.
And it came out amazingly because the Bleach video was like fucking awesome. It was one of my favorite videos you ever did.
I love all of them and you seem to have a different mentality about that channel that every video has to be tight and complete.
My Japanese Animes is my YouTube channel. It's my best channel if you're looking for a YouTube channel because I don't really consider Endless Jess a YouTube channel at all.
Endless Jess is just my fucking clubhouse and you're there by special invitation and so you better obey the rules or I'll kick you out.
And Man Child Incorporated is another thing. I sort of have a different philosophy behind all of my channels and how I approach the content when I make them on there.
And that's why they're separate and what keeps them interesting because I take those gimmicks seriously.
It was kind of a reversal on the original intent because for a long time Drowning in Footwear was the main channel and it was supposed to be mostly big videos.
And then you would routinely hide the vlogs because you would do like a month with a bunch of vlogs and then you'd feel upset that they were on your main channel and then sort of hide them all.
But then at some point it was like a switch flip and you went fuck it Endless Jess is now the everything channel.
And the reason that I do that I get into these periods of just doing like weird vlogs on Endless Jess there is a philosophy behind it and there's a plan behind it.
I always know what I'm doing people. I'm always 10 steps ahead of you. I'm always 10 steps ahead of myself.
The reason is that Endless Jess has a problem and that problem is videos going viral.
I can't fucking stop it from happening. It happens when I least expect it to usually the worst possible videos that could possibly go viral are the ones that do like fuck updates
or Batman v Superman the best review. Those videos get the norm that video get it has a lot of views. It's got over 10,000 views.
And those videos get the normie views and normies see those videos and they flock to my channel and they subscribe expecting like YouTube content.
And then inevitably they don't understand what they're subscribed to and they leave asinine stupid comments that piss me off and they downvote my videos.
Because they're they just expect some kind of fucking YouTube channel of a guy screaming in front of a bookcase about movies every week and that's not what it's going to be.
So because I get so many normie subscribers that I don't fucking want who aren't going to get it who are just going to be a burden and a drain on my channel.
I routinely I'll go okay I'm going to make really really stupid videos for like three weeks straight and I'm going to shake off some of these subscribers.
And anyone who doesn't get it is going to unsubscribe and the people who stay subscribed are going to be the ones that I know get it.
And that's sort of how I cull the herd and keep things that you know I keep the normies out as best I can because otherwise they just infest it.
I mean if you look at fucking any big YouTuber who doesn't moderate their comment section which is another reason I moderate is because they all become a fucking sea of poison.
If you look at Anthony Fantano's comment section for example.
Holy shit and it's just memes people saying stupid shit and what that is it's the normie views those fucking normie subscribers.
If you don't keep them in check they will turn your entire channel into poison.
I think it's amazing that Fantano like ever reads or responds or has any opinions about his comments when they're as bad as they are.
Like I mean I get upset over bad comments but my comment sections are still by and large pretty good because everyone knows I read them.
And it's usually the people who are like you said it's the new people who don't get it and who leave like the shitty comments.
It blows my mind that you wouldn't moderate it because I view my videos sort of my videos on my art and the comments are on the video which means that the comments are a part of the art.
So if your comment is not worthy of being on my art then it's just going to be weighing it down for people.
You know when I fucking watch a YouTube video and I scroll down and I see shitty comments I like the video less it's annoying.
I don't usually read comments on other people's videos unless I'm really curious how people reacted to it but then like you said if it's like a Fantano video then it's incomprehensible fucking nonsense anyways.
It's always just like people asking for the next review of the other thing.
Like if I paint a painting and they hang my painting up in a museum and somebody stands in front of my painting and starts jacking off.
It's ruining the experience for everybody else who's trying to see the painting.
That's why he has to be tased by security and escorted off the premises.
Yeah I think we both pretty much agree on that.
We covered most of it in the commenter rules so I don't want to get too far down the comment hole but we both...
That's what it's called. It's not a comment section. It's a comment hole.
I think you and I both had this experience where we... I don't know if you thought this going in but I thought that doing commenter rules would help to put some of it behind me.
And instead it made me way angrier about comments.
It only made the fire stronger. It kindled that fire big time.
Yeah you were saying in the chat recently that you think us doing this podcast has made you an angrier and worse person.
And I feel like it's done the same thing to me because every time we bitch about people then I start thinking about that more and more.
Like the things that annoy us about people like I'll go out into the world and see it happening and be like ahhh.
You know didn't we just talk about this?
Well people would complain about the PCP podcast being clusterfuck and us all talking over each other and yelling over each other.
And my defense of that was well come on haven't you ever been at like a family Thanksgiving?
That's how we talk in my family and that was my defense of it but then I remembered oh wait I hate that about my family.
I've always hated that. Shit.
And now it's like I'm in Thanksgiving with my family every week with you fucking guys.
Every week I have to sit down and I have to steal myself for the onslaught the avalanche that's coming towards me.
Of everyone trying to get a word in edge wise and nobody succeeding at it.
And everything I say you know it creates this pressure and this stress on every idea that comes into your head.
Because everything you want to say you know that you have to say it forcefully and quickly or else you're not going to be able to finish it.
And that makes it ten times harder to articulate what you're trying to say.
So nobody is being able to say what they actually want to say and nobody is listening to what anyone else is saying.
So it just becomes a fucking a cesspool. It's like it's 4chan in audio form.
You know honestly I think it's all Nate's fault and I think we have to have an intervention about it.
Because like lately because I kept getting so much shit from people telling me that I was interrupting other people all the time.
That like eventually I started to reflect on it and like really be like okay maybe I interrupt people more than I realize.
Maybe it's a problem. So I've been trying to like really curb it back and not interrupt people.
But when you I realized this on like the sleep podcast because I really thought I wasn't going to have anything to say about that.
But the few times I did I realized that if Nate will always talk it doesn't matter if he has an idea.
It doesn't matter if he has something to say. He will talk.
Damn Digi I could almost kiss ya.
So if you don't get your ideas in there if you don't force them in Nate will talk.
And so you have to be forceful. You have to wedge it in and poor DeVue.
Like DeVue tries because in the early days he wouldn't get a word in because he wasn't cutting people off viciously enough.
But now he cuts people he cuts in so hard and it makes him hard.
Like it sounds like he's being way too serious and it just makes you like gloss over his point.
I think the whole thing is I think the whole it's an anger factory for all of us.
We're all just everybody always sounds completely pissed off by the end.
Like I'm never I am never as pissed off as I am immediately upon entering that podcast.
It's like it's like an aura to it. There's like an atmosphere that just gets into my skin.
Well the worst part is like because we tried after like with the Dark Souls one.
The idea was we were trying to scale back and do what more that were like three people.
And then the last two we did like Nate kept going like hey who else wants to be in and I'm like no.
Because it was not not the sleep one but the one before that where we had like six people in there and he like at messages you.
Hey Jesse want to be in the podcast. I'm like no he doesn't want to be in the podcast.
There's six fucking people in here. He's going to get pissed off and that's within minutes.
Jeff made you leave out of sheer rage.
That was that was by the way that was real. That was not like a skit that I had planned or anything.
No I literally like two minutes into the podcast.
Jeff made me so angry that I fucking got up and had to like storm around my kitchen for a while.
And then I just left the house and I just like I have to go to a walk.
I left the fucking recording on the podcast was still going on.
I just went outside and went for a walk and I went around the block and as I was coming back.
I see my secretary miss Jezameen Jezebel sitting there in her car and I'm like what are you doing here.
And she's like well I came to hang out and I'm like OK let's go back in the house so I can tell these guys I hate them and leave the podcast forever.
It was great because you sent me your audio recording and it's like two minutes of dialogue and then just this long like 30 minute silence.
And that was the whole recording of the first part and then like there was a separate recording for the Jezebel part.
But like you can I can hear you like when I listen back to it I can hear you leaving like all the audio of you leaving the house was in there.
It was fucking great.
Yeah I don't know it's it's weird for me because I have been talking to you for so long and I so approve of you and your art.
That you don't phase me with that kind of stuff anymore.
And I think there's a lot of people who legitimately can't handle that.
You know like do you remember when I had you on the pub crawl one time and you got into like this big fight with some of the other co-hosts.
One of one of them was being a huge gay lord.
I don't know which one Mr. Jeffrey Berger or whoever his name is.
Yeah you got into this fight with them and it got really legitimately awkward.
And like all I could think was like man I'm used to like Jesse's argument style which is that everyone else is wrong and that's all that matters.
You know like I think for you it always seems like proving yourself right comes later.
It's that I don't like being in arguments.
I hate arguing which means that when I get into an argument the fact that I'm in the argument makes me angry which makes the argument worse.
So it's a self-perpetuating cycle of rage that once I'm trapped in there's no getting out.
It's all or nothing.
We're going down in flames and I'm taking everyone with me.
See like I've put it to people like Jesse the Jesse Wood argument style is that you do know somewhere in your mind you know why you're mad and how to articulate it but that doesn't come out first.
What comes out first is no fuck you you're wrong.
I'm right.
And it takes about five minutes of that before you will then articulate it in a way that the other person like gets it.
And then they'll be like well why didn't you say that from the beginning and you're like I did say that just a simplified version of that because you didn't have the articulate version.
I hate about the Internet because I hate verbally sparring with people like right in real life.
I'm like kind of an incredibly violent person like I immediately like I have a line and everyone who crosses it I immediately want to fucking punch everybody.
Like if I'm standing in a store like if I like four teenagers so much as walk by me I instinctively my hands are in fist and I'm just waiting for them to fucking say something.
I know they're gonna fuck with me.
I'm gonna kill them all.
And then they keep walking and they don't do anything to me.
I'm like you sons of bitches you deliberately trying to make a fool out of me.
I see how it is.
I can't remember if you shared the whole straight out of Compton story on the podcast.
Did we tell it on the podcast before?
I don't know.
It seems like I've told that story a bunch but I don't know where I've told it.
Well you can't get enough of it if you want to tell it again.
It's fucking great.
We were seeing straight out of Compton me and my friends and there were these fucking teenagers sitting right behind us.
It's always teenagers.
Teenagers are human cancer.
They should not exist.
They should be put in prison until they're 25 all of them.
I was, you know, we're watching the movie and these fucking teenagers were talking during the entire fucking movie.
Making stupid jokes.
Not even making jokes.
Just talking.
Just fucking being teenagers.
And my friend asked them to shut up.
Or she asked them politely to stop talking.
Like two or three times throughout the movie and they wouldn't.
And then like eventually it gets to the part where like EZE is dying of AIDS.
And it's this emotional part of the movie and everybody's crying.
You know, it's like, it's the emotional crux of the movie.
And these fucking kids are back there and they're giggling and chuckling and laughing.
And I finally just, I turned around and I said shut the fuck up.
And like the whole theater kind of applauded and snickered.
And they shut up for a while.
And you know, everyone was, you know, all my friends were like, yeah, that was cool, yeah.
So we watched the rest of the movie in peace.
And I knew that it wasn't over.
Like I had a feeling in my gut because I've gotten myself into these situations many times in my life.
And I know when it's not over.
So the credits are rolling and everyone's filing out of the movie theater.
And I know these kids are gonna fucking kick my seat.
Or they're gonna try to start something.
And when they do, it's gonna be the last mistake they ever fucking make.
And so I'm sitting there and I'm waiting for them to do something.
And I'm sure that they didn't realize that I was waiting for them to do something.
They thought they could get the drop on me, but they don't know who I am.
So I'm sitting there, fists balled up.
I'm fucking, I'm as intense as a fucking cocaine-addled macho man promo.
I'm ready to fucking ignite at any minute.
And it fucking happens.
This kid dumps his entire popcorn bucket on my head
and thinks that he can get up fast enough and get out fast enough.
And I shot up like fucking lightning.
As soon as I felt that shit going over my head, I fucking shot up
and I fucking leaped over the seats and I grabbed him
and I fucking punched him right in his fucking temple.
I hope I did permanent damage. I hope he's dead.
I have no fucking remorse for this whatsoever.
I fucking punched him right in the skull like two or three times.
And he fucking, he kept trying to go and I was fucking chasing him out to like where the stairs were.
And I fucking, the last punch that I landed on him, I punched him in the head so hard
that my fist sent his head flying into the wall of the staircase.
So like I punched him and it bounced off the wall.
It was like, it was like two hits for one.
It was like a fucking, like a pinball machine.
And he's fucking, he's fucking running around.
Oh my, everyone's screaming.
The whole fucking theater is watching this.
And by the way, the whole time that this is happening, it's the credits.
So straight out of Compton, the song is playing.
Fucking NWA is blasting.
It's the soundtrack to me beating the shit out of this teenager.
And he's fucking running.
And then his fucking fat, lard ass girlfriend is like, what the fuck are you doing?
He's only 13 years old.
And I fucking got right in your face and I'm like, I'll fucking hit you too, you fat bitch.
Get out of my face. Get out of my theater.
And they fucking go.
And then, so they run out of the theater and I calmly, I fucking like straighten my shirt
and I walk back to my friends and I just say, we should probably go right now.
We should probably go out the, out the side exit.
We should, we should get in our cars now.
We just fucking left.
And it was, it was a proud moment.
It was a great moment.
I have no regrets and no remorse.
I hope he, I hope that fucking kid, I hope he hasn't had a decent night's sleep since.
I hope it, I hope my face haunts his every nightmare.
I hope he went to school with a bunch of, with like eight black eyes all over his face.
And I hope all the other kids, I hope word got around his school of what happened
and he's getting made fun of to this day for it.
Fuck him.
I hope he killed himself.
You know, I love that story, but there's only, there's one detail I just realized is weird.
Why did he still have so much popcorn left?
Like who finishes a movie and hasn't finished their popcorn?
Some, some faggot, some teenager.
No fucking skinny ass tiny stomach, can't fucking fit his popcorn.
You'd think his, you'd think his lard ass girlfriend would have, would have finished it off for him.
But I guess she was too busy fucking, sucking strange dick in the bathroom.
I don't know.
She was too full of cum.
Yeah.
I, I think I want to address to the audience that like, I think more than any of the other members of the, the PCP at least,
you have probably the biggest like, how do I put this?
Like on and off camera, like is pretty different.
Like even though you, you definitely like a, you know, not to say that anything you're doing on camera is like not real or not really what you're like,
but like, you're much more in your own head and quiet and like, um, like when I hang out with you, you're not constantly ranting like, like you're on camera.
It's more like concentrated bursts of when you have an idea to rant about.
Whereas hanging out with me in real life is legitimately, I never shut the fuck up.
It's exactly like it is on camera.
Do you feel that there's like a big difference to you between like on and off when you're a,
I'm definitely, I'm definitely quieter off camera or more, um, pensive, I guess, or aloof.
I don't know.
I don't know. Maybe it's because I'm so on when I'm on camera that I've become even more, you know, decompressing when I'm off camera.
Because I value, I value being off camera because it's to me, it's important.
I don't know if that makes sense.
Well, I know you, you like to have like a private life.
That's not the, like, like for me, there's very little that I don't talk about on like Digi Bros. or in my vlogs.
You know, like, it's almost like every emotion I have.
Although I don't talk as much about like my stresses or negative emotions because I just think it would be kind of annoying.
But like, I think you have a lot more value in doing something that nobody hears about and is just something you got to do.
Um, would you say so?
Yeah, I, uh, and lately, like, I make an effort.
I have to kind of force myself to do things without recording it at this point because it's become such a habit of if I play a video game,
I should be recording it in case I say something funny.
If I have a thought that I should film a vlog or I should be, I should be creating something right now.
I should be making a rap song or something.
So I kind of have to force myself to just shut out the world and make myself not be turned on or not be in fucking entertainment mode
and just enjoy myself by myself or like hang out with friends.
I never hang out with friends not because I don't want to, just because I'm always focused on creating stuff
and I don't think to call anybody or hang out with anybody.
Yeah, I have the same problem.
That's why I was saying, like, uh, that I need a hobby on Twitter the other day because I'm like, I,
everything I do is either, like, in service of making a video or it is a video, you know,
with the exception of, like, going out to eat and stuff like that.
And it's like, I need something to do that's not immediately relevant to that.
But I don't have it.
It's weird because, um, in my, uh, in my videos, there's like a difference in anger in my videos
because in my videos, it seems like I mostly get mad at stuff, at things, like computers or whatever.
In real life, I mostly get mad at people and, you know, just random, you know, bad luck doesn't really bother me.
If I'm, like, I'll be in situations where, like, there's a flat tire or everyone's stranded somewhere.
Like, some horrible disaster happens and we're stuck in the rain and everyone else is always freaking out.
And that stuff never phases me. Like, I'm totally aloof. I'm always making jokes because, to me, that's just a story.
Everything that happens to me is some funny anecdote that I can talk about later.
And so, I'm not bothered by stuff that happens.
But when it comes to people, um, I'm always kind of on edge.
I'm always paranoid because I just, I guess it's the way that I grew up.
I'm always, um, I'm just used to getting fucked with and used to having to fight and used to fucking, so...
I know you've had a lot of, like, for whatever reason, the police don't like you.
Oh, yeah. Well, I grew up in a fucking, a very hodunk, white trash, very small town.
And the thing about small towns is the cops are fucking bored.
And when the cops are bored, they fuck with everyone.
And they especially fuck on poor kids who don't look the way that they think kids should look.
Yeah.
And, uh, so, I was always getting fucked with.
You were always, like, long-haired, uh...
Yeah.
Like, surfer slash pirate guy.
Yeah, I always had long hair. I always had a leather jacket on.
So the cops just, like, pull you over and, like, hassle you for no fucking reason?
Yeah. They always thought that I was fucking stealing something.
They always thought that I was, you know, up to no good.
They always thought that I had drugs on me.
They always thought that I was a fucking stoner.
Even though I didn't look like a stoner, that's the thing that bothers me.
Nobody knows what a stoner looks like or sounds like.
Because they would look at me, oh, long hair, leather jacket, that kid's on drugs.
I never touched a fucking drug in my life.
The kids who were smoking weed were the fucking skinny kids in the tank tops and the beanie hats
walking around doing this.
Yeah.
That's their fucking mating call.
That's what they all sound like.
Yeah, to clarify for the audience, um,
you have not, until very recently,
have never been high in a video because you hate weed.
I hate weed probably.
I say this about everything, but it's definitely up there among the things I hate most in the fucking world.
I can't stand it. I can't stand the smell of it.
I can't stand other people smoking it around me.
It just brings my fucking piss to a boil.
Generally not a drug guy at all.
Yeah, something about it. I have like this vast psychological aversion, this hatred of marijuana.
Yeah.
But you do drink, but not as much as people think probably.
Oh, yeah, finish that story.
Yeah, recently I got very, very high for the first time in my life, not from smoking anything,
but because my secretary, Jezameen Jezebel,
she was like, hey, look what I got.
This is pot candy.
This is a nerd rope, but there's marijuana in it.
It doesn't make you really high.
And I'm like, no, it won't.
Shut up.
And I ate it.
And she's like, I'm warning you.
I'm warning you.
Only eat half of it.
And I ate the whole thing.
I'm like, shut up.
I'll eat the whole thing.
I don't care.
I'm strong.
And yeah, so I ate the whole thing.
And then I started time traveling.
Yeah.
Then I became the fucking master of the universe.
I don't know.
I was just sitting there.
I listened to a few albums whilst time traveling.
I fucking surfed through the galaxies.
The channel art for Endless Jez became my actual life in that moment.
It was me surfing the cosmos on an electric guitar.
And then I got on fucking online and started just completely seducing women.
Like my fucking powers were out of control that night.
My powers of seduction.
It was cool.
By which I mean it was terrifying and never ever again.
Yeah.
That's exactly because I got high for the first time on Christmas and it was a waking
nightmare.
I jacked off six times.
Yeah.
Me too.
What the fuck?
I actually had to go to bed just because my dick hurt from jacking off.
Yeah.
My winner was sore for like three days.
I was like, what is this doing to me?
I just assumed because it hurt the next day and I was like, Jesus, I guess because I had
no self-control because I was too high to know how to use my body.
I guess because of the time travel that was going on, my hand was connected to the speed
force.
Bury down with electricity shooting out of it, burning like fucking, burning through dimensions.
I had my own flash point.
I fucking, I erased people from existence and changed the very fabric of reality.
By coming on them.
Yeah.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
It's all right.
My cock became a Gurren Lagondrill.
I don't remember if I was going to go anywhere else with that.
So all right.
I want you to, you turned 26 this year, right?
Yeah.
Last year, last July, it's coming up.
Okay.
So your birthday is about to happen.
I'm going to be 27 in about a month.
You sound very upset about it.
I am very fucking upset about it.
It's the most upsetting thing in the world.
We're going to die, Digi.
We're all going to die.
There's nothing after you realize that.
Can you imagine non-existence?
No, you can't imagine it and we're getting closer to it every second.
Well, Jesse, thankfully I have religion and my religion is the singularity where I get
my brain inside a computer.
That's my religion.
It's what keeps me going.
My only goal in life is to live longer than the people younger than me.
Yeah, that's a good goal.
So you're the second oldest member of the PCP.
I think Tom's the second oldest.
I think Tom's the oldest.
He might be already 27.
But anyway, I want to get a picture because obviously you haven't been doing YouTube ever
since whatever you were doing before it.
You graduated high school.
Yeah.
And you went to college for a while.
What were you doing in college?
I don't know what I was doing in college and I didn't know what I was doing there when
I was there.
That's why I eventually stopped going.
How long did you go for?
I think I went for four or five years?
Long time.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Was it like community college?
It was a community college.
I majored in everything.
I got a degree in nothing.
That's how mine went.
I understand.
I think around 2012, I dropped out of that school and I started going to Spex Howard,
which is like a video editing school.
I went there for one semester and I really liked it there.
I would have completed that course except that it was like an hour and a half drive away
from my house twice a week.
Eventually I had enough of that shit so I stopped going to that too.
Luckily around that time, I was starting, I guess the next year I started drawing horseshoes
and started making Patreon money so I didn't have to fucking.
In the meantime, I worked like crappy jobs.
I worked at a cyber cafe at nights and stuff and I did farm work all the way through high
school.
Ben mentioned that in the last podcast because I was trying to figure, I was trying to remember
what everybody else did for jobs.
You said through high school you did farm work?
Through high school and right up until like I was about 23, I guess, I was doing, I worked
on a farm that was run by my friend's mom, a fucking sheep farm and a fucking, yeah,
it was terrible.
It sucked.
What did you do on a farm in all that time?
Oh god, everything.
Like a lot of like bailing hay, stacking it in big piles and moving it around, barns and
shit, which is fucking grueling and horrible and no one should ever do it.
Why did they let you do that in high school?
Oh yeah.
It's gotta be some, was this like under the table work I'm taking it?
Yeah, we were all paid in cash.
I mean, it wasn't like a, we sort of fell into it because like it was my friend's house.
Let's go hang out with my friend.
Oh, by the way, while you kids are here, these sheep need to be herded and shorn and this
hay needs to be stacked and eventually somehow that turned into an actual job and like,
okay, you're all my workers now and fucking, yeah, so that became like a job and we all
fucking lived there.
It was like a sort of a second home.
Like for a while, like I had two homes.
Like there's like my house house and my friend's house and I would just travel between them
down the road and it was cool.
It was kind of like living on like a hippie commune with my friends and like I look back
on those days with a lot of fondness just because like it's in the past and you were
just me and you were a child and everything was good.
I definitely would not say that I was happy.
Okay.
I was, there were some times that I was pretty miserable, but like just the fact that I was
miserable with my friends and that we were always together and they were always around
me is something that I don't have anymore because now I live a very solitary existence
and by choice, I hate people.
I'm completely misanthropic.
I never want to be around anyone, but I also can look fondly on being around everyone.
If you were around them enough, you would get completely sick of them.
Yeah.
I know for a fact.
So that's where a lot of my oldest inside jokes came from is that time that I still use
on my channels like the Donatello thing.
Right.
Donatello was, I wanted to ask about that because you have all these characters who like recur
all the time.
Oh, they're not just characters.
There's a lore.
We have an entire backstory.
There's an entire universe of this shit that we have been creating since like the first
years of high school because we started doing fucking Vegeta impressions and then we started
doing Goofy and then we started doing Donatello and then we started doing Dingo, which is
such an obscure character.
He's from Disney's Gargoyles.
He's the Australian member of the pack with the Mohawk.
Nobody fucking remembers Dingo, but we did Dingo.
Dingo was one of our guys.
He has a dome.
He has many wives.
He's a polygamist.
And you know, Goofy has dinner parties every week.
All the friends go there.
Godzilla's there.
Shaggy's there.
Scooby's there.
Everyone.
The whole gang and Mickey's there.
Nobody really likes Mickey, but he shows up uninvited.
You know, Donald's there.
Everybody's afraid of Donald because Donald has the worst temper.
You know, he really beats people up.
And for the longest time, Goofy and Vegeta were mortal enemies.
They were bitter rivals.
They were always locked in mortal combat because they were the most powerful guys.
Nobody's stronger than Goofy when he gets angry, but Vegeta's super strong too.
You know, he's a super saint.
So Goofy and Vegeta, they would lock horns all the time.
They would have these great epic battles all across the country, but eventually they became
the best of friends.
It was like fucking Dharmak and Jalad at Tanagra.
It was like fucking Gilgamesh and then Ketu.
They became like brothers.
And to this day, they're the best of friends.
But then fucking Donald shows up.
Donald is a fucking loose cannon.
He's out of control.
He has the worst temper of all.
And he's so fucking powerful.
He kicks everybody's ass.
So Goofy and Vegeta are constantly afraid of Donald.
And you know, sometimes, you know, Donald has the secret stash of 80s drugs.
And one time, Goofy and Vegeta, they raided his closet.
Donald doesn't know about this.
I hope he doesn't listen to this podcast.
He's really mad.
But they got into the closet.
They raided his stash of 80s drugs.
Vegeta and Goofy got on the 80s drugs.
That was a whole fucking thing.
And you know, they had such a fucking wild adventure.
That's why Dingo stays out of it a lot of time.
You know, Dingo stays in his dome now because he's kind of over the hill.
He can't handle the wild partying ways of Goofy and Vegeta when they're on those damn 80s drugs.
They go fucking crazy.
And then Donald tells us just a fucking psychotic asshole.
He's the worst guy ever.
What fascinates me is that you've been writing these characters into your videos all this time.
And no one knows why.
And not even in a way where I think people are questioning it.
Like they probably just don't even realize there's anything to that.
You know, like Man Child Marsh had like almost all these guys in it.
And they talk like they do in your story.
And that's why in Horseshoe Finale, when I'm doing the CM Punk part,
that part where CM Punk turns to the camera and goes,
Hi Colt Cabana, how you doing?
I did that part and the original line was going to be,
Hi Colt Corona, how you doing?
That's essentially why Colt Corona was created.
But at the last minute when I was making Horseshoe Finale,
I realized it would make more sense because of what the video became to me,
that I should go back even farther.
So the line became, Hi Vegeta, how you doing?
Because Vegeta was the first.
He was like the first character that set me down this wacky path of creativity, I guess.
So that was a little nod to that.
Yeah, it's interesting.
I feel like I wonder if anybody has ever questioned,
because you do these impersonations of the characters,
but again, they're not based on the characters from the shows.
They're based on your interpretations of them from this story.
So Vegeta in a Jesse video is not Vegeta from Dragon Ball Z.
Well, it's weird because when it started,
it was sort of just a straight impersonation.
And it was like in character as a TV show,
but over time he stopped being,
he became so much of like my thing,
that there was like character development that went on.
And he became the Vegeta that we now know,
who's like sort of a lazy, underachieving,
kind of fucking surfer bro who doesn't give a shit about anything.
Donna Tello is my favorite though.
And you originally did have,
I'm mad that this video is not up anymore,
unless it was taken down the one with just how Donna Tello is insane.
Like, you had collected all the scenes of Donna Tello
and all the Turtles movies,
and it was just a video of him being fucking insane.
And like, I think that video,
I never thought, I never realized how crazy Donna Tello was.
Where I started doing Donna Tello was when James Rolfe did
his Angry Video Game Nerd video on Turtles 3, the movie,
because it's the stupidest of the trilogy.
He kept pointing out all of these scenes that are like,
this is the dumbest line ever in a movie.
This is so stupid.
But the thing that he was missing,
that I realized, all of those scenes were Donna Tello.
All of those dumb lines were him.
And so then I watched,
I started watching all the movies back to back,
and I watched the third one, and I realized,
because the original Turtles movies,
Donna Tello is a smart one.
He's the guy who does machines in the cartoon.
But the movies didn't really have a place for that
in the narrative.
They didn't have a lot of him doing computer stuff
or working on machines.
For a while in the first movie,
he works on a truck with Casey, but that's about it.
He doesn't really do machines in the movies.
So I guess how they compensated for that
was to just make him the oddball of the group
and make him so fucking weird.
And everything that Donna Tello says in those movies
is the most insane thing you've ever heard
in your fucking life.
Yeah.
It's like,
I think I swallowed a frog.
I hope it wasn't an ancestor.
I love stuff.
It's a legarama shooing.
Someone in our comments has caught on
that I love stuff is a meme among the procrastinators.
And that's entirely just because
of your Donna Tello impressions.
Because we met at BronyCon
and we were all doing, like, me and you kept going.
The best one is, yeah.
Yeah!
Which is just, that is a Donna Tello line.
Yeah, that's not a Tello.
It's from the second movie,
which was the only movie where he was not voiced
by Corey Feldman,
which is why he sounds different in the second movie.
This is some very important turtle's trivia.
Corey Feldman only played Donna Tello
in the first and third movie.
In the second movie, he was played by a different guy.
So while he sounds different,
he is still the same interpretation of the character.
He is still insane.
Yeah! Yeah!
He's in like a toy store
and there's like this giant, like,
one of those dolls that just like
goes back and forth and he like pushes it
and it goes back and he catches it
and then he pushes it again and he's like,
Yeah! Yeah!
And then he gets the idea to become that guy
and he like, he starts leaning back and forth
to like disguise himself as that inflatable guy
and it totally fools the foot ninja
and he starts fucking with him and beating him up.
It's hilarious.
Like the best thing that we ever did,
like what really cemented Donna Tello
as like a part of my fucking haul of heroes
was when I was way back in the fucking commune farm
where I used to fucking live and work with all my friends,
whenever we weren't working,
we were in the basement playing video games
and hanging out and stuff
and we had like three TVs in the basement.
We would all play like Gears of War
or Halo System Link or whatever
and one time, me and my friend Dylan,
we had all three Turtles movies.
We had three DVD players.
We had three TVs.
So I wonder what happens if we turn on
all three Turtles movies at once
and just sit in the middle and absorb it
and we played all three movies at once
and we fucking laid there on the futon together as lovers
in the middle of these three TVs
absorbing this triforce of power
and the fucking love of the Turtles
and Donna Tello was like going into us
and we laid there for the entire duration of the movies
for the whole things just like
vegging out to this insane cacophony of Turtles.
I'm glad that's caught on now.
Vegging out, I love it.
And there were like moments when like
one of my other friends who was so outside of work
and like he walked in the room like
hey guys, do you have a...
What the fuck?
Like he was laying there in the middle
of like the three Turtles movies
and just fucking closed the door
and walked out and just fucking
he just left.
And that was one of the greatest moments of my life.
Oh, that's great.
That might be where I got my powers from.
Alright, so to move ahead a bit from that
again I feel like there's a lot of stuff in your videos
that because I've known you for so long
I get and I feel like no one else can
get because they haven't been.
And that's one of them because we...
the procrastinators have kind of adopted those memes
because...
What happened? What's going on?
What do you mean?
I'm in a void.
Can you hear me?
You cut out for like 30 seconds there, buddy.
That was scary. I thought that was the end of the world.
Oh, Jesus.
Did it just happen again?
It keeps happening.
This is madness.
What's going on?
What is my life?
Am I here now?
I don't know what happened. It just disconnected for no reason.
What? Am I here?
Holy shit.
Alright, so anyway, I was saying...
I can't tell if you're really here or not.
Can you hear me right now?
You're not here.
Oh my fucking god.
What is happening?
What is this nightmare?
Oh my god.
Help!
Alright, uh...
Jesse.
Jesse?
I broke discord again.
Sorry, guys.
I was messing around with the triotubes.
And I broke the audio transistor.
Yes.
I love podcasts.
Hey!
I was saying how...
like, we...
the other PCP members,
we all, like, found out
about this whole lore
of all these characters.
And so we're all in on the joke now, too.
So that's why it's so surreal to me
when I see something like Man Child Marsh
and I'm like, no one gets this, but us!
You know, like, yeah.
I don't know.
And another one is
to sort of seg you into...
or segue, if you want,
into talking about more of your history
of how you
got started on YouTube.
You originated from
that guy with the glasses forums, right?
Oh, yeah.
I had almost blacked that out of my memory.
So what got you into that
and how and where did it go?
Um, it was just...
it was just...
when I started making videos,
that was what was
the popular thing.
That was kind of, like,
considered, I guess, the big boys' club.
Um, so...
I started hanging out in that forum
because that forum had, like,
a Your Video Review section
where people would post their stuff.
And, um,
no real effect to it
because it was just people posting
their own shit and, you know,
the only people who ever watched your stuff
were the same fucking people who hung out on the forums
all the time, so it was pretty worthless.
And, um, if you can imagine
the kind of
content creators who would hang out
on those forums, imagine
that guy with the glasses,
but worse, somehow more
amateur than that guy with the glasses.
Right.
Because it was, like, in those days,
there was no, like,
there was nothing to compare to.
You realize just how amateur everyone is
on that fucking website.
Like, even the big names, they're fucking terrible
video makers, and they haven't evolved.
They're still making the same trash
they were five fucking years ago,
and the people on the forum
were, like, the fanboys of that,
so they were even fucking worse.
And there were only a few diamonds in the rough,
and you pretty much,
Digi, you know all of them
because there were the friends
that I made on there. It was
Digi, and, uh, Johnny Old School,
who isn't really a YouTube person anymore,
but he was a pretty good one back in the day.
Um, we became friends really quick,
and, uh, the Cinemacicist,
we became good friends, I really liked his videos,
I still really do, he's got a great channel,
and, um, Aiden from the
Examined Life of Gaming.
And we were, like, we were the horseshoe crew
of those forums, and we were the best guys,
we were the only people on there
worth a damn, we hated everybody else,
so much so that eventually I just stopped
going there entirely, and also when I
fell out of love with the whole concept of whatever
that site does. So fuck it.
Yeah. So, like,
what, what era,
uh, like,
the last video you would have posted
to the forums, what do you think it would have been?
Like, when are we looking at for the time frame of this?
I think, uh,
it would be around,
I'm pretty sure you just cut out again,
but I'm gonna keep talking as though you haven't.
I think it was around,
oh god damn it, this annoys me, this is freaking me out.
I think, I think I'm here.
Oh, there you are.
I don't think I said anything else after you,
when you said that. Well, I could, god damn it,
I feel like it keeps, I can, I can tell
when it's like the dead air where nothing
is being recorded. Are you sure?
Okay, now you're back.
Go ahead
and continue. Okay, um,
I don't know, I think the last video that I really
remember posting there, it might have been
Altered Beast, I think that was in
like 2013 or, was it,
I don't even fucking, so that'd be pretty early.
Yeah, I did that in like the Silent Hill Downpour
review, I know that I posted there,
and that was in 2012.
So,
so yeah, so you, you were only there
for, not
too long, but you made those friends
and then, all of them,
I am assuming left as well.
Yeah, I got everything
decent out of there that I could,
which was the few friends that I made there
and then we took our talent elsewhere.
And I'd say the, at the time
the most successful out of all of you was
Johnny Old School, right? Yeah,
because he had his site and he had ads up on
Spoonie's site, and he got a lot of traffic
on his site. He didn't get a lot of
subscribers or repeat traffic, I don't
think, but he,
I remember him saying once that he did get checks
from AdSense on his site, so he must have been getting traffic.
Great.
And he eventually sort of retired
from YouTube, right? Yeah, he, uh,
he, uh, started,
he moved around a lot,
he became a chef, he, uh,
started going to art school, and he had this
like, uh, this big, like
philosophical, this
burst of hippie, artistic,
personal growth.
And he became, like, very, like,
super
one with the earth. We all need to join hands
and be brothers.
So, he's, he's- A midlife crisis,
essentially. Yeah, well, he's not that much older
than me. I think he's, like, 33.
But, um,
yeah, he's, uh, he just decided
that, you know, I don't want to be
Johnny Old School anymore. I don't feel like that person
is me anymore, which I totally get
because I look back on, you know,
the beginning of drowning in footwear. Like, that person's
not me anymore, you know? Right.
And you're very into, like,
changing names and having
names for, uh, yeah,
different meanings and stuff like that, because
there was, like, for the longest
time, everything was the
drowning man. You were drowning
in footwear, drowning in horseshoes,
drowning in K-fabe,
and then once the horseshoe
finale came out, then all of it
changed. And we're
not drowning anymore, as the song
went. Yeah, it's, um,
I sorta- I- I like
collecting accolades and titles for myself
over time, because I sorta feel like,
you know, every chapter
has its end, and it shouldn't overstay its welcome
and you should always be evolving and changing.
And I sort of view it like
how in the Hobbit, in that scene
in the book, where, um, he-
he is, like, describing himself to someone
later on in the book, and he's giving himself
all these fanciful names, like, I am the
barrel rider, Bilbo Baggins, I am
the troll fucker, I fucking-
I have a ring in my pocket,
I'm the pocket man! Look at me!
You know, he's, like, giving them- he- he's giving
himself all these fanciful accolades. That's always, like,
what comes into my head when I think about it. When I
go on my five minute
spiels of catchphrases and names for myself
when I'm-
Yeah.
Well, now it's been ruined by, uh,
Daenerys Targaryen.
That's true, she took that, she ruined my thing,
that was my thing, she stole it from me,
I should be getting residual checks on that.
Yeah.
Oh, she does it, it's not nearly as cool.
I am- I am the master of the listing
of the accolades.
I am the gu- I am the king of names.
And that's a new name right there.
I- I, like, I definitely found it
exciting when you changed all the names,
but it was really funny just because
of the fact that again, and-
Ah, fuck!
This is, like, the biggest piece of shit
right now in the history
of mankind. I don't know why he's doing this.
He keeps cutting out. This is out of control.
I'm gonna fucking kill myself,
I'm gonna kill every person
in the world, I'm going to grab a fucking
end to mine, I'm going to run
into an angel and blow myself up,
they're gonna replace me from a clone from the
spank tank.
Why the fuck is this happening to me?
I just wanna do a fucking
podcast.
Oh god, can you hear me?
Yeah.
Okay, Jesus fucking Christ.
Oh man, I don't even remember
what I was gonna say, I was blinded by rage,
I was fucking screaming when it cut out.
Um,
yeah, again, just,
when you changed to Endless Jest, it was really funny
because at the time,
that was gonna be the, like,
this is gonna be the channel of just big
videos, and then it, like,
very quickly became
not the case.
But, um,
I don't know, I've been pretty down for
everywhere that your journey has been taking
you, because on the one
hand, yeah, I do want
the big, intelligent
Jesse Wood content, because
obviously, it's always
exciting to get that from anybody,
but I still think the stuff
you're doing is stuff I don't get anywhere else,
you know, like. Yeah, and definitely
I still have the plans for those videos
that I was planning a year ago.
A lot of them have been pushed back
because so much of what I do is spontaneous,
even big videos, like, what you're gonna
do, or the two-flaggots videos,
those weren't videos that I planned, I had planned to do,
you know, I had a whole list of things
that I wanted to analyze and make big tributes
to, and videos about, but those ideas
came up, and I had to focus on those and make those,
and those were big videos too, so
I just do everything kind of spontaneous,
spontaneous. Spontaneity
is my blessing and curse. It gets
in the way of everything that I want to do, but sometimes
yields positive results, nevertheless.
Right. I think I'm
a lot more positive, uh,
rather patient as a viewer,
because, like, for me personally,
I get all these people all the time
who are, like, asking me to talk about this show
or that show, and I'm like, guys,
my channel's not going anywhere.
Like, this is,
like, for me, when I look at the future,
it's like, it's always gonna be
making more stuff, and making
more videos, and if you hang around
long enough, I'm gonna talk about everything,
you know, and I get
that same sense from you, where
there's never this sense of, like,
that you're only
that you're just coming up with it on the spot.
There's always a sense that there's way more
waiting in the wings, that it's already planned,
that there's already more stuff coming,
where, like, uh, you know,
I watch a lot of YouTubers, and I can sort of
feel the moment when they ran out of ideas,
when they, like,
hit the wall, and now they're
they're trying to come up with new stuff
fast enough to keep their audience
entertained, but they don't really
have the ideas. I have the opposite problem.
Like, I wish that my hands could work
as fast as my brain. I can never
catch up to the
monument, the monumental fucking
mountain, the backlog of ideas that I
have at any given moment, and it's always getting bigger.
I can't really chip away at it,
because, like, I don't feel like
I'm never getting another
big Jesse experiment
thing, like, I know it's gonna happen, because I know
your nature as a creator, you make things
get too big, you blow them out
of proportion, um, so
eventually it's gonna happen.
Yeah, like, just the other day, like,
I, uh, I got this
idea to do a vlog about comics,
and I'm like, this is a good idea for a
vlog, so I go to film, I can't
film because people are home and they're making noise,
so I fucking, I go outside
and I walk around, and while I'm walking around, I'm thinking
about what I want to say, and
the more I think about what I want to say,
the more it becomes things I have to say, and the more it becomes
a script, and so then
I get home, and I can't fucking film it
as a vlog anymore, because it's become too intelligent
and too important to just
spew out an inarticulate, incoherent
vlog, so I gotta write it all out, and now
it's a script waiting to actually be created
and edited, which is ten times more work, and it'll never
fucking get done. That's how it always happens,
and I think another thing that
like, uh, hinders
the videos coming out that I want to make
is because, um,
my videos
just the way that I make them,
they all tend to have, like, an inherent
continuity to them,
and not even when I'm deliberately
telling a story arc or something,
not even when I'm deliberately putting continuity
in them, just always in the background
or, like, philosophically when I'm approaching
what videos I'm currently making,
because it'll be, like,
uh, I fuck, totally lost my
train of thought right there. I like the beer quest.
Yeah, it's like,
if I'm doing fucking, like, I have this
great idea for this video,
but this video will only make sense
after I do this video, and I
can't do this video until I get all of these
little things out of the way so that that one makes sense.
But none of these little things are going to make any sense
unless I set them up with this thing first.
So no matter what I want to do,
it always becomes, like, this weird act of
dominoes where, like, I have to
fucking foresee 30 steps into
the future and then work my way backwards
from what I want to do to get
to the point where I can make that video.
Yeah, I'd say
more so than a continuity, it's like a
train of thought. Like,
I mean, even with all the
random vlogs, there's always this
very vague sense of
them happening one after another
and that that's the best, like, the
reason this vlog is happening is because
of the last vlog, you know,
where, like, something happened in that
one that's affected you to make
this one. And
yeah, I mean, it makes
sense, and I've gotten into
that too before where I've had
stuff that only made
sense to me at the time, and then once I
held onto the script for too long, it just no longer
felt like it would, like,
why would I do this now? This was
a story for then, you know,
um, and now it's
dead. And it's weird to me that, like,
all of the ideas that I had
for endless just content when I started the channel
are ideas that I still have
waiting in the wings, a series that I want to
do, like, uh, fucking,
I don't even fucking know, like,
I don't know what it is that makes it so hard
for me, because, like, I similarly have
an endless sea of ideas,
and it's just a matter of, like,
psyching myself to
write them, like. Yeah, and it's also,
like, you know, um,
breaking them apart into little chunks,
because I do want to make more,
like, analytical videos, like,
Nerdwriter, and I've, like, as much as I complain
about Nerdwriter, he's kind of
becoming an influence, like, just the way
that he makes his videos, like,
I don't have to make a huge
blowout analysis of a show,
I can pick the elements
of the show one at a time, and make five
minute videos about those. So, for example,
that's, that's a huge thing I've
been doing now. So I have this,
I have this gigantic, like,
I have a gigantic, I have, like, a 30
page analysis of Hey Arnold,
that I wrote, like, two years
ago, and I'll
never fucking do it, except
just recently, I took a look at it, and, like, wait a minute,
I can segment this off here, and here, and here,
and make, like, four different videos about this.
And maybe that'll help in the future
to get these analytics, because I want
to go back to having more analytical videos.
I just, I don't just want to be
vlog, I don't ever just want to be one
thing, ever. Right.
Not just a ranty man,
it is a, it is a basement. Yeah.
Um, yeah, man, it's,
I, I picked up on that, like, big time
recently, too, where it was, like, it always
felt like I had to either do
a short review that didn't say enough,
or a long review that had to say
everything, and that at some point, I went,
like, hey, what if I, like,
did Ava episode by episode,
you know? I'd say that was, like,
that was sort of what made me realize I could do
that was the Ava stuff,
because for years, and you've had the same problem
with the same show, I know,
that you've wanted to talk about Ava for so long,
and it's just the daunting nature of it. And here's,
here's what I came up with
to solve that dilemma, and this is going to be
happening, and I'm going to let this cat out of the bag right now,
because I'm excited about it, I want everyone to know
this genius idea that I've had.
I'm going to make a new series on my Japanese
animes, loosely based
on Nate's series,
and it's going to be called, Best
Anime
Ever.
And it's all going to be Ava.
Eh, eh, yes, applause,
applause for that brilliant fucking pun!
I'm a genius! I'm going to take the anime
YouTuber world by storm!
That's pretty great. And then all those fucking
gods on the Ava subreddit
who fucking downvoted and
whined about my Ask
AMV, they're all going to see, when I become
the internet's undisputed king
of Avangelion analysis, they're all going to see
how wrong they were, and they're going to
beg me for forgiveness, and I will say
the nay! Be gone with you
cad! Be gone from my kingdom!
You are banished from the land!
We'll lead us to kings,
We'll fucking lead us to kings!
Oh man, that is a good idea.
Yeah, I thought it was interesting too
you mentioned Nerdwriter, because
you said the phrase, the medium is the
message twice at the start of this podcast
which is his video
that I keep quoting all the time.
But yeah, it's, I would
love to see more of it, and I think another thing
that would help you
that I've adopted
is just not being afraid of retreading
stuff, like
at some point I realized
that, because I'm always going to hate
my old review of something, like
my opinion changes over time, or I figure
out more to say about it,
and so like, when I
first started doing anime videos
it was mostly these 10-20
minute reviews of a show
and now I'm going back
and looking at those, and being like, this doesn't say
anywhere near all that I have to say about it.
And I could do
like 30 more videos about this show
you know, I could just keep doing videos about it
forever, and what's great about these
vlogs I've been doing is that it
lets me just like
get the basic thought out there, like
you know, all these ideas that I've got
in my head that I'm like, oh well
it's not enough to make a whole video out of it
but I kind of have this idea
and I just like burned through like 30 of those
things that have just been like weighing on
my mind, and some of them
it's great because they were stupid
like the Metroidvania thing
like for like a year I legitimately
wanted to make like a full analysis
video about why Metroidvania is a bad
term, and then I made the vlog about it
and like within days I was like, that's the
stupidest vlog ever, like
no one gives a fuck
this would have been a terrible video, it would have
been a huge waste of time, I'm so glad you
bring up it. It's funny that you bring up the
Metroidvania vlog because it goes into what we
were talking about before, with things
spiraling out of control and getting too intricate
because I made a reply video
to that vlog to go with yours
and Nate's, and
in the making of my reply
video it became
way too intricate and it became an actual
video, and then
I realized that I
can't post this video yet
because in order to make this video how I
want it, Colt Corona needs
to come out of the furnace room and he hasn't yet
so now that
video is now waiting in the wings
because Colt Corona is still barricaded
in my damn furnace room.
Do you even still want to do that video
now that you've heard me talk about how
retarded even I find my own
Metroidvania video? No, I still
want to do it because it's going to be hilarious, it's going to be great.
Don't you have some
Dark Souls 2 response videos that you
made as well? Yeah, I made
Baby Bro plays Dark Souls 2
and it's
I made a character called
Baby Bro, first
he was named Dildo Bro, but then I changed it to
Baby Bro, and it's
just a big fat you in a diaper
going around going
why is the animation
so bad? These
ladies are mean, they're telling me the game
is hard, it's stupid
and I did
that for about an hour
and then that's still coming out, right?
Yeah, I made
that, but then to go along with it
I also made a let's play of me playing
the game with my like normal narration
talking about the things about the game that I like
and I was going to splice them together
and just the act of splicing them together became like
I don't give a shit about this anymore, fuck it
and I don't care at all
about those Dark Souls 2 videos
Yeah, that's the thing, it's a
debate that neither of us care to win
No
I don't, it's like
well like I said, I really went into it
like with this venomous like
yeah, nobody's chat on this game enough
I'm going to shit on it harder than anybody
and then like very quickly I realized
I have two problems with the game
that aren't like, obviously
if you like the game, those two things
don't bother you, so
this is not helpful for anybody
you know, like the only people who are going to be entertained
are people who already feel exactly like I feel
and don't need me to tell them all this stuff
you know
so yeah
those videos are terrible
man, especially after like part 4
they just get really... it's funny that like
you did that video
and then immediately after
Aiden did his Serious Sam video
which was the same video
but much worse
yeah, but like
watching both of you guys do that
it like sort of inspired me to like
I wish that there was a game
that I hated this much, that I could also
let's play and do one of these of my own
and just pedantically bitch about
every single tiny detail to the point of absurdity
but like I couldn't think
of a game that I hate enough
and like take it off the rails in a way
like because I know that's how it would go with you
you would eventually
it would go beyond the impossible
like the only things
like the only things that I could think of
were like, okay, Final Fantasy 13
but everybody's already done that
it's the most overdone fucking thing in the world
and there's only one complaint
it's a hallway
wow, that's the whole fucking video
that and the story doesn't make any sense
two complaints, so why, what's even the point
and then the other one
was Mass Effect 3
but that's a fucking 40 hour game
I'm not ever playing a 40 hour game
that I know I hate
well, it's only like 25 hours
well maybe I'll do it then
well that was also the conclusion
I reached with Dark Souls 2
it's long and
if I had unique things
to say about every level
then it would have been worth it
I recorded three episodes with Shade
two of which I haven't released yet
but when I'm playing with him
because he hates the game too
but he's amazing at it
and watching him play it I really couldn't
even process what was happening fast enough
to complain about it and I was like
why am I doing this, I have no stakes in this game
and even Mass Effect 3
is so over talked about
who gives a shit at this point
I actually think
Mass Effect 3 might be
underrated at this point
people shout on it so much
when a lot of it's pretty good
there are parts of the story
that are really cool
like the fucking
the part with the fucking
yeah
the Morden
the Morden's part is great in that game
that's about it I guess
it's one of the best parts in the whole fucking series
the game has to get some credit
but yeah
so there has to be like I have to find
a game that's like
all gameplay
that only I hate
and I hate psychotically and no one else does
and I don't think a game like that exists
or if it does I can't think of it
so alright
I know that for the future
of your work
you're definitely planning to put more into my Japanese
animes
that's like the channel you're considering
this will get me big
that has to be the channel that I
promote when I'm telling people about myself
because it's the only channel that makes sense
and I'm determined to have it keep making sense
I'm determined to
keep all of my weird meta shit
away from it as far away as possible
no dumb story arcs at all
my Japanese anime has to remain pure
for the good of all mankind
well I've always felt like what makes
my Japanese animes work is that
it seems like
you have less
stakes in anime than any other
medium
where it's kind of like you're not the big anime guy
like I am
and because someone like me exists
you don't have to be
cause it's so irreverent
and dumb in a way where
if you made a Hey Arnold video
you wouldn't want it to be that
cause you want to prove to the world
how cool Hey Arnold is
but with Japanese animes
it's like attack on Titan who fucking cares
write the dumbest
most irreverent review of it possible
but it's funny and that's what makes it work
and in a lot of ways that's better than doing a critique
or an analysis because I talk all the time
about how I can't stand
critics or reviewers
and I think reviews are a medium
where I can't lie and be wiped off the face of the earth
and what I like about my Japanese animes
is like even if I sometimes
like I complain about bleach in the video
but the video is more about
sharing bleach with everybody
the purpose of the videos on that channel
is to like I like anime
let's all like anime together
and talk about how silly it is
I always felt like what's great about those videos
and this is something that they really have
the most in common with the donkey I think
who I only got into more recently
but like they're good at
cutting very quickly to the heart
of like how you feel about it
it's not about like
it's like a very like with the bleach one
the point of it is
I liked it when I was a teenager
because it was stylish and cool
it went downhill over the years and like
that's the important facts to you
not like the why
but the fact that that's what happened
and you presented in this hilarious way
or with Pokemon where
that one's fucking amazing because it's really
it's not really about
Pokemon per se it's about
the disillusionment that comes with growing up
and realizing that you were
infatuated with a commercial product
that has moved on to another generation
you know and
it's fucking genius like
because yeah you could talk about
what actually happens in Pokemon
but instead you just concentrated
on the emotional connection
you have with it and
I think that's what a lot of those videos are
with something like Madoka
it's just like it's a fun blue be cool
show so here's a fun blue be cool
poem about it yeah we did it
you know there's nothing more that needs
to be said you made the point
it's cool
so yeah I think
that channel works well for that
but anyway back the reason I brought
it up that channel
I know you're planning to put some more
focus on you've got the big endless just
videos that are still
stashed away somewhere
at some point the man child incorporated arc
will end is that channel going to stay active
after that do you think
yeah I think man child incorporated will still exist
because I still think it's a funny gimmick and I still
I still have ideas
for shows to cover on it
that I didn't get to do before so I'll probably
get to them after I finish up the stupid arc
it's such a stupid
thing and like it's such a knowingly stupid
thing like that's the point like
the horseshoes saga was kind of meant to be
deep or like insightful
or poignant or important
to me right so that's what it's
so that's what it became but like from
the inception of this one
this was meant to be
retarded and so
I've succeeded more than I thought
possible in that
I've made it so fucking retarded I barely
even want to do it
right I I completely
know that feeling though because I've got
I think that's what happened
with uh I have a lot
of these ideas like plans for very
small anime videos that are
like they'll be easy to write
and like catchy and fun
but they're so
not artistically fulfilling
that I can't bring myself to write
them where it'll be like
like some of the like cool character designs
and stuff like that like I have a bunch of great ideas
for that but for me it's
like if I'm not doing this 12
part you know hours long
takedown of some show or whatever
then I don't feel like I'm
doing like I don't feel like I'm living up to my full potential
you know so it's like
when am I gonna make
the next video that makes people
rethink what an anime analysis
on YouTube can be like that's what I
you know what I'm worried about
even though I don't have any ideas for that so
instead I'm just doing nothing
because I can't do one way or the other
um
would you say that's comparable
yeah we all uh
I think you might have talked
about this on Digi Bros maybe not
but we all as a group decided
that like we had squad goals for June
and we all amongst ourselves
were like okay guys we're gonna kick
so much ass in June we're all gonna have a bunch
of great videos we're gonna stop fucking around
where the fuck's Nate's new video now that you mention it
and
like we all were gung ho about June
none of us have done anything
with this been the same shit
no it's
it's particularly bad because it was like
the last day
of May I got out of
video you got out of
vlog and uh
I think Hippo had like a short video he did
or no he did the GRPJ video on Kingdom Hearts
and Nate was saying
that he had a video that was gonna come out
that day
it's been nine
fucking days
and Nate's video hasn't come out yet
what the fuck is happening
I haven't done
jack shit
you haven't done jack shit
in terms of what you said you were gonna do
um
I know Hippo's
working towards a video
but he's having difficulty on the technical
end but yeah
it was definitely like squad goals
June's the month and
yeah
I just keep doing podcasts
instead
it's just easier and again like I said
like
like when I said like June
like yeah I'm gonna have all these plans
like I have so many ideas for videos
and I just like I can't get excited about them
because they're not big enough nothing's big enough
to make me feel like I'm following up
the asterisk war videos
yeah it's like fucking it's like heroin
you know that first high
is the best one and then
you need a bigger one you need only
a huge fucking hit will satisfy you
everything else just feels like small potatoes
and you finish like 10 vlogs in one day
and you've got all this content but none of it means
anything and it's just killing your soul
slowly well for me the hardest part
is that like because
last month I got so used to doing vlogs
and I'm having fun
with it and I like that I'm sort of like finding
new ways to do them
but I can't
monetize vlogs and I have to pay
the DeVoo like he has
dedicated his self
to full time being my video editor so if
I don't give him videos then he's also
fucked so it's like
we both need me to be writing scripts
um
and I'm so down on ideas
but uh yeah
enough about me this podcast is about you
what I was leading up to
by saying that I I know but we are all the
DeVoo
um
I know what the future holds
for the the endless
Jess saga but are there any
like big projects that you completely
will never do that you wanted
to do like throughout your whole career
um I don't know
I remain hopeful about pretty much
everything I mean
there might be videos that I've written that I wouldn't
now would think are stupid
and shouldn't be done but I can't really think of them
like I still want to do gun buster on my Japanese
anime is I still want to do all my millions of
Ava videos and my big cowboy bebop video
and all that shit there's a million endless
Jess videos I want to do
I it's
you know logically I know it's impossible
that I'll ever do all of them but I have to
remain hopeful about my
because I have so many like complete scripts
that are good that are so good
that have been sitting there for some of them
for years and it's
just sad that I that I
don't have like a team of editors
or something to finish this shit for me
and you also are but you also don't trust
editors you're not a fan
of the idea of handing your work away
yeah well I was talking to DeVoo about
this and it's not
necessarily that I don't trust the editors
it's that I don't trust
my ability to articulate myself
to them over the internet because
if DeVoo and I
if you're if you were editing a video of mine
and we were in the same house I could come up to
anyone and say hey man put this here
and put that there alright but over the internet
like I hate communicating
over the internet it feels not human
and it feels awkward and it's hard to express
like an artistic idea
over the internet
I would agree with that
and I'm not I'm not into collabs
either like again I've said this
before but the reason I hired DeVoo is
because he understood
everything I was doing perfectly
and can do it better you know
so there was
because I think I was
like re-listening to some podcast
that we did where I was describing
that like
I just like it's not that I
don't have an idea of how to make the videos
better I just won't do it
because like I'm lazy and
I want it out too fast
so like I'll think well
this might look better if I did
some effect here but uh fuck it
you know and so I give it to DeVoo
because he'll have the same instinct but he'll do it
so
that's what makes him a great editor for me
but yeah I could easily see
like you know he can't just
instinctually know what funny
anime face you'd put in at a part
you know yeah
in the editing that you would do
so alright
so you don't have any projects that are just
completely cutting room floor gone
at least at present
I know there was a point
where you were gonna adopt Johnny
old school's name and become
oh yeah yeah before I settled on Endless
Jess
my idea was uh the old school
fool
and that's where that silly catchphrase came from
where um uh Johnny was gonna
give me his domain name
and I was gonna
because I had so many channels and I didn't know what I was doing with him yet
so I got the idea that I wanted like a website
for all of them I don't really I guess that's
something that's on the cutting room floor that I don't care about anymore
is getting my own website because who gives a shit
right I think we've all
had that like there was a long
time where we were coming up with all these different
ways to make a website for like the whole
horseshoe crew or just some of us and
it's just nobody goes to websites
anymore so it doesn't feel like there's a point
to it
um oh
here's one though that you used
I just remembered this
you used to talk about starting
up the series all the time but I have no
idea if you're still intending on it at all
because I haven't heard you bring it up in well over a year
spirit of the 90s
oh yeah I forgot
about good old spirit of the
oh fuck god the thing about spirit of the
90s is that I'm running
out of time because
the joke behind
spirit of the 90s it was
gonna be like a 90s nostalgia show
but
I would be in like
an old man costume
and the joke was that
I'm only in my
20s but I feel like a fucking old
man so I'm like
doing this like 90s
nostalgia show from the perspective
of remember those stick on
earrings and that you would put
in those fucking braces that you'd
slap on your hands I'm gonna
die soon and that was funny
because when I came up with the idea I was
23 now I'm almost 27
I feel like the joke is
running out of time I'm not gonna be
in my 20s much longer
and I'll just be legitimately
an old man which will ruin the entire
joke right I
didn't even realize that was part of it I just
remember that you were buying posters
for spirit of the 90s
like you bought the good burger poster for that
I think yeah another burger posters
a part of my room yeah because that was
like I always had the impression that the way
a Jesse Wood saga starts
is you buy everything for the set
and then you start writing the scripts
and all the Genesis it all
starts with me buying a poster
at 4am drunk on Amazon
and then a fucking arc comes
out of it
the fucking Miss
Elizabeth poster
got like 3 vlogs out of it
there's 3 videos and that's still
one of my favorite posters it's super cool
I uh yeah
I now have
more than enough Oscar posters
to put an entire wall
just Oscar
and I'm waiting for the right moment
to unleash that gag on the world
it has to be the right video
I remember
a time you told me
that you realized
that you suddenly looked around
your room and realized that you had all these
posters of a 14 year old girl
and that you're a 27 year old
man and you were like this is creepy
even for me
it's getting weird
I have to change I have to put
Misato posters up now for the next 15 years
and then I'll be 45
and I'll have to put up Gendo posters
oh god yeah
and then 15 years later it'll be Fuyutski
and then you can just die with that one
my whole life will just be a series of Ava Waifus
and Husbandos
oh shit
I'll just segment my autobiography
into the character names
so as
I'm wondering if this is going to become clear
when you start doing Ava videos
that much like
the previous mythos we've discussed
of all the
the characters that you have
you have been developing your own Ava
mythos in your head
that I've heard of
I'm going to just like hype people up
I don't know if you're still working on it
but you sent me the intro
chapter of a fanfic you're writing
that was fucking
amazing
and I
I know I'm a fan of all your work
but even you
if you post an Ava fanfic I go into it
like okay what's this going to be
and I read it and I was like
oh my god this is
like legitimately gripping
character portrait of Ray Ayanami
and the lead
in is that she's going to play Smash Bros
it's amazing
well the idea of it
I wanted to take
the dumbest possible premise
or the silliest possible spin on the series
but then approach it taking it completely
seriously and like really get into the character's
heads like
like a legit like I was actually
writing for the show and like really show
off that I understand these characters
while also having them
like the whole fucking plot is that
they're playing Nintendo 64
yeah it's
fucking incredible um I hope it
I hope it gets published at some
point I don't know how much of it you want
to write before any of it comes out
but the part you had written was fantastic
well it's another one of those things that like
in the making of it it's become more intricate
in my head than it originally was
because originally it was like
I'm gonna make a it's gonna be that
uh
Ray has an existential crisis
and decides
instinctually inherently as all
children know
that Nintendo 64 is the bomb yo
and so
she decides that she has to buy Nintendo 64
um
and what draws her eye to it
this was one of my proudest
little tidbits that I threw in there
was that it was one of the translucent purple
Nintendo 64s that they came out with
and it reminded her of Ikari's Ava
so
hahahaha
in all this is appropriate
because Ava takes place well never mind
it takes place in 2015
I was thinking it came out in 95
so it's appropriate but it's not
but that's uh
that's gonna be an element of it when I
because I'm still writing it um
one of the one of the ideas was that
Misato wipes the floor
with everyone at N64
because she's a fucking millennial
and she grew up with it
yeah that's actually genius
oh man I don't want you to spoil too
much of this thing but I legitimately
love it and I'm kind of expecting
that when you start making Ava videos
elements of
your ideas of the characters that go
beyond what's presented in the show
will probably creep in
because um
Idle Yukai who is a huge fan of all of us
on Twitter yes she's been going through
and she's been drawing pictures of us
like hanging out with our waifus
and I
already have instructed her to incorporate
an element of my coming fan fiction
into the picture just to make it
that much cooler
I just I have to wonder like
um I think
as I've said before I know your work
probably better than anybody else and
because of that I feel like I get more
out of it just because there's so many little
jokes and references
and I just wish
there was like a way
to stream every idea you have
out of your brain onto the internet
like just for everyone to know
all of these little details
because it would enhance it all so much
to get the whole narrative
of like
you know
you make an oska joke and like
it means more to me because I listen to you
talk about oska so fucking often
like I understand that it's this
legitimate obsession and
you haven't made that many videos
that talk about oska she's
around you clearly have a lot of posters
of her but like
you know I don't know if anybody else would
be as it seems like the things that are
like that I'm the most into
I end up making the least amount of content
about yeah I'm
dude I fucking feel the exact same way
just because like almost like I feel
like I owe it something
grander yeah
man like because
in a way it was
like when I started doing anime
videos what allowed me to
talk about all like my favorite shows
is that they all became my favorite
shows in the process of writing
about them because like all my
old favorites I haven't really
talked about a lot of them like
like a wreck of seven was
like my favorite anime for a long time and
like you know
now if I watch it again my opinion is
totally different because I've grown up so much so
like I had this weird lucky stroke where
back in my anime blogging
days I would never cover my favorite
shows because I felt like I had to write
the biggest post ever about each of them
and I just wouldn't
and then because of the fact that
I'd forgotten all my
I forgot everything about anime then like
now it's like I'm rediscovering
each one and I get to write about it because
you know like Kaon I
watch it again after all this time
and like now I'm trying to remember oh
this is why I liked this show so much
oh now I get it and I can write it much
more easily so I feel like
having this two-year gap away from anime
like really helped to make it so I could
finally write about shows I actually
care about as opposed to just random
bullshit because
it's way easier like I said with the
my Japanese anime thing before it's way
easier to go like watch attack on
Titan and you don't give a fuck about
it so you can write a five-minute video and it's over
you know yeah like the stuff that I
have like a lot of
passion for it's almost
daunting to like
get it done I can't
like get to it like um
like I'm passionate about music
I've wanted to make
my fucking debut rap album
for like seven years longer than
I've had a YouTube channel
and I release rap songs
all the time I make rap songs all the time
but they're all like weird freestyles
and dumb shit with like beats that I just
rip off the internet and
they're not like what I consider to be
part of this album that I formulated
in my head like in my head
in my head I have like
my first seven albums planned out
and there's a fucking they're all
fucking concept albums they all have a
purpose and a place like a fucking jigsaw puzzle
I you know I think about
but I haven't even fucking made the first one yet
and God knows when so many
things that like I want to do
that I'm almost
afraid that I won't get to do
because YouTube will always be in the way
unless I find a way to pull myself
away from it at some point
like uh like stand up comedy
I love doing stand up comedy
I never fucking do it and I hate myself
every minute that I'm not fucking doing it
yeah I have some uh
I don't know if I'm as
afraid as you are because for me it was
kind of a relief that
like I feel like I'm a lot better at
YouTube than all the other things I wanted to do
so like sometimes I think
hey I still want to be a novelist I still
have all these great ideas for novels and
like I'm never gonna write them because it's so much
easier and more fun and fulfilling
to just make YouTube videos and not try to
write this shitty book I watch I'll watch
like a Bo Burnham special like his new
special just came out and I watch like
the stuff that he does on stage and it's
like very subversive and he does all this
like bombast and pomp and circumstance
he's always got like recordings going off
and lights and like flashing steam and shit
and it's just like
I like that's the kind of stuff that
I watch and I feel like I'm I have
to be wasting my potential on YouTube
I should be on a
grander stage I don't fucking know
yeah I
I get you and especially with music
because I obviously
me and you collab on music
yeah and I definitely
think I mean I've been saying all this time
that I think I'm the biggest fan of your videos
but I know I'm the
biggest fan of your music because I don't think anybody
else cares about it but me
but like legitimately
I uh I have often
I have often said this of myself
and I don't
say it necessarily on line
as much because
I feel like I haven't
posted enough to prove this to people
so I feel uncomfortable saying it
but in real life I sell the time
I'm the greatest fucking lyricist who ever lived
in the face of the earth
and I'll fucking plant my flag in it
I'll fucking draw the line it's my hill to die on
I'll say it until I'm dead
but I just I
I never say that on line because I feel like I haven't proved it enough
I legit from what I know
of your lyrics I can't
immediately disagree with that
like I can't name a lyricist off the top of my head
who I think like blows you out of the water
and like it's such
like an ever present like feeling in my head
that like uh
maybe like old Eminem
yeah Eminem I definitely put up there
Eminem has
made some incredible wordplay
in his time
but then he did fucking
rap god fucking garbage
but um
yeah it's like it's to where like
you've
you've seen the you've seen this phenomenon
play out with me in the past
I cannot stand
to see other rappers complimented
it burns me up inside
on like a primal level
even like like
that video that we're going on like
look at how these rappers are such
great lyricists and look at how
you know people say things like oh man
Kendrick Lamar he's bringing lyrical rap back
or and I just
fucking even if it's like an
innocuous compliment of some rapper
who I agree is good I still like if I
hear someone praising
the other rapper I just fucking sit there
and I stew you sons of bitches
don't even fucking know I hate all of you
you're all worms are beneath me
it's well it's
upsetting right because I mean music
is incredibly hard to promote
it's upsetting to me that I haven't
um had
put in the time to prove that to people
because it's something that I feel
is true of myself but I've
I'm always focused on YouTube well it's that like
you've got you've got great stuff but it's
all hidden behind like
like the fact that the
productions never that good you know because
up until recently you didn't have a great
microphone and
you know you don't really know
audio mixing and most of the beats like
you said are just ripped from YouTube
so it's harder to have like
something that you can put
out there and be like hey guys listen to this
rap it's on iTunes and they'll be like oh
shit I'm paying for that it's
it always feels like kind
of internet but if you actually
pay attention to it
the songs are great like
legitimately one of my favorite songs
ever is the coolest guy
rap where it's just this
really hype beat that you
took from YouTube
and you just wrap this completely
nonsensical insane
verse over it it's like one verse it's like
four minutes long and it's
fucking great it's legitimately
like that I walk around
my house rapping it to myself
because I've spent years learning it
that's one that if I
ever get around to actually making the album
that I have in my head that would be
on it I would probably re-record it
and tighten up the lyrics
in some spots but that song would definitely
make the cut for an album
but like I could easily see
hearing that song and being like
whatever it's just some
YouTube guy rapping about dumb stuff
but then like when you
really pay attention to it like
the lyrics fit the beat really well
um you know it's not gonna
knock your trunk or anything
but like it's kind of funny how
like a lot of people will listen to something like
uh folk music or
drone or something that's like recorded
or black metal like shitty recordings
uh like that sound like they're coming out
of a fucking cell phone
but it fits the music and
that can be great and I think that when it comes
to rap so many people have the expectation
that rap is supposed to be this heavy bass
trunk knocking, fun time
listening stuff
and I don't think it has to be
and the coolest guy is a song
that I think works in spite
of the production
not being all there because
it's still a fun hype beat
and it's still fun hype lyrics that have all these
character and you use all these voices
and the part where you know
you just get into this deep rasp and you're like
sitting on the beach and it looks like hell
the water's blood red because it's L-C-L
look at Ray's head
and you can tell everyone's
dead so what's that smell
it's my asshole you know it's like
like in the middle of this otherwise
fairly technical and like
clever wordplay rap
and then it's just this weird
demonic end of Ava
if you listen
to enough of my raps if you listen to
enough freestyles for me
you will very quickly see that the two things
I always fall back on are
what's that smell
and suck my dick
those two lines will make an
appearance in everything I do
there's no suck my dick in the coolest guy
but there is what's that smell
but yeah I've heard them
come up a few times
but yeah I really enjoy the rap
something about what's that smell is inherently
the funniest thing in the world to me
and I can't explain why
and some of the like
again to me knowing a lot more about you
the song Alright
which is
this like very
open-hearted lyrical song
and
like it just sounds like
if it was any other artist
it sounds like just a list
song kind of thing like you know
you say my friends think this about me
and they're right they're alright
but fuck them I'm alright you know it goes through
this like chain of each different type
of person and what they say about you
but because I know you personally I know those are all
exactly what those people think
like you present
like there's even a difference
between a verse where you're talking about your offline
friends and your online friends and I can tell
which ones which because
you know the
offline friends think of you as like this volatile
like this very honest
and caring guy who's also very
volatile and has no chill
and then your online friends think of you as this
visionary genius but also just this fat
weirdo you know and like
you go through each
person in your life and like
describe how they feel about your girlfriends
who all think you rock in bed of course
you know and
and then the ending like you know
of your friends you'll say and they're right they're alright
but so what
I'm alright but then when it's your fans
then you're like but fuck you
I'm alright you know it's like
the different levels of regret there's a lot to
get into it and like I
get it all because I know
that it's all real it's a complete
psychological picture
yeah it's fucking great
and I've listened to that song you know a lot
of times and then
like just
like with rotten
like I'll break this down because I guess
we did this in the chat so I'm gonna break it down
for the audience the like analysis
I did of rotten
of your verse
this was a song that shade was making
he's just making a beat
in a FL studio
and it sounded kind of like a Tyler the
creator beat so I decided
I was gonna write like a dark grimy like
Earl sweatshirt Tyler the creator type
rhyme over it and I
end up writing this verse about like
just being in my room drinking and trying to
get over my problems right
you know it's got a little bit of fun
in it but I'm not very good at like word play
or like really
complex stuff like my rhymes are usually
very direct it's usually like exactly
what I say is what it means
I record these two verses
I send them off to you
and within hours
you've completed like you didn't even
you've never heard this song before you didn't know
the concept you didn't know what it was gonna
be and I sent it to you and
you perfectly captured
all of the emotions
that were in my part
in your own you even worked in stuff that I hadn't
like the very last line of my song
of my verse is I'm grown
I'm grown I'm grown I'm grown I'm grown
which I hadn't planned to be in there
it was just like at the very end
I thought what if I do in this suggestion
that like
you know that I shouldn't be this way
because I'm grown up and then you throw in a line
that's like I used to dream of how I'd
be when I was grown picture me with a six pack
not not the kind that foams which
is a fucking phenomenal
line great word play great imagery
but also
totally is in there just because of my line
I'm grown I'm grown I'm grown like you expanded
on the concept of the song
in a way that it wouldn't have been like that would have felt
out of nowhere at the end if not for the fact
that you put that line in your verse
so it made my verses
better and then the word play
in there is like
I gotta get those like three
like triple syllable rhymes
in a row in it because it's like
come to on the floor in a pile
of trash and piss shit stained drawers I'm
a hot mess hoarder the lord of disorder
calorie absorber performer
a camcorder and on board
that's in insanity
that's four
three syllable words that all rhyme
and then it goes
like stick more horrors with my thick
pork sword it's crazy
and you didn't even try to make it technical
that was just what came into your head
that's
next level that's what the best
rappers do that's all
the techniques that they were talking about in that
rap analysis video all the things that all
the greats do what they're all known
for you did all that
in an hour
yeah so yeah that was about
three percent of my lyrical
power I'd say
and yeah so
for me it almost like
hurts to know that
other people like when I played
butt sugar for my friends and they all were just
like this is one of my friends kept saying
this is just Tom Green
this is just my bum is on your lips
I'm like no it's not it's Tom Green
song is fucking stupid butt chugger
has a whole narrative arc
a whole emotional arc about this character
when will people appreciate the technical
mastery of butt chugger
well like
cause that's the thing when you listen to butt chugger it seems
like it's just gonna be a dumb song about
butt chugging but then it has this whole narrative
about this this kid who like
you know
butt chugging is basically a metaphor for
art or for getting into
something that like passion you know
like he discovers a passion but then
society hammers him back down
and forces him to become like a normal
stiff and then he
realizes that the butt chugging was
in him all along and he just has to be
himself it's like a whole fucking
film you know not to
not to take anything away from
Tom Green's legendary masterpiece
lonely Swedish to bum bum song
which is one of the greatest songs
ever written I just want to clarify that for everyone
that fucking that part
in that song where like he breaks it down
it gets to like the bridge and it gets quiet and he's
like my bum is on the phone
my bum is all alone
and then it like stops and then it goes into like
get the poo off my bum
get the poo off I need the poo
off the bum I gotta get the poo off my bum
that fucking song is
a masterpiece I legitimately love that song
I'm realizing I've never
actually heard the full song
oh god it's great
I mostly know it from fucking M&M's
and then the video ends
and he's like he's on the beach and he's in like
like waist deep water and the video
just ends with him like picking up this duck
prop and there's like a string on it and he's just like
none of this is real
the video ends
Tom Green was a visionary
alright more credit to
Tom Green's bum song
but yeah but sugar's great
um
obviously the t-bap
really saw something in it because they became
fans on the basis of that song
which is fucking fantastic
but yeah
it hurts me to know that you
that you have never achieved in any
avenue the success
that I think you deserve
um and it's just like
a matter of the audience
I feel like there must be people out there
who would get it you know
I feel like your work is
just oddly more
highbrow than
people appreciate
and I was so glad because
I made that video of the top 10
analysis videos of 2015
and I had both what you're
gonna do and the horseshoe finale in there
and you know my old
mentor ghost lightning
you know he's more my friend but I always call
my mentor so people get like a mental
picture of you know the fact that he
that I based a lot of my
writing style on him but he's like
you know like an old
like lit major guy he's a dude
who's like big into like high
concept novels and shit and
he watched what you're gonna do
twice after seeing it
in my analysis
video stick it absolutely loved it and I was
like that that to
me was the moment I was like yeah this is the
people who should be watching Jesse's content
like people who appreciate
the like the high-minded
meta nature of it and
that ending fucking
bit that's just perfect
you can't that song will never
be better than it was in that video
that Kanye West song like it's
the most appropriate context that it could
ever be given that's right you're
fucking welcome Kanye
you fucking hack you're welcome
for me making your song worthwhile
for making it art
I mean it was a great song
that's uh that's one of my
that's one of my favorite shots that I've done
as a director
of me sitting in that corner with all those
wrestling posters and the hot red
shirt and um
I think one of my favorite things
because I think like
a lot of the thing the part that
doesn't get talked about
with YouTubers especially
a YouTuber like how I do things
and not even I really talk about this much is that
like the directorial aspect
of it of like
because um I'm really
into
iconic shots
shots that are um
instantly
descriptive of the video itself
or that and that are
completely unique to me like
I've only done two shots like this
I think that really work on that level
because so much of my writing
is referential
and you know has bits and like
you know like catchphrases that I've stolen
from wrestlers and little references to things
and in-jokes and stuff um
but
some of the things that I'm really proud of are these
shots that just completely stand on their own
and encapsulate the video one of them is
at the end of what you're gonna do when that
fucking thing in the corner and the other
one is the shot of me
right at the end of horseshoe finale where I'm sort of
curled up in the fetal position
and the
and the fucking dog that fucking
dog
Jesus Christ one of the greatest miracles
that ever happened in the history of art
that the day that I was
filming that my sister
happened to randomly bring her dog home
and I fucking
I brought the dog
downstairs and I'm like
this might not work but if it works
it'll be the best thing I've ever filmed in my life
and I fucking laid there
and I had the dog just off camera
and I was just hoping that it didn't come too soon
and then when I got to the
when I felt like I had laid there long enough
I just fucking just a little bit
on the floor so the dog
would hear and come over and she fucking came over
and it was
it's the best thing I've ever filmed in my life I'm so
proud of it I look at it all the time and I just
come I come bullets
it's great
yeah I mean we covered a lot of that
in the authorial intent video which again
I know you weren't there for but like we talked a lot
about how nobody
appreciates that every shot has to be
set up it's never like
I mean a lot of the time when we're vlogging it is
just like point a camera at myself
and film but like we choose
what angle to film from and
what like what's going to be in the
background and you know
one of the most complicated ones
that to this day nobody appreciates
because I don't think anyone noticed it
is um
at a certain part of
Horseshoe finale how like
the video is sort of segmented into like different
me's in different parts of the room
that sort of represent like different aspects of my
personality
and the one where I'm in the
the bookshelf room and how
there's that corner and it's directly across
from the bookshelf
I put a fucking video camera
in the background
playing video of myself recording on the
other side of the room as though
I was delivering these monologues
at the same fucking time actually
teleporting across the room and if you look
at that fucking shot you can see me
in the video camera fucking ranting
while I'm ranting and that was so
retardedly
complex to set up
and no one notices it until now and
now everyone will notice it and I'll tell me I'm a
mess all over again
I believe I do remember that I need to
rewatch I have I've never
rewatched all of Horseshoe finale like
it was just a one time
sat down and watched the whole thing
and at the time
it felt so fucking massive
because like
I would say that that video is probably what broke me
to long videos because now I watch them all the time
like I will watch a video that's an hour
and a half long just because I'm sitting
at the computer and it came out
like there's no hesitation there's no
like waiting around for a time
when I have time it's just like nah it's
put it on so
like at the time Horseshoe finale came out
it was like an ordeal to watch this whole
thing especially because so much
of it is just ranting and like
you know like
holding in all this information as it goes
but uh I think
nowadays it would be much easier to just like
consume all at once
I am overdue for a rewatch
of it and uh you know
it's funny because I keep thinking
I kept thinking well I really have to rewatch
the whole Horseshoe saga but now
that I think about it I've seen End of Ava
and Gileon way more times than I've seen
Ava so
so maybe it'd be justified
you know there are a lot of people who've
told me over the years that they've only seen
End of Ava or that they saw it first so
maybe people should go watch the Horseshoe finale
uh because it does kind
of stand on its own I did get one comment
once of a guy who watched that
first and then worked his way backwards
and he seemed to
enjoy the experience so maybe that works too
I don't fucking know
yeah I'd say it's where I mean it does start off with
like a summary of all the other videos in a way
so maybe it's easier
that way I don't know
I'm overdue for it
alright well
we're getting close to three hours on this which I
guess is gonna be my time limit
for these things because it seems reasonable
and it's about how long it takes for my eyes
to start bleeding out of my fucking skull
so uh do you have
anything else you wanted to talk about to share
with our fans about yourself
just stuff that
I hope to be able to do in the future
and stuff that I plan to do
um like
stuff beyond YouTube
like I talked about the album and I talked about wanting
to do more stand up
um I also
want to make more videos about comics because
that's like a medium that's important
to me that has been like
woefully underrepresented throughout my YouTube
career like I've never made videos about comics
before and I want to and I should
because there are no good comic book
YouTube people right at all
well now we've got Captain
Christian but his stuff is very general and
broad
yeah and not just videos
about comics but even like outside of YouTube like
I think all the time about
writing comics
or fucking specifically like Marvel
and DC because I'm so in love with all the characters
and
you know I'm not a fucking comic book person
so it would be impossible
so I always
because like I think about superheroes all the time
like I not even like as
like a YouTube analyst guy I just
lay in my bed every night and I just like reflect
on like what makes
Spider-Man a great character as opposed to
what makes Wolverine a great character
and Superman is totally different in his own
way and the Punisher is great in his way
and I like I feel like nobody gets these
characters but me and it's like this constant
nagging feeling in my head like nobody
I should be writing all
the comics in the world on the own I have all
the best ideas but like
I don't know like I talked I think
all the time about
collabing with Ben and me like
writing out some dumb fan fiction
idea and having him draw it
I've never approached him about it because he's always
busy writing his own comics and I don't want to fucking
bother him with my stupid shit if you have money
then he will
be on board
that's why I'm like I'm such a huge
fan of Ben just because
he's really good at
something that I haven't done yet
yeah that's I think that's exactly
why I'm a huge fan of Ben because
like I just want his I want
to eat him and steal exactly
I want to be
with him
and he's like
it's just that Ben's good at drawing
and exactly how I want to be good at drawing
like I don't want to be able to draw
like hyper detailed stuff I just want to be
able to draw dynamic poses and like convey
the idea of what I want
you know and like
since becoming friends with Ben I've gotten like way more into
like
buying like independent comics
that like aren't Marvel or DC shit
like these stories that people come up with
because like I guess it never clicked
before I never realized in my head oh
that's where these come from
they come from guys like Ben who just
fucking write them and then they become comics
whoa
like I never put two and two together before
yeah you're used to them coming from like
a look at industry
yeah
yeah I'm excited for that because I specifically
requested it I think a month
ago I was like hey Jesse
you've got all those comics in the background
I want to hear about all of them because
I don't know anything about comics
and what I really want to do I had this
idea the other day is um
because I've talked before in videos about
uh whatever happened to the Caped Crusader
which is like my favorite Batman story
right and um
I got the idea of like
doing like a Matthew Matosis style
read through of the whole comic
on a video and like stopping and
analyzing like every panel I want to do it so bad
but it's impossible to do anything it's too much
shit to do as a friend since that never happened
I would love to see that man I mean
I'm I like whenever
there's a medium I don't know much about
like every video that
explains it to me is like
deeply fascinating like that
time you linked me like Razor Fist
Top 10 Daredevil
comics and I was like I don't know
anything about Daredevil and I can't stand
Razor Fist but I watched the whole
thing just because I was like
man I'd really love to know what
makes Daredevil cool like here's a character
that everyone else knows about but me
it seems like and I don't give a single
fuck about him so please
tell me why he's so cool you know
yeah um and
and and and that it that it so
clearly was like here's
10 read these you know like
I wish he had put them in order
of like which ones you
should read first as like a new
reader that would have been helpful too
because for me comics are just overwhelming
there's just too fucking much you know
um
which is why I was kind of excited over
new 52 I know you're not a huge fan of it
but like it was a great way to be like hey
I can pick up any of them now and it
doesn't matter man you mentioned new 52
this is a totally off topic
I mean then again what is off topic this is
a fucking podcast about me
man that fucking
DC rebirth comic that just came out
was the best fucking thing I've ever
seen I fucking I like I got the
feeling that comics were saved
like maybe I got too excited
but it was so cool because like I've
been complaining about the new 52
since the new 52 was a thing
because it's this like it was
this like marketing ploy of like resetting
continuity but they reset continuity
in such a weird way that it like messed
up everything and like holds
chunks were like gone and you couldn't
fucking figure it out
and so DC
they printed just two weeks ago
this fucking 80 page comic
that was essentially we're sorry
in comic book form
and the whole fucking comic was like the flash
has like been phased out of
existence because of flashpoint which started
the new 52 and he's trying to get back he's like
everybody's forgotten we've had 10 years
of fucking of continuity
stolen from us 10 years of love stolen from
us and he comes back at the end and they get
all their fucking memories back or whatever
and it resets the thing and I'm like I'm gonna
jack off I'm gonna jack off and I'm gonna
come right in this fucking comic pages are gonna stick together
I have to buy a new one I don't care jacking off right on
it oh yeah DC you did it
it was cool comics are great I love comics
when comics comics are like wrestling
for me in that they're often terrible
but when they're great they're my favorite thing in the world
right that's the impression I
that's why for both of those
I can't like I'd rather
experience them through you
because experiencing them myself
is like it's so hard to find
the gold nuggets and
for someone who's an outsider to it it's like
you know it's too much
like with wrestling I know what's good
about wrestling now that I've had you
tell me so much and I've read some good articles
on it but like I would have to watch
all of wrestling history to find
the good shit you know
I'd rather just have people
pick it out and re-explain
it to me and yeah
like is there any other mediums
like for me I know
there's no other
only the epic lore
of the insane clown posse
that's the one avenue
of my fandom that nobody
knows about yet
that I have yet to analyze for the world
yeah I know you're
big into the ICP
and nobody will probably understand
that unless you
get into it in a deep way
um
yeah I wish
I could get it like
I kind of wish I could talk about music
because music's a big part of my life
uh I
it's so hard to
discuss
I have a whole series that I've wanted to do for a while
called awesome albums
where I just talk about the albums that I like
and like the thing was that
I would rate them on a scale of
1 to 10 but regardless of what
score I gave them they would all be certified
awesome albums even if it was like a 1 or a 2
like Saint Anger by Metallica gets
a 2 out of 10 and it's an awesome album
yeah I mean I finally did
something like
again this whole vlogging thing
I mean you already vlog
but I do recommend it as a way to
like for some of this shit
where I was never going to write a video
about my beautiful dark twisted fantasy
but like I just sat down and talked about it for
45 minutes and it was pretty fucking gratifying
to just like have all the
thoughts about that album out there
and now I never have to explain it again
you know like I don't have it eating away
at my consciousness that nobody understands
why I like this album so much
I think there's something very liberating about
random vlogs
and people seem to eat the shit up is what I don't
get like I'm amazed at how much people
like don't hate them because I definitely
hate my own vlogs but the
fucking the people it's what the people crave
apparently
yeah it's it's people just want more
they just want more of everything like
I started I did this video
of me laying on the couch
watching an anime and just turning
the camera on I don't know if you have you seen
either of my two latest vlogs I haven't watched
them yet I've seen them on my sub feed
you should definitely watch the newer one
it's like an hour long
you could probably skip the first 30 minutes
but the second half of it is fucking hilarious
and it's so Jesse like
it's amazing because
I got really drunk and just started
like screaming about everything
and like getting really emotional and like
going into different locations and like
taking a breather and stuff like that
and trying to kill myself
it's great
but like the first one
is just literally 45
minutes of me turning on a camera
after each episode of the show and going like
well that episode was kind of stupid
you know and then like people
like loved it
and I didn't I thought nobody was
gonna like it and it got like 7000
views and I was like what the fuck
this is nonsense and everyone's like
make more make more and I was like
okay I guess so I made the next one
an hour long and I was like no one's
gonna watch that and then
cause first they want a second one
and then it becomes a series
and then it becomes something you're tied to forever
and they all want it
and like I recorded a third one
today and like after I was done with it
I was like I legitimately don't care
about this like I will release this
and people will like this but this video
I legitimately could throw away
right now and it will make
no difference to me I don't care
you know the only
incentive to release it is knowing that it
will get views anyways and there's
like how hard is it to throw the
clips into a thing and render them for an hour
you know that's a nightmare
yeah
anything else you wanted to
talk about that you're
I'm the best guy
with the biggest dick and I have the most
women's and I'm the best
at art
alright
I guess we covered everything
thanks for listening guys
yeah