Hello and welcome to the first and only ever Magecast! I'm your host, Mage, and I'm joined
today by Mage. Say hi, Mage! Hi! So, the topic for today is actually a YouTube user we both
are very familiar with. Her channel is Little Aurora, Mage, but that's a mouthful, so we're
just gonna call her Mage, because it's faster that way. Indeed! Anyway, so a bit about her.
We know that she joined YouTube in 2013, but this isn't her first account, isn't that
right, Mage? Why, yes. I know for a fact that she has had several YouTube accounts
over the years, but they were all abandoned when she grew out of the content she had made
on them. One of her first videos on YouTube was actually a crappy Naruto AMV, I believe.
She made several of those? Yikes, I built from that ship too, had I been her. But that's
all in the past, let us look at what she has been up to in the more recent years. But not
to every sin, let's start off by looking at her Magnum Opus, the critically acclaimed
collaboration video from way back when she did pony stuff. The lethal Halloween. Pony
stuff? Yeah, my little pony stuff, she used to review it. I don't see those videos on
her channel anymore. Oh, they're just unlisted, just go to her playlist on Mage page. Oh,
I see. Bit back to the half an hour long product of love and labor. But doesn't she hate that
video? What? Yeah, she keeps frequently telling people how much she hates it now. Any reasons
as to why? Uh, because it sucks? But Magnum Opus? No, she never claimed it to be. Frankly,
I can see why. The script is terrible, the voice acting often lacks direction and she
was too timid to ask people to redo their lines when she thought they didn't sound
right. Oh, let's not forget the main premise is just a rip-off of Danganronpa, a game and
anime series. The art? It's good though. Just barely holds up. Things got rushed there
at the end too, as she was late to post it on Halloween. Took her months to pull all
this together. Well, uh, we can still talk about it anyway. Yeah, sure, I guess. Well,
fun trivia. All the people who participated in this collaboration were politely asked to
make little videos to link back to this project. Most of them were little skits about how they
got kidnapped from their channels. Inkrowse had to pull hers down though due to the majority
of her audience being little kids who got scared by the collaboration video. Seriously. Yeah,
NKP never put hers up to begin with. At first she said she was just late but then she just
met. Oh, that's Rich, coming from a person who later asked people who featured for a
weapon of two seconds in an animation she did, didn't even animate to upload linkbacks
to her project. Yeah, funny that. So, this was back in her pony days. Three, four years
ago? Why does she up to now? Means. What? Means. Animation means to be precise. What
are those? Oh, people take snippets from a song and animate a character dancing to it.
I use the term animate loosely here as some settle for flipping an image or peg just a
slideshow. That sounds lazy. Sure is mage, but mage's animations are not that thankfully.
Hers take literally days to complete because instead of learning how to use a proper animation
program like a sane person, she draws everything on Psy and saves each and every individual
frame separately as a PNG to later be edited in a video editing program that is not made
to cater to animation makings. To top it all off, she has no clue on how to do fancy
effects on the video editing program. Nice. But yeah, so, final words on her channel?
Uh, give her a 2 out of 10. Needs more edge. What about you? I give her a U-Try Gold Star.
Good luck in the future, mage. Hope you actually do fucking work instead of procrastinating
by doing stupid things no one asked for. Well anyway, time to wrap this up. Thank you for
joining me, mage. You too, mage. It was nice. I hope to never do this again with you. Me
too, mage. Me too. If I never see your face again, it'll be too soon.