Hello, everybody, and welcome once again to the Pro Crastinators Interview series, the one that's been on hold for six months.
Forever?
Yeah, after a mere five episodes, but we're back.
Hey.
For some reason, that reason being, we've got a new member of the Pro Crastinators podcast who's interested in being interviewed.
Is it Sheepover?
No, Sheepover...
Is it Psy?
Sheepover declined to...
Is it King Critic? Who could it be?
Oh man, three hours of King Critic, can you imagine?
No, it's Mumkey Jones!
Mumkey Jones!
Look at that audio clip, there we go.
Maybe I'll turn it back down.
So, Mumkey, what is it that made you want to be a part of this little club, this little gay ass internet arrangement?
So, clearly, I didn't have the same background as you guys did, you guys all met with your pony days and all that shit, and that's kind of...
Pretty much everything you guys represent is what I set out to humiliate and destroy.
Yeah.
So I was as surprised of being invited as I was that you guys even liked me in the first place.
But I think it's because after finding out who you guys were and being invited to be on episode 30, I think that was the empathy episode,
I watched most of your guys' stuff and I liked the vast majority of it, and I thought you guys were all cool guys,
and I thought, you know, I'm more than flattered that they liked me too, so hell yeah, let's get on board of this shit.
Yeah.
From our perspective, it was like, I mean, from the very first time I saw your videos, I was like, well, this guy's clearly coming from a similar angle to us,
but like, you know, we didn't know who you were, and then after...
It's one of those things where it's kind of the way that people have gotten into the PCP, and this is why there's this weird misconception that you can just join the PCP by having good enough videos.
Which you can.
Please send all of your amateur videos to DigiBro.
It's digitalboyreviews at gmail.com.
Like, the general way that the PCP formed was by all of us being big fans of one another, and with Monkey, it was just kind of a case that not only were you clearly like all of our videos, and all of us like yours.
Well, most.
Most.
Yeah.
Well, we like...
I've seen Ben's work, not impressed.
Initially, it was just Jesse who found you, and then he showed you to me.
God bless him.
When I find a YouTuber who makes like one video I like, I watch all of their catalogs.
So as soon as he showed me the BegottaHK video, I watched like every one of the videos on Earth.
You were fucked.
Because I had like a new video every day at some point.
Yeah.
So I watched all of it, and I was like, oh yeah, this guy's really cool, and I really enjoyed the Nuzlocke series, because I'd never seen such a like high production Let's Play before.
Hey, that was me attempting to emulate the style of Pro Jarrod, because I really liked his Nuzlocke series, but I think I did it better than him, even though he's like a big shit.
Well, it helps that you're funny.
Yeah, and Pro Jarrod is a total normal.
His audio mixing, we don't need to go too deep into this, because I know how much you love talking about audio mixing, but it's hard to hear him, because he has the game volume.
Too loud.
This is a struggle to get through, because I can't hear half the shit he's saying, and he doesn't do any audience interaction.
He's like makes up sounds, and I'm like, okay, I can take his formula and perfect it, get some audience interaction with the names, polish up the sound a little bit more, even though in the fire red days I was using like a shit microphone.
But I still think it was better than his, you know.
I mean, this is somewhere that me and Endless Jess don't quite see eye to eye on, is that I really like the audience interaction aspect.
Oh, he doesn't like it?
Well, he just hates the audience.
Yeah, he hates the idea of interacting with the audience and letting them get away with being a bunch of idiots, which you kind of do.
Which if I handled it, I wouldn't handle it the way you do.
What do I do?
I would have audience interaction, but it would be on my terms.
You kind of let the audience run wild and say whatever they want.
You mean like in the Nuzlocke, what do you mean?
Well, I just mean in general, like you interact with your audience a lot, but regardless of what they say, you will interact with it.
Like if they shit talk you, you'll still put that in a video.
It's funny.
For me, I would, I love having discussions and stuff, but like if someone's just talking shit, I'll just ban them, you know.
And then like I'll promote the, it's about cultivating your audience.
Like what you want them to be like is how you sort of promote them.
But you've kind of let yours just run free and do whatever they want.
I think it's because you and I are making very different types of content.
Yeah.
Mine are very much the, like this is the wild west of the internet where anything goes.
And I'm going to say the edgiest, most offensive, racist things I can think of.
I'm going to make fun of everybody.
No holds barred.
Whereas you're like, you know, let's, let's analyze this show and appreciate it or hate it.
So I, it makes sense that I would want more of a wild west.
The internet is a hellhole sort of comment section.
Whereas you would want a thoughtful discussion of a soul eater.
Yeah.
Hey, soul eater is cool.
He said it in a cool way.
He's excited.
It's cool.
I'm a baby.
I'm 12.
Anyways, so you, uh, yeah, you've got, you've got a very active comment section.
I imagine,
It's my favorite comment section.
I imagine that your audience interaction is heavily inspired by the, the biggest problem
in the universe podcast.
Oh, sure.
I could see that.
Yeah.
They would always bring in voicemails of people shitting on them and it was the funniest
stuff.
Yeah.
And that's like, I always wanted to get more in on that, but it doesn't fit my, again,
like you just said, we're doing very different kinds of content.
And like for me, uh, if I just make, if I'm tried to make a video like one of yours, it
would just be weird.
You know, like on the main channel.
Yeah.
Like it just, it wouldn't inspire the same kind of interactions that yours would.
Whereas like with Maddox, he's kind of had that character for so long that it was like,
you know, people were talking to him the same way they would have on the old website.
Um, you know, I remember one of the early videos I saw from you was the monkeys anime
reviews, monkeys anime reviews.
When I review myself.
Yeah, but you, you cite all these things that you've been ripping off and a lot of them
were stuff that I also was a fan of.
And I was like, when I saw a fucking biggest problem, not only that you put in Maddox, but
also Dick Masterson, I think, and I was just like, Oh my God, this dude knows his shit.
Yeah.
Um, and a touch on that a little, I mean, this is.
I touch on everything a little bit.
This is, this is breaching away from just you personally.
But you are like one of the only people I know who got into biggest problem via Dick
Masterson.
That's right.
And what's the deal with that?
So I was on poll one day.
The best four-chan board.
Oh, okay.
Let's go back in time about 10 years when I was a sophomore in high school.
10 years.
Well, let's go back in time about six, seven years.
I would have been like 15 or 16.
So yeah, about five years.
I found the, the Dr. Phil clip, the infamous men are better than women with Dick Masterson
on Dr. Phil.
And I was really inspired.
I thought it was the coolest thing ever.
And I bought the book.
And then in my sophomore year, I did, you always have to do those book projects in high
school, like read a book and write a letter to the author or write a three page report.
So I did mine over the biggest, or I did mine over men are better than women by Dick Masterson.
But little 15, 16 year old mum, he didn't know it was satire.
I thought it was a real like guy.
I was like, what, this guy has the coolest name ever.
It's perfect.
So I wrote this.
The letter I wrote to the author was kind of satire because I just wanted to piss off
my teacher because she was a hardcore, like feminist, you know, feminazi bitch.
I was like, okay, I'm going to write a letter to the author praising his genius piece of
work, men are better than women.
So then that's the end of that.
You know, Dick really didn't put out anything else that I could find.
Did you not get any trouble for that essay?
She thought it was funny.
Yeah.
So she has a sense of humor, at least.
Mine would not have.
No, not.
My also feminist AP English teacher.
You probably would have gotten sent to the guidance counselor.
Again.
Yeah, again.
But then fast forward, I guess three or four years later, because I couldn't find anything
else from Dick.
He kind of, the character disappeared and he went off and daxed at his own thing.
But then I'm on poll and I see there's a whole thread about how Dick Masterson just
did a podcast episode about SJWs and I'm thinking, what the fuck?
Yeah.
What?
That's a dream come true.
So of course I clicked the link and there we go.
It's like what?
Episode 50, something of biggest problem.
I'm like, holy shit.
This is a gold mine.
There's a whole Dick Masterson podcast.
I didn't know who Maddox was.
I had never heard of him up until that point.
Haven't even seen him at that point.
So I go listen to the back catalog.
It's the best podcast I've ever heard.
So yeah, I joined it.
I started listening because of my love of Dick.
And then I grew to love Maddox and now it's a full circle of...
Yeah.
It's a...
What's the...
A parabola.
Sure.
It's a roller coaster because you go on the ride but you end at the same place you get
on.
Yeah.
So you took a lot of influence from that podcast in the way you interact with fans,
reading comments on the show, allowing lots of shitposting.
It's a shame you don't have a voicemail.
Yeah, that'd be fun.
If people sent me like a soundcloud of them shitting on me, I'd probably do an episode
about it.
It'd be fun.
I always thought it's interesting how you take it kind of to the next level and that
you've had people just outright make videos on your channels.
What is the deal with Baku Boys and it all that?
How does that come to pass?
Baku Boys in particular is just somebody who over the last year of me doing this with
an audience, he's just like somebody who became my friend and he wanted to do a parody of
the show, which was just this unwatchable garbage of a parody, parody anime review.
And Mumkey Jones 2, my second channel, which used to be my main channel until it got
striked and I was like, nope, I'm not putting up with this, time to start over.
And now that the strikes are gone, Mumkey Jones 2 is my designated shitposting channel
and I just straight up said, anybody can send me anything and I'll put it on this channel,
I don't care.
So that's how we get the Cream Man, Nuzlocke Let's Plays, we get Baku Boys, Terrible Reviews,
there's all kinds of fun stuff on there.
Because I mean it's just a shitpost channel, you know, it's fun.
So how many YouTube channels have you had?
Oh god, like my whole life?
Infinite number.
I was talking to Jess about you and he was saying something about you being fairly new
and I was like, well, I'm pretty sure Mumkey Jones is like not even close to your first YouTube channel.
It's just the first one that's gotten popular.
What is the first YouTube channel you ever made?
What year and what was on it?
First one I made was when I was 11, so actually 10 years ago, and it was called Nubs because
my nickname in I guess middle school was Nubs because I would pull my arm inside of my shirt
and then just stick out the elbow so it was like I was a war veteran who got his arm chopped off.
So everybody called me Nubs back in the day.
Have you ever not been a human shitpost?
I don't think so.
I would get in trouble all the time in elementary school.
My whole life I've always gotten in trouble for just trying to be funny.
For being what we in professional circles refer to as a little shit.
Yep, I mean some people seem to like it.
And on that channel I would, my mum had like a shitty little tiny picture camera,
but it could also record videos so I'd have my little brother Patsy who would have been 8 or 9 at the time,
record me doing like Chris Angel Mindfreak parodies and I was also a fan of the movie Super Size Me
with Morgan Spurlock where he eats McDonald's every day for 30 days.
I started doing parodies of that where I would like drink milk for 30 days
or be trapped in my bedroom closet for 30 days, but I mean obviously it's fake.
I'm just doing it all the same day.
It's all sound genius. How watchable are they?
They're not. They're awful.
I don't think they exist anymore because that channel, so this is the first time I got a channel taken down.
I assume for copyright reasons.
Or possibly community guidelines violations.
So I was 13 at the time. I'm 2 years deep into this channel.
I got just tons of horrible, unwatchable garbage on there that I would relentlessly like post all over the internet
because I wanted to become YouTube famous as all 11 year olds tend to do.
This is 2007, right?
Well now that you're 13 it's 2009.
So like YouTube celebrity is not really a thing yet.
It's just that we knew there were some videos that were big.
That was back when Little Caribo and AVGN were celebrities and they had like 40,000 subs.
Yeah, and they weren't even really on YouTube at the beginning.
Yeah, they're on websites.
Yeah, I knew both of them at the time, but I didn't associate them with YouTube at all.
I also didn't think they made money.
I didn't think anybody was making money doing this until Game Grumps revealed that they were making money in the first episode.
So here's how the channel got taken down.
This is the downfall of nubs.
There's this video I found.
I don't remember what it was called, but the premise is that they have an Elmo toy.
And this is like a professional film company made this video for their channel.
And it's called like, it's like Elmo's a pimp.
And Elmo's like, I'm gonna bitch slap a hoe. I'm Elmo.
It's like that kind of thing.
So what I did was I downloaded their video and then I uploaded it on my channel and I called it Elmo's a pimp in all caps.
And it got like a good amount of views.
So you just straight-free booted their video.
So then the company-
Why did you think that was okay?
This is not the end of my hubris, my friend.
So the company very politely just sends me a YouTube message saying, hey, this is our video.
Can you take it down?
God, this must be like way before the whole content ID day.
It's way back in the day.
I can't even imagine a company politely messaging me to take my video down today.
Believe it or not, I did not take advantage of their kindhearted gesture.
Because I reply, I'm ready.
I'm like, hey, this is a good opportunity for me.
I said, how about you make a video like making fun of me or something?
Oh, I see. You tried to game them back.
And then the next day my channel was deleted.
Wow.
It didn't work.
That's a little shit when I was 13.
That was a foolish endeavor all around, I would say.
So all those videos are gone.
Why in the first place did you think it would be a good idea to re-upload their video?
Because I was like 12.
I thought it's popular, so I'll also get...
What even could you rip it with back then?
Did they have YouTube rips? Websites?
They must have. We had something.
Yeah, well, so that's your first channel, Dead.
So I'm assuming you didn't have any side channels at the time.
It was just that one.
I didn't know. I didn't need any side channels because nobody was watching.
So what's the next channel you make?
Then in, I guess in high school I had one that still exists,
but once Monkey got big I changed the name and I put all the videos on private.
So all these videos are still out there.
And I can post them sometime, just not yet.
I'm biding my time for these ones.
But these ones, like, maybe there's some that are watchable, you know?
What kind of videos are they?
Like sketch comedy, kind of stuff.
I've talked about this other places, but we did a kind of a game show
based off of impractical jokers and kind of like based off a jackass
called Challenge Showdown where my group of friends, each episode,
one of them would be randomly picked to do a crazy challenge,
like chug five, five hour energies at the same time,
or go into Walmart and throw spaghetti all over the cash register person.
Now how bad is the production quality of this shit?
Are you talking like barely audible wind noise everywhere?
Um, most of it was filmed indoors, so it's not too bad.
Wait, one of them threw spaghetti at a cashier.
Yeah, that's inside Walmart.
We were filming inside the store.
Oh my god, you didn't get in trouble for that one?
No, we left. We ran out.
Well, so okay, you had this show, then just sketch comedy.
Yeah, I had a sketch show.
I started a film club in my school because I wanted people to make videos with me
because like nobody really wanted to.
I was the only guy in the whole school making videos.
So I started a film club and the show I started using the people who joined the film club
was called Family Sitcom.
I wanted to call it Family Shitcom, but it was associated with the school so I couldn't.
And the idea was I wanted to, every week I wanted to have a new sketch out
and I did that for about two months.
And some of those are pretty golden actually.
Some of them I consider to be like the best things I've made.
So you've always been pretty prolific.
Yeah, I've tried to keep myself to a schedule.
Yeah, because I think it's the most important thing about building up skill is to work fast
and get lots of stuff out there.
And it's especially important when you're young.
Like you build up that speed and that stamina and then you never quite lose it.
It's like once you've done a video every week then you now know that that's a thing you can do.
So then going into the future you are always like, well I know I did that before.
So I know it's possible.
And something that pisses me off is I'll always see comments about like,
oh, monkey, it should be quality over quantity.
And I'm like, bitch, fuck it, they're quality and they're quantity, fuck you.
Well, I mean that's the thing, it's like you can do, if someone only gets out one video every six months
and it's extremely high quality, but you get out a video every week
and at least one out of four is extremely high quality, who's got the better channel?
Yeah, I would rather watch a weekly show that's like a six out of ten
than watch one episode of a ten out of ten show that comes out once a year.
That's just me and I can see why people wouldn't like that as much,
but I'd rather just have more consistent shows.
Yeah, it's helpful for, it works well with what YouTube is now, which is a replacement for television.
No one's watching TV, we need something to be, we need a constant drip feed of YouTube content
to fill in our day and as much as I love those ten out of ten videos
where I can go back and watch them again, it's like this isn't helping me on the daily grind of my life
where I need there to be a certain number of hours of YouTube content every day,
which for me, I don't get enough of it from other people so I just make it myself.
Yeah, you have to make your own videos.
I think I heard that DigiBro just watches his own videos all day because they're so good.
I heard that somewhere, I don't know where.
That's not true at all.
So what do you watch?
Because in spite of making a channel called Mumkey's Anime Reviews, you don't really watch much anime.
No.
And you've indicated a few times that you don't watch a whole lot of YouTube, it doesn't seem like.
So what do you spend your time on? What do Mumkeys get down to?
Most of my day is just spent sitting there wishing I had something to do.
I've said this a million times, the best treatment for depression is distractions,
and I think my problem is I keep running out of distractions and that's why I always feel so depressed all the time.
That's precisely why up until you come, like all I've been looking forward to all month is you coming here today,
and then me planning what I'm going to do for the next month and a half,
because I've been depressed for most of this year so far,
and the only thing that's going to get me out of it is...
That Donald Trump election, man. Really got to you.
I don't even care about that.
But I've been depressed for most of the year and it's mostly because there's not enough to do,
sitting around in your room, even if you run out of YouTube videos, you're fucked.
You're just like, well, I don't know what else I'm supposed to be doing right now,
and watching anime is too tied to work for me, so it's not as relaxing as it should be.
You can't just sit there and watch, you have to analyze everything.
Or even if I could, I just feel like it's all tied to work somehow.
But I'm like, I need to get out of the house or just hang out with other people,
and I'm like, well, at least I'll know that the weekend that Mumkeys at my house,
I won't be depressed because we'll be doing things.
We'll just occupy our time.
And the best part is, I don't have to look at Twitter, I don't have to look at my YouTube comments,
because I don't need something to distract me from what's going on.
And Twitter and comments are just going to make you more depressed.
Right, exactly.
Well, that's the thing.
The only reason to look at them is that you have nothing better to do.
I would never go on Twitter at all if I had anything to do,
but because I don't, I'll just sit there and read people talking shit about me all day
and getting more and more angry and making more and more drunken rants,
all because I'm too bored and I don't have enough to do.
But I'm certainly not thinking about shitty commenters while we're doing a podcast,
aside from the fact that I'm referring to them.
So, all right, we kind of got off away from your YouTube videos.
I still want to know more about your other channels.
So, you've got the one that's all set to private right now.
What came next after that?
Then came The Mumkey and Big Show, which is what got this whole Mumkey thing started,
which was just a shitty Let's Play channel with me and my old pal Biggs,
who has appeared in a few anime reviews.
And a lot of Drunken Minecraft.
Yeah, yeah, he came back from The Let's Play Show.
And I've told this story a million times, but I'm sure somebody doesn't know it.
But the gist is, me and Biggs did a YouTube Let's Play channel for about two years.
Then I started making the anime reviews just because I was bored and I thought it'd be funny.
And so the first one was Girls Bravo.
And then like seven months later came The Death Note 1.
And then five months later came The Yamada 1.
And then like half a year after that is when the Yamada video went viral for the first time.
Got a shit ton of views and I was like, okay, okay, finally something. People like it.
Wait, which channel was this all on?
This is on The Monkey and Biggs Show.
Okay, so the original post of Monkey and Biggs Show,
which was mostly a Let's Play channel that just had a few anime reviews spliced in?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
So at that point we got a bunch of subscribers on The Monkey and Biggs Show,
but I knew, well, when we upload more Let's Plays, they're gonna leave.
They don't want to watch this shit.
Right.
So I made a new channel called Monkey's Anime Reviews.
And that's where that's where that started.
And I started making anime reviews on the weekly.
So how much did the Yamada video blow up on The Monkey and Biggs Show?
What view count were we talking?
Like 400,000.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
So huge.
Huge.
So you can imagine my sadness when Biggs makes the decision to delete the channel
without like asking me or, you know, he could have just quit being on it.
But no, he had to delete it.
And YouTube, of course, the great company that they are,
if a channel gets deleted for any reason, they're not gonna give it back to you.
Christ.
So my big viral video gone forever.
Yeah.
That's a serious fucking view count.
400,000.
Yeah.
What was your subscriber total on that channel?
I think it peaked at like 1,000.
Okay.
So the viralness did not attract subscribers because most of the channel was Let's Play.
When they saw it was a Let's Play channel, I imagine they scurried away.
How many, like what was the frequency of uploads of these Let's Plays and what games and stuff?
So this is when I got real serious about doing a schedule.
And for a long time, The Monkey and Big Show, for almost an entire year we had two new videos
a day.
Oh my god.
We had-
Full Game Grumps.
Yeah.
I've heard parts of this story, but I didn't realize that The Monkey and Big Show had been around
for so long and had so many videos.
This was like a serious full blown channel.
Yes.
Why did he delete it?
That's why it was so devastating.
And you didn't kill him.
I almost did.
I didn't talk to him for a long, long time.
Yeah.
Which I shouldn't have even talked to him ever again, but-
Did he ever like apologize?
Of course not.
Of course fucking not.
Fucking piece of shit.
He still thinks he's justified to this day.
Why did he delete it?
What was his reason?
Because now that we had an audience and like we were averaging about 100 views per Let's
Play episode, I was like, oh yeah, people are actually watching.
So Biggs took it upon himself to actually, because I would edit and upload every single
video.
Right.
And my internet was shit, so it would take me like three hours to upload each video,
living out in the boonies.
So I said, hey Biggs, can you edit these and upload them?
All you have to do is watch them and make sure we don't say each other's names and if we
do, edit it out and then upload it.
He said, oh yeah, I'll do it.
I'll do it.
Three days ago by, he wouldn't upload a video.
So I'd be pestering him in the text.
Yeah, dude, you missed the upload again today.
What's going on?
Oh yeah, I'll do it.
I'll do it.
Doesn't do it.
I keep pestering him.
He's like, oh, oh, fine, fine.
If you think I'm so lazy, I'll just delete it.
What?
It's early enough.
It was gone.
What the fuck?
Yeah, that's the, and that's one of the best friends I've ever had, did you?
One of the best friends I've ever had deleted my viral video.
Yeah.
Biggs, you are a human waste.
I hope you get diabetes and die.
I think he hopes that too.
You're singing him praises as far as he's concerned.
All right, so Monkey and Biggs gets deleted.
Where do we go from here?
So now I still have the Monkey's Anime Reviews channel, which luckily a lot of people had
already switched over to.
But now I have to find a way to get all those views back on the Omni Video, which doesn't
happen for quite a few months, but at some point it does go viral on Reddit again.
So this is the second time.
The same video goes viral and gets on the front page of Reddit.
Unbelievable luck that that happened.
It's happened like three times total.
So it was luck the first time.
I mean, I guess that video is just that good.
I guess so.
I mean, it's a lot like I had a similar experience with my why good anime is hard to make video,
where that one had like went viral when it came out and got up to 300,000 views.
And then a full year later, it just suddenly rocketed up to a million.
And I have no idea why still.
I don't know where you don't know where it was posted.
No idea.
I don't know if it was posted in a place or if it just got caught up because it was around.
It was like I hit 100,000 subscribers.
And right after that happened, like all my videos started getting a lot more views as
a YouTube start.
I think YouTube starts promoting you more once you hit 100K.
I need to hit 100K.
It takes you more seriously as a channel.
And so it starts, it puts you puts you in the algorithm more.
And so that video just caught a second wind and fucking like wildfire blew up the channel.
Yeah.
And I gained like, it was like I hit 100K after like a slow steady buildup.
And then the next 30K in like a week.
God damn.
Well, I hope that happens to me.
I can't wait.
It sounds great.
What were you about to say?
You're continuing your story.
You've got monkeys anime.
Yeah.
Okay.
So it blows up again and I'm ecstatic.
So what kind of blow up are we talking about this time?
I'm getting one new subscriber, I think every 10 seconds.
Jesus.
And this happens for a full night.
So I wake up the next morning and it's like thousands higher than it was when I went to bed.
And it's still growing and growing and growing.
I'm like, oh yeah.
Yeah, this is great.
I got him.
I got him in videos.
How many views does this second Yamada video?
They always end up with like half a million.
Okay.
Yeah.
So three times this video has reached half a million.
And this motherfucker, Flutterbutter, who God bless him because he patroned me at $50 per month for a long time to make up for this.
When he found it the first time, he took my Yamada video and put it on his Facebook account without any link to my YouTube or anything.
So free booted it.
Yeah.
Like who would do such a thing?
Who would just download somebody else's hard work video and upload it further as if they made it?
Like I can't think of a bigger scumbag.
Do you know that term free booting?
No, I mean I can assume what it means.
Well it was coined specifically to refer to the Facebook because there's tons of people who do this who take YouTube videos, re-upload them to Facebook with like the identifier scrubbed off and they go viral there because it's easier on Facebook.
It happened to Jesse with Fuck Up Dates.
That video has a lot of views anyway though.
It has like 100,000 on YouTube.
It has millions on Facebook from people's free booting.
Hey I was going to say my Yamada video on Flutterbutter's Facebook got 2 million views and I, like that, I was flabbergasted.
That's a lot.
Yeah.
I'm imagining all the ad revenue I missed out on.
Uh, $2,000.
The ad revenue you missed out on.
Hey Flutterbutter thanks for I guess the 250 you gave me on Patreon.
Did he make money off of the Facebook?
I have no idea.
I don't care.
I really don't care.
Yeah.
So uh, so you've got, you're now gaining subs on Monkey's Anime reviews.
At this point, my channel, so my channel has two strikes on it.
Because I made a review of Boku No Pico where I did, I made no effort to censor anything.
Yeah.
Because I thought that the anime having a pixelated penis was enough censorship.
No.
Not even close.
So that's strike number one.
Strike number two.
Not to mention there's like cum everywhere.
Well, I mean, I said in the review that it was like ice cream or something, so I thought it was okay.
Yeah, no.
Not happening.
Uh, so you think I would learn my lesson?
No.
Because then, number two, strike number two, I make Boku No Pico abridged.
Oh no.
Which is currently still uploaded on my Facebook page if you're curious to see it.
Again, that gets, that gets blown the fuck out.
They're like, nope.
Strike two.
Now my channel is blowing up and I think, okay.
These are community guidelines strikes, by the way, which are much harder to beat back than, than, than content ID.
Because they usually, I've had a couple of them on totally innocuous videos that still managed to, I couldn't get them back.
I couldn't beat the claims.
What was there?
What were they saying?
What's wrong with it?
One, one was on a video about a pony ask blog called Ask Princess Milestia.
And there was a huge, like.
Well, I wonder why they took it down.
Well, the thing is, none of the imagery was actually, like, 18 plus or anything.
But this, there was a, this is how I found out about SJWs.
Because there was a huge SJW screed against that blog.
And they got it taken off of Tumblr.
They got Tumblr, a website full of porn, to take down Ask Princess Milestia because they were offended about it.
I think there was an internet aristocrat video about this very thing.
I, I distinctly remember something about that.
But yeah, they got that blog taken down and then they got my video taken down about the blog.
So, and so I got a guideline strike on that, contested it, didn't win.
The next one I got, this one's just utter bullshit, was for a review of JoJo's Bizarre Adventure that there was literally, I have no idea.
I think someone just had it out for me and got a guideline strike on it.
And yeah, it just went down.
And then I think I did beat that one, but it took a while.
And it was just like, yeah, guideline strikes are hard to beat.
They're pain in the ass.
Well, I didn't get an opportunity to try to fight the third one because once you hit strike three, you're out.
You don't even get a chance to say, hey, you know, you took this down wrong.
So when I see him blowing up, I think, okay, I got to make a new video right now to celebrate all these new subs.
So I wanted to make a satirical video mocking how like porn on YouTube and people are always looking for porn on YouTube.
And if you're like, I had it on the Let's Play series that there was, we're doing Mega Man Legends too.
And at the time, each episode had like maybe 20 views, but then there was one that had like kind of a pornographic name and it had like 10 times the views.
So that was my inspiration.
Like, why the fuck it says Mega Man Legends, let's play episode 14, like role hentai or something.
Why does this have so many more views?
Why are these idiots clicking on this?
Why are they searching for this on YouTube?
So the whole video was making fun of kind of that idea.
But I think where I fucked up was that the title of the video to play into the satire was all caps.
Hentai porn, XXX, YouTube naked girls, boobs, blah, blah, blah.
So I think that just hit the computer, the system, they're like, oh, take it down, take it down.
Like there's no way computers don't understand satire, I guess.
So they see that title and they take it down.
It's also that misleading titles are against the YouTube problem.
It wasn't misleading.
It's a satirical thing, right?
I would argue for it.
I would argue against YouTube about that, but you didn't get the chance.
Yeah, I didn't get the chance.
So they take down the video and now I have no YouTube channel, they're all gone.
So when I make the new one, all the old fans have to somehow come back and find me.
Because I don't have a Twitter, I don't have a Facebook or anything at that point.
Or maybe I'd started the Facebook maybe.
But yeah, so I have to pretty much start from scratch again and all the fans have to find me again.
I'm sure there's hundreds, if not thousands of people out there who just forgot about me and never bothered to find me again.
Which is so disappointing and sad.
That's why I keep...
The reason I have so many social media accounts everywhere is for this exact reason.
There's always people who won't...
I mean, there's people still who watch all of my main channel videos and somehow don't know about Digiroft or Dark
or the Twitter or something, even though I mentioned it in every video I make.
But there's always someone who's discovering it for the first time.
But for me, it's just, I just need there to be...
It's like one of those ancient demons where as long as one percent of it survives, the rest can grow back.
That's how I feel. As long as there's some people who know who I am, I can grow back.
So if the YouTube channel goes, at least I've got the Twitter guys, they'll follow me to the next channel.
And that channel will grow on its own.
But you were kind of an up shit creak with literally no power.
Had nothing.
So that's when... What is now Monkey Jones 2? That's when I made that channel.
Which was just called Monkey Jones at the time.
Because I dropped the name Monkey's Anime Reviews in favor of Monkey Jones.
I think that's what happened. This is all a blur in my head over the last year.
But then, of course, I start getting strikes on this channel too.
I'm like, fuck it, we're starting over again, boys!
So I make the new Monkey Jones channel, switch the old one to...
It was called Too Damn Monkey as a reference to Filthy Frank's shitpost channel.
And it was called this for a while. When I followed you, it was still called Too Damn Monkey.
It was called that for about half a year, I think, and then I decided, now let's just make it two.
People are too confused by what it means, and I'm tired of explaining it.
And then all the strikes, you know, cleared off, and now I have, you know, all four of these channels.
So this is why if you go all the way back through Monkey Jones 2, some of the Anime Reviews are there.
Yeah.
Some of the early ones.
But I made the new channel, I just reposted all of the Anime Reviews again.
I think there were like 10 up to that point.
So the current Monkey's Anime Reviews, Yamada's first time blows up a third time.
Yep.
This video has saved your life countless times.
Because if not for it blowing up again, you would still be in the situation if no one knows where you are.
I'd probably still be at like, you know, 500 subs at this point.
But yeah, it keeps blowing up, and then that gives people opportunities to find other videos that have potential for blowing up.
The Elliot Rodger video has been posted in some subreddits.
The InCells video gets posted to InCells like every week.
That's fucking great.
How do they feel about it?
For the most part, they think it's funny, but they're like, oh, he's misrepresenting this guy.
Oh, of course.
And I'm like, dude, I just took posts from here.
Yeah, literal quotes from you guys.
But I mean, I did go out of my way to find the funny stuff.
Right, of course.
I mean, I don't know.
The concept alone is hilarious.
And the Corey in the House video has been posted some places because it's my second most viewed video, I think.
Which I think it should be first.
I think it's way better than Yamada.
But I just have a personal preference for Elliot Rodger stuff.
I think the Yamada one is...
It's one of my favorites on your channel just because it's got that...
It's such a clear line.
You know, there's no...
Like most of your videos, they go in a lot of different directions.
Yamada is just one tension build the whole way through.
It just starts off seeming one way, then it starts to lean.
It just keeps leaning further and further until it just falls right off a cliff.
And that's what's so great about it.
And people say, why don't you make more videos like Yamada?
You need to keep making...
This is the video everybody likes, but I feel like I can't.
No, it's not duplicatable.
No, you can't.
And it'll be so obvious that he's just doing Yamada again.
You can't please these fucking idiots.
Well, that's what people don't under...
People who aren't creative don't understand that like...
You can't just make Yamada again.
Yeah, you can't just fucking recreate the same thing.
And it's going to be obvious and it's never going to top it.
Because now everybody's expecting it, so the joke doesn't work.
If it was already...
It'd be one thing if you made a video that wasn't super successful,
it was a good idea, and then you iterated on that and made a better version.
But if it was already a huge success, there's no topping it.
There's no surprise anymore.
Yeah, like we already have the Yamada video.
It's already done the rounds.
Several rounds.
Now it's time for something else to do the rounds.
Can I find another video that is not the same, but will also become a huge hit?
Oh, Jesus.
Alright.
That about capitalizing your whole YouTube history.
Do you have any other channels we should know about?
I mean, we've got the new gaming channel.
Yeah, yeah.
So, well, that's another sad tale of a co-host that didn't work.
But it started off as a monkey and an animal's gaming expedition.
And I tested the waters on the main Monkey Jones channel with my fire red Nuzlocke Let's Play.
And, you know, a fair number of people have liked it.
So I said, okay, I'll do a separate channel so that your feed...
Most people just want the anime reviews.
Let's not clog up their feed with three times a week of Pokemon Let's Play.
I'll do a new channel with it.
And my buddy, Manimal, he's been wanting to do video game review videos for years.
And he keeps talking about how he's going to start his own video game review channel.
I said, dude, you can join up with me.
We're like best buds at this point.
I'll give you a free audience of a thousand people.
This great opportunity that most new content creators don't get.
You can just... I'll give you my audience.
You have the exact mindset I do, Monkey.
That's what I've told so many of Victor or other friends of mine, where I'm just like...
You don't understand that if you make anything and I like it and I can promote it, you're in the door.
You know, like a shade as a music producer.
He's made hundreds of dollars just because he makes beats for me and I'm already famous.
So people will buy my album because I'm Digi Bro.
It's like shade, all you have to do is make...
No other musician gets this opportunity to just make money just because you're tied to this other guy.
But it's totally worth it because you can launch a career out of it.
If people like your beats, they're going to want to hire you to do more.
I've been trying to convince Victor for years to become a YouTuber.
He just doesn't have a good idea for what he wants to do with it.
Isn't it weird how frustrating it is that nobody wants to take advantage of you?
I don't say that with any irony or anything.
I want my friends to take advantage of me so that they can be making things with me.
You know, Cob always wanted to make videos with me. He made a lot of videos with me back in the day.
Cob, hey, I got 10,000 subs. Let's make some stuff together. People will watch it.
I don't know.
Part of the problem is that it's so hard to convince people that it can take off.
For instance, on DigiBros, it's a Let's Play channel that for a very long time we didn't take seriously at all.
It was just for fun and I would have my friends and stuff on there.
I would always be like, you know guys, if we want to take this seriously, this channel can take off and it can become a job.
But no one would ever do it because they just don't see it.
Even though I'm standing here with a 300,000 subscriber channel going, I know it's possible.
I even know how to do it.
But it's just a matter of convincing people like, hey, I know that this seems like it won't work out
and for a year it's going to seem that way, but eventually it will take off.
I think it revealed to me that there is a very clear distinction between those who are consumers and those who are creators.
And I think it takes a very particular type of person to be an actual creator who has a bit of a work ethic
and actually is motivated to do things.
And I found very quickly that none of my friends meet that criteria.
So I was like, oh man, you want to do this, here's the audience for it, do it, oh yeah, okay.
What you just described is how the procrastinators happened.
Because individually, none of us have friends who will do things.
Ben and Nate are brothers and that's why both of them are, they both work on creative projects,
which is why they're both in the PCP.
We've had times where my brother and Hippo's brother were both in there.
We've had them in the chat before, but they never posted or anything and they never made anything.
So they're very talented, either one of them could launch a YouTube channel.
They just didn't have good ideas for it.
And all my other friends, I would try to get them involved in every video all the time.
I always wanted them in less place.
That's been the last year of my life.
I would always want to do skits, no one ever wanted to do skits.
It's so frustrating.
It's really difficult because you're just, it's like you can see the successful version of it.
You can picture in your mind, guys, if you just, if you just for one afternoon,
decide you want to just like stop sitting around being ironic hipsters about everything
and work on a video and take it seriously.
There's a chance this video could set us all up with careers, you know,
but no one will do it because they can't picture it the way that you can.
And the thing that makes me the most angry is that these fuckers are all talk.
They're all bark and no bite because they would spend, you know, the years before I was monkey,
we would just sit around and they'd talk about how they want to make all these things.
And now that I'm actually doing it and they have the opportunity to join me,
suddenly now they don't want to.
And I'd rather just play Call of Duty again tonight.
Where the fuck was the cop from three years ago who was making videos with me every fucking weekend?
Now that we have success you give up, that doesn't make any fucking sense.
It's just people become complacent because at some point, as a creative minded person,
I think there's a definitive moment when it sinks in, I'm not built for this.
You know, and it's like, it's when, I think maybe it's because you got successful that they realize.
I sense a lot of resentment about it.
I think it was a lot of jealousy and that might sound conceited,
but I feel like a lot of them felt that way like, oh, monkey doesn't deserve it.
I do. I'm grumble, grumble. I don't want to eat off of his success.
I do.
I mean, my friends weren't quite like that, but I definitely think that it was when I started,
I started really making it that it, when one person makes it, it makes everyone else assess
what's the difference between me and them.
And then that's when they realize maybe I can't do it.
Like when they realize that you were doing work every week
and that they did not want to do that work every week
or like once they understood what the work would be
and that they didn't want to do that work, you know?
They decided, you know, maybe I'm better just as a consumer.
Right.
Not as a creator.
I mean, that's why I never became a filmmaker because before I did YouTube for years,
I wanted to be a film director.
Me and my cousin Boyd and my brother Victor.
Well, the thing is that like we got all the material, we had a camera, we had, you know,
I'd listened to all these Quentin Tarantino and Robert Rodriguez talking about like,
just pick up your camera and go outside and film stuff.
I didn't go to film school.
I went to films.
Yeah.
Well, there was one quote in particular where Tarantino says,
spend your whole, like every day when you come home from work, work on a script.
And then on the weekend, shoot that script.
That's how you become a great filmmaker.
And I was like, that makes perfect sense.
That's obviously what you have to do.
But if you come home from work and you don't want to write a script
and this keeps happening and you keep telling yourself you'll do it eventually,
at some point you have to say, well, this obviously is something I'm never going to do.
And I think that might be, you know, what happened to my cousin
because he for a very long time was saying he was going to be a director.
And then at some point he just stopped bringing it up, you know,
because I think he realized, well, I'm not doing it.
So I'm obviously not doing it.
Whereas Victor is now doing it.
Yeah.
And I mean, I feel the same way as my cousin.
I gave up at some point I realized I like, like,
how about instead of forcing myself to try to make films,
which I'm obviously not doing,
I could look at this thing that I do every day for no reason,
which is right about anime and try to make a career out of that, you know.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess there are some things that you're just more pre pre built for doing
and you should figure that out.
Anyway, what I'm trying to get at is that Manimal was super excited about making these reviews
and then he never did.
But we we did want it.
He was very adamant that it shouldn't be just a let's play channel
because he looks down on that.
I used to as well.
But now, now that I know, like,
I think everybody does until they do it.
Right.
It's not because I realize podcasts.
It's not because I realize all this is easy and easy video,
but because like it does mean something to a lot of the audience to have like every day.
Here's my 15 minute video where I hear these people who I like talking about.
If you're if you're fucking entertaining enough that people will watch it,
you've earned it, you know.
Yeah, that's true.
Like people people can shit all day on like the Game Grumps, for instance.
And I mean, I don't think they're funny anymore.
But like the idea of being as funny as they are as consistently as they were
for a fucking year with two uploads a day, 20 minutes a day of you being funny.
You know, that's 20 minutes of improv comedy coming out every single day.
Like in the game does not carry it.
Like people watch Game Grumps for them.
People don't care about the video games they're playing.
I can't remember the last time I watched the Game Grumps without it being open in a different tab.
Yeah.
I just listen to them talk.
I mean, if sometimes it's a game they're more reactive to you will.
But like, you know, if you're watching like Pokemon, you know, look at that.
Yeah.
Open it up in a new tab, sit around, listen to it all day, you know, or,
or just have it on like when I binge watched the entire Dan era, I just had it.
Fuck.
I just had it full screen.
Was that like a year and a half at that point?
Yeah, it was close to two years.
That's a lot.
Yeah.
And I hadn't seen any of it because I'd quit after John left.
That's fair.
And so I caught up on all of it in the span of a couple of weeks after my,
it was when my channel got deleted by YouTube.
So I was depressed.
So I just laid on like the couch and watched and just binged it for fucking two weeks.
And was it a good two weeks or a bad two weeks?
Well, I mean,
Gingrumps numbed me to the crushing pain that I was feeling outside of watching Game Grumps.
Now, did, did you dislike Dan at first or like, did he grow on you?
Or are we always the same?
Um, he definitely grew on me in this.
I don't think I disliked him.
It was just that the breakup was so traumatizing.
And it was so out of nowhere.
Yeah.
And then that Dan sounded a lot like he, his voice was too similar to Aaron and he wasn't
confrontational in the way that they've been before.
It just didn't have the same chemistry.
And suddenly he was half the channel because he was on both steam train and Game Grumps.
Well, and I found steam train insufferable and I still do.
I've never been able to sit through a whole episode.
Is it because of Ross?
Yeah.
I mean, it's, it's that, uh, like Ross and Barry can be funny, but just not on that show.
Like they can't be funny as, uh, as guys playing video games.
Yeah.
I, I like Barry probably 30 times more than I like Ross.
I think Barry is pretty cool.
I think, I think both of that.
Like if you listen to like Ross and Aaron talk about animation, like that one, uh, let's draw that they did.
It was like 50 minutes of them just discussing animation.
Ross comes off as like a cool and interesting guy.
Um, but when he's trying to be like funny and off the cuff, he just comes off as an obnoxious fucking boy.
Uh, and then Barry is just, uh, too normie.
I think he's just not a comedian.
He doesn't have like the comedy chops.
He's a good editor and he's, you know, he can write a good script, but not a good, uh, anyway, we're, we're off in the weeds.
Yeah.
So he, Manimal didn't want it to be a standard Let's Play channel.
He wanted us to put in a whole bunch of work.
He wanted all the boring parts to be cut out, which for a long time we did.
I think the first game we did was his, one of his favorite games, Shadow Run.
Was it the first?
Yeah.
And like those are heavily edited.
There's always shit getting cut out all the time.
Yeah.
He also wanted us to do skits and stuff.
And those almost, almost primarily or almost exclusively came up in the Nuzlocs.
Like the FireRed Nuzlocke had some fun live action skits with Manimal.
And then, uh, I don't know.
We did some other things.
Which the live action skits in the FireRed playthrough are legendary.
That's some of my favorite parts of your whole channel.
Just him running shirtless through the woods in like this weird junk pile.
That's out there.
Yeah.
Going like, beef jerky.
Need food.
And then like, doesn't he tear his shirt off in one of them?
He does that all the time.
Yeah, he tears his shirt off.
There's a part where he's, he's like running around your house and there's just like a sink full of beef jerky.
And he just like sees it and just starts eating it.
Like eating out of the trash and shit.
And then he like suplexes you or something at one point.
Yeah.
And then at the end when he's leaving, he like steals my garbage can because he loves garbage.
And he runs off with it.
That's my, that's one of my favorite like skits ever in a video.
It's the whole Manimal.
That's why I was so sad that Manimal's not around anymore.
Yeah.
So he wanted to do all these skits and to highly polish these Let's Plays.
And then he also wanted to start his big game analysis thing.
But then none of it happened.
He's like, hey Manimal, you want to come over and record some skits for a video?
Oh no.
Okay.
When he's over, when he's over and recording a Let's Play, hey, we should do a skit for this.
No, I don't want to.
Hey Manimal.
You said you're going to do a Nuzlocke.
How's that coming?
Oh, I'm working on it.
Yeah.
So I'm starting to realize, oh, he doesn't have it.
He doesn't have it.
Without me, Manimal's nothing.
He's not going to make anything on his own ever.
I mean, I could tell that immediately.
Like I loved him as a skit prop and I thought if he was, if he was serious about like participating,
he would always have been a good guy to have around.
Like it's great to have a cool, strong guy.
To just have one to show off in a video, like a such a great character because as a bunch
of nerds on the internet, I think we all have a certain reverence for big, cool, strong,
beefy men, you know?
Sure.
And like when we...
And to have one who's like your...
Your buddy.
Your soft-hearted best friend.
Yeah, exactly.
Like the idea of having this cool big, which I have a bunch of friends like this.
Most of my friends are way more jacked than me.
Hard to believe.
I love, well, because they're all, I'm not jacked at all, they're all jacked.
But I love the idea of like showing off my strong friend, you know?
Getting to say like, hey, you guys all think I'm some, I'm some little nerd.
But look who my friend here, he could kick all your asses, you know?
I finally understand.
Something gratifying about it.
I finally understand why all women want Chad.
Yeah.
Because they want to show off their big manly trophy.
Exactly.
God damn it, we never stood a chance, Reggie.
Yeah.
So, I don't even think...
Like Manable doesn't even qualify.
Manable looks like a bear game.
But he brings out my latent homo lust, for sure.
I just want to be held in those strong arms.
That protective coat of fur he has.
And I'd sleep in it, you know?
But yeah, like, I mean, as I was watching those videos, I was always thinking like,
well, this guy is clearly too normie to be a YouTuber on his own, you know?
We did like a handful of skits.
Cause your comedic chemistry with him is exactly like mine with my friends on Digi and friends.
If you ever watched any of the non-Victor Digi Bros.
No, no I haven't.
Yeah.
There was a series called Digi and Friends, where it would just be me and whatever other friends were around.
We'd usually release...
Digi Bros was also two episodes a day for the first year that it was around.
And it was usually one episode of Digi Bros and one episode of Digi and Friends.
And yeah, I mean, I carried all the conversations.
Of course.
Like, it's just how it is.
There was like the meme of Manimals Subway Sandwich, so we did a couple...
Which was great.
We did a couple jokes of like the Subway Sandwich reveal video, but like those skits were super easy to make, so it was no big deal.
But otherwise, he just, he didn't really want to do it.
I really wanted him to join in the Monkey's Anime Reviews lore as a character,
so he was in the B-movie review, and then he was in the Pokemon review.
And after the Pokemon review, after that day, I'd never heard from him again.
He recorded his audio, we recorded the skit in the bathtub and everything,
and then after that day, he never messaged me again or anything.
He just disappeared, and I was like, oh, what happened?
Was I mean to him when we were filming this?
I don't understand at all.
So then after like three months of no contact, I took his name off the channel.
So I was like, well, I guess this is the final thing.
There's no coming back from this.
He's going to notice that the password has changed and that the name has changed.
And now it's just a Monkey's Gaming Expedition, and I haven't talked to him.
I don't know what happened.
You don't think he's dead, do you?
No, no, no.
Because we have mutual friends who he still hangs out with.
It was like, is it my fault?
Like, I didn't message him either, but like, surely if he still wanted to be Adam,
maybe he's thinking the same thing that I am.
But I guess neither of us made the effort for whatever reason.
That's what happens with me and most of my friends.
At some point, neither one of us has contacted each other, and I keep thinking,
should I, but surely if he wanted to hang out, he would have contacted me.
They're probably thinking the same thing about you.
Yeah, but then I'm also like, but that's the thing.
I'm not contacting them because I don't know what we'd hang out and do.
I'm like, well, you know, I don't want to lose this friend,
but at the same time, what the hell do I have them around for?
You know, just to sit around and do nothing.
And it got to the point where maybe he felt like I was using him in some way
because the only times we would ever hang out would be to work on videos
because that's all I ever want to do.
Right.
I think that's why a lot of my friends got married.
It's just what happens.
This job gets into your head.
It like really, I mean, this, what, what, you come over to my house for the weekend.
By the way, this is a live podcast.
If anyone couldn't tell, we're in the same room on the same microphone.
And we're both naked.
Because it's very hot in here.
And the plan was, monkey was like, I'm coming over to your house for this weekend.
Let's record a thousand things.
Yeah, that's all we've been doing.
That's all we've done.
And that's all I want to do.
That's for me, it's the best possible thing.
Yeah.
Like I, like that's, that's why I'm so close with the PCP.
Like we don't, I think there might be a conception of us doing anything other than the PCP together.
And we don't, we hang out in this chat where we either are, I mean, some, we share our random thoughts and stuff.
But like, we get into vicious arguments that are hurtful and personal sometimes.
Yeah, but like, I love you, Jess.
But like most of the, most of the, um, the times that we talk is all for recordings.
We don't do calls.
Random.
No, I hate calls.
At the end of every PCP, as soon as I turn off the recording, I exit the call because I don't want to talk.
I hate it.
I do too.
The only reason Nate hangs out in there is because he's trying to pressure everybody to get their audio before they leave the call.
Yeah, that's fair.
Yeah.
So we don't usually hang out and talk afterwards unless we have like, I don't know, sometimes we do and it can be nice, you know, but like, and sometimes I will orchestrate a podcast just so that we can have a conversation.
Like there's been plenty of podcasts that were recorded just on the basis of I want to talk to my friends.
We did one recently that I threw out.
Yeah.
He just thought it didn't come out well.
And I, I, I kind of agreed.
And I also, the thing is that the conceit of the podcast was just an excuse to talk with friends, you know, and like when it was just me and you at the beginning, I thought that would have made a good podcast.
But once everybody else joined in, I was like, well, this is just a conversation.
Yeah.
I thought this doesn't really need to be public.
This is going crazy.
Yeah.
Um, but that's, that's a thing that happens with us.
And I don't necessarily see that as like a huge negative.
I just really enjoy making stuff and I enjoy having people around who can make stuff with me, which is why I've kind of taken to you so much because you have the same mindset I do.
And you're as prolific as me, which, you know, it's harder for me to work with the other members of the PCP because they're all working on their own stuff.
And they, like if I, if I get Nate to do something else, that's taking away from his videos.
Yeah, it sounds like he doesn't have a lot of time to do his own stuff as it is.
He's already working a full-time job and he's working on the PCP, which it used to be he edited PCP.
And the only reason he stopped is because it was taking too much time away from editing his regularly.
Well, because he would do a lot of editing.
Autisticly go overboard because he cannot just fucking post a video to the internet.
But, uh, but that's why, that's why as soon as I, like, I feel, I feel like me and you have the same mindset about videos, which is it's more important that it's done than that it's perfect.
Sure.
You know, like, you can't watch something if you don't put it up.
Yeah, I don't care much about editing. I don't care much about, like, uh, like making it pretty or, or perfect for everybody.
Because not every video has to be seen by everyone, you know?
I make lots of stuff that I just post on my subreddit and that's it, you know?
Um, or on Pornhub.
Wait, what, what have you posted on Pornhub?
Well, I, uh, I assisted a friend of mine in making a video.
Oh, okay, yeah.
Yeah, I know that Hentai Samurai wasn't you.
No.
But you helped him out.
Yeah.
He's, he's currently, he's not around today because he, he's, uh, he's taking a sabbatical to the porn store.
He's taking a, he's a, he's a, uh, he's an assistant manager at Got It Video.
Wait, it doesn't sabbatical mean he's not working?
For Hentai Samurai, it's a sabbatical from porn, from jacking up.
He takes a vacation to go work at another job.
Basically, he, he goes to work at a porn store to, because as a samurai, he has to-
Samurai!
Yeah.
As a samurai, he has to have a certain level of like countenance.
Like he has to be, uh, what's the word I'm looking for?
Like Bushido?
Like that Bushido code of like, uh, temperance or whatever?
Of jerking off?
Well, basically he's trying to not jerk off and by going to work for eight hours a day
and, but being surrounded by porn, it helps him to build up his, uh, you know-
His chakras.
Yeah.
He ends around at work all day, like fuming, like...
I would imagine that 3D porn would disgust him and he only wants to see Hentai.
Uh, Hentai Samurai is, he's, he loves all porn.
He's a, he's a connoisseur of all times.
He celebrates it.
Anyway, I think the point we're trying to make is that these friends of ours feel like they're being used,
whereas in my mind it's, I think we have a fun chemistry, a good friendship,
and I want to share that with the whole world.
Yeah.
And he might feel like, oh, he's just using me to have a co-host on his-
Let's, let's play.
What's so difficult about it is that, like, I, the reason I had all my friends on there is
because I think they're cool people.
Yeah.
You know, I like all these guys.
So it's especially painful when they no longer want to do it or be friends with you.
Yeah.
Like, these are all people I wanted to show off.
My only crime was that I love you.
Yeah.
If you listen to all my videos, you will probably have heard me talking about how much I love
these people a lot.
Like, I always am bragging about them because I think they're cool.
Or if you listen to all the old music I used to force them to do, because that's, that was
also a thing.
I used to have all my friends were musicians, but none of them were, like, willing to actually
make music.
So I would just force them all into a room and have them, like, bullshit improv stuff,
and then I would upload it.
None of them wanted anything to do with it.
But, but I love it, you know, and I still listen to all that stuff.
They probably don't even remember half of it.
So anyway.
So, yeah.
So you've gotten to that.
You are now in the same position I am, falling out with all your friends, trying to get the
hell out of your hometown.
Yeah.
You're moving the hell out.
By the time this is up, I'll probably be moved out.
Oh, I don't know.
This could come out tomorrow.
Yeah.
Well, I'm moving at the end of March.
Okay.
Yeah.
So you're currently visiting North Carolina.
I don't think it's any secret that your girlfriend is sheep over.
No.
Not at this point.
She's sheep over who you, how did you two meet?
I think the first time we talked was on Snapchat.
She sent me a snap and I thought she looked like Murph from Interstellar.
Interstellar?
I was like, oh shit, dude, it's Murph.
Man, she's like this.
She's two of the top ten waifus of all time, dude.
Yeah, she is.
I got to get in with Murph.
And the rest is history.
So yeah, you've always had a very public Snapchat, which I thought that was another
thing that interested me right from the beginning was your willingness to not just have fan
interactions, but to let them get closer to you than I think most people would.
Like Snapchat, I was always afraid to have a public Snapchat because I'm like, I'm going
to get dick pics.
I do every day.
Do you really?
Of course.
I've never gotten one.
I have a public Snapchat now.
I've never gotten a dick pic.
I think your fans respect you.
Well, that was the saddest thing that ever happened, in my opinion, was you opened a
P.O. box.
I know where this is going.
Well, that monkey opened a P.O. box, which I've been meaning to do for a long time, but
I just, I guess I had assumed it was too expensive or too much of a pain in the ass.
How much did you end up paying for it?
60 bucks, I think, for six months.
I did like 100 for a full year.
Yeah, so you opened a P.O. box and when you did that, I was like, well, shit, if monkey
is doing it, I want to do it.
I'm even bigger than him, I'll probably get even more shit.
And you sure did.
Yeah, but the funny part is, because what you got was a bunch of dildos and sex toys, I'm
expecting that.
And it never happened.
Seven months of having a P.O. box, never once did I get any sex stuff or anything weird,
all just love letters.
You get gifts and posters.
There's unbelievably long fucking soliloquies about how my content changed someone's life
and Bubki gets boy pussy aroma handles.
And you'll be putting up a new mailbag once a week and it's like an hour long with just
a constant stream of gifts.
I struggled to make an eight minute episode with three packages, all of which are just
fuck you gifts.
And I wanted to bring that up because I think there's a perception of you that because you
embrace that, that that's what you want more of, but I don't think that's necessarily the
case.
That's a fear that by laughing at it and propping it up, it seems like I'm encouraging it.
Well, that's what I think when Jesse says that he has a different mindset about the
interactions.
I think it's because he thinks you want just that, but you don't.
It's just that's all you're getting.
If it was just that, I mean, I'm not going to complain.
I still think it's funny because in my view, the Internet should be the wild, wild West.
And I think everybody on the Internet should be an asshole all the time, which I know you
all very much disagree with, especially Jess.
But I mean, the Internet in my mind, ever since the beginning of me going on the Internet,
it's been like going on 4chan, going on these cesspools of hatred.
And that's what I love.
And I think that's what the Internet should be about.
You could be nice to each other in person.
That's the human interaction.
The problem with it is that the Internet is real now.
And I think that the people who have the mindset like what you have, there's a lot of people
who don't recognize or won't admit that it's no longer the same people.
There was a time when the Internet was like a closed off place that was just for freaks
and weirdos.
It was like, if you can't make it in normal society, here's a place for you.
But now everyone's on the Internet.
And it's like, now if we're just assholes to each other, then it's no different from
doing it in real life.
And it's like, especially for those of us who don't have anywhere else to go in real life,
it's like, I don't want to go to the place where everyone's an asshole.
I want to give me the hug box.
I need something on here.
Somewhere I can get my hugs.
So I have to assume some people, the appeal of monkey is that it's a corner of the Internet
where almost anything goes, like anything that YouTube won't ban before.
I'll make a video of me saying the word nigger in a rap song.
I mean, you do that all the time, obviously, but that's just one example.
I'll make a video about 9-11 and the Jews and all this stuff because it's the Internet.
I don't care.
Anything should go.
And I want to be the shining example of, oh yeah, on the Internet, anything is possible.
But it seems like you're saying that's dying and now it's becoming a norm.
I think you can keep it alive in that corner.
Which is my goal.
The problem is that we brought you into the PCP and brought your fan base to ours.
That's your problem.
We mixed them in an unfortunate way.
So now your fans are coming to our channels just to get banned.
I mean, once you ban them, what's the problem after that?
Well, the problem is there's a thousand avenues on the Internet.
But anyways, I understand the desire to keep that alive.
And that's kind of why I still go on 4chan for the same reason.
I like that the Internet can be a place that normal stuff can happen.
And my channel, obviously, I try to preserve meaningful conversation and stuff.
But I don't always want that.
Sometimes I just want to go to 4chan and see the assholes be assholes to each other.
So I totally understand the idea of having it alive.
But would you not say that if fans sent you genuine stuff, you would also be happy with that?
Oh, yeah.
I mean, let's not say that everything I've gotten is bad.
I've gotten some good things.
I think there's been a couple of times where I didn't show it in the video,
but a letter, I actually teared up because it was just so nice.
I think that because of the monkey persona,
there's a lot of people who assume that you would rather get negative comments
and people shitting on you when this is not really the case.
It depends on the type of video.
If the Elliot Rodger review, I would like a serious discussion there.
It's a serious video.
But all these fucking videos about yelling about Jews and stuff,
just shit up the comments.
Let the comments reflect the video.
I think that's fair.
Do you think some of your audience has a difficult time discerning
between when they should be serious or not?
Probably.
I mean, I don't care.
As long as their mean comments are funny, even if they're genuine,
if they're funny, then I still love them because it makes me laugh.
Funny is always the problem.
I think the biggest problem with commenters is that so many of them aren't funny
and think they are.
That's by far my biggest.
I don't even mind.
I've gotten comments that shit on me that were legitimately funny
that I will upvote.
It's not every day.
If you leave a comment that's just like, fuck you, then I'm like, well,
I think that's funny because the lack of effort is funny on its own.
It can be.
But if it's just like someone, because I usually am like, I know why.
It's just some snob fan or something to say fuck you.
I'm just like, yeah, you're banned.
Do you ever get comments where it just says OK and nothing more?
Those do make me laugh.
It's like, why did you post this?
I actually do think those were funny.
What the fuck is this in reference to?
I always get so confused.
I don't know what to do about it.
I'm like, is this a shit post?
What is this?
I love those.
Yeah.
That's the thing.
Fuck you is too unambiguous.
If you're so confounding, like I've had some where they're shitting on me,
but they're just like so incompetent at English that I leave it up
because I feel like they've defeated themselves.
Oh, yeah.
It can be a lot of fun.
If you're still listening, just comment OK on this episode.
Someone probably already did.
Before they even got to this point, it's just that guy who does it.
It probably says OK and then edit dot, dot, dot, shit.
Now they're going to do that on purpose.
You fucked it all up.
Maybe they'll take it another step farther from where we've thought.
Yeah, let's not give them any more freebies.
So you are planning to either before this comes out or right afterwards
to end Mumki's anime review.
Come and do an end, baby.
I'll finally be free.
Yeah.
Episode 50.
I thought I'd go to 100, but I think I've exercised the lore enough.
Mumki can only go through this cycle of knowing that it's all conspiracy
and then thinking it's real and back and forth.
It's already gotten to a point of saturation.
Yeah.
I'm like, OK, well, this needs to end.
I can't stretch this out forever.
Let's end it once and for all.
I'll keep making the exact same style of video,
but we just won't call it Mumki's anime reviews.
And it won't have the narrative with Uncle Alex and Jumki and all that.
Yeah, I know.
All that's going to get retired.
I'll keep Jumki and Alexa as characters,
but it'll be a different canon, maybe.
So, oh, God, I got a burp coming in.
There we go.
Where are you going to go after this, after it's all over?
Do you think you'll ever construct another narrative
or do you think you're done with that whole aspect of it?
I think it was a fun little experiment.
And a lot of people seem to really like it.
But if I don't have a good idea for it, I don't want to do it.
So I'm not going to try to force it.
That's why I've never done one.
The pitfalls that people fall into,
people think, oh, I have to do a narrative.
The Jon Tron has a narrative sometimes and all this shit.
So I have to force it in.
And then that's when they're bad, is when you try to force it.
It has to come naturally with me or with Jess when he does it.
With Jesse, he can't help it.
It's like it's a destructive force in his life
that he can't help but tie narratives into his videos.
And it's hurt his chances of success on YouTube, unfortunately.
It's like the same thing with the triflers,
which I'm sure we'll talk about later
because we have another three hours of this to go.
But people keep saying, oh, you got to write a sequel to the triflers.
I'm thinking, I'd love to.
But if I don't have the good idea, I'm not going to write something that's shit.
I mean, maybe you'll have a good idea in 10 years or something.
Yeah, maybe.
Who knows?
Yeah, and why does everyone...
People are demanding this of you, not thinking about the fact
that it's not like triflers is a New York Times bestseller
and that wasting two years writing a sequel is going to be a huge payoff.
Yeah, they don't seem to understand that writing a book is a huge process.
They think, as far as I know, I wrote the triflers in an afternoon.
And I didn't edit it once.
That's just how they think it just came to be.
They think, just do it again over the weekend.
Now, if I'm not mistaken, the triflers was completed before Monkey's Anime Review started.
Yeah, yeah.
So give me the timetable.
I have to go to the bathroom, but you can talk about the timetable of how the triflers came to be.
Okay.
The initial idea for it of this group of kids in a basement who watched horrible videos,
it came to me, I think, my senior year of high school.
And I kind of played around with it for a bit.
And then my freshman year of college, I completed another book I was working on,
which I have not released or anything.
I think the only person who's read it other than my grandma and mom are sheep over and Tom Oliver.
So then after I finished that book, I said, okay, let's see what we got with this triflers thing.
So I worked on that.
It took about a year and a half, maybe two years.
I think I finished it my junior year of college.
And then that's about when I started the Let's Plays, I think.
I think that timetable makes sense.
Maybe it was a little bit before.
But yeah, then I started doing Monkey.
I forget about the book for about a year.
I do Monkey for about a full year.
And then as I go, hey, maybe I could polish up this book and people will buy it.
Because there are a few anime reviews where I just took straight pages from the triflers and that's the whole review.
The Traps review is straight from the book.
The Depression review is straight from the book.
And people like those videos.
So I thought, well, maybe they'll like this book.
And they did.
They overwhelmingly did.
So it all worked out.
Have you had any particularly negative reviews of the triflers?
No.
No, I'm astonished by it.
Not one person said this book was not good.
Nobody's given it lower than like a four out of five.
Which I have to assume if they bought it in the first place, they were already interested and they were already a fan.
So I don't know.
I mean, I was just like, to me, the fact that the book even has like competent pros is enough for it to be like, oh, this is a 10 out of 10.
Like, you know, most of the stuff I get sent by people who are like on the internet who are like, yeah, I'm writing a book.
And then they send it to me.
And within two sentences, I'm sick of it.
You know, like most people just.
Writing is hard.
Yeah.
It's hard.
But if a lot of people just think they can't do it, like they just can't do it.
Right.
And like most of the problems I have with your book were more like, like, like high level problems.
Like it's like, like small structural things and nitpicks.
And like maybe this word would have been better in this sentence.
You are sweating up a storm.
I'm noticing.
You mean?
Yeah, you look like you're sweating up a storm.
It's hot in here.
Yeah.
It's a little, it's a little, a little warm.
I get heated when I think about books.
Yeah.
Very passionate.
I guess so.
I didn't notice until just now.
I guess the sun got brighter.
Yeah.
I want to close that goddamn curtain.
I can do that.
I don't know if that'll make it cooler in here, but fuck the sun.
So, so yeah.
So you, you finally put out this book.
So your other one, which is a little shorter.
Yeah.
You, you're thinking, still not thinking about releasing?
Maybe.
I think there are some major things I need to change about it.
If you thought that there was too much sexual stuff with, with minors and the triflers.
Boy, howdy.
This book's going to get me arrested for sure.
So I think I need to achieve over, you know what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
I don't think anybody, Tom, I asked Tom about the specific chapters and chapter five, just
the most gruesome thing I've ever written in my life.
And I asked him what he thought of it.
And he's like, Oh, well, I mean, I'm so used to this kind of stuff.
Thanks to the internet.
That didn't really bother me, but everybody else was like traumatized.
My mom, grandma, and sheep over.
That's the thing.
They're, I mean, if you, if you're, your stuff is like for internet people, I think, like
this is when I read the triflers, my impression of it was like, this is the most millennial
book ever written.
Whoa, wait, it's a bad thing.
No, I'm a millennial.
I understand it.
I wanted to give you this quote.
Keep forgetting to mention this to you, but a few years back, back when I was, I guess
probably five or six years ago, when I was trying to become a writer before this whole
YouTube thing.
I'm a writer.
I've been saying that a lot lately and completely meaning it.
But when I was trying to be a writer as opposed to a YouTuber, there was a party going on at
my house with my parents, all their friends and stuff.
And one of my mom or dad's friends who works with them was like sloshed.
She's probably late 30s, early 40s, got kids who were in high school kind of thing.
And she was like drunkenly telling me that what, what she wants, like what I should write
about is like all the illicit stuff that, that high school kids are getting up to like,
hey, all the young kids, like tell me about like all the, all the, the drugs and sex life.
And I was like, I was never, I wasn't a part of any of that.
Like why would I know this story?
Like I only am good at writing what I know, which is about being.
You should only write what you know.
Right.
Well, the way I saw it, I was like, what the kids are up to these days is not all that
stuff.
They're up to being isolated in their rooms at computers.
But then when I read the triflers, I was like, this is exactly what that woman wanted.
This is exactly what she wanted is the seedy, fucked up shit that young people are getting
up to in high school.
You know, I mean, granted that probably went a little further than she could have handled
a lot further.
I imagine.
Yeah.
But, but I was like, this is exactly that.
And so I do think it touched on something that a lot of people want, which is, you know,
to, because, because it feels real, like everything in the triflers, aside from the fact that Don
is like a legitimate, like high level, like light Yagami, you know, like schemer.
How'd you know my inspiration?
Aside from that, like everything in it felt like, yeah, this is the kids I knew in high
school.
Like this is the kind of shit they, the edgy shit they would have got up to, you know,
sitting around a basement watching live leak videos and stuff.
You did have a friend who planned a school shooting.
Good old Phillip.
Yeah.
Good old Phillip Bay was going to do it.
Not just playing.
He had the weapons and everything.
He was ready.
He's a regular Mario Quintanilla.
I think he was busted because he had posted stuff online and people found it.
He pulled an Elliot Roger.
Yeah.
But except he actually got caught unlike Elliot.
I don't, I think he was before, yeah, he was before Elliot.
His attempt.
He was, he was post Virginia Tech.
I think that was more his inspiration.
I could have done a whole 30 minute review of your friend, Phillip, if only he would
have gotten away with it.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, so do you have plans to write another book anytime soon?
Do you think that'll happen?
Do you have any ideas for books popping around?
I've been thinking very hard about how I would approach a Triforce sequel.
And I have like vague impressions of what it would be and things that would happen.
But.
Detective novel starring Mason.
That'd be, that'd be a little bit of it.
Yeah.
But like I said, unless I get like a really good idea, I'm not going to even attempt it.
And I, writing a book is hard and it takes a lot of time and I just don't feel like it right now.
Like I just got off the high of this one being released.
Yeah.
If anything, I would polish up and release the one that I wrote before the Triforce.
Well, I'm really curious about where, where your heart sort of resides in regards to content
right now because you've mentioned that YouTube has become a little bit too formulaic
and you're kind of sick of it in a way.
I think I was just getting sick of the anime reviews videos.
Yeah.
Because I have, as soon as this ends, I have like three new series in my mind that I really,
I'm really excited to do them.
Okay.
One of which is, I think what I'm calling it is the tenisms where I take ten words that
end in ism and I just dissect them and I go through them for like 10 to 15 minutes.
So things like communism, autism, atheism, et cetera.
So I'm really excited about that.
It's like the same style as the anime reviews without the old joke that atheism is a Japanese
anime.
Yeah.
We get it, monkey.
You've done it 50 times.
Let's move on.
So you've got, you've got some, some more YouTube stuff planned.
Yeah.
Lots more Let's Place planned.
Once I move in with Sheep and I, I hopefully.
Is Sheep going to become a co-host?
No.
I hope not.
I don't think either one of us want that, but hopefully I'll be able to film more often
because I've been having a lot of trouble filming in my current apartment.
Once I have more time, I want to, I bought Mario Maker for the 3DS.
I want to play the fuck out of that because I think it's fun as shit and some other things.
So.
Leaving aside the, the anime reviews, you do plan to continue the monkey character.
Yeah.
But, but without the surrounding narrative.
So will he still be making reference to being molested or anything?
Or is it just like a screaming monkey?
I'm putting Uncle Alex to bed.
We've had enough.
So.
It's only so far you can go with that joke.
Yeah.
But you're still going to be like a, like a, like a gravelly voiced monkey man.
I'm still, I'm still going to be myself.
And the mask is staying on.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
We'll see how often I do live action.
Right.
Cause that's always, it's, it's hit or miss and it's also a lot of effort.
Do you think there's a chance that the mask is going to come off at some point just be,
just to be able to, she's giving me a look like, yeah, it's happening.
Like there's no way he's keeping this up forever.
I think if, if I get more handsome.
Cause I figured the same thing, the fact that you're not bad looking at all.
No.
You, I.
I hate it.
When I said, I asked the monkey, like, uh, like why he wears the mask or he, he said,
he was telling me that he was trying to become a teacher.
And I said, is that why you wear the mask?
And he said, no, horrible acne scarring.
So I expected you to be like legitimately ugly.
And look, look, monkey, I'll tell you right now.
I, I cannot look ugly people's directly in the face.
I'm not joking about that.
If you, is that why you look away when Ben comes in the room?
Shit.
That's not true.
But we're learning.
But when, when, uh, if I thought, if I didn't think that you had a face that I could look
at, I wouldn't, I would be looking off into the distance the whole time we were talking.
I guarantee it.
So, um, I'm, I'm, I'm not, I'm not even kidding about that.
I'm a terrible person.
Let me tell you this, Digi.
The day I, cause I'm only here visiting sheep for 10 days and then I'm going home for a week
and then I'm moving on into North Carolina.
For the day I get back, big brother, the TV show is doing a casting call in my city,
like, like a few blocks from my house and I'm going to go fucking apply.
And if I get on big brother, like this is all out.
My, my face is going to be out there.
My everything about me will be out there.
And my life will probably be ruined because after, you know, you get exposed as
mumke on national television.
I don't think you get a job after that.
No, but I want to be on big brother so bad that I'll throw away any semblance of a future
at that chance for $500,000 and then after taxes, like $8.
I mean, I've, I, I don't know if you feel similarly to me at all because like you,
you're just now sort of taking the internet personality thing more as like a career.
And even then you're planning to get a normal job when you move to North Carolina.
Yeah, I fucking hope I do.
Yeah.
Cause like for me, the second I started making money off of YouTube, the prospect of ever doing
a normal job again was just gone.
Like I never thought about it and never looked back.
Like the only reason I never get a new normal job is if like for some reason I couldn't
do the internet at all.
Like, but I don't feel like that'll ever happen.
Like why, what would ever stop me, you know?
So like for me, it was like, well, you know, it doesn't matter what I say online now
because this is who I am now.
And then like, that's why I'm so willing to go around saying nigger on podcasts and writing
songs about it.
It's just like, this is, this is who I am now and fuck the old, the old me.
So do you think you'll ever reach a point like that where it'll just be like, I'm not
worried about preserving my ability to have a normal life?
Well, I think if I was that serious about that worry, then I wouldn't do the kinds of
videos that I make.
I make things that are highly offensive in this SJW culture.
I mean, I guess if Donald Trump could become president after what he said, maybe I do stand
a chance.
Yeah, but
You just gotta go to the right places.
Don't move to California.
No.
Stay in the deep South where just find, find an establishment who unironically agrees
with the things you've said in your videos that you're set, you know?
The fear of the job, Lynch mob is very real.
But ultimately, I mean, I feel like I'm at the point of no return already.
Like I've crossed it.
So if it's going to happen, it's going to happen.
Like I've already put these videos out and they're on the internet forever.
Once you put it up once, but the prospect of doing this just as a job and do nothing
else like you do, it's such a new type of job.
And it hasn't been around long enough to know if it's sustainable.
Five years from now, maybe Digi Bro isn't making any money anymore.
Or maybe you're making 20 grand a month.
We have no way of knowing.
That's the scariest thing about it is there's no benefits and there's no insurance.
There's no boss.
Like you work for YouTube who's only out to fuck you.
True.
Like they say they want to help you, but they fuck you at every turn.
Yep.
And you're really relying on like, like if I didn't have Patreon, I would be fucked.
Right.
Like there's a lot of YouTubers who do just rely on ad revenue and sponsorships.
I really wonder how Jon Tron's going to survive his controversy.
Digi he'll be fine.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
But like just like he makes so much like, I mean he'd have to, if he lost all his sponsorships
for the things he says, he'd have to scale back his production, I'd assume.
You know?
That would help his videos a lot.
It would.
He should do that.
But if Jon Tron makes a Patreon, he's making five grand a month minimum.
That's probably true.
So I think he's fine.
Yeah.
But that's the thing.
Like it's an interesting culture because we don't know if Patreon's going to start cannibalizing
itself in the future.
Like that's always been a concern for me is the more people find out about it, the more
spread thin the money gets, you know?
There's going to get to a point where people, like that was a big concern of all of us when
we made the PCP Patreon.
Oh yeah.
Are people going to unpatron one of us to patron the group?
Which I think did happen.
Probably a couple people.
Some people, like, lowered theirs from five to one so that they could throw in a buck
to the PCP.
Yeah.
Which is, like, I mean, that kind of fucks us over in a way.
Because, like-
Definitely does.
Because we're all splitting the money anyway.
So like now instead of Digi getting that two bucks, now he's getting like 20 cents.
Yeah, a problem.
So, like, do you really, do you really like Ben St. that much that you want to take away
$1.80 from Digi so that Ben can get, like, a 20-cent share?
Like, fuck Ben.
Just give the money to us directly.
Don't, I don't know.
But I shouldn't say don't do the PCP Patreon because I get, like, what, 20 bucks a video
off of it?
That's kind of good.
Yeah.
I mean, the way I see it though, and this is why I think you would be able to do it,
like you would be able to make a career out of this, is again because you're so prolific.
Because if you are constantly putting shit out, I see it as you've got a dart board and
you're just, like, throwing dart after dart.
Like, if you spend all your time and money trying to craft the perfect dart before you
throw it and then you miss, you've wasted a lot of time.
Yeah.
You know?
But if you've got, like, 100 cheap darts, all that matters is that it hits the bullseye.
It doesn't matter what the dart looks like.
If it hits the bullseye, you hit the bullseye and you make all the money, you know?
So, like, I think the fact that, you know, you could just be putting out, like, a bunch
of podcasts, a bunch of Let's Plays, a bunch of other shit, you know?
And, like, something's got to hit eventually, you know?
So, like, for me, you know, if for some reason I can't do anime anymore because they keep
fucking hitting me with copyright strikes every other day.
They're going to keep doing anything.
Like, if I decided, like, hey, the problem here is anime.
Let's just cut anime and go to another thing.
You think you could do that?
I think I could do that easily.
I mean, I cut pony and went to anime and became twice as successful.
Go back to pony.
Three times as successful.
They need a new messiah over there.
The bronies are struggling.
The bronies are dead.
There's no going back there.
They're gone.
MLP probably gets, like, what, 200 posts a day on the 4chan board?
It's the worst board on the whole website.
I hope you know that.
I wouldn't know.
They're the worst board on 4chan.
It should have been what everyone thought it was going to be, which is that everyone,
a repeat of the furry board.
You know about the furry board?
No, no.
Like, 10 years ago, maybe more, 4chan made a furry board, a containment board for the
furry, and then they left it up for one week and then anybody who posted there all got
banned.
It was a carpet ban.
It was all a trap.
Genius.
Even if you go there and troll them, just get fucked.
That's what MLP should have been.
They all deserve it.
That's crazy.
Yeah, and that's what people thought it was when it first came out.
But yeah, I think that you could, because you're so prolific, you could eventually,
and that there's people who, you have a base now.
Like, all you need is a base.
Even if you only have 100 people, if they will continue to post your shit everywhere
and follow you whatever you do and stuff, then there's always somewhere to go.
I think that the hardest part of being a creator on the internet is just establishing
enough of a base that cares deeply enough to follow you to the next thing,
which is kind of what fucked over Tom, that he had a little bit of a base,
but he had already kind of lost most of his followers from Brony Curious by the time he
made Rebel Pixels.
And then Rebel Pixels was like such a different thing.
I still don't even know what that channel is.
I looked at the videos and he was just talking about his computer.
What is this shit?
The idea of it is that it's supposed to be helping creators on the web.
It's supposed to be a guidebook for internet creators kind of thing.
So half of the videos are motivational speeches, and the other half are hardware reviews.
But because he mostly got successful through reviewing tablets,
then he just kept doing tablet reviews, and so it kind of became very focused on that.
But it was just that the subject matter was so different,
and his base was already so broken after his original channel,
that it took a long time for Rebel Pixels to even pick up the steam that it has,
which is over 10,000 subs, so it's not that bad.
Whereas for me, I went from ponies directly into anime.
So anybody, which was probably out of my 70,000 subscribers,
there was maybe 4,000 who cared enough to watch the anime videos.
And it was good and bad.
It's like, oh yay, but really?
I went from averaging 40,000 to 70,000 views of video to averaging 2,000 to 5,000 views of video.
But that's the thing.
That base was there, and they were still sharing the videos,
and they were still watching it just because they liked me,
or they just happened to also be into anime,
and eventually it grew out of that and blew up again.
So that's why I think as long as you have that core audience
who cares enough to follow you to the next thing,
you've always got a second chance if you can capitalize on it.
It makes me think of the tragedy of Ben, Nate, and Hippo,
because I was shocked to learn that they had old pony channels
that had like three times as many views as the ones they have now.
And when they started over, like fucking Gibbente has what, 15,000 subs,
and then poor Hippo is at like eight.
Well, part of the problem there, especially in Nate and Ben's case,
was that they deliberately hid it from their old subscribers.
Why?
Because Nate didn't want to have the baggage of the MLP community,
which in fairness-
They're just people!
In fairness, if you knew these people.
It's a human being, they can like two things.
Right, but he was scared that his audience would end up just being those people
and that a new one wouldn't form around here, whatever.
And so he never, like on the T-Bap channel,
that channel was dead for like a solid year
before Ben finally put up a video telling everyone what they had done,
which incidentally, that video is how he met his girlfriend.
Oh!
Because she had no idea.
Like, she had been a huge fan of the T-Bap
and then didn't know that they'd gone on to do all this other stuff
until Ben put up this video, like,
hey, by the way, we're alive and we've been doing stuff for the last year.
That's all great, almost two years.
So, yeah, they just, they just didn't announce it to their old fans.
So that's why their base was so broken.
And then Hippo-
That's bizarre to me.
I don't know why you would make that choice.
Like, I get what you said, but-
Who cares if the audience is all bronies?
Let them watch my fucking anime analysis.
I don't care.
Yeah.
Well, I'm just saying that that's, that's, you know,
my mindset is like, even if everything fails, there's always a pickup.
Like, we can always keep trying,
especially if you have enough money saved up from the previous one.
When I make a Patreon exclusive video,
which is for the $5 and up people,
and I make like, maybe two of these a month,
like, I'll do like a commentary over something
or just talk about something that's going on,
I always tell them,
I'm making these videos just for you,
not the Patreon exclusives,
but every video is just for you guys,
because I could lose every subscriber,
except for the 100 people on Patreon,
and I would still be doing this.
I would still be doing this just for you.
There's no, that's why I've put out two videos this month
that aren't even on YouTube,
because it's like, as long as the patrons are there,
that's all that matters.
And if the patrons start complaining,
that's when I'll start listening, you know?
Like, I put out these videos about
anime soundtrack composers, it's a totally different style,
and like, in the comments on the videos,
there's some people who really love it,
some who don't like it,
but no one's complained on Patreon yet.
So as long as no one complains on Patreon,
those videos keep happening, you know?
Do you think that's healthy, though,
to be subjugated to the opinion specifically of the patrons?
Like, if they complain about something,
would you stop doing it?
I wouldn't stop it just because one guy complained,
or anything, but like, if...
What if it was like a guy who's giving you
100 bucks a video?
Would you be like, oh, well,
maybe I shouldn't do that.
I don't...
No one does that, and when they do,
I don't trust them.
Yeah.
Because there's nothing...
Like, dude, if you're gonna be a patron,
like, at maximum, give $30.
No, not give me 50 yet.
There's a lot of 50s,
and I really like those people.
I don't have any...
I had...
Like, the highest pledge I ever had
that was consistent is this woman named
Anna Esther Volos, who has a couple
YouTube videos that are pretty alright,
and she's like an animator.
And she used to be a patron to, like,
every one of the PCP for, like,
really high amounts.
She gave me, like, $35 a video for years.
Oh, my God.
So she personally has given me, like,
thousands of dollars.
Yo, Anna, hit me up.
But she eventually reduced it a little bit.
But, like, to me, that was like...
That's like the most...
Like, that's the most you could pledge
that I'll take it seriously,
because I've had people...
How could you not take it seriously?
Because I've had people who pledge 100,
and then immediately get declined
and have to reduce it to $5.
You know?
It's like, it happens all the time,
because they always think that it's going
to work one way,
and that it just doesn't work out
the way they think it will.
You know?
They somehow think they're going to
either have $100 to give you,
or that they don't understand
how Patreon works, you know?
Or they get declined,
and then they can't make it go through,
and it's just like...
Because to me, it just inflates my numbers.
Like, I don't want it to look like
I make more than I do.
That's true, because then people will be less willing,
like, oh, why would I give them two bucks?
He's got a thousand.
Yeah, exactly.
So, yeah, well, we've gotten off
into the weeds on that again.
I don't remember...
I don't know where we started.
So, Manimal,
he stopped being on the Let's Play.
Yeah.
Well, now we've got the
Let's Play channel is kind of
free-for-all at this point.
You've got a show with...
You do some with Biggs,
you've got some with Patch,
you've got the Spyro...
Well, those have all come to an end
now that I'm moving.
The Spyro series,
that's with Random Guest each time,
which I think is genius.
Yeah, that's a fun idea.
Since I realized it's so hard
to find a good co-host,
I thought, hey,
let's just let everybody be a co-host.
I'll give just any random person
three episodes to listen to me
play Spyro because they can't see the screen.
So, it's just kind of like an excuse
to have random conversations.
I've had Jess, Hippo,
and Munchie from the PCP,
and then I've had my brother,
my real-life friend Maddie,
and then my internet friend Odd Belly.
And in Spyro 2,
now that Spyro 1's over,
I want to branch out and get, like,
fans and listeners and stuff.
Like, people I don't even know.
But I'm going through a vetting process
to make sure that I can listen to them
for an hour.
That reminds me,
you once had a podcast
called Anime Fight.
Yeah, let's talk about Anime Fight.
Which I've never actually watched,
but because I could tell
from the thumbnail alone
that you had not vetted the people
Odd there,
and that they were a bunch of fucking idiots.
What was the deal with that?
So, a big fan of
the Movie Fights podcast
on Screen Junkies,
where there's a judge,
and they give you a topic like,
what is the best Quentin Tarantino movie?
And then the three contestants argue it out,
and then the judge awards a point to the winner.
And I thought, hey,
let's do that with Anime.
But I'll let the fans join in,
because I love my fan interaction.
So I was like, hey,
send me an email if you want to join in,
and you can be on the show.
Surely enough, we got, you know,
nine people in total.
Actually, Baku Boys,
who we talked about earlier,
was on one of them,
and he actually won,
just because he was the funniest.
Because the idea was,
it's not a serious Anime Fight.
They're all emulating me,
and they all chose to do this
of their own accord.
They're trying to do the
monkey memes of, oh,
World War II is an anime
that had over 6 million
people who didn't like it,
and that kind of shit.
But most of them
weren't very good at doing monkey.
No.
Not, you know,
not everyone's a comedian.
Especially not in a very specific
personal style of one comedian
that you're trying to emulate.
And it doesn't help that most of them
are like 15 and 16 year old guys.
Right.
Like recording it kind of quietly
upstairs, hoping that their parents
don't hear what they're saying.
Doing the soft scream.
Yeah.
And that's why Death Note
is the best anime
of all time.
So if you want to just,
if you want to cringe really hard
for hours at a time,
I'd say go watch the old anime fights.
Full body cringe.
I accidentally clicked on one.
And even just hearing my introduction,
I don't know if I had to get out of there.
Even, I cringe that myself.
Terrible.
Even the shitposts
master himself can't sit through
with that level.
I've never watched them.
They just uploaded immediately after.
They were live streams.
So there was a live audience the whole time.
So I didn't have to watch it.
Incredible.
I love it.
You just have it all this time.
You still have never even bothered.
I'm not going to take them down.
I'm sure somebody can get something out of it.
Maybe it's like the Digibro idea
of never taking anything down
so they can see how I've grown.
So that's just like...
There's a dark corner in my channel.
There is a bunch of stuff that's set to private
on my old blog.
I don't know if I would...
It's too late to go back and make it all public now.
But I don't know if I still would have hidden it today.
I just know that I did at the time
because I was like,
well, here's a lot of tracks that need to be covered.
Let's not let all this exist
for too much longer.
What were the sorts of things on there?
Otaku sexuality analysis.
That seems like something you would do today.
I would,
but not in the same way.
How did you do it?
It's just that the way I wrote back then...
Was the hentai samurai giving you advice?
Me and the hentai samurai
go way back.
I imagine.
He's like a father figure to you.
He's grown a lot as an artist over the last decade.
With his whole one video.
He did have some guest posts,
actually, on my old blog.
They were published under my name.
I never...
He was shy back then.
He didn't want anybody to know his real name,
Hentai Samurai.
He didn't have the mask yet.
He didn't have the underwear mask,
so he didn't want to be public without the mask.
Anyway, oh god,
I don't remember what we were saying again.
This has been a series
of me forgetting what the fuck we were talking about.
You're the navigator, so you figure it out,
because I don't remember either.
Let me think of some more shit to ask you about.
We've mostly been focused on your
sort of YouTube career,
but it seems like that's kind of dominated your life.
Tell us about what you were trying to do
in college,
because we know you almost
became a teacher
well into...
This was only recently that you finally abandoned this...
This terrible dream.
Yeah.
The only thing that I was really good at
in high school was English.
I was in all the advanced English classes.
All my papers I would write
in like five hours,
and then get an A on where everybody else would be like,
oh, it was so hard to write three-page paper,
because I'm a retarded 17-year-old.
I always over...
Oh, of course.
It's like easy and fun
to put out an argument.
All I wanted them to do was like,
every day I was like, when are we going to get another written assignment?
If that was all this class was,
school would be amazing.
The best class I've taken in my life
was creative writing in high school,
but that's partly because
all my friends got into it too,
and it was just the constant harassment hour.
There's that one writing exercise
where everybody
writes a paragraph of a story
that has it behind you.
And this motherfucker, one of my
good buddies, his name was
Zach.
So Zach would ruin every single
story with this character he created
called Earthquake Man,
and he wouldn't even read what had been happening.
He would just write down,
and then Earthquake Man killed everybody
in the world with an earthquake.
And my poor-bodied chum
was sitting behind him,
so he would have to pick up the pieces
of the asteroid world time and time again
and try to
resurrect everybody who had been killed
by Earthquake Man.
So that was like
shitposting the class.
We ruined it for everybody,
and it was tons of fun.
It sounds like your whole life has been shitposting their life.
It was fun.
I loved that class.
So yeah, in college,
I was like, okay, I guess I'll major in English.
I knew there were no prospects in that.
I don't need a major in English to do that.
I just need to write a book.
So it got to the point
in my sophomore year when I realized,
well, if I'm really doing this English major,
my only option is to be a teacher.
That's the only career path that this leads to,
as far as I know.
So I studied to be a teacher.
I kind of liked it.
I did student teaching a little bit.
I would go into classrooms and give lessons and stuff.
I thought it was okay.
I've always liked kids.
I've always either gotten along with people
who were younger than me,
or way older than me.
I typically don't hang out with people my own age.
Not my own age or one year older.
Well, because younger people always look up to me.
And I think you probably for the same reason
we have a younger brother
who's pretty close.
And so I think it's like you have a certain
nurturing tendency towards younger people.
And like,
all growing up,
most of my friends were usually just Victor's friends.
People who he had around
who would also
treat me like I was their big brother
as well.
And Manimol was two years older than me,
so that was perfect for me.
I hang out with all the older kids,
lightning along Johnson the same.
Cobb even was a year older than me in school.
Didn't have a whole lot of friends in my own grade,
but that's fine.
So yeah, I like people.
Typically I get along better with those who were younger
and those who were older.
And then I started doing monkey.
And I was like, well, as soon as this is found,
teaching's over.
They're not letting me into school.
So I was really disheartened by that,
thinking, well, I just wasted four years of my life
at this college.
And then I make a couple videos and now I'm fucked.
You make one a Feebiel file video
and it's game over when it comes to teaching.
As soon as they find it, it's game over.
So when they announced,
I went to the meeting for
the big student teaching thing,
I went to school for like a whole semester,
like half a year.
And just hearing all this shit they were saying
and all the papers I had to fill out
and all this garbage.
I thought, I don't want to do this.
People have told me all the time
that like people watch my videos and I'm like,
you'd be a great teacher. Why don't you teach at university?
I'm like, because do you know what teachers have to do?
It's not just get up in front of a class
and be eloquent for an hour.
It's like work constantly
and tirelessly for no money.
Right. It's a lot of unpaid overtime
that people don't understand.
I appreciate teachers infinitely more
than ever because I've gone through the whole process
of what it's like being one.
And I also now know
which teachers really sucked
and why they sucked at their job.
So I have a new found respect for it
but I just don't think I can do it
and now I'm kind of in this weird limbo of
I don't have a job, I can't get a job
right now because I'm in the middle of moving
and I don't know what to do
with my career path.
I have a useless English degree
as Avenue Q would say
what do you do
with a B.A. in English?
So I'm in that position
and I have this
beacon light reaching out to me
saying,
do monkey has a job
and that's just crazy.
Right.
And you've got these PCP guys who
when I found you, you were very like
oh, this YouTube is not a job.
I still feel that way.
You kind of had a chip on your shoulder
about it though and I first talked to you
that you were like...
Oh, it's just pure jealousy.
The fact that you can do this as a job makes me sick
because I want to.
But then as you became friends with the PCP
it started seeming like you were taking your Patreon
more and more seriously and that it became
like once you knew other guys who were doing it
it's like well fuck, if Digi's making all this money
why am I not making all this money?
I'm just going to say right now I'm sitting at
19,000 subscribers which thank you
you gave me a thousand in a day from your
your big famous video.
But if I'm making $600 a month
at 19,000 subs in my mind
like just you double the subs
you double the money. I see that correlation
in my head.
So I'm just at like the cusp
of becoming like a
D-list YouTube celebrity
and I think if I do, you know
get this to continue to grow
and sustain me as an actual career
but it's so unknown.
That's something I'm glad you thought of it that way
because I had two and I think a lot of people
don't. They don't think about the fact that
like every small amount of
growth on YouTube is exactly
that much to your paycheck
and like if you
like a lot of people are thinking like
man I'm really wallowing in this like 10k
realm or whatever
and then you don't even think about the fact that
like they're thinking everyone's eyes is on the
horizon like everyone's thinking
man I have to hit 100,000 before this will be
serious but if you just double
your subs you double your money
you know like almost
if it's correlating to the
view counts you know and so people don't realize
like even making a small step
you know it all affects
what you're making you know it's
always a constant incline
and everyone's so worried about catching
the brass ring at the top that they're not thinking
about how every step up the ladder is also
an improvement you know. Yeah
people don't seem to understand that if you have
40,000 subs you could be
living very comfortably like that could be your
full-time job at 40,000 subs
if you just did digibro after dark I think you'd
still make a decent amount of money
if uh if the I mean
I would if I just if I came out tomorrow
and said uh digibros cancelled
it's all after dark now I
your patreon would be like 10%
of what it is today it would
it would plummet yeah um
I wouldn't have to pay DeVoo and
I you know
wouldn't have to pay as much in taxes I think
because I've had a lot of patrons
telling me I will patron after dark
I have lots of people telling me like I don't
care about the main channel I just care
about after dark uh you know
like I just follow you as a person
so if I cancelled digibro
first of all I wouldn't lose all the patrons immediately
second of all I'd probably put more
effort into after dark because I wouldn't have to
worry about the main channel so I think
some I would argue that some of the
like the big 20 30 minute vlogs
you do on there about even like things
in anime more interesting yeah I
like those more than normal videos
the reason I do so much after dark is that I legitimately
love it yeah it's just harder
for me to charge for it because it's hard to draw the
line it's hard to say like where does
what's the difference between an
after dark video that is patronable one that's
not because I also love
stuff like insomnia analysis
which is like an hour of me doing
random weird shit right that a
lot of people will not sit through but
to me that would be like the most
patronable video you know like if there was
a channel doing all stuff like that I'd be
patient to it but like so it's it's hard
to draw the line of like what's worth and what's
not so I just make it very clear if it's a
main channel video it's patron if it's not
it's not you know unless it's like a
podcast it's on the main channel or something
but like yeah if I
if I'd went full after dark I think I
could still make a few hundred dollars on
after dark I'd still make enough ad revenue
to kind of it would just be
where I was as a pony guy
like I could probably make
three hundred dollars a video put out four videos
a month well I guess I'd probably
change the I don't know how
how I'd do per video on
after dark I don't think you should I think
after dark would be a per week
I think has to be per month and you can do
what Tom Oliver was doing
for a long time was just he would make a
patron post every week so it was
set as per like his because you can just
write in per whatever yeah so
he wrote in per week and then he would just
collect all his videos from all his different channels
hmm that's a smart idea
so if I wish I could do that but they won't let me
change it now that I'm stuck in the month thing
oh yeah I feel like I'd be making more
if I did it I'll let you change to the other
not it's too late
I have the setting where
as soon as somebody pledges the money immediately get charged
yeah so now I can't change anything I'm just like stuck
yeah
yeah I would do it per week
and I would probably
make I could probably still make
over a thousand dollars a month on just
after dark and I mean that's minimum
wage working at some that's what it was
that's what I was making up to last year
when the channel suddenly blew up so
um yeah
uh I
encourage you to try to
be a youtuber because I think you're cut out for it
in a way that not a lot of other people are
you know then I'm just worried about the benefits
and what if I get sick
like insurance is a lot of money
and luckily I do have until
like what I'm 26 to get off my parents
insurance
no no that's one thing he's gonna keep
yeah he said he's gonna keep that
yeah so it's all good
maybe we're in luck
ugh that chump guy
pretty cool guy
I don't want to talk about Trump on here do I have to
uh no you don't have to
I want us to go for another hour
I kind of have to like
excrete everything from every orifice
of my body you want to put this on hold for a little
bit yeah I'm fine with it
yeah alright um
just remember to edit out the shitting part
yeah okay
we're back from the crapper we're back from
evacuating those bowels
ever been more empty so monkey
I wanted to ask you some stuff about your
influences okay um
part not only
in a few different ways
like for instance that we
both seem to have the same stance
on uh
on working
working putting putting out lots of content
and sort of being self motivated
and stuff and when I brought up
Quentin Tarantino you immediately
had a quote from him that you cited
so like was that
were you influenced by him and his ethos
or like who kind of inspired you to work the way you do
uh well to
to say about the Quentin Tarantino quote
it's because that's a meme on
tv the 4chan board
where like they use it I guess to make fun of him
even though his films are great so I don't
know what the joke is even though that phrase
makes I mean perfect sense
like if anything it's uh bragging
right I think they interpret
it as being just extremely pretentious but
if if anybody
has earned being pretentious it's Quentin Tarantino
because his movies are great
uh so what was
the question who who sort of influenced
your uh work ethic where did
you get the idea to work the way you do
oh that's just something I've had since
I was born but
god like even in
elementary school I was just chugging along
doing those multiplication tables
I just have to keep working all the time
or else I I guess I fall into depression
I don't know it's just it's an
innate drive like there's
an inner locomotive that just keeps
chugging along and I can sometimes hear
it just in
my head I've I've previously described
my own depression as
like it's all it's a base level
like on a basic level you're always
depressed and everything else is just
stuff you're stacking on top of that
and so you need it
because as soon as it's not there you fall back
to the basic level and would you say
that your work is like that like like
when you're not making work you're
depressed or when you're not like doing something
talking to somebody but then so
like you have to do it to keep away
from the depression I think that's
a perfect summation because I
hardly ever feel
suicidal or like
depressed to a point where it like physically hurts
when I'm working on a video or writing a script
or I guess
watching Survivor but that's not really working
well I think that's what I mean by like
doing something right you know like something that makes
you that that brings
something out of you that makes it so you're not
just sitting around thinking about
depression and for those of you at home
who don't relate to this you're probably thinking
well it's as simple as just
if you don't want to feel depressed go do a thing
and that logically makes sense
but once you fall into the trap
like you get convinced that you don't feel like
doing anything at all and I think
there's all these movies I want to watch but I don't really
feel like watching them
one of the most
the most resonant criticisms I
ever got was from my
mentor Ghost Lightning where I was complaining
about I was telling him about something
I wanted to make like I was kind of bragging
about something that I had an idea for but I
hadn't actually made it so why am I bragging?
Good job, Animal. Good job, Cob.
Yeah this is me before
YouTube you know back when I was an anime blogger
so I'm bragging about some idea
I have and he's like why don't you you know why don't you
work on that thing I think I was telling him
I was like upset or something he was like why don't
you work on that thing you were talking about and I was like I'm not in the mood
and he said you you have a real
problem with always letting these moods control
you and I thought I never
thought about it as something you had power over
that like you have to try to
escape the mood because
the mood if you if you just let yourself
be governed by moods you'll never do anything
you know you'll just be like well I'm depressed I'm not
in the mood to do this or that so it's always
a fight like like when I
when I get out of that it's not because I'm
like just able
to change it it's like it takes a real
like effort to like examine
what you're doing and be like no I have
to make a video today
like this has to happen
you know or else I'm uh I'm
fucked so do you think there's a lot
of that like just trying to keep
to your schedule and stuff is that what like
motivates you to help get you out of those those
funks yeah it definitely prevents them
from occurring in the first
place it's kind of have you seen the movie
never ending story
not so there's something called the swamps
of sadness where if
if you're standing in it and you're feeling
sad you'll keep sinking but if you have positive
thoughts you can keep going through and
it's the saddest part of the movie because the horse
drowns to death and the swamp is like kids
movie is very intense
and the kid is screaming and crying
but I think depression in a
way is like the swamps of sadness where
if you just think of other things
you can keep walking through the muck but
once you start sinking it's hard to get back
out so I
so having the schedule is
is like my version of keep
on walking through the swamp
so how how much
like what do you think you're
what are you trying to communicate
in your videos because it like
is your main motivation just to be funny
and to be entertaining for people because like
for me so much
of it comes from a desire to be understood
to like like like
the reason I have to make these analysis videos is that
if I go out there and I say chaos the greatest
anime of all time or something
people are just gonna look at me like I'm insane
unless I justify it you know
so to me so much of my videos
is like justifying these opinions I have
so that people will understand where I'm coming
from but your videos
deliberately obfuscate
your opinions to such an extent that there's
lots of people who just don't understand
what your opinions actually are on on most
things does that ever bother
you at all or does it like is it a problem at all
that you have created it cultivated a
character of just not being able to
be understood the last couple
PCPs I've been on
I just
shitposted and I hope people appreciated
them because otherwise it's got to be terrible
listening to me talk we did one like
how did you lose your virginity story and I just
described the plot of moonlight exactly
so and that's because
I think that me as a
person as a human being I don't find myself
interesting and I don't
think other people would if I let myself
go that much
so I'm not that interested I'd rather
just you know do be
I don't want to be me because it's fine
who cares I don't think anybody
should care do you feel like it backfires
it all though when like for instance
in the in the PCP chat I've described
you as the boy who cried wolf because
anytime you try to be sincere nobody
can tell because you've
gone so far into presenting an
insincere character I mean
I'm okay with that it's fine yeah
it doesn't bother me that much you don't
you don't find it like a frustrating when
people can't tell when you're trying
to be real about something well I think
if it's a main video like the
Elliot Roger one I don't think very many people
think I was being ironic in that one yeah
you kind of well you use a very different tone
and everything
and I'm and there's not really
any jokes in that video so
it's pretty clearly straightforward
yeah and then like
the countdown to suicide channel I don't
I don't shit post on there ever other than
my drunken live streams but that's just fun
yeah well that's what I like about that channel
so much is that I can always kind of
trust it like it always feels like okay
I think that's why
like that was kind of the key for me
understanding you enough to feel like
that we could be friends because if
all you did was shit post constantly
I just wouldn't be even be able to have a
conversation with you right but I was
like well there's clearly like a guy in
there somewhere it's just a super boring
guy who needs to
always be ironic or satirical
in order to be interesting because I
like
yes me like what what do I do on a daily basis
if I fucking I do what everybody else does I jerk
off once I sit there watch TV
that make videos and only the videos part
should be like anybody
should care about nobody should care
about what I as a human being
do I'm not saying that like I want to protect
myself or like oh don't look
at me don't look behind the curtain but because it's
just genuinely uninteresting
right I mean
I find the countdown to suicide videos
interesting but
I mean do you not think that if you
made like if you could convert
the the sort of what you're talking
about in the countdown to suicide videos into
main series serious content do you
think people would would find that interesting
well I think the depression review is the
closest thing I've come to doing that
and a lot of people seem
affected by that video
in I don't know if it's a positive or
negative way but both are
I think good do you think you
would you would consider like
when monkeys anime reviews is over are you
going to bring more sincere content
to oh yes yes I'm
going to branch out I've got
three different types of videos I want
to make I talked about the isms one
but what level of sincerity
would that one be
that's gonna be all over the place like sometimes
I'll be talking about how great
feminism feminism is
and then like I'll be shitting on atheism
even though I'm an atheist like just a bunch
of crazy wacky fun stuff
because I think that would be
it's somewhere in between
me and you is where is where endless
Jess is where you've been like
nonstop inauthentic and I've been
nonstop authentic because I have such a
difficult time making a video
because I've had times before where I make
something like your style and then people
will message me like well what's your actual
opinion people people are so invested
in like what I think about stuff that they're
like oh well it sucks that we don't get
to make a follow-up vlog explaining
my actual opinion about something
and Jesse kind of falls
in the middle where he'll represent both in the same
video and that's why
his so much of his audience can't
parse the difference and that's why
there's so many misunderstandings around them
because it seems to be difficult do you think
that this that you'll run into this
issue and would it bother you even
if it did like does it bother
you to not be understood in your intentions
no
because it's so rare that it's even
relevant to
I don't I can't think of one instance
where I was being super sincere in a
video and that people wrote it off as
being sarcastic
or disingenuous do you think there's more
of a chance of that once you mix the
like for instance
I mean to me this was clear
but I don't know if it would be to everyone else
that when you did your 10 anime heroes
the whole Hank Hill analysis is like
a completely legitimate and great
analysis of why Hank Hill is such a good
character and I was like well this seems
sincere to me but will people think
do you not know the story behind
the Hank Hill part no what so
so that's a that's a copypasta
I didn't write that oh I didn't know
that at all yeah I I
told more people caught on but a lot of people
just kind of praised me as like a great
analysis of Hank Hill
great point about why he's a good kid now that
you've mentioned it I feel like I've heard it
years ago like like a long time ago
it gets posted and every king of the hill
thread on TV I see
I thought it was funny like somebody
took the time to write that and I was like
I'm putting it in well see now now you understand
that your intentions work
everyone thinks you're an amazing analyst but
that's a good thing I'll take it
don't tell everybody
listening don't tell anybody that I didn't write that
I'll take the credit it's fine but are you at all
concerned that in the future when you try to
make more sincere content that people won't
understand well so I did
something I did that a while ago I did
the top five YouTube channels that
deserve more subscribers and I don't think anybody
thought that was sarcastic I think
I mean I explained what the channel was
and why I liked it and it's hard
there's no clear joke
then because I know
um Jesse was
saying how he was you you had said
that you you floated the idea of having
monkeys reviews and jimmies reviews making
it very clear the distinction between
that idea didn't last very long
yeah well just because
it's less funny that way
the ambiguity makes it funnier
but it also makes it riskier
because you never know what you're gonna get when you click
on the video is he actually gonna talk about the
top 10 anime heroes that's the thing it relies
more on the audience to understand
you know it's that like it's
if you make it completely distinct
then it might
it's more audience friendly maybe
well it's more audience friendly
but it also is
less artistically
interesting you know and that's why
Jesse was so adamantly against it even though
if he did that it would cause
none of these misunderstandings would happen
but he wants to put faith on the audience
and I'm wondering
I'm surprised he is putting faith in the intelligence
of his audience he seems like he wouldn't do that
it's that he would rather
elevate them rather than
stupid to them that's how he sees
that's kind of how he sees the whole world
rather than bringing my stuff
down to your level you have to come up to my level
unfortunately they won't do it
because they're idiots
how do you
how much faith do you have in your audience's intelligence?
I just think
it's all in the script
and if it's clear that I'm not making jokes
then like they should know
I actually mean what I'm saying
it's hard to get out of those moods
when you're kind of sinking in the swamp
and I was there's this video idea
I've had for a while that I think I'm gonna do next month
just
my top five favorite YouTube videos
and these are the videos that I always
go to when I'm feeling bad
and they never fail to make me laugh
or to smile and I was just gonna show them off
and say go watch these fucking videos
they work for me
I don't think anybody can misinterpret that
because it's so straight forward
why would I waste the time giving
reviews of random videos
that make me laugh
if I wasn't being serious about it
yeah I think
but you are putting some level of faith
in the audience's intelligence there
but I think you're definitely
doing enough to
but even if they misinterpret it
I don't see really the negative
if somebody watches that and thinks it's satired
it's not very bothered by not being
understood
I don't know why
for me it's just I can't do it
like the second someone misunderstands
I have to correct them
to one guy's comment
that misinterpreted it and I'm like
well I don't want to have to type out the whole reason
that this isn't the case so let me go
record a fucking 30 minute vlog
I have to pee really badly
we'll just cut this part out
um uh uh
damn it I know something I was gonna ask you
but I forgot I'll think about it while I pee
that's fine I suck at talking when you're out of the room anyway
make noises
fuck cub
better eat those chippies while you can girl
I've been eating them
how dare you
I'm a sneaky eater
sneaky girl
fuck cub
we gotta keep saying that even after I move
yeah
I can't live without saying fuck cub
we'll walk around the house and sing that
that's when I walk into the room and say it and walk out
fuck cub
yeah he says it back
sorry I'm such a leaky boy
that's okay I'm sure once we start drinking and we're doing a let's play
I'll be getting up between every episode again
yeah well we usually both are
so um
alright to get back into your influences
what are your influences like what are the direct influences
what is your style made of
I have a lot of guesses but you can
share some
well I guess in the video
we talked about earlier the mumkees anime reviews
of mumkees anime reviews
they're pretty much just list everybody
it's like the biggest problem in the
universe
Jon's run a little bit
I don't know I think that
I was listing like half
influences and half people
who everybody says I'm stealing from
but I've never actually like
I'm not inspired by them at all
like video game dunkey I like his videos
but I wouldn't say my style is even
close to what he does in any way
other than that our names are
kind of similar it's just having any
irreverence whatsoever everyone gets
compared it's like everyone
compares you to Jesse which is a closer comparison
but his are more like actual anime
reviews and yours are like
nonsensical and it would be
it's impossible to say that I'm inspired
by him because I made 30 episodes
before I even knew he was
alive and and
or demo people compare you to demo
never seen a demo video funny and talk
about anime and there's no other connection
really I promise if we watch some of his videos
you'd be like why do people compare me to this
this is nothing like my style
yeah you did you both did a video on
bokeh no pico that's okay
that's it I think somebody said he also
did a boon eye sisters but I was too afraid
to watch because I didn't want to steal his jokes on accident
yeah um
like I don't know
I don't really know
what my comedy influences are
you've been quoting a lot of the
widest kids you know I imagine that was an influence
uh yeah yeah
I mean I like their comedy
I don't know if it's really
similar to what I do
I mean not everything I mean
I was influenced by widest kids you know
it's not similar to what I do at all
a lot of just the
just simply the gallon of PCP
skit just that
skit was a huge influence on me and
Victor's sketch comedy before
you know what no I'll take it back I think
Trevor more specifically the leader of the widest
kids you know is a major comedy
influence to me because
you asked earlier what my kind of goal is
with it and the most important thing
to me is to fight against
any form of censorship and I want
I think anything that
can be said like
exercise it and say it
even if it's ridiculous and offensive
we should exercise this right of the freedom of speech
and Trevor Moore
in the first episode of widest kids you know
it ends with a music video called the hitler rap
where he's dressed up as hitler and he's
doing a whole rap about
the third rikin shit and it's like it's really funny
and
a lot of people would say you shouldn't be able to do that
I know they got in trouble once because
they had a music video
that was an instructional guide to children
about how to get rid of their fathers
by framing them for pedophilia
yeah it's called get a new daddy I know every word
yeah that's it's great
it's one of the best skits
it got them in real trouble because people were like
you can't you can't do this
because what if kids actually take it seriously
police would take the old one away in a catty
you can get a new daddy
get a new mommy, new brother, new sister
a new house, a new mommy
so at that point he'd ruined his entire family
and it was getting adopted into a new one
so is there any other
who else would you say
is a big influence on your comedic style
or your approach to comedy
I don't know
shaped the young mind of monkey
everybody knows when I was 11
or no even younger when I was in elementary
school I loved bo bo bo bo bo
I mean that's a satire
and that's what I'm kind of going for
and I liked how random and funny it was
and I
I get really meta a lot
and that's a very meta show
Don Patch is actively trying to become
the main character of the show all the time
and he says it
he's like I want to be the main character
so yeah I guess
I'm influenced by bo bo bo bo
and how meta it is and all that shit
so
I know you're
big into film
yeah
one of the things that I've always had
when it comes to people doing criticism
on a more serious level like with monkey's anime reviews
it's obvious that they're all sort of
irreverent and random and it doesn't matter
how much you know and even on
like my Japanese anime
which is more analytical but it never tries to
put the stuff into the context of anime
it's always just the show
you know and I'm
wondering when you do film analysis
or when you do film reviews with you and
and E-Rage one of the
difficulties I have with the show is that I have
no context
and you're putting these movies into the context of film
like is this movie good or bad
but I don't know what movies you think are good
or bad or things like that
and I'm wondering like
for instance when I watch YMS
do you watch
I love his top 10
of the year lists because
they give you such a clear picture
of his taste that anything
he says about a movie you can just think about
his top 10s and you're like well of course
you wouldn't like a superhero movie
it's just completely outside your genre
you know so
if you started doing movie reviews
like I'm curious like
what context do you have for films and like
how many have you seen how much do you
how how integrated
into the medium are you and would you present
this in your future videos
I think outside of just giving my
hot take with E-Rage I wouldn't
want to do film reviews because I mean
I'm not that knowledgeable
in the field and I don't really
have an established criteria of what makes
a good movie or a bad movie
if I see a movie and I like it I'll say
here's why and if you like these things
you'll like it too so I wouldn't say
it's a deep analysis
I understand why you're frustrated
when you watch it
it's not so much that I'm frustrated is that
I know you seem to care more
about film than other mediums
but it's difficult to tell
how much you care
is it like me with anime
everything and know everything or is it just
like I like going to the movies every week
you know it's probably more the second
one I just I like going to the movies
more than probably 90%
of people is there any
like artists like is there any stuff
that you're really passionately that
you follow like that you
like not not necessarily a medium it could
just be I know you're really big into survivor
yeah like how like
what's your relationship with that kind of
stuff if you had to put together a top
10 list of shit mom monkey cares
about what would be on that top 10 oh my
god
so my Prague music
your Arians your your dream
theaters your
Spock's Beards your transatlantic
I spend most of my time with that
podcast like the biggest
problem the dick show
the flop house that kind
of stuff those are the main ones I've never heard the flop
house it's the
two of the three guys are writers for the
daily show and so they're pretty funny
I mean most of the time and they
they just watched a bad movie
and they talk about it and
I wouldn't recommend it I just know that I
like it okay that's
interesting yeah well because I don't recommend
everything that I like because I know why
I like it and I wouldn't expect other people
to like it for the same reason
so yeah we have the music the
podcast yeah I like watching
movies probably more than
watching I guess like anime
or TV like I'd rather just watch
a movie but
there are a lot of TV shows I'm really passionate
about like I was huge into Breaking Bad
now I'm big into Fargo and Better Call
Saul a survivor obviously
all I do these days
is pretty much watch old
survivor seasons like just
and binge them all day when I'm not working on stuff
you begin to like big brother
yeah I'm gonna I'm gonna go audition
for big brother in like a week
so you know wish me luck
if I if I disappear and stop making
videos it's because I'm on TV
go turn it on channel 8
I was really fascinated by your
attachment to like reality TV
which most people on the internet
completely because people
don't understand because
I think the problem is they
think it's all on the same level of
like the bachelor which I think
most people watch because it's shit
but survivor is it's
like a completely different genre I wouldn't
even lump it in with the reality
TV like that they think it's all like your real
housewives bullshit
but it's totally not yeah
survivor was kind of the original
the original and the best kind of survivor
is by far the best yeah like way
more product I mean I've seen a lot of it because my mom
is a huge survivor fan and like
yeah the level of production
is way above all the other ones but it's
still not real
like what do you mean by not
real like a lot of scripted
not scripted but there's
a lot of staging there's a lot of like
when you know behind the scenes the magic's
kind of gone you know where it's like
but it's still a competition at
its heart like it's no different from a game of
baseball there's a lot of things that are organized but
it's still a game it's about the
I mean they put together a good narrative out of
it you know sure it's not a lot of
editing but it's just not real in the sense
of like oh this is all like exactly what
it's like for sure it's because there's like
40 stage hands to
immediately off camera at any given time
the problem is they have to edit
three days of footage into
a 40 minute narrative so sometimes
I mean in the editing room you have no choice
if you want to have a cohesive narrative you have to do
things like that but at the end
of the day it's still a real game that's being played
and you're watching like
these Don Brackens manipulate people
and become the king of the island
and it's really really interesting to me
and I love watching the strategy talk
I don't care so much for the competitions
I don't care for like the petty fights over stupid
shit I like to watch those
strategic masterminds the puppet masters
who rise and use their intellect
to just rule over
everybody else and win the game and that's
why I love it it was a great
quote from Dick Masterson
I don't know the I don't remember exactly what he said
or how he phrased it but it was on a recent
podcast where he was talking
about people complaining that the show is like
just you know using gossip
and like trying to like oh it's all guys
he's like oh I'm so sorry
that I have an hour of narrative
content with a gigantic
viewership every week that like that we spun
a human drama that's
deeply interesting to lots of people
that happens to be based in reality
I was like yeah like that's why I'm watching
the dick show is like I want
the goss I want the drama
because it is deeply interesting
to see this like character portrait
of Maddox as this this
this man whose whole identity
is shifting in the eyes of people
to like recognize him in a different way
it's so if this was all scripted it would be like
oh whatever it's not a drama but the fact that
it's actually happening in real life is what makes
the whole drama of the biggest problem
so great and and it would be
so like people people
are saying like oh you're you're just you know taking advantage
of the goss but it's like you need
someone who can spin that and make it interesting
and Dick's willingness to
withhold so much information
and dish it out at just the right moments
and to keep finding ways to spin it
and to get more people involved like
he's managing it perfectly and that's
why it's such a good show it's great
like if if this if the exact same thing
happened with me I would have made
a five-hour podcast explaining
everything in the next day
you know like I would have laid out every single
thing that happened between me and Maddox
and the show would have been over
and dick you know looked at it and went this can
be a story and and the fact that it keeps
that Maddox keeps doing
things to make it keep going is why
and why it remains that interesting
even on the first episode of the dick
show like we're all anxiously waiting
to hear what happened and he doesn't even
like really mention it until the last ten minutes
and like what the fuck like I was on the edge of my seat
the whole time there it is like he knows how
to how to hold a story
yeah and
yeah I know you you've said that you
you've kind of fallen out with the dick
show because it's just too much it's
it used to be like an hour long
and now it's like two and a half
hours long the funny thing about it is that he's
he was saying that like it's that long
because of the fact that people are
paying for it and he's like I want to give them
a lot you know like people are paying all
this money to get this this big chunk of show
every week and like
on some on one hand I appreciate
the other hand if I am at all busy
that week yeah I am not going to be able
to make the like I mostly watch it
in like seven-hour marathons when I find
it like when I find the chance
and I watch it I have the
video so I'll sit back
on the couch and just like drink beer
and watch it all day when I finally
catch up yeah that's the problem I'm into right now
is that I'm like three episodes behind
so that's it's going to take me
seven hours to catch up and I was like
I don't know if it's worth it I don't know
but I just I skipped two episodes
and jumped into the mad cucks one because I saw
he was on there and I think that's a great
idea to have a straight up parody
of Maddox there on the show
and and they're gonna they did a
recording of a full biggest problem
biggest problem episode which I'm greatly
looking forward to. I can't wait for that.
April Fool's Day.
Yeah it's going to be great
but um
anyway I don't want to talk too much about
other no other other creators that
our audience might not follow but this is
it's kind of integral to how we
like why I wanted to contact you is that
you knew these these guys
you know stuff like that because like in the
movie me and me and Jesse
uh and who else
me and Jesse in particular
are really big fans of biggest problems so we've been
following all this as it was happening
and stuff and I think yeah we don't I was
already in contact with you when the breakup
happened I think definitely
yeah and then and I kind of message you like
uh monkey and you know like
we weren't like close yet but I was like
I don't know how to reach out to this guy
to tell him like what's going on do you see
this happening you know yeah I noticed you
like a couple comments sections and then I think
you probably found out that I liked it
either from the mumkeys anime reviews video
or in one of my nuzlocke in my nuzlocke
I talked about it too but uh
I think it's interesting you asked me
like what are my the 10 most important things
to me and it sort of fell apart because like I said
me as a person I'm not interesting
but then once we start talking about something
that we both like then we pick up the
conversation again well I think I mean if
you I don't think I'm
interesting but I have
interesting ways of interpreting things and I just
will always
talk about them like like if
my uh vlogs were just
literally like digibro a day
in the life it would be a story of me making
the vlog I'm making which
has been some of them
uh that's kind of the joke
in uh Insomnia Analysis 3 is that
I keep um I
hit record and then I set up the shot
so like every shot starts with
me setting it up and like moving the camera
like dragging the tripod across the room
and stuff like very meta yeah
and just because
yeah like it's it's not
that you are interesting it's that you present
things in an interesting way which I
feel like I need
the cloak of monkey to do that because
I I think I took all
the most interesting parts of my personality
and then put them
on like you know
I increased them ten fold with the character
so now when I go back to just like
talking as me it's like oh this is
a boring version of this well
we've been doing a podcast for almost three hours
yeah yeah it's been fairly entertaining
I would hope so I mean I think
I think there's always like
it's kind of the reason I don't ever want to
lose the main channel of digibro like you were
saying that I could probably subsist off after dark
and that's true but to me
um like
the second I do that I'm just
I'm just some guy
you know like it's the the
partifice of that I am creating
something that I consider to be
bigger than myself
is how I'm able to also
have this off-air persona
like if it was just
digibro talks about being digibro it would
quickly become an uraburo
to start eating itself and I would
it's like a celebrity that's only famous for being famous
exactly like I want
there to be that like the
reason you're interested in me
is because you got in through this
other thing you know you had to come from somewhere
and like yeah I mean after dark
has a lot of interesting vlogs that on their own
like you said are better than the main channel videos
pretty damn good and are not necessarily
uh
like it's not all just me being
me you know it's not all the digibro
show um but like to me
it's important that that exists but I think
that that allows for this other
life to happen that's why I'm interested in
um you know countdown to suicide
like those videos wouldn't be interesting on their own
but they also
are interesting like just because
monkey exists and I want to know
what that guy is about I'm like what
what drives someone to make this video
that I thought was hilarious like what is there
to that guy you know
and I think that inherently makes you
interesting even though you wouldn't be
if not for that content you know
much like the
the anime fights podcast thing
uh I cannot watch
the countdown to suicide videos
and I don't watch them I record them upload
them and then I try to pretend it never happened
other than reading the comments I
can't stand to hear those
things I said about myself
there's a lot of my uh after dark vlogs
that I can't watch back like I will
when I when I make it
I'll watch it back like to check to see
if it's like coherent and I'll enjoy
it but then if I go back like a week later
it's just because the
because it's not written all the phrasing
is just so bad
like it's all it's every point I make
is something that the more I think about it
I realize how I could have said it better
you know and then you listen back and it's just like
ugh this
this is why no one understands you
because you phrase everything so fucking incoherently
um and of course
you know I have to like watch myself be drunk
and like walk around the room screaming
now that's fun that's fun
I'll watch any video of me being drunk
I think it's always a blast
and at the god of war rant where I just scream
for 30 minutes
that's a little difficult to get
to again
now that's the kind of video I would watch again
for sure the ones where I get like super
serious and talk about
I've been depressed
for five years I don't want to hear it
I don't want to hear it you definitely can't sit through
the decompression chambers oh yeah I imagine
but particularly
the last one where it was the one that
was like the
that's a good one when you talk shit about yourself
but also talk highly of yourself
at the same time that one was so hard
to both finish and
get through because I had listened to it back
like because I was so unsure of it
I kept listening back to the segments
and every time I would just be like
ugh
I can't believe I'm releasing this
I encouraged you to release that a lot because I wanted
to hear it and I mean a lot
of people I think
ultimately enjoyed it and got something out of it
but like there was not never a point
that I didn't regret it like I released it
and most of like I didn't want to
hear people's reactions to it and like
every reaction I heard I was like yeah I knew this
was coming I knew that was coming
this is not I don't want
this to exist I don't want to do this again
let's not have it be this way
is that why that show is cancelled
partly I mean that
and I just got busy after that and
like yeah
I lost interest in the format
you know like I'd rather just
I've done a few things that are similar
to decompression chambers on my reddit
it's just a matter of there's a lot of stuff
that I want to exist now that I don't want
to be public you know have you ever had
like that that's I mean you
you separate your channel so surely on some level
like countdown to suicide is
meant to be hidden
like I mean I it's
in every single description
of my videos when you list all my channels
it's like I mean my reddit is always listed
too but I'm not like out
like if I posted something there it's because
I want I want to
hear what like my closest fans have to
say but I don't necessarily
want everyone's reaction
to it like I don't want this to be
like not that I'm hiding it from
everybody but that it's not meant
to be seen by a wide audience
like like my book like that
book was six years old great book
and written you know like it was written by a
different me and if I release that on
after dark I just don't want
to have to read people like criticizing
the book as if I just wrote it you know
it's like no this is an ancient piece of work
that barely is related to me anymore
I just wanted it to exist out there
and as long as a few people can get something
out of it that's fine you know like
so do you do you think that you
have any kind of inclination to like
release stuff that is deliberately
not for the public
not really I think
if if for some bizarre reason
monkeys count down to suicide blew up
and it had like half a million subs
and it was my biggest channel I'd be like
okay that's fine I guess people like this
I'd be I'd accept that
I think any of us would accept that
that's cool like I wasn't trying to hide this
I don't care if people see it I mean
I don't try to make
things that I don't want like thousands of
people to see I mean you seem to be
when you were you were a little upset
when all the normies came to the channel after
I shouted it out on the PC
that's mostly a meme
you know normies get the fuck out
yeah
your fans are always
mad when you get more
yeah and they're not being sarcastic most
of them I think they actually want the normies
to get the fuck out but it's not like
I'm gonna change my content style
because there's more people watching it
like they can just choose that it's too edgy
for them and they can leave yeah that's the natural
flow of things
um
alright well I've run through
most of the questions I had thought of
but that was a good 45 minutes
we still need another 15 minutes of content
does that include
all the times we weren't recording
because we were in the bathroom and stuff
yeah it was only like 10 minutes that we were short on
well we don't have to go to 3 hours
I mean it's no big deal to me
was there anything else you'd want
people to understand about you or anything
anything else you would say
about your content where it's going
why it exists
so I could
I could talk
I guess about some of my ideas for
the future things on Mumkey Jones
because some people seem a little
cautious about me saying
Mumkey's anime review is ending
they're like oh god no
I have to un-pledge my Patreon
he's gonna stop American videos
it's not true at all
I still want to make the same exact thing
only just drop the joke about anime
and drop all the Uncle Alex jokes
it really has been fleshed out
as much as I think it can be
so I'm ready to get away from that
so some ideas I have
I said the top 10
isms thing
I want to do some serious videos
like my top 5 videos
that are my favorite on YouTube
and then other things I want to do
I think it'd be fun
every now and then did do another
anime review
of like an anime but I just don't call it that
I would just it'd be like
you know
a soul leader and then instead of Mumkey's
anime reviews it would say Mumkey Jones
I think that should be like
the new subtitle and I also
want to do a series called
Mumkey 101 where the
title of the video is like a big question
and then I explore the question
and try to answer it and some examples
I have are can women
be forever alone
and I would go through
edits of like forever alone women
versus you posted some screenshots
for that which were hilarious
because they were so fucking
like I'm going to compare
the difference between what the forever
alone women sub is
and what the normal forever alone
one is and then like
compare that to the incels who are
actually forever alone
so just exploring questions like that and having fun
another one I have which
you and me did
we've recorded a podcast last night
I don't know if that'll be out yet or when it's coming out
I don't know
it's going on my channel it probably won't be out until like
the end of March
but another question I want to try to answer
is do Muslims deserve rights
which is
it seems like a joke question but then when you
get into the stick of it
yeah there's a lot to be said on the subject
obviously they deserve human rights
but then when you get down to the nitty gritty of
you find out that subways
some of them are banning all pork products
now to adhere to their
Muslim customers like
is that a right that they deserve because of their imaginary
friend I think not
well I mean if it's good for business for
Subway to do it then of course they should do it
yeah but then you're like the poor white guy who lives
in the newly enriched community
who can no longer get bacon on his sub
like is that fair for him
just because of this imaginary friend bullshit
go to another restaurant
yeah well whatever
so I'm gonna do some research on that
and see how many
communities are being culturally enriched
and all the rights
that are being changed
so more controversial
stuff that will make me lose thousands of subs
every upload well I love that you're
taking that even-handed
approach of like everyone gets
shit on everybody no one's safe
even me especially me the Christians
aren't safe the Muslims aren't safe the Jews
aren't safe and now the atheists aren't safe
I'm coming I'm gonna go to the atheism
plus subreddit and just oh you all
think you know so much
you just think
no proof that God
doesn't exist and yet you're
so convinced
just have fun with it
yeah and pick on some
some some like edgy teen atheism
obviously lots of fedora jokes
just easy stuff yet
I think it's it's very important
that I think the problem with comedy
these days is that everybody
is getting way too political with it
but they're choosing a side
I think if you're gonna get political with it
attack everybody don't just
choose one side I mean that's what's so great
about George Carlin is that his politics
were just like I
fuck everybody all of you are wrong about
everything you know I'm the only one who
makes any sense in this world
you know which is why
if Jesse
I always compare to Carlin and like everybody
compares Louis C.K. to Carlin but
no fuck Louis C.K.
I think he used to be but not anymore
just going just that
yeah the attitude of like
you've all wronged me
like whatever system
you've all created I'm not happy
and it's because I'm in this system and you're all
a part of this system so you have wronged me
you know
it's sort of the mentality
it's important to be even handed with your hatred
because it's not
discrimination if you discriminate against every
group equally it just
it might seem like I attack
feminists and like Muslims and stuff
more often but it's just because they have more
out there to make fun of and because they're
the ones who are being more defended now
yeah and they're the ones who are causing
the most problems in my mind
I mean it's
it's like
you know I feel like
you're trying to keep the scales from getting
tipped like
when like it's getting
harder and harder to make fun of Muslims
right now
even though it should be they should be made fun
of just as much as Christians and anybody else
it should all be equal and so the harder
it gets to make fun of them the more you
have to kind of push back and go no it's still
okay
I want my bacon out of the subway
everybody still deserves this
I have to pee again
I'm a fucking
I've had like four bottles of water I don't know why I keep drinking it
he's a thirsty dude
you haven't had to go at all
well I went
working here
fucks you
fuck
are your balls sweaty? mine are really
sweaty
my fucking balls are sweating
the storm up in here
did you leave this all in
your whole body is sweaty
you sweat when you like record
yeah I do
I think like my whole body is just like
okay we're in work mode baby
let's do it let's all focus all the energy
up on that brain
and even then it doesn't work
I can't wait till we can get drunk and record funny
let's plays
let's do it already I'm so sick of being
a serious boy
time to be a funny boy
are we gonna have dinner?
what do we do for dinner?
I really want like a vegetable
if we're gonna get dinner we should do it way before
yeah we should do it immediately after
this podcast before we start drinking
I've been like
back and forth like should I
drink a golden monkey now or wait till
we're after the podcast
I mean a sheep can drive us
so alright I guess I'll
I'll leave us out
on a big question
okay let's say
is there like a question that you ask everybody in every interview
no there's nothing like that
let's say that tomorrow
um
um monkey jones one of your videos
goes viral again
do I get to pick which one?
sure
that's top 10 suicide methods
I know that's your favorite
yeah let's go with that one that's fine
this goes viral
spikes up to 50,000
subscribe
because finally it's a video that everyone understood
they checked out the rest of your channel
they realized it was more of the same
which has been happening on a micro level
like the last week
I think mostly because of you
because I've got an influx of comments on every
video now instead of just like the most recent one
and they're all saying whoa these videos are great
dude this whole channel's gold
I'm like yeah you're right
you're fucking right they are
we did it
so let's say you get
you're suddenly 50,000 subs
hell yeah
patreon jumps up
you're making a thousand dollars a month
fuck
my goal on patreon says a thousand dollars
this is my full time job
so we'll see if that happens
so you reach a thousand dollars a month
you get 50,000 subs
it looks like things are going to keep growing
it's going to just do the same thing I'm doing now
I don't know how I would switch it up
I mean if they subscribe because I like
what I'm doing so far so I just
keep doing it I guess
do you think you would
let's expand it out
let's say monkey
this happens you live off of monkey jones for a little while
you're goddamn right
monkey explodes again
now you're making 10,000 dollars a month
fuck
what do monkey do
I don't know what are you expecting
what do you do if you have a ton of expendable income
and all the time in the world to spend it
cause like for me so much of what
I've been doing is on the basis
of the fact that I can make
if it
really came down to it I could make
two videos in a month and that's enough
if I'm just worried about sustaining myself
like no advancement
or anything like just paying the rent
and eating
you know
you could even make one video a month
if Davoo didn't edit it definitely
one
so for the rest of the month I can do whatever the fuck I want
so if monkey jones
is on a timetable now
where you don't have to have a video every week
trying to grow the channel
because you're already grown
and you're making a guaranteed amount of month
that is in excess of how much you need
do you keep
doing weekly videos all the time
keeping to the same schedule
or do you try to expand
or do you try to do something different from the main channel videos
where do you put this extra money you've made
I think I continue
to do the
a video weekly or bi-weekly as my job
but then now that this dream is accomplished
I go back to the original dream
that we all had back in the day
you had it too of being a writer
cause at the end of the day
in my mind that's the high arch
that's what I want to do
because you've written a book
I believe this book could be it
if I just get that lucky break
of somebody in the industry
who wants to give it a chance
which has not happened yet
and I'm losing faith
if you had the time
would you just write another
if you were making enough money off your channel
that you knew you didn't need
any regular job anytime soon
are you just going to go full in on writing the book
when you're not doing the channel
what's the fucking book
yeah well I think that's a great answer
cause it's something that
I think about a lot because of the fact
I guess nobody thinks about this until they've made it
but I got to that point
in November
where I said holy shit
as long as I write four scripts at the start of the month
and give them all to DeVoo
I can do whatever I want for the rest of the month
I can make any dream project I've dreamed of
when's that book coming did you
yeah good question
well a little thing
happened where January
rolled around and I wrote out this huge schedule
of all the videos I was going to make
that were going to come out at certain dates
and dates in January and I was going to expand
the channel and blow it up
and then it would leave me with all this free time
to work on a book
and then Radcon 2 happened
all of it went out the window
and then I broke you as a human being
yeah I've been depressed
so
that's Radcon for you
yeah
it wasn't so much Radcon
well it was Radcon's fault
nevermind
what am I trying to defend you
I don't know those Radcon boys
they sure do make me depressed too
I guess that's what I meant to say
it's not any of their fault
it's the event itself and the time that it took out of my life
let's just say it was Ben's fault
yeah why not
I want to end this interview by saying fuck Ben
let's wrap it up so I can say fuck Ben
alright um
subscribe to Monkey Jones
subscribe to Monkey Jones 2
we've got a ton of shitposts coming
like we have recorded
probably 30
shitposts to be released one a day
for the next month
for the month of April probably
as well as
a Let's Play
that will be on your Let's Play channel
Monkey's
Gaming Expedition
we actually did a full Nuzlocke
last night we recorded a full Nuzlocke
we stayed up all night
drinking beer and recording
a full Nuzlocke
at hyper speed
and we did the whole thing
one of the most impressive things I've ever seen in my life
I think so and with Victor
you and I also did some
I guess Vincent I should say we did some Let's Plays too
we recorded like three episodes of Let's Play stuff
that will be on Digi Bros
yeah that will be on Digi Bros
and me and Monkey are going to start doing
podcasts together that's right I hope you guys like it
we didn't do as much prep as we should have
but I think it's a good pilot episode
yeah and if it's successful
maybe it'll
I would really love it if we just became a podcast
in many ways I would rather do
podcasts than anything
I'm doing right now
one hour comedy podcast a week
sounds like the dream
I'm so jealous of Dick
is it what we should all aspire to be
he has a successful book
and this podcast are you kidding me
I was having
I was talking to Jesse about this the other day
what I admire the most about Dick is that he's
proven that you can be hugely
successful on the internet without
participating in the internet
which is what I think me and Jesse both dream of
is escaping the internet
a lot of people don't understand that because a lot of people live on the
like are younger than us and grew up with the internet
always being there I mean that was kind of me
and to me growing up
the internet was always shunned
as a place for freaks and weirdos
I was on it that's why I wanted to go on it
I've been on since 2001
but I've always seen it as
this is not what you're supposed to be doing
supposed to be out there living life
old people are fucking dumb
but it's ingrained in your mind
and I've got all these memories of having friends
having fun
what was it like
my best friend deleted my viral video
yeah
I don't know what friends are
I would have killed him for that
I would literally have fucking killed him
one day my revenge will be complete
when I look at Dick I'm like this is a dude
who only interacts with the internet
as much as he wants to
and otherwise is able to be a man
about town and have real relationships
he's like the CEO of a company
it doesn't even need any of the money
does not need any of the dick show's money
puts it all back into the dick show
other than buying his house
which is obviously a huge benefit
that's very important for the show
you can't have those goddamn apartment neighbors
so
he's
definitely living the dream of
when I look at him I think
man I need to get out of here because
it's not a matter that I'm not successful enough
to have what Dick has
I'm not living my life right
I think we should all aspire to be dicknested
in every different way
he's the perfect man
he's my idol, he's my hero
back around episode 60
of Biggest Problem
I got on the Biggest Problem subreddit
and I posted like a shower thought
I said
childhood is thinking Maddox is the genius
but adulthood is realizing it's dick
and everybody down voted me
they thought I was wrong
because that was back when everybody still praised Maddox
and Dick was like just a derpy co-host
that was the
the parabolic arc that me and Jesse
both followed watching the Biggest Problem
is that in the beginning
Dick seems like the asshole because
he was playing up the comedy and the character
but then once, because Maddox took the arguing
so seriously
then Dick started taking the argument more seriously
that's when you realize, wait a minute, Dick's the only one
who actually makes any sense
Dick's the smarter one, he's like a normal dude
and by the time you get past episode 50
consistently Dick is way
blowing Maddox the fuck out
oh my god, Dick's my hero
I think that's a huge reason why
Maddox wanted Dick off the show
because he was upstaging him so much
towards the end
Dick said that he was saying
I feel like it's gonna get this way for Rucka
he's probably in the mind state I was towards the end of the show
which is that I have to have this show
end before it becomes apparent that this is just
me beating up on an autistic guy
that's all Rucka is really doing
he was really concerned
that's what it was gonna turn into
that's exactly what it was
well everybody that's been
three hours of
man I hope you made it through all of that shit
of Mumkey's
interview
hopefully this will mean
the interview series is coming back
I still have never interviewed Nate
you haven't done Ben have you
I did Ben, Ben was the first one
yeah cause Patreon was in the title
we did Ben, we did Ben, DeVoo
Jesse, Munchy
and
who was the other one
Psy
no I haven't done you
so it's six out of ten I haven't done Mage, Tom,
Nate or
King Critic I did Hippo
and I haven't done
who's missing from that King Critic
David Clegg
who the fuck am I missing
I haven't done Nate, Tom,
Mage
maybe I've done six
oh yeah myself that's number ten
I mean
someone should interview me
now you should do a three hour interview with yourself
that's just did you wrap the dark
just upload like a three hour compilation
of those so hopefully we'll get
to the last three guys
and girl
two guys and a girl, poor Mage
thanks again for listening everybody
and I'll see you in the next one
fuck Ben
bye