Hello, everybody, and welcome to yet another entry in the Pro Crastinators Podcast interview series.
I've got with me a very special guest, Munchy, the king of evils back to deal a rightly fucking deserved punishment for these goons, these villains.
You people did not press one hard enough, and now I'm here to take my fucking, my spoils, my spoils of war. Best guy's head ever on a fucking platter. That's what I'm giving for Christmas this year.
Technically not a member of the Pro Crastinators, but an honorary member, for sure.
So Munchy, what the hell? Why is this happening?
I made a joke, and I said, you should add me to an interview, and he said, that's the way the cookie crumbles, crumbles right onto my flaccid wing.
Alright, well Munchy, you're sort of an ancillary member of the Pro Crastinators.
We usually just introduce you as having done my avatar, which sounds like nothing at all compared to why the rest of us know each other, so why do I know you? You want to tell that story?
Yeah, it's a very heartfelt story. I could turn this into a summer blockbuster, all a forced gump. You obviously being the retarded cast member.
So I met you, I think, I honestly want to say, I think I met you before you knew about Jesse. Maybe not knew, before you were friends with Jesse. I'm not sure.
That seems possible.
Yeah, I met you the very, well I didn't meet you, but I found out about you the very first time Tom ever liked one of your videos. It was something like the ages in My Little Pony.
So were you already following Tom?
Yeah, I was following him. It's a long trail of just fucking random people I found and I eventually just hopped from one personality and one podcast to another and eventually I found out Tom.
Then I found you and I was like, ooh man, I have no time and this guy has a lot of videos. It's time for me.
I didn't have that many at the time, if it was Pony Ages.
Yeah, I know, but still it felt like a lot because I just waste all my time.
Great.
Yeah, and the way I just followed your content for a while as a normal person, I didn't comment or nothing.
Then the reason why we even started talking is I would start to send you very, what's the word, sensual and strange pickup lines on your Tumblr.
Pretty much every week, maybe even twice a week for how long would you say?
God, months. I would just get these fucking weird pickup lines and I thought it was funny that it was happening, but you seemed legitimately psychotic.
I was like, it's kind of early into me having somewhat of an internet fame or whatever in the My Little Pony community.
This is obviously a consequence of having people know who I am.
This is the fucking burden you're going to have to live with.
It was kind of funny, but it went on for so long and the thing is that the most important fact about it is that you would send these to me as asks on Tumblr and I never published any of them.
So I was thinking, what is wrong with this guy that he keeps sending me messages for months with no reply, no whatsoever response.
I didn't need any due.
The act of sending them in and of itself was gratifying enough.
Yeah, it would just be all these weird fucking pickup lines.
And then the story continued at BronyCon 2013.
Was it 2013?
No, I'm sure it was 2013.
You were having a Q&A with Tom. You were high on, this was in your prime, I think.
I just picked up, I don't remember what I said.
It was something about the Smurfs 2, I think, if you're ever going to review the Smurfs 2.
I can't believe I forgot all about this.
A fucking con was a treasure.
Anyway, I picked up the mic, I asked you if you were going to review Smurfs 2 and then at the very end I said, oh by the way, I'm the guy who's sending you pickup lines on Tumblr.
And you just fucking looked at me with the most like, you were fucking a deer in the headlights.
All your fears are just fucking materialized in front of you.
It was so amazing that it was a real person, a real human.
And the way you were acting was exactly what I expect from the guy who was sending me pickup lines on Tumblr.
Because you got up and very loudly asked about the Smurfs 2.
In the middle of all these other people asking legitimate questions, you get up and you're like, are you ever going to review the Smurfs 2?
And while holding a bucket full of shit, you had this like pale, this red pale full of crap that you were carrying around.
And I asked you to sign my bucket and you were very pleased.
Yeah, so that was like right after the Q&A I think, right?
Yeah.
You got me to sign the bucket and I, because I'm just thinking this guy is a troll.
So I think I signed it.
What did I sign it with?
It was something derogatory.
You know, it's just like something like this guy sucks and sucks is spelled wrong.
I think I just spelled my name wrong as all it was.
Oh yeah, yeah, something like that, something like that.
I know something was misspelled.
That's the main thing I remember.
And we just kept finding each other.
I don't know if you knew this, but I wasn't intentionally stalking you.
I would just always be where you were.
Well BarneyCon's not big.
It's not a very large convention.
The way it was that you would do it though is that you would, we'd run into each other,
like we'd be in the same place.
And then you kept drawing things.
And then just like walking up to me and handing me the things you'd drawn.
And they all were like these insane, like, it would be like me farting into my own mouth or something,
like screaming about Nazis or like holding a Schwastika or something.
And I'm like, all right, cool.
And you'd like run up to me, hand it to me and scurry away.
Scurry away.
Yeah, I remember one time I was just sitting on the floor.
I just didn't even know you were around me.
And then I just like see you fucking approach from the corner of my eye and you just look down at me.
I'm fucking crisscross applesauce on the floor and you just say,
Well you drawn this time.
I just think I've made it.
I've made it big.
He wants to know.
I do remember that.
Yeah, because I just saw you like in the hallway drawing something.
And bear in mind, because I think we've made this clear to our audience before.
If you're going to say something about age, then yes.
Yeah, well, that you don't look your age.
Yes.
That you were at the time, I think, 13.
Oh, God, yeah.
Oh, my God.
If it's in August, I might have been 12 years old.
Yeah.
So you were like 12, but you were only probably a couple inches shorter than me.
You weren't quite as tall as me at the time, right?
Because now you tower over me.
I think we might have been the same height.
Or if not, you were just very slightly taller than me.
So you were like my height sort of heavy set.
You had long hair and like a little bit of a peach fuzz mustache.
And you're like a Mexican, right?
Or some mix?
Yeah, just some mixed shit, I don't know.
Right.
But you have darker skin.
And I just thought that you were just like a Mexican guy who was like my age.
And I had no reason to think otherwise.
Yeah.
But the moment that sort of changed my perception of you completely at BronyCon was you handed
me a picture that said how I can draw Digi and how I choose to draw Digi.
And how I can draw Digi was this really nice looking like picture, like with this really
unique art style that was cool.
And then the other one was like the usual shit you'd been handing me.
And that was when I was like, oh, he's actually like a good artist.
He's just deliberately.
Well, up to that point, I had no reason to think you weren't like a legitimately insane person.
Yeah.
But then when I saw that, I was like, this is all tongue in cheek.
It's like this is all on purpose.
You know, he doesn't draw this way because he's crazy.
He draws this way because it's ironic and it's supposed to be funny.
And so and I still have it.
I kept all those drawings in my wallet.
I remember.
Well, continue.
And then I'll talk about something after.
Oh, that's it.
Okay.
Well, I remember you got home and you made like a like a decompressing vlog where you were
just a veggie now with Victor.
By the way, I'm a pinpoint that because I'm going to talk about how you're fucking stupid
for not knowing veggie now it isn't thinking it's cool.
Anyway, you were a veggie now with Victor and you were just reviewing all the shit you got
at BronyCon.
And then there was just like fucking 10 or like nine minutes.
Just feel about fucking me.
And like there was like time codes in the description where it was like, oh, we talked about da da da.
And then there was just fucking one.
There was like 10 minutes.
Munchy.
Just munchy.
And I guess I found out your name from this at some point at some point.
Yeah.
I had gotten your Skype through that.
Okay.
And then so yeah.
Back then I accepted almost everybody on Skype.
Yeah.
So the fact that you got my Skype.
And then so 2013 is it because like at some point we started talking more and then it was
when I got into my relationship with my ex-girlfriend, she started dragging you into calls with us all
the time.
Your girlfriend was odd.
Yeah.
She was.
I mean, I don't want to, she's not here right now.
She was fucking weird, dude.
She was weird.
Well, she was obsessed with me.
And I think, you know, I think the reason that she was so interested in you is that I talked about you in that
vlog because like, because when I met her, she had told me that she had rewatched that BronyCon 2013
vlog like over and over again because she had wanted to go to BronyCon and she couldn't.
So she sort of experienced it vicariously through my vlog.
I actually, like there's a lot of people who tell me that they like, like Jeff Burgess
like loves watching like parts of that vlog.
I don't know why.
Like I get that there's certain videos I have from that era that like almost all the views
I think are from the same people just watching it over again.
And that's one of them.
So I think she knew she had heard that story before.
And then when she found out that you were like a kid, then she thought it was adorable.
She would always like refer to you as like our son or something.
It was, it was, it was very interesting at the time.
It was just like, oh, I mean, I get to talk to this guy more.
So I mean, I'm not going to deny this, but that's a little weird, man.
Yeah. And to me, it was always really awkward.
Cause like, cause she would do it when I clearly didn't want like, cause we sit in Skype calls all the time
and she would just get bored and start throwing other people.
It would be like you and Vita who is even worse, far worse.
We're not going to, I don't think we're going to talk about that.
We're not going to talk about him.
But she would throw the two of you in and it would just be like weird and awkward.
Cause I'm like, okay, now I didn't, I already, it's, it was already weird how much we skyped each other,
but it was doubly weird that she was throwing in other people.
And you know, and I could tell for you, it was always like, I can tell I'm not wanted here.
Yeah.
But I don't want to leave.
Yeah, I'm not going to leave.
This is an opportunity to, this is going to be my breakout role, dude.
Yeah, but, but she was really attached to you.
And then you started drawing, what got you started drawing the avatars was that you just drew like a bunch of pictures
of like all your friends, I guess, right?
Yeah, yeah.
And it was just like these simple black and white like portraits of like, I guess everyone you knew
cause you drew one for both me and her.
Yes.
And I don't even remember drawing one of her.
I guess I did.
Yeah.
Cause we both started using them as our Skype avatars.
And then like, I liked it as cause this was in the period where I was starting to get away from Pony
and, you know, wanted to move into anime and I was like, it'd be cooler if I just had an avatar that's just me, you know,
and you had drawn one of the only pictures of just me.
So, and I liked it.
So I made that my YouTube avatar and it was that for like that, that particular drawing for a long time.
Yeah.
And actually I just got so fucking sick of it.
I just could not stand to even look at it because I would have you on Skype,
but I would occasionally just talk to you and then I would just see that fucking smug ass.
I hate it.
I loved how smug it was.
But yeah.
It was funny.
No, go on.
Yeah.
Cause you, you're an artist and you've been improving overall this time and your art style has been changing.
So like every six months or so, you'll look at my avatar and go, I can't look at it anymore.
I'm too good at drawing now.
I can't have that be your avatar, you know.
I gotta say the one you have now is easily my best work in a while.
I'm very proud.
Yeah.
I definitely like it a lot.
And now it's got a whole metal fucking faceplate.
Yeah, I know.
That's so awesome.
Shout outs to whoever did that.
I don't remember your name and I don't care.
It was another JoJo avatar guy.
Yeah.
Yeah, I saw.
He's my Josuke dude.
I'm his fucking slave master.
He's a dungeon master, dude.
Before we, we move on to anything else.
There was another art project besides avatars that I was with you creating.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
So you can start this off.
Towards the end of 2013.
Cause again, we, we had started talking and you just like, cause the thing is back and still to this day, I never asked people for art.
Like I never come to people and I'm like, Hey, draw something for me.
Like all the avatars you've made, it's always been you telling me I drew you a new avatar.
Replace the old one.
It's never been me coming to you going like, Hey, let's update it to look like, you know, current me or whatever.
But, um, yeah, I've never been one to ask for art with the exception of like the header that cotton candy drew where like, I think I actually asked her to draw that cause I liked her before I was just using a random picture.
She drew of me.
But, um, so you would contact me and be like, Hey man, I want to draw this or that.
And the project that we worked on was discorded Digi Brony.
So I had this, I had this weird character arc thing where this is going to be hard to explain cause our audience doesn't know my little pony for this show.
Oh, they don't?
No, this PCP audience mostly is, yeah, it's mostly not pony fans.
So, um,
Ah, it's fucking disgusting.
In my little pony, there's an episode where this character called discord shows up and he like, change, he basically inverts all the characters personalities so that they'll act like the option.
They all turn gray and they all start acting like assholes.
And I made a video about that episode where I Digi Brony gets discorded and he turns gray and he becomes an asshole who hates analysis.
And then, uh, I decided cause in the my little pony community, there's this huge, huge culture of ask blogs on tumblr where people would have like an original character and they'd have a tumblr for it and people would ask them questions and they'd answer it with art.
So it'd be like, you know, like, what's your favorite sandwich to a rainbow dash tumblr?
And it'd be like, they draw a picture of rainbow dash eating some kind of sandwich and that would be the answer.
You should have a ton of those, by the way, but I'm not gonna even know.
Yeah, I do remember you having more than one, but like, yeah, ask blogs were such a big deal and it always looked like fun and like, I have no artistic ability at all, but I thought it would be fun to have one.
Panels you drew, man. Holy shit.
So I would just take my discorded Digi Brony avatar and I would just put him in a panel and just, I would just hand write the text next to him.
Like in this really scratchy, like, angry looking text.
Fairly, it's fucking readable sometimes.
Yeah, and so it was just this weird spinoff of this one video and like, I don't think even a lot of people knew about it.
It was just kind of like a hidden thing that I was doing and I think I did three or four comics and then you were like, hey, your art is fucking garbage.
Yeah.
Why don't you let me take over discorded Digi Brony and I had already like lost interest in doing it myself.
So I was like, okay.
And your art was great for it, but I had like this whole narrative I'd already concocted that I wanted it to go through.
And I think you probably drew like 10 updates or so before you were like, this is stupid.
And yeah, either one of us cared anymore.
And then I was just like, I just messaged you and I said, I was in the middle of an update and I was just like, I hate this.
And you're like, you know, you don't have to do it.
And I was like, oh yeah.
And then I just drew a picture of you like, like Digi Brony getting fucking stabbed.
And then that was the end.
It was great.
Yeah, it was truly a radical adventure, a funky adventure if you will.
So did you meet the other PCP guys just through BronyCon?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
You know how in the last interview we were saying that Davoo is the Ascended Fan?
It's me, you are wrong.
It was me.
Well, Davoo's actually in the PCP, although I will say Munchy.
I don't know if I'm supposed to tell you this.
What the fuck is this conspiracy shit?
We have been talking about that we would put you in the PCP under the condition that you became a professional artist.
Because we've kind of agreed that the one, like the one glue that holds the PCP together is that all of us work in...
Professionally.
Like professionally in art and we can talk about that aspect a lot, you know.
Because a lot of what we do in the PCP chat is just complain about our jobs and things like that.
I want to touch on this later, but I will say that I am constructing additional pylons.
I heard as much.
Ben made it out like he was going to invite you in as soon as you launched whatever your big project was or something like that.
I guess he knows about it for some reason.
I'll say this.
It's about an alligator.
And that's all you're going to hear.
Okay.
Alright.
What were we fucking talking about?
You being an ascended fanboy.
Yes.
Okay.
I met Jesse.
I don't think independently of you, but it wasn't like you.
You didn't talk about him.
It was you just liked a video of his.
That's what I thought about you and Jesse.
It was just through liked videos.
I would always search those.
Let's see.
I want our audience to understand this.
I have always had a very strong policy to hit like on any videos I like because that's also how I found out about a lot of stuff in the early days when I wasn't subbed to a lot of channels.
Because I would see like Egoraptor liked this video and I'd go find a channel that way.
And I don't think people like everyone always says like likes are really helpful and they never say why.
That's why because if you're if you're on the like main page of YouTube, it shows the liked videos of people you subscribe to and it can be a really big help.
Yeah, it's awesome.
So the first exposure to Jesse I had was fuck cars.
And that's a great one.
I this idea of revolutionized the way I fucking perceived reality.
The idea that somebody gets so mad at an issue that I didn't even consider any of my fucking like I just didn't even think about it.
They think that someone could get so riled up and peeved.
It got my blood pumping.
It made me appreciate like rage is an art form.
Yeah, I always said that Jesse is the Lord of rage.
If he was a homestuck character, he's the fucking defender, dude.
He is he's all out and that's what I love about him.
I think it's amusing how I do think Jesse would make an amazing homestuck character.
Yeah, in spite or perhaps because of the fact that he hates homestuck, he would make an amazing homestuck character.
Yeah.
I don't know if his name is the right length of characters.
Six characters for the first name and four characters for the last name.
So it's like a reversal of the of the main characters.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
Well, whatever.
I found out Jesse, uh, Jesse through that.
And I thought he was the fucking like because he had like, like two subscribers.
I mean, I'm only five characters.
Whatever.
Stop.
Anyway, he had like no subscribers.
And I thought, who is this fucking underground like cave hermit?
Like fucking hermaphrodite just just dwelling in the fucking shadows.
The shadows of reality is between the cracks of space and time.
He's fucking in between worlds.
And I just have like, I have a fucking taste.
I have like a little nib, I have a little sip of his true power.
And just one day he will show it to me in all of its glory.
I will be walking down the street late from fucking like, like I'm out late.
I'm coming home from work and I will see someone fucking out of the corner of my eye.
I'll turn and there'll be Jesse and he'll just fucking flash me.
But instead of a wiener, it'll be fucking knowledge.
Uh, that's how I thought about Jesse.
Yeah, so how'd you get into contact with him though?
Uh, I, when he, like the first fucking millisecond, he started drying horseshoes.
I thought, finally, I can't draw humans very well, but I can sure draw the little horseshoes.
Oh yeah, you drew his fucking, you drew his pony.
And he never credited me.
I remember that because he said, um, because he, he had the drowning in horseshoes thing and you drew it and he put it in the, uh, the intro or whatever.
And then he, you also drew the one where it was me and him as the critics from the Muppets.
And yeah, and me and him, I remember him being like, oh, some, some guy, Munchie drew this and like, I saw it and immediately recognized the art style.
I was like, oh, hey, I know who that is.
And I think I probably explained who you were to him at the time.
Oh, I wish I could have seen your fucking description.
He's this, uh, serial killer.
Don't worry about it.
Well, like, I mean, as soon as I learned how young you were, then it was like, from then, because it was weird, because it's such a reversal, right?
Because if you had been a 23 year old guy who was doing the things you were doing, then it seems insane.
But knowing that it was a 13 year old, suddenly I was convinced you were a genius.
Because like, because I don't know any other people who have that understanding of irony at that age.
You know, like, um, yeah, you grew up on Homestuck to some extent, right?
Like, how old were you when you started it?
Um, I think Act 4 had just ended, so...
Okay, it's around the same time I got into it.
But yeah, I think, like, because there's a lot of kids who are into Homestuck, and I don't think most of them get it.
Oh, I think, like, one percent of them fucking get it.
I think one percent of the adults get it.
Yeah, I think only I get it, actually.
That's a very jessie scene right there.
But, uh, yeah, like, because I read it all, and I was like...
Cause I had never heard of it before I read it, and when I read it, I was like,
this is like the most intellectual thing I've ever fucking read.
And then I found out how big it was, and how big it was with kids, and I was like, there's no way.
Like, there's too much to this, there's no way.
But then, when I met you, and you were a big Homestuck fan, and you attributed it,
and I was like, I feel like, even at his age, he gets the idea of Homestuck.
Like, I felt like you got it, even as a kid.
And, uh, and like, you had that same sense of humor that Dave Strider had, or that, uh, that Dirk had later, you know?
Yes.
I very much look up to Dirk in pretty much every way, except for the gay way, but I still look up to him that way, too.
Uh, the part where he explains that when you enjoy something on so many different levels of irony,
then it just doesn't matter anymore, and it's just like, that's one of my favorite parts of the whole thing.
Yeah, I did, too.
I was like, yeah, you can just like whatever.
Like, it's not about, like, at some, at some level, like, with Garzy's wing, for me,
it's like, it's not really ironic enjoyment, because like, I like it because it's bad, but that doesn't mean I'm like...
You're leaving today?
Why do you have to go back to your hometown now?
You failed the college entrance exam twice now.
God damn it.
It doesn't matter.
I will return later, Rumi Ko.
Bye.
You are so easygoing.
That's my favorite fucking line for how angry she sounds.
You're so easygoing.
You are so easygoing.
Oh, that's fucking shit, dude.
There's parts later where she's like happy, and she's still screaming like...
Like, that's just her natural voice.
God damn it, dude.
Yeah, man, irony is my fucking bread and butter, and I'm not good at it, but damn it, one day I will be.
So we all met you at, at a...
So did you know, like, how early did you become acquainted with like, Nate and Ben and Hippo?
Cause I guess you probably followed all of us, right?
Yes, yeah, I followed all of you, Sans Hippo.
I didn't, I didn't, I met him, I really met him at Bronicon, but I found out about Ben and Nate.
Like, as soon as they're, like, as soon as the video started becoming, like, watchable.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, so, I found out about them then, and then I was like, oh, these people are all that I like,
and I like, I like the one that's the B the most.
I like that man the most.
And that's when I started jacking off to Ben every single night, and continued to this day.
Then I, I didn't watch Hippo, I never, I never knew who this man was, but I knew he had a very soothing voice,
and if I, I touched him, I would probably bruise him.
If I just laid a hand on him.
He's very small.
Yes.
I don't know if our audience is aware that Hippo is like five foot one, and probably like less than 90 pounds.
He is a very, very small man.
I could use him as a toothpick, or as a, as a thing that I used to clean my ears.
Well, by, by Bronicon 2014, you had grown massive.
Because I, like I said, you were about my height before, but by the next year you were like six,
what, how tall are you?
I don't want to jump the gun because I haven't officially measured it, but I'm fairly certain that I'm six three.
Okay, so you are quite tall.
Yeah.
And you're currently what, 16 turning?
I'm turning 16 in three months, yeah.
Which is less ridiculous that you're that tall at that age, but you were that tall at 14.
And you were there at, at Bronicon, and like every single person who I introduced you to,
because you were walking, that was the year where you had the pizza suit, right?
Yes.
Yes, it was.
It was a full body like jumper that was all just pizza.
By fucking my, my, my years are fucking bleeding together.
There were, I think the latest Bronicon is the one where I had the pizza.
I don't know.
Last year, like the first year was.
Well, there was three different years that we were at Bronicon.
The first one, they weren't there though.
It was just me.
Yeah.
So, and then the second one, I like met everyone and I was just wearing some like stupid fucking spike cosplay or something because I thought it was funny.
Okay.
And then the second one, the third one, I mean, was really where I think I dazzled and I pressed.
Impressed.
And everywhere, because everywhere we would go, because here's the thing.
You're talking very calmly and quietly right now.
I'm sure someone's asleep in your house.
This is not the munchie I know.
The munchie I know walks into the room like, hey everybody, let's fuck everything up.
Like the munchie I know would yell obscenities at small children.
And the thing is that, because it's Bronicon, right?
Half the people there are autistic and no one can tell the difference.
And we'd all be sitting around with some people that I barely know or have just met and munchie would come over and start like just acting like an insane person.
And the reason I would always tell people how young you were is just for reassurance.
Because you look like you look like some crazy 20 year old guy who's coming over and yelling about anal sex.
And everyone's like, there'd always be someone looking at you like, I am scared.
And then I would go, I would go, how old do you think that guy is?
And they'd be like, I don't know, like 22 or something.
Yeah.
And I was like, he's 14.
And they'd be like, oh, but it changes the way people look at it because they'll feel bad if they're like, if you're, they just think you're a crazy kid.
No.
Like, oh, he's just some weird kid as opposed to a scary man.
To a threat to everyone.
I would constantly, everyone we hung out around, I would explain to them how old you were just for that reason.
It doesn't help that nowadays I talk about school shootings and being like a the Zodiac killer.
Have you gotten into the YouTuber, Monkey Jones yet?
No, I haven't.
I really appreciate his stuff.
He's an anime reviewer, although most of his anime reviews are not actually about anime, who screams constantly and has done a whole audio book on Elliott Rogers autobiography.
Definitely think you'd appreciate it.
I'll link you his video that went viral that me and Jesse found him through.
It's great.
But I love him.
Anyway, sounds great.
Yeah.
You hung out with us at BronyCon and we did this drawing thing.
Yes.
You want to explain that?
How it worked?
Ben pioneered it and he would basically cut up, not cut up, but like draw a line through a piece of paper and there would be four panels.
The first person would draw the first panel, then he would pass it on to the second person and they would draw the second panel.
And basically they had to make a story like fucking like hot potato style.
Right.
The first year's crops were like painstakingly reimagined and re-digitalized on the computer by Ben himself and posting on the TPC, not the TCP, the fucking whatever that stupid show was that I don't care about that I love.
Oh, now we've got to put them on the TPC subreddit so that people can see it when we post the story.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck yeah.
What's his name?
Steve, you've got to find that shit dude.
I swear.
Your ass is going to be fucking butter and I'm going to be eating toast.
You can't have toast with butter.
So to clarify though, the way it worked is that you had to draw the panel in like five minutes, right?
Yes.
It's like on a timer and then you could, but you could start with whichever one you wanted.
Like each person got whatever, like if you wanted to draw panel three first, then you could do that and then the other people had to imagine the story up to or from that point.
I don't know if it was that we were on a, I don't think we were on a timer.
It was just fucking impatient.
Well, the second year we definitely had an actual timer, but yeah.
So the first year it was like you and Ben, I don't even know how you, like how did it get, how did that get organized?
Like you just sat next to him and he started doing it or what?
Like did he even know you were an artist?
Oh yeah, yeah.
The first time I ever met Ben and I just walked over and I said, hey, I'm Munchie and then he like, like looks over you very nonchalantly.
Just like looks like just fucking peeks a second.
Then looks back to me and then he just says, I've heard a lot of things about you, Munchie.
I guess I must have told him about you.
To say I just wonder like what fucking lies have you been feeding him?
Because of all the reasons that we've talked about, I've always considered you one of my most interesting fans.
So like when people ask me about like, you know, what is it like to have fans or what are some of your fan experiences?
Like you are one of the, because it's a positive story overall, you know, like it's that unique mixture of funny but not creepy.
Like if I talked about some other people that may have been named earlier, you know, that didn't go so well.
But like, yeah, it makes for, I've probably told a lot of people about the 13 year old who looks like a man and draws really well and eventually did all my avatars, you know.
Yeah.
That's how I met Ben. And we were at the who's line is it anyway.
And me and Ben thought this was the worst thing that's ever happened to anyone ever.
And so we decided, yeah, we need to either kill ourselves or entertain ourselves.
And we chose the latter thankfully.
Ben had the news and I had the knives, but we were just an inch away.
And then his date or whatever said, how about we not kill ourselves in front of all these public people?
And I said, well, you know, being a martyr is fun too.
And then I died. But anyway, the way this is the date we were talking about in Ben's interview.
By the way, the well-laid.
Anyway, we started fucking drawing and basically who by the way, she left a comment on that.
Did you see that?
I have to see it now.
She left a comment on a Ben's podcast saying I was the one who slept with Ben at Bronicon.
I wonder what it was like after PM for the Deeds.
But the three of you and I guess a fourth person did the start of it.
There wasn't a fourth person. It was just someone who did it two times.
Jesus.
And then I caught on to this at some point.
Like you guys were doing it in a space that I happen to be.
And then you're like, let me try.
And me and Ben look at each other and we're like, hmm, okay.
I know you can't draw at all.
You're just going to make our pedals look shitty.
But then Ben is actually really fascinated with my drawing.
Like he likes my shitty ass artwork because it's so out there and distinct.
Believe me, I'm a fan. I just think it's terrible.
Yeah. I mean, I feel the same way about my own art.
Yeah. I'm a definite fan. Don't get me wrong.
You should draw your own avatar from now on and see how many clicks that gets you, bitch.
So I guess as a result of that, Ben has just kind of walked over.
I guess as a, because of that incident of us all hanging out at Bronecon,
you guys drawing together, Ben has always loved you since then.
He thinks you're super cool, which I do too.
I think anyone who can draw really well in like a style I like is automatically cool.
Well, unless they're a total douchebag.
Yeah. I'm trying to think.
I can't find any douchebags in my database, but I know what you're saying.
I enjoy how, because you are definitely someone who your sense of humor doesn't necessarily mesh with everybody's.
But Ben seems to appreciate all of it.
Like when you guys did the Nuclear Throne podcast, it was so funny to me when I got to listen to it,
because you would say something weird and DeVu would clearly not know how to respond and just be like,
okay, and Ben would like lose his shit.
He was so down for every weird thing you said.
And Hippo loves it. He said of you after meeting you at the second Bronecon,
he said, Munchie says all the things I am thinking.
Like every time we're in a situation, like whatever pops into my head,
the crazy thing I don't do, Munchie does.
And he said it was gratifying to him, because it would always be that way.
I'm so glad.
Yeah, but you flew off the handle that year.
The second year was like, you know, I'm going to be like a human.
I'm going to make sure that I make a good first impression.
Second year was, it's time to accelerate space and time.
I need to bend it to my will.
And my vocal chords after that weekend, oh boy.
I remember at that Bronecon, I have no fucking clue what sparked it,
but I went up to Dr. Wolf and I saw this video on my phone.
I want to send it to Jesse one day.
I've sent it to him before, but I think you fully appreciate it.
I went up to Dr. Wolf and I said, did you kill Dr. Indian horseshoes?
And he just looked at me for like fucking 10 seconds and he said,
I have never met Dr. Indian horseshoes and I don't know anything about Dr. Indian horseshoes.
Which is a blatant lie, but we have an answer.
So he officially did not kill Dr. Indian horseshoes.
It was the media that killed Dr. Indian horseshoes.
It's the color yellow that killed Dr. Indian horseshoes.
And you're actually on Jesse's side in that debate, yeah?
You're with him on the yellow.
We're not going to get too into that.
No, no, no, we're getting fucking into that shit.
Every day, every single day of my life, I have people coming up to me and they say,
you can't possibly think it's like clear, right?
And I just say to them, you need to go back to elementary,
but you're not going to be able to go back to elementary because your face is going to be so fucking disfigured from what I'm about to do to you.
You're not even going to be able to show your face in a circus, dude.
You are going to be.
What do you mean by clear? What are they saying is clear?
No, they're saying it's fucking yellow and they're like, oh, you can't, you can't say it's not yellow.
It's clearly yellow.
And then I'm just, I want to murder.
I'm going to take out my Zodiac killings, my murder weapons for all the Zodiac killings I did and I use them.
They're full extent.
Well, that podcast will come out next weekend.
Oh, did you do an actual whole podcast on that?
Well, it's the thing is it was we got into a huge fight about it right before the procrastinators recording last weekend.
And this has happened a few times where we all get into a fight about something right before the show.
And then if Jesse is involved, he will keep the argument going once the show starts.
So the the topic of it was things you can't get into.
We recorded three and a half hours and about an hour of it is arguing over yellow.
It is a you're going to love it.
It's going to be your favorite podcast ever.
Total cluster fuck.
It is madness.
And then the argument ever since then, like after that podcast, Jesse was so mad that he hasn't even been in the chat like all week.
He left and he went on Twitter and he started going on this whole thing about yellow.
So like all that was after we'd already been arguing about it for a whole day.
He went on Twitter and him and Ben started arguing on there.
And I'm just like, guys, please, I don't I don't even care about reality or facts as much as I care about not hearing about yellow.
And then I made that political cartoon about Ben being colorblind and he was a homeless man who wore a patron shirt.
And and Jess was a fucking blonde haired blue-eyed fucking God that just had the words endless tattooed on him.
Yeah.
So he still hasn't been back in the chat since but that podcast will come out next week after a few days after this podcast releases this interview.
But yeah, at least it's nice that someone is unequivocally in Jesse's camp.
Yeah.
Is no one else?
Um, I am philosophically but not.
You'll understand when you hear the podcast.
It is a it is a riot.
A literal riot.
Things get destroyed.
Fucking samurai is going to take all this fucking appliances to Andre now.
It's going to need to smell.
Yeah.
Tell me some things about yourself.
You live on the West Coast.
Yeah.
Oh, West Coast for fucking life.
Maybe I live in the most Southwest city on the United States of America, continental.
I kind of know why Hawaii is a piece of shit.
I hate it.
I live in San Diego, but I'm actually San Diego.
I live in another city.
It's more Southwest.
You're not even going to know the city, so I'm not even going to say it.
I live in San Diego, basically.
Victor was born in San Diego.
No way.
Yeah.
That proves that he's my real brother and you're just a fucking faker piece of shit.
Well, I was born in Oakland.
We were both born in California, but.
That's good.
California is the where you need to fucking come, baby.
It's the fucking good life here.
Yeah.
It's my dad's from California.
So we were out there when we were first born and then we moved across the country.
But you're the only, because the rest of the, all the PCP guys are all like either East
Coast or like close to it.
I know they're all pieces of fucking shit, dude.
I swear.
Devoos in Missouri, but.
Oh, that explains so much.
Jesse's in Michigan.
But the rest of us are on the East Coast and well, except Jeff.
Now we have Jeff who's in like what Vancouver or something.
He's somewhere in Canada.
He's a Canada.
Subway.
So he might be, yeah, he's closer to you on the West Coast, but yeah, you're a, you're
a good old California boy.
Yes.
I would rather fucking die than set foot in another state.
Except that you went to Brony con twice.
Well, don't worry about that.
It was Baltimore.
It's basically a fucking ghetto.
Are you planning to go this year?
Are you?
Of course not.
You people aren't going.
Yeah.
By the way, Nate needs to get fucking on.
We're trying to push for a new con, but he's fucking on his ass not doing anything.
Well, we're all going to go to my house this September.
Oh, great.
We're having a conference.
They're inviting me a piece of shit.
Yeah.
It's not a convention, but a conference.
Oh, great.
Yeah.
So it's.
Fucking relive the group poop and get Jesse to draw like a picture of me and just make
him do the munchie voice wherever he goes.
I bet he'd do that.
He seems to really appreciate you as well.
I'm so glad.
He did that whole video about you.
Yeah.
Just like every line you said in the memes that need to type on.
All the times I laughed, which you should make another one of this video.
Is that what it was?
Was it times you laughed?
I thought it was just like every single thing you said.
Yeah.
It was everything I said, but including all the laughs.
So he just wouldn't.
He would just put every single laugh without the context of why I was laughing.
Just to do.
Yeah.
Everyone, everyone fucking says that Munchie's laugh is great.
I don't know what's understood.
I don't fucking understand it.
It's just laugh.
You both have pretty good laughs.
This has been a good laugh podcast.
It has been a good laugh podcast.
I will agree.
If anybody's into laughs like in a weird way, this is a good.
A lot of LOL is in this.
All right.
Tell me some stuff about you, Munchie.
I don't know really where to ask because I don't know much of your life story.
Yes.
What are some interesting facts?
Interesting facts.
I was fucking, I was born and then a lot of stupid fucking shit that didn't matter until
I got on the internet.
Now I'm on the internet.
I started out as a Pokemon mystery dungeon role player.
This is where I connect to DeVoo through space and time.
Space and time because Pokemon Mystery Dungeons travelers or explorers of space and time also
joke because space and time is a real thing.
Yes.
Anyway, I would do that.
And that's where I got the name Munchie is because I, oh, Munchlax.
He's fat and short.
And I was fat and short.
And one point before I became tall and fat.
And I was like.
It just so happens that me and you are both huge Munchlax fans.
I was so excited when you found out or when I found out that you like Munchlax.
I thought he was so underrated.
Yeah, I agree.
I've always, he's been my favorite Pokemon ever since Destiny Deoxys, the movie.
Yes, yes.
That's the same movie because he would just fucking do nothing and then he evolved Munchlax
just by fucking just to survive.
There's a part where he like, like he's like, he's always lazy and walking around.
Then there's a part where he like leaps 30 feet in the air just to get over somebody
and then like keeps going and then just eats everything and he's such an asshole.
And I was like, this thing is so fucking adorable.
I know.
We're also both really big Kirby fans.
Yes, yes.
Because I am innately attracted to anything that eats a lot.
Not attracted sexually, but.
Oh, well, that's the difference between you and me though.
Right.
Well, anything that eats a lot I love because I love eating.
I'm a huge foodie as I always say.
Most people do.
You'd be surprised.
Shade doesn't enjoy eating.
Shade is a crazy person.
Shade is a weirdo.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's another another funny thing about me hanging out with you is that like, um,
I know a lot about your family life and I'm with your brothers.
It's it's funny because of the fact that I I am the type of person who doesn't spend
a lot of time with other people online.
I think that like you and shade are part of a generation that does that and I'm not like
it to the same extent like I talked to the PCP guys, but it's in a chat.
We only ever do calls if it's for the podcast.
We don't do things together.
We don't like play video games or anything like we talk when we have something to talk
about and we just kind of pop in and out and say shit and it's it's very much like a
like everything is either a conversation or it's business and there's little in
between, you know, we don't schedule things.
Whereas like I know shade and probably this is true for you too.
Spends a lot of time on Skype with his friends.
He gets into lots of calls.
He plays video games with his friends.
Yes, I've never done any of that.
Like when I was growing up, you had local multiplayer where you sat with your friends
next to you and you all played together and I love that me and my friends play fighting
games and shit, but like I don't play online games at all.
And I hate being called.
You're a busy guy.
Well, but what's funny about that is that I've known you for a long time.
But because I'm not the type of person to do that kind of stuff, me and you don't spend
a lot of time together.
Whereas shade who does that kind of stuff all the time, it's totally normal for him
to get into a call with someone and play video games or something, you know, so or Victor
even when he's not busy will sometimes play games and stuff.
I've been playing fucking smash together and it has been orgasmic.
I beat the fucking shit up Brandon Tolentino.
I made fun of them both.
It's the best thing that's ever happened.
Yeah, I wanted to ask about that.
Are you like really good at smash?
Like how good are you?
No, Brandon shit at smash four.
Oh, that's true.
He is shit at four.
But I mean, are you do you consider yourself pretty good at four?
Because you were talking on Twitter about wanting to have like a Mewtwo for your pocket
and stuff.
You were using kind of technical fighting game terms for your Mewtwo.
I do.
Yeah, I do.
You know, I do know about the competitive scene.
I don't think I have the I don't have the fucking processing power.
Smash is very CPU intensive on my body.
And it's hard for me to do the inputs, but I'm aware of shit that happens.
I know shit fuck.
I just I find it very amusing that like, you know who Victor and Tolentino are because
they do Digi Bros with me.
Yes, which I fucking love, by the way.
Yeah, and they probably have interacted with you.
Well, maybe not Tolentino, but like, no, no, he has more than me is what I meant to say.
Oh, yeah.
Just because and this is probably true for a number of people who watch shows like that
because it's just funny because with something like Digi Bros.
The people involved don't think of it as their show like Victor Victor now does like over time
he's come to think of it as like our show.
But like when I get my friends on there, none of them care that much about it.
Like they have no real interest in the show itself.
They just it's something to do, you know, and then like when it comes out, it's like, oh, yeah, it's out now.
But then they're all way more receptive to like accepting every friend request they get on Instagram.
Because they're not famous people who are getting that all the time, you know, like for me,
if I give out like my Snapchat or something, I'll have a hundred fucking thousand Snapchat friends
sending me pictures of their dick and shit, you know, whereas like for smaller people,
that's another thing that you might appreciate about that monkey Jones guy is that he's very audience interaction.
Like he gives out a Snapchat freely.
He responds to lots of comments and stuff.
So which I love, I love that he does that, but I can't see myself doing it because I know it would at the level of popularity
I have, it would take up too much of my time to constantly interact with fans.
And I would eventually get weirdos who I don't like who the biggest problem for me is when you have someone who
like doesn't understand that I have lots of people vying for my attention and you have none.
Yes.
Those those people.
I felt that ever since I was in the means that need to die.
Yeah.
I fucking amassed a cult following and I hate them all.
There's like a weird it's like because when when someone doesn't have a lot of friends, then and you talk to them,
then it's like they want a lot of your attention and you can't give a lot of your attention.
You know, and I always get like one or two people like that where it'll be someone who, you know, it's like they're they're
not they're not a bad person.
It's not that I don't like talking to them, but then they'll message me all the time and I'm like, dude, I've got a lot of stuff to do
and I've got a lot of people who want my attention and I know you don't get it because I'm your only friend,
but I can't be your only friend.
I don't have time, you know, that's why you're talking about how this is like, like I can't relate to this,
but I've literally only related to this because of fucking you people.
You people have like got me on the podcast.
Have you really gotten people that like that?
Yes.
They're probably listening, by the way.
I know they're all listening.
I hate every one of you.
I don't remember any of your names and I don't like you.
All right.
You gotta you're the you are our eyes on the inside.
Yes.
I've been waiting for this the chance to talk to you about this.
Let me see what they're up to right now.
What what the fuck is the PCP fan club?
We need to know.
The PCP fan club is a chat that has the name the PCP fan club and is really just a bunch of fucking dweebs and losers who don't
understand the PCP nor its artistic integrity and just think it's another run of the mill podcast.
And they don't fully understand how amazing and fucking incredible it is.
And they are just a bunch of fucking normies and retards and I hate them all.
They're none of them are cool.
And there I wish I hadn't joined.
I only joined because I thought, oh, they're going to fucking talk about how great I am.
Which is true.
And I whenever here, I'm gonna press one, one, one and chat right now.
And I can't fucking to you in five seconds.
Someone else is going to say one, one, one, one, one, one, one.
I'll talk back in a second.
But anyway, they're fucking all scum and I hate them.
So do they actually talk about the PCP there?
No.
Okay, I didn't think so.
Like, like, like, if someone put out a video and someone puts it, it will be like, cool.
Daveau is a guy.
And then they'll be like, hey, want to be my boyfriend?
Here's a dating channel I made.
That's always how it is.
Like, I, I hate, I hate fandoms.
I've come to hate fandoms.
Because people don't use fandoms to engage with the work.
They use it to engage with each other.
And the work becomes just the, the means to facilitate it.
Yes.
You know, we're like, I mean, most of the best pony art back when we were in the pony days,
like a lot of the best art was from people who didn't interact at all.
You know, like, like music wise, I think everyone respected so great and powerful, right?
Dude had no internet presence.
He would never talk to anybody.
He would delete his own fucking.
Do you remember his fucking Tumblr dude?
That Tumblr was nothing.
It was literally nothing.
And then he just erased himself from the internet and disappeared.
But like, he, because to him, it wasn't about the social aspect.
He just wanted to make music.
And then he hated all of it and got rid of it all.
He was definitely a weirdo, but like, nonetheless, he wasn't, he wasn't in it for like, there
was so many of the pony musicians who really just were in it because they made friends
that way and they kept making that content because they had friends there that they didn't
want to lose or an audience they didn't want to lose.
And they make a lot of money at conventions.
Really, most of the fucking pony shit was bad and I only made the good art.
And I fucking blessed the world when I sent out my fucking ask blog about Fuller Shy,
who was a pervert and hang out in bathrooms and constantly hit on everyone that went there.
Yeah.
I, I hate, I think I really hate, I hate forums.
I hate like fan clubs that are like chats and stuff.
Not that I hate the people who are in the R fan club.
Like you guys are fine.
Oh, I do.
I do.
But well, you've been there.
I hate them.
You have reason.
But like, I hate the concept of it.
What I like is like reddits where it's like everything on there is relevant content and
the discussion is about the content.
It's not like, if you go on Tumblr or I mean on Reddit and you go into some thread and
you're like having a conversation with your buddy in the thread, then that thread gets
deleted.
You know, it's not relevant.
So I do like that.
I do like that.
Yeah.
That's why I think those things are cool or like 4chan where no one even has an identity.
Yes.
That's, I mean, I'll talk about how much I hate 4chan and I really fucking hate 4chan.
But you hate 4chan from experience.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, I go on 4chan every single day of my life.
Yeah.
I just hate it.
Talk about 4chan.
Tell us about it.
All right.
I got interested in 4chan for the MLP board as I'm sure a couple of people did.
I don't know if you were into 4chan at all.
I was into it way before that.
I've been on 4chan since the mid-2000s.
Oh, okay.
Well, perfect.
Anyway, I got through that and I thought, these people are funny.
And then a second, like a week would by, I thought, oh, these people are the same every
day.
Oh.
And then I eventually just branch out to other, like, oh, video games.
I like video games.
This board isn't about video games.
And then I just branch out through there.
And I go on there every day.
There's always a thread that will make me laugh every single day.
But most of the threads are things that make me want to die.
Yeah.
And that's the push and pull of fucking 4chan.
I always say that what makes 4chan work for me is that I don't read it because I go on,
I have my 4chan in catalog mode.
And I'll go on A and I'll look for it.
By the way, I told you about that.
I told you to put it in fucking catalog mode like a fucking year, like a year or two ago.
And you're like, no, I can't read.
I can't read the threads about.
The funny thing, yeah, I remember that.
And I didn't use it for a long time.
But then I got this thing.
It was some kind of 4chan like sweet, like mod sweet thing for Chrome where it changes all this stuff.
It made it more convenient.
And it automatically set it to catalog mode.
And it was like a pain in the ass to change it back.
And then I realized that catalog mode was way better.
Yes.
So I'll go through it.
I'll find a thread that looks interesting.
And I found that it's not just that the images are the best part of 4chan.
But when someone wants to write a post on there and they put an image next to it,
those are always the people who work the hardest on their writing.
Yes, exactly.
If you only read stuff that has an image next to it, you will read the real thread.
Just ignore all the other shit and just read the ones with images.
And you'll get the actual perception of what's happening.
Not that you'll agree with all of it, but it'll be a much better thread.
I've employed this myself.
Whenever I'm in the Homestuck threads on code because I want to kill myself,
I always, whatever I want to shitpost about how much I hate Homestuck,
Andrew Hussie, and Undertale, even though I love Undertale,
I will just have no image in the Lobby Lowercase.
But then, when I want to make an actual post about Homestuck,
I will use Dirk's fucking his writing style,
and I will put an image of Calibur next to it.
That's how you know it's me.
I see.
Does anybody recognize you that way?
No, of course not.
Say stuff about, I have to pee really bad.
I'm just going to mute myself and turn up my volume so I can hear in the bathroom,
and you can just keep talking.
No, yeah, here, I'll keep talking.
West Philadelphia is born and raised.
It's been most of my days.
Chillin' out, laxin' out, outside of school,
and a couple of guys were up no good and started making trouble in my neighborhood.
Got two little fights with my mom, got scared,
and said, you're moving with your uncle and got a fucking belly or something.
I do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
I'm Will Smith, and I'm going to go beat my kids.
I'm going to make them star moves they don't want to star in.
I'm going to make sure they are just like me,
and I'm Will Smith, and I hate everything.
When I beat my wife, I'm going to beat my kids.
I'm going to beat myself in the afterlife.
Every person I kill will become a slave in the afterlife,
and I'm going to be the king of the afterlife, baby.
My name is Will Smith, and I'm going to be the slave master.
I'm going to become the slave master in heaven.
That's going to be my name.
Slave master Will Will Smith.
My name is Will Smith, and I'm going to beat my wife.
Alright, now that that's over,
now that that devilish topping is over,
I was watching some documentaries about the zodiac killer earlier,
and you know how the guy, the zodiac killer,
killed these people, he tied them up next to a lake of some sort,
I don't remember what the lake was called,
and then he had this executioner outfit on?
That fucking police sketch of what he would look like
with the executioner outfit on.
It's so fucking cool, it's such a cool character design.
It looks like a fucking moral combat character,
or some sort of like, like doom character.
So I have a couple of images I have been drawing
of what the executioner like outfit.
Now you got to say, I really like the character design,
and I might use it in my upcoming project.
It has like a background character,
just an executioner background character.
Okay, I'm back.
Yeah, I talked about Will Smith beating his kids,
and I talked about the zodiac killer.
Yeah, I heard.
Okay, good.
You know, as I was listening to you do the,
the Fresh Prince opening,
the first thought that occurred to me is,
you weren't even alive yet when Fresh Prince was on TV.
And then the second thought that occurred to me was,
I calculated your age,
and I triangulated all the information,
and I looked at the triangles,
and I realized 666,
were you born the same year that fucking 9-11 happened?
No, no, I wasn't.
I was a year before.
It was my first birthday,
and everyone was talking about it.
Was it really, are you born on September 11th?
No, no, I was born on September 14th.
So it was, yes, it was very close.
But you did not cause 9-11 with your birth?
Well, maybe not in this life.
Maybe not in this life.
You know, you know how you can't really remember stuff
from when you were born?
Maybe I just hijacked the plane and I just can't remember it.
Yes, as a fucking baby.
As an infant, you hijacked the plane.
That's how no one saw me, it's because I was so small
they didn't look down at their feet.
I could just crawl away.
I've always wanted to ask this of someone your age,
like 9-11, does it have any effect on you whatsoever to think about?
It's literally a joke.
It's really funny.
It is funny, but for so much, I don't know why I made that sound like it's obvious.
Because I was like 10 when it happened, or I guess 9.
But wait, before we go into this,
I just want to say one day in middle school when it was 9-11,
and we were all outside, we were saluting the flag,
I used to stream Tappy Terrorist Day,
and no one knew who it was, and I got away with it.
That's awesome.
Yeah, continue?
Yeah, just like for everyone always says,
in all the analysis videos and stuff,
they're always like, oh, it defined our gender.
Have you ever watched any movie, Bob?
No, and from what you've made it sound like,
I think I would rather cover myself in gasoline than watch that man.
It's just funny because he always comes at things from this perspective
of the historical context, and he has this whole video about
Spider-Man and its connections to 9-11 and stuff,
which is accurate.
But it's funny to me to imagine someone your age watching that
and just feeling nothing about it.
Like having no history.
Yeah, I wasn't there.
I mean, I'm sure you learned about it in school and shit.
Yeah, of course.
9-11, that's when the Jews are burned by Hitler, right?
Yeah, that's what I was about to say.
To you, it means about as much as learning about World War II for me.
I'm like, yeah, whatever.
It's a thing that happened before I could even imagine.
Yeah.
Before I was just a sperm and my father's sacricle.
So you're like a true millennial, though.
You were born in the new millennium.
Yes, exactly.
I know this sounds like obvious stuff, but I make a point
not to talk to a lot of teenagers.
You are like the one exception.
The one teenager who I think is cool enough that I can talk to.
Believe me, my highest oaks for this interview was to be about age.
I think that's the most interesting thing about me when comparing myself with you.
I wasn't sure if you thought it was annoying to talk about all the time
because I feel like you just brought up a lot with you.
Mostly, the extent of it outside of you constantly talking about it
is we're not going to meet someone
and then my mom will usually be right next to me
because it's usually a psychiatrist and she'll ask.
She'll ask, how old is he again?
And then she'll just say, oh, he's 15.
And then I'll fucking, I'll bend down, I'll get down on the knees
and I'll be able to go, she'll be at my crotch level.
And then I'll say, yes.
And the thing is, I really do imagine you as this mighty warrior
because you are giant and you always talk about how you could crush people
and I completely believe it.
You could crush anyone.
I want to try to describe it because you're not just tall
but you're not, I don't see you as fat, I see you as just large
because you look strong.
I am formidable, yes.
You don't look like just a fat guy, you look like a big guy,
like a guy who could probably crush something.
Which is why we always keep, after last year's BronyCon
we were begging you to become a professional wrestler
because you have the personality for it perfectly.
And by begging you mean Jesse mentioned it one time.
I've brought it up all the time.
I'm always talking about how like,
we gotta come up with names for Munchie's wrestling career and stuff.
Oh, oh, oh, believe me, believe me, I want to,
I desperately need names.
I want my custom beat Captain Crunch themed.
So have you actually considered going into that as a job?
Well, see, the only thing is I don't know how we would get into that
but if I, like, if it was just a career option
then I would totally take it.
Like have you watched any wrestling or anything like that?
No, I just think it would be funny.
Yeah.
Well, because like, I mean, most of it is just yelling
and being insane and then throwing people.
That's most of your job.
And like, you would be a great like,
like 90s throwback crazy man wrestler.
Crazy man wrestler.
Because that's what a lot like, from what I've got gathered from Jesse,
the 90s was mostly people just being off the wall
because they were all on drugs and they would just go crazy.
My wrestler name would be Zodiac version 2.0.
Yeah, that would be acceptable in wrestling.
Like half of them are named after like serial killers or shit.
Oh God, I forgot we were talking.
Oh yeah, you want to talk about age.
I've come to realize I'm obsessed with age
because I've started noticing that if I watch my...
Do you watch any of my vlogs?
Like the Digibro After Dark shit?
Yeah, I watch all your content, you fucking retard.
And I hate all of it.
Stop.
Yeah, well I know you don't watch anime
so it's funny to me that you watch all my fucking anime vlogs.
By the way, have you seen my Mal by the way?
No, I have not.
I have watched including like, like movies,
like the two girl in the gun movies, including all those.
I have watched 10 anime before.
What are they?
They're fucking, they're, they're, they're
Popey the Clown, fucking girl in the gun movie.
Oh, you've actually seen Popey the Clown?
Holy shit.
I love that shit dude.
It's like the most obscure thing you could possibly have named.
I love it.
I'm not surprised you love it.
I'm just surprised you've heard of it.
I was introduced to it by a friend who watches this.
Hi.
Because I only know one, I haven't seen Popey the Clown
but there's a friend of mine named,
there's a friend of mine called Shin Maru
who's like obsessed with it.
Like he found it like a few years back,
like, like no one had heard of it and he found it
and he was like, what is this masterpiece?
And made it his avatar.
Popey the Clown.
That's what the intro is.
I see.
Yeah, I'm impressed you've seen that
but what are the other 10?
Here, here, it's, it's just all fucking,
it's Ava just fucking newbie shit.
It's a...
Ava's not that.
I mean, I guess it's, I guess it's newbie shit
and that most people know about it,
but it is great, you know.
If I think newbie shit, I think Naruto, you know.
I have never seen a fucking episode of Naruto.
Yeah.
I mean, you're kind of too young to have seen Naruto.
It's kind of before your time, like it's mid-2000s.
Yeah.
I grew up with Pokemon.
Surprisingly, I watched the original Pokemon too.
Interesting.
Yeah, I didn't watch like Sinnoh or something.
Right.
Well, like if you had gotten into anime at your age,
the most likely intro level would be like fairy tale,
would have been you.
Like, that's the kind, like that's the big shounen
that's from your generation of 12 year olds
would have been fairy tale or like,
if you're a super lucky hunter-hunter,
like the newer edition.
But yeah, like, pretty much just fairy tale,
most likely intro level show.
I don't know if you have friends who watch that.
The first season of JoJo, JoJo, Stardust Crusaders,
Killa Kill, Ava, Indoveva, Penny and Stocking,
Popey the Performer, Gurren Lagann,
then the two Gurren Lagann movies.
That's it.
So, what do you get out of my videos?
It's just fun to watch me talk.
I like the character of Digi Bro,
he's not a character.
Yeah, he's not a character.
It's just a heightened read.
I mean, when I'm not on camera,
I'm on the internet not talking, you know.
But like, when I talk to other people,
I don't think the character is any different
than the on-camera character,
so I wouldn't say it's like an act at all.
And you mostly talk about like, what makes a show good?
Yeah.
Which I really am surprised people think your channel is negative.
That's another thing.
Go ahead and get into it,
because I'd love to hear someone rip on the people who think I'm negative.
Well, here, I'll do that in a second.
You mostly talk about what makes a show good, I think?
Yeah!
That is what made the show good.
Now I don't have to watch it,
because now I know all that's good about it.
Yeah.
I understand that because I watch way more analysis videos
than I do shows, or...
For me, it's video games mostly,
because like, with anime,
Well, with anime, I know all the shows,
so no one can tell me stuff I haven't figured out
unless the rare case someone covers a show I haven't watched.
But like, when it comes to video games,
I barely play them,
but I watch hours and hours of analysis every week,
because there's so many fucking game channels.
And so I know everything about all the games that are coming out,
even though I don't play any of them.
So like, if we wanted to have...
We could probably right now have a whole conversation
about any new game that's out,
and I would have not played it,
but I could hold a whole conversation about it.
There's only one problem there,
is that I haven't bought a new game
between Super Smash Brothers,
and that's the first game I bought since the Wii U watched.
I'm almost surprised you're not an Overwatch guy.
I was thinking about it,
and I realized I hated everything about it.
I think the art style is the worst thing that's ever happened,
and I think all the characters are not only boring,
but their designs are probably the worst thing
that has happened in this country since 9-11,
and for the Holocaust.
I like Widowmaker, and...
No, she's the worst one!
She is the worst one!
She is single-handedly the worst one!
She's like...
Oh, hot!
No, that's what they want you to think.
That's what the Jews want you to think.
That's what they fucking...
What about the...
You know what, actually?
Here's the funny thing.
The girl in the pink robot.
What's her name?
Do you remember?
Diva.
I saw her, and I'm like,
yeah, she's cute,
and I liked that she's cute,
but she's supposed to be like a Korean pop idol?
I don't know if you've ever seen Korean pop idols,
but they are fucking beautiful.
The most attractive people in the world
are Korean pop idols,
and Diva is supposed to be like an 18-year-old Korean pop idol,
and I don't buy it.
She just looks like a normal Korean girl.
She does not look like a pop idol.
Those women are unbelievably godly beautiful.
I thought she was supposed to be like a Twitch streamer.
She's that, too.
She's like a pop idol and a Twitch streamer.
Oh, great.
Yeah, but I can't believe that she...
I can believe Twitch streamer.
I can't believe she's a pop idol.
She's just not...
She doesn't have that level of superhuman beauty.
Yeah.
Going back to Widowmaker and how I think you may be
the worst human I've ever encountered,
Widowmaker is literally frozen.
She's like,
oh, we're going to make attractive character designs.
These are what humans find attractive.
We are robots.
We've created this in a lab.
My name is Shadman.
I run Shadbase.com,
the worst internet fucking place ever to exist ever.
My name is Shadman.
I'm going to create a character.
Let's just make it the most cartoony.
I hate it.
No good.
It's not good.
It doesn't make anything of my rocks.
It doesn't do any...
And I hate it.
I don't disagree.
And I especially hate Tracer's design,
because she looks like if someone tried their hardest
to just make Pixar,
which is already what Pixar is doing.
I can't stand...
I hate the Pixar aesthetic.
Yeah, me too.
I hate it so fucking much.
When I look at Big Hero 6,
all I see is marketing.
I just see dollar signs.
That's the best way to say it.
You are the man.
That's why you're the words, man.
That's why you're the man with the words.
Because you know how to make words happen.
Yeah, and that's what I feel when I see Tracer.
When they first announced Overwatch like two years ago,
and they had that cinematic trailer for it,
and it had Tracer,
and I literally thought it was Big Hero 6,
because that wasn't out yet.
And someone showed me that trailer,
and I thought it was a trailer for Big Hero 6,
and I was like,
wait, this is like a Blizzard game?
This just looks like a generic Pixar movie,
and I hate the way Tracer looks.
I hate all fucking 3D animated movies.
They need to go.
All of them?
What one do you think is good?
I like Frozen.
I like Zootopia, it was okay.
I thought Frozen was super boring.
I like Zootopia actually.
You know what's funny is,
I saw Frozen,
and I loved it back at the time,
and then it got really popular,
and I started feeling like it was overrated,
and it beat some movie I wanted to win
at the Academy Awards,
and I was like,
this is fucking bullshit, right?
And then like,
and then,
but at the time that I saw Frozen,
I made an analysis video of it,
with me and Clover Keen,
where we had our alpacas.
Do you remember that?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, I remember everything you've ever done.
Well, me and DeVoo did commentaries
on that whole era of my videos
that are for patrons,
and we watched that video,
and I made all these great analytical points
in that that I didn't remember at all.
And I was like,
whoa, Frozen is deeper than I remember.
I was impressed with my own analysis,
which is not usually the case
for my older videos.
They're usually garbage.
But that one, I was like,
oh my god, this is intelligent.
Yeah, I thought Frozen was boring,
and I hated all of them.
Wait, that's not even a Pixar movie.
No, it's a Disney movie.
We were talking about 3D movies.
Yeah, yeah.
I thought it was boring,
and I thought the character design
made me thought I wanted a guy.
Did you like Tangled?
I don't remember Tangled.
I remember I saw it when it came out,
and I thought, yeah,
I don't remember why.
Same here.
I feel exactly the same.
When I first saw it,
it was at a time when I hadn't seen
any movies in a while,
and I was like,
this is my favorite movie ever.
And then like a year later,
I don't remember anything about it.
Yeah.
Or didn't rather.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know what 3D movie
I could bring up that maybe you'd like.
Wreck-It Ralph was like,
I, like, whatever.
That was pretty okay.
Yeah.
I liked it.
I'm the glitch, man.
It's in my code.
Kanye Weld.
Do you know that from my videos?
I feel like...
Well, I heard it before,
but I didn't fully appreciate it
until you brought it up again.
And I was like,
oh yeah, that was fucking insane.
So I know you've always been in the
pro-victor camp when it comes to
Digibus.
More than you can ever imagine.
What is it about Victor
that you find so attractive?
He's funny.
He's charming.
He's kind.
He's gentle.
He's always there for you
when you need him.
Well, except that he hasn't
been around at all
for two weeks now.
I have seen less than two hours
of him in the last two weeks.
He's gentle.
He's kind.
He's always there for you
when you need him.
He's got that look in your eyes.
It's like a baby giraffe.
Victor's like a baby giraffe.
When I look at him,
I feel like I'm at peace.
Like I'm at Nirvana.
Not like I've reached Nirvana,
but I'm at a Nirvana concert.
Looking at Victor,
he's being at a Nirvana concert.
Oh.
You know what's funny is
all that stuff I was saying
about 9-11 to you,
people who are a generation older
than me would say all that
about Kurt Cobain
killing himself.
Who the fuck is Kurt Cobain?
The lead singer of Nirvana.
Who gives a fuck?
I hate Nirvana.
It was a really big deal.
I don't even know what it is.
In like 1991,
or whatever,
like around when I was born,
he killed himself
and everybody was like,
sure.
You know who I honestly
thought Kurt Cobain was?
I thought he was Bill Maher.
I thought he was like a liberal,
like fucking...
like city house.
You really didn't know who Kurt Cobain was
till just now?
No.
You just heard the name
a bunch of times?
Yeah.
He was the lead singer
of Nirvana.
It's like the most important
and influential band
in the 90s.
And I would always hear him
like Kurt Cobain.
He's always on the red side.
He's so good.
He was so great.
And it was always by like liberal parents
and I was like,
oh, he must be one of those guys.
Oh my god.
By the way,
by the way,
by upbringing,
I don't know if this will
I'm going to wait until you're done laughing.
Go ahead.
Uh,
my upbringing
was entirely,
entirely,
reruns of Seinfeld.
Every single day
of my life,
Seinfeld was on in the background.
No,
I didn't watch cartoons.
I watched maybe like three cartoons.
After that,
it was only Seinfeld.
Only Seinfeld
for 15 years.
I know you love Seinfeld.
Oh, I love it.
Everyone thinks it's like,
dude, it's Seinfeld.
I'm going to murder.
Wait, are there people who like,
who think Seinfeld's like a meme?
Like Seinfeld's great.
No, yeah.
Seinfeld's great.
Larry David is great.
Jew humor is my favorite kind of humor.
And I'm being brainwashed.
It is now that you've mentioned it,
it's your family at all
related to Judaism,
or at all?
No, no.
They are,
they are,
they are, they are,
they are divus.
I ain't having no that shit though.
Are they like that hardcore,
like divus family?
That's,
no, I don't think no one can be
as hardcore as divus family,
but they're up there.
My mom downstairs sleeping,
like I'm going to stop my foot.
She heard that probably.
She has like a little fucking shelf
that just has like a whole,
like different pictures of Jesus.
Just fucking,
so when she wakes up,
she can immediately look at Jesus' face.
Are they like Catholic?
Cause that sounds like a Catholic thing.
No.
I don't know what they are honestly.
They're just,
they just believe in God.
And that's all I know.
And that's not for me to be.
You're not having that shit.
No, I am not having that shit.
And then I,
they were like, dude,
why didn't you want to go to Easter?
Or why didn't you want to go to church on Easter?
And then I just looked at them and I just said,
uh,
dude,
are you really asking me that dude?
Do you want to know the answer?
Yeah.
I don't know if you're prepared.
Well, I asked that because it's a,
it's funny because my family's not,
in no way do we practice
any form of religion,
especially not Judaism,
but because Victor looks
very Jewish.
And we come from like a Jewish ancestry.
Victor's like really into,
like,
the comedy.
Like he loves Larry.
A lot of Woody Allen.
Yeah.
Loves Woody Allen,
loves Larry David,
loves Seinfeld.
And like,
has this like,
like really relates to like Jewish guilt,
even though he's not Jewish.
It's super,
super funny.
Oh my God.
I'm going to,
I'm going to make a new mean
super smash brother.
It's called Jukill.
And it's just going to be called Victor.
It's going to be Victor.
By the way,
I've made a whole bunch of fucking me's.
I've just been waiting to show to Victor
for when we finally do the,
the Digi Bro is smashed for.
Yeah.
We were,
we,
you guys both got like,
there was a time where Victor comes up
to my room all excited.
Like,
we got to do this smash thing with Munchy,
like right now.
And I'm like,
I think I was like really drunk
and out of it at the time.
And I was like,
I didn't want to do anything.
And he comes in like,
I'm excited.
And I'm like,
dude,
I don't even begin to know how to set that up.
Like I have no idea
how we're going to capture audio
from all these,
because the thing is
if both of me and him are playing with you,
then we can't be wearing headphones.
So that means that your audio
is going to come out of the speakers
and get picked up by my microphone.
Oh fuck.
So even if you played by your,
like even if you had,
you know,
headphones and a mic and everything like,
this is why you don't do group podcasts,
like a group of people doing a podcast.
Although,
there might be a way to do it
that only Cider,
that only Cider knows.
Because,
fun fact,
in the pub crawl,
none of us wear headphones.
Because Cider has a bot
that he puts in the thing with him
that records everything.
And the bot records
each incoming audio itself.
What the fuck?
So like,
all the audio that's coming into his computer
is recorded by his bot.
And so it doesn't,
it doesn't matter what you have on there.
Yeah, it's crazy.
Every call he has,
it's called Cider Bot.
And if he taught me
how to make a bot like that,
I'd be able to do shit
with no headphones.
That's crazy.
But yeah,
and like,
it was hard for me to explain,
because like Victor came in,
all excited,
wanted to do this thing with you.
And I was like,
explaining to him like,
we can't do it,
because it's going to sound like shit.
And I also don't want to right now,
because I'm fucking
completely out of it.
And he was like,
mad at me,
like I was like,
like a super villain
for denying this podcast to happen.
And like, we can't,
we can't do it.
Like, I don't know
how to make it happen.
I don't know what you want from me.
I remember,
he was super fucking sad
when he came back and texted me.
He was like,
I can't do it.
Conrad doesn't want it.
And I was like,
it's okay, man.
It's okay.
But after that,
he completely just,
it was like,
I'm never going to even ask again.
I am never even going to entertain
the thought ever again.
He's brought it up a couple of times.
He wanted to do it.
Yeah.
I didn't think he,
he still fucking cared.
There's just no way of,
there's no logical,
like I said,
for the reasons I just explained,
I don't know how to organize it.
Like,
I mean, I've had it in mind.
Like it would be fun to do,
but I would need the method
by which to do it.
I hate,
that's why I hate doing stuff
all over the internet like that,
because it's such a pain.
That's why Digi Bros.
is always just whoever's next to me.
And I've never done like a,
like,
over the internet guest Digi Bros.
for that reason.
That's why you need to,
you need to make Victor,
you need to,
like,
without him knowing,
take out,
you know how he's like,
rushing around to find a job?
Get him like some sort of,
like fucking backwater Chinese job.
And all of his fucking profits,
like 99%,
doesn't go to him.
It goes to a fucking secret fund
that you have at City Bank.
And all that fucking money,
it will accumulate over time
and it will be a,
like a plane ticket.
No, not even a plane ticket,
a bus ticket.
For me to go all the way over to your house,
and I'll just show up unannounced.
And it'll be like,
did you,
I mean,
whatever the fuck,
why am I getting paid
literally two nickels
for 300 hours of work?
And then I'm gonna,
you're gonna walk over the door
of your fucking castle,
and you're gonna say,
this is why Victor,
and I'm gonna walk in with my bombs.
And then you're gonna just,
all the walk bar,
and blow us all up.
Yep, it's all over.
This is what you've been
waiting for is terrorism.
Oh, God.
Oh, should I have the pee again?
Why would you fucking pee?
I've been drinking,
this whole time,
I've been drinking like nonstop gin
mixed with orange juice,
and it's a,
I don't know,
it's messing me up.
Just, just get a little,
like two.
But now I'm out of orange juice.
Just a little tube
and I'll re-route here,
toilet, dude.
That's what I have.
I know you haven't had time
to listen to tonight's
procrastinator podcast,
but we talked a lot about piss
in it for some reason.
Uh, it's a poor part of life.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom
again so you can just keep
talking again.
Pokemon, it's the biggest
winner ever choice.
Oh, wait, no,
I'm not gonna do that with
no one shit.
To be a master,
a Pokemon master.
I think it's Pokemon master again.
Do, do, I'm gonna beat Pikachu.
My name's Will Smith
and I'm a Pokemon trainer.
I'm gonna beat Pikachu.
I'm gonna beat Misty.
And I'm not gonna beat Brock
because he could probably beat me up
because he's taller than me probably.
I don't know how to tell Brock
his beast.
Probably taller than me,
so I'm not gonna beat him up.
But I'm gonna beat up
all the people who are shorter than me.
I'm gonna pick on people
who aren't my same size.
I'm gonna force them
to be in movies
and they don't want to be in.
Uh, my name is Will Smith
and I'm a bad Pokemon trainer.
I'm a Team Rocket group.
I'm gonna make sure
that they, uh,
Pokemon aren't just not,
but you're just not
have the same fucking skills.
They do not develop properly.
They have fucking anxiety disorders
and they grow up
because I'm constantly beating them
for doing well.
You know, no matter what,
no matter the outcome,
I still beat them.
My father did to me.
I'm gonna do it to my kids.
Will Smith,
the Pokemon trainer.
I'm gonna do it to my kids
and my Pokemon.
And it's just not
gonna be pretty for anyone.
I'm telling you, dude,
you gotta stop this.
This is a plea for help.
Right now,
I'm on the fucking phone
with the police commissioner.
I'm telling them
about how I'm gonna
fucking shoot up some schools
of Pokemon, Pokemon schools.
And I'm leaving a message
and no one's gonna take me
seriously until it's too late.
I'm gonna think,
oh, just crazy Will Smith again.
Crazy Will Smith
from fucking Seldon City.
What are they gonna know?
They're gonna fucking realize
it's gonna be too late.
I'm gonna have shot up
a Pokemon school
for Pokemon learning
where you learn about
the different types.
Grass, fire,
flame, electric, water.
Don't forget about psychic.
To be a master,
Pokemon master.
a Pokemon master.
I'm back.
Hey, welcome back.
That was perfect.
Lee time.
Um,
hey, Monty,
I have this impression
that you're a man
of liking a few things
very intensely.
Yes, yes.
Rather than a lot of things.
Like, I'm a guy
who doesn't like anything
that much,
but I like a whole lot of things.
But you seem to like
Pokemon,
Homestuck, Kirby.
Although you don't
like Homestuck anymore.
No, uh,
it's very complicated.
Me and Ben and Nate
and Hippo
and probably another guy.
No, not the other guy.
I don't, never mind.
I changed my mind.
Not the other guy.
We're probably gonna do
a Homestuck podcast
once Nate is not
fucking gay.
Oh yeah,
I want to,
I want to be in on that,
but I have to read
the whole fucking thing again.
Yeah.
Have you seen the ending?
No, I haven't.
I stopped.
God, I stopped like two,
two, maybe two and a half years ago.
Like I just stopped reading
and then haven't caught up.
Well, I mean, most of that was,
there was a big coming out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just realized that,
yeah, that was probably like
three pages.
I want to say like Act Six,
Act Six is where I stopped
or something like that.
Yeah.
And I just never caught up
from there, but.
Uh, yeah.
You know how,
what do you think,
define an ending?
Um,
the place where the story stops.
Yeah.
And that, that's not,
that's.
What are you hoping for?
No,
I know you guys happened
and what it wasn't.
It wasn't.
I know you guys are not happy
with the ending of host.
Because nothing happened.
Nothing happened.
I mean, I'm,
I'm very curious about it.
Like what I'll feel when I get
to it.
Because historically,
I've been someone who's
never been that bothered by
non endings.
But.
You're going to be like,
ooh,
Hidiakiano,
Andrew Hussey,
same person.
Oh, they're so cool.
Oh, I like them so much.
What are the other,
what are all JoJo's
and other things?
What are all the things you're
really into?
What are your.
I'm,
I'm big into JoJo.
I haven't finished it.
No spoilers.
You can put spoilers though.
That was a joke.
You can put spoilers.
Because I fucking hate you.
In a way.
JoJo.
Yeah.
No.
Don't laugh.
It's not funny.
It's not a joke.
JoJo is something that I'm
really into.
I'm also into Kirby.
I'm,
I'm in all the stuff you said.
I'm also very big into
chicken wings.
Very spicy stuff.
I should say,
actually I should broaden that.
By the way,
the next time we ever meet,
I need specifically you,
Victor and Ben.
These are the three people,
the three,
the three men that I've chosen
to go on my,
on my quest with me.
We need to eat hot wings together.
You gotta bring shade.
Shade very recently got
really into spicy food.
That's fine.
Yeah.
I'll bring shade if you
please to argue with me.
Anyway,
we'll eat,
that's how,
that's the bro pack I've made.
We all eat spicy chicken wings
together.
That will solidify our
fucking,
our ooze together.
Our celestial ooze
will be together.
Our man ooze.
Yeah.
Yes.
Our mayonnaise.
I like the view.
Oh man.
Yeah,
we, we just need to do it man.
We need to fucking meet up
and eat chicken wings.
That's we,
it dude we can fucking come we can we can combine I think we should dedicate a
little about this talk about anime since I've seen 10 anime and I thought they
were all 10 out of 10 oh yeah really yeah I I have a policy where I don't
watch shows unless I know that I will fucking jizz every single episode okay
so I have very like like I remember my friend who got me into Jojo he said hey
dude I know you're really gonna like this anime and since I got you into Joji
you gotta trust me dude I was like all right well I'll watch and I'll end up
watching episode and we'll see that episode was the fucking that anime was
Cancullo collection whatever it's called can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can
I actually don't think I finish the first episode either. I
Think I got halfway through and stopped same way
So every since then wait wait, he wait wait wait so the sentence he said to you was I
Know you liked Jojo
So check out
Canty Collection
Like it was like you gotta trust my opinion on things you gotta know that I have good taste
I showed you those are like not even slightly remotely similar
What a fucking idiot
Yeah, what a fucking douche, dude
So yeah, I very I
I'm very picky and so I only watch shows where I know that I'm going to fucking oh
every time
So the I think it's it's been too long for me to talk about kill a kill because I don't remember anything about it
I remember thinking oh, it's funny. Also boobs. Also. It's kind of cool and has some stuff to say, but I don't really care
Yeah
That was just letting my cat into the window. I oh hold on. We just stop talking about anime. I don't even like anime
Let's go about fucking cats. I
People okay, Jesse's gonna get mad at me for the same this but and I know this is like some sort of like normie like
Like oh, you can't have this opinion. These multiple have it cats are the worst. They aren't cool
They don't do anything cool. They haven't done anything. They're like, oh, yeah, they're cute
Yeah, if you can get the right like Facebook angle for them. What's the time that you're fucking assholes and like, oh, yeah
Oh, I bet you like dog. Yeah dogs are better. They're every way and better
There's no downsides to a dog and you're gonna be like, oh, but I hate all animals
Yeah, that's cuz you're a serial killer and I hate you. You're not cool. I
Don't get like I don't
What do you mean? There's no downsides to a dog. They're they smell bad. They
Give them a bath you fucking retard loud
They fucking you can train your dogs to not bark all the time. I have they they want attention
And I don't want to give them attention. They don't need attention. They just want it
They'll look up. I mean in fairness the cat was attention to and I can't fucking stand her so yeah
I mean, okay. Okay. This is my relationship with my dog. I
Love the room. I have no interaction with them and I go down and it's like, oh, yep. Yep. Hey, and I'll be like, hey
I'm gonna spend like 30 seconds. I'm gonna I'm gonna give you the best massage I've ever done
Then I'm just gonna go on my merry-away and then he'll be like, all right
Bye and then that'll be that'll be it. And it's the best relationship I've ever had
Including all the women I've been with which is zero. I
Find I find animals to be terrible people
The pretty needy the pretty clingy like I you know
This is gonna sound really fucking weird and and I can hear Nate scratching his head through space-time
At this because he thinks it's weird that I come that I constantly compare unlike things
That like I that I look at porn the same way I look at art or that I look at like food the same way
Nate stupid alright, I
compare everything right yeah, and the way I see it like
There's no reason to judge animals on a different scale from how I judge people
Like there it's another living being I don't get why I give them special rights and privileges just because they're not people
Animals are too dumb to talk
Most of what I get out of people is talking like I can appreciate liking
Like companionship if you like a dog or a cat or something like something that likes for some people the fact
They can't talk is the appeal they have no opinions about you
They don't they don't care what you're like you give them food therefore. They unconditionally love you
I don't feel that way because what I get out of people is interesting conversations
And I've never had an interesting conversation with my cat and therefore she bores me and so I
All she ever wants for me is to get up out of bed when I'm asleep and let her into one of various doors
That's around my room. So all she ever does is cause me problems, you know
She's she's adorable. I'll give her that
She's been around for fucking ten years. So I'm used to seeing her so
You know but otherwise I see I see she's not a good person if she was a human
I would long ago have been like get the fuck out of my house, you know
That's how I feel about that's that's the difference between you because I have had a lot of meaningful conversations with my pets
I consult them on pretty much everything I do
Yeah, they look at me and that's how I know
Okay, if the answer is no then they'll say yep. Yep, and then if the answer is yes, it's like yep
You know much you I've always been jealous of people who who have tulpas
Yes
I'm jealous of people who can convince themselves
That's that their own imagination is talking to them. Yes, because I can't do it
I'm not saying those people aren't doing it. I just can't myself. So I am legitimately jealous of like people who are crazier than me
Oh, believe me. Believe me a son of a gun. I'm crazier than you
I don't doubt it
The things I could do are things that you have nightmares about
And the things I do are things that I revel in
I'm a champion. I'm a champion of blood. I hate to potentially bring your mood down
But how do you feel about school? You're in high school, right? Yes. How do you feel about it?
Very interesting relationship about school. I don't want to talk about my individual experience with it
But okay, well, well, I mean I'll talk about my how I feel about it
But I don't bring up the specifics about the situation. I'm in bad situation. Anyway, I think school is
The worst thing that has ever happened ever. I
Think that nothing is ever any good
It is all not good and all the things that are good are not good and they can be good elsewhere
Other than a place that is not good everything about it next to feel bad
I don't want to do it because it's fucking gay and it doesn't make any sense
And it's stupid and I hate it and it's not even cool. It's not even fun
And it's not even important and it's not even anything. It's gay. I don't like it
It's not cool. All the things that are cool. Like, oh, yeah, like, oh, you're gonna have friends there
You know, like I don't give a shit
I don't even like 99% of the people the only people I like I like super smash others and I get to beat them
It's super stretch others. That's the only reason I like it. It's just the shit
Oh shit, I think I just inhaled a beard hair
I
Wanted to ask you because uh, I assume you listen to our school PCP. I yes
I listen to everything. Yeah, and I wanted to know what that was like from the perspective of someone in the high school
Yes, yes, I believe me. I was raring. I was a raring. I
Did it make you want to like drop out and go do other things or something? No, okay, uh, I mean
Did you want me to
Hey, man, they might accept you as like a car
Can you imagine me as a clown I would be the best clown ever it would be great. I would definitely pay to see that. Yeah
Popeys I come
Yeah, how did you feel though I
Felt like everything everyone said was on point except for anyone ever saying that anything good about school ever happened
That all the positive points. Yeah. Yeah, Ben was like, oh, you know, there's some benefits and then I just wanted to
Go inside, you know how when you were little kid
You always want to have the superpower to go inside TV shows and like alter them like be inside
Not really personal. Okay. Well, you're gay and you are stupid anyway
Everyone else has that opinion and you are just an anomaly and you shall be you shall be
Yes
Anyway, I wanted to do that but with Ben and I would go inside of his dreams and I would make all the dreams of bricks
They would all be bricks from now until forever like
Like he sees bricks or his dream itself is a break like what is the what is the brick?
I think that's up for
interpretation
I think the art I think art beauty is in the eyes of the Holy I
Think I have a I think I have a mustache hair in my like in my esophagus
What is it like having a beard like that? I don't have a beard, but I don't have a beard like that
It seems like it would get in the way
It's definitely in the way. It's it's it's funny because
The beard the beard is pretty in the way the mustache is super in the way
Like when I go out to eat a lot of stuff is hard to eat because of it
I have to constantly wipe
After every bite and every time I'm out eating
I think I really need to trim this mustache or just fucking get rid of the whole thing and then I get home
And I forget and I don't think about it at all
So it's like yeah, it just so happens at the times
It's most annoying or when I'm in the least position to do something about it. Yes. Yes
I know how you feel. You know how there's there's like videos on YouTube
Where it's like we found this homeless man a homeless event
And we took him to a barber shop for the first time in 50 years
And he's finally been able to like see his face and like we've like we like pampered him
I want that for you not to shave the beard, but just to make you
Human yeah, just to make you human again
To be human again will be do do do do that's from the eating the beast
I mean I kept saying that I was going to shave it once the summer came and the summer's here now
And I haven't done it and it's just I don't know I get very attached to certain
looks and I'm also lazy, but like when I
I I like the idea of me as a bearded guy like this guy with this big giant beard, you know
It's I'm not saying get rid of the beard. I'm saying make it not look bad
That's impossible
The way it grows is just too fucked up. There must be a way. There must be there's no way
People people are always like if you just trim it or if you like brush it. I'm like guys
It's not like that. It's the way it grows is just this I have terrorist beard like it looks like
I I am of some degree of Middle Eastern just not even Middle Eastern
I guess my my my grandparents on my dad's side are were jews
And this is how their facial hair grows
Like it's just like a terrorist. Yes
Every time I've wanted to shoot up a school a hair pops up on my body
A hair pops up on your body. Is that where all of your hairs have come from? Yes, you're pretty hairy guys
I'm talking about you. Oh
Well also me
Every time I've wanted to impersonate the zodiac killer a hair spot on my body
What did you how many times do you think I've I've mentioned the zodiac killer?
A number
Is the zodiac was he a real killer?
I can never remember he tarred
Well, I can never remember if the zodiac killer was a real killer or if it was the character from the movie seven
No
Who was the killer from the movie seven? Uh, Kurt Cobain. No, not that one
I
I don't fucking know. I don't watch movies. I hate movies. They aren't cool. They aren't art. Oh, this is why I want to talk about you
This was uh, uh, Nick put this in like the list, but I don't think he actually put in the list
I think it was just humor in me. Can we talk about how books aren't art?
I guess sure
All right, books aren't art. They aren't cool. They don't have any fucking merit. They need to be all be gone
That's it. What do you have against books?
Uh, they don't have images their words. I have to look I have to have a book in my hands to read them
Uh, just I don't like I don't like books either for the record. I mean, there's some I I love house of leaves
Uh, which is a book
It's one of my favorite things
But it's kind of an exception to the rule and house of leaves is
Is a lot like homestuck in that it's yes, exactly
Homestuck is a book, but it's the only book I like because it's not stupid
I mean, homestuck has a lot of pictures in it though. So it's hard to think of as just a it's it's mostly
It's mostly a book man. There's a lot of fucking pester logs
Yeah, but there I mean, there's whole video games in it too
But whatever house of leaves doesn't have any pictures
But the way you read it is like homestuck and that's very it's very complicated to you
Have to actually move the book around to read it like you have to flip it around and do like go between pages and shit
It's like a it's a maze of a book
So it uses the the medium of being a book to the fullest
There have been books I have enjoyed
But overall I don't like the medium of books as much as I do the medium of moving pictures like it's exactly
Not even moving pictures. There can be still images
I mean picture says a thousand words
People ask me all the time books people ask me all the time like why do I stick to anime so much and why not other stuff?
And it's like I I legitimately think anime is the best medium
Because it has it has all the things it has
Dialogue it has writing like you can write anything you could write into a book
You could write into the script of an anime not all of it would make sense
But you could write it all in there
You and then you can also add images and you can make them move
And you can add music and you can add voices like you can do everything to it
And there's no there's
There's almost no limitations
The biggest limitation is budget, you know
To what you can or cannot do a lot of the time
I think the seal images are better than moving images in some like in looking home stuck
The page is like they're they're you know, obviously remember some of the great gifts like the day of getting covered in fucking puppets
But then there's just this page. There's just pages where you just there's just a still frame like fucking john looking at jade's dream self or whatever
Dead and it's just
Well, that's that's the funny thing about anime too is that anime
Yeah, well, it's been criticized a lot by like by fans of western animation
Because like all the classic western animation like disney or like tom and jerry and stuff was all about the movement
And the expressiveness of the movement and in japan like originally as a cost cutting technique
They focused more on the individual images, but over time like
If you ask me what the best looking anime is I always say kill law kill and kill law kill
Is rarely animated and it doesn't even have any moments of like really exemplary animation
It's just that the individual images are all amazing
Like any one shot of kill law kill is the best looking picture frame you'll ever see, you know
And like it doesn't have to move to tell the story well and to be inventive and and
More creative than actual animation is we're like there's parts in disney movies where everything like old ones
We're like everything's moving and I don't give a single fuck
Yes, I feel the same way the only disney movie I like is Aladdin Hercules if you don't like those ones
You're not quote because those are actually fun
Those are two of the best disney movies because they're actually entertaining and like have
Interesting characters and Mulan. I like Mulan just because will smith is in it. I mean whatever his name Eddie Murphy. Yeah
Will Smith the the pokemon beater and the child beater and the white beater and the misty beater
I want that to become a mean by the way if that's not a meme. I'm gonna make someone mad
So what what do you spend most of your time doing munchies? I spend most of my time working on
Fuck it. I'm just gonna say it. It's a story about an uh, well shit
Shit because I don't I don't know to what extent because I'm still very much in the writing phase. I am writing
I'm actually doing something but
The way I'm doing it is I'm gonna write the script and then I'm going to try it
So I don't I don't want you to end up ruining this for yourself by talking about it
Yeah, yeah, what do you spend most of your time doing that's not working on this art project? Okay, it's uh
Most of the time I am like you said, I'm talking to people or I'm playing video games
I I rarely rarely have any fucking like I don't watch
Fucking I don't know
Gay enemies
Yeah, game of whoo. I'm I'm okay. I'm convinced that everyone doesn't like game of thrones, but it's just like a meme
It's like, oh, hey game of thrones is on two guys
Like oh, yeah game of thrones
Classic like that. It's not a real show. Yeah, just like a break being played by all of society. Yeah
That would be fucking hilarious. Yeah
Um, but what do you see you spend a lot of time playing games. What games do you play other than I play?
I play I play mostly smash
I I play mostly games that are off the wall and fucking weird
Usually like weird multiplayer games
I can't think of any good examples, but
Just fucking weird shit that you find like not on steam, but fucking direct download shit from 4chan. That's my bread and butter, dude
So you spend a lot of time in like the uh
The weird boards of 4chan. Yes. Yes. I love I love x
I love
Fucking I love adult gif not for the porn, but for the you uh, you laugh you lose
Just because there's usually weird stuff
Like like every thread is like the same shit, but then there's that
That one post that has all the replies and like a thumbnail that you can't really tell what's going on
So you always think what the fuck is going to be inside this
What could possibly be drawing all this attention?
And then that's usually where you find the
How do you feel about the fact that you would be underage banned from 4chan?
Or most of the things you do
I was banned I I was banned
Because some moderator thought I posted child porn when I hadn't posted the entire day
And I tried to appeal like I yeah, I was perma banned and I thought like I I literally didn't do anything
I didn't post anything and then I I tried to appeal and then immediately it was like your appeal has been denied. Uh, goodbye
And then so I was like, oh
Let me google how to get by this and I got by it in three seconds
I got a week-long ban from a once for posting porn
Really?
You fucking retard you gotta check it can't go by the thumbnail. It was
It was uh, I don't remember the it was like some
Some thread where for whatever reason I didn't understand at the time like what the rules were about porn on 4chan
And like someone else had made a thread that had
Like porn in it that hadn't been banned
So I thought it was okay in the context of this thread and I posted some porn image and like got uh week-long banned
This was like oh eight
So uh
You've been using this mid-2000s, but you haven't realized what the rules are yet until 2008. Well, no, I would say it's more like
Like late 2007 early 2008 is when I got into uh 4chan
But I didn't understand it that much at the time like I knew about it
And then it was only in like later 2008 that I
Actually started like going there like regularly for any reason other than curiosity, you know
Yes, exactly. I don't spend a lot of time on 4chan though. I don't post there almost ever. I mostly look at stuff
I go there, but I'm like so bored. I have no idea what to do with my life. Yeah. Yeah, same same
Uh, I would say about 30 minutes not 30 minutes about an hour and a half
Maybe are playing games then 30 minutes is on 4chan and then the rest is usually drawing commissions for people
Or just just making gifts and photos. So you do
But like what do you do commissions from like your tumblr?
Uh tumblr and my twitter. I posted
Commissions there before how how much money are you making on uh commissions?
Like nothing just pocket change just enough like oh
I want to get a pizza now
I
Mean it's impressive to me that you're making money at all on uh on the internet
I up until I was well into adulthood. I didn't even understand how money transferring worked on the internet
So like did you I want you to realize something?
in about
Not maybe less than a year. I'm gonna be able I'm gonna have my own patreon going. I'm gonna have a
Going
I'm going to be 16 and I'm going to be able to make money from patreon. Well, I'm still in school
It's pretty fuck. I mean if patreon had existed when I was in high school
I would probably have utterly failed at trying to do that
But see you you were a dummy. I'm a smarty
I I break the laws. I'm the guy that again is why I'm always so impressed with your age because I wasn't that smart at your age
like I wanted to be an artist, but I didn't have any clue how to go about it and
um, I mean
Sure, I was I was writing back then in the style that would eventually become what I do now
But I think that the level of my writing when I was 15 is like
Exponentially lower than the level of your drawing at 15
Like thank you, man. I don't think like because 50
You can read my old blog post from when I was 15. They're they're almost unreadable. They're garbage
Like whereas I actually like your drawing enough right now that I use it as an avatar. So
Yeah, yeah, definitely definitely
Uh, I I'm I have no idea what I was going to say. I was going to say something important
About patreon. I had no fucking clue
Uh, basically
Fuck you all I'm going to be rich. You're all going to be stupid and you're not going to wish you were me
And that's not that's not directed to you. That's directed to you
Yeah, like like like the world
Like every every you every single you
I'm gonna I'm gonna be I'm gonna be Scrooge McFuck
Well, monchi, uh, do you have anything else you want to talk about on this interview?
We're coming up on two hours. These usually go for three hours
But uh, yeah, but we've gotten so fucking sidetracked that we we fucking completely missed the point of the entire thing
Well, I I struggled hard to get devu up to three hours because he uh, was it was for whatever reason
Completely not interested in talking about his personal life at the time
I only remembered after the interview that he lived in Africa for like years and I didn't get to talk about that
Uh, he lived in fucking Africa
Yeah, his family did like his family did like missionary work in Africa
And that didn't get into the podcast
The interview I I literally asked him like is there anything interesting about your life and he was just like, uh
Has there been any trips I've been on uh, there's
I've been to oh, I I don't know if I want to make this a story
But I once you know how I I'm you said I was Mexican really, you know, I can pass as a Mexican guy, right?
Uh, I once went to Tijuana and my mother forgot to bring my passport
And uh, when we tried to go back to the United States, uh, I think you can imagine
The how did you even leave the country without a passport?
We can just what do you mean? We just walk
You just like what what do you tell you didn't walk to Tijuana? Yeah, we walked to Tijuana. Yeah
That's how close our house is to Tijuana
But you like do you live literally on the border like what the fuck are you talking about? No, no, we live like okay
Okay, we drove until we were like
Like we drove like 10 minutes
Then we got the car and then we just walked over the bridge and we were at Tijuana
Is Tijuana like the first city past the border? I don't know. I think so. Yeah
Can you walk through the border without a fucking visa or passport apparently?
I guess that's why we have some maybe illegal immigrants in the country
Where the fuck's the trump wall?
While I was there, it was actually quite a great experience for me
I think it opened up a lot. I took a picture on a next-way donkey
His name was bill and the next thing said
And I was like, I did not understand that but I do like donkeys
It's I I was next to a donkey and he was like
And I was like, yes
So how did you get back into the United States?
Uh
My mom was like, oh, shit. And then the guy was like, yeah, you retard. I'm not falling for this
This is my this is my fucking fifth year on the job, dude
I'm not I'm not falling for this shit again. And then my mom was like, uh, please. He was like, oh, okay
I mean, I was thinking like wouldn't it be easy enough if you if you're in walking distance
Couldn't she have just walked into the u.s
Ran home got your passport and brought it back and like pretty short amount of time. Well like like
I
Like it's weird. We could walk over just fine. But like we had to go through a line to get back
Right. It wasn't like we like we could yeah
Because no one in the u.s. Gives a fuck if you're going to Mexico. Yeah. Yeah
Mexico is happy to have you the u.s. Does not want what's coming back. Yeah, exactly. That's pretty fucking funny though
Yeah, it is great. I eventually got out your passport
I didn't fucking do shit. I was like, oh mom you have the passport, right? And she's just like, yeah
And then uh, no
And
by the way, uh
my passport, uh
I don't can you imagine me looking like a kid?
Uh, I I could
I can picture you being small
But at no age can I picture you being small for your age like
I would imagine you being slightly too big for whatever age you were
So if I'm picturing you at five, I'm picturing a seven-year-old. That's what I'm saying
When I was born I weighed, uh,
9 pounds and 14 ounces
That's fairly big. Yeah. Yes. Uh, the doctor said he's a big guy
And my mom said for you
That's actually but not the for you part, but I said before you because I knew
I knew I knew I knew the meme
I knew the meme. No more travel stories. I I don't travel outside the country. I'm I'm I'm very
Secluded in my lifestyle. I don't like venturing out into the wilderness
I remember I talked to you a long time ago about how I would literally get raped if I step one foot outside my house
Get raped?
Yeah, who is gonna rape you?
Uh, I don't know
Someone who or what like I'm a chupacabra gonna
I'm gonna get kidnapped and I'm going to who can kidnap you
They'd have to be armed to kidnap you. Yes, exactly. You need fucking hulk hogan to kidnap you
Yeah, that's not the same guy
I just want to let that I don't I don't want just you to kill me now
That's um macho. Yeah macho man ready. So I don't just see please. I I was a simple mistake
What happened again master
Uh, I I don't I only travel out when I want to be the people I know my quintices and super smash brothers
how um
You say you watch all my videos that is a considerable amount of time
Because these days i'm releasing like at minimum 45 minutes worth of video a day
Uh, are there any other content creators you follow to such an extent?
No
I I follow the pcp
and
I can't
I don't think any I I watch some I watch stir
And germa. I know, uh, I think nate and jesse know about germa. I know about germa, but I've only seen like one video
Jesse watches them. Yeah
Uh, I I don't I I don't follow any person religiously like uh, like I follow you people
So it's mostly yeah, I would say that most of the content. I don't even like most of the content
I get nothing out of but I just like well
I'm I'm too I'm I might as well if I can't be the best I might as well be the worst
So so you mostly come to youtube for our group. Yes, and not so much for anything else
Oh and for a race site shout out to race site. Ben knows what I'm talking about
He's a crazy old seven-year-old who makes uh
Interesting videos
Okay, I know there was a time
Which may be a very long time ago that you were into game grumps pretty heavily
Uh, I mean, I don't know if I would consider it very heavily. I was a fan definitely, but I don't
The people people get really into game grumps, right? Well
Yeah, I consider myself pretty into like or was pretty into game grumps before the last year when I
They completely went to fucking shit, but uh
Um, oh, you mean four years ago? If you
Well, that would be the beginning
That'd be the whole time
Which is true. Yeah
I can't pretend it's not
But there's definitely people who are uh too into it. Yeah
There are I have a I have a very
broad range of uh people I talk to
And by broad, I mean there are a lot of like okay imagine
I'm in the middle of a spectrum and at the very fucking ends are like normal socially adjusted people
Uh, they're the worst kind of humans. I I wish I was on the normie so I could really just drive at home
How much normal people just don't understand anything?
They don't know anything. They know nothing
They're all in yuppies and I'll kill them. I can't take normies man. I I had a year
I've had a few normies re moments recently. Have you had any recently?
Recently not
Not super recently. I've had a lot in the past
I don't know if I want to tell mine because it kind of be co-opping your uh podcast. You know
Uh
Go go ahead and tell tell one story and then I'll get back because I have a I have a
I've just had lately. I've I've been having the I've been making the mistake. Um of going out
To get like food at 2 a.m. On Friday nights
I don't know if you're aware of this, but that's when the like
2 a.m. Is when clubs let out like they they they stop selling shit at 2 a.m.
So uh on like I'm used to going out at 2 in the morning and and no one being out because
Why would they be it's 2 a.m. On like a wednesday, but on fridays
The clubs and on saturdays the clubs and stuff are full
So like if I go to like walla or it's like a 24 hour cafe like right at 2 a.m
They're fucking packed on friday and it's all drunk people and I'm short so you fit right in so
Yeah, well, you know, well, I don't I don't drive drunk. So if I'm if I'm going out, I'm not drunk
But I don't leave you for a second. I'm a short guy
and I
Unlike even though I I kind of look scary. I don't see myself as being intimidating
Like I I feel like I'm a small person
And when I'm surrounded by like large normies who are all drunk. I feel like unsafe
Like I don't like I feel like normal people are volatile when they drink
It's like all these giant dude bros who just got out of the club and obviously didn't get laid because
You know, they're in they're here and not somewhere else, you know
It's like just a bunch of like slightly pissed off drunk dude bros
And and and it makes me uncomfortable that I know they because I'll be like at wawa
Which is like a convenience store and it's like packed with drunk dude bros
And I'm like these guys are all about to go drive
Like they all drove here and they're about to go drive home and I'm going to be on the road with them
And well, you see did you it's disgusting what you need to realize is that you can pay me to be your full-time
Bodyguard. Yeah, I would totally do that if you were around
If you lived anywhere near me, I would bring you everywhere because I would feel so safe with you around
Like like it's it's not that they're going to do anything
It's just that if they just see me they are instantly
I am not going to make it out here alive if I even look at this guy. Have you ever seen the uh mtv show robin big?
No, it's it's this show. It was about this guy, uh the skateboarder
I think it was bob burnquist and he he was like this like so much shrimpy white guy
He was like a famous skateboarder and he had this giant black guy as his bodyguard
And like they became best friends
And so they had like a show on mtv. It was just about him hanging out with his giant
Bodyguard best friend and that would be us if we if we hung out
Yeah, I would just bring you everywhere to look intimidating and eat just to scare off your foes. Yeah
Like I would hype up the idea that you were mexican
Because it would make you scarier like I would have you eat churros at all times so that you look maximum scared
I come up with a fucking sombrero
Hey, hombre, I give me my pay or else you are gonna come for your fucking head's gonna come off
By the way, I'm picturing you in the pizza outfit. Yeah
I'm picturing you following me around in the pizza onesie
And the sunglasses by the way, I have prescription one sunglasses now
So I can I can I can have only sunglasses unlike the the double the double fucking glasses that I was doing last time
Dude the the sunglasses
And the pizza onesie is absolutely clusterpunk aesthetic. You would fit right in with my clique, which is just me
No, dude, uh, I'm fucking in I'm down. I'm down to clown with that. Yeah
The clusterpunk I want to go briefly back to uh, I want to piggyback on the topic of schools and
shootings and
I go right ahead
That'll keep everyone real comfortable school shootings
My favorite topic as I'm sure everyone the tcp fan chat knows because they constantly talk about doing it
Uh, this time I'm really gonna do it though. It's not a joke. Anyway, back when I was a little kid. I
But like I've always been like this
This is this is the beast that I live with. This is just me. This isn't like an act
I I'm I'm I'm insane. I'm an insane person and everyone around me is scared of me
I I go to school and I just fucking scream and I hug the people
But that was all by youth. I would just scream
Like fucking nonsense. I would run up and be overly affectionate to people
I would just hey dude. Hey. Hey. I hope you're having a great day. Can you do something for me, buddy?
Can you do something for me? I want you to have a great day and that would just run away
This sounds like a bunchy. I know. Yeah
And then uh, the only people I fucking the the only friend I've ever had in high school
Is because he wore in a tari shirt one day and I walked up to him and said hey, dude
Nice shirt. I wish I had one of those shirts, you know, and he was like, yeah
Ever since I've been being him in super smash brothers
Do you even care about a tari at all? No
I don't give a fuck who gives a fuck about a tari
No one even relevant in my lifetime much less yours
No
Um, it was just I don't fucking know. He's black too. So I have bragging rights. Oh, yeah, sweet
Nothing's better than black bragging rights
By the way, I haven't ever seen don son, but I used to imagine he is a typhoon
He is just he's uh, how much do you weigh?
100 or no 240 I think
He's bigger than you
Um, because he's about your height, but uh a bit fatter because he's probably
Pushing 300 right now. So holy shit, dude. Yeah, don son is like my fucking like a nega
Not not not not my nigger, but I mean my my like nega form
Oh my fucking yeah
Like like we we need a fuse to become one again don son if you're listening to this
We need to dance. He does not listen to anything
Don son if you're listening to this we need to fuse
I wouldn't be surprised if don son has literally never watched one of my videos before
If he has he's never mentioned it and I've never asked so, uh, yeah
Uh, there was a period of time where after doing the the crazy person thing for a while
There was like a like a month where I thought
You know, this is kind of pushing people away. This is kind of making people not take me seriously
Not taking me seriously as an artist or as a person
I think I need to tone it down for a little bit
Yeah, and then I became like a normal socially adjusted person for like a little bit and I was like this is fucking boring
That's how you lure them in man you need victims. It's like the that's like the angler fish the little dangly thing
Lure them in you
You know, there's a guy who my my cousin boy and he used to work with this dude
Who said that he would uh, he would go to clubs and he'd pick up
Women who were too drunk to know what was going on
And he'd take them home and he said what you do he advised this to my cousin boy
He said what you do is you lure them in with the Marvin gay and then you put on the dmx
And you just go crazy
And that was his method and he legitimately did that and uh
That's what I've been saying ever since you lure them in with the Marvin gay. Then you hit him with the dmx
Huh, you gotta add the huh after so it sounds like a song lyric
By the way the tweet I posted earlier you and Shaden just need to do you need to do a cover of that
Uh, which which tweet it was something like
Yeah, I I tripped and I fell I wound up in a cell for a pizza on my plate. I'm a pope. I'm a pizza pope
Yeah, I did see that
It was it was I came to me much like all my ideas in a fever dream about pizza
Pretty pretty much all my dreams all my entire life have just been pizza related or nightmares about pizza
Yeah, that's amazing. Are you a big pizza fan?
Yeah, I love pizza. You're fucking weird because you don't like pizza
I absolutely love pizza
I got the impression that you were indifferent towards pizza. No, I am a huge pizza fan
Oh, that's great. I am uh, I would consider I actually consider myself a pizza aficionado
To some extent. Oh, I see. I see uh, jesse hates pizza. He made a video
I mean, he likes to eat it, but he also likes to complain about it
Shade shade legitimately doesn't like pizza at all
taste wise when I've heard shade is not real
I do I don't get it. All he eats is fucking beef jerky. It's like and ramen. That's it beef jerky and ramen
That's enough for him to live like like and it's not you know
I grew up on a lot of ramen because we didn't have a lot of money
And then once I ate other foods, I went. Oh, there's like good food out there. I don't have to eat ramen
Shade eats other food and he's like I could just be eating ramen. Like that's how he feels, you know
Like nothing is as good to him as ramen and beef jerky. I mean ramen is good, dude, but
Yeah, it's it's a little much pizza. Yeah, he doesn't like pizza. He likes calzones not pizza
But you know why he doesn't like pizza why shade and this this this applies
Whatever you're if when I say this you're gonna go you mean even and I'm gonna say yes even
shade does not like any sauce
No sauce whatsoever no condiments no sauce no no liquid that is applied to food. Let's put it that way
What he eats everything dry
He eats everything dry everything dry with the exception of like
Like ramen or like spicy foods like he will put he'll eat like spicy wings
But he won't put like if you gave him chicken if you gave him a box of chicken nuggets and every dip known to man
He would not open any of the dips. He would just eat the chicken nuggets
I mean, I'm very similar. I don't like very many
I don't like salad dressing or anything like that. I I normally don't eat my shades ever eaten a salad before
I I normally don't like like ranch or anything like that. Right, but there's a there's a lot. Have you ever heard of a thing called ketchup?
Ketchup's pretty good. It goes good with literally everything. It's pretty good
It's pretty fucking good. And I hate tomatoes. I always remove like actual tomatoes by
Yeah, I'm not a big fan of it like growing up. I was but you're the disheveled man of tomato-based products. What are you talking about?
What? I don't know what you're talking about
of
You know growing up I was a picky eater
So I kind of get it like I didn't like a lot of the sauces and condiments
But like as I got older I started eating them but shades like 18 now and nothing's changed like
We all just assumed he would grow out of it, but he hasn't at all and there was one time
You'll you'll like the story
We were at this Mexican restaurant and I ordered these three
chicken empanadas like it was like a
a
Appetizer and it's just like it just looks like a fucking hot pocket full of chicken, right?
Yeah, and we got three of them and I was like all right one for me one for victor one for shade
It was just the three of us and shade looks at and he's like I don't want to eat that and we were like
Why not? He was like it just doesn't look appetizing
Like like the way the chicken looked didn't look good to him
Even though chicken's his favorite food
But the way the chicken looked didn't look good to him and he was just like I don't want to eat that
And we were like
Dude, how can you like you don't have any idea what it tastes like and we're both eating it and it tastes like something
We know you'd like
Why won't and like we were like begging him to eat it and he was just like he got mad and he was he was like
You guys it feels like you're raping me
Oh
My god, dude, honestly, I sympathize with the fact that if food doesn't look good. I'm not fucking touching that shit
I mean has to look somewhat appealing. Yeah, I don't think it looked bad
I understood why like I understood what he thought it looked like
But it didn't it wasn't like that like it looked like it had some kind of sauce on it and it didn't you know
But like we could not convince
Just did it. I just wanted him to take a fucking bite before making up his mind like
I was like, how can you know
Like how how do you ever learn new things if you don't try new things? He was like, I don't want to try anything new
I just I like the stuff I like. I have no reason to eat anything new ever
And I was like, oh my god, you're a fucking robot
By the way, when I when I talked about you how you're the the uh disheveled man of tomatoes based products
I was referring to the first tweet I ever made. I think
I'm gonna send it to you and if you want to if the fans at home want to see it, you can just go back
Oh, yeah, I do remember this if you see this while scrolling the first page
It's a picture of me squirting ketchup on something
You have been visited by the disheveled man of tomato based products full ketchup bottles and french fries will come to you
But only if you post lay off the sauce digi in this
Is this from like
What videos is from
I have I jeff uh, uh, not not not jeff brother's basement jeff the
Burgess. Yeah, Burgess
Yeah, we we conspire a lot to bring you down
Take you down a notch
Is this from the uh, because this
Now i'm seeing that i'm wearing the party hard shirt, which I know i was wearing when he came over to my house
So did he take this when he was at my house?
He did he gave me no information. I'm sure he don't information give him
It looks like because this he has a video from when he was at my house and I looked exactly like this in that video
So that's probably what it is
Yeah, probably
But for forever until the end of time you will be known as the man of the disheveled man of tomatoes based products on my mind
Good to wear that. Yeah, I think you wear that probably
Uh, uh to go back to the interview we're doing. Yes
Uh, uh, I was talking about how I for a while
I wanted to be respected as a human being and letting that didn't go well because I
Hated being a human being and I always wanted to be a turtle and I thought frogs are cool. I want to be a frog
uh, anyway
I I came back to my senses and I that's when I really started becoming like an art guy because I've always like drawn
I've never like drawn
right
I uh, so yeah, so
I would realize like, okay. I'm not gonna like
Go super all out like crazy, but I'm just gonna sit down
I'm gonna draw and if anyone ever even fucking comes up to me
I am going to turn on like a faucet and they are not going to
See the light of day ever again
It's gonna be it's gonna be like fucking p.t. But for in like one second
and forever
Like the game pt. Yeah. Yeah, like for the game like the game pt in this person's mind
Just looking at me. I am going to like through my speech. I'm going to literally give them like a visual pt
Like like all my words are gonna become in such a way that will make them literally like play pt in their mind while they're talking to me
How did that go
It went good. I I started drawing the guy who I I saw it had a nice Atari shirt started uh
Like fucking coming over to me and since uh, I had loaned him a book and I didn't get the book back yet
I let him be next to me
Uh, and then I I eventually realized that I I can do more with this man than just be even super smash brothers
Yeah, he gets more used to me as a black person
And
So what did you do?
So we fucking became friends duh, okay
So so so i'm the lord master and he's my guy
Yeah, and uh, there's a few others, but they don't those don't matter
Uh, we basically became friends and all like we we the reason we're all friends is because we all do different shit
And there's the stream monday
It doesn't matter what or fucking how or in what context, but one day we're all gonna do something at the same time
And it's all gonna be this like a like one thing so all this different shit squad goals
Squad goals. Yeah
exactly
Man we have yeah be careful with your squad goals because the pcp had squad goals for june
and we failed
miserably
It was the worst I saw because I watched everyone's videos
Everyone was like it's gonna be june guys. Yeah, it's mark your calendars guys. It's gonna be june
Nothing well jesse had this whole plan to launch my japanese animes into like overdrive in june
and then he started making a
One-year anniversary video for horse shoe finale and apparently that became like an
Overwhelming project just like horse shoe finale. Hasn't he learned his mistake? No
Never you haven't we've been through this and then I had this idea like
Because for me like the month of may I did all my work for may before may started as you probably know and uh
The idea with that was that during the month of may I would do something big and instead I did nothing
So then when june came around it was like, okay. Well, I completely failed at may so in june
I have to get things rolling and then it took like two weeks before I got anything rolling
So see I was literally earlier today thinking about that and I got really mad at you, but I forgot until just now
see
Big projects are terrible
Good like what's good is just a bunch of tiny little like tiny
Micro micro fucking organisms. They're just tiny polished to a fucking shine
Tiny just tiny just so tiny, but there's just a million of them
They're cells they're cells in a body and the body's youtube channel
I mean, I agree
But I find those unsatisfying to make
Because for me, I always feel like I have to be challenging myself
Like it always has to be something that's better than what I've done before or like something new, you know
Or something. I'm excited about we're like
Like I think if you're if you're trying to become
The most marketable youtube channel without throwing away your dignity
Jeff has it right mother's basement that channel is fucking it's exactly what it should be like
He has a follow up with what dignity
I'm just a joke
Like in internal like just being able to look at your work and being able to say I'm okay with this, you know
Like jeff does good enough work that he doesn't come off as a vapid cunt like a lot of people on youtube do
But his video is his videos are easy to make and accessible and
He has a format that works well with like that
That style which is like what he's trained to do because he used to work for like a proper video game magazine
So like this big sense to him, but like for me
Like it always has to be
Like I I could do stuff that way
But like I have a mental block against it
We're like I launched all those series in in april where it was like, oh i'm gonna do this every week and then
You know I can't
Because i'm crazy. I don't want to get too deep into that. I'm distracting from your interview
I've gotten a lot of complaints from uh from the other tpc members that every interview is actually an interview with me
Yeah, uh, don't worry, dude
It's more even though like I constantly fucking belittle you on every forum I have available
I I think you're a good guy. I like hearing it. I like hearing it
Well, I imagine you wouldn't actually watch all my videos if you didn't appreciate the content
Like I've never been under the illusion that you think i'm shit because if you actually thought that you wouldn't be interested
I'm actually surprised by how long you've maintained interest in my content considering
I don't even talk about anything you watch anymore
Uh, I mean I didn't really care about pony at all
I mean I I did I thought it was cool
But I was never like that into it, but you were pretty in the community
You had I was in the community a lot of friends in there and stuff. Yeah, exactly. I was in the community
I didn't care about the fucking show who gives a shit about the show
Interesting. I actually meant to ask that like how much you actually cared about the show itself
Or about my little pony very little
So you wouldn't say you weren't you weren't you're not you were never into it the way you were into like homestuck or pokemon or curbie or jojo
I'm not that and like I was I wasn't a pokemon kid. I was never a pokey kid
I'm a pokemon guy now
But I I mainly just played the games like like on a very surface level didn't do any like anything crazy
I remember yeah, my my first exposure to anything that wasn't pressing attack over and over
Was I I did the battle like frontier in platinum and the first fight
Was a munchlax and I was like, oh cool. I wonder what he's gonna do
He would do stockpile over and over. Do you know what stockpile does? I don't
It raises their fence their defense and their special defense up. I think a stage
And he would keep doing that and little me. I have no fucking idea what anything
Ever does I just think status effects just whatever who gives a shit same here and I just I just could not
What why can't I hit him? Why is he not dying? He's a baby pokemon. How can he take this much hits?
And then I eventually he did like I got him like that. I was shizzling down like oh
She's gonna fucking tell me this piece of shit is fucking over
Then he uses swallow
You know swallow does I do not
It is a move that has to be used for stockpile
And it uses all the stockpiles that you've done to recover a set amount of hp
I see so
He's he used all his like 15 million stockpiles to get back to
100% hp and I turned off the game and I wanted to die
Uh, that's my first yeah, I've never done any high level pokemon stuff like even the stuff that's in the games
Yeah, I'm doing showdown now. It's an online balance simulator. I want I want sun and moon
I swear dude, it's gonna be it's gonna be the new this is gonna be the genesis
The neon if you will
Yeah
Of genesis, how did you feel about even going on? He said you finished that show. Yes. I did finish it
Uh, a funny thing. I I refused to watch it until I was sick and I wanted to throw up every second
And I thought this is the perfect climate to watch even gillion
I was miserable
I was miserable nothing made me happy
I was I was constantly on the verge of just fucking pissing and shitting and throwing up on myself
And I just got my laptop out and I watched it all
I'm fucking like one night
And I was like, yep
That's how I feel right now
The last because the last line of end of eva and gilly on the film is oska says
Kimo chi warui, which means I feel like shit essentially or I am disgusted
um
And yeah, it is often translated as I want to throw up. So it's a perfect
Perfect thing to be doing
Yes, the the line was actually unscripted
and it was a result of
Hideaki ono really wanted that actress to come like to have a good a good line at the end
And he had the voice actress who played shinji
actually strangle her
and then he told her
to
Imagine someone masturbating over her and what would she say at that moment and that's what she said
He's a guy. He's Andrew Hussie. He is Andrew Hussie
Uh, I to be honest with you I
Every single day I think about home stuck and I guess I my urge to get on the podcast goes
Like fucking like hotter and hotter. So Nate been get on it retard. Anyway, we're ready to go back to
By the way, do you like how this entire podcast up to like a couple of minutes ago?
Like I this wasn't even about me, but now it's like about me and I have stuff to say
Yeah, go ahead
All right, uh, I started to get into art and that
I I guess I should talk about pony because pony was like like it was a big part of me
But I didn't really like it that much
I thought it was okay, uh about the community
Like you and the other people that you the pcp literally shaped me and I don't know if I like that
I don't know if I'm okay with that
I think I'm gonna start again
I'm glad you're self aware enough to know that because one of my biggest concerns is always that
I'm going to inspire people
Uh, and they're not gonna realize why that could be a bad thing. You know, yeah
That's why I I always throw those little things where I say like do you really want to be like me?
Like I said in that one video like I aimed the camera down at myself and like do you want to be this guy, you know, because
It's like it's not just for self depreciation
But to like legitimately ask people like you know that if you try to act like me
I'm not like a normal like me. Yeah, I'm not a normal guy
Like I'm not someone who can show my face in public and you would think that guy is normal
Like I get weird looks, you know sometimes not often because I live in a pretty liberal area
But like I'm walking down the street. You get the neighborhood watch called on you. Yeah
that's
Well, they didn't call them on me, but they they they did
I well that was mostly because I was with a black guy. Uh, I think he had more to do with that than me
but um
Yeah, like I'm not a guy who
Like if you if you want to act like me you have to be ready for all that that comes with
You know, like can you be a person who lives in a room full of anime shit and lives off a youtube
Donations, you know, like yeah, which I mean when I said that in the video
I actually got a lot of people who were like, of course. I want to be like you. Are you kidding?
You seem happy with your life
But uh, yeah, thanks for letting me talk about what I wanted to talk about
Go ahead
I was just so happy to hear that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, uh, I got the first
Uh, the first ever like fandom thing I did. Do you know what brony breakdown is? I'm sure you do
No, I'm not sure. Oh the thing that paleo steno does with saberspot. Oh, yes, I do know about that
That was how tom got his career, right?
Yes, that was the
I was at the very fucking inception. I was at the sperm in the egg moment, dude
Really? I was at the and I immediately the second fucking episode. They're like, hey, dude
We got fan art by this guy named mucho and I was like, yes
I'm in
By my entire internet career. I have been the second the fucking second fiddle to a famous person
You're just you're you're not special digi
You're only you're only the latest in a string. Is that how you found tom because of brony breakdown?
Uh, yes, I think so
I I don't know like explicitly because of brony breakdown, but I know he was a friend with paleo
Yeah, well because they he had drawn some
Uh comic about scoodaloo
And they I like how you refer it to some comic about scoodaloo when to him
It's probably like the greatest thing that's ever happened and like the way he's tom hates everything. He's ever made
So I'm sure he would describe it the same way, but uh, he drew a comic about scoodaloo
And it was like his first major project thing and they invited him onto the show
This comic was a very long comic by the way. Yeah, it's like not not super long, but it wasn't like a like a fucking
It was a considerable effort that he'd spent like a year drawing, but uh, yeah
That's how he got on the show and that's where all of his brony career started
His brony career
It's a thing. It was it was legitimately a career
Yeah, yeah
God damn it. I wanted it so bad. I wanted it so bad
I
So I would always draw fan art for people and like I would always be friends with them, you know
I would always get there
It's just the right time where I would be able to be friends with everyone I met and drew fan art for
Just because I'm I'm such a likable and a good person
I mean, that's what the brony fandom was like. It was it was always like, hey, I made this thing for you
Let's talk and be pals, you know
Yeah
So I I would always uh
Do that and I remember there is uh, there was a moment
I don't I don't know if it was I think it was I just found out like I just started getting to you
But I was still with with tom and then started I have so much power
I can start influencing these people and I will have a proxy to spread my ideals
I can influence them and they will talk to it to their fucking mindless idiot fans
And I will be the one with the power
I will be the puppet master and they will be my puppets and I will make them do heinous acts
I will be
Yes
And then I realized now that's actually gay. I don't want to do that
Hmm, but one day I'm gonna make you shoot up a school digi mark my words
Uh, uh, that that's that's my brony really I only just drew fanner
You can you you can do this if you want to
go on uh
It's it's not it's not munchie is the tag you want to go on a king munchie
King munchie you go to derpy boo king munchie
You will find my old deviant shit. This is when I was using a mouse to draw
A mouse to draw on the fucking derpy burroo being the pony version of yeah gel burroo
Yeah
Whatever died anyway, dude, there's so many fucking images on bruh. It's crazy
Anyway, you can see all my old old shit there. There's not there's not anything for munchie, but there's there's shit for king munchie
Since munchie was already taken
uh
That's that's basically where I I don't update my art frequently
But but I should say that as an I don't post my art
I'm always drawn like every single day. I'm drawn, but I just never post it
Which I I been might get angry at me for but I I don't know
Uh, I I I've been doing a lot more through twitter
By my utumbler was atrocious because I would only
update once like a month
At most
I I would I would always be like hey guys. I'm sorry. Well, thank you for clicking on my youtube video
I'm sorry. Oh my god. I swear my schedule is gonna be better guys
V's michael here
I don't I don't want to talk about what what I remember from your tumblr because I feel like it would be embarrassing for you
What no, I don't I don't get embarrassed. I mostly remember you
Reblogging this one girl who you were like yeah, don't talk about that. That's what I thought
Oh, I don't get embarrassed
Five seconds later
Anyway, anyway, yeah, yeah, I refer to that as my gay period
Where I was just really gay
Oh, that's perfect
I know what you mean. I had a gay period when I was your age where I was just like
I'm gonna be friendly. That's fucking gay dude. It's really gay
Uh, anyway, yeah, there's there's my there's my pre pre-bescent. There is my gay and then there's my super
Super power. This is my superpower phase right now
I don't know what's gonna. I think it's gonna become uh super dad after superpower
Powerful dad powerful father. Maybe it's gonna be something with power and father in it. I know that that's what I'm gonna call my next
power
great name
I am power father
I've come to kick ass and chew bubblegum. Anyway, uh, what was I fucking? Oh, yeah
Anyway, twitter has been like a revolution for my for me
Doing anything because on top of it. There's some sort of resemblance of
Make like a post right that people will see
But on twitter, it's like
Yeah
And you can just do anything twitter is just shitting into the void. It's
Because the only time the only time a tweet matters is in the moment. It happens
And like whoever is there to see it
Then they can respond to it, but it leaves no lasting impression and it's gone, you know
All my tweets are hilarious though. I don't know if you see my tweets ever but my tweets are amazing
I read everything on twitter. So I see all your shit
You tend to tweet in large torrents of madness like yeah suddenly ten crazy completely different tweets in a row
You're very much along the lines of like drill in your twitter. Do you follow drill?
Oh, yeah, I follow it too. Yeah
Uh, it's either like right before bed. I just think I have so many ideas that I didn't think about until I can't think about anything else
So I just need to I just what what can I do twitter?
So it's always just weird fucking shit
Uh
I don't know a good way to think about this or to say way into this
I'm just gonna briefly mention it because it's like a side project. That's not really anything. Uh, I'm writing a
I wouldn't say a novel. I'm writing it. Uh, basically a fan fiction, but there's it's not a fandom. It's just a fan. It's just a fiction
of uh
Everything I hate about society
Oh god, is this your fucking manifesto? Is this what we're gonna be if I get to do an audiobook of this after you shoot up a school and kill yourself
Uh, it's called john major
it's about uh
It started out as a joke in tf2 where I would make it. My name's john major
I'm a video game soldier personally drafted by obama to eliminate all islams
That's what it started out as and then it grew into this this fucking
What if the future is the worst thing ever?
And and I just make all these yes
So it's just all my fucking anger about how terrible everyone is and all their flaws
But in the future that's okay, and it's it's like fucking celebrated. I see in the future
Uh, uh, e-sports have completely eclipsed normal sports and the super bowl gets like 300 viewers
Why does it still happen?
It just just cuz
Like a few traditionalists. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
And uh, like a civil war re-enactment
Exactly exactly
I'm not gonna go to the plot because it's not very interesting. I just want to mention it here because that's that's a lot of what I'm doing
That's that's the reason I'm so fucking weird is because I I'm I'm always looking for a new john major character
I'm always looking for a new fucking psycho for john to defeat
The whole plot is for john to eventually wipe out uh,
Muslims and and take down their their their video game bomb that will destroy all video games
Is this a future where
Muslim just applies to like everything bad in society?
It doesn't even refer to a religion anymore. It's just a catch-all. I could totally see that happening
Like the way that our world is going I could easily see muslim becoming that a catch-all for just bad things
Oh, that's pretty fucking hilarious
So so we have all these weird characters one of them is named sandy hook. She's a pirate
Go on
One of them is named darryl pluto. He's a fat guy who's sponsored by arby's and he has all this bling on him
And he's really fucking fat and he has like he's like jacks. But if he just never fucking did anything and they only ate arby's
How does he get jacked eating nothing but arby's
That's just that's just what he does, dude. That's just his power
Everyone has a gaming prowess and that's they're like super that's their like standability
That allows them to play video games differently. This is all like video game based by the way
So they they like they john is going to defeat them through video games. I was so unprepared for sandy hook
Perfect
Uh, we have a lot of shit like that
Really, you're just gonna have to wait until because the funny thing is we have been talking about john major for
Easily two years now. We haven't ridden anything. We're just coming up with new fucking characters for jaw to just come into contact with
Who is we?
I just told you i'm doing it with a team. Okay, not a team, but someone else. All right
Yeah, yeah, it's it's it's a coalition. It's a coalition
Uh, we're fucking uh, i'm proud that it's a collective. Didn't you realize did you? Oh you started this collective?
Yeah, but is uh, so is your main project anything like this at all? Is it at all this kind of edgy?
Insane just kind of edgy
No, no my my main project is very
It's it's a munchy, but it's not super munchy
Okay, it's is it more like munchy. Who's a curbie fan or munchy? Who's a uh?
Uh zodiac killer
Uh, munchy. Who's a curbie fan? I'm just gonna say this
It's about an alligator living in miami. Who's a private detective. Oh
That sounds fun. Are you good at like you seem like you you are creative enough that you could come up with mystery stories
Do you think that is true? Have I said a yes, uh
Really, I don't think it's gonna be a mystery. I think it's just gonna it's gonna be uh, it's gonna be a thriller, dude
It's gonna be it's gonna be uh, I'm gonna name it
gone
Because it's something's not there anymore. It's do you get it? Do you get it? It's a reference to me and jeff arguing about
What a mystery is right? Yes. This comes up every once in a while
Every time I mention the word mystery someone's like jeff's gonna kill you. I actually don't remember what we argued about so
I so don't give a fuck about what people think a mystery is
No effect on me that he doesn't think it's a mystery
It's gonna be a mystery in the same way the part four of jojo's a mystery
It's like you obviously know you're just here for the fucking crazy shit that's gonna happen in between the bad guy going to joe
I'm gonna say too much because it's it's bound to change and I'm not fucking courage myself
Well, I wanted to get out there. I know you know my policy. I don't talk about anything
I'm working on because did you listen to that pizza party podcast I was on
I
I got halfway through it and then I realized that wasn't you were the only person I could even remotely stand in that
Okay, so you don't think I should go back
No, no, you should I was just what I I found it boring
Um while I was there
But it was funny because I listened that the thing is they remove all the pauses like that
podcast was way longer than the one that actually got released like
Everyone was really low energy and everyone talked really slow and it'd be like so
Zootopia came out and the next guy'd be like
Yeah, I saw that it was pretty good. But then like they cut out all the pauses. So it'd be like zootopia came out
Yeah, I saw that it was pretty good. Yeah. Well, that was you know, like it all flowed so much better at the final recording
That I was like, this is not the podcast that was a part of
And I think they might have even sped it up slightly like just ever so slightly
Really because it just felt so much faster than what I remembered. I was like, this is not the same show
Do you think uh, you were accidentally watching youtube on your sega genesis?
No, I don't think so
I don't even owe to sega genesis
Just wondering because because I do that often I wake up. This isn't my fucking computer. It's a sega genesis
Also, I'm in the trash
I probably get out of here
Do
And we're back at mushy hq
Uh, the news today. I shot up another school
Good job. When will he stop?
When when when will the pain stop?
All right, mushy. Do you have any other things you want to talk about?
I mean, I I don't want to I
The things the things are boiling things are boiling when when the food will be ready to serve. I can't say but
I
Before 2017 things will have happened
Are 20
Don't say any dates. Just yeah, it'll happen
Let's leave it at that
When people ask me like, oh, are you ever gonna cover a full metal album? It'll happen. Yeah
I'm not saying it'll be this decade, but it'll happen
It'll it'll happen. We live long lives. You're only 15
You have all the fucking time in the what you're you're not even like even by current life expectancy predictions
You're not gonna die until the year 2100. You've got you've got a lot of time ahead of you to do this
So, uh, no one needs to be concerned
Yeah, it will happen while you're breathing
Unless you get hit by a truck, but you know, well tragedy
I'm I'm what you need to realize is that I could easily
Lift the truck. Yeah, I could I could lift the truck. You can hulk the truck
I think that happens in Avengers, right? He like hulk gets hit by a truck and he throws the adventures
I watch it because I want to be with my friends and also play smash with them and beat them
Yeah, that's something to say while playing splash. Yeah
You hear about the Avengers. No, fuck you kill yourself
You hear about the new episode of game of thrones. Oh, no, you're choking me
Bunchy is choking this character. No
I want an alternate version of game of thrones where you show up and just murder everyone
There's like it's like fucking homes like where gambling just starts murdering everyone for no reason. Yeah
Does that kid I don't I don't want to spoil myself. I'm not too. No. Well, it continues. Does it conclude? Of course not, right?
I remember when he killed like
Nepeta and everything and they were like and in everyone thought the most worthless character, but aqueous was the best character. So
Let's balance that
Uh, let me think let me let me think of a closing a closing settlement
um
If you think that I like you and and you found me through
This podcast or or through any of these podcasts. Can you think that I like you? I don't
Don't talk to me
and please
For the sake of all mankind kill yourselves
Please
I don't feel like you're memeing me. So I feel like this is serious. You really have had some annoying
There's this one guy. I'm not going to say his name for it for the sake of public humiliation
This guy this guy is fucking hey, dude
20 minutes later. Hey, dude
I'm so I don't I don't respond. I don't respond. Why why do you think I like him?
You should just type the name into the chat so I can know
Okay, I feel I must know these secrets
I need to know who to look out for
Okay, I don't know that person so
The person probably knows too is the best part
Well, that's why I'm always I'm always very careful to like when I'm when I really mean one person
I make it sound like I'm talking about 40 people that have all done it, you know
But uh, I'm just like, yeah, there's all these people who do this really annoying thing and it's like mostly like one guy
Who's really the worst?
Really
Just die
To all to all of the listeners out there
Everyone who listens to this
Please die. It doesn't have to be soon. You don't have to do it yourself. Just one day. Please be dead
Well, munchy, I know we plan on bringing you on more of these in spite of the negative attention you've been getting from the audience
I know we definitely want to have you on the homestuck one
If and when that happens, which hopefully I'll read it and try to get on that one myself
I'm rereading it dude. You better catch up. Oh, so you so you you still like it enough to re-read it. I'm taking notes
Yes, I love homestuck. Okay other than the I just fucking I'm just fucking ballistic and I hate everything about it
That's not the parts that I like
Yeah, I have homestuck is the best thing that's ever happened and the other half is uh,
It makes me want to actually be a zodiac
I
But only for Andrew Hussie
Yeah, but I love
No matter what he does with homestuck. I can't not like Hussie because I just idolize his work ethic too much
It is worth it or whatever. Who gives a fuck if he's turning out shit. He's turning out shit
I I miss his blogs. What happened to that. I miss when he would write stuff that wasn't homestuck. That was so cool
Remember fucking problems with remember whistles and it don't stop remember the fucking olive garden story
God damn it
It was beautiful. Hussie. What happened?
Why did toby
What what happened to him? You gotta give us the inside scoop dude. I know you're listening to this toby
I know you're a big fan of munchie. I know I know you're the one who's constantly pressing one one one in chat
I know it's you toby. Just let just let me just pee in me. What happened, dude
We did start this podcast with a whole undertale podcast, didn't we?
The best game ever one episode
So surely he's a big fan
Hey, I want to know
Uh, I mean, I'm sure you don't know the answer but when did that podcast come out and when did guys video come out?
That podcast came out in like december and guys video came out in like april
I see I see I see yeah
Uh
Thanks for having me on
Uh, this has cooled my temper. I decided that I will not uh get the bombs made today
I won't postpone it until I am uh hungry again
No problem. Glad to have you on munchie for yet another podcast
Uh, it's a fun surprise because we didn't tell anybody we were doing this so
No, this is a surprise for you as it is for me because I haven't been here. Hold on
What what why has my computer been on? Why is my mic been on digi? Is that you?
Holy shit, we've been podcasting and you had no idea. Oh my god, that's crazy
All right, I'm gonna go hang myself. Bye. All right. Bye. Bye