Panel number one, a demon fox?
Hello everybody and welcome to the Nauru Cast. I am your host, Mumkey Jones.
But I'm Mage, I guess.
And me and Mage right now, we decided, evidently, there is an opening slot here on the PCP for a new podcast.
I guess there is some other podcast on this channel that has moved to a different one, I don't know.
But Mage and I saw this as the perfect opportunity to start our own manga, anime book reviewing podcast.
But, you know, instead of doing it chapter by chapter or something stupid like that, we decided it would be better
to enrich our Naruto reading experience, to dissect this, to analyze this beautiful piece of art.
Panel by panel. So each week we're gonna review a new panel of the Naruto manga. How does that sound to you, Mage?
That's great because when you review it like by chapter, you miss out on all the wonderful art and detail that goes into each every panel.
So we're gonna go into very detailed stuff.
Yeah, because when you're doing it by chapter, you're gonna be more focused on like the plot and the characters.
And you really do miss out like the showmanship that goes into each panel. You know, how big should this individual panel be?
What will be happening? What is the art style we want to go for here? Where do we put the words? Are the words in Japanese?
I don't know. There's so many decisions that go into every little intricate detail of manga that people don't appreciate when you review it on a grand scale.
Yeah, they just take it for granted. Like, have you ever tried making a manga? You know how hard it is to make panels? That's an actual problem.
Yes. And we are blessed because the first panel of the Naruto manga is an entire page.
It's a full page. So we're gonna review the first panel and the first page at the same time.
Now up at the top, we have the introduction. You know, it's chapter one.
And what's interesting is that before the one, instead of like a number sign or something, they have this this ominous looking paw print.
Do you do you see what I'm looking at here? Yeah, yeah, I see it.
Now we don't know starting off because we're only looking at the the chapter number right now.
We don't know if this is the paw of like a wolf of a dog of a cat.
You know, we don't know what this is going to be, but I think having read this first panel,
I think this might be foreshadowing to what the first paragraph of the panel is going to tell us. Very subtle of them.
And then we have we have a colon and then it tells us the name of the chapter, which is Uzumaki Naruto.
With two exclamation points. Not three. It's very exciting. Not one. It's two.
Now, why do you now you're a bit of an artist, right, Mage?
Why do you think that the artist chose to do two
exclamation points instead of one or three? See, because one would not be enough and three just makes it like
it's kind of a bit too much.
So I'm guessing it seems like they're trying too hard.
Yeah, so I think like to find that perfect unique balance because you don't see people use two exclamation points.
If people always just kind of go between one or three or like infinity, but never two.
And you know, that's a pretty good angle because I think from the very beginning Naruto is trying to be original.
So even the number of exclamation points, you know, it the originality shines through even in something like the first chapter title.
Very interesting.
So now we move into there were
Four sentences on this page one in each corner and the center image is
Should we talk about the art first before we dive into the exposition?
We should we should read the text first because oh, okay. Yeah
Yeah, go ahead
Okay, so should I read out the first?
Oh, yeah, I think we should I think we should always read what's on the page since these are short enough
Yeah, okay. So like any manga we start reading from the right side rather than the left side
Now that always confused me as a kid because they always teach you you know with you know, English books
You read left to right. So I'm a kid. I'm sitting there holding this what I assume is a comic book
I don't know what Japan is. I don't know what a manga is or an anime as far as I know
Everything is just a cartoon or a comic book. So when I'm start reading this shit as a kid
It starts off, you know on the left. I'm like, well, that doesn't make any sense
It'd make more sense to start on the right. So
It's like a big cultural gap
And that's another thing that that I appreciate about this is that it stays true to Japanese culture to Japanese customs
And it teaches American kids our English kids
What have you about how cultures can have even something simple like reading can be completely
Backwards and different and I really like that. Yeah, I remember when in Latviania manga became a thing
Um, they had this sort of old warning that like, oh, you're supposed to read it that way not that way
But I think they only did it on popular manga like Dragon Ball Z and Naruto
The other mangas that I bought
They didn't have that warning but luckily for me. I already knew what manga was. So I knew how to read it. Yeah
You were a cultured child
Well, manga came in pretty late in telephony. So I was already a teen by that time
No longer. Oh, that's so unfortunate. You didn't get to grow up with Naruto
Uh
Kind of like I I discovered Naruto in my early teens when I discovered internet and it was actually one of the first
Animes I've watched
So I think it's the ideal gateway anime because it it opens you up to this wonderful world of Japanese cartoon
I absolutely loved Naruto when I was younger
Okay, so should we read this first sentence? Okay, you want to start?
Okay, I can it says once appeared a nine-tailed demon fox
Now this is interesting because and I know we don't want to dive into the art yet, but it looks like
It's it's kind of an abstract depiction of what I think this fox would be like
And it has these weird spirals coming off and if I count them one two three four
There's nine. Okay. So it's consistent with the words on the page. That's good. Yep
Uh, it it's mighty tails could crumble mountains and cause tsunamis
Well, okay, so
So it's setting up this concept of a giant evil demon fox now
Do you think that this is kind of
Ostracizing to a new viewer if they if they pick up a Naruto book and they see like this orange ninja
Who looks like he's having crazy adventures?
And then you open it up in the first panel is like talking about some weird mythology stuff with like a magic demon fox
Do you think that was kind of a risky move on the part of the artist?
Or do you think it's a good way to introduce us to the world of Naruto?
The art probably is confusing because when I first saw the the whole page
I I couldn't make heads or tails of what it was
But after reading the words and looking into the picture. I was like, oh, I see now
I see what they're what they're saying and
Like
It's it's a 50 50
I think on a lot of people it depends on how interested they are if they're just flipping through and they're
Probably just going to see
Like a mess and they're just going to you know skip it not bother to look into it
But those who stop and smell the roses so to speak will get treated to the nice little
imagery of the actual words on so
I don't know um
Do you want to move on to the next? Yeah
Okay, should I read it?
Yeah, yeah, go ahead to fight the demon the people assembled all the shinobi from the village
Now I don't know about you and this might be an issue with just the translation
But I think the word assembled is spelled wrong on this page. Is it spelled wrong for you too?
Oh, I I yeah now that you mentioned it it might be spelled wrong
They have it spelled a s s e n m b l e d
Now do you think that in the original japanese kanji that they spelled it wrong as well as some sort of symbolic reference to the people
Assembling although later on in the show and this will probably be a good
Since we're doing this panel by panel we'll probably get to this in about 80 years
But there's a great ninja war from all the different clans
And so this might be foreshadowing to how the people didn't actually assemble and that's why they spelled it wrong on purpose
as sort of you know
A symbolic way of saying these people might be assembling but as we all know that's not actually going to happen
Hmm
No, I think it might be just a spelling error on the translators part
You know, I think I think both of our hypotheses are equally possible. Well, yes, but at the same time, I'd like to believe that you know, um
It's kind of like you're going like you're giving too much stuff to it at least
How I see it made me
because
um
By the time they get to that part where this little hint makes sense, I think people would have forgotten that misspelling
That's a good point. That's a good point
All right, I'll move on to the third sentence. It says
One brave shinobi was able to seal up the demon but because of that he lost his life
Tragedy on the very first page. We have somebody dying
It it tells you that this is going to be a series of fights and death
And sorrow and sadness and violence and in the third sentence of the entire
Manga, we have we have a brave shinobi dying. What do you make of this?
Well, it is certainly tragic and once we get to the fourth sentence
I might talk a little bit more not about the tragedy but about the
All the whole thing. Um, I would just like to say that
The word shinobi first time comers would probably not know what it means
And no, no, I don't think do do the ever explain it. Um
Meet me. I think you you just kind of have to
Figure out on your own that kind of role looks like warrior ninja that kind of thing
Yeah, I think like
Now it's popular to say oh Naruto's a ninja and stuff like that
But in the manga they use the word shinobi
Which is I'm guessing that Japanese word for it or something like it or you know
Uh, but yeah for newcomers it might be confusing. Um, to
Uh be be uh assaulted right on the first page with unknown words with all this weird terminology
In the vernacular that you might not be accustomed to but again, that's just it's introducing us to a different culture
And I think it's an important thing
That's the second time on this page that Japanese culture has been you know thrust upon
non-Japanese
Readers but in a good way. Yes
And the final sentence in the bottom left corner says
That shinobi was called
The fourth hokage again
We're not only do we have the word shinobi again, but now we have something called a hokage, which you know as a reader
I don't have any idea what hokage is supposed to be let alone being the fourth
Yeah, but I think they actually do explain later on what a hokage is or what a kage is but
Unlike shinobi, which I'm not sure if they do or not
Right, but yeah, there's now there's two words right on the first page that the readers might not be familiar with
Right, it's opening them up to this whole new world where even the words are different
It's quite risky though a risky action for the translator because a lot of people might drop things if they feel like they can't
Understand what's going on and usually that's a result of using unknown words
It's what a lot of creative people suffer from when they try to explain the mechanics of their world
And right off the bat
But because people don't know the setting or the story or the characters or anything
They have no one or nothing to relate it to so this is just a big blurb
They can't really picture it in their heads and they don't understand what's going on
So yeah, at least it's only two words rather than like, you know four or five on the first page
And speaking of of setting up, you know the world of your fiction at the beginning
This you know panel this page consists of four sentences, but already we have so much lore
We have so much backstory so much exposition just from these four not that long sentences
We know that there's a magical demon fuck
So now we know we're thrust into a world where magic and demons exist and that there are
You know, there are different villages full of shinobi. We don't know what a shinobi is necessarily
But we can assume if they're gathering to fight there's some sort of warrior or fighter or something like that
We know that
You can seal demons with magic spells and that there is something called a hokage
And evidently there have been four of them and we can assume because the shinobi
Who sealed the demon became hokage that in some way being a hokage means you're very powerful or you're some sort of
Tragic hero something like that. So I think it's astonishing how
Miyamoto when he wrote this was able to
Have so much lore within four short sentences
Another thing the fourth sentence that I quite like is that instead of giving the character a name like, uh, you know
Bob or whatever
They specifically said this person was called the four of hokage
Which sounds like, you know a title the fourth something like the fourth president or something
So it means that this person's status is more important than this person's actual person
It's more important to the story to the plot to know what he is rather than who he is
And it's probably a good thing that they that they do that for two reasons one
You're right. It does establish that you know a hokage is a it's a title
That's more important than your name
But two and this might be spoilers for for 800,000 panels in the future
But when we find out who the fourth hokage actually was that's a huge turning point for naruto
So I think it's good that we keep this a secret all the way back from panel one. Yes
Now ready to talk a bit about the artwork now. Yes. I have quite a few things to say
Sheer go ahead
Okay, so like at the very bottom under the fox thing that we already established has nine tails and stuff like that
There's a there's a circle and within that circle
We can see an inches star that not a lot of people at least not first comers would be familiar with if they're not familiar with
Japanese culture and whatnot right but within that
Star you can see a figure standing on top of a frog that has a symbol on its belly. You see that
Yeah, yeah, do you do read japanese? Do you know what that symbol means?
Sadly, no, uh, I used to be familiar with a few
Symbols, but this is not a symbol unfamiliar with no
That's too bad. Somebody in the comments will have to let us know. Yes
And he is surrounded by little fire things which usually
Denotes like magic because they're floating fire things like wisps or whatever
So I'm assuming it's you know referencing how he sealed demon
And if you go back up to see right behind the the demon fox you can almost make out like a little
Sigil the word may be like a kind of not a circle
um
How many corners I can't really tell how many corners it is, but it's like uh
Well, it kind of looks like an alchemy circle
Yeah, it kind of almost looks like a seal which makes sense because this person is sealing up the demon
And the whole picture is connected like that
And basically now it's a go ahead. I'm sorry. Yeah, and it's basically just illustrating
Illustrating the force the four sentences we just read. That's why I wanted to read the sentences first rather than analyzing the image
Uh, I think it's a good thing that we're analyzing this one panel at a time because there's so many little details to the art that you know
I never would have even thought of before unless I was doing a show like this
But your description was pretty apt of you have the big ninja star and then the guy on the frog is standing in front of it
But what i'm noticing now is a bit of jesus imagery because the the shinobi
Ninja star is is sitting up in a way that it resembles, you know, the cross
You know, it's like, you know up and then across, you know, yeah
And it can also resemble, you know, the death of the person
Exactly because
The whole point of the cross is that jesus is making the ultimate sacrifice for the good of the people around him
And this shinobi is standing in front of this ninja star that is in the shape of a cross
So it's like he is sacrificing his life to save the people around him, which is exactly what he's doing
According to the text exactly. So that's crazy. He died to save others
That's just it's phenomenal. I never would have observed something like that
So do we have anything else we should talk about on this panel or should we should we save it for next time?
um
I think we're done here. I I just wanted to point out that um, I quite like the sort of messy inky look of this
It looks tattered and kind of old
Of like you're reading an old ninja scroll that is telling you stories of the past. Yes, it's very very messy very
Uh, maybe almost rushed in a way, but at the same time you can still make out the important details
And and also it's rather than written. It's illustrated. So anyone at any point any time from anywhere could
Try and understand what's going on
Yeah, it's kind of like when somebody messes up their hair on purpose to make it seem like they don't care about how their hair looks
You know, this art is kind of wacky and crazy and sloppy on purpose to resemble something greater
Maybe the chaos that the demon had brought upon the land
That's brilliant
All right. Well, everybody. Thank you for joining us for the naru cast where we review the naruto manga one panel at a time
I'm looking forward to the next one made. Should we do this daily?
Should we put these up once a day once a week once a month once an hour?
What do you think how often should we put these up? Let's keep it a surprise
Okay, okay. We'll keep it a surprise. We'll see you guys next time for panel two of chapter one
Of page two of naruto. I've been monkey jones and this has been mage