Hey everybody, welcome to yet another Pro Crastinators Podcast interview. Long, long fucking time coming, this one.
That's right.
I'm finally interviewing the man behind the channel, really.
Yeah, the man behind the curtain.
Definitely, it's like actually an official position now. You are the manager of the channel.
You always kind of were, but now it's like we actually have like a documentation that you get paid to be that guy.
That's true, and I am underpaid for all the work I do, but I understand that, and it's a passion project anyway, so I'm cool with it.
So what is it with the, like what the hell is the deal with the, you get these fucking feet away from me, you fucking dude.
I got my feet off sticking over his face, okay.
We're the same room by the way, he's visiting my house.
Yeah.
There you go, yeah.
Visiting Cincinnati.
Not doing video because this is three fucking hours long, and you know.
It's a hassle.
Who the fuck wants to render three hours? Who wants to look presentable for three hours?
That's the real thing, I don't know.
We both got our pants, like, riding all the way up into our crotches and shit, trying to expose as much leg as possible in this 99 degree house.
Hey, maybe that's the problem for you, dude. I look good as fuck. Everyone loves my legs. Check that Aromanga video.
Yeah, that's true. People love it.
So, Nate, you essentially started the PCP.
True.
Well, you're the one who sort of, I guess we all had this idea that it would happen, that we would have a podcast together.
And then we kind of sussed it out. You're the one who sort of took charge, started the channel.
And you've been on every episode but one.
The one that Nino was on.
Yeah.
Racist.
Nate is a goddamn racist.
Yeah, I would have been there too, if I had.
I was out of town in, like, Washington or something at the time.
And the funny thing about it is that, like, even though you've kind of been, like, even though you run the channel, you've been on every episode, you clearly have the most investment.
I don't think anybody realized it, like, until we started doing the Patreon, because we created, or you created, probably, a table of, like, who all had been on every episode.
And you're on all of them. We were like, what the fuck?
Oh, that actually wasn't me. The credit for that goes to the, like, the fans, the PCP fan chat.
They were the ones who actually made that.
But, yeah, it was interesting to look back at it and see how Nate, on every single one, except for one.
What is it, like, I want to know why? Like, why are you so into the PCP?
Because nobody else seems to give a fuck about it.
That is true. It's really simple, dude. It's really simple. It's that I see all of you guys as incredibly valuable resources that I am interested in maintaining, excuse me, a relationship with for, you know, for whatever purposes.
And so, you know, because, you know, we've been saying for a long time, we used to have this countless times, but, like, we are interested in the idea of doing projects together, in general.
And the PCP is, like, one, just, it's just an excuse to, like, keep us together, to keep us doing stuff and involved in each other's shit.
Because, you know, as you've seen, like, I'm the guy who generally pushes for what little space for collabs there is between us, like, in the Monster Musume video and stuff.
So, I'm more than any of it, because, you know, like, my dream job is what Red Letter Media does, having a crew running shit, you know, making stuff, like, having a...
It's like, they've got a life living with their friends, doing exactly what they want to do.
And, I don't know, like, they divvy up the work and the profits amongst themselves, and they've got incentives to succeed and play the game well.
And that seems to me like the perfect life. So, out of purely selfish reasons, I'm interested in keeping everybody together.
These people who are very talented, you know, all you guys, and have these skills that many of which I don't have, that are, you know, we fill each other's holes and stuff in a very gay way.
Yeah. Extra gay.
So, let me emphasize that.
That's right. Please. And that's really the long and short of it, you know.
Because, like, before the PCP, before we started that, like, we weren't doing anything together.
And we were hanging out in the fan chat, or not just, you know, like, a chat that we called Procrastinators, and that was fine.
But, and, you know, we've been saying, like, hey, we should do a podcast, we should do a podcast.
I mean, we had done podcasts together before.
The horse cast and whatnot.
Which is sort of how we understood that we would all, like, cause the horse cast were great.
And we all loved them, and we all thought that they were worthwhile, so it was, like, obviously we could do this together.
It was just that someone had to, like, go through the rigmarole of making a fucking channel and, like, naming it and doing all that shit.
And just knowing that it...
That's what I'm good at, actually doing the shit no one wants to do.
And it was a question of, like, how interested is any, like, whose channel is this going to be on, and if it's its own channel, how are we going to grow it?
Like, is any of our individual audiences going to care?
Cause, um, there's sort of a push and pull with the PCP, where this is, like, the greatest advantage and the greatest problem with it,
is that it inherently causes people to associate all of us with each other.
Right.
And this is, like, the benefit of that is that, um, you know, we have lots of cross promotion.
If we do collabs and people get it, people can become a fan of us as a group and stuff like that.
Uh, but then the negative parts are, like, that we just kind of get sucked into one another's enigma, in a way.
You know, like, uh, there's ways that our channels are all different, and they shouldn't necessarily be, like, having the same viewership and stuff like that.
It's right, right.
And so, in a way, it was a question at times, like, especially in the beginning of, like, well, I'm friends with best guy ever.
If we make a podcast, that makes perfect sense to each of us.
Sure.
But our audiences might have no idea who one another are.
Um, like, for me, the biggest problem with doing a podcast with you and Jesse, in particular, is that you guys are very edgy.
Uh, not, like, intentionally.
I don't mean to say, like, oh-
Remember, kill a kill one back in the day that you had to put a big disclaimer at the beginning of?
Yeah.
Well, just, like, what I mean by edgy is, like, not like you're going out of your way to be, but just like, you guys have no filter.
And I had always had, like, much more of a, you know, I'd never tried to be, like, politically incorrect to put it simply.
Um, especially back then, because I was coming out of the pony days.
And I was like, I was borderline SJW in some ways, you know, like, not that I, I believe in joking about other stuff.
I believe, like, hey, I don't have to think this stuff to talk about it.
And now I do, like, insufferable social media argument, which is beyond the impossible level.
You've had your journey along this road, yeah.
Because I see it as, like, if people don't get it, fuck them.
You know, it's not our job to make it understandable for them.
But back then, I was like, a lot of my audience isn't going to get this.
They're going to hear the constant misogyny jokes and be like, I don't like this and I'm upset that you participated this.
Well, you know, I mean, for me, I think a lot of it comes from, like, my many, many years spent on 4chan.
And I'll defend that place till the day I die because I love this little niche community of people who retell their own jokes endlessly.
Perfect the art of telling their fucking jokes.
And, you know, it is fun to have, like, a little area where, you know, you can make jokes that are incredibly offensive and everyone gets it and everyone's laughing.
And that's the thing about, I think the problem with 4chan is when people bring it out of 4chan.
Like, Jesse hates 4chan to death and he hates everything about it, but it wouldn't be a problem if those people were containing it in 4chan.
Sure.
And that's the thing is, like, when people defend 4chan, they always talk about, oh, the internet's the Wild Wild West.
It's the only place where you can be, like, everybody can be yourself.
It's like, yeah, do that there. That is the Wild Wild West.
The rest of the internet has been, it's been homesteaded.
You know, people are, you can't, like, the internet is real life now.
You know, like, Facebook, your whole family's on there, your job is on there, and the things you say have consequences in the real world.
So, like, you've got to deal with that.
We have to get into the specifics of, like, the particular issues here.
Because, like, if the issue is, like, people are saying shitty things to you in your YouTube comments section, like, what can you do?
Like, people are always going to be jerks.
If it's, like, them, like, giving you death threats, like, I mean, that's a different, we're having a different conversation at that point.
What I mean really is that, like, it used to be that people saw the internet as a place where you can just be an asshole because it's not the real world.
Even I don't subscribe to that.
But the internet is the real world now, you know, so it's like, rather than see the entire internet as, oh, it's a place where you can go to be an asshole,
no, the internet is the real world.
But 4chan is a place where you can just go be an asshole, and it should be that way.
When I, when I am on 4chan...
Just don't take it off 4chan.
When I'm on 4chan, I am a big shitposting piece of shit who's deliberately out there to make people angry.
When I log into my Gaia online account, you know, I'm a delight.
I'm a gentleman, a scholar.
I'm tipping my fedora all day, you know, when I'm not closing the pool.
It's just about, you know, knowing who your audience is, what company you're in, and because most of the internet is rampant autism, they don't know about it.
I was going to say, it's a lack of social awareness for what you're doing.
People who bring that kind of super edgy humor out of the proper context, that's their problem.
They're fucking up, and, you know, they'll be probably socially punished accordingly.
Guys like Jesse will shit on them and tell them to die and whatnot.
And, yeah, but like, I do want to talk to you about 4chan, because you are a long time 4chaner, and I am too.
Like, I've never been like a huge memer.
I've never been on B, like, at all.
I think I went there once, and never again.
Were you ever a B-tard?
I was really never a B-tard at any point.
Monkey's probably a bigger B-tard than I am.
I don't even think he is.
He was like an R9K guy.
Yeah, he was, wasn't he?
No, I've spent like 90%, 90% of my time on 4chan historically was on V.
And V is like B-light, in a way.
Like, V is the second most popular word.
V is at least on topic, though.
Well, I mean, the shit-poster would disagree.
They would complain about those fucking hot pocket eating mods,
not doing their goddamn job, keeping shit on topic.
Too many fucking E-celebs, man.
Yeah, I've spent...
V really is like its own little culture.
Well, I mean, that's what I love about 4chan in general.
Every board has its own culture.
I've got a friend, John, who's a gigantic TV board goer.
And all the time, he'll tell me about these jokes that...
I don't know how anyone lives on TV.
Monkey's a TV guy, too.
They've got their own culture, dude.
TV is awful.
It seems...
Okay, everyone says that...
That board is...
It's like literally...
It's literally 50% Bane posting.
And 50% is this Kino.
And that's every fucking thread.
You're missing the...
Oh, God, what's that guy's name?
Like, there's that pedophile from the Nickelodeon Network.
Like, there's posting about him all the time.
I don't know who you're talking about.
I mean, Bane posting's a bit...
I forget...
There's a fucking joke.
People from TV correct me in the comments.
I forget what it is.
Third Night Rises came out in, like, 2011.
It's become its own universe, dude.
It became real, as I think Monkey documented in one of his recent videos.
Yeah, the porno parody.
Well, the porno...
But even more than that, there was an incident of a plane crash with no survivors over Le Bain in France.
Oh, yeah.
And at the wreckage site, you could see, like, guys who look like Dr. Pavel and CIA in the crowd.
And the flight number was for you.
So, like, their efforts made this thing real.
It became real.
It was a...
What's the word?
It's like a standalone complex.
That's...
Yeah.
That's what it is.
So...
But yeah, so you've been on V forever.
Yeah.
And I was gonna say A, to a massive degree.
Yeah, I've been on A forever.
And also fit.
Those are the three boards that I historically went on.
Yeah, you worshiped the altar of Zizz.
I actually was...
I mean, I like Zizz.
I respect him.
He made some mistakes, which got him killed, unfortunately.
What did he die from?
Well, he had, like, a heart issue, and he was in a Bangladesh brothel.
And he was doing a bunch of, like, speed or something.
Of course.
What better fate for a member of fit...
It's a good way to go.
...than to die.
It's fucking taking his feet in a brothel in Bangladesh.
There's no every fit.
This is why you worship him.
Of course.
He lived the dream.
And he...
He died the dream.
He has, you know, he's heart cracked out.
His heart, like, blue or something.
But actually, you know, much more than Zizz...
Did he die balls deep?
I don't know, man.
I hope he died balls deep.
I don't know.
I don't know if that was in the police reports.
I'd like to find out, though.
You know, Monkey wants to travel to Isla Vista to interview the people to find out what was
really going down with Elliot that fateful day.
I got to go to Bangladesh and talk some prostitutes for a little bit.
But really, Scooby 1961, or just Scooby, is my real fitness hero, who I've been watching
for many years.
He is a god of fitness.
He taught me everything I know.
Like the sticky on fit has a link to a bunch of stuff that's relevant.
And I read Starting Strength and all that stuff.
But Scooby's videos were really what taught me, piece by piece.
And you know, I've got a long way to go.
So like, everyone says I'm really fit, but all I see is like all the inadequacies I still
have in terms of that shit.
I can lose 10 pounds.
What body are you trying to get?
I would like, well, I mean, I know what he's a meme, but like, like Vegan Gaines has a great
body or Jack's Blade has like a great body.
I like to get that.
Jack's Blade is like maximum, Jack's Blade is like 3% body fat cut.
Yeah.
I mean, he's super cut, which is great.
I don't know if you're trying to be like a cut guy.
I know I am going for a cut guy.
I'm purely interested in these sets.
And then you do have a long way to go.
I have no interest whatsoever in like functional strength.
Just don't give a shit.
I'm only interested in looking pretty.
So everybody, if you care about fitness, Scooby 1961 on YouTube, he's a god.
Let me tell you the quick pitch for this guy.
He cares about fitness incredibly, dedicatedly.
His whole life is devoted to it.
That's actually not true.
He's an engineer, which he, that's actually a great thing about the guy.
He's so able to devote his time efficiently between being a fucking engineer, which he's
retired of now, and just like builds a plane in his garage that he makes videos about.
And then fitness, which he does just as a pure passion thing.
And he's totally dedicated to doing it all for almost free, as little as possible.
Like he's about getting you fit for free, unlike those fucking six pack shortcuts, you
know, all those pieces of shit faggots.
They're trying to take advantage of people and this craze.
Scooby is a fucking philanthropist trying to better humanity and he's a hero for doing
so.
You ever end a Hodge Twins?
Actually, yeah, but I usually watch their, I watched a little bit of their fitness stuff.
I was always more interested in their, I'm doing the head shake thing.
They do, balls deep, them sugar walls.
Yeah.
I have watched a lot of their stuff.
I'm blowing up the fucking mic.
For fitness, a little bit, but Scooby's the best.
You can't do better than Scooby.
I think the, I think maybe part of the reason I've never gotten fit is that the only fitness
channel I follow is Bro Science.
It leads you down a dark path.
Yeah.
Well, because I had friends who were big into fitness and fit, so I know all these guys
are talking about just from them, but like the only one I actually followed was Bro Science.
Bro Science Life is just one of the funniest one, but he'll put you in, not T-Rex mode,
the opposite of T-Rex mode, where you only work out your upper body and don't do likes
or likes.
Well, they'll also put you into like heart attack at 30 mode, because it's all about
like drinking and during the weights and doing random shit.
You know, he's sometimes, guys who are intense into fitness can get a little too cut up in
the game.
You got to learn to enjoy life sometimes, and I'm just, I'm just saying Bro Science
Life is there to remind us of that sometimes.
So he serves, even though he's a big meme, he still serves a purpose, and he's, he's
a fit boy.
He's funny as hell.
Yeah, he's great.
Um, yeah, so you spent all that time on fit, you've got, you've learned how to be a fit
boy.
More or less, yeah.
Um, I'm surprised you're not going for Commina body.
Well, the thing, I've, oh, don't trust me, I've analyzed Commina's body.
Commina is really not that fit.
You can get way more fit than Commina's level.
Yeah.
But I mean, one of my goals in life is to be able to do a decent Commina cosplay, and
I've got-
I think you're close.
You just need to lose a little midsection weight.
That's true.
Yeah, yeah, and get a little tan.
I'm not doing the tattoos.
I don't know.
That's something I think about doing that.
I love Commina.
Want to be him?
He's my hero.
That was like-
There you go.
My brother Victor, like his whole high school career was, I got to get Commina's body and
get the tattoos.
One of those guys, yeah.
You know, I was never, um, uh, the guy who really got me, I started my whole fitness
journey and I, you know, went on and off of it, but it started in really an elementary
school and then I took a couple of years off just because I didn't know what the fuck
I was doing.
I went to an elementary school when I saw DBZ and, uh, specifically-
Everybody, man.
It was Goku.
Yeah, it's everybody.
Everybody who grew up on DBZ, like, what the hell?
It's, yeah, I didn't watch Dragon Ball, I had just seen DBZ and, uh, we had, we were
moving around, uh, my, you know, my parents were moving us around a little bit and we
didn't have cable for a long time and occasionally I had seen the show and, like, when I would
go over to a friend's house, see the show called Dragon Ball Z and I was like, what,
what is this thing?
This looks crazy.
Like, I remember being blown away by the fact that there were, like, a story that continued
between episodes.
Yeah.
This is my fucking mind, dude.
Um, and I just, one day we finally got cable and was finally able to, like, sit down and
be like, oh, so this is what the show is and it fucking expanded my horizons.
I was like, I want to, I want to train, I want to be strong like this guy.
So the first time I started going to the gym was when I was like, like, younger than 12,
like 10, and I didn't do it very long at that point, but that was when the seed was planted
that would, you know, bloom to an extent later on.
Do you think Dragon Ball Z has done more for fitness than Naruto has done for ramen?
Absolutely yes.
I mean, I have never eaten, this is personal, but I've never eaten ramen because of Naruto,
but I have worked out because of DBZ.
So that's, that's what I think.
Well, I have the opposite experience.
Oh, really?
I've never worked out a day in my life, but I've eaten tons of ramen.
The funny thing about ramen was, or about Naruto is how much it was because of Naruto.
I didn't even realize that Naruto was like a, was like a reference to like a thing in
ramen.
You would have known that if you read Shonen Jump because they explained it all the time.
I, well, I mean, I, I read, I mean, I read the Naruto chapters, but I didn't study them.
You didn't read all the little in-between shit in Shonen Jump.
Oh, okay.
So yeah, I never got the books.
I read it all online as soon as I, I got into Naruto kind of late.
Like it was after my whole adult swim phase.
What I meant by read Shonen Jump is like the actual magazine that was published in America.
I, um, that would have explained to me.
I remember the day that I realized that there was something funny about Naruto's name.
And it was when like years and years later, it was when Jiraiya dies, like a
way later in the series in Shippuden, um, when, uh, Naruto, yeah, when Jiraiya dies
and like there's a flashback to like how Jiraiya came up with Naruto's name.
And it shows him like eating ramen.
And he's got like the little stars with the swirls on him.
That's, you know, he's what a Naruto is.
The Naruto, yeah, it's a fish flake.
And see, that's still weird to me that that thing is a Naruto because I don't
even have that association in my brain.
I just think that it's this orange ninja man, but it's like, oh my God, he was
like named after a fucking ramen thing.
And that's why he loves ramen so much.
It's all connected.
Did you go back to chapter one at all?
I had no fucking idea.
Yeah.
Um, yeah, man.
So, so DBZ inspired it.
Yep.
Fit stoked the flames.
Yeah.
Now you're a fit boy, but you have firing.
I would say, would you say that you're, I mean, your origins as a fitness guy,
are obviously more aesthetic and psychological.
Yes.
But you talk about fitness more in a philosophical terms these days, I would say.
Sure.
Like it's good for like, if you want to maximize happiness in your life, yeah,
being a fit is a good way to help.
Well, in just the general, like humans should all be trying to better themselves.
Right.
Sure.
Which you, you go on about that kind of stuff a lot, but that's not really the
origin of why you're a fit boy.
Well, I mean, when I was 10, I wasn't really interested in the future of
humanity, you know, more selfish at the same time.
Exactly.
Yeah, that's fair.
So I'm curious about like, I mean, normally with these interviews, I sort of
towards the beginning go through your whole life.
So tell me about where you were born and to whom and why.
Sure.
What happened?
Yeah, I don't know how much this will be a repeat from the, the Ben interview,
because of course Ben St. is my older brother.
Ben mostly started from like college.
So.
Okay.
If you want to start younger or later at all.
Well, you know, okay, when I was a kid, my parents moved around a bunch and I know
Ben was kind of carted along with him, but that was when he was very young.
By the time I was born, we had moved back to, or maybe like just after.
What is the, what is the difference in age between you and Ben?
Ben and I are about two years difference.
So yeah, right about two years.
We had moved back to Massachusetts, or I think we lived in like Texas for a little
bit, moved around maybe a little bit, but soon after I was born, we moved back to
Massachusetts, essentially like where my parents had started from.
Because my dad, he's a psychologist and he was working for this company that had
like a lot of chains kind of across the country.
And so, you know, he just got shipped from a bunch of those around, but that,
that company closed down.
And so he moved back and started his own practice in, in Massachusetts.
So, you know, I grew up there in this kind of, in this town, Rehoboth, in this little,
it's kind of pretty rural, like there's lots of farms in the town and stuff.
It's, it's a pretty big town.
But like where we lived, there was like no kids anywhere nearby.
So all growing up, it was just me and my siblings.
You know, there's me, Ben, who's two years older, and my sister, Grace, who's four
years younger.
And so it was pretty much just us.
And I think it was because we were so kind of isolated that when video games got
introduced into our lives, and like we, when I was like five, I was big into
Power Rangers.
It's a huge TV guy.
And then when video games came along, it was like, holy shit.
Now I've got this whole thing I can actively participate in that's, that's
going to change my life.
Our, our uncle, my mom had a sister, Maggie, who died of leukemia when she
was young-ish.
And like her boyfriend, Chuck, I believe it was his name.
I haven't seen him in a long time.
But Maggie's boyfriend, Chuck, he gave us a original Nintendo console when we
were very young.
Just thought we'd enjoy it.
What year would this be?
This would be about 1994, 1995, maybe?
Super Nintendo's already out, but you've got a regular Nintendo.
I mean, you know, it might have been before that.
It might have been even before that.
I was born in 1990.
And Super Nintendo came out in like 1989.
I mean, this whole part of the story is hazy, because I don't really remember
like when these things happened.
We got a Super Nintendo sometime later, and then later on we would get like a
PlayStation, whatever.
We don't need to go into the specifics of all that, but like was introduced to
video games, was introduced into like TV shows, specifically like Power Rangers
made a big impact on me, as well as Transformers.
So right out of the gate, like Japanese stuff was like appealing to me on that
level, not that either of those is necessarily all Japanese, but not all.
Well, you know, they're Japanese in origin.
So that in Transformers is Japanese animated shit.
Right. Am I wrong about that?
It has Japanese animators on it, but it's it's an American show written by I
know, I know, like, you know, Hasbro makes Transformers and shit.
Right.
Okay.
Well, maybe I'm totally wrong then, but Power Rangers at least had its roots
in Japan. I'm trying to fucking connection here.
Did you get me out here?
I get out here.
I also grew up on Power Rangers and Beast Wars.
So like, yes, you know, okay, cool.
Yeah, I don't know.
I did that for a while.
I guess in school, in school, I was, I don't know, it was funny when I was like
a real young kid, and this is probably common.
I was a little bit more outgoing as I got older into middle school and high
school, I started to, I don't know, pull back and stuff a little bit.
I was more, I guess I'm kind of like I am now.
I was really focused on like achieving the stuff I wanted to do and didn't give
a fuck about the people around.
What did you want to do as a middle and high schooler?
I wanted to act.
I wanted to do films and well, not films, but I wanted to do stage plays and
stuff through, through mostly high school, but a little bit.
Well, in middle school, I started doing chorus and elementary school too.
But like, I was a big chorus guy through my entire childhood.
And this is something that hasn't really come up much in your content since the
Pony days, but you're a big musicals guy.
Yeah, I sure when, especially when I was a kid, I was really big into musicals.
And even now, you know, I've just enjoyed and listening to the music of
Hamilton quite a bit.
Oh, yeah, I'm not, I do like it a lot.
It's actually took a little while to grow on me.
The whole rapping thing, just it's not like typical musical fare.
So it's a little bit different the way I just do it.
But now that I've been kind of immersed in it, I am really enjoying it.
Though it's funny, my, my favorite song in the soundtrack is like what King
George sings, it's like the only like white song on the soundtrack.
So it's just like some dude singing like a classical musical.
And he's like the evil racist, you know, like slave driving evil king.
And he's got the best song in the album.
Of course you'd love that.
Of course I do. Of course.
That's that's me to a T right there.
Exactly.
Yeah, so I, you know, in high school was really when I when I started doing
bigger stuff and did did plays and musicals every single year.
Did a whole bunch of stuff.
I was some of your favorite musicals from from back in the day.
I mean, I really enjoyed Wicked, you know, people shit on Wicked.
I thought Wicked was I saw it on Broadway.
I went to me and we took a class trip at one point.
I think it was with like the musical or the performance, the theater group.
We went to New York and saw Wicked on Broadway and it was fucking sick.
It was dope.
Plus this girl who I liked was there and she was totally into it.
Was not into me, but she was there and I enjoyed having her near me.
So that made it a really good time.
Yeah, so that I don't know.
It was I just had a really good experience of musicals all through high school.
I know you like Jesus Christ, Superstar.
I fucking love Jesus Christ, Superstar Jesus Christ.
That's the meme song, but there's there's better ones.
It's it's not a meme.
It's a good song. OK, that's a good song.
But the best one is mine when you think of the name of the show.
The best one is the Overture, the opening song.
Exactly. That one.
I'm trying to remember how it goes.
Me too. Fuck, it's Judas is such a fucking badass.
Jesus, do you something, something or so?
Yeah, why'd you get your backwood chance?
It's such a strange land.
You'd have managed better if you'd had a play.
And now you're doing the meme song.
What? That's the meme song.
Oh, fuck, you're right.
That's a reprise from the opening song, I think, in the meme song.
God damn it. I can't fucking remember how it goes.
It's the one about Jesus, a Judas like being like, Jesus,
why are you fucking up? They're going to get mad.
Jesus, listen, won't you something my hand?
Oh, yeah, all I have is that I want us to live.
And remember, I've been your right hand man all along.
You have set the world on fire.
They think they found the new Messiah,
but they'll hurt you when they find they're wrong.
Judas is fucking dope in that musical.
Like the ones from the 70s, the new Broadway ones are kind of shitty.
I saw it.
What a singer that guy is.
I saw the I saw the newer Jesus Christ Superstar,
where it had the original Jesus, but everyone else is younger.
That guy's been playing Jesus for like a thousand years.
Yeah, I think he finally retired a little while ago,
but yeah, he's been into it.
I saw him with that, which was pretty good, except the Judas is white.
And I was not. Yeah, that's not good.
That's not OK. Judas had to be black.
Judas is evil, so he has to be black.
Oh, yeah, I apologize for that one.
That's beyond the line.
All right, so a joke.
Oh, why do black people have light palms?
Why do they have white palms?
Because there's a little good in everybody.
There you go, folks.
Enjoy that one.
I've actually heard that one from real racists.
Oh, I'm in trouble now.
I'm just playing, fam. I'm just playing.
I really have.
I really have heard that from real racist people.
But you see, that's the trouble about being such a big four-chan guy.
Yeah, I make a lot of racist jokes, and they are 100 percent ironic.
I mean, if you just listen to like the stuff I'm passionate about
philosophically, it's completely contrary to all this racist shit.
It's just so funny.
It is so funny to offend people.
So yeah, there you go.
It's it's funny, especially because, like, I'll say all that kind of stuff.
Yeah.
But I do it with, like, total self-awareness of the idea
that this is going to offend someone.
And you always do it in this way that's just like, like, you like,
you can't even understand that someone would get offended.
Yeah, that's true.
That's like, it almost feels like you're always kind of shocked
when people are, like, actually, like mad about something.
I just wish everyone were chill.
Yeah, I guess I wish everyone.
I wish that.
Yeah, I suppose I'm a little naive when it comes to that.
Yeah.
Anyway, so you in high school,
yes, musicals, theater, trying to become a theater boy.
Yeah, just I was there for really just the the sheer enjoyment of performing
on stage. So they really got you ever like a main guy?
I was a main guy the entire time.
I was by far the best male singer of the group and was always the lead man
every single time.
OK, and did any popularity come with that?
Yes, as a matter of fact, in high school, I had a fan club as it happens.
Wow.
They were a bunch of, well, I don't want to shed on them, but they were,
they would, I think they would agree.
They were kind of a creepy group of like three girls, no offense to them.
And you didn't manage to fuck any of them.
Oh, boy, we don't want to get into my sexual history, but let's just say
that I made a few mistakes along the way in terms of being a pussy.
Here, I'll give you one.
There was one time when my friend Jillian in high school came up to me and said,
Nate, look at me at this time.
I famously I had really long hair down to my waist like all throughout high school.
So this is and I wore these sick Kingdom Hearts arm bands,
one with the nobody symbol and one with the heartless symbol.
Yeah, dude, four years.
I can only laugh because you and Victor had the same exact high school life.
Yeah, we've identical.
And not to mention he also was in theater and got popular because of it.
I never got really popular.
I mean, he was also like a quiet dude who nobody really talked to.
Yeah, but then there was his most famous moment was like he did a play.
They were doing like some shitty drug PSA play or whatever.
And like, you know, nobody was like really taking it seriously.
But like the people in the audience weren't like we're just talking over at
the whole time that's fucking Victor just like snapped and gets up and like
lectures the audience on how they like, like, you know, I know like look,
none of us care about this either, but you can at least have respect and like,
you know, like listen to the thing and he became like like famous after that.
That's like an incident or something.
Hey, man, those those those what is the word I'm looking for?
Taking charge moments.
You know, that's what makes you a man.
But he also had long hair and wore like a black trench coat and shit.
So I mean, like he looked like he could be in section 13 or whatever.
Organization 13.
My I don't know.
I mean, I've talked about this before, but famously there was a pivotal moment
in my life that made me like this weirdo introverted guy.
I also was in like marching band through all college through all high school and
stuff.
But I was I was deeply anti-social and it was all because of this fucking movie.
One of my favorites of all time, Vampire Hunter D.
Bloodlust vampire fucking Hunter D.
Bloodlust changed my life in the worst way.
It made me think like, oh my God, D is such a fucking badass.
All I need to do is be like because like all the bitches and all like the men
in that shit are like he's so he's so stoic.
He's such a fucking badass.
You never said that he's a half vampire.
So like he has a magnetism that like literally mind control people to fall in love with.
I didn't get that.
I didn't get I didn't realize that just being quiet in the corner all the time
and like thinking you were such a badass would like not do anything alone.
You're not drawn by Yoshitaka Amato.
I know that was my problem right there.
So I spent my high school days.
It had some weird effects on me.
But yeah, I was just like I decided to stop talking in class because I wanted to be though,
you know, to some to be fair, some of this might just be an internal
rationalization for legitimate shyness that I don't want to cop to.
It's possible that's true, too.
I can't. I really don't know.
But that movie sure felt like a turning point in my life after I watched that.
It was too good. It was too fucking good, dude.
They brought to the is a crime.
It's a crime.
It owes me my sex life on high school back.
I want that back.
So you spent all that time trying to be cool of a serious and it backfired.
Yeah, did I mention that, you know, in addition to the Kingdom Hearts wristbands,
I wore weighted leg bands with like weights to make me strong at all times.
Did you learn that from DBZ?
Yeah, sure did. I was copying Goku.
I did a lot of that.
Did you, too? Yeah.
A lot of times I thought like, oh, like instead of like, you know, like working out,
I'll just have like some kind of innate training going on by like wearing something heavy.
A little bit. I mean, these were like five powders.
And then the thing was they were full of sand and like as I walked,
because I wore them all the time, they would get worn out and the sand would start to leak.
And like people would be like, where's this sand coming from?
And I don't fucking know, dude.
I have no idea where the sand's coming from.
You're going to have to ask somebody else about that.
It was fucking great. It was pretty good.
So so anything else you want to share about your early life or you want to move into college?
Yeah, anything else of interest.
Oh, I didn't finish that story about that girl that one time.
Yeah, it was just that.
So my friend Jillian came up to me and said, I'm going to take a piss.
You can just keep talking.
OK, I'll probably do that at some point, too.
There was a time when you see, right, so my friend Jillian walks up to me and says,
Nate, look over there at that girl standing in that doorway.
And I did. And there was a, you know, an attractive, blonde, curly haired girl standing there.
And she said, Nate, that is Jess and she likes you.
She wants to date you.
She said these like this was the time when God was giving me my chance.
And and I looked over, I made eye contact.
You know, actually, in my, no, I did not make eye contact.
I was too much of a pussy. I looked at her.
I looked her up and down and I said, OK, and then I turned back and started reading
my fucking animorphs or whatever again.
That's that's how I handled that situation,
which is just indicative of my social skills in general.
I have a lot of stories like that from all of my school.
I just really remember this one because it was so clear.
Like, Nate, there's your chance.
We're giving it to you.
And I just, you know, I just I'm such a different guy than I was back then.
Different, different times, man.
Thank God. Thank God we're all different.
Yep. Thank God none of us are like our high school.
I would not have been a fun person to hang out with in high school.
Me neither.
You know, to this day, I'm still kind of weirdly moody sometimes.
Like my reaction to being mad at people will be to walk outside and just stand
there and wait for hours until they come out and say, Nate, what's wrong?
I mean, not so much anymore, but I've seen you in I've seen you in like just kind
of this low simmer mode of like just annoyance.
Remember the time there's an like there's just a there's just a thread
of annoyance boiling on to the surface and you just can't quite talk to anybody.
That happens. I've seen that that happens.
Remember at Radcon, too, when I started cleaning obsessively?
Yeah, that that was one of those.
Yeah, that was how I chose to express my frustrate.
I don't even remember what it was about, but some frustration.
I just started walking around and was like, I started cleaning.
I didn't talk to anyone.
I just started cleaning up and everyone was like, what's happening?
What's going on here?
Yeah. And they were like, Nate, do you want some help?
And I'm like, yeah, sure.
You feel like helping.
Yeah, you know, I've got it.
But if you want to help, sure.
And and then other people joined in.
Yeah, I don't know.
That's just how everybody felt guilty.
Yeah, like they hadn't cleaned up and you were doing it.
I guess I guess it's kind of a passive aggressive thing I do to avoid
confrontation, which I wish I could change about myself.
But hey, I've been working on it.
I'm working on it.
Yeah.
Oh, so that's high school, I guess.
So that's pretty much high school.
So what would you study in college?
What did I study in college?
Oh, right.
When I started college, my plan was to become a doctor
because I really liked Blackjack.
Blackjack was like, again, my major life choices
controlled entirely by anime since birth.
I was like, Blackjack is so cool.
I want to be a doctor.
At least you had patrician taste.
That's true.
Like there's two characters like you weren't just trying.
And Blackjack.
Yeah, I mean, you had DBZ as a kid and that's fine.
Everybody gets DBZ.
Everyone needs an entry point.
But at least you weren't trying to be like Sasuke or something.
True, man.
You had like fucking D and Blackjack.
We're both bad asses.
It's not bad.
Yeah, they are, they are.
Both classic 90s OVA.
Why not 90s OVA for Blackjack?
Why had you seen so many 90s OVA as a teenager?
Shit, man.
I, you know, we got you into these.
I saw them all on On Demand.
They weren't available on any channel, but they were on On Demand for some reason.
And why were you allowed to buy On Demand movies?
Because they were free.
If they weren't free, I never would have seen that shit.
Me and my siblings spent a ton of time when we were young,
watching shit On Demand on our fucking TV cable plant.
And thank God, I mean, I never would have gotten into anime.
Yeah.
Wasn't for that in like the big way that I have now.
Because those, I mean, those were like stuff that you could maybe find at Blockbuster,
but it'd be hard.
I never paid for shit.
To this day, I don't buy any anime.
I don't do any of that.
I don't support the industry at all.
Yeah, why are you so into that philosophy of not supporting art?
Okay, I'll tell you why.
I'll explain this right now.
So I don't buy any anime ever.
And it's not like I'm opposed to it, but I just wouldn't even think about buying any of them.
And it's entirely because it is so easy for me to get them through like, you know, torrents and stuff.
I've just developed such a rhythm of doing it that way that it is way harder for me to do something like
even search Crunchyroll for a show I want to watch, even if it's free.
It is easier to me to get it downloaded and just have the file on my computer.
I mean, Crunchyroll aside, I mean, the only reason I use
Crunchyroll is that I find it easier than torrenting because when I want to watch something,
it's always spur of the moment.
And I just want to put it on and it be there.
I don't want it to wait for a download.
But like that is a hassle.
But like the only reason I would ever pay for anime now is just to put money into the industry.
You know, and like anime aside, because honestly, I don't think your money goes anywhere.
Like I don't blame you for not paying for anime.
But like, well, if it's like an album or something or like Patreon, you've never given to a page.
Never patron to anyone ever at any point.
And is it just a philosophy of like, like if you had lots of money, would you start doing it?
Oh, if I was like super rich and had no monetary concerns, I'd be happy to give away my money.
I would totally give it to the people who I think are doing like good work and deserve and like I want to see more.
Let's let's say in a year and a half.
Yeah, this is my prediction.
Yeah, this is my very optimistic, happy prediction for you.
Things are going pretty good right now.
Let's say in a year and a half, your student loans are completely paid off.
You're living entirely off of Patreon.
That's crazy. That's gonna happen.
Let's say you're making, let's say you're making, let's be fucking generous.
Sure.
Say you're making four grand a month.
Okay.
Uh, are you patroning people?
Absolutely not, no one.
Not a chance.
And I'll tell you why, it's because that is not a level where I'm like 100% set.
If I, I would need to be a millionaire probably before I'm like comfortable giving away any money.
And it's all, it all comes back to the fact that if I can get away with not paying for something,
I will do it.
I am entirely motivated by a desire to have as much resources as my disposal as I possibly can.
And like my survival and my well-being comes first before, you know, because I'm a big guy who's into
like, you know, like we were saying self-improvement and self-reliance and
you know, not, not like fucking over people to advance yourself with that.
I'm completely against, but you know, just, just bettering yourself is the way you can
better the world, is my philosophy.
So I really think it is, I mean, I probably take this to an excessive degree with my like
never patron anyone, just have no interest in that.
If the money went 100% to that person, I'll tell you, I would be 10 times more likely to do it
than the fact that any of it gets snagged up by Patreon.
I don't give a fuck about the Patreon people.
They're fucking suits.
I don't give a shit.
Even though they put on that millennial face about,
uh, what, so do you ever feel like guilty about the fact that you
profit off of the existence of anime, but don't put anything into it or anything like that?
No, I don't feel guilty about it at all, but I would, I would like to contribute.
I would like to.
Or like, like, like any of the YouTubers who like were a huge influence, like if Mr.
Beetong opened a Patreon, would you consider or just like, if you just had a PayPal donate link,
would you just like, throw in $15, you know?
I'll tell you this.
I would never do it.
Just like, I'm feeling like donating to Mr.
Beetong today.
If Mr. Beetong was like, guys, I'm going to be a full-time YouTuber.
I need to make $100,000, you know, whatever.
I need to raise that much for this project I'm thinking of.
That would tempt me much more, that if there's like-
Have you ever given to a kickstarter or anything?
Never.
Never?
I'm super frugal.
I don't give money to anyone.
Fuck everybody else.
I mean, I just, just to describe to the audience, like, I think you make the
at least the second most amount of money in the PCP is total.
At this point, yeah, at this point.
I don't know-
Though that was like, within like, that changed from like, yesterday to today.
So that's a very reasonable thing.
No, I don't just mean on Patreon.
I mean like, all together.
Oh, oh yeah.
Like, amount of money you make.
I have a real job that's like, I could live on my normal job for the rest of my life happily.
Right.
I mean, I don't, I don't know how much you want to say any specific numbers to try to
figure out if you make more than me or not.
I don't, I don't feel the need to do that.
I don't feel the need to do that.
Let's leave it ambiguous as to which of us is doing better.
That'll be more fun to speculate.
Well, the point is that I, I'm in your house right now.
And it is very clear to me that you are living well below your means.
Oh yeah, that's true.
Like, you could easily afford a much better place.
Yep.
I'm just going to describe to you-
This is the interview, but I'm going to describe the stuff that you want.
Okay.
Nate's entire apartment is three rooms.
And a bathroom.
That are all in a row.
So it's like, you start off in like, a little living room area.
No door is either.
No doors in the house.
So it's a little living room.
It goes right into the bedroom with a bathroom in the middle.
And then right into the kitchen, all the same size.
All about, let's say, oh, what, how long?
I'm just, I don't know, maybe, maybe like 40 to 50 feet long.
Is that accurate?
Is that good?
What?
You mean the whole house, right?
Are you talking about length, right?
Yeah, I was talking about one room.
I'm trying to think of one room size.
Oh, you took square footage.
I got no fucking idea, dude.
I did not know.
Each room's probably like-
Like it's a small-ish room, I guess.
8 by 12 feet or something.
Kind of high ceilings, I guess.
I don't know.
Anyway, point being, it's in like this kind of rinky-dink
apartment complex.
It's a shitty neighborhood in a shitty apartment complex,
for sure.
Yeah, definitely like the, like, it's weird that parts of it
don't seem so bad and then other parts do.
Well, it's because there's a university up the street.
Like, out on that back porch, it looks like shit.
Yeah.
But then out front, it looks fine.
But anyways, like, yeah, it's kind of a shitty neighborhood,
shitty apartment.
Yeah.
You can hear other people.
I'm sure other people.
Fuck it.
People can hear us.
Yeah.
You've got, there's not a lot of, like, furniture or anything.
Like, it's very bare bones.
Dude, like, your trip here has motivated me to actually get
some furniture.
Yeah.
So consider, like, half of what I got now just not here
before you got here.
Yeah.
More or less.
Like, what?
My chair, my chair, the chair you're sitting on right now
is a car seat from my car.
Yeah.
So that's the kind of shit you're doing.
That name brought in a couple of car seats.
So that was for me.
Like, you brought those in no way I was coming.
Yep.
That's right.
So I'm sitting in a car seat.
It's comfy though, right?
That's a good car seat.
And where did that other, like, you bought a new bed
and I'm sitting on your old one.
Well, you know, in fair, I had to mean to get a better bed
just because, like, mine was, it's like a, it's a twin.
It's like a small car.
I could not imagine that being my, like.
But you know, like, a week ago.
Like, like, that makes sense to me as a guest bed.
But the thought that you were sleeping on that full time
and you could easily afford a real bed.
A week ago, that was my permanent bed for the last,
like, one and a half years.
That's my bed.
I sleep on like a thousand dollar, you know, twin size.
This thing, this mattress, my, my good bed here.
Full size mattress.
My good mattress is like, was like 240 bucks.
And I was like, oh, shit, fuck.
I can't pay this much for a fucking mattress.
Do you not have any back issues or anything?
I'm fine.
I don't know.
Maybe it's because you work out.
Maybe it makes it easier.
I was thinking about that earlier.
Like, I was sitting on your bed and I was like.
Is that, is that bad shitty?
Is that bad?
It's not bad.
It's just that, like, I get bad back.
Like, I had like a really bad back pains
because I was on like just an average mattress
and in an average chair
when I literally sit or lay all day to do my job.
So I bought like the nicest bed and the nicest chair
and no more back problems.
But I suspect if you're healthy and you work out,
you don't have as many of those anymore.
It probably helps.
I mean, that's the thing.
Like, like it, your house is super Spartan,
but like it makes sense for, you're comfortable here.
Like, you don't care.
You're not even concerned about it.
This was the, like, yeah, as soon as I found this place,
this met my requirements.
It's got internet that actually wasn't as good
as I was hoping for, but it's still everything I need.
Which, that was like 90% of my concern
with getting the price.
Right, with internet.
It's in an area that is, dude,
you should have seen some of the places I was scoping out.
They were like shit, like garbage.
Like, I crack dealers.
Seemed like they would be infesting the woodwork.
I didn't see any, but they would have been there
if I had been there at night.
So this is like a decent neighborhood
compared to the places I was looking at.
But all I was concerned about was just like,
as low rent as possible, you know,
has the bare minimum.
It's got, this place is nice by comparison.
I'm happy with it.
I don't know, it's just great in winter.
It's just that it's below what would be my standard of living.
Yeah, I see your point.
Yeah, that's my thing.
So that's the kind of guy I am.
Even though we make about the same amount of money.
It's because all my money, all I give a shit about doing
is getting on that grind, making them videos,
and paying off my student loans.
That's what I'm, that's what I'm all about.
So if you, if you, let's say you pay off your student loans
tomorrow, somehow, they, they magically go away.
You leave your job, like because you live so frugal,
do you really need that much money on Patreon?
Like, because Ben is similar to you
and that Ben lives extremely frugally.
But Ben, like because of that,
like Ben only needs to make like $400 a month and like he,
that's, he's okay with that because he's, you know,
but you're kind of similar except that you want to have
all this overhead money.
I got ambitious for expanding operations all over the place.
I want to studio space because I do shit in my room here,
which is perfectly fine.
It's good.
But I want like a studio where I can have all my
shit ready to fucking go and make things whatever I want.
And that would probably be, you know,
in a separate location from my house.
Yeah, man.
And like, I'll tell you, like, I'm not as,
well, actually, I made a big post on my Patreon today
and you are a patron.
Yes, I read it.
Yeah.
So you know that like I'm not going to drop everything
as soon as I make like the amount that I'm asking for.
That is the goal for like survivability.
And that's, I might, I'll probably change to monthly soon,
so that's going to change as well.
But like I'm looking for like a middle-class lifestyle.
Like that, that is really what I'm shooting for.
And right now with my current job, I basically make that.
So I'm hoping to like emulate that because even though
I personally am willing to live super spartanly,
the bitches don't come for free.
You gots to have the green to make the scene.
And that's not a joke.
I want to have a place that will impress women
because that is what you have to do.
You got to do it.
If you want to play the game, that's what you need.
So, yeah, there you go.
I need to make a certain amount of money to have
the certain kind of lifestyle that I'm looking for.
And like, I want to be able to go out and do things.
I don't want to live like I did during me and Maffifa all the time,
just like only focused on turning out content every single day.
It'd be nice to have some time off.
That's the world I'm trying to escape right now.
Like I'm at your house because I'm trying to find a way out of this.
Literally all I do is make videos.
And I salute you for it.
It's exactly the right thing to do.
Yeah.
So, but let's say tomorrow your Patreon makes exactly what you make it work.
Do you leave your job?
The only reason the answer is no is because Patreon is inherently volatile.
And I'm afraid that that would change.
There's no job security with Patreon.
Let's say I would build up some savings first.
Let's say Patreon tomorrow is making 150% of what you make it work.
Do you leave your job?
I mean, that's great.
But what I would, I would definitely build up some savings first.
I would, I mean, plus I got to pay off my student loans.
I'm not doing anything till I pay those off in terms of, you know,
quitting my job and shit.
So I'm doing that.
Then I'm building up, like, I don't know the number,
but I'm going to save up some money because like, you know,
as you can tell, I'm an extremely careful planner, frugal guy.
Yeah.
I want security.
That is the defining characteristic of best guy ever in my, in my head is extreme planning.
I really think that the people say this, but I really think it's true.
I am, if you're seeing my girl in login video,
I am a Ross you who desperately, desperately wants to be a commune.
That's just, and I'm just not that guy yet.
Maybe one day, maybe one day.
I'm going to take this opportunity to take a piss.
Oh, well, that was fast.
Well, whatever.
We'll edit this out totally.
Talk about how cool my new glasses are.
Nate got some cool new glasses.
Yeah.
I'm not actually in front of the microphone yet.
Crank your volume audience.
Yeah.
Good thing you don't pay for this content anyways.
Fuck you.
I wonder if they can hear you pissing because you've left the door open.
I'm just so used to peeing, you know, alone and being naked in my apartment and shit.
It's weird having a guest.
Yeah.
In a goo, in a goo.
Doesn't matter.
I'm gay, so I will look at your pee pee.
Quality content.
This is high quality, high quality content.
Me a math if I never ends.
What do we do?
50.
Oh, it's only been 51 minutes.
Holy shit.
Fuck, I've gotten to my old.
Hey, we haven't gotten to college yet.
That's when chicken's great.
These interviews are always like, you never realize how long three hours is until you limit.
Yep.
Anyway, what I was about to say, yeah, like no one can really appreciate the level of
planning you do unless they work with you.
Dude, that's entirely true.
And the thing is like,
have you seen my new, the final meme of AFV yet?
Yeah.
Okay, so you saw the ending.
Yeah, I watched it today.
So in the ending, I announced like the ghost and the shell thing.
Which is hype as fuck.
And it's great.
And like, it's this goddamn pixel animation.
And I have told exactly zero people that I commissioned that like a year ago.
Yeah, well I knew.
Did you know, have I shown it to you?
Yeah, I've seen the pixel animation when you first got it made.
Okay, I probably did for hype purpose.
Just like show off to you guys.
You just showed me and Ben.
Yeah, that sounds right.
But I mean, I've shown like, no, like I've got several of those things
right now that are like various projects in the world.
The video parts of this video were filmed two and a half fucking years ago.
That's not true.
It's getting close to slightly over two years ago.
What?
The one piece one was, right?
The one piece one was filmed approximately
1.8 years ago and the ghost and the shell one was filmed 2.1 years ago.
I think that's about right.
Okay.
So over two years ago.
Yeah.
You filmed footage for this thing.
Yep.
And over a year ago, you commissioned all this pixel art animations for this thing.
That's right.
And it's still in the woodwork.
And it's not like I've been fucking around at all.
It's that I have a, I had to finish my goddamn degree
and my fucking full-time job.
I forgot you were working on that degree until like a couple months ago.
Yeah.
When I finished it in January.
It was when it was finally done for final good and all.
Holy shit.
I forgot you were still in school.
Yeah.
So we're just just for context people.
Remember.
So the MF of O would not have been possible before the time it happened.
Absolutely not.
Like I could have done it a couple months ago, I guess, but not by much.
Yeah.
Yep.
So to just give it like perspective, like the way I do content
is I have an idea and then I write a script.
There's no note taking, there's no planning, except for when I do like if I go into a show
and tending to write about it, I might take a bunch of notes.
But it's at best like a whiteboard full, you know.
Yeah.
You will come into like a podcast with pages.
I mean, if you guys have watched the Aromanga podcast, you'll see that Nate had four pages
of printed notes, granted lots of space that you should.
Yeah, that's right.
That could have probably fit on a page and a half.
But like, yeah, he comes in with shitloads of notes, you know, always doing like double
checking prep.
I think you always read the one piece chapters more than once for podcast.
That's right.
And sometimes you'll even go back and read older chapters just to be completely sure
that you remember what you're talking about.
That's 100% accurate.
Yep.
The fucking Kingdom Hearts lecture.
Yeah.
You spent like three hours just drawing that whiteboard.
And it didn't turn out great.
It looked great.
Yeah.
I mean, you had to make sure I was correct.
You probably spent half an hour just recreating the fucking logo at the top.
That's true.
That did take a while.
I wanted that to be good.
And like had like extensive notes.
Like it's just, it's just funny to see the way you work because like, you know, yeah,
I can watch you do all that.
And then you'll have like me and Jesse who will literally sit down in front of a camera
and just stream of consciousness, a bunch of bullshit.
And like, yeah.
Do you think it's, how much of the note taking do you think is like that you have to do it?
And how much of it is just confidence boosting?
It depends on what the topic is.
Like every PCP, you know, I'm like the biggest talker on the PCP.
And I don't do any preparation for that stuff.
You know, that's like, that's like my fun.
That's what I do for fun.
So I'm able to do that sort of stuff when I want to.
But like, I don't go into my main projects, I guess that projects into like the Aromanga stuff.
Like I have a philosophy where I really hold myself to a high standard of like accuracy.
Because I think about like what I ask for other people when they're talking about a show is,
I don't want people to be fucking or if you're talking about Aromanga and you're criticizing
Aromanga, I expect you to know your shit.
I expect you to be accurate.
And to a certain extent, I think guys like you and Jesse are just like better at understanding
things quickly and easily.
Whereas I think I need, I always think of them in Bakuman.
I always think of I'm more like Ashiro Gimuto.
The guys who think they describe like they are not the our tours.
They are the hard worker.
Think about things over a thousand times.
I mean, if we're going to bring up the Bakuman thing.
Like I read through it in 2014 and was constantly comparing everybody to the PCP.
Yeah.
And you and Ben were Muta Ashiro G, especially since you were actually working together at the time.
That's right.
But like, both of you definitely have the philosophy of like,
you know, coming to meet the audience and like just working extra, extra hard.
And like, it's not about like, to you, it's about making videos, not necessarily about what the videos are.
I'm interested in telling a story.
And like in my in my case, like the anime is my medium to tell my story or to like make a point.
It's like you, you're not doing it in like this idea of like, I have a grand vision from the beginning.
I mean, you, you, sometimes, sometimes, I would say that the way you create videos is like,
I don't want to say based on a template, but it's like, you look at what is like,
what even is a YouTube video.
And then you like make that kind of, you know?
I suppose so.
Like, like, like, like the Guru in the Gaon one is heavily influenced by that Mr. Beetong video
that you had so much respect for.
Right.
You know.
And like me and Mathova is like this idea of let's try to make this
more easily made and consumable content that could come out every day.
Right.
You know, it's, it's more about this like experimentation than it is about creating the specific video,
which is like the opposite of Jesse, where Jesse is like,
doesn't care what YouTube is.
He just wants to make his thing, like whatever he, exactly how he came up with it, you know,
which is kind of why he doesn't have the YouTube success.
Well, you know, I would argue that I have become more in tune with that as I've gone on, that I,
I feel a lot like Jesse a lot of the time when I'm making content.
But you know, I mean, my recent success starting with Galco, you know, that was me playing the
game of YouTube more.
I mean, the video itself was when I'm making an idea for video, I'm really at that point
not thinking about what YouTube wants out of it.
I am, I, you know, when I was writing that script, for example, I was only thinking like,
I watched Galco.
Wow, it was really good.
Had these thoughts about it, wrote them down.
And then I'm sure there was some, you know, decision making as to like what to include,
you know, based on it's going to be a fucking video.
So I got to put the shit in it that makes sense.
But it's, it's after the video is really the writing and editing are done to amuse me, you know.
And I mean, that video had an editor snooping turtle.
Oh God, I hope I got that right.
And he did great work.
He was wonderful to work with.
But I was approving like every step of the way.
He would show me like a minute, he was like, how was this, you know, is this good?
And I would be like, okay, tweak these things.
So, you know, I was involved in the whole process there.
And it really, like the whole point of that video was kind of to get to that end shot
and to like make that little speech at the end.
Like I make entertaining videos as an excuse to lecture people about things I think.
Like that's really what it comes down to.
And I'm going to find a way to do it no matter what.
That's what I'm interested in YouTube.
Like YouTube is my way to feel like I'm making a difference in the world in a way that I enjoy,
which is great.
But, but just to get back to the original point here.
I felt like for a long time I wasn't making content that was really working with YouTube very well.
Like the, like you're looking part two.
I was definitely like I was doing something very similar with Mr. Betung had done.
But I don't feel like I was copying him.
I just felt like my ideas were all inspired by it.
But I mean, like at the time, there was definitely, and we all in the PCP had this.
And still due to some extent, though, it's waning away as time goes on.
We had this intense respect for like what we saw as the ultimate type of video,
which was the 45 minute, in-depth, highly edited analysis that covers everything.
Like that was kind of what we, we worshiped.
You had a Cantorlot wedding by Anthony C was like your favorite and the Mr. Betung video.
Climax is fucking unbelievable.
The classic Mr. Plinkett videos, the Star Wars reviews that we all sort of look up to,
Egoraptor Sequelitis, which was my big one, you know, in the beginning.
So like all of us could kind of gotten into analysis videos by way of
these gigantic, epic 45 minute, highly edited videos.
And we all did ours.
You know, I did the sort of online videos, YMS, another good example.
Right, yeah, yeah.
I did the sort of online videos in the Astroscore.
Movie Bob, another hero of ours, yeah.
I'm joking, I don't.
I mean really that good is kind of this kind of video.
You see, I actually have no idea what his content's like.
I just hear people shit on him, so that's what that joke's based on.
I actually did take a lot of influence from Movie Bob.
Hey, okay, there you go.
In your physique, I'm assuming you mean it.
Hey, hey, hey, I'm fat and dangerous.
That man is gross.
He's pretty fat and dangerous himself.
He is disgusting.
Especially to those fucking men's rights piece of shit.
Watch out for Bob Chippman, he'll fuck you up.
Anyway, you did the Girl in the Gone video.
Jesse had like the horseshoe reviews and the horseshoe finale.
And like that was kind of like at the time just the atmosphere of what we thought
like a YouTube video was supposed to be.
And like because we liked it so much, we thought surely this is what everybody wants.
Matthew Matosis was out by this point.
Right.
And then like there was just kind of a moment where it became apparent
that no one wants that anymore.
Well, you know, it's funny that you're saying it this way.
Like these things I think were apparent to you.
And the rest of us, I think you've always been ahead of the curve when it comes.
I mean, because this is what you do.
You're a YouTube guy on, you know, in serious ways.
Right, of course.
And to some extent, and like, you know, like the Galco video was titled
and thumbnailed the way it was, because basically of your suggestions, you know,
and it worked incredibly well.
If I had just called that best anime ever, Oh Shit to Galco Chan,
would not have worked, would not have happened.
And Mia Mafova was, that was me saying like what I'm doing is just really not working
the way that I wanted it to.
Like I wanted, like if I had kept doing what I was doing, you know, to that degree,
and maybe I'll fuck up and keep going and go back to that.
But because Mia Mafova just fucking ended.
I got to emphasize this to the audience.
Like the the PCP, like the concept of us as a group is that we're YouTubers.
Like we are friends who are YouTubers.
And a lot of what we talk about is how we're doing our jobs.
Right.
Like I don't know what, like it's hard for me to imagine what other people think we
do in the PCP.
Like is it just a, I don't know.
Oh, what's the word?
Bust a link.
Yeah, we're all just burst leaking out there.
And I mean, yeah, we have lots of just casual conversations and shit around.
But like, I would say, especially for for a long time, the bulk of what we talked about
was YouTube, like what we're doing, how we're doing it, what we should be doing,
sharing ideas and advice and stuff like that.
Complaining when it's going bad and.
Yeah, bitching about commenters.
This is like probably 80% of all the interactions we've had.
Anyway, like we, you know, but the point, like the reason we're all friends is that
we're doing the same job and it's a weird job that not a lot of people have, you know,
and so there's not so many people you can relate to about it.
And like, yeah, sort of when, when we all stopped doing Pony and we moved out into our
own channels, we all kind of were doing our own thing in a way and it was very much like,
let's share notes, like how is it working for you?
It's not really working for me.
Why is it working for you?
Oh, I'm doing this.
Oh, well, you know, I don't know if I want to do that.
You know, and like a lot, I would say the last year or so has been a lot of me growing
more and more successful and going, guys, this is what I'm doing.
This is what I'm doing.
Everybody else going, I don't know, man, I can probably make it without doing that.
That a year later going, okay, I didn't make it doing that.
So you're really describing me.
You're really describing me.
Not just you, like Jesse and Hippo are very, like, Jesse started up not a review,
essentially, for that reason.
Still not committed to, I think, a-
But it's, it's, Jesse knows-
No, man, Jesse, I love you, brother.
Jesse knows what to do, though.
It's just that he-
I think Jesse just, he feels like an anger that he has to change to adapt to YouTube,
whereas I am not coming back.
And also it's just that his life is so all over the place that he,
Jesse will just blink off the map for a month, you know, and like, you can't do that.
Yeah, he's tough to schedule things when you're-
Right.
He'll come in and do, like, a whole month of perfectly tailored YouTube content,
but then he'll stop for a month, you know.
He would say that, like, a lot of that recently was due to his basement
flooding and fucking up his life.
I mean, that's what I'm saying.
His life situation is always the main reason.
Like, Jesse, the man goes through hard times, you know.
But like, it's because he never just fully commits to,
I'm gonna be a YouTuber now.
He'll do it for a little while.
I mean, he still goes on about, like,
I can't wait to escape this fucking hellhole of YouTube.
Yeah, well, he hates YouTube, you know.
So like, but like, he also, if you look at the way
his thumbnails and titles have changed over time,
you can tell he's trying to do the thing.
The not-of-our-view is, like, my Japanese anime,
some of those he works, I mean, you know, for YouTube,
he works too hard on them.
But like, as putting that aside, the length is great,
those are really good videos, and like, even he acknowledged,
like, that was his most successful channel.
He's always said that my Japanese anime is the one he wants to protect
from his bullshit.
Like, he tries his hardest to make sure
nothing that gets posted there is completely retarded.
So far, so good, I think.
Yeah.
But it's definitely been, like, a thing amongst the PCP
that, like, I've been kind of being like,
guys, we have to change.
The only person who, like, immediately did it is Jeff,
who then blasted past everybody.
Like, if you look at the early Jeff videos,
like, whatever you see as a difference
in the titles and thumbnails, I taught him that.
He just took it farther than I was willing to.
You know?
Like, respect that to some degree.
He's even worse than that is Lachlan Still,
who is a monster.
I don't know if you watched The Pedantic Romantic at all.
Oh, right.
I forget that that's the same guy.
He's blowing up, you know?
He blew up because he's using, like, the dirtiest tactics
because he loves it.
Because he sees it as like a-
He's a Jeff type, I guess.
Dude, he literally will make, like, videos of nothing to do
with Sword Art Online, and like, he made one that's called
Sword Art Online is not what this video is about,
and it's literally just a review of a different show.
20,000 views, because Sword Art Online's in the title.
That's some next level shit.
Yeah, he doesn't give a single fuck.
I should make a Sword Art Online video.
You should.
It's free.
I'm not going to.
I'm not going to do it.
I can't do it.
You don't even have to make it actually about Sword Art Online.
Just give it a title, and says it's Sword Art Online.
I don't know if I have it in me.
It's literally free views,
and like, Lachlan took it to such a fucking extreme.
But I mean, this is basically just like,
everyone taking the stuff that I was preaching,
and just going even farther with it, you know?
That's great and all, and then that's totally cool.
But one thing I wonder about is,
if everyone's just copying you all the time,
with the bubble break, I think so.
Yeah, when's the bubble break?
Well, that's why I love MiaMath of us so much,
because when I look at Jeff,
I think Jeff's got a big problem where he shills so much,
and everyone really hates it.
People are getting annoyed, yeah.
And he doesn't, I don't know if it's just because
he has enough people who like him anyways,
that I mean, you know,
I have lots of people who hate my videos.
Sure. People who turn on me.
So, you know.
Couple of heroic YouTubers outfinding the crusade
against the egotistical DigiBro.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, a couple of valiant YouTubers
who are fighting the Great Battle.
Who is this enigmatic man?
I just don't know.
But like, you know, Jeff definitely has an issue
where like, he's gotten to a point
where there's a significant amount of his fan base
who like, hates him now.
His fan base you're saying.
Yeah, like people who are big fans who are leaving him
because they can't take the shilling,
and they can't take the constant YouTube algorithm playing.
You know, like, I do it.
I even tell people I'm doing it.
I give people the blueprint of how to do it like me.
That self-awareness goes a long way.
Yeah, exactly.
And like, and the fact that I'm like,
telling people how to do it,
and then not doing it a lot of the time also helps.
It makes people think you have integrity.
Right, whereas Jeff, like, people don't think he does,
you know, because he's not being open about it,
and he's going so far.
And with Lachlan, I mean, he's obviously just having fun,
and he's trying to grow his channel as big as,
as fast as possible, because he's trying to also leave,
you know, be a full-time YouTuber.
But like, I can see him adapting, changing with the times.
But like, what's so great about me in Mavva
is that you basically did it without copying me.
Without being.
Without copying anybody.
Like, me and Mavva, most of these videos are totally.
Well, some would argue Fantano was ripped off at a time or two.
Sure.
I mean, you definitely.
Fuck you, Mellonhead.
This is my shit now.
You copied plenty of little things from other people,
but like, there's some stuff in there.
The fucking Final Fantasy Songs video,
I can't believe it.
I've never seen someone do that before.
Like, just seeing the background music of their video.
That's the funny thing about me.
I am a genius, but I am such a perfectionist
that all my genius ideas get bottled up,
and they don't come out.
Which is why somebody like me in Mavva
is such a great thing for a guy like me.
Right.
Well, it's such a good testing ground,
because like, I watched that video,
and like, I don't think it worked
just because the picture was too close.
The mixing was fucked.
Yeah, it was messed up.
But like, I was like,
but this is a formula you could do with anything.
Like, you could have a whole channel that's just this.
Yep.
You know, like, I'm thinking about Smooth McGroove.
That dude's been around for like five years now,
and he makes one kind of video,
which is a dude singing acapella
in eight different screens.
Like, me and Mavva,
there's probably about seven video templates
in there in total,
and any one of those could have been a whole channel.
Right.
You know, like, you could have a whole channel
of super energetic workout guy reviews,
random manga.
Yeah.
You could have a whole channel of like,
Nate does Let's Plays or whatever.
The great thing about it,
yeah, that's really cool.
I do like that about it.
And the great thing is people are really starting
to get invested in me as a person,
as a creator,
and they see legitimately that I,
like, I'm not,
I'm not fucking around.
I've got a lot of fucking ideas
that I want to share with people.
It was really the Angels Egg video
that where I, like,
where it was like,
it was all crashing down on me,
like, that I was like,
oh my god,
I didn't realize that I desperately want
a video from Nate every day.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, I, because I,
I just have always thought that you would never do this.
Like, the whole time I've known you,
you've been the perfectionist guy,
the iceman six months on a video guy,
and all those videos are great,
but like, I don't know,
I guess when you see someone doing that,
you kind of assume that the,
like, the amount of time spent
is a consequence of the greatness.
Like, like, you couldn't make a great video
in three days.
You have to put in that much work.
Right.
And then seeing me in math,
I was like, no, this guy could do it.
Like, he could,
you could put out videos as frequently as I do,
and they'd be at least as good as mine.
You know, so like,
that was kind of the thing,
and it was Angel's Egg that brought that on me,
that I was like,
he's just talking unscripted about this movie,
and I'm super interested, you know,
like, especially because it was a movie that,
I'm sorry for talking so much
through Nate's interview,
not that any of the audience expected it to be.
This is relevant.
Yeah, but everyone knows.
Everyone knows what to expect.
Yeah.
But, and I talked to you about this.
Right.
Like, fucking Demolition D two years ago
announced he was going to do an Angel's Egg analysis,
and he was working on it,
and like, this dude talked,
I mean, he talked about it forever.
He was like, it's one of his favorite movies,
and I watched Angel's Egg in like 2008
while like, barely awake,
and like, I didn't understand any of it.
Right.
I just watched it and I was like,
well, that was fucking weird.
She was.
I had no idea what happened, right?
I mean, I thought it was cool,
but no real opinion.
I just went, oh, it's another Mamoru Oshii thing,
because they're all like that.
So quirky.
Yeah.
So like, he's saying he's going to do this,
and I was super hyped for it.
I was like, dude, fuck yeah,
because he's only really done like,
one serious analytical video,
which was the Eva vs. Rebuilds,
which was a great video series.
It was.
So I was like, man,
I'm so hyped for Demo to get like,
legit again, you know,
and he was talking about it,
and then he kept putting it off
to do other things,
to do like,
fucking Himoto,
Himatuchan,
who the fuck cares.
That video's a little bit of a disgrace.
No, I take it back.
I love you, Demo.
Please come back.
I worship you.
But like, he'll come back
and do like a little thing here and there,
and then he just like,
blinks off the map,
and the thing is,
I was following his Twitter,
and he was like,
he literally can.
I mean, he's gone.
He's gone.
Been over a year since his last video.
Yeah, and he doesn't even tweet anymore,
or livestream.
Really?
No, he's still livestreams.
That's not true.
People, yeah, he does stream.
Well, he, for a while,
he was talking about the Angels Egg video on Twitter,
and he was like posting screencaps of like,
I guess there was some kind of compression problem
with this video,
so it kind of had like artifacts in it.
Oh, so he gave up on the project.
Yeah.
Like a pussy.
Like, he couldn't figure out
how to encode the video, right?
And like, I think he lost some of it at some point,
and then just like gave up.
I mean, I would feel the temptation
to give up at a point like that, too.
Yeah, and I even like,
brought it up to him in like,
Nino's livestreams that he was in.
I was like,
hey, when's the Angels Egg video coming?
And he's like, uh, I don't know, man.
Like, and so I'm sitting here like two years later,
like, I really wanted this video
because no one else has stepped up
and explained Angels Egg.
And I've had people ask me to do it.
Have people be like,
hey, you ever thought about doing a video on Angels Egg?
And I've told them,
demo's working on one.
So I'm not going to do it
because he's going to do it.
And he already has,
like, if I just go watch this movie
and like try to make an analysis,
like, who's to say if I'm even going to find
the real meaning of it?
Like, this dude clearly found something meaningful
and that's why he wanted to make a video,
which you also did.
I mean, full disclosure,
I did research to understand what was going on.
It's not like I understood it immediately myself.
But you watched it
and desperately wanted to understand.
Like, as soon as I finished,
I was like, I need to know
what the fuck is going on.
Because you care a lot about
Yoshitaka Amano's art.
Yeah.
You are obviously very into the visuals of the movie.
This is the best Yoshitaka Amano film.
So.
And Bloodlust, the one that ruined my life,
is another one.
And I'm saying this one's better.
So there you go.
Did you ever watch A Thousand One Nights?
No, but I really want to.
I will one time.
At some point.
But yeah, so you come out with this video and it's like...
Are you saying it's better than Angel's Egg?
I'm just, I'm just totally...
No, no, no, no.
Okay, I just want to...
It's just pure.
It's like no narrative whatsoever.
It's just like crazy animation.
Knowing that going in, it sounds great.
I would love to.
Yeah.
It's like 20 minutes of nonstop insane Yoshitaka Amano.
It looks like he animated it himself.
That's what's good about it.
Dude, like, seriously?
That sounds insane, bro.
Seriously, okay.
All right.
But, but, you know, you make this video and like it's just a vlog.
But I didn't understand this movie and now I do.
So to me, that was worth as much as Demo's video ever would have been.
Like, yeah, this is not...
All the Holden reviews like whacking yourself off,
animating the like fucking words,
moving around the screen.
Who the fuck gives a shit?
Yeah, exactly.
No, no, no hate on you Holden.
I just think you're wasting your time with that shit, dude.
Total hate on you Holden.
I'm not, I don't have no hatred for the guy.
Anyway, like, yeah, like, sure, it's not like a super rewatchable,
like, piece of art YouTube video.
But I got something out of it in a big way.
Anyone who wants to watch a fucking YouTube video
about what the fuck Angel's Egg is about, you can watch the video.
By the way, if people commented and as I was doing other research,
like, there are alternate interpretations.
Like, there's this whole thing about how you really can make a strong case
for how the anime is like...
And it's not like it excludes like my interpretation at all.
It's just like, there's multiple layers here.
You can also say that it's all about like masculine
and female relationships.
And you can say like, like, it's this woman,
it's this little girl like protecting her egg,
and then like a strong man comes along
and like shatters it, robs her of like...
With a huge fucking knife.
With a giant fucking, you know, schlong.
And like, then she immediately like turns into an adult, dies,
and then like eggs are produced.
So like, she's like sacrificed for like, you know,
the future of mankind or whatever.
So like, there's tons of parallels you can make to that shit too.
But I mean, as I admit it, it's what I got out of it.
Like, it's my interpretation.
And I'm sure they put lots of loaded imagery into it
just to be able to have all those different interpretations, you know?
Without a doubt.
Um, like, that kind of symbolism is pretty fucking blatant, you know?
Like, oh, an egg and a huge weapon.
What could these represent?
I wonder, you know?
But like, that video, it even gave me more confidence in my own stuff
because like a problem I have is that I make shitloads and shitloads of logs.
And like, I'm always explaining something I've already thought about.
And so I watched the video back and I'm like, okay, and then I'll post it.
And then like a day later, I'm like, this is worthless.
Why did I make this?
This is so stupid.
But then I watched something like the Angels Egg video and I'm like, okay, this,
like, now that I'm outside of myself and like watching someone else do what I do,
I get why people enjoy it, you know?
Like, I, like, because you already know what you're trying to say.
So you explain it and you're like, who the fuck cares about this?
But it's like for the audience, if they don't know this stuff,
then it's like, to them, it's a total mind blow.
That's a struggle.
I go through with every single video.
And like, considering that, like me and Gabe have talked about this a lot,
like the fact that we work on a video for so long,
like that feeling only gets worse.
The longer you're looking at the same idea you came up with six months ago.
That's why I, it's brutal.
That's why I keep my fucking work schedule so tight.
Because like, you really have to manipulate your own psychology
and have like a grip on yourself and keep yourself disciplined.
If you'd want to do that shit.
There was a time I really wanted to do stuff like the big 45 minute edited videos.
And like, you know, I can do it.
I did it with the part one of the sort of line season two video.
Like the reason I don't, it has nothing to do with success on YouTube.
Like this was before I knew that you needed to have constant content.
It was entirely because after about one week, I hate my video.
Right.
It happens to everybody.
Like just happening, like having to hear it over and over again,
you gradually are like, this doesn't make any sense.
Like, does anybody get this?
Like, am I saying anything?
And in some cases, I might have even been right.
Like there's some videos I go back and watch and I don't get the point.
And I'm like, okay, I guess I was just totally wrapped up in my own head on this one.
And like, I didn't really explain things that well.
But like, um, yeah, it's really dangerous.
Like the more time you spend on a video, the more you gradually come to hate it.
So like when you do get it out there all at once, like, even if you don't get it,
you know, if the audience likes it, then the audience likes it.
Like even if you're not sure why, you know, like there's some vlogs I make where I'm like,
I literally don't know what the appeal of this is.
But it's got 10,000 views and it's got all upvotes and the commenters like it.
And nobody's bitched on me on Patreon that I'm not making good enough content.
So I guess it's fine.
That's kind of the funny thing about living the Patreon lifestyle.
Like really, I mean, I always, well, I don't really say this all the time,
but I'm always thinking that like, if you're making like 10 billion,
whatever, you're making like $10,000 a month on Patreon.
But like what you make is like something that seems worthless.
Like you make one fucking MS Paint drawing just as whatever, as an example.
You're a postmodernist artist and you make shitty MS Paint drawings once a month and you make $10,000.
Like people might be angry about that or be concerned, but that seems silly to me.
It is purely a contract between you and the people giving you a money.
If they are satisfied, that is literally the only thing that matters.
And which is, which is why I mean, to a certain extent, I don't really like that people can just
see what you make on Patreon.
But you can hide that.
I know you can hide it, but even doing that is kind of like,
you have to make a choice to hide it.
And I think the audience will resent.
I mean, because I personally would be a little suspicious.
Just I don't even know why.
I think I'd only be suspicious if it changed from what like,
if you started off that way, which some people do, then like,
I don't like the idea really of people knowing how much money I make.
It rubs me the wrong way a little bit.
Because I mean, you fucking people out there don't tell everyone how much you make.
Right, well, it's not, it's not normal to have your,
your paycheck known to everybody.
And really it should just be, but like,
people shouldn't be basing their patron pledges on how much you've made.
It should be based on how much you value the content and nothing else.
Which is something that we all absolutely do.
You don't patron anybody, but like the rest of me and Ben have both done this,
where like, we see someone reach a certain amount and we're like,
well, he's already making enough money.
Exactly, exactly.
Like, God, who did I do that to recently?
I've done it to a lot of people.
Like, like, like when they pass me and I go,
That's really, that's not how it should work.
That's not how it should work.
Oh, that's why the, yeah, the version of Patreon where it hides the money is great
because it still shows the goals.
Like it says, oh, we've, we're 80% to our goal.
You don't need to know what my goal is.
Because it's what's comfortable for me.
It's not what's comfortable for you.
Right.
You know, some people will be like,
how come you need $2,000 a month to live?
I need to fucking live, nigga.
God damn it.
I need to survive in this fucking earth.
Oh man, I really get fired up about this issue.
People like, like, this is a big thing on 4chan.
This is one of the things that I hate about 4chan.
Like how, it's not that they're like anti-e-celeb.
Like, you can hate e-celebs all fucking day.
That's fine.
It's that they resent people for making money online,
making content.
It's because they are just so fundamentally wrong
in their basic assumptions that like,
what they're making is not valuable.
And it's, that's just so wrong.
It's like, why aren't you giving your money to fucking,
I don't know, Comcast.
Like, they deserve your money.
Or, I don't know, like anything else.
Comcast doesn't deserve anyone's money.
Yeah, that's a bad example.
But like, you should be fucking giving it to us
like some, give it to fucking, I don't know,
blocks news or whatever.
For me, for example, give it to the anime staff.
Don't pay the guy who's just talking about anime.
Pay the people who make the anime.
But for a lot of people, I'm giving them more
than what the show is.
Like, I mean, for me personally,
I'm obsessed with analysis videos.
And like, with video games in particular,
I don't play games.
I just watch videos about games.
I think I beat two games last year.
And that's like it.
I played through Doom and Dark Souls 3.
And that was it.
This is reminding me of how excited I am
now that BMMafa's done.
I can finish playing Demon's Souls
and I can beat Hollow Knight.
Oh my god.
Oh, you haven't beat Demon's Souls?
Of course.
I've beat it many times.
But I'm playing it again because I love it so much.
This is perfect.
It's gonna be great.
It's a perfect game.
It is perfect.
Okay, but was video about it?
Everyone go to Hippo Creek?
I haven't seen that yet.
I didn't get the chance.
Oh dude, you should watch the video
and look at Jesse's comment from The Virtus Room.
Oh, didn't he leave like a giant?
It was a giant novel-sized comment.
It was fucking great.
Why?
Shout out to Hippo Creek and hit this, Jesse.
Write a novel-like comment.
Because you like the video so much.
Okay, that's awesome.
He should just make a video
out of literally that comment.
It would be great.
That's excellent.
I love you, Hippo.
I thought that's another thing I love about the PCP
is we all love each other's shit so much.
Yeah, we do.
In spite of the fact that like,
and this is funny because Jesse's always advocating
for the death of the PCP,
but like I don't know if people understand why.
And it's because the PCP podcast brings out
the worst of our interactions.
Sometimes, yeah.
We're like, it's because we overstuff it.
There's, we always end up letting too many people in.
We're working on it.
We're never working on it.
Like the last one I was on,
there was like five people scheduled to be on
and then Hippo just would not not be on.
Well, I'm sure we agreed that he would be on.
No, he just complained all day.
Hippo complained?
Yeah.
Hippo's not a complainer.
It's because you weren't there.
Yeah, okay.
And like, like you and Ben weren't around.
And you were like, we were waiting for you guys.
And Hippo was like, oh, I really want to be in this one.
And we were like, there's already five people signed up.
Your name's not in the thing at all.
And he's just like, yeah, but I really want to be in this one.
And we were like, well, maybe Ben won't show up
because he hasn't gotten there yet.
I want Hippo to be involved in everything I do.
Yeah.
He's so wonderful.
That's the only reason none of us kicked him out
because we always wanted there.
Who could deny Hippo?
But then we ended up with a six-person podcast
that turned into a clusterfuck.
And people always argue.
And then everybody, I mean, I never do, but like,
a lot, like Ben or Jesse, if we get,
if they get mad in the podcast,
that is real anger that stays with them all day.
Like they will keep bringing it up,
how mad they were about that argument, you know.
And like it, it, you know, mixes our audiences
in annoying ways, tons of memes and bullshit
and the awful PCP fan chat that probably shouldn't exist.
You guys hate it more than I do.
I'm in there all the time.
I just poke my head in every once in a while.
I find them, I find them totally inoffensive.
But, but, but all this stuff like springs out of the PCP.
Yeah.
But when you, when you look past that,
and it's just like us as friends watching one another's videos,
we are just like on each other's dicks.
Like it's burst linking all fucking day.
True.
Like half of the PCP chat,
if any of us actually makes a video,
the PCP chat is just all of us talking about
how fucking great the other person's video is.
That's true.
Particularly if it's you, Hippo, or Jesse.
Yeah.
Like we all kind of, you know,
those are the ones that we're all like particularly invested in.
But that might-
Nobody cares about me and Mumkey's videos,
because we post so much that nobody can possibly give a shit.
That's the thing.
That's the only thing.
Like I don't blame anyone.
Neither does Mumkey.
It's like, no, we post like four videos a day.
I can't expect anybody to care.
Currently one of my favorite videos in the world is Mumkey's
like Yu-Gi-Oh dual destiny playthrough.
Oh, you watch that shit?
Every morning when I wake up on my way to work,
I listen to that shit and I fucking love it.
It's so good.
Mumkey, do that forever.
It's my favorite.
I prefer the Spyro playthrough.
That's done though, right?
Or is that still going?
No, he started out the second game,
but he's only done one.
I think he said I was supposed to be the first guest
that Motherfucker hasn't invited me on.
Me either, I still have it, but he did one with Sheepover
and that's the only one I saw so far.
I did see that.
The fuck is Spyro?
Yu-Gi-Oh, Yu-Gi-Oh forever.
That's what I want.
I can't do the Yu-Gi-Oh ones because I won't watch it.
I kind of watch it a little bit.
With me, my way of watching Mumkey was that for a really long time,
I was always getting a sandwich for lunch.
Subway sandwich, you get the deluxe secret?
Usually Wawa, but I'd go get a sandwich and I'd come back
and it takes me exactly 18 to 20 minutes to eat a sandwich.
So I'd always watch the latest Pokemon Nuzlocke video,
but then I got sick of the Nuzlocke's because same fucking shit every time.
You got boring with those, but he fixed it by making Yu-Gi-Oh videos.
I like the Spyro.
Ben, finish your fucking Nuzlocke piece of shit.
Yeah.
Fuck you.
I'm literally the biggest fan and fuck you.
You're the only one I think who watches all of Ben's Nuzlocke's.
I love those fucking Nuzlocke's so much.
They're really well made, I just don't have time.
I got nothing but time, dude.
When I'm at work, well, I mean, when I'm at work,
I just have a lot of, because I'm working on code,
I have a lot of time to listen to podcasts and just veg out and do my work.
So it's perfect.
It's great for consuming YouTube stuff.
Right.
All right.
Well, to get us back to our chronological timeline,
get us into your college years.
What did you study?
I went to the College of New Jersey,
originally as like an open options science major,
because I wasn't good enough to be on like the pre-med track.
I might have just not been decided,
but I was not that great a student.
I was like a B kid.
And I'll jack myself off and say it's cuz.
I was like bored and didn't give a shit.
Maybe I was just dumb, who the fuck knows.
But so I go to college looking into science stuff in general.
It takes me like a year or two to decide,
and so I wasted all that time,
took a bunch of classes I didn't need,
which is why I spent, took so long to get my fucking degree.
Yeah, you took like six years.
It took me eight and a half years.
Eight and a half to get a bachelor's.
That's correct.
But that's a lot.
That's literally double the time it's supposed to take.
It is a long time, but in my defense,
like it's not like I was taking full classes.
Like I was working full time at various, you know,
jobs while I was finishing up like one class per semester
after I left full-time schooling.
And like I made money overall,
but like there was a life cost.
Like that was like the worst time in my life doing that shit.
You lost all your souls.
What's a good metaphor here?
What's a good video gamey metaphor
for the draining effect this had?
It was like you were cursed.
You were gaining lots of souls,
but you had a curse on you.
That's true.
And it would just get my HP bar would be lower.
Like before they patched Dark Souls 1,
it just kept getting lower back in those days.
And I would walk up to my,
I'd be in the catacombs, you know,
when there's the basilisk there.
I would see my soul pile there,
and I'd be like, I'm gonna get to it.
I'm gonna get to it this time to reclaim all my souls.
And then I would die.
And all my souls be gone, no way to recover them.
And your HP's cut in half.
And my HP keeps getting cut in half.
That was fucking brutal.
That was sick though.
I like that.
In any case, so eventually I settle on computer.
Not even computer science.
Did you play Dark Souls early enough
to have the original version of the fire fucking lava place?
What's it called?
Eazelith.
Lost Eazelith.
Um, actually my friend got into Demon's Souls
right when it came out.
But all of us played it and all of us were like,
this is shit.
This game fucking sucks.
The version I'm playing right now was bought like,
like the year that it came out.
And like none of us,
none of my friends appreciated it at the time.
We all thought it was garbage and didn't get it at all.
And it was like, it was like well after Dark Souls,
one was out.
Like the hype had started to build.
So you probably didn't play original Lost.
I probably not.
Why?
What was different about it?
Well, when the game shipped Lost Eazelith,
which is the shittiest level in the game,
but originally-
Everyone says that.
I think it's okay.
I don't know.
I mean, the Demon legs are shitty.
Yeah.
Well, originally those all had like a giant aggro range.
So like the whole way through Lost Eazelith
was just constantly fighting those
like one after another in packs.
Those do suck ass.
And then they, but then they patched it
and just made it so they have no aggro range.
So now Lost Eazelith is you just run through.
You know, I remember playing that
and I remember them all getting aggroed.
So I think I did play the original version.
I literally fought none of them.
Oh, I fought all.
Yeah. Like they would all run at us.
If you fought them all that you played the original.
We fought them and the way that we beat them was
because I played this with my friends back in college,
like they would all like attack us,
but they would hit each other
and they would just kill each other.
And that's how we managed to get through.
Yeah.
That's probably what they intended,
but it was just like didn't work well enough
and it was too hard and they-
Not a great level.
No, it's definitely the worst level of the game.
I think they'll ever like remake it
because like they've said like,
yeah, we just didn't finish it.
We just didn't have time.
I would have who cares.
Anyway, so you're losing all your souls
going through college.
Right. So, but before that,
my four years in college were pretty good.
So around latter half of like sophomore year,
I get into like games development
with my buddy Rich and my buddies John
and Mike and Femi.
And Mike-
Wait, wait, you had a Rich and a Mike
and you almost had a Jay.
You had John, but you're close.
Why was that?
You almost had Red Letter Media.
Like you had almost all of them.
That's true. It was close.
And yeah, like we-
I was friends with-
Let me see.
I didn't know any of them at first,
but one fateful day at Anime Club,
we were-
I don't know why they were there.
Like they-
None of these guys were as big anime bosses,
but okay.
So it was me and I'm just describing this
because I want to jack off myself
about my friends Rich and Rich, Femi and John.
So one day at Anime Club, John and Rich,
I believe happened to be there
and we just met and we talked and we became friends.
We went back to their place, played Smash Brothers,
became friends, it was great.
I believe it was the next year
we were at my townhouse where I lived
and I lived with her with John.
And down at the end of the hall
was this guy Femi,
this little Chinese kid,
in his own place,
in his own room.
And I don't remember how,
but I believe it was a discussion
about Melty Blood was going on
and he overheard.
His ears perked up when he heard Melty Blood.
It was like-
Not something you hear a lot about.
If you hear about Melty Blood
and you know what it-
I've played literally one match
of Melty Blood at Necocon before.
I don't even know what the characters are in the game.
I just know it's all Type Moon characters.
He got Earth or whatever her name is.
My point is that I don't even like Type Moon.
I don't like highly technical fighters.
And still, if people were talking
about Melty Blood near me,
I'd be like,
Whoa, are you guys talking about Melty Blood?
It's a certain type of person
who would talk about Melty Blood
that you know that they're in your wheelhouse.
So we like-
To clarify for our audience,
Melty Blood is like a-
Type Moon fighting game.
Yeah, but it's like a doging game, right?
Like it was sold at,
I don't think it was ever professionally released.
It's like a commentary-
I didn't know that.
I mean, I played it a little bit,
just like fighting with some of these guys.
That game's old as shit, you know?
And it's from the people who later went on
to make Under Night Inbirth
and Dengeki Bunko Fighting Climax.
And they became like a major fighting game developer
It was like a borderline fan game, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
That they just kind of made
and with all the Type Moon characters
from like back before-
I mean, I guess Fate's Stay Night
was popular at the time,
but like,
they were not the gigantic fucking thing
that they are now, you know?
That's true.
It was definitely obscure.
It was the kind of thing
that if you knew about Melty Blood,
you had to be like a deep level otaku coming back.
That's right.
So that's when, I believe,
Femme-
it might have been something else
and that came up another time.
But there was something that tipped off Femme
that like, oh, fellow people
interested in this shit.
And he joined our circle of companions
and we all became fast friends
all through the end of college.
So meanwhile, during this time,
like me and my buddy Rich,
we decided to make a video game
to enter this contest.
So at this point, like,
yeah, we were doing like video game development.
There was this new major
at the school Interactive Multimedia
that we were like,
this is like the games I won.
Let's get into it.
And eventually I would like get away from that.
But at the time I was into that,
I was doing a double major of that
in computer science,
just because like Rich was a very practical guy
and was like, you know,
you should, you know,
interact in multimedia is cool and all,
but you should still do some computer science.
It's like, you can be like an idea guy
with the IMM shit,
but like, you're going to want an actual job.
So get the computer science degree.
And that's exactly what has paid off in my life.
But in any case,
so we decided to make a game
and we entered this,
it was like a GameStop funded,
like full ride to this thing called
full sale university,
which is like a game design school in Florida,
I want to say,
this is somewhere around.
And we were competing to win it.
And we, we finished our,
it took us a full year working on this game,
but we did finish it.
And incidentally, you can play it.
If you go to my Twitch,
it's like twitch.com slash definitely best guy ever.
There's like videos of us playing it.
Oh, you know what?
It's on,
it's on Bestie Boy as well.
Yeah.
I think.
Go to, go to like full play.
It's on Bestie Boy.
Find it on Bestie Boy.
There's like links to it
if you want to play it.
It's this,
it's this RPG maker.
We made it like RPG maker XL
or whatever,
like the fancier one was,
where you,
it's like a mystery puzzle game,
basically,
with a couple of little,
little bits of action in it.
And it's,
it's really fun.
I call it an adventure puzzle game.
Like an adventure puzzle.
Sure.
If you've played like Ibb or something,
it's along those lines.
You know, Ibb?
I'm not a fan.
No.
We were inspired a lot by Firefly,
or not Firefly.
Oh, what's the Jonathan Blow game
that was super famous?
Braid.
We were heavily inspired by Braid.
And Rich was really the one
who like had the idea
for what the game was going to be.
I was mostly the puzzle designer.
I didn't,
I couldn't program for shit.
I'm still not a great programmer,
even though it's my job
that I do every day.
He was the one in charge of doing all the,
what I consider the hard stuff,
and I designed puzzles.
So I was the idea guy
where that shit's concerned.
In any case,
we finished it,
we didn't win,
but we loved making it.
And Rich decided to go off to another school
that he finished,
and he got like a,
it's the one that hasn't like
an affiliate with Nintendo
up in Washington state.
Oh my god,
your friend works for Nintendo?
He doesn't actually work for Nintendo,
but I visited him in Seattle a while ago.
Like many of his friends
work for Nintendo,
and like Reggie works in that town
and lives there.
Like there,
it's,
that's Nintendo Central in America.
Does he see Reggie out
like eating bagels at breakfast
and be like,
yo Reggie, what up dog?
Is your body ready for breakfast, Reggie?
No,
but like there was a,
there was a friend of his,
this girl,
his name was Reggie.
Is he the one who originated
my body is ready or did he?
Yeah, that was Reggie.
He was like,
he was like,
get ready to do
we exercise or like we fit.
He just like,
are you ready?
My body is ready.
That was,
yeah, that was him.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's an old school one.
I didn't know that that's where it came from.
Yep.
It's all Reggie.
That's one of my favorite memes.
I say it all the time.
Really?
My body.
Well, I usually say my body is lady,
which is a compound.
Right.
From Idolmaster.
You know this one.
Yep.
I've seen that one.
It's for the audience.
It's the Idolmaster opening song.
They say,
are you ready?
I'm ready.
Which is literally,
are you ready?
I'm lady.
So,
so to me,
it's dumb asses.
My body is lady.
That's how I say it.
Um,
okay.
Well, in any case,
so,
so yeah,
as you can see,
I had an Anderson games design a big way.
I was in like the game design club
that my friend Andy started.
Magic Circle is what we called it.
That was cool.
I had like a little team.
We actually developed this phone game.
We did this thing called a,
we did a game jam,
which is like a 48 hour game development thing.
Crunch.
Yeah.
Um,
I had this idea for-
Finding advice,
it started as a game jam.
Yeah.
Yes, we learned from Florian.
Shout out to you, Doug.
There was a,
oh, what was I saying?
Oh, there was a game jam.
And I came up with this idea
for a game called Monochrome,
which is,
it's like,
what's it like?
It's a bit like bejeweled.
Okay.
But the idea is,
so,
you've got a field full of multicolored gems.
And if you look at like a color wheel,
you know how there's like,
it goes from like purple leads to red,
leads to orange,
leads to yellow,
leads to green,
to blue,
back to purple
in like a circle like that.
So the idea behind this game was that
you would click on something like purple
and if there was either one,
like next to that color on the color wheel,
either red or blue,
if you clicked from like purple
to one of those,
it would like consume that color.
So like the idea was,
it was a puzzle game
where you would kind of
eventually spread your color to,
it didn't matter what color,
but you could like end the game
with all the blocks as one color
was the basic idea of it.
And we actually developed
a functional phone app of this game
that I don't have anymore.
I think got deleted,
but it's on my like drive somewhere.
So I could install it again.
It's pretty fun.
We never finished it.
We wanted to make it like a full release,
but I guess as many game,
aspiring game devs did,
it never got out the fucking door.
But in any case,
Cool concept though.
Yeah, I really liked it.
It was really good.
And it was actually pretty damn fun.
Don't steal that audience.
I'm going to make that's my idea.
So, okay.
So I was big into game design.
Oh, incidentally,
my theater stuff didn't work out
from high school
because my grades weren't good enough.
And my dad forbid me to do any more theater
because he was like,
you're spending too much time on theater.
Even though the real problem
was that it was fucking around
and like not doing my homework
and just didn't give a shit.
I was just a very lazy guy.
Just didn't give a shit
about what I was doing.
I mean, that's school for you, right?
Right.
Well, that's that that's school for you.
Taking you away from the thing
that you're actually passionate about
because it's because it's supposedly
distracting you from the bullshit
that will never matter in your life.
Yeah.
Like, hey,
which set of skills do you think
is benefiting you on Patreon right now?
The theater skills or the fucking
whatever bullshit you had to do
in high school?
Yeah.
Fair question.
I think it was the theater skills.
A little bit.
I'm a bit of a human.
What do you think?
You think you think you've got all those patrons
from fucking knowing how to like
history of English or some shit?
No.
Yeah.
You got it because you gave an impassioned speech
about the human bullshit
while wearing a Picard outfit.
You're literally in costume in that video.
Yeah, it was great.
That card costume was a good investment.
Or it's not it's a it's a standard issue
uniform captain uniform.
So incidentally, there you go.
Tight fit on me.
Yeah.
It's a little bit of a tight fit on me to be honest to.
Yeah, but it's good that it's a tight fit on you.
I guess that's true.
Because it makes your chest look fucking huge.
That's true.
It does.
On me, it makes my tits look fucking huge.
My nipples were literally poking through that.
Disgusting.
Okay.
So in any case, so theater was out.
And I was just doing like game design stuff.
I guess my grades were okay.
I was never a great student at any point in my life
other than when I was like a little kid
and I could just coast by by like being
kind of smart.
And yeah, that's just how it worked out.
And never had any drive to do any of that shit.
But in any case, like another thing that happened
to me in college that was a big deal
is that I finally got a girlfriend.
I got a girlfriend and this was a revolution.
It was it was kind of a formative experience in my life.
Changed me actually getting the girlfriend
didn't change me at all.
I was totally the same guy up to that point.
I was still this like shy vampire,
hundred D loving, you know, cool kid.
I at that point, I never had hair that long again
down to my waist.
But I had it down to like shoulder length.
Right.
I've got kind of wavy hair.
So it was kind of like curled around.
I was like, I don't know.
And this girl inexplicably was into me
because I was the biggest fucking pussy.
Such like I let this girl walk all over me.
Like not to shit on her.
She was fine.
But I was not a man.
I did not do the things a man needs to do
as in assert yourself in any way.
Yeah.
Like I have a tendency to couch out of people
and try to please people.
And like that's nobody wants that in a relationship.
It's fucking shit.
So, you know, the relationship was mutually unsatisfying
and went on for like a year and a half
until she dumped me rightly so.
She, however, did not sex me.
And that is a big problem.
He dated for a year and a half and didn't fuck.
Yeah.
Well, she gave me a couple of handys.
You know, so that was nice.
But she's willing to give you a hand job.
Why not?
Because she's because she was a big weirdo Christian.
Oh, okay.
And that, you know, there were two, two things.
And this is cool.
There were two things that I stood up to her on.
One, I would constantly laugh at her
when she talked about her Christianity,
which I fucking love.
That's great.
And the other one was she worked as hard as she.
She worked that little white ass as hard as she could
to make me admit that Aris was the better girl for cloud.
And I never gave in.
It's Tifa for life, you stupid whore bitch.
Never giving you that.
You will never get the satisfaction.
Aris is fucking dead.
Tifa was cloud's destined girl from the start.
You idiot.
So on those two fronts, I retained my manhood.
And everything else, I was a big pussy bitch.
No, I really don't blame her at all.
You really stood for yourself on the issues that matter.
No, I know.
So, I mean, the whole girlfriend thing was actually,
it was a big deal for me.
So, you know, this was me desperate.
And I can admit this, I didn't give a fuck about this girl.
I just wanted to have sex desperately.
It was a huge deal in my life and never happened.
And I was extremely upset when the relationship ended.
And I'm like, I just dated this girl for like a year and a half.
And I know this kind of count sounds like a psycho,
but it's what I was honestly thinking.
It doesn't if you're a fucking 23-year-old virgin.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like, how old were you, 20?
I was, no, I was like 20.
I was like dating her from like 19 to 20.
That range, more or less.
And yeah, it was real fucking bad, real fucking bad.
But in any case, so eventually, between junior and senior year,
a grand opportunity arose for me to travel abroad.
Because actually, one of the main reasons I chose to go to the
College of New Jersey is because they had a mother fucking
Japanese language program.
And that was like number one on my list, needed that shit.
And it was by far the best thing about that school.
I fucking loved taking Japanese there.
Reading those fucking Genki books, practicing vocab.
God, I miss, I want to do more desperately.
But I got to buy some Genki books immediately.
We got to talk about that later too.
Yeah.
Because me and you are planning a possible thing.
And my new girlfriend also wants to learn Japanese.
Dude, don't bring your fucking girlfriend into this shit.
No, no, no, no.
I'm not going to bring her into our thing.
Okay, okay.
I'm just saying that I'm very quickly becoming surrounded
by people who want to learn Japanese as badly as I do.
Right, right.
And this is the perfect time.
Like, I need to learn this language.
I'm going to kill myself if I don't learn Japanese by the time I'm 30.
Like, if I'm not fluent by the time I'm 30, I will fucking kill myself.
That's a high bar.
Go for conversation, like high level conversation.
No, no.
I got to be fluent by the time I'm 30.
You don't have that much time to get fluent, dude.
It takes a long time to get fluent.
Five years is plenty of time.
Well, we're not, we're not fucking beginners at Japanese.
We both took three years, you know.
That took four years.
I took three.
I went.
I've been watching anime for 15 years.
I would bet your Japanese is better than mine,
because I have been completely not a professional.
That's pretty likely.
But so in any case, so I was taking Japanese,
fucking loving it, Ogren sensei, and Yamashina sensei.
Thank you for being there for me.
I appreciate what you did.
Because I'm sure they'll listen to this podcast.
But in any case, I was also a Japanese language teacher.
Oh, but that was after I came back from the thing
I'm trying to get to.
I traveled to fucking Japan and I spent two months,
a whole summer in Tokyo, living the fucking good life.
And it was by far the best single decision
I've made in my life, except maybe deciding
to start doing YouTube.
And it was, it was, I mean, it wasn't like
a fucking magical experience.
It was just one of those things where like so many
opportunities opened up to me when I like took
the initiative to get this thing done,
which is why, you know, people say yes to
opportunities that come before you people.
So I went there.
I went to Japan and I was at this place called the,
I believe it was the KCP International School,
or something like that.
You can, you can Google it because they take
international students and they, you know,
they teach them shit.
They've got a lot of like Koreans and probably
like some Filipinos.
It's like the school is mostly full of Europeans
and like a bunch of like, you know, a couple Brits
and some Americans, you know, all bunch of big
weaves, most of the Koreans though.
But in any case, they teach them Japanese
as good as they can.
And they have a bunch of levels.
I was in like the middle level one.
I was actually in one that was a little bit too
high for my actual language control ability.
So I was a little bit like not able to keep up
with things that were happening,
which was a little bit shitty.
But it's because I've always had this pride.
When I was in school, like I was the only kid
in the entire school who took every single AP class
that was available.
And it's because because I would have felt
angry at myself for not taking the most difficult
challenge possible.
Like I would have felt dumb and our valedictorian,
she didn't take every fucking AP class.
Only me and my friend Doug did.
And it's because I think we have this like weird,
maybe his parents pressured him,
but for me it was like, no, I've got this weird,
um, I don't know, self critical ego thing going on.
We're like, I need to challenge myself
like the hardest thing is possible.
I don't feel it anymore.
But so I did that.
And so, you know, when I was in Japan,
I chose to take like this level that was definitely
a little bit too hard to be 100% useful for me.
Like you need to be at a level
where you can actually keep up.
My biggest problem in Japanese class
is that I got a D all three years.
Each year I had no idea what was going on.
I never knew what was happening.
Oh, that sucks.
I spent my whole time in three years of Japanese,
like a deer in the headlights.
They shouldn't have asked me.
I was constantly trying to play catch up.
Like, yeah, things would blow by me
and I would have to catch up.
That was, that was tough.
Like, I mean, when we, in my third year,
we had this Russian guy of Shinnokov Sensei,
who like he had been, he'd studied in Russia,
then he'd taught, like, I think he'd taught
either English or Russian in Japan.
Yeah.
Then had taught in America a little bit,
like at a nicer school, then came to my school,
which is dog shit, you know.
And, like, he gets there and, like,
all of us are so far below the level
we're supposed to be at for that.
And, like, in so varying, like,
the top students in class knew everything,
and the bottom students in class, like me,
knew jack shit.
And so he, like, the whole time,
he was just, like, exploding with stress.
I feel something, guy, that's tough.
This dude was, like, man, he couldn't deal.
Like, it was, like, three layers of culture shock.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, he'd been used to teaching
at Japanese schools where kids, like,
super diligent when he comes here.
What the fuck is with American schools?
We are a bunch of fuck ups.
Why do we even have them?
I don't know, because it's possible
just to make us feel good about ourselves,
you know, like, pretend like
we're doing something useful.
There is a certain service being served, but, uh...
Go listen to PCP schools.
Yeah, go listen to that one.
PCP fuck school, I think it's the time of it.
Fuck school, yeah, something like that.
Okay, so I went to Japan, right,
and it was fantastic.
The best thing about going there, though,
was not that I kind of learned
how to, like, be independent a little bit.
Like, college is kind of cushiony,
but, like, I lived just in, like,
an apartment by myself in Tokyo for two months
and had to, like, figure shit out,
like, how to survive.
But more importantly than that,
I hooked up with this dude Garf,
and I think I've told this story a couple times before,
but, like, me and this buddy Garf,
he had yellow fever.
It was ridiculous.
He wanted to get laid like a motherfucker.
That we both got...
She described it to us as the worst yellow fever
you've ever seen.
The worst case of yellow fever I've ever encountered,
without a doubt.
Like, he was into deep-level, like,
geisha shit.
Like, that's what he wanted.
That's his, like, ideal woman,
from his own mouth.
Deep-level geisha shit.
Yeah, man.
So he would...
So we would bomb down to Roppongi at, like,
late night.
Like, even on weeknights,
we would just go to Roppongi,
get absolutely sloshed.
By the way, people don't know this,
the best thing about Japan
is that you can drink alcohol
outside anywhere you want at any time.
It's wonderful.
Beautiful.
Um, it's really not to be underestimated
how great and liberating that is.
That's all I'm gonna do when I go to Japan.
It's fantastic.
It's probably because they, like,
trust their citizens to not fuck up
and, like, be reasonable.
But it's funny because it draws a lot of tourists
and, like, foreigners who are not reasonable.
And, like, me and him would just be, like,
puking in the streets sometimes
and just be being irresponsible in the club and, like...
How old are you at this time?
Well, let's see.
When I was in Japan, I turned 21.
So it was, like, right at that time.
And by the way, the drinking age in Japan,
I believe is 18.
It's 20.
Okay, yeah, 20, yeah.
So I was able to drink.
I turned 21 when I was in Japan.
So a little bit anticlimactic,
but, you know, it was still a great time.
I met some interesting characters,
like this guy named Nash,
who was, like, a competitive MMA fighter
who was, like, training at various dojos across Asia
and was, like, friends with some of the students
at the school I was going to,
or some of the teachers who would, like,
help him buy plane tickets places.
Can I have a slice of your apple pie?
Sure, yeah, go for it.
Thank you.
Um, let's see what else is going on.
So really, like, the main idea that I want to talk about here
is, like, my life changed dramatically
because I developed a fixation
with actually going out,
like, no longer being a pussy.
Like, this was the time in my life
I got really into, like, pickup artist shit.
And I started obsessively consuming
everything I could find,
specifically while I was in Japan.
I downloaded tons of, like, videos
and, uh, and all that kind of shit.
And, like, a lot of the philosophy
has stuck with me to this day,
though the, like, the, I don't know,
like, the specifics have kind of faded.
But I always want to defend it
when I talk about it,
that pickup artist shit is, like,
it's about self-improvement
more than anything else.
So, like, what I have gotten from, like,
these guys, like, Tyler Durden.
That's, like, that's the guy, Tyler Sensei.
He is, um, I mean, I call him Tyler Sensei,
but, like, it's not like he's known by that.
It's just, like, I met,
I found out about this guy when I was in Japan.
So I started calling him Tyler Sensei,
even though he just goes by Tyler in America.
But in any case, um,
like, these guys are all about, like,
you become a better man
so that you can attract better women.
And, like, it's not like you're tricking anyone.
It's, like, you are a better person.
And the women that are into you,
because of that, are just being given,
like, more of a product.
I think what people are averse to
is, like, people are really into, like, destiny.
And, like, they feel like I'm born this way.
Fucking with that order is wrong.
It's not good to improve your station.
It is.
Yeah, it's, it's disgusting.
No, we are clay dolls
that we mold through our own power
to a certain degree, you know?
We have a certain level of influence
over our own bodies,
if free will exists,
which I don't actually believe,
but we'll put that aside for now.
But the point is, like, this is when I,
like, I, all, what this boils down to is,
like, I now decided, you know what,
I should actually do something
because I want women in my life,
and I should actually, like, work on that.
Like, so nobody, I think,
in the right mind would ever find a problem with that.
So that's what we did.
We went down to Roppongi,
and our choice was to get super drunk.
That's with our solution.
And we would go into clubs.
We would, we would, we would grind up on,
on hot Japanese women
who were looking for sexy American men.
And we just, we kind of grew up, you know?
We became grown up guys a little bit more.
Neither, I did not get laid
through during my time in Japan,
which was a big bummer for me.
But Garoff did, though.
Garoff, and as I was saying,
like, he, he's really into Japanese chicks.
Devastatingly, he banged a Vietnamese chick.
And, yeah, he's, he regrets it intensely to this day
that he, he, when he was in Japan.
Still, still yellow.
Still yellow, you know, on the spectrum,
getting, getting closer to what he wants.
I'm sure by now.
The color spectrum is what I'm talking about.
I'm sure by now he's banged
quite a few Japanese ladies.
If his yellow fever persists,
because who knows.
He was actually Indian,
so I don't know if that is relevant,
but like, he had yellow fever
despite being Indian.
But whatever.
So, but the funny thing was,
so after I came back from this wonderful time,
oh, by the way, I met Moot when I was in Japan.
Oh, yeah.
When I was on, I was on 4chan,
just one day, and I saw it,
like, and a bunch of the guys who were there,
you know, a lot of the white guys who were there,
were a bunch of, like, big weebs like me.
And, like, I saw a post one day
that was just, it was the banner on 4chan.
It's like, hey, I'm Moot.
It was, like, a sticky on every board.
I'm gonna be in Akihabara at this time.
Be there if you want to hang out.
And I was like, I'm gonna be there.
So me and a couple of the guys,
we went down there,
and we hung out with Moot for a while.
And we went to eat.
We met his crew.
What did he seem like?
He was, like, a skinny, I don't know.
I mean, I imagine he's just a, like, nerdy programmer guy.
That's really the impression,
for the most part, that I got.
He didn't have any kind of, like,
bombastic personality or anything.
He was pretty chill.
Yeah.
And we talked.
And if you look around online,
there's some, I don't know if you got,
if you search around,
there are some famous pictures.
If you search, like, Moot in Akihabara,
there are pictures of me with him.
And there's one of, like, all his crew,
like, want us to take a big, like, group photo.
So we all lined up in a row.
And he took a big picture of all of us.
And what was funny to me is that,
even years later, I see that photo
reposted on, like, 4chan now and then.
And I'm right there wearing, like,
a Soga King from One Piece shirt
that I bought at Uniqlo when I was there.
And it's, people label, like,
every person in that group as, like,
a different board.
Like, Moot was B, you know, like,
there was a girl, like, a pregnant girl,
like, with a baby who was, like, CGL.
Just, like, a bunch of other, I am.
Which one's CGL?
CGL is the cosplay.
Like, the slut one.
The slut girl one.
Right.
Of course.
So it fits.
And I was consistently labeled as co,
as the comics board.
Even though you're wearing a One Piece shirt.
Even though I was wearing, yeah,
inexplicably, I think it's because I had
a shit-eating grin and looked confident.
And I was already getting fit at this point.
So my muscle definition was improving.
Which isn't an A thing.
Why would that be a co thing?
Because it's not an A thing.
I think A is more fit than co.
That's bullshit.
And you know it, dude.
Comics and cartoons.
Co has some normies.
Co has a decent normie population.
So those people even out the fitness curve.
The A's are a bunch of fucking fat weirdos.
Why weren't you just fit?
Was somebody else fit?
I don't know if there was a fit on this whole thing.
There might just not have been a fit.
Okay, but the point I'm trying to get to,
I just thought that's a cool thing that happened to me
while I was there.
When I got back,
like a month after I got back to school,
I immediately got laid.
And it was just like, I did the grind,
I put in the work, did my training,
and all of it paid off when like,
I completely changed as a person when I got back.
I was way more like outgoing,
willing to just do crazy shit,
you know, kind of,
like the guy I am now on the PCP
is like post-Japan Nate.
The guy from before Japan
was a completely different guy.
Big pussy, sucked a lot of dick,
mostly his own, not a fun guy.
I imagine, I mean, I think,
I think pretty much all of us on the PCP
have some kind of turning point like that.
Yeah.
Like, I don't know.
Like for you it was when you realized you were gay.
That was a big day for you.
Yeah.
Yeah, right.
I think all of us, well, I don't know.
I don't know if I can speak for the younger guys,
if they've quite had like a definitive,
like I don't know how different Hippo is
from how he used to be, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
I'd have to ask him, but like for me,
it would be pre and post BronyCon 2013.
Was that the first one you went to?
Yeah.
Yeah, so with Tom, yeah.
Because like, if I, I mean,
like, there's lots of moments in my life
that like things change, like me going to the Philippines
would almost be comparable to you going to Japan,
except that it didn't change much
about my life back in America.
Right.
It was really going to BronyCon and like becoming,
having a moment of like thinking of myself as famous,
or something like, or like being a personality in public
and like having to respond to all these people,
like completely changed the way I think about interacting
with random strangers.
Sure, sure.
Like it's just, you have this moment
where all these people know who you are,
who you don't know, and like all you,
like all they expect of you is to be cool.
And so like, I'm there and I'm like,
I have to be cool for these people, you know,
like I can't be some boring nerd for all these people
who are coming up to me.
I have to be like this larger than life figure
who they're expecting.
And so that's like what I became in my real life.
It's like, I just kind of transformed into like a,
you know, a guy who thinks of himself as someone with fans.
You know, I remember you talking about,
there was a phase in your life that I remember,
I think I was just a fan of yours at the time.
And it was when you were doing like a big purge
of all your contacts and you're like,
I know too many people right now.
Yeah.
That seems relevant.
That was not too long after that BronyCon.
Just, I had, that's just because I literally accepted
everybody who sent me a fucking Skype request.
And that's a huge mistake and nobody should ever do that.
Yeah.
I still get messages on Discord just from people,
usually from the fan chat,
because like I'm in there and it's easy too.
I got no problem with that,
but I just ignore them for the most part.
Right.
And let me see, was there anything else?
I had like 400 Skype contacts at the time.
That's why I had to get rid of phone.
I'm merely going to talk about this because it is important
context into who I am.
And this is like the podcast about the kind of person I am.
So like this getting laid thing was like it, I don't know.
I feel like there's a tendency to like diminish.
It totally matters.
It's a really important thing.
It totally does matter because it's just that you can't,
like even if it's not good, even if like you,
even if what you take away from it is,
oh, I don't even care about sex, you have to know.
You have become like you have changed
and you will now have something socially
that gives you like an aura of confidence.
Like you're now part of the club, you know,
you're no longer an excluded, you know, loser.
And I mean, even if you only,
not that anyone who hasn't had sex as a loser, you know, it's fine.
Right.
I mean, like, I mean, I had said, I had, you know,
my ex-girlfriend and I had sex with her plenty of times.
I understand what it is and it was pretty good.
I think I'm good at it and it's fun.
But like after that, I spent the last three years
not getting laid until like last week.
And like it didn't get any easier to make it happen again.
But it's just like knowing that I could, that I have and can, you know.
It's a world of difference.
Post-Virginity lost to, pre-Virginia lost to post, it is different.
It's a difference between thinking, will I ever have sex?
Exactly.
I know I can.
I've done it before.
I just have to put in more effort.
Like the last three years, I felt like I could,
I could have sex anytime I want.
I just got to put in effort and I'm not willing.
Many of my friends are still virgins to this day.
And they're 26, 27, just like me.
And I don't know, man.
It could have been me.
Could have easily, if I didn't go to Japan, it would be me.
It would be me.
Yeah.
It was, um.
And I don't think I would have.
These guys are my brothers.
I love them to death, you know.
I don't know.
I guess I just wish they would.
Incidentally, because you're saying one month after,
after that's when you got laid.
Yeah.
It's exact same for me with BronyCon 2013.
Oh really?
Because that girl, the girl who was my first girlfriend.
Yeah.
Like literally like BronyCon had been like one week before
and I'd just gotten back and it was like my birthday area.
Like the day after my birthday.
Right, you were complaining about it on the cast.
Yeah.
And I was just talking about it on the on the pub crawl
and this girl starts messaging me in the in the chat
and that's how we hooked up and like a month later.
Yeah.
It's, there's definitely something to this effect of like
just doing something that's so like something that it's not
that it's out of character.
It's out of character for who you are,
but it's in character for who you think you should be.
Well, you know, you know, like back in the day,
I also heard describe it's like the whole thing about like
the self-improvement stuff that I got from a lot of the,
like the, they're like more like life coaches,
these kind of this pick up stuff.
But it was like, it's you at 100.
Like, like you're not, it's not like,
you can't even be someone else if you try.
You're always going to be yourself.
You know, you can act fake or whatever.
But like, if you're just going out there and you're just,
I really resent this notion that people like trying to change
themselves are being fake.
I reject that whole heartedly.
I do as well.
That just, that stagnates people so hard.
And I hate it.
And it happens to a lot of like nerdy guys,
like they fall for that trap hard.
I did, I certainly did.
But don't be a fucking idiot.
Make yourself better.
Exactly.
Not just to get laid, but like for every reason.
Consider your entire life an engineering problem.
And if there are deficits that you need to improve, work on it.
If there's literally anything you're not happy with,
then what the fuck are you doing?
You know, like, fix that.
That's right.
Like, yeah.
That's how it should be.
If something's broke, you fix it.
That's like, you know, are you going to be the guy who,
I don't know.
You watching any Casey Neistat at all?
Yeah, I've seen a lot.
Yeah.
Like what's great about Casey is he's got this,
this sort of workshop that he works in.
Workshop is great.
If anything is not exactly what he wants, he fixes it.
He'll get a tool and just make it.
He always says like, there's two kinds of people in this world,
people who can build something and people who can't,
you know, or people who can use their hands or whatever.
Like, you know, if something,
if he needs something to be a certain way,
he immediately, immediately makes it that way.
And that's how everyone needs to get into that fucking mindset.
If something's broken, look around you right now,
look around your room, the audience.
If something is broken and you've been meaning to fix it,
fix the fucking thing.
You know what's funny about that?
Fix it now.
That's entirely true.
That is the best way to live.
Yeah.
The funny thing is I cannot necessarily adhere to that
as often as I'd like to.
Like this thing about like getting a new bed,
that's been like an issue for like a year.
I've wanted a new bed.
It's only because there was something that happened
that was like a motivating factor.
Like, you know, I could use a second bed for like a guest.
Right.
That's what really got me to do it.
But like then there's other things like nobody,
nobody asked me to make me a mafia.
Nobody was like, hey, why don't you, you know, whatever.
You recognize a systematic problem with your content.
I decided that it needed a solution.
That's exactly right.
And I mean, it's not always easy to identify what's broken.
Right.
But there is kind of like, for me, a lot of the time,
if I'm not sure why I'm not happy, I'll just go and make a bunch
of different shit until I figure out what am I missing.
You know, like, I mean, this trip I'm
on right now, that's kind of what inspired like,
I didn't know what the results of this would be.
I'm just like, hey, I'm going to leave the house
because I've tried everything here and none of that's working.
So the solution must be out there.
So let's just go out there and drive around aimlessly
until something changes.
And something did change almost immediately
upon leaving my house.
Like it's obvious that this is what should have happened.
It's like, yeah, you should have left like months ago.
And that's why I so value and think it's a great idea
to shake up your life in a big way.
Absolutely.
At the very least, like things like traveling,
long distances, people, it's so easy to be like, I don't know,
like if you dreamt of like going to Paris or whatever,
it's like, yeah, I mean, what am I really going to,
oh, the fucking Eiffel Tower, I've fucking seen that
in a million pictures.
Actually putting in the shit to go to Paris is just,
it's going to be worth it, probably.
Probably.
I mean, it's just worth the experience of figuring out
how the fuck to get to Paris.
And I mean, to me, like a lot of people hate travel.
I love travel just because like, even when it sucks,
it's interesting because it's just something new.
Absolutely.
Like I'm the type of guy.
You're collecting stories and life experience at a minimum
that you won't get if you're sitting in your ass in the room.
I'm the type of guy who will sit around
like and just walk around the airport.
Like let's say I have a two hour layover.
Yeah.
You can compare different airports.
It's interesting shit.
I live in Norfolk, tiny airport, nothing there.
Right.
Then you go to New York and you're in this giant fucking LaGuardia.
These huge food courts and all this crazy shit.
Hey, everything costs twice as much in New York
because the taxes are so much higher.
And like just learning shit, you know, like you can't,
you literally can't go somewhere and not learn anything.
Like you will learn something because that place
is not the place you were already in.
And you will inherently pick up on something,
even if you don't immediately recognize it.
Even if it's just like a talking point,
you can walk up to some girl at the bar and be like,
hey, yeah, what's going on?
I went to Boston yesterday.
Oh, yeah.
What was that?
Like, oh, cigarettes are like $12 there.
It's fucked up, you know.
Icebreaker, you have something.
You have something to talk about.
Something's different about you, you know.
You know, there is that's entirely true,
but there is nothing harder on this earth
than doing a cold approach to a girl.
And I've done it many times.
And every single time I felt like I was dying.
Yeah, see, I have, I went through the fire.
I faced my fear and I haven't conquered it.
It's still there.
I still feel social anxiety.
All the, like, if I want to talk to a girl, it's hard, man.
It's hard shit.
Every guy knows it is.
It's a skill that you have to work at,
if that's the kind of guy you want to be, you know.
I mean, you could take the route of becoming a YouTuber
and getting 100,000 subscribers and waiting for a girl
to say like, hey, you're cute.
Let's go have sex.
Literally the route that each of us is taking all the time.
It is very inefficient.
If you can avoid it, there are faster ways.
It is hyper inefficient.
Yeah.
If you can build a career out of it too, hey, great.
Two birds with one stone.
Wouldn't recommend it though.
Go, guys, go improve yourselves and go harass women in the street.
That's what I'm trying to say.
I don't even know how, like, pick up culture.
It's not called that anymore.
Honestly, like, with the whole picking up girls
through YouTube thing, I think it would only even work
for people like us who were destined to be YouTubers anyways.
The reason it works for us is that, like...
We're so personality driven.
Yeah, like the kind of stuff that we would use to pick up a girl.
It's the same stuff we'd talk about in a YouTube video.
That's true.
I have literally seduced women by talking about One Piece endlessly.
They get entranced by the passion I show
when I talk about how much I fucking love One Piece.
It literally happened.
I have literally gotten laid off of that shit.
The kinds of women who would be into us
are the kinds of women who are into just guys being passionate about something.
That's right.
I mean, passion is just an endless wellspring of something I have.
Right.
Well, because it creates an association
that if he can get that passionate,
maybe he can get that passionate about me.
Maybe he can get my nut.
Yeah.
Oh, god, you reminded me.
I have to try that now.
Oh, shit.
I totally forgot.
You.
I'm glad I reminded you.
Oh, boy.
Thank god.
Um, I got a hot date in like two weeks.
Great.
I'm gonna get in there.
Get that.
Pew!
Tragically after National Sex Day.
Next June 9th, everybody.
Get out there and get yourself a date.
Oh, god.
It's also National Marriage Day.
If you see any tweets about me being like heartbroken,
talking about how my girlfriend broke up with me,
just know it was because I can't avoid it.
Yes, it's gotta be done.
I have a date with destiny.
It's gotta be done.
I'm so glad you reminded me.
So I was, I was gonna say,
so after I got laid the first time,
which was a big deal for me,
I then spent the rest of senior year
pursuing like casual sexual relationship.
Like my, I didn't really dwell on this that much,
but my heart was absolutely broken and has not recovered.
I do not trust relate,
I don't trust anyone.
I do not trust anyone to do anything for me.
I only trust myself.
I will never have any confidence in anyone ever again.
I expect them to betray me at a moment's notice.
So I organize my life where when they betray me,
not if, I will be able to survive
and it won't be a big deal.
So that's, that's me.
But I was able to have a,
have good times with a bunch of nice ladies senior year.
You know, I had a bunch of casual things going at once,
was living the dream for a while with a couple ladies
and then senior year ended.
And that was, you know, that was sad and all.
Nothing, none of it was like too tragic.
It was just, it sucked to be away from my boys.
But eventually I went back to Massachusetts
and from there I just spent my time
doing like one class at a time
working terrible, shitty jobs
because for years the College of New Jersey
was useless at finding me a fucking internship
where I could like work and make decent money
with those, with the skills I had developed.
It took me four years and of an account,
like my dad's best friend since he was like,
in like elementary school,
having to work for a software company
and was like, hey, like we could,
we take interns all the time
from like the University of Cincinnati.
So I'm living like an hour south of Boston
where, you know, where I grew up.
And he's like, hey, want to move out to Cincinnati?
You know, you have to interview and shit
but you've got decent qualifications.
You can finish your degree out here
at like the University of Cincinnati
and, you know, at work and have a fucking job
and not be a poor piece of shit.
Like you have been for the last three, four years or whatever.
I was like, yes, please, save me from this hell.
And so I went and started,
I lived out here in Cincinnati
and that's what I've been doing ever since.
Finished my degree a couple months ago,
checked that box and now my pay went up a bunch
and now I make a comfortable living,
live well below my means
and I'm spending all my money
to pay off my student loans,
so I'll be free.
But, and so that's where I'm at right now,
like financially.
But, during that three years,
and this is where I wonder
if maybe this was all a blessing in disguise,
I heard of a little website called uporn.com
and I knew that's where my future lie.
No, it was YouTube.
So actually, it was funny, Ben during this time,
you know, my older brother, Ben, remember that guy?
He had been doing a lot of crazy shit during that time.
He went to Europe, he taught Polish,
no, he taught English in Poland.
Oh, no, no, no, sorry, he taught physics in Poland
because that's what he got his degree in
and he did a bunch of crazy stuff
and he lived in California,
you know, I've been around for a while.
Go listen to the Ben interview
if you want the full story of Ben's crazy ass post college.
Ben's done some really interesting stuff with his life,
despite being a useless bum.
It's generally because Ben does not care
about having a safety net.
No, not at all.
You and him are kind of diametrically opposed
in this regard.
I wouldn't say, like, I'm very much like my dad
in that respect.
He is like, and I've only become that way
over the last couple years,
like since I moved out here
and I've like been forced to become an adult.
Yeah, like now I really have my shit together
in a big way and Ben does not.
And I, I wonder if that's-
But it doesn't even matter,
because he doesn't care.
It doesn't, he does not care.
It does not faze him
that he doesn't have a shit together.
I guess he's more like my mom a little bit.
I don't know, it's a mix.
This whole thing about like,
oh, you're just like your mom,
you're just like your dad,
that's a meme anyway.
But in any case, so during that time,
Ben was got into,
Ben had been watching a ton of shows.
Like he's always been a big consumer of media.
And one show he watched was My Little Pony,
that he was like, hey Nate, check out this show.
And I remember when he was in, I believe Poland,
he sent me like something,
it might have been California or whatever,
when he was far away,
he sent me links to like the show.
And I was like, I do not believe
that My Little Pony is good.
I believe that you are lying to me,
that this is a fucking joke,
that you're an idiot.
And I just ignored him for a while.
But eventually like on 4chan,
people were talking about it,
and I was just like, okay,
maybe there is something to this thing after all.
So I took Ben up on it.
And the first episode I watched
was Putting Your Hoof Down.
And it was like the best episode of all time.
I'll describe it to you.
Season two, that's the Iron Will one, right?
As made famous by Keg Standard Reviews,
Putting Your Hoof Down, that's right.
And it's the greatest episode of anything ever.
It's literally about like this,
like the kind of motivational speaker
sort of pickup artist guy
that was like my hero.
And it didn't even make him a villain.
It just made him like an antagonist for the episode
with like, hey, you owe me money.
But then Fluttershy is like,
fuck you, I didn't appreciate your service.
All Fluttershy does is like learn from this guy,
become like an alpha herself.
And then he's like, yeah, you know, okay, all right.
I'm with you.
So like, he respects the co.
He's not even a villain.
He's a good guy.
He is a good guy.
Okay, I'm getting too deep into this thing.
I fucking love that episode.
Go watch Keg Reviews.
Go watch Keg Standard Reviews.
Putting Your Hoof Down on T-Bap.
It's actually a great video that I love.
I did a song for it and two or three songs.
I did three songs.
That video's kind of the precursor
to what would be best guy ever.
Like, it's the first example of you going
way the fuck overboard
for the production of a video.
Which would be continued in Phantom Reviews.
Way overboard.
We've banned Ben's fucking animations
and like the song.
Oh man, that was a fucking crazy ride.
Took us like six months to finish that video, I think.
Yeah.
Which would establish a pattern for me,
which would be very destructive,
but make some decent stuff.
But in any case,
so Ben convinced me to watch My Little Pony.
I did and I got into it.
And I would watch it like at work
when I was supposed to be working
at this other shitty job.
And I would just watch My Little Pony instead.
And it was great.
I remember I was watching it
when the Boston Marathon bombing happened.
I was watching Some My Little Pony
and was like, I don't give a fuck about them.
I'm taking it with rarity and the girls.
This is way more important.
And long story short,
like so we were goofing around
and then eventually Ben came home
and Ben suggested one day,
he's like, yo, I've been watching this big faggot
like Digi Bro and like other guys
or Digi Broney and Broney Curious
and these other guys.
And in fact, he showed me the video
that really made me even interested
in YouTube in general,
was like horseshoe reviews.
God, what was it?
It was like, it was the one.
He knew Jesse even before he showed any of this to you.
Yeah.
Like the first video that I saw of like YouTube,
this was like my introduction to YouTube
was seeing Jesse's video.
God, what the fuck was it?
It's like magic.
It's that it's the season three opener,
the Crystal Kingdom,
like the Magic Crystal Kingdom one.
Oh, the Colt Corona.
The Colt Corona video, that's the one.
Where he crawls out of that fucking
like the carousel boutique thing.
This is before horseshoe reviews.
Yeah, you're right.
It wasn't even horseshoe reviews.
It was when Jesse was doing his crazy shit before that.
This was, that video was fucking magical.
That video is incredible.
Jesse, I love you brother.
You're a hero.
But so I realized that YouTube was a thing.
We were both into My Little Pony.
Ben was back home.
He suggested, hey, let's do a,
because every time an episode would come out,
we've been doing this our whole life.
We would be like up late watching anime together
and we'd talk about it for hours.
He's like, yo, we're doing this again
with My Little Pony.
Let's make a motherfucking podcast.
So we did.
So we made T-Bat episode one and just like,
that's two best brothers bitch about ponies.
Yeah, don't tell mom though, because that's a swear.
So, right.
So we did it and I believe,
our first episode was just a still image
and shitty audio.
And shitty art.
The original designs are pretty shit.
I remember Ben, the keg had this
amazing like number one finger
that never got reused.
What a tragic loss for that character.
Could have had so much development
with that number one finger thing.
But yeah, I had the Kanye Shades
and Ben Phantom Horn.
Oh, it was good times.
But what's interesting about T-Bat,
looking back at it now,
is that that was literally the first video
I ever made outside of like this one
like video editing AMV I made,
like on a VHS tape back in high school
that is totally irrelevant.
I started learning YouTube at that moment,
like editing and shit.
And now here I sit like three and a half years later
and I consider myself a pretty damn great edit boy.
And yeah, learned a lot of shit real fast.
But like the way that T-Bat evolved quickly,
even at that time,
it was as fast as I could learn how to do new shit.
And you know, to give Ben credit to,
he made new art.
We were grinding that shit.
We were grinding that T-Bat wheel,
like as hard as we could.
I'm sure I probably said this in Ben's interview too,
but like both, like the early T-Bat episodes
were all submitted to me
because I was running Equestria Daily's analysis thing
at the time.
Right.
I'd been well established by this point.
I'd been around for probably seven, eight months
and I was pretty famous.
Known for propagating heroes like Dr. Wolf
on another legendary internet figure.
Exactly.
Right, okay.
So I'm working for Equestria Daily,
season four has started
and people submit their videos to me.
And the first T-Bat was submitted to me
and I thought this is fucking dog shit.
Sure.
Because the audio is so bad that I can't listen to it.
And I'm just like, who are these guys?
What is this shit?
Who are these plucky young heroes?
Who do they think they are?
But then like literally two weeks later,
I get submitted another one
that's got like vastly superior art and audio.
It's got like a whole intro segment that's hilarious.
It's got these legendary pony designs.
You guys had easily the best OCs in the fucking entirety.
Agreed.
Our OC game was on point.
If you include the whole,
like all the characters you guys made up
for that one video.
Sticky situation.
Like those are...
Horsefister.
Look, most of our audience doesn't know MLP.
They don't appreciate how meaningful this statement is
because there are hundreds of thousands
of My Little Pony OCs.
That's true.
And there are some very creative people who made them.
There are a lot of great ones.
There are ones who have had whole fandoms.
You know, like fan made OCs with fandoms exist.
Like like a snow drop or something, you know?
Right, yeah, yeah.
You guys made the best OCs in the entire fucking fandom.
It's true.
I think...
And never got the credit you deserve.
You know, it was funny.
We never appeared in like those big group shots of everybody.
And it's entirely because we were like a little bit,
we were a little too original, you know,
where there are like Ben, we made a big mistake
by not playing it like exactly like everybody else was doing.
So like including us, somebody like eventually made like vectors.
But even then they never showed up in anything.
Yeah, like Ben's designs were like cartoony
and like had their own style going on and they were...
I think that was just because like,
this is a big part of how the horseshoe crew,
which they became the PCP came together,
is that we all respected one another's work.
And I think a lot of what we were like pissed off about at the time
was that like, you know, I was famous,
but I had like a kind of squeaky clean character,
which when I eventually changed it, people were mad about.
Yes, they were.
But like you guys never did.
The T-Bap and Jesse...
We had a swear in our name, dude.
Yeah, and you guys, you know,
you'd make constant misogyny jokes and shit.
Yeah, especially me.
And like that kind of shit just didn't fly in that community
because there's a bunch of fucking autistic children
who didn't want that, who just like couldn't parse
what was a joke and what wasn't.
I always thought like we had a certain atmosphere
that didn't get as much shit.
Like I think the number one thing I ever got shit for
was one time when I got really mad at...
There was an episode where Pinkie Pie kept making Fluttershy Cry
and I was like...
I mean, yeah, I think it's fairly in character,
but like I was being like,
oh, that Pinkie Pie is such a like fucking autistic piece of shit, faggot.
And like it was the way that I like vindictively called her autistic.
The audience got really mad,
and I wonder why you said that word.
Well, like, and that's the thing, like even for me,
like I liked you guys' stuff, like you guys and Jesse,
but even I would like hesitate to post it on Equestria Daily
because I knew I'd get shit for it.
You know, like I'd gotten shit for my own videos
for saying that kind of stuff.
Dude, the whole point of the Phantom Horde character
is specifically to mock transsexual people.
Like that's what the characters of...
Well, transgender people.
Right, transgender, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, like, I mean, yeah, and like MLP Phantom was highly steeped in like...
By the way, we have no hatred for them.
We just think it's funny.
It's this whole, it's just hilarious.
Well, that's the thing, like MLP Phantom was highly steeped in like neo-liberalism
and a lot of social justice stuff,
and like we're not even really like idealistically opposed to that kind of stuff.
We just are willing to make fun of shit,
and those, like a lot of them aren't.
That's the big problem with that whole movement.
Yeah, and that's why like promoting T-Bab
and promoting Endless Jazz or Drowning in Horse Shoes
was always really difficult for me,
because like I couldn't bring people to that,
and it would affect the way people looked at me too,
people were like, oh, why are you associating with them?
You know, I'm like, well, because I think it's funny, but like...
And because I'm working for Equestria Daily,
who now I have to represent their interests and stuff,
and like when we would do...
Yeah, when people would draw those crowd shots,
like they'd leave out you guys, I think for that reason.
You know, like I think some of them knew about you guys,
and just didn't like you because you were transgressive.
Well, okay, you know what? Entirely possible.
I'm sticking with my theory that it's because our art designs were too different,
because these people did not have standards.
There was a lot of those like big crowd shots.
Dude, they put like fucking 50 subscriber nobodies in those.
Yeah, exactly. There'd be literal nobodies in these,
and yet Drowning in Horse Shoes and T-Bab wouldn't be there.
And sometimes Gibbon was, you know, sometimes...
If he was in there way more than the rest of us, yeah.
And that's... He was never aggressive.
He was never like, you know, offensive or anything.
I think it was mostly that you guys were offensive to the bronies,
and they're like, literally a bunch of fucking pussies about it, you know?
Like, because they really were.
Like, I knew people who were extremely squeaky clean,
who didn't even had a darker sense of humor, but wouldn't show it, you know?
And like, I mean, you saw what happened to me.
For example?
Well, well, she's...
I don't know anything about her.
No.
She, yeah.
I like that one song she made at whatever.
Yeah.
Um, anyway, I got a lot of trouble with her.
She blocked... She literally told me to stop listening to her music.
I remember that.
Interesting.
Yo, white people, don't listen to my music.
Hashtag cats millionaire.
Yeah.
She wasn't black, but...
I'm just... I'm making a joke.
Like that rapper who told white people not to listen to his music.
Kanye West?
No, Kanye West.
Was that... Like, you made a thing about this.
Like, there was some rap...
Oh, Milo.
Milo.
Well, he didn't say white people don't listen to it.
He just gets mad at white people who say n***a,
even if it's like singing along to his songs.
Right, n***a.
Fuck off.
Yeah.
So...
But yeah, like, I really think...
Like, you saw what happened when I made my pony start smoking.
Like, people blip shit on me.
Yeah, just smoking.
Is that weed?
Is... Oh my God, cigarettes are evil!
Fuck!
But this is a children's show,
and what if children watch your videos and get influenced to smoke?
Like, I'm not even portraying it as a good thing that my character smokes.
I'm portraying him as, like, a half-dead, tired,
don't-be-like-me kids abomination.
People don't want to look into, like, the whole...
When it comes to anything, like, questionable or even slightly edgy,
they're not interested in context.
No.
They're just... I mean, it's like the Anita Sarkeesian thing.
Like, if you're showing X, you're supporting X.
Whether you say so or not, like, context is irrelevant.
If you show, like, a sexy woman, that's you, you know,
just, like, whatever, you're objectifying or whatever.
It's that same argument.
It doesn't make any sense.
It's ridiculous.
Though, it's only ridiculous.
Okay, you know what?
Maybe Anita's right.
If everyone is really stupid, and if nobody's thinking about it,
maybe that's the problem.
Which is not the case.
Which I don't think is actually the case.
If people think attention.
I think most people who take offense to things
are taking offense on behalf of other people...
Right, yeah.
...who aren't actually being affected, you know.
How far in are we on this?
Two and a half hours.
Two and a half?
Yeah.
All right, so you've...
You started up T-Bab.
Yep.
How did that go?
Because you guys got...
That channel was not unsuccessful.
No, we all...
You know, it took a long time for you to pass T-Bab
as best guy ever.
I just did it recently.
Yeah.
Right before the Galco video, I finally reached my goal
of 17,000 subscribers, which was a big deal for me
because I never got there with the T-Bab.
And I was always like, oh, we're so close.
I mean, it was a meme number because it was just like,
oh, yeah, now we'll get the next thousand.
Now we'll get the next thousand.
And it happened to be that T-Bab never quite got to 17,000.
And it was always like, ah, shit.
Fuck, I want to do that someday.
So I finally did it.
And then Galco happened immediately
and the channel doubled in size within a week.
Yeah.
And...
That's how it tends to happen.
And then Mia Maffova happened.
And I mean, it didn't like have an explosion,
but I've gained like 4,000 subscribers or so
over the course of Mia Maffova or something.
Yeah.
And I mean, I know I've got a long way to go,
but this is like huge progress for me.
And my Patreon is like exploding a little bit right now.
So it's everything great.
All good things are happening right now to me.
But, you know, for T-Bab itself, you know, it was...
T-Bab was great.
It was another like confidence boosting thing.
Because, you know, again, I was a different man
than I had been like a couple years ago.
I was more confident and willing to do things
that were, you know, would have scared me off,
you know, in my childhood.
But it was doing it, getting some success,
getting some positive feedback was really good for me.
And especially at that time in my life
where I was working these shitty jobs
and, you know, didn't have my degree,
was like student loan debt,
having to pay that shit off all the time,
like no money, living with my parents,
you know, no girls, you know, at all at this time.
And, yeah, it was just really shitty.
But T-Bab gave me something to feel good about in my life.
I was really achieving something that was making an impact.
It was making people happy.
It was earning me even a little bit of money on the internet.
It was amazing to me.
It blew my mind.
And I was able to work with Ben,
which was usually very good
because Ben is a very competent guy,
but needs the first put to him on occasion.
So, you know, it just was a very positive change
to get, I don't know, to really understand it.
Like, yeah, if I set my mind to something,
I can fucking do it.
I can achieve this shit,
which I'd already kind of understood,
like with the whole, you know, girl thing in college.
It was just, like, this was like a professional validation.
And it was at this point that I was starting to wonder,
like, I really had those thoughts of, like,
like, what is the point of, like, all this school shit I've done?
Like, why have I spent all this time slaving away
at something that I don't even want to do?
Like, I so easily just fell into this, like, you know, career,
quote unquote, career at this point,
that, like, I'm passionate for and I love doing
and is earning me money
and could theoretically be a way to live.
And, like, I talk about how, like,
the most productive time in my life,
now it's me and Mathafa.
But, like, forget, before me and Mathafa happened,
like, and I'm actually,
I'm a ridiculously hard worker on my videos.
It's just they really do take that long to come out
because I have to work all the time.
And I have to, like, go to the gym and shit
that takes up time.
But, like, every Saturday was New Pony Day.
And it's, nothing else matters.
All that matters is that we get the fucking Pony episode done.
And people probably don't remember this,
but we consistently were the first review out on the Saturdays,
despite being also the best review.
We did it every week.
I mean, our only competition was guys like,
I mean, like, Dr. Wolf will get his out real quick.
Granted, you had the advantage of it was unscripted.
True.
But, like, like, yeah.
We would have our intro skits and shit, though,
and animations and all that stuff going on.
But you did those in the week.
Animations.
Well, the animations we had to do during the thing.
Well, I mean, what's your point?
Like, yeah, we planned, dude.
We planned.
We were playing the game.
I'm just saying that, like, it was impressive,
but, like, you know, there was, like,
a certain team of people who was the day ones.
And it was, like, me, you guys and Tom
were always, like, the first starting line,
like, these guys are going to be out.
You'd always beat me just by virtue of being unscripted.
Like, if I hadn't written my video.
Oh, I see.
This is a personal ego thing for you.
I see.
Okay.
Well, I'm not saying, I wasn't even really trying for,
like, being first.
I was always just trying to have that day.
That was our goal.
So, like, oftentimes, I would, like, you know,
dick around for a few hours or something.
But, like, I think in terms of, like,
like, we were probably working at the same speed.
I just was writing out all the videos, you know.
Sure, sure.
We had some advantages.
You know, we had two people doing the work,
etc.
And yeah, we, like, but is that the fact that we worked on
our intros and outros ahead of time,
I think is a good thing about us.
Yeah.
Like, we worked really hard on them.
And it's not, like, it's not easy to get all those
fucking poses.
No, it's not.
Plus, like, the original art Ben would generate.
Like, to this day, I still love some of those.
Like, do you remember the one of, like, Love Lesson Zero?
For one of our fucking intros,
we Ben made an, like, a full, like, fake foe love.
What's the word I'm looking for?
Like, like, harem.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Visual novel is the word I'm looking for.
He made, like, a love visual novel intro thing with, like,
it was keg as, like, a character who was playing, like,
some guy who was hoping to date this girl.
And then, like, Spike was, like, a baddest in Twilight.
Honestly, like, it was nuts.
To our audience, if any of you have never seen any of T-Bat
because you don't care about MLP,
I feel like we've done a real disservice,
all of us in the procrastinators, to ourselves,
by, like, insisting that our MLP days are, like, a meme
that are in the past and we're, like, ashamed.
I suppose.
We all did a lot of great work back then
that people should go back and see.
Phantom reviews, that is great.
Peg reviews is great.
Don't even, don't even, like, go to the, go to T-Bat
and just watch the intros to all the videos
because the intros were fucking awesome.
And so the actors are great.
There's one where it was, like, it was live action,
Phantom Horn trying to draw something
and he had, like, actual hooves.
We worked so hard on that.
How did you do the hooves?
Okay, what we did was, like, I think that was my idea.
We, like, I had seen some video of, like, someone with hooves
and I was, like, I've got an idea.
Let's do, like, a live action drawing thing.
So we bought some hooves.
Like, you can just buy online, like, these, like,
rubbery horse hooves, like, glove type things
that go all the way up to, like, your elbow.
And we spray-painted them blue.
We just spray-painted them blue so they'd look like phantoms.
And then we just, this was, we used, like,
our setup for filming that thing was so fucking jank.
We taped, like, one of our, like, Samsung Galaxy 2s,
like, the top of a thing and, like, filmed downward.
And, like, we had to do so many takes of all that shit,
like, trying to get it just right.
Essentially, the joke is that he tries to draw,
but he has hooves so he spills ink all over.
The joke is that phantom constantly,
phantom is doing, like, a how-to-draw.
He's fucking up everything horribly.
And then somehow, at the end, he ends up with this, like,
beautiful drawing.
It's like, and that's how you do it.
That's how you fucking do it.
Great skit. Love it.
Yeah, these guys would put out, like,
that the opening skits of T-Bap were literally better
than anything else happening in the pony community
unless it was from, like, me or Jesse,
or Hippo, or Gibbon.
And I'm not saying it was worse than any of those,
just that those were also not terrible.
It's true.
And Jesse's stuff, like, I actually have had people tell me
that they've finally gone and watched the horseshoes reviews
and been like, holy shit.
They are that good.
They are legitimately incredible.
Don't even watch my little pony, it doesn't matter.
Just go watch the horseshoe reviews,
watch the intros to T-Bap,
watch at least, like, Gibbon finale or something,
or his last one where Gibbon takes sales off and dies.
Except now he's back.
He's a pirate boy again.
Yeah, and I'm sure I had something worthwhile.
Who knows.
Yeah, I'm sure you did.
Something that's worth revisiting.
Yeah, it was good times.
And, you know, we picked out the other people
that we recognized as not incompetent,
actually with interesting things to say,
and we eventually got together.
And, you know, and I've been just to tell the story again,
because it's fun and I like it.
I think, like, the first time we interacted was when,
like, Ben and I were big fans of All You Guys.
And specifically, Jesse and Gib were our favorites,
and we respected you as an authority figure.
And, you know, enjoyed your content,
but we just liked the personality they showed of,
like, the goofy shit as opposed to, like, the information stuff.
I was never funny.
My videos were, like, really fucking straight forward.
We came to your videos when you were like,
okay, let's get serious about what the fuck this episode's about.
Jesse was the one who was making, like,
like, Jesse's content, it didn't matter
that it was about My Little Pony.
It was just, like, these masterful, like, films
that he was putting together, you know?
So, one day, like, Ben and I,
the first thing we did was we decided, like,
I came up with this goof, like, let's say, for, like,
President's Day is coming up,
let's pretend it's Valentine's Day in this intro,
and we'll say we're doing a special love episode
with Digi Broney.
And so, we did this whole gag where you don't show up,
and then at the very end, it's this whole, like,
crazy, like, zooming out weird, high concept thing,
where, like, the whole episode takes place
constantly zooming out from within the universe,
deep within Digi Broney's eye,
and then, like, at the end, like,
we've zoomed out all the way and you appear,
and you go, it stinks,
and then, My Little Pony, the end of the episode.
God, it was a fucking great bit, it was so good.
I'm so proud of that one.
The editing was tight and perfect at that moment.
So, and, yeah, I don't know, whatever,
like, we, you recognize that point,
and then Give, actually, this was before that,
Give made, like, a thing where he showed us
in, like, his big analysis roundup videos.
He animated us a little, we loved that.
But then, eventually, I don't even know how we,
oh, of course, we did the Q&A, and the Q&A,
and we all, he found out that we loved you guys,
and at some point, there was a conversation
where we all decided to do a horse cast,
blah, blah, blah, we all got together
and started doing stuff, and became friends,
and just kept doing that shit.
We were rushing through this part
because we've told the story so many fucking times.
Exactly.
Like, hopefully, this isn't your first
PCP interview or episode, because, like,
we've literally told this fucking story
of how we all met dozens of times.
Certainly dozens of times, yeah.
Yeah.
And that's showbiz.
How far in are we?
We are two hours, 38 minutes.
38 minutes?
38.
Feels like, feels like we've reached the hours.
I'll just keep asking you about shit, I guess.
Yeah, well, so, so, Teabab, you guys kept doing it for,
we stuck with it for a while.
I want to emphasize this as well,
that when season four ended, me and Hippo were done.
Like, or Gibbon at the time.
Mostly, yeah.
I think we did like a couple more here and there.
Gibbon's, like, his final video came out
like a couple months later, I think.
Yeah.
But after that, yeah, he did like the one about
Klopp or whatever, and one about Diamond Tiarra,
and that was about it.
He doesn't like, I love that video.
I think it's great.
I think he just doesn't like the way
like people react to it or something like that.
Yeah, that's right.
Of course, in a while or something.
But he, he went on for a little while,
but didn't really go farther.
I quit in, like, after season four,
I hardlined, stopped covering My Little Pony,
stopped watching it, never told about it again.
I left the fandom that piece of shit.
I did.
I actually.
How dare you.
So for those who don't know, this is a huge meme
in the My Little Pony, not even a meme,
something they take seriously.
Like, it's an offense.
You can commit it a crime.
It's, it's, it's like, you either are in or out.
There is no like.
You're either an ally or an enemy.
There's no like, waning interest or like,
hey guys, I just want to work on other stuff.
It's like, if you're not still producing
My Little Pony content, then you have left the fandom.
And that's the phrase they use.
And like, yeah, it's like a huge offense,
like to leave the fandom.
It's very silly.
So I left the fandom and Gibbon wasn't really doing much,
but like, Jesse took a whole fucking year
of putting together Horseshoe Finale.
Like he wasn't done until 2015.
And then you guys came back for season five
and did the whole fucking season in podcast form
just without the animations.
I was already on the fence.
Like there was much discussion as to whether or not
to even do it because we had like other ideas.
And the only reason you did was because the Patreon.
Because we had Patreon.
It's like, I mean, and Ben was a big driving force
for that stuff, wanting to do it for the money.
And you know, nothing against him.
I understand, but.
But like season, season four ended.
There was a huge gap between season four and five.
And that's when you guys got out the,
the like big gun videos.
Is that when we did?
Phantom reviews had to open at that time.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
Because you know, you guys were working on like huge projects
that were like kind of operating in the background
of the weekly reviews, which again,
come together in like an hour.
You know, like we, we all were like,
it's funny to think that like we're currently
in this period of like,
let's get back to making smaller, easier videos
when we all launched our careers by doing videos
that we made in literally a couple hours.
That's the fascinating thing about it
that I think about a lot.
It's, and I'm always, I'm sort of lamenting to myself
the fact that the pony days were perfect for me
in terms of like the time crunch
because having that deadline of get it out
as soon as fucking possible,
you've got to meet this goddamn deadline, be the first.
Having that goal in my framework
of like how we were making videos
was so helpful for a guy like me
who does have a tendency to get lost in the details
and obsess over little things
that ultimately just to have diminishing returns.
Having that crunch time was so good
and that's why I describe it
as like the most productive time in my life,
like working on those.
Except for Mia Mafia, that was the best.
Yeah, Mia Mafia unquestionably is like vastly.
I cut down on like,
this is the first time in my life
I really have cut into my sleep
and my like ability to live,
to make content in a big way.
And like, we're talking like two hours of sleep a night
and it was hard.
And I fueled myself with coffee and caffeine
and like, God, I don't know
what my work guys were thinking of me.
I mean, I did the work, but I don't know.
I don't know, maybe it was okay.
I really don't remember.
Hopefully it was okay and it was a big deal.
I just, I often think about like,
what would my coworkers think
if they, you know, knew all this shit?
And like, I have, I regret it,
but I have told them that like I do this shit
and I have shared like the channel name
just because like, what are you gonna do
if they's like, hey, what's your channel?
What are you gonna say?
I don't wanna talk about it.
You gotta, I know you just gotta pony it up.
Hey, I love my little pony.
Um, so I wonder if any of them are watching.
What if any of them, like,
I'm walking around in my work, right?
All these guys are working on software development and shit.
They're thinking about like enterprise level systems
deploying to like various companies,
like fucking Boeing and Honeywell,
like big defense contractors and shit.
I'm thinking about like, I gotta go home
and work on this like anime review
and like tell, you know, like 17,000 people
and now like getting close to 40,000 people.
How good fucking Angel's Egg is
and like how fucking God has written like shit.
How great this one obscure boss
in this new Kingdom Hearts spinoff.
That's an important video.
Fucking game is.
I liked that video.
That was good.
That was, that's a message
that I'm really glad I got to get out.
God, thank God for me and Mavva enabling me
to get out all these things that I had bottled up.
Yeah.
Well, that's what I'm so excited about
is that me and Mavva, to me,
the funny thing about it is that to you,
it was put in as little effort as possible.
But what it really represents to me is a middle ground.
That is my, that is my low effort, you know,
the middle ground.
That's that's as low effort as I can go.
It's yeah, it's a middle ground
because for me, my content has gotten to a point
where it's all either a good enough script
that DeVu can do it or I'm going to do it
and therefore it's going to be nothing.
You know, like I am not going to do anything with this
except for what is required for it.
It's not that my content is like all exactly the same.
Sometimes something different or interesting happens,
but like me and Mavva kicked it up a little.
Like I look at it and I think,
okay, this is like what I'm doing,
but if I actually thought about each video
and like what I could basically,
if I thought of it as a video you can make in a day,
instead of a video you can make in an hour,
I was explaining this to you that like to me,
there's the two kinds of videos I make are a written video
which takes a day or two and then it's out of my hands
or a vlog, which is it has to be done in one sitting,
you know, like one concentrated burst
and I can do four of them in a day.
And me and Mavva to me was like,
oh, this is what the middle of that would look like,
of like I could spend a few hours on a video.
And I mean, I've done stuff like this before.
I don't know if you ever saw my handfuls of Zen videos.
Sure, I've seen those, at least most of them.
That's like very similar mindset to me and Mavva,
which is like it's unscripted.
The people want more of those, you know.
I want to make more of those.
And like it's that combination of like unscripted,
but there's lots of notes
and there's a level of editing to it
and there's like prep work to be done.
It can be done in a day, but it's, you know,
it's not something that's just fucking,
I turned on a camera and then uploaded it, you know.
And like what was so exciting
to me watching me and Mavva was like,
if, like all I could think was if you put out just,
I mean, even four of these a month,
like if you put the level of effort that it took
to make three me and Mavvas into one video
and released it once a week,
this is the greatest channel of all time, you know.
Like one video a week at the level
of three me and Mavvas of effort.
And you can do seven me and Mavvas of effort in a week
if you had to, but you're not going to time crunch yourself
like that for the rest of your life.
But if you left your job,
you could put seven me and Mavvas of effort in a day.
That's why it's really not a joke.
Like what a big difference me leaving my job will really make.
This is not a meme to trick people to get money out of you.
It really will be a world changing thing for my channel.
And if you care about getting more content faster,
that's the thing to do.
Like I hope people like really sit back.
I know it's harder for the audience
because they don't make videos.
So like fully process the difference here.
But like Nate spent those two months that you worked on
like the loose from the biscuit hammer video.
Like I won't say you were working
as much as you did during me and Mavva,
but like that was consistent work.
Every night I worked every day.
Like my evenings were editing for two months.
That's what they were.
Yeah.
And that video was overdone.
You shouldn't have spit that log on it.
Agreed.
But like imagine-
You can see the work that's in it though.
You can see it.
Imagine though if you could have done that
with if you didn't have a day job,
you could have done it in two weeks.
And with me and Mavva, those 30 videos,
you could have done, if you didn't have a day job
and you had done me and Mavva exactly the same way,
you literally could have done two months.
Like you could have just cut out the time you spent at work
and done another me and Mavva in that time.
It could have been two videos a day
and that could have been two months worth of content.
If you guys want to see best guy ever stockpile,
like you know, I mean what you,
let's say you didn't have to work for two months
and you decided to do me and Mavva level videos all day every day,
you're going to end up with like a year,
and let's say you stagger the releases for once a week.
You've got a year of videos in two months.
You know, I hear you on that,
but you know one thing that people don't really talk about as much
that I think a lot about when it comes to me and Mavva
is how I really went out of my way to make it an event,
to make it a spectacle.
That's my Huey's Law in action right there.
Which is great.
Yeah, like it's got its own theme song,
it's got its own logo, it's got merchandise.
And only you could deliver on that
because I fall into this trap that I've talked about continuously.
And it's a real psychological principle that
if you talk about something you're planning to do,
you're less likely to do it
because it gives you the vindication of like,
you know, just describing it makes it,
you feel like you did it.
And you don't fall into that.
You talk about stuff years in advance.
Yeah, that's true.
Like, I mean, I've known about your Ghost in the Shell video
for two fucking years.
I announced it two years ago, but yeah, yeah.
Like, I mean-
I did not give up on it at all at that point.
Yeah, like, there's just this, somehow you are just
disciplined in a way that you could,
if I had announced me a Mavva, I wouldn't have done it.
Yeah.
You know, and I, as you may know,
I did a whole month of a video every day, October 2014,
and I never mentioned what I was doing
until like the last video.
Really?
Like, or towards the end,
I did a video on the first three episodes of Shirobako,
and I said like, oh, somebody who's been doing this deliberate
one video a day, all month, and here's the fucked up part.
No one noticed I was doing it.
Not one commenter ever mentioned that I done a video every day,
all month.
Between yours and mine, that difference right there.
Just because mine were of such like,
my audience was like weird and in this transitional phase
into anime.
So like, some of the videos would be like,
the biggest video I've ever made,
and then another one would have like,
1,000 views, you know?
So like, people just weren't seeing all of them.
Was this because you were afraid that you might not be,
you know, miss a deadline or something?
It was 100% that I was afraid if I talked about it,
I wouldn't finish it.
That's okay.
Because that had proven true every time
I've ever talked about a project.
I mean, because I'm with you on that,
but to focus on me, because my problems matter more than yours,
this is your interview.
That's right.
Like my, the fear I had,
which was definitely a fear,
and of course it's inevitable with this,
is that I would fail.
Is that I would mess up.
I actually had some other ideas in mind beforehand
that I floated around with a couple of people,
just seeing what time.
I think this is why you can do it and I can't,
is because you're way more afraid of failure than I am.
That's true.
Because what actually would have been the consequence
of me and Matt have a failing?
Me being embarrassed.
Exactly, that's it.
That's it.
Like, your audience would have been like,
well, he couldn't do it.
What a, what an asshole.
You know, like you would have felt like dumb
for a couple of days, maybe a couple of weeks.
I don't care about that.
Like I fuck up so frequently that it doesn't matter.
Like I've got a character as somebody who like,
you know, like my audience literally doesn't expect
me to finish anything that I start,
because I've started so many shows that just die.
But like for you, like just the sheer level of like,
I can't fail at this.
Yeah, that's true.
Carried it all the way through.
Yep.
And that's a good thing.
I think it's a healthy mindset to have.
If you're proud of the product and you know.
And I always am.
Yeah.
You look very tired.
Um, I am somewhat tired.
We're almost at three hours.
Yeah.
We can crank out a little more.
Some of them are like a few minutes short of three hours.
It doesn't have to be exact.
I want three hours, god damn it.
Let's talk about, um.
I'm wondering if, if somebody finally interviews me
in this series, like,
or is it going to be three hours?
Or am I going to, because there's like a thing.
Yours will be like everyone's to combine.
We're talking like a 25 hour interview here.
That'd be fucking epic.
It would be epic.
Well, it really depends on who's interviewing me
and how long are they willing to go.
Maybe we could, you know, I was wondering about that.
Maybe we could split it up.
Everyone does a piece, you know.
Oh, that'd be interesting, right?
Could all come with our questions.
I feel like nobody's curious enough about me
to want to do an interview.
We know everything.
Yeah.
There's nothing left.
We'll have to come up with something.
Yeah.
Um, what, um, what's your favorite anime?
Why are you asking me?
What's your favorite anime?
I'm filling time, Digi.
You wanted to go through.
I, we're almost there.
We can do it.
I know your favorite anime has grown the gun.
Your favorite bomb is one piece.
Yeah.
Um, your favorite movie is American Beauty.
That's true.
You want to say anything?
I'd be happy to.
And, uh, I think if anybody's seen American Beauty,
you, you understand very much why.
Um, it is a movie about casting off the shackles
of societal expectations and like embracing your dreams
is really what it's about.
And every character in the movie does that to an extent,
or like in their own way.
For example, I'm going to spoil this movie, by the way.
So if you give a shit, uh,
I'd highly recommend watching it.
So, you know, do whatever you want.
But so the main character, Kevin Spacey,
he wants to fuck his teenage daughter's hot ass, uh,
like girlfriend, like her, her buddy.
And she's like a captain of the cheerleading squad.
She's like a model, uh, Mena Savari,
whatever, some famous actress.
Like he wants to fuck this girl.
And she's 17, 18, something along those lines.
So she's pretty darn young.
And like he sets up his whole life, uh,
where he, he did like,
so he worked this like shitty corporate job
and, uh, he fucking hated it.
It's actually very similar to Fight Club in a lot of ways.
Like he just says, fuck it one day, I'm done.
And I, you know, it's slipping my mind right now
because it's been a little while since I've seen the show.
Why exactly he does it?
I have to think about that.
Oh, I remember it's because he meets a new neighbor,
a new neighbor, neighbor moves to town,
like the weird kid who gives him some weed
and he gets high and he just has some revelations.
You know what, fuck this shit, I'm done.
He quits his goddamn job, um, in a, in a brilliant way.
Like he literally says, like to his boss,
like as they're doing like corporate restructuring,
look, if you, I'm going to, uh, quit now.
Um, and if I'm going to say that you asked me,
if you could blow me and sexually harass me, uh,
if you don't give me like a huge severance package.
And, uh, oh, by the way,
the movie starts with him just saying like as an announcer,
I'm going to be dead in one year.
So know that going in.
That's just how it starts.
So he does this.
Oh, and he also has like some information
about like shady business dealings the company's been doing.
Anyway, he, he finally like mans up
and uses his leverage to fuck over this company.
That's been screwing him and not treating him
like the way that he deserves to be treated.
And, um, he just, he pieces and he leaves.
And like now he's got like this money
where he can just live on for like a while.
He's got like a year's salary,
which lines up perfectly with like the time
he's going to die at the end.
And he immediately goes and gets a shitty job
at a burger joint just to get another job.
So he's like, I want to do something in my life.
And so he starts working there
because he wants a job with zero responsibility anymore.
Like this guy is just unburdening himself.
That's what he's, he's unburdening himself
with the shackles of like, of, of his job.
And like then his family is another huge thing.
So he's got his wife, Carolyn,
and his daughter, June, Judy, whatever.
And his wife is a frigid bitch, uh, who is like just not,
I don't know, they don't vibe, you know,
they've grown apart over the years.
They used to be really into each other.
But like, so, so he starts like exercising, right?
He starts working out.
And over the course of the year, he gets fucking fit.
He gets swole to an extent as much as you can get in a year.
And it's just, it's just about the self-improvement shit, right?
Like he, like something happens to this guy,
he has an awakening and he's like, you know what,
fuck this, I'm going to take charge of my life
and actually go for the things I want.
So I think you can tell why something like that
would appeal to me.
But it's not just about that guy,
because all the other characters do it too.
Like, uh, Carolyn, his wife, she starts cheating on him.
She starts having an affair.
But she is like so happy and empowered by it,
that like it's, it's not good to cheat on people.
But what she's realizing is like,
I have been unhappy in this situation I'm in.
I need to do something.
I need to like change.
This has got to end.
This is no good.
And so she has her own little development arc,
related around that.
And the daughter, Judy, I believe it's Judy,
like, you know, she's best friends with this girl
that like her father lusts after.
And she feels like so self-conscious
and like thinks she's ugly and all this shit.
And this new neighbor kid moves to town and um,
he uh, uh, uh, like he introduces her.
He like makes her believe that she's beautiful
and like makes her feel happy for the first time in her life.
And they fall in love and they, you know, do the do.
And it's totally hot.
She totally shows her tits.
Nate just mimed to be like finger-druful.
I did the finger, I did the hole in your finger
and put your other finger through the hole.
Yeah, they did the sex.
It was sick.
And uh, it's, it's about, you know,
it's about all that shit.
It's about like just saying fuck it
and doing what you really want to do with your life
and not giving a fuck what anybody thinks anymore.
That's what it's really about.
I can't remember if I talked about this
in Ben's interview or where I did,
but like that I'm endlessly fascinated by the fact
that your favorite movie is American Beauty
and his is American Psycho.
That's one of my favorites,
but that is interesting, isn't it?
That they're both like,
not just that the titles are the same,
but like just the idea,
like one is all about like this vision of self-betterment
and like becoming the perfect you.
And the other one is about like this underlying
insane neurosis behind everybody.
And I just feel like it matches up
with both of you perfectly.
Isn't that interesting?
You guys are, you and Ben to me have always been like,
like mirror reflections of the same person.
Like a nega version.
One of you is the nega version of the other.
I don't know which.
Because Ben and I talk and I've come to understand
through a lot of the PCP conversations,
I have this extremely optimistic view about people.
I really think that humanity can like evolve
and develop and change.
There is a future for us if we work hard at it
and strive to achieve it.
Ben is extremely not like that.
He's like, no, people are fucked.
Why are we wasting our time?
And it's weird because that seems like
such a fundamental difference.
But like aside from like the basic mindset you two have,
like the actual like person is extremely similar.
Yeah.
Like the ways you talk and think and act are very similar.
But then like the mentality is totally different
and like almost opposed.
Maybe it goes to show that like,
because Ben and I, you know, we grew up together,
exposed to all the same shit for the most part,
that like that kind of that part of your brain,
like your your fundamental like psychological
and not psychological philosophical approach
to like the way you live.
Maybe it's less impactful on your personality
than we would assume.
You know, maybe we are a little more divided
in our brains than we think.
Yeah, maybe it's maybe maybe you have the same left brain
but totally different right brains or whatever the fuck.
Yeah, maybe that's nobody fucking science me on that.
Just spitballing philosophical questions.
And by the way, I just wanted to say that at the end
of American Beauty, what is the best thing about that movie
is that the way it ends is wonderful.
It ends with, so you know, at the beginning of the movie,
Kevin Spacey says like, I'm going to be dead in a year.
Here's like the story of that year.
So all these crazy things happen,
like everybody changes their life,
all this crazy improvements are happening.
And Kevin Spacey at the end,
through some shenanigans that are just too complex to go into,
he ends up getting murdered by his next door neighbor.
Okay, well, his next door neighbor is like the father
of the new kid who's like, who's changing everybody's life.
That guy is like a military dad, but he's actually gay.
And he's been repressing it like his entire life.
And over the course of the movie, you find out that like,
oh, wow, this guy's actually gay.
And like on this last night, he just,
he's like feeling really vulnerable
because his son is going to run away with the daughter
like they've had this gigantic fight.
So he just walks over to his neighbor.
Like he ends up at Kevin Spacey's garage
and he's just like, it's raining.
And he's like, what the fuck's happening?
And Kevin Spacey is just like, hey, come in.
No, it's okay, man.
What's, I'll take care of you.
What's going on with your life?
And they, like he ends up kissing him.
And so like it's that, it's at that moment
that the colonel or whatever realizes like,
someone knows, someone knows my fucking secret now.
And long story short, like, so he comes over,
he kills Kevin Spacey,
just shoots him in the back of the head from behind.
But, and what's cool about it is like,
all of these characters are set up
like they could be the one who killed Kevin Spacey.
Like his daughter kind of has a reason to do it
because like she's going to run away
and like he might try to stop her.
And the wife actually has a gun and is headed home
because like she's fed up with like,
the stuff that he's been doing
to like get back at her for cheating on him
with that other guy.
So he gets killed by the next or neighbor guy.
And, but like it's the way that he dies.
And the film, you know, really focuses on this.
Like he's looking at like a picture of his family,
specifically I think of his little daughter
when she was a little girl.
And he's just like so overjoyed
that he was able to experience
like the life of his daughter
and like his wife when they were in love.
And like he gets shot and he's dying.
And like the characters like they come in,
they see him dead, but they look at him and he's smiling.
He's smiling and there's this speech at the end
of how like when you're dying,
it's not like the lights got instantly.
It's that all the experiences of your life
like stretch out like a vast ocean
and you just witness them
as they're passing you by.
And it goes on to an infinite degree.
So it's almost like you never actually die.
It's just like your existence continues forever.
And like the takeaway from that is just like,
that's the value that life has.
And don't waste it on bullshit
that you don't give a fuck about.
You know, do things that are meaningful to you
and you find value in and bring you joy
and legitimate satisfaction.
And you know, as a guy who lived
like a little faggot bitch for a long time in his life
and then something changed
and I decided to do things differently.
You know, things like that.
Guys like Kamina who just do whatever
the fuck they want to do
and don't give a shit about the consequences.
Even though I'm not that guy, I really want to be
and I work to be more like that.
There you go. That's me.
Sick.
It's the best guy ever.
Gains, bruh.
Are we at three hours yet?
We're past three hours.
We're at 302.
We did it.
Yay!
A full analysis of American beauty
took us over to the other part.
Yes, it did.
Literally, you could probably repackage that
as a behemoth of a problem.
Maybe I will.
A geomath of a...
G or something, yeah.
All right, well.
A geomath of a...
God may wilt fucking end.
I was thinking with a J, but that worked out.
Someone had pointed out in the comments
on the Aromanga video that we did last night,
that it's literally the night after BMF,
so it basically isn't even over.
I know that, like I said in the last video,
like, yo, I probably won't even take a day off,
and so I didn't.
Or maybe that was actually a day later, but whatever.
Nor have you.
This is also...
Yeah, here we are again.
See, I'm not quitting people.
I'm a real deal.
I'm committed.
Neither.
We're not capable.
This is why you should be supporting
both of us on Patreon.
Right.
We are human content machines.
We don't have other purposes in this world.
That's exactly correct.
This is the only thing we know how to do.
I have eliminated all other distractions in my life,
deliberately, so that I can focus on doing the thing
that I have found brings me my satisfaction and my joy,
just like Mr. Kevin Spacey would want from American Beauty.
Yeah, and if you like listening to me and Nate
talk on these bullshit podcasts,
get Nate's Patreon up to a point
where he feels comfortable moving out,
maybe he and I will more successfully than I did
with Ben and Davoo.
Not that I had ever really planned those two
to be like my guys that I was going to do stuff with,
but me and you have a lot of ideas
of what we could do if we lived close together.
We sure do.
So move Nate and I nearer.
Yes, nearer, nearer.
Not in the same house.
And you know what, I'm done with that life.
Yeah, Ben is a lazy piece of shit,
but you know, I might be willing to indulge him
and just move to wherever he is to get him involved.
Atlanta's not a bad place if he wants us all to go there.
And I wouldn't mind.
Like I resent him for forcing me my whole life
to just go along with his pace
because he is the lazy piece of shit.
And if I want him involved,
I have to slave around what he wants.
But you know, in this case,
it might actually work out pretty nice.
So hey, maybe that'll happen.
Yeah, or somewhere else, whatever.
Hashtag get us all somewhere.
Yeah, hashtag buy me out, nigga.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, everybody, thanks for listening.
Thanks, guys.
Hope you enjoyed.
Look forward to Tom Mage and maybe me in the future.
We'll see what happens.
Bye, guys.