Welcome everyone to PCP Destructive Criticism.
Just whenever there's someone who is a PCP viewer, or any other correspondent of any of us, or potentially even one of us, who has made a thing that isn't a video, especially a video game that can be played.
This is a series now, even though this is just an impromptu idea we just had.
Hypothetically, it may happen again in the future, so we have to make it a series now. We have to capitalize on the future potential.
So this is Nemesis.
We're playing Nemesis, a game by what's his name?
I don't remember. Well, I think on social media he's just called Nemesis Admins. We'll just call him Nemesis Admins.
Well, this game is on Newgrounds, but it's also at www.nemesis-game.com.
He sent a message to Digi saying, yo, I've been listening to the PCP.
Of course he messaged Digi. What a fucking pleb.
A pleb tier PCP viewer.
And he said that listening to your show gave me the motivation to finish it, or to really finish working on his project.
To not be one of those average suck boys who just sits around and doesn't actually do the work to make the shit happen.
That's fair.
Actually, this is the third weapon.
I won't get into specifics about what we can talk about.
Right now, Ben is playing, and I'm just here next to the microphone.
We're too lazy to actually record the video. This is mostly for the guy who made the game.
If you want to experience the game while we talk, you can just go play it.
Go visit the website if you would.
We figure the guy who made the game knows the game well enough that he can just feel in the blanks.
He'll know what we're talking about.
The reason why I wanted to give this guy direct feedback, or open letter feedback, is because it's professionally presented enough.
And the guy seems like professionally in his dialogue.
Seems like he's pretty serious about it, which is cool.
And will be accepting to people talking about it and giving notes.
So fucking...
How do I begin?
This game is very similar to a Lambria game.
The designer himself said, like, yes, this is basically a Luftraus.
I was annoyed because in his messages, the one that I saw you quoting, he didn't say anything about Luftraus.
And I was like, well, this is just Luftraus.
That's fine. Whatever.
Gotta start somewhere.
I would totally advise that if you're making games, just rip one off completely.
Yeah, sure, that's fine.
If you're gonna make a guitar song, you gotta play someone else's song 5,000 times so you can get an idea of how it works.
Absolutely, of course.
If it's a game thrown up for free, then you're essentially ripping off Lambria.
So that's two birds one stone, right?
Yeah.
So for someone who hasn't played Luftrausers, I immediately jump in and I'm like, this is fucking impossible.
Well, of course it's impossible. It's a game where you just go until you die.
So you always die.
It's just a question of how long.
That's the tricky point for me is that I'm not into games like that.
It's just sort of fundamentally.
So basically there's two goals for me, which is talk about what the game is like from the perspective of someone like me,
and then talk about trying to hone in on what I think the dev is going for.
I don't fucking know.
I think it's gonna be a super annoying demographic and just know what I think, right?
Yeah, just completely not the target audience for this game.
Not completely not. I don't hate these kinds of games. I just don't get that into them.
You are much more the target demographic for this game.
Yeah, I never went crazy for Luftrausers or anything.
I didn't buy the final version, but yeah, it is the sort of game that I'm generally into.
The fact that you didn't immediately...
Holy shit!
We just got to a giant fucking...
A new fucking thing has appeared.
We just got to a giant flail? We didn't see that before.
It's just getting intense now.
Like I said, I have not really played Luftrausers.
I don't know if this thing is just taken from Luftrausers or not.
What? This is like...
They keep fading in and out, too.
This is an interesting enemy. I'm sure it's taken from something.
This is two out of nowhere.
It's too much like Luftrausers.
I don't know. I didn't see anything like that in Luftrausers, but I'm sure.
Just like that one time where the main character in one piece was picking out pants, that was Luftrausers.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Gotcha.
So the fact that you didn't immediately gawk at how weak your weapon was like I did?
No, yeah, I did.
This is too fucking...
No, I did. That was my first thing.
The first plane has a main weapon that is completely worthless.
But I don't know. Maybe that's intentional.
Probably not.
Well, this is one of those games where you've got 15 minutes to get in and get out because it's on new grounds.
You're going to lose interest immediately.
That doesn't make any sense.
That has nothing to do with whether the main weapon is too weak or not.
What I thought was like...
He was saying that just in relation to the difficulty in general.
I get that it's supposed to be hard.
For me personally, I generally prefer video games where the first time you dive into the mechanics
everything just sort of pre-scripted works correctly.
So that you know how things are supposed to go.
Because when I first played it and I immediately died, I was like wait, did I do something wrong?
I wasn't sure.
That's just you not getting it.
Well, I did get it. It took me two extra minutes to get it.
Again, this is different.
Me personally, I do have the patience if I decide to sit down with a game.
So consider the giant swathes of people who will in fact click away after 30 seconds, right?
To make that really great first impression.
Well, this game is not for that.
Okay, well, this video is not for that.
But if it is, then there you go, right?
Because I don't think there'd be any harm in just like you have this starting wave of enemies
that shows up that are obviously super easy and weak.
And then they get knocked out in one hit by your thing.
And then the actual challenge begins.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, quit poking me with your thing.
Sorry, totally unrelated.
I wasn't fucking...
I just wasn't sure what to do at first.
Because I wasn't sure if it was going to be one of those games you got to get to an objective goal.
If you got to shoot down a certain number of dudes.
Because there's no score either.
At least not on the screen, right?
You only see the number of enemies you kill at the end.
So I just didn't know what to do.
Which also brings me to the fact that the screen is very barren.
It's not barren.
Well, look, there's nothing on the screen right now.
Yeah, because it just started.
Soon there will be huge swarms of planes and bullets and shit all flying around.
I don't know, man. Some of your criticisms seem a little weird so far.
I like density. I'm far of hashtag density core.
What are you talking about?
Give me one minute and you will see the screen will become dense with shit.
Yeah, and I'm just saying that you have rounds of this game,
sessions of this game that last three minutes,
and the first minute is going to be mostly empty.
So that's 30% of the game that's mostly empty.
That's like an RPG with 30% empty corridors.
The better you get at the game, the longer you'll last,
and proportionally the less time you'll spend in the boring first 30 seconds.
I guess.
I don't really see what the advantage is though of having sort of a barren first 30 seconds.
What's the alternative?
Just having more interesting shit go on.
Just have it start immediately?
I guess it could get going faster.
Yeah, probably there's nothing...
Oh, I get hurt if I go out into space.
Yeah, it would probably be fine if it started up faster.
Because once you've played a little bit, you don't really need to fuck around with the first...
But really, it's like 30 of them at once.
This third plane has a really good weapon for that.
We'll get to that in a bit.
Yeah, I guess in principle I agree that the faster it gets going, the better.
But whatever, it's really not that bad.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Now that I'm seeing how far we're able to get in, and now there's just a bunch of shit,
then that's pretty reasonable.
But my point is, compared to Loot Browsers, that game has more stuff going on immediately.
Or at least it's got a smaller screen.
It's got a smaller field of view.
It's also hung up on the barrenness of the screen.
The size of the screen is an advantage.
I like that better than Loot Browsers because it just lets you concede more and you can play smarter.
I guess I'm not trying to propose the idea that it's bad.
I just want it to be something that is considered.
I want to know how much was it intentional.
I think it is a good design choice to make the screen proportionally bigger.
I guess my point is, I just want it to be something that is kept in mind.
Because barrenness and too small a screen was the number one pitfall that I fell into when I made an RPG.
Where everything was so fucking small.
This is not an RPG. This was working totally differently.
Sometimes it works, sometimes it doesn't.
I just thought, was the dev keeping that in mind when making it?
That's why I'm bringing it up.
So let's talk about the second weapon for the second plane.
Hang on, there's three planes.
Before we get into that, I want to say that I do really like the opening screen.
It's like a pilot console and you have to hit all the buttons that the game requires you to use.
That unlocks the console and then you can get started.
I don't know, it's just neat.
It's neat because you just gotta press the buttons and now you know the buttons.
For me, that was also confusing. It gave me this first 30 seconds.
Wait, how does this thing work?
It was awesome. It was unequivocally great and I love that.
If I'm going into a video game and I know for a fact I'm going to give it a really long trial period.
Let's say everyone in my circle is saying it's amazing.
Then something like that is great because I've been given the promise that extra effort is going to be worth it.
It's not extra effort to press four buttons to start the game.
You're just not sure what the buttons are going to mean, right?
That's what the point of it is, is that it shows you the buttons and it prompts you like these are the buttons and these are what they do.
Now hit them in order to start the game up.
It feels like powering on a console.
I like it. I like it. I like it. I do.
You see the screen you're on right now? You're on the main screen.
It took me a while to realize that those blue lights in the middle don't do anything.
They're just denoting the different volume levels.
In fact, they're lined up symmetrically right next to the level selection buttons.
It made me think that they were inherently coupled somehow.
Then a little bit later, I was like, oh, okay, so there we go.
Over there is basically unrelated.
Those buttons over there is the volume choices.
The stuff on the right is the level options, right?
Once again, I guess I'm basically framing these problems, but more queries or more statements, I guess,
where obviously leading players into confusion or forcing them to get outside of their comfort zone
to do an old thing in a new way has a lot of value,
but it should be done very consciously, and you know exactly what kind of misconstruions
and confusions you're going to put the player on, right?
So you can manipulate them better.
You don't necessarily want to send them into a confused tizzy unintentionally,
because then that might not be a good experience, right?
Well, I suppose not. I don't think that's what's happening here.
I'm just saying that, like, I don't know.
And I guess as a general principle, I would agree with you,
that you're confusing the players bad and you shouldn't do this.
Well, I'm just saying that, like, just know what will cause confusion.
Okay.
Because I remember, like...
Well, I eat nothing in this game. Nothing in this game would do that, but okay.
Well, like, you know, 10 seconds of, hmm, what's this, right?
Which, you know, in a game that, like, as he says, you'd play for 15 minutes,
that comprises, like, 5% of the whole game experience.
So it is very relevant, you know?
No, it isn't. You're totally out of line and you're totally off base.
You just flip through games, like, in the span of minutes, you know?
It very much happens.
People could, like, watch a Let's Play and they might click away in 2 minutes,
based on the experience the Let's Player has.
It's a really tight market, you know?
You have to really, really work and manipulate the player to command their attention.
I... I guess.
Yeah. So...
You know, it may as well if you're gonna put lots of work into it.
So what would you...
Okay, if you could change something, if you could change something about this game
and deviate this issue, what would you do?
Uh, I would probably put, like, a little graphical separation line
between the volume options and then the level selections
and maybe I'd make them a slightly different color.
Right?
Okay.
Yeah.
I remember in the Art of Game design, the Book of Lenses,
there's one part where the author talks about how he was making, like, an Aladdin game,
where you're riding off flying carpet.
And, like, there's a part where you get up into, like, a big chamber
and you're supposed to go straight to, like, a throne area in this throne room.
Now, the players would always go up into that room
and just wander around not knowing where to go.
And so he put a fucking line on the floor that leads to the throne
and everyone will always go to the throne immediately, right?
Sure.
But then in co-op mode, uh, they wanted to make it to where people wouldn't all go to the throne
because only one person can grab the scepter,
so they wanted everyone to just sort of...
They wanted one person to go to the throne and everyone else to hang out, right?
So they drew a line that goes to the throne
and then splits off into three random directions.
The three players in co-op would always split off into random directions
with those lines on the floor that none of them consciously noticed, you know?
So it's all about manipulation of the player.
Yeah.
Um, you know, just stuff to keep in mind.
Okay.
But so, for ref, we're just talking about the opening menu.
We're just talking about the menu screen right now.
Yeah, man.
Okay.
If the menu feels good, the game feels good.
That's not...
Wait, I don't... Who said that?
That guy who remixes everything that we say into weird shitpost videos.
Oh, was that Steve?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So anyway, uh...
Well, yeah, we were going to talk about the weapons.
So the opening weapon of the game.
See, I just feel so demoralized when I start up the game for the first minute
because I feel like the weapon isn't even doing shit, right?
Yeah, my...
Well, my first...
My first criticism of the game is that it is Luth Trousers,
which I think is a comprehensive...
which I think says all I need to say.
But...
Okay, but I know that I'm seen as some sort of pariah
because I believe in originality and I think that it's valuable.
Like I'm some kind of moron or something.
But...
Okay, so I'm just going to leave that one.
I'm just going to leave that where it lies.
My only other criticism...
Well, my second criticism is that, yeah,
the first plane has two weapons.
There's like a spread fire shotgun machine gun,
although it doesn't fire that fast,
and a laser beam.
And they're both underpowered,
but the first one is underpowered to the point.
The main weapon is useless and I never used it.
It's unbelievably terrible.
Like I did not kill anything with it.
Yeah, and then you basically...
I think if you just play one round with the first plane,
you can then go back to the main menu and unlock the second plane
and then the third plane,
and they each have in turn more powerful weapons than the last.
I liked the second plane better than the first,
and I liked the third plane better than the second.
Although the third plane is like...
Overpowered almost.
Yeah, I think it's probably a little overpowered,
and also it just feels really different.
It's a totally different kind of game.
The third plane does not feel...
I'm not actually shooting anything.
All I'm doing is leading planes behind me
and then sort of leaving this mine in the air
that they just run into.
It's like a buzzsaw boomerang.
It is.
It's really cool.
It's pretty cool, I like it.
I love fucking games where you have a variety of weapons,
each with their own totally different mechanic, right?
That's a good game I like,
so I like it when things get outside of the general zone
of shooting on a straight vector, right?
Yeah, but it kind of makes me wonder
why this game is a game about flying a plane around and shooting,
but by far the best time I'm having with it,
I'm not actually shooting.
I feel like a game about that boomerang
would be much better.
I think if there's one thing...
If this is an experimental game,
just kind of made, oh fuck, I ran into a deadly thing.
Okay, if this game is an experiment
and this guy is, I assume, a pretty new dev
and he's probably just trying things out
and figuring out what works,
I think what really works is that boomerang,
I think, is the lesson that he might want to take away from this.
Indeed.
That's my opinion.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, another tricky thing
about the game's design that misled me
is that I didn't realize that if you went back to the main menu
you'd unlock more weapons, right?
Yeah, the new planes.
Right, you'd unlock the new planes,
because you have to go back to the main menu to do that.
And for me personally,
I would have probably just been stuck in a loop
playing with the first plane.
I would have too.
Over and over again if Digi hadn't mentioned it, right?
Yeah.
So my thought is...
Yeah, I think it should notify you when you unlock a new plane.
Which is really the reason why
I felt like I was a little bit too misled
by the confusion of the menu,
because you have to kind of know what that menu means
in order to understand this immediately.
Yeah, I think that a notification
when you unlock a new plane would be pretty good.
Right.
And for me it's like,
especially when you're on browser game level,
notifications basically should be translated
to shove something right in your fucking face.
Yeah, like why do you think all those mobile games
always have like a mascot character
on the bottom right corner of the screen
that like tells you everything,
just to make sure that you're not fucking missing it, right?
Yeah.
So I would say like have,
like in the middle of the screen,
like you got a new fucking plane, you know?
Yeah.
Especially because the game only really gets
more good and interesting when you get to the third one.
Yeah.
So you want to talk about the aesthetic of the game?
Well, the aesthetic of the game is just Luftrasse.
I guess.
But smaller.
Well, I guess I will say I like the cityscape.
I like the cityscape underneath.
I like the parallax scrolling and I like the sun.
I like how the higher you go,
like there's this red sun in the background
and it like illuminates more of the city
because like it's shining on it more.
The dev here clearly has a grip on how to synthesize
the different multimedia elements, you know?
Like he's able to put the different graphics together
and they weave around in an interesting way.
I mean, I guess I would say that differently.
I would say that he's just got a reasonably good sense
of aesthetic design.
Yeah, just how to make the fucking,
because none of the individual graphics
are that impressive, right?
They're really consistent too.
Although, you know, I, well,
okay, I was going to say that it's a bit odd,
like the sun, it's odd, like the sun
really calls attention to itself.
Like I find myself looking at the sun
whenever I go up high because...
I think it's fucking cool, but it looks...
It is cool, but it commands so much of my attention
even though it's irrelevant to the actual gameplay.
I don't hate it, but I think it's odd.
Every element of the graphics,
they all look like a different art style.
Like the sun itself is like a perfectly circular,
like it's probably not even like a graphic,
it's probably just like in whatever language
they're programmed in, like they probably just use,
like straight up the program to make a circle.
That's what it looks like to me.
Could be.
Because it's so like anti-aliased.
And like the graphics of the weapons
and the enemies and you,
they all look like...
They look like loot browsers.
Then the cityscape looks sort of MS Paint-like.
You know, it looks a little sloppy and like unprofessional.
It looks cool, but it doesn't look like it was made
by an artist, if you know what I mean, right?
It doesn't...
I guess I would say that it's...
Well, you know what I don't like about it?
I don't like how it just cuts to black underneath.
Well, that's the water.
I know, I know.
Like the tops...
Okay, well, here's what I don't like.
The tops of the buildings, they feel...
Yeah, the perspective feels off because
the tops of the buildings are tilted down
as though you're looking at them from slightly above.
And yet the waterline is a perfect horizontal line
implying that you are looking at it exactly from the sideways.
So I feel like that doesn't quite work.
Yeah, and I think that the fucking battle ships
in particular have a lot of precise detail on them.
Like the way that they're lit up,
which I don't know if you're able to have the...
Fuck.
Being able to pay attention to even notice.
But see those ships, how much cool little details are on them?
The little lights on the side.
They kind of looked like they were drawn by a different person,
but probably just that the methodology he went into drawing
that was very different, where he probably modeled
the ships after photos of ships,
and he probably just drew some fucking buildings
to make it look like buildings, right?
Yeah.
I assume he probably wasn't looking at a cityscape
when he drew it.
Well, that's just what it comes off like, right?
It just feels like a different art style.
And particularly the clouds look like a cartoony
with a thick black outline.
So each element has a different art style, basically.
Which again, if you want to go for art style fusion,
again, not good, not bad, not great, not terrible,
not mediocre, just not a value judgment,
just a point, right?
Yeah.
To keep in mind the different cohesion,
the different art styles, you know,
how they can work off one another.
You know what?
I hate the second plane.
It's stupid.
It's special.
It's got a machine gun, and its special ability
is that you can like,
Spin it around.
You can instantly reverse direction.
And if you do that, you die.
So it's just a kill me button.
Because you always have like a horde of planes
flying behind you.
I don't know.
Maybe there's some tricky strategy to use with it.
I thought that maybe it would be good for like,
flying down into ships,
because it's really hard to kill the ships.
The ships are positioned in a way that it's just,
it's just not natural to shoot them.
I thought maybe that like,
this would be a good plane for killing ships.
Okay, that kind of worked,
but then I got hit and almost died.
I kind of thought that maybe you could like,
swoop down at them firing,
and then like, before colliding with the ground,
you can like, immediately reverse your direction
and fly back up into the ship.
Oh, you got to kill the ship.
That actually worked.
Okay, I'm going to keep trying this.
It's still really awkward,
and I feel like I'm going to die every time I do it,
but okay.
Maybe I've hit on something here.
Oh man, didn't do it that time.
Okay, I'm going to try again.
I'm going back.
Fuck.
Oh, well, you got it.
Yeah, I got the ship, but I died,
because reversing direction
just puts you right in the path of death.
So my point is, I think this guy's got,
he definitely got all the baseline talent
to make a really good game.
I don't agree with that.
He's got the baseline talent
to copy a really good game.
I don't know.
Look at that fucking skull.
That's exactly from Lufthrausers.
Lufthrausers does that exact thing.
When you die, it puts a skull on the screen.
What?
Yeah.
I told you this game is Lufthrausers.
That's basically all you need to say.
I'm sorry, man.
I'm sorry, Dev, but you know it's true.
I'm not crazy here.
You just made Lufthrausers again,
and you did a competent job.
Sorry.
I was annoyed, because I looked at you
and Digi in the chat
talking about this game,
arguing about its merits,
and they're just discussing the merits
of Lufthrausers.
This game doesn't really merit discussion of its own.
He immediately said it's like Lufthrausers.
Well, okay.
Fair enough.
I don't know if he said it is Lufthrausers,
but that is like Lufthrausers.
Okay, but you and Digi,
without actually having played Lufthrausers,
you can't appreciate the true depth
of just how much simply Lufthrausers it is.
Well, that just means
he's one of a very exclusive group of people.
There's only three people in this world
who've made Lufthrausers,
and it's the two people of Lambeer and him.
So that puts him in a pretty special position.
I guess you got a point there.
So from that position,
he can just rip off every game in the world
and eventually do whatever he wants with his unlimited power.
Yes.
Sure.
All right.
You got anything else to say about Nemesis?
Oh, yeah.
I forgot that's what it was called.
I mean, yeah.
Well, just kidding.
Well, I don't know.
I mean, the title's right up there.
Lufthrausers 2 Electric Boogaloo.
Yeah, Lufthrausers 2 Return of Jafar.
Return of Jafar.
All right.
I guess that's it.
Yeah, that's it.
That's it for the first episode of PCP Destructive Criticism.
Yeah.
We're going to be, we'll be back.
Just anyone who's a PCP viewer, make something,
and then maybe we'll criticism it.
Make something a little good.
Don't be a piece of shit.
I mean, this is good.
This is fine.
This is the level.
This is a good baseline to shoot for,
to share your work with us
and have us give a fuck about it.
Yeah, indeed.
So good luck, everybody.
All right.
See ya.