Come on, you fuckers think that just cause a guy reads comics, he can't start some shit?
Aw, fucking take all you want!
Leviathan, you ready?
Home again, home again.
Gibbontake the love!
Class is paying 101.
I guess one person can make a difference.
Yeah!
I'm starting it out dick style this week.
Welcome everybody to the panel cast.
We are back after a long hiatus.
There was no panel cast last week.
Everyone was fucking furious at me.
I got all your tweets, all one of them, from all my fan.
He was so angry with me that there wasn't a panel cast.
I was like, you know, it was such a busy week.
I had to finish my big election video.
And then I was busy with other stuff.
You know, I was busy being a well-laid lefario.
Traveling the country on my love quest.
But I'm back.
The election week is finally over.
The election's over people.
And I really think that America needs this.
You need the panel cast right now.
This country needs to be united in the panel cast more than ever.
You all need to come with me on the SS panel cast.
My pirate ship and sail through the cosmos
into my dimension of comic book panels
and become wire frame res people with me.
And I'm back.
Oh my god, the election's finally over.
I think it's the election that won't die is what it is.
It's still going on.
It's still all over.
It should be over by now.
But these fucking people, these god,
I'm gonna say it, these god damned millennials
who won't shut the fuck up.
It's over.
Stop fucking whining.
You fucking brainwashed idiotic.
It's, you know, all these cowardly females
who are so convinced that Donald Trump,
you know, now that he's president
that they're gonna walk outside,
the whole world's gonna be on fire.
And there's gonna be like rape drones
swooping down from the sky to grab everyone's pussy.
I know I already said this stuff.
I know, I have, oh god, I can't, I hate them all so much.
I had a fucking existential crisis the other night
because I went to a friend's house on election night
and saw my friends like crying,
like putting their hands in their faces and weeping
because Donald Trump won,
because they're so fucking brainwashed by the media,
they'll legitimately think that now
they're gonna like lose all their rights to vote
and their right to have an abortion
and the whole country is just gonna become
the United States of Rape.
That's how fucking retarded people are.
But enough about the election.
For god's sakes, enough about the election.
I know that I'm being part of the fucking problem right now.
God, I just want it to die.
It should be dead.
It's over.
It's been like three days.
It's Thursday now and they won't shut up about it.
They won't let it die.
The election that won't die
is continuing to lurch along like a fucking zombie.
And I just want to bash its fucking brains in.
I want to take everyone who cared about the election,
all of these whiny millennials
and delusional females on Facebook and Twitter
who won't stop fucking crying about Donald Trump,
even though it's fucking over and done with.
I want to take them all.
I want to take all the fucking voters
and I want to line them up on their knees
so fucking Negan can bash their fucking heads in
and just, I want them all, I want all voters to die.
I want to run someday on the presidential platform
of kill all voters and I'll be the last president
that this country ever fucking has
because once I'm elected, you're all fucking dead.
Everyone who voted for me is dead.
Everyone who voted for the other guy is dead.
I'm just going to become God Emperor forever,
outlaw democracy and just give everyone free comics.
That'll be my tax plan.
Instead of paying taxes, you all get comics every year.
Holy shit, I'm so mad.
Anyways, welcome to the panel cast, everybody.
We're going to talk about some fucking comics this week
and I have a special guest this week.
This is a two-person panel cast.
I have with me, I forgot to give her a name.
I like to give my friends names.
I like to protect people's identities.
That's why secretary is secretary.
I didn't give you a...
This is the amazing Alice, everybody.
Hi, that was a marvel just now, witnessing all that.
Oh yeah, she had to sit next to that.
I hope they can hear you.
I hope this microphone can pick up both of us.
Oh yeah, no.
You're kind of sitting in like a lawn chair
and you're sinking into the floor
so you're not totally close to the microphone.
It's my fault.
No, it seems fine.
But anyways, this is my loyal scribe.
She's been staying with me for the week,
all the funny things I say and posting them on Twitter for me.
And she's a comic book girl.
She owns...
You tell them what you do.
I help run a comic book shop company.
That's about the gist of it.
Aren't you in charge of like four stores or something?
I help out at four stores, basically.
She was flipping out like earlier.
She wanted to do this panel cast so bad.
She was bothering me.
I was trying to listen to all of my podcasts for the week
and get my stuff done.
I was trying to watch my stories, watch my shows.
I was listening to The Dick Show.
I was trying to listen to Digi's Decompression Chamber
and she's over there fucking whining.
I didn't do the panel cast.
I love comics and I want to tell the world
that I know about comics and I want to show the world
that girls can love comics too
because girls aren't going to be allowed to read comics anymore
and that Trump is president.
I want to show the world that women have rights
to read comics.
And she was just pestering me.
I'm trying to listen to all of my stuff
and then I'm like, okay, I'm ready now.
Let's do the panel cast
and then immediately she's fucking over there on her laptop
doing some work shit, yelling at her employees,
throwing a fucking fit
and I had to fucking sit there.
Once I got ready to record this,
then I had to sit there and fucking twiddle my dick
while she went off
and yelled at her boss on the phone for like an hour
and then she comes back all huffing and steaming like,
oh god, and I'm just like, okay.
And so that was another hour.
What do you have to say for yourself?
I'm a nuisance.
That's about the chist of it.
She is a nuisance, like all women.
You know, thank god that Trump's president
is going to bring back the ancient technique
of putting five across the face
on a hysterical woman to calm her down.
That's the first order of business.
That was trending, I think, Trump's first order, hashtag
Trump's first order.
That's what I think it's going to be.
Trump's first order is to bring back
slapping hysterical women to make them act right.
You know, I had a dream like that once about rape drones.
It was a good dream. I liked it.
Were they just like a helicoptering on with little dildos
hanging off the bottom of them?
Beware the ghost of Boo Radley.
He is a rapist, possibly.
Vanguard One is not.
Vanguard One is a noble, a feminist, a male feminist,
but a good kind, not like a beta male.
Boo Radley, though, is his evil alter ego.
Jesus Christ, what am I talking about?
Anyways, so much fucking to talk about
on the panel cast this week because I missed a week.
I should explain why there was no panel cast last week,
partly because I was busy making that big election video.
But also, I did start recording the panel cast.
I recorded the intro for it.
It was this big 20-minute rant of an intro.
It was really funny.
You'll probably hear it next week.
I'll stick it on that one.
I recorded the intro for the panel cast,
and then when I started to get into the meat
of talking about the comics,
what happened was the comics last week were all so terrible
that it broke me, and I couldn't even muster any words for them.
I was so seething mad about these fucking comics that I read,
specifically one.
I'll just fucking say it.
There's this comic out right now called Champions,
and I read the fucking, you know what I'm talking about?
Oh, yeah.
By Mark Wade, right?
The same guy who turned Daredevil into like a San Franciscan hipster
fuckboy, sweetboy, manjina for like 10 years.
This comic champions, where do I even start
with how much I fucking hated this?
I have to say it.
Even though it came out last week,
I won't be able to function this week unless I get this off my chest.
It first of all takes place after the Civil War II event,
which is still fucking going on,
because Marvel can't fucking get their shit together
and do anything right.
So every comic that you read now, half the Marvel comics that you buy now
are just going to spoil the story that's going on right now.
Like, I know what happens at the end of Civil War II now
without having it spoiled.
They spoil their own shit because their stories are so bloated
and they take so long to get them out
that they have to release the stories after them
before they're even done.
They even extend them.
They're like, ah, Civil War.
You guys wanted an extra issue of that, didn't you?
Oh, God, it's terrible.
Yeah, so this champion's book, it takes place after the Civil War II
thing that's going on.
So I guess the young heroes, the teeny-bopper Avengers,
they're all so angry at the adult Avengers
for having the Civil War II,
for having this big, boring comic book event,
that they're like, fuck you, we're going to go be actual superheroes.
I feel like I've seen this plot in comics over and over my whole life.
A team of heroes that says the heroes aren't doing it right,
so we're going to get back to basics,
and it's always a lie.
It's always an unfulfilled promise.
The offshoot team of heroes who wants to do it right
and not get wrapped up in events, they do anyways.
I mean, the prophecy repeats itself always.
Yeah, it's a self-fulfilling.
It's like an uraboros of shitty comics
that's perpetually eating its own tail.
Yep.
But so the teeny-bopper Avengers,
they try to start their own little Avengers team
and first of all, this lineup of these teeny-bopper Avengers,
half of them are characters that I fucking hate
and loathe and despise.
And, oh, I'll get to it.
And half of them I hate, and the other half I like,
but were ruined in this comic,
because I read the first two issues.
It's two issues so far.
But, I mean, I'll just go through the lineup.
First of all, Nova.
Who the fuck is Nova?
I don't know and I don't care.
Don't even explain it to me,
because I don't even want to know who he is.
I hate him.
He's just some little sweet boy in a helmet
who fucking flies around with a rocket ass.
You can tell me who he is.
Well, I mean, they're bringing back old Nova,
so it won't matter anyway.
Well, yeah, of course,
because every superhero has to be five superheroes now.
There's got to be ten Captain Americas.
We have to have a Captain America to represent
every minority and sexual orientation on the planet.
Yep.
Like you said, Marvel is Tumblr.
Yeah, Marvel is Tumblr incarnate.
They are not two separate companies.
They are one entity.
Oh, I hate them.
Don't worry about Nova.
He doesn't matter.
Yeah, that's what I assumed.
Nova doesn't matter.
What has Nova ever done?
What even is this character?
Why does he even exist?
He's got a special helmet
that lets him do special things, moving on.
Wow, that's like a Disney Channel original movie.
That's not a superhero origin.
I found a magic pair of sneakers
and now I can jump high.
Wow.
What a bitch.
I hate him.
You know, so much of the cosmic Marvel stuff
I hate anyways.
I can't get into it.
It's so weird, but enough about that.
So there's Nova.
He's fucking nobody.
I don't care about him.
He's not interesting at all.
He has no like, you know, like every good superhero,
a great superhero, Spider-Man, Batman, the Hulk.
There's always something at the core of the character
that everyone in the world can relate to.
Some struggle that defines the character.
And I hate these like second string characters
that just don't have that.
They're just like one dimensional
or not even one dimensional.
They're multi-dimensional
because they serve the purposes
of whatever story they're in
because they don't have a personality
or a backstory that anyone cares about.
And I think Nova's a great example of that.
Fuck them.
If you're a big fan of Nova, you're not.
Yeah, I'm not even,
I don't even know what to say to that.
No one's a big fan of Nova.
So there's that guy that I hate.
Next up is Amadeus Cho,
the fucking, the genius intellect,
teenage fucking Bro Hulk.
The teenage Asian Bro Hulk
who like spends this entire comic
like macking on all the honeys
because I guess the Hulk should be cool now.
Like, I can't imagine,
they do this like all the time.
Jekyll has done this like periodically
every five years since the dawn of Marvel.
They go, hey, what if the Hulk wasn't angry?
Well, then he's not the fucking Hulk.
He's not interesting.
The whole thing that makes the Hulk interesting
is that like basic,
like that iconic Jekyll and Hyde storyline
that everyone can relate to.
Like everybody has like a side of themselves
they don't like.
Everybody, you know, might have a temper
in security and that's what the Hulk speaks to.
That's why he's a great character
because Bruce Banner will never
and should never be able to control the Hulk
or contain him.
And every fucking five years,
Marvel gets on this kick where they're like,
maybe like, you know, Dr. Banner,
the Hulk is a genius now or Grey Hulk.
He fucking works in a casino now
and he beats people up with a crowbar.
He's like a bouncer or some shit
or there's a Red Hulk now.
Thunderbolt Ross is a Hulk
and Betty's a Hulk too.
Everyone's a fucking Hulk now.
And now his little sidekick,
this character, I'm frothing at the mouth.
I'm working myself up already.
It's only been 13 minutes.
This character they introduced in the Hulk comics, right?
Or no, Hercules.
Uh, Hercules.
Why are we talking about Hercules?
I'm just trying to remember where
Amadeus Cho was introduced.
Uh, God, you know, it was a little while back.
I don't even remember.
I just remember the comic releasing
and I was just like, oh,
what is this called?
The totally awesome new Hulk?
Yeah.
New Hulk.
And I actually read the comic begrudgingly
because I immediately saw that title
and I hated it.
I was like, this is a stupid title.
This is airing it, this is stupid
and I don't want to read this.
Well, making the Hulk cool,
it's just not what makes the character interesting.
The Hulk is interesting because he's the Hulk.
I mean, if you just have a big strong guy
who's also smart,
that's just the thing.
The thing already exists.
There's already a big strong guy who can talk good.
I mean, as well as the thing, can talk.
Yeah.
Well, I mean...
He is kind of a, like, Brooklyn trash.
He is.
Grumble, grumble, clobber in time.
Oh, Yancey Street.
Uh, my mother,
poker.
Yankees.
Well, I'm not going to lie.
When I did read the totally awesome Hulk
the first time, like the first issue,
I sat there, like, at the end of the issue,
just holding it in my hands, going,
I can't believe I liked this.
I know.
And he's just...
Amadeus Cho as Hulk,
he's just another one of these characters who are like,
they don't want to make new superheroes.
They just want to make new versions
of the guys who already exist.
They want to sap away everything that's special
about the characters we love
and try to, like, put the costume
on some other character,
as though it automatically infuses them with that...
A younger character, no less.
A younger character, a blacker character,
a, you know, a heterosexual,
fucking non-genderqueer, binary...
Well, you know, they have to get ready for the movies.
Down syndrome.
Like, young Stephen Hawking
in, like, a little motorized cart.
They're going to put, like,
they're going to put a Thor helmet
on some, like, sentient tumor
that's, like, growing off of some other guys.
That's the new...
You got to be as inclusive as possible.
You got to represent the sentient tumor
in total recall.
I mean, technically, the helmet is already
on a cancer patient, so...
Yeah, fuck.
Well, there you go.
But it's just because they're getting ready for the movies.
Like, they're pushing these films so hard,
and it's like, they're like,
our actors are getting old.
They're going to be obsolete soon.
We have to create new characters.
I never thought of that.
Do you think that's why?
Because the actors will get old
and they want to be able to, in the movies,
keep them going.
Oh, that is fucking insidious.
That's nefarious.
Yeah.
No, that's...
Well, that's what I think.
Oh.
That's why we're seeing, like, a...
You're probably right.
That's horrifying.
That...
Oh, my God.
You thought that...
You thought that the vision of Trump's America,
you thought that future was bad.
Imagine the future ten years from now,
when Robert Downey is too old to play Iron Man,
and they get some little black girl
to beat Iron Man in the movies,
because they're already doing it in the comics.
Iron Man's a black girl now.
Thor is a cancer woman now.
Fucking Captain America's a black guy.
Miss Marvel's a little girl.
I don't know about the old Miss Marvel, anyways, but...
Well, Doom is also an Iron Man, so...
Oh, that's right.
Dr. Doom is Iron Man now.
Uh-huh.
I forgot about that, because he's got a good face,
and that made him a good person.
Yep.
So, two Iron Men, two Captain America's.
We have one Captain Marvel, one Miss Marvel.
There's fucking five Spider-Man's.
There's gonna be two noes.
There's so many goddamn Spider-Man's.
There's so many...
Oh!
There's Peter.
There's Miles.
There's Silk.
There's Kane.
There's fucking Spider-Gwen.
Kane is the best.
Go on.
Well, Kane...
Yeah, I like him.
He's back.
I'll talk about him in a minute.
And then Renew Your Vows.
That's the thing now.
Yep.
Mary Jane is a Spider-Man.
Their daughter is a Spider-Man.
Well, it seems like every couple of years, Mary Jane becomes a superhero
for like one issue, and then they forget about it.
She was already an Invincible Iron Man.
Oh, my God.
Mary Jane as Tony Stark's secretary.
I'm getting ahead of myself, but I'm just so angry about everything having to do with Spider-Man
for the last ten fucking years!
Oh!
I'm not even there yet.
I'm getting ahead of myself.
I'm gonna fucking burst.
Thinking about Spider-Man has been like a non-stop await on my soul.
Like, I'm constantly...
If people want to know the source of my anger, it's because for the last ten years of Marvel
Spider-Man comics, I'm constantly on the verge of committing like a...
Like that game hatred.
A genocide crusade.
All right, go out in black and white with a shotgun and start killing people because
of what they've done to Spider-Man.
But I'm getting ahead of myself.
I'll get there eventually.
And I'm still yelling about champions right now.
Okay?
So that's...
Okay, so the theme is...
Nova who I hate and isn't interesting.
Amadeus Chohulk who I hate and isn't interesting.
Fucking...
Who else?
What's the other...
Miles Morales, the little black Spider-Man from the Ultimate Universe who isn't interesting.
He was.
I haven't been reading his comments lately, though.
Okay.
What is his origin now in the new Marvel Universe?
It doesn't make any sense anymore.
Wasn't...
Okay, I think that the thing...
Miles Morales was a character who was introduced in the Ultimate Comics.
The Ultimate Comics were like Marvel's attempt to sort of make like a second universe to
kind of get new readers in in like the early 2000s.
And it was sort of like retelling of like contemporary origins of superheroes.
And it was a really big success.
There were a lot of really great stories, especially in the early part of the Ultimate Universe.
Ultimate Spider-Man was fantastic for like the first hundred issues.
Oh yeah.
But eventually it kind of crumbled in on itself.
And the weight of its own continuity became too much.
And it turned to shit.
And there was a lot of weird stuff that happened.
What's going on with my haunted door over there?
It's slowly creaking itself open.
Boo Radley is going to come in here and rape us both for Trump.
I had a dream like that once.
But so the Ultimate Universe lasted for like ten years.
And it eventually crumbled in on itself.
And it started having some really awful stories that everyone hated.
Like Ultimatum where like the blob ate the wasp.
And there was like this really graphic panel of him like munching on her intestines and shit.
Yep, I remember that.
And like there was a tidal wave and a million people died.
Anyways.
And Scarlet Witch and Silver, what's his name?
It's Quicksilver.
They're fucking?
They're like a sinister thing going on?
Yeah.
But everybody.
Oh, and like Ultimate Wolverine fucked like teenage Jean Grey.
Yep.
Oh, that was so creepy.
That was where I like I signed out where I stopped reading the Ultimate X-Men comics.
I stuck around with Ultimate Spider-Man for a while, but...
Because it was Jean Grey or because she was a teenager?
Not because she's a teenager.
I'm a hundred percent for having sex with teenagers.
I think it's what...
I think that'll make America great again.
If we all...
If we lower the age of consent to like twelve and a half,
I think that would make this country great again.
But um, I just think Wolverine should never ever ever have sex with Jean Grey.
Because it's a...
It's like a vital part of his character.
We're like...
Forever pining for the world.
Well, like Wolverine...
We're going off in so many different directions right now,
but I mean like Wolverine, you know, in the old Claremont X-Men stories,
he was introduced as like, you know, the rebel of the team.
The guy who's always a loner and he's always grumpy.
He doesn't get along with anyone.
But like a huge...
Like he falls in love with Jean Grey,
but like this huge vital part of his growth as a character
is accepting that it is not meant to be with Jean Grey
and accepting that, you know, he can love her deeply, passionately, forever,
but it's not to be and like going off to Japan and marrying Mariko Yoshida
and like it made him be a better person.
It was like his like...
That was his source of growth in the X-Men comics in the Claremont era.
And um, so it just feels like a weird grimy, slimy betrayal to me
to ever have Wolverine fuck Jean Grey.
It just kind of makes...
I'm like totally like anti-shipping for that one.
I don't like it.
It's creepy.
Every time I see it in anything, it creeps me out.
And now they've got...
I'm going up on so many tangent.
Now they've got Old Man Logan and Teenie Bopper Jean Grey
and I swear to God, they're gonna have him fuck her.
They're gonna have 90 year old Wolverine fuck 16 year old Jean Grey
and I know that I just said that I love fucking little girls,
but something about it being those two characters
really sickens me on a primal level and I don't want it.
I don't like it.
It's not feminist is what it is.
You know, Donald Trump's gonna be president
and suddenly Wolverine's gonna be fucking little baby Jean Grey.
I know I'm flip-flopping on my feelings for Donald Trump,
like every five minutes.
I go from making fun of him to like praising him.
To back to making fun of him.
It's just funny.
Everything about Donald Trump is hilarious to me.
Except for the fact that all my friends are turning on me
for not voting for Hillary Clinton enough.
Yeah, um...
I actually really like the Old Man Logan series.
Oh yeah, Old Man Logan.
Everything like the original series was fantastic.
And the news, the ongoing is really good too.
Definitely marriage writing for it, if I remember right.
And he's one of my favorite writers.
What the fuck was I even talking about?
I was talking about like Wolverine and Jean Grey.
Right, winding back you were asking about Miles Morales.
What is his origins?
Get my fucking eye of Agamotto and fucking turn back the clock.
Roll back the clock to the dawn of time.
That's the fucking weird back reference.
You weren't expecting that, were you people?
That was a Doctor Strange reference combined with a weird back.
A dinosaur story reference.
That was like, nobody can do this shit but me.
I've got so much in my brain.
These fucking spider webs firing off synapses
in so many fucking wild directions.
That's why I'm the best there is at what I do.
And what I do ain't cool.
Now you were asking about Miles Morales and like what even is...
Right, okay.
So the origin of Miles Morales before the ultimate...
Fuck, there's so much to unpack here with comics.
That's why I was so like pumped up and like pacing back and forth
to like do this panel cast because there's so much to do.
Everything with comics that you talk about,
you have to talk about 10,000 other things.
Everything has 70 years of history before it
to even get to your point.
It's so stressful.
But Marvel in particular is bad.
So okay, the ultimate universe, you know,
there was a bunch of big events where like a million superheroes died.
Everyone started to hate it.
The people started turning on the ultimate Marvel universe
pretty strongly and they finally decided,
okay, it's run its course.
We got to fold it.
We got to sort of fold it into the main Marvel universe.
So all the characters that were popular,
which I mean just Miles Morales because he was the only person
still alive in the ultimate universe by the end of it.
Yep.
But so they did a big event last year
where Dr. Doom did some magic fuckery
and became king of the world for a while.
It combined like the Marvel multiverse into one planet.
Secret Wars.
Yeah, and the end of it,
the fallout from it was just that, you know,
the Marvel universe sort of combined
with the ultimate Marvel universe and sort of...
They pulled the same thing that DC did with the New 52.
Yeah.
Like after, it wasn't convergence.
It was the one before that. Flashpoint.
It wasn't as badly done as the New 52 though.
I mean it was, I liked last year's event,
for an event, I hate them all,
but I thought that the Secret Wars was decent.
It was fine.
Yeah.
It just took a really long time to finish.
And I think a lot of people lost interest in that.
But yeah, the main Marvel universe
folded in on the ultimate Marvel universe
and they adopted Miles Morales.
I'm gonna barf.
I'm barfing.
All this over the champions?
Yeah, the champions...
It's not even finished.
It's a lift issue too.
I know already you wanna barf.
Okay, Miles Morales was a character
invented in the ultimate Marvel universe by Bendis.
Yeah, Michael Bendis.
So, he was the little black Spider-Man.
He was a guy...
I don't know...
I might be wrong.
Correct me if I get anything.
She was fucking giving me so much grief earlier.
You go on that panel cast
and everything you fucking say isn't correct.
You get so much stuff wrong.
What?
You fucking...
Why am I always made out to be the bad guy?
I don't know, because it's funny.
Because I'm a woman.
Exactly.
This is Trump's world now.
I'm allowed to be sexist.
It's Trump's world now.
So, he was a guy who got bitten.
Was it the same spider that bit Peter?
Like the exact literal same spider.
Unlike the same day?
Or was it different?
Because I don't even know.
I don't remember.
But he had spider powers too.
And I think like he wasn't doing anything with them.
They had a big event called Ultimatum.
Spider-Man died.
Did he die in Ultimatum?
Yeah, I think.
Peter Parker died.
Yeah, he died.
And, um, you know, so Spider-Man died.
And everyone was really inspired by Spider-Man's heroic death.
And Miles Morales, this kid who had spider powers,
but didn't do anything with them, he said,
oh my god, Spider-Man died.
And here I am doing fuck all with my spider powers.
And that's how he learned about responsibility
and that whole thing.
Yeah, but it was followed up by a whole mess of things.
And then he became Spider-Man, basically.
We haven't even gotten to the meat potatoes yet.
Okay, there's Nova, who I hate.
Amadeus Cho, who I hate.
Miles Morales, who I hate.
That was my point.
That's why I got him the Ultimate Universe fucking story.
Because now that he's in the-
The main Marvel Universe?
Yeah, in the main Marvel Universe, Spider-Man never died.
So why is Miles Morales a Spider-Man?
What is his new origin?
I mean, if he's still got the powers, why not?
What are they gonna do?
Go back home?
That's stupid.
That robs him of all of his coolness, I think.
Yeah, and I saw recently some new issues coming out.
I guess him and Spider-Gwen are gonna be a thing at some point.
Oh my god.
No.
How old is Spider-Gwen?
I don't know.
Same age?
Isn't she Cradle-Grobbing?
Shouldn't she be Peter Parker's age?
Aren't they both like 16?
See, I don't keep up with their ages very well because they never age.
Or they reverse ages.
Or they just kind of-
It's different in every single comic.
How fucking old is Gwenpool?
I don't know.
When she was introduced last year in Howard the Duck,
the way that she was drawn made her seem like she's 27, our age, an adult.
Maybe.
But then you read her ongoing, and maybe it's just because of the change in art style.
Now she looks like she's a teenager.
They can't even keep-
That's like a real huge pet peeve of mine, is Marvel being fucky about the characters' ages.
Like, in universe, the Fantastic Four were the first heroes,
and they started, I mean technically like the original human torch,
the robot-looking guy.
But for all intents and purposes, in Marvel continuity history,
the age of superhero started with the Fantastic Four,
which is generally considered to be 15 years ago.
Right?
And then pretty soon after them,
15-year-old Spider-Man got bit by the spider.
So when I read comics, to me, I always feel like Peter Parker should be 29, 30 years old, an adult.
But they always want to make him like younger, like his early 20s, and it makes no sense.
The timeline of Marvel is so fucky.
I hate it.
I can't stand it.
It drives me crazy.
How old is Scott Summers?
He should also be in his 30s.
No, no.
That's an alternate dimension, Scott Summers.
I don't- oh.
Oh.
Here we go.
That's right.
How could I forget about the original Five X-Men,
who got fucking shucky-ducky-quacked-quacked into the modern age?
Yeah, no.
That's supposed to be the Scott Summers that becomes an evil, tyrannical person.
I'm sorry.
This is the most like cluster fuck panel cast that has ever existed.
I'm so riled right now about everything.
I haven't even like- we haven't- I have like notes here that we haven't gotten to get all
the comics that I actually read this week that I haven't talked about yet.
You are technically still yelling about champions.
This is all connected.
I hate champions so much.
But moving on.
Nova, who I hate.
Amadeus Chohulk, who I hate and is not interesting.
Who is the other guy?
Miles Morales, who is not interesting and I don't like him and I don't care about him.
Scott.
Oh, young Scott.
Young Scott Summers.
Teeny Bopper Cyclops.
So, a couple years ago in the pages of X-Men.
No, wait.
I have to start this story 10 years ago.
Oh no.
I have to start it at like Grant Morrison's new X-Men.
This is-
When Grant Morrison, you know, after fucking years of Cyclops existing and nobody liking
him when Grant Morrison in the 2000s made Cyclops the coolest fucking character of all time
and then Joss Whedon made him even fucking cooler after that.
You know, he started fucking Emma Frost.
He started, you know, kicking major amounts of ass.
He like, the character evolved from like, you know, Cyclops was always this like stoic,
you know, the Leonardo, the nobody's favorite.
The guy who's just there for Wolverine to bounce off and be the rebel who everyone likes.
He was like the uptight, rule Nazi who, you know-
The principal.
Yeah, the principal.
That was how people viewed Cyclops forever.
That's how I viewed Cyclops as a kid.
Watching the animated series as a kid, I liked Gambit and Wolverine and I never cared about Cyclops.
It's like the Breakfast Club principal.
Yeah.
But, you know, in the early 2000s, these two fucking, these golden gods descended from the heavens
and their names were Grant Morrison and Joss Whedon and they said, hey, shouldn't Cyclops be fucking cool?
If he's the leader of the coolest fucking team, shouldn't he logically be the coolest fucking guy?
And they put in all this work, they made these storylines where Cyclops like grew as a character
and he turned from this uptight sort of rule Nazi who nobody liked into this sort of like maverick,
take no prisoners fucking super stud who was like always five steps ahead of the enemy.
This like tactical genius who was willing to break the rules.
He fucking started like just kicking everyone's ass, you know.
He started like, like, like Magneto started becoming more of a good guy
and Cyclops became this like, this perfect combination of Xavier and Magneto's philosophies.
Like, he took the best from both of these, like, from like the Malcolm X and the other guy, Martin Luther King.
That's who they always represented, those two characters.
And Cyclops became this like amalgamation, taking in the best of both of their philosophies
and coming this like mutant hero, this like outlaw hero, this badass
who like suddenly Cyclops is the coolest fucking character to read about
and that continued for like a good ten years and they just kept upping the ante.
Suddenly you get to like, like when they move to San Francisco
where like, where they started the Utopia and Cyclops, he like gets his own island fortress for all the X-Men
and he's flying around in a fucking jetpack and he's like riding in convertibles
and he's like, yeah, I'm fucking Cyclops, I fuck the hottest girls, I got eye beams, I'm the coolest guy ever!
He's the best character ever. I fucking love Cyclops, he's awesome.
And like, he became like, they like slowly had him becoming like really good friends with Wolverine
and they were like, they had this like buddy cop thing going on for a while
where they like had grown to respect each other over all this and that's what I fucking love.
I love like, when the continuity from all these years of stories manifests as characters,
their relationships changing and growing together because, you know, Wolverine and Cyclops
who like butted heads for like 40 years, suddenly Cyclops has become this badass
and Wolverine has grown into this like mature, you know, hero
and they've become like really good friends and instead of like fighting over Jean, now she's dead
and they're like kind of bonded over their love for Jean and they're like best buddies and it was great
and it's this beautiful era of X-Men comics where I'm like, you know, all's right with the world
and then stuff started getting fucky. You know, Marvel can't let a good thing exist for too long.
They gotta fuck themselves in some way. They gotta rock the boat.
There was this storyline called Schism where like, in the pages of Wolverine's comic,
Wolverine's ongoing by Jason Aaron who is a great writer who I love.
I loved his Wolverine. I loved his Thor before he started doing the girl thing.
There was a storyline with this group of people who wanted revenge on Wolverine
and it was like the brilliant plan to finally, like Wolverine had wronged them all at some point in his long life
and they had planned this, they had schemed this revenge for so long
and all of these guys, these like weird super villains, showed up to beat up Wolverine
and he kills all of them. But then at the end you find out that the main, like his ultimate plan
was that all of these like weird super villains who Wolverine has killed were actually like his illegitimate children.
Like Wolverine's, like because he's been around, Wolverine fucks. He's a man who fucks.
He's been around fucking, he's sired so many illegitimate bastards that this guy collected them all
and turned them into super villains and had Wolverine kill his own children so that he could reveal it to him
and it's like this devastating blow. And so like Wolverine in character, this was a nice bit of character building
because Wolverine suddenly, Wolverine goes fucking crazy and he goes,
we can't fucking have children fighting our battles anymore. We have to protect kids. I murdered all my children.
So Wolverine is going apeshit and he's like, I don't wanna, you know, we can't have kids fighting anymore
but at this point Cyclops has matured into the opposite direction
and he's become this like badass motherfucker like no, this is a war. We're at war with the world.
We have to have children fight our battles. So they butt heads and I thought Schism was a pretty good story.
You know, I hated it because it was sad to see a friendship be ruined but it was cool. It was well written.
What am I even fucking talking about? You see, you have to go so far back to even get to where we're talking about.
Um, we were talking about champions and how much you hated Scott.
This is gonna be a five hour podcast and it's just gonna be champions going into the history of the Marvel Universe
that you need to understand and order to understand why I hate everything about this one comic that I read last week.
So we went down the list of people you hate.
Oh no, no, no, no, I'm not even done. I'm not done talking about Teenie Bopper Scott.
I haven't even gotten to him yet. That's what started this.
No.
Okay, so we're at this point. I have to take my sweater off. I'm fucking, I got the hot sweats.
Ah!
Ah, comics.
So this is like, now we're up to like, this was like 2009, a couple years, like seven years ago.
Schism I think happened six years ago.
Fuck.
So now we're at this point where there's two teams of X-Men.
Wolverine has taken a bunch of the children. He's gone back to New York and started a new Xavier Institute.
He calls it the Jean Grey Institute.
So Wolverine is now dedicated to, I guess, protecting the kids.
And like, Wolverine has become dedicated to Xavier's dream.
He started a new school for gifted youngsters. He's wearing a suit and tie.
He's trying to be like a changed man, a principal.
Meanwhile, Cyclops is over here in like the San Francisco area in Utopia.
And he's become like a bad, like they've switched.
Cyclops has become the rebel and Wolverine has become the uptight sort of rules Nazi.
And it gets worse with like AVX.
Oh yeah, I'm getting to that, baby. I'm getting to it.
So, so that's how the characters had matured and that's good maturation.
That's good character growth. It's interesting to read about.
But um, oh yeah, throughout all of this, Beast has become the worst person who ever existed.
Should I get to Beast yet? I'm not even at Beast yet.
Oh no, he's not even a part of the Chieftains.
I have to, I have to, I have to start.
Well, it's his fault that teeny bopper Cyclops exists.
So I have to talk about Beast and that's going to be another hour.
Because they ruined Beast 2 in a way that's so insidious, I'll get to it.
But I have to talk about, okay, so there's fucking Wolverine has a school, Cyclops has an island.
And they don't like each other anymore.
And now there's this event called Avengers vs X-Men.
And it's the worst thing that ever happened.
To that point. Worse things happened after it.
But um, basically the Phoenix Force, it's coming back to Earth.
And Cyclops and the Avengers, they don't like each other.
And they got a fight. I'm getting, you have to explain this one.
Because I need a break.
So on AVX, the Phoenix Force returns to Earth and decides to split itself between five chosen people.
It's either five or six, I can't remember.
Cyclops wanted it to go to Hope.
Who is his...
Illigent, like his child from a different dimension. I don't, whatever.
She was the first new mutant born.
She was the first new mutant born after House of M.
Mutant stopped being born.
And she was the most powerful mutant that anyone had ever seen.
She had the potential to reignite the mutant race.
And she was raised by Cable in the future.
Cable is Cyclops's son from an alternate future.
And he comes back sometimes and he's a time travel guy with a big gun and he's really cool and everybody likes him.
He has a lot of pouches and a big shoulder pad.
Cable is a good man. He raises the girl.
Her name is Hope Summers now. She's like Scott's adopted granddaughter, I guess.
And she looks just like Jean.
Because everyone who is important in X-Men comics is a redhead who looks like Jean.
I don't know why. Nobody knows why.
The Phoenix Force.
Cyclops wants it to go to her because it's going to come to Earth no matter what.
And it might destroy everyone unless it is harnessed by the right person.
So Cyclops in his infinite wisdom because Cyclops is the only smart person in the Marvel Universe.
He's the only superhero who's still a superhero. The only guy I trust anymore.
Cyclops says, okay, look, it's coming here.
It's going to destroy everyone unless we train Hope to harness the fucking Phoenix Force.
We know how to do this. We're the X-Men. We've been handling the Phoenix for fucking 50 years.
Just let me handle it. I know what I'm doing.
But the Avengers, they just shit all over.
No.
Because...
Because fuck you?
Because in order for these event comics to work, in order for these superhero battles to work...
There has to be conflict.
One side always has to be made up of idiots.
One side is always out of character, always retarded.
So the Avengers, Captain America becomes this weird, brain-dead, fascist asshole who's like, fuck you.
We have to kill the 15-year-old girl. We have to murder her because I'm a fearful, hate-mongering idiot.
You know, I enjoyed AVX to an extent.
So they fight, basically.
Yeah. They do fight, and it was stupid because they separated all the fights into like its own thing.
Yeah.
And the fights were always stupid.
It's like, well, clearly, who would win in a fight with the Thing vs. Namor deep at the bottom of the ocean?
Yeah.
Well, I guess clearly the Thing does.
Who wins in a fight between Iron Man and Magneto?
Apparently Iron Man somehow.
Even though he's made of the stuff that Magneto's one power.
Magneto has one power, killing Iron Man.
That was one of my favorite bits in the entire AVX dialogue.
Iron Man's like, you can't do nothing to me, Magneto.
This suit isn't something that you can manipulate.
Magneto's like, oh no, whatever shall I do as he drops the Golden Gate Bridge on Iron Man.
Like, are you kidding me?
And Daredo vs. Cylock, I wonder who would win?
Nobody, I guess.
They can just do it on the rooftop or something.
So anyways, the fallout of AVX.
Ugh.
Because Captain America, you know, stuck his dick in the punch bowl and basically fucked
with the X-Men and made this problem 10,000 times worse than it needed to be.
What happened was the Phoenix Force ended up getting split and it went into five people.
It went into Cyclops, Emma Frost, Colossus, Magic, Namor.
And so they became the Phoenix Five and they took over the fucking world.
But they fixed the world.
Yeah, it wasn't even like forceful per se.
Like, we want to help the Earth.
They didn't become tyrants or despots.
They didn't become corrupted by it.
They literally fixed the world.
They ended all crime.
The Marvel Universe was at peace for a brief span and Captain America fucking hated it.
That really burned his bacon.
That another superhero saved the world forever and not him.
The Avengers wanted to be the glory hogs, basically.
How dare you create world peace forever and end hunger and end suffering throughout the entire planet?
How dare you actually be superheroes with this power that I don't approve of?
So they kept pestering them.
They kept fucking poking the bear and kicking the hornet's nest.
You know, Captain America and the Avengers became like this weird mosquito constantly pestering Cyclops,
who was fucking busy fixing the world.
And eventually they pushed him so far that they caused the Phoenix to briefly go corrupted.
They caused Cyclops to lose control and the fallout was that in a moment of rage, he killed Charles Xavier.
And everyone hated him for it forever.
Even though no one in the Marvel Universe has ever respected the X-Men,
even though nobody has ever respected Charles Xavier,
suddenly because they have a hate boner for Scott,
Scott's the worst person who ever lived.
Scott is now mutant Hitler.
He's worse than Magneto ever was in The Avengers Eyes.
I want a shirt that says Magneto is right.
I do want that shirt. It's a good shirt.
I want a shirt that says Cyclops was right.
That's another good one.
And that became like a meme for many years.
Still to this day, unlike 4chan and Ko and stuff,
the Cyclops was right meme.
Because Cyclops was right.
They tried to portray it.
They still try to portray it.
Like he went evil. He went rogue.
He's a bad guy now.
But he's not.
Everything he does is logical and noble.
But the narrative wants you to think that he's become like Magneto at his worst,
even though he's become the greatest hero in the Marvel Universe.
It's one of those weird things where the narrative doesn't understand
how the people are reading it.
It doesn't understand how badly it's written.
Whatever makes sales, I guess.
Whatever continues it.
So the fallout of all this is that even though Scott was totally in the right
for the entire...always.
Scott has always been in the right and he always will be.
All the superheroes hate Cyclops.
He's considered a pariah now.
He's a bad guy.
He has to live in an old Weapon X facility
in the fucking frozen tundra in Canada.
Because it's the only place where the cops won't come for him.
He has like a secret team of X-Men.
And okay.
So everyone hates Cyclops for no reason.
Now we get to Beast.
You remember Beast, right?
Henry McCoy on the X-Men, the animated series.
He's this...you know...
He's an archetype.
He's a character that everyone understands.
He looks like a monster.
He looks like a beast.
But he has the mind of a genius.
He's a brave, noble, compassionate soul
dwelling in the body of this abomination.
That's what makes the character interesting.
The fact that he looks like a big scary gorilla man,
but he's a great person.
Marvel didn't like that, I guess.
At some point, slowly, this happened insidiously
over the last decade or so.
They slowly turned the beast that everyone knows and loves
into the worst person who ever lived.
Like, the beast has become the supervillain
that Marvel thinks Cyclops has become.
I agreed X-Men comics and I want a barf.
Like, I don't know, he gets...
So the beast does all these horrible things for a decade
and is never called out on it in the narrative,
except for one time, in one glorious comic
where the Watcher showed up in Beast Room.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Um, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There was one comic where the Watcher...
The Watcher is like the narrator of the entire Marvel Universe.
Well, it was.
But, uh, you know, his job is to watch.
He's the audience surrogate for the Marvel Universe.
He's a cosmic guy who watches everything that happens.
The Marvel Warrior.
Yeah.
And there was this one comic, I forget which one it was,
but where, like, the Watcher just comes into Hank's room at night
and he wakes him up and he goes, I am the Watcher.
I have seen all that was and all that will be.
Hank McCoy, you are the worst person I've ever met.
And I'm like, I really feel like that page was written
by, like, some disgruntled guy at Marvel
who saw what was happening and wanted to have his say
before they fired him.
I wish I knew who wrote it.
But, um, so they had, like, ten years of, like,
everyone vilifying Scott while the Beast was quietly turning
into, like, the worst person who ever lived.
And it culminated in this really awful storyline.
This awful bloated, like, three-year storyline
by Brian Michael Bendis where, like, the Beast,
in order to teach Cyclops a lesson to show him
how far Cyclops had fallen, he invented a time machine
and he brought the original five X-Men from, like,
the 60s as teenagers back into the present.
I guess to traumatize them and show them
how horrible the Marvel universe is.
I guess his plan that, like, his genius plan
was that Cyclops would see his younger self and go,
oh, I guess I've become Hitler.
I guess you were right all along, Beast.
Whoops.
But instead what happened is he brought the original five X-Men
here, these teenagers, from the past.
Cyclops, Gene Gray, Iceman, Younger Beast, and Angel.
And, um, he couldn't get them back.
The time machine only worked one way.
He built a one-way time machine.
That's how fucking retarded he is.
Um, so they're stuck there to this day, but...
There's so much wrong with that.
Yeah.
Go on.
So he's created all kinds of horrible paradox
that really, like, that break the entire Marvel universe
if you think about them too hard.
Um, so instead of his plan working,
instead of showing present Scott how far he had fallen
in Beast's eyes, it just made Scott, like, more angry at Beast
and more righteous.
And it made everyone angry at Beast,
and they kicked him out of the X-Men, and he joined the Inhumans.
The Inhumans are, like, the bag serial X-Men.
I don't have the energy to talk about how much I hate the Inhumans,
but I will next week, maybe.
Um...
You know, on that note, IVX is going to be a thing soon.
It is going to be a thing.
Um...
But after Death of X, after Death of X, we gotta wait for that.
Fucking...
The Beast was a bad guy.
So basically, he invented a one-way time machine,
like a fucking dummy,
and he brought these teenage X-Men to the present,
and they're still there.
This was, like, three or four years ago this happened.
They're not even teenagers anymore.
They haven't been sent back.
They're still there, just fucking around the Marvel universe,
ruining continuity with their very presence,
ruining everything, making everything dumb,
making the whole universe dumber,
and... fuck.
Getting sweats.
I'm pouring right now.
So anyways...
And they just want to kill off Cyclops.
That's, like, the crux of why I hate it so much.
Well, they did.
Yeah, they did.
He's dead.
But now he's back again.
Younger, not evil yet.
Yeah, they want Cyclops to be killed off
so that they can have a younger version of Cyclops
and reset the character arc,
and get rid of all the character development.
They just want to replace him,
replace this character that has grown for 70 years.
All this character development,
they want to throw it in a fucking garbage can
so they can replace this character
literally with his younger self,
literally with a less-developed version of him,
so that they can have a new, like, weird status quo thing.
I hate it.
So that's four people on the Champions team.
Now you have to get to the girls.
You got Miss Marvel.
So, yeah, those are the four people that I hate.
Are we still talking about Champions?
It's been an hour.
Yeah, we're back to Champions.
I'm sorry, I apologize to America.
We had to talk about why Scott,
why bringing in Young Scott was terrible
and all the things that were connected to it.
Now we're back to Champions
and on to whether or not you hate Miss Marvel
and The Visions.
Yeah, so that's those guys.
Miles Morales, who is not interesting and I hate him.
Nova, who is not interesting and I hate him.
Amadeus Joe, who is not interesting and I hate them.
Young Scott Summers, who is the worst thing
ever created and I hate him.
And then there's Miss Marvel,
who I talked about last week.
Miss Marvel's an okay character.
I have no problem with her.
She's written poopily in this comic.
And then there's...
She's kind of a killjoy.
Yeah, she's being written as, like, the killjoy.
The mom.
They even address it.
They're like this fourth wall breaking.
Like, you're not gonna treat me like the woman
is always treated on these teams.
Like a buzz kill.
As she's being a buzz kill.
Yeah, literally as she's being a buzz kill.
So, like, Mark Wade,
because everyone that works at Marvel is a huge SJW,
he is aware of these storytelling tropes.
He's aware of what he's doing,
but he's too lazy to do something else.
So he thinks that if he addresses these stereotypes,
he can get away with doing them by addressing them
and seeming like he's self-aware about it.
Not that I have a problem with tropes.
I love tropes.
I have a problem with Marvel being cowardly about using tropes
and trying to fucking, like, fourth wall their way around it
and trying to be meta about it.
But anyways, and finally,
the final member of the champions,
Viv Vision.
My home girl.
Marvel did not waste any time ruining this character.
She was just invented,
and she's already ruined forever.
Um, Viv Vision, I talked about her.
I talked about the Vision in the last,
whatever the last edition is.
She is the Vision's daughter.
He made a little family for himself.
He made a daughter, and he had a series,
and it was like the best series,
the best comic in, like, five years.
It was really good.
Everyone loved it.
I'm still hurting over its conclusion.
Yeah.
And, you know, Viv goes through this character arc,
and at the end of it, you know,
she's kind of like this kind of sad,
kind of hurt, broken teen who's been through a lot of shit.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, if you want to know more about that,
read Vision.
Yeah.
We can't emphasize that enough.
Read Vision.
It's like, what, two volumes long?
It's not that long.
Just pick it up.
It's great.
So she's on this champions team,
and I see it, and I'm like, oh, cool.
This new character is being integrated
into the larger Marvel universe.
I'm okay.
I like her.
I'd like to read about her.
Issue two, the end.
You know...
Not even the end.
Before that, when...
Issue two is that all the champions
are trying to get to know each other,
and they're sitting around a campfire,
telling stories.
And I think Miss Marvel suggests,
let's tell ghost stories.
Yeah.
And there is this page that is one of...
The worst things I've ever seen in a comic.
Just like...
Viv goes...
In this weird alien,
star-fired,
Teen Titans Go voice
of not understanding humanity,
even though she was totally human before.
Yeah.
They're writing her as this weird robot archetype
who doesn't understand anything.
They want her to be the data of the team,
learning about humanity,
even though that's not who she is.
She, for all intents and purposes,
she's a human female girl.
She goes to a high school.
She's not like learning about humanity.
She's learning about the grievances of the human.
Yeah, but I mean like,
she's not that kind of character.
Yeah.
But they have her playing that role,
and Miss Marvel suggests telling ghost stories.
And Viv goes,
a ghost story.
A ghost is something that is alive,
but not really.
Like an android.
Is that...
a microaggression?
Oh my god!
No.
They...
They did it.
Marvel, your tumblr is showing.
They fucking did it!
They put the word microaggression
into a comic,
and not only did they put the word
microaggression into a comic,
they put it in the mouth
of a character who had all the potential
to be interesting.
That we all liked and wanted to see more of.
Immediately ruined.
Immediately they've taken her,
and they've perverted her
into this weird Marvel tumblr bullshit.
It gets worse.
Oh no.
And then at the end of the book,
she...
The Hulk fucks her.
Yep.
You know,
when I saw that,
that last panel...
The last page of the book,
the last page of the book,
is Viv making out
with the fucking
teeny-bopper Asian Bro Hulk.
When I saw that,
all I could think was,
it must be like kissing a horse.
Oh.
Just, he's so massive.
How could they do this?
How could they do this to me?
How could they...
I don't like it.
Oh my god.
And you know, before that,
before that,
like all of that was led up to
her and Amadeus kissing,
making out.
You know, they're like,
they were, you know,
little teenage thing, you know,
you know,
you have your first kiss,
and she's like,
no, I haven't had my first kiss.
And like,
starts leaning in Nova's direction.
And then again,
it's Amadeus' show.
Like...
Just that fucking microaggression.
No, no, no.
I want to...
It makes my skin crawl.
All of it does.
It's all bad.
It shows the lack of self-awareness
on Marvel's behalf,
that they think
that a hyper-intelligent android
who understands,
who can have all information
in the world in her brain at once,
like a fucking genius,
that she would have this personality
of like,
don't microaggression me,
don't fucking,
ah, whiten me up, privilege.
You know,
but they think that is like enlightenment.
They truly do.
They think that that's how,
like, a hyper-intelligent android would speak.
Don't microaggression me.
You know, champions have the potential
to be really good.
The first issue
was actually really good
by itself,
for what it is.
Like, compared to what we've been dealing with lately,
it was sunny,
it was upbeat,
it was positive,
and Marvel lately has not been any of those things.
It's been devastating and sad.
And inclusive.
Don't forget inclusive.
Oh, yeah.
Devastating, sad,
shitty,
miserable,
pathetic,
poorly written,
but inclusive.
They've sacrificed it all for inclusivity.
But there's,
like, you're right,
that second issue was really off-putting,
for whatever reasons.
It was revolting.
And like,
like, I imagine
that I am Tom King,
that I have written this story
that is being praised,
critically acclaimed,
as one of the best stories
ever told in the comics medium.
Some people are saying that.
That it's up there with,
you know, like,
like, Watchman,
or fucking Swamp Thing,
or Animal Man, or whatever.
What is?
The vision.
Oh, yeah.
Right, you're right.
Yeah.
And I imagine that I've written this piece of literature
that has touched people.
That is like,
that is like a,
um, a diamond in the rough.
And in the sea of shit,
that is like,
Marvel Comics,
that I've written this amazing story,
and I've created this character
who has so much potential,
and immediately,
they sticker in a book
and have her complaining
about microaggressions.
If I was,
if I was the guy who wrote the vision,
I would be at Marvel right now
throwing Molotovs.
I'd be losing my shit.
Gotta develop avalanche for Marvel.
Oh, God.
There was one thing
I liked about Champions.
I would be remiss
if I didn't mention
the one panel
that gave me a chuckle,
a sensible chuckle.
It was when they were asking,
when Viv mentions
that she emits Wi-Fi,
so they can use their phones.
And they say,
cool,
what's your Wi-Fi password?
And her answer is,
even an android can cry.
Which is right up there
in the upper right corner
of the panel cast background.
One of my favorite panels of all time.
Even an android can cry.
That was a nice,
cute little nod.
It gave me a sensible chuckle.
I read that and like,
hey, this comic's not bad.
The very next page!
She's whining about microaggressions
and making out with a fucking,
a weird Hulk guy
who's not the Hulk.
Sucking his big green dick.
Filling her,
her, her fuel canisters
with cum,
hulk cum.
Wonder if it's like,
bright green like the rest of them.
Ugh.
Anyways,
that's Champions.
It ruined my life,
and now it's ruined this podcast.
It's been one hour.
Hahaha.
Everything,
I spent so long praising
the vision comics
in the last panel cast,
all of it's ruined now.
They've blown it all up.
I'm like,
Charlton Heston.
Those maniacs.
Charlton Heston,
and there's a giant,
the Statue of Liberty
is a giant,
broken,
viv vision on the beach.
She's been mangled.
Her head is ripped off
and her arm is sticking out of the water.
And I'm just sitting there
on the beach.
You maniacs!
You blew it all up!
Damn you!
Damn you,
salt to hell!
I didn't like it.
I didn't care for Champions.
That's fair.
Eight out of ten.
Hahaha.
Anyways,
now we can finally
talk about the things
that happened this week.
This is,
this is the giant sized
panel cast.
This is the special
third episode anniversary edition.
It's got to be,
this is an 80 page panel cast.
It cost ten dollars.
So let's talk about this week.
You and I,
yesterday,
before we talk about the comics,
we saw
Doctor Strange,
the movie.
Because I've just been
unleashing this torrent
of sweat and rage
for an hour.
I'll let you talk first.
What did you think
of the Doctor Strange movie?
Starring
Benedict
Cumberbunch
The Scrotum Supreme.
That's his name.
He's a great actor.
It's not an insult.
That's what I call him.
I just want to say firsthand
that I don't find him attractive.
But,
but I tell that to the world.
He's a great actor.
He was perfect for this role.
Great casting choice.
No, he was perfect.
Like,
within
five minutes of watching the movie,
I didn't see Benedict Cumberbunch anymore.
Nope.
I just saw Stephen Strange.
Yep.
He totally,
it was,
just like when Robert Downey
stepped into that fucking...
He embraces it.
He owns it.
He is
Doctor Strange.
Yes.
It's the role he was born for.
I loved it.
Doctor Strange
is definitely up there
as far as my favorite Marvel movies go.
I put it up there
with Guardians of the Galaxy,
honestly.
Give me a top five.
Top five?
Not in any kind of
particular order,
but for sure,
Guardians.
Doctor Strange.
I did not care that much
for Ant-Man.
I guess I can skip that.
I still had fun
with the first Avengers movie.
I thought that was
really well done.
Winter Soldier was good.
Lower top five,
probably.
What am I even missing?
I'm going to...
Thor?
Thor was fun.
The first Thor was okay.
The first Thor was fun.
Does anybody even remember
the second Thor?
Honestly,
honest to God.
I remember Ragnarok.
I don't.
I watched it.
And I don't remember anything.
Let me give a...
Let me try to give
my top five here.
Yeah.
Descending from five.
X-Men Days of Future Past
was really good.
Yeah.
The Ending Alone
was one of the best things
ever in a movie
that I've ever seen.
How the ending is
totally retconned
in the third X-Men movie.
That was such a
fuck yeah moment.
Yep.
I'll remember that moment
in the theater
for the rest of my life.
Okay.
Are you...
Civil War?
Was it great?
Did you not like it?
I don't think
they should have called it
a Civil War movie.
No.
Number three,
The First Avengers.
The First Iron Man.
Yeah,
you know,
I forgot about that movie.
I love those.
And number one,
the greatest Marvel movie of all,
perhaps the greatest film
of all time,
Spider-Man 2.
Which one?
The real Spider-Man 2.
Oh no.
With Toby.
You don't like Spider-Man 2?
Spider-Man 2
is the citizen cane
of movies.
Thank you.
I...
What are you doing to me
right now?
What is this?
This hesitation?
It's like you're about to tell me
Spider-Man 2 is on me or something.
That's the look on your face right now.
You're about to tell me
the kid isn't mine.
I don't remember anything
about Spider-Man 2.
I remember the horrors
of Spider-Man 3
and that is all I remember.
You look like
you're about to tell me
the secret of my black son.
What?
You're gonna...
You're gonna burst that bubble for me.
What happened in Spider-Man 2?
I remember the amazing Spider-Man 2.
Spider-Man 2 was Doc Ock.
Okay.
That fucking scene on the train?
The greatest scene
in the history of cinema.
It's like...
Dr. Alan Grant
seeing the Brontosaurus
for the first time.
It's that.
And it's like...
Captain Jack Sparrow
on his sinking little boat
stepping onto the dock
at the beginning of Pirate of the Caribbean
and then the subway scene
in Spider-Man 2.
When all of those fucking New Yorkers
they take his mask off.
I'm gonna start crying again.
And they say...
You know?
He's just a kid.
He's no older than my son.
And Dr. Ock is gonna start wrecking shit.
He's gonna beat the shit out of Spider-Man
and those fucking New Yorkers.
You know?
The real America shines through.
That's something that we need
right now in this divided country.
Okay?
With this fucking election
that we've just been through.
Okay?
Where we've gotten to the point
as a country
where we say that elections
are something we need to heal from.
How insane is that?
That the phrase
we have to heal from this
is said after a fucking election.
That's how broken this country is.
Okay?
We've got people
even after the election
crying.
People breaking down in tears
about Donald Trump.
People are so fucking sad right now.
The country is tearing itself apart.
This poisonous election
has ruined us as a people.
But I'm telling you
just sit down
and go watch Spider-Man 2 again
and you will feel the spirit,
the power of the real America
pumping through your veins,
marching through your body
like electric soldiers
filling you with power
all throughout your being.
Your essence will transcend.
You will become,
you will achieve broken brilliance
as you feel the power
and clap for the new day
of the real America.
As you fucking see those New Yorkers,
they come together.
They put aside all differences
and they say,
Dr. Octopus,
if you mess with one of us,
you gotta mess with all of us.
And then Spider-Man,
he fucking gets up.
He's not wearing his mask anymore.
The secret identity is gone.
Everybody has phones.
Everybody has cameras.
Nobody's even so much
as taking a picture.
These people will keep this secret
to their grave
because that's how much they care
about Spider-Man
and he's fucking holding,
he's holding the tray
with his arms.
Ahh!
It's the greatest film ever made.
How dare you
not sing the praises
every day, every morning.
You should wake up
the first thing you should do
five times a day.
You should get on your hands and knees
and face towards Mecca
and praise Spider-Man 2.
I guess I'll rewatch it at some point.
I don't really remember.
What were we talking about?
The Doctor Strange movie.
Yeah, we were talking about
how great Doctor Strange is.
Oh yeah, I was supposed to put
Doctor Strange somewhere
in that top five.
Oh, somewhere.
Okay, top seven because,
okay, Doctor Strange
and Guardians,
I'll also put them in the top seven
Marvel movies.
There you go.
Yeah, no.
Spider-Man 2 is number one, though.
I really enjoy Doctor Strange.
Just everything about it.
It was fun.
Like, he really owned the character
like we mentioned earlier.
The effects,
like the special effects were lone.
I don't know.
I really, it was,
everyone's like,
oh, it's the Marvel's inception,
but I thought it was better.
It really looked like
those old comic book covers
from like Jack Kirby.
Yeah.
Like, you know,
all the fucking colors
and the weird shit
in the dark dimension.
Like just the fucking scene.
The old foil covers.
Oh, God, yes.
It looked like a special edition,
like 90s foil cover
that glimmers in the light.
That fucking scene
where the ancient one first
throws him out of his body
and it's like this 10-minute scene
of him just like
having this total mental mind fuck
and like seeing all the
the wonders and horrors
of the infinite cosmos.
And that was so cool.
It was a good movie.
It really was.
I can't praise it enough.
All the casting was great.
The ancient one was awesome.
I think this might,
people might have complained
about her being a woman,
but I think that was
probably blown out of proportion.
They actually complained
specifically about her
being a white woman.
That's right.
It wasn't that she was a woman.
It was that she was white.
Even though she's a great fucking actress.
She was so good.
Like,
I don't know.
I believed it.
I couldn't,
I don't know if I would have wanted
like another,
a different kind of ancient one
because how many times
have we seen that archetype
of an old ancient wise
like Tibetan guru
or Chinese guru
with like a big,
with a fucking Paimei beard
and a fucking,
you know,
we've already seen that
in every movie ever made.
It was a brilliant casting choice
to make the ancient one a woman
and a cool woman,
a hot babe.
She was awesome.
She was charismatic.
She felt like she,
you know,
she embodied that,
that simultaneous ferocity
and compassion.
She was good.
She was a nice thing.
A lot of the supporting cast
is really good.
I feel like the antagonists
were a little bit forgettable, but...
I like what they did
with Baron Mordo
because in the comics
and also like,
I mean, like,
I have an old, like,
from like 2007,
like this Marvel animated
Doctor Strange movie
that was really kind of boring
and not very good,
but I watched it like 10 times
that, you know,
same basic plot.
It's Doctor Strange.
He learns his powers.
He fights Dormammu or whatever.
You know,
in the original Doctor Strange origin,
Baron Mordo was like the Anakin.
He was power hungry
and it corrupted him
and he like tried to kill
the ancient one
and that's why he became a villain.
And this movie did something
like a little bit more unique
and a little bit more clever with it.
We're like,
instead of being like
a power hungry bad influence,
Baron Mordo was kind of like
the moral rules not see a little bit
and he was upset
with like the ancient one
breaking the rules
and it was his sort of devotion
to the cause
and his,
it was his strong moral sense
that caused him to become a villain
by the end.
Yeah.
Instead of like any kind of like
typical overdone, greedy,
I just want to be,
that was like the Caestilian role.
Or like in Ant-Man.
Yeah.
Like with the wasp.
Oh, Ant-Man was a good one too.
Top eight Marvel movies.
Ant-Man is on there.
You didn't like Ant-Man?
I was,
it was not blown away by it.
Well,
get out of my house.
I just felt like Paul Rudd
was a very Paul Ruddy in it.
Very watered down
compared to what I'm used to seeing out of him.
But anyway,
I don't know,
I really like Doctor Strange.
I really like the supporting cast.
Rachel McAdams who,
if you're not familiar,
she was the main antagonist
in Mean Girls
and now she is the
straight shooter, I guess,
that kind of part,
that just kind of helps
Doctor Strange out along the way.
Oh, Wong was great.
I loved Wong.
Wong was the best.
He was awesome.
Oh yeah.
Papa Wong.
It did a really good job of
I guess making me give a shit
about Doctor Strange.
Because I've always felt like
Doctor Strange in the comics
is a character that sort of
only works as a supporting character.
Like he'll show up in like a
Gwen pool
or in someone else's comic
and do some mystical stuff.
Or like in the original Civil War
he just kind of shows up
and he's like fixed.
Yeah, because his powers
are so like beyond the scope
of what people can grasp.
Like there's no rules to them.
So like...
If he was always on a team,
like everything would always be fine.
Like I feel like
reading Doctor Strange comics
or trying to,
I always feel like
what the hell is going on?
Like how can I get invested
in a story with no rules?
Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe I haven't read enough
of the character.
But he's always been
like one of those
that's been a little difficult
for me to care about
or to grasp.
And they did a really good job
in this movie of making him
understandable.
And this is who he is
and what he does.
And there he goes.
Yeah, I'm really glad that they did
like all of the origins
and like the traumas
of what he went through
as a neurosurgeon.
Yeah.
It was really good.
And of course,
spoiler alert,
the actual,
not villain,
like just the
the cosmic force
in which the antagonists
were trying to get a hold of.
I was very excited about
Oh, Dormammu.
Oh my God.
Yes.
Yeah.
I was,
I was shaking in my chair.
I was like, yes, I need this.
How did you feel about
the look of Dormammu?
I had no problem with it.
I feel like it was fine.
Like the way that they portrayed
him in the movie
is suiting to the movie
and its theme
and what they were going for.
If they had just done
the actual Dormammu,
like design him
and his like
the guy with the scary head.
Yeah.
Like I feel,
I feel like that would have been
very thematic.
I don't like,
I don't think it's thematic.
I get what they were going for.
Like I,
like if he's in the dark dimension,
of course that he would be
like some giant,
eldritch fucking face
in the clouds, man.
But it just,
it kind of gave me
vibes of like,
of the,
the cloud Galactus
in the second
Fantastic Four movie
or like,
or like in Green Lantern.
Oh yeah.
Parallax was just like
It was a big ol' angry cloud too.
Yeah.
But they did it better.
It was definitely
better done
than in the Fantastic Four movie.
Because in that movie is,
that was like
in the early days
of the Marvel movies were like,
they didn't want to be
too comic booky
or too hokey.
They wanted to put
like the X-Men
and weird leather
costumes,
which now look
way more dated
than the superhero
costumes could ever look.
But um,
yeah like,
they can't have Galactus
be a big purple guy
with a helmet.
He has to be
a faceless cloud of
bullshit.
Like a total,
a maelstrom.
Yeah.
Um.
Anyways,
it was a minor thing that I was like,
well,
I wish he was a guy with a scary head.
But it didn't bother me that much.
It was a great movie.
No,
I'm glad that it wasn't.
Anyway.
And I really liked the ending.
Um,
and there are two
ending credit
or after
Oh yeah.
Oh man,
the first one,
the first after
credits was so cool.
I am really excited
for the new Thor movie.
Yeah,
please,
please.
No,
we were standing outside the theater.
You were,
you mentioned that you said like the
second Thor movie was pretty
forgettable.
And I was about to say like,
no,
it's not.
Remember that hat?
Uh,
well,
what about the part where
the,
the doctor,
the doctor was in it.
He was an elf.
It was Malaketh.
He did.
Natalie Portman
did something.
Two broke girls.
Um,
shit.
Yeah.
White male privilege.
Straight.
Sis male.
President Trump.
Election.
Hashtag.
Free all niggers.
Outlaw abortions.
Hashtag.
Free all niggers.
It's time for my people to rise up.
Hashtag.
Fucking bullet hole.
Hoodie.
Loot cage.
I'm not a fan of
shit.
I'm not.
I'm not a fan of
shit.
Hoodie.
Loot cage.
Sorry.
You saying all this
reminded me.
I had a customer once who,
I had an employee.
She was black.
She was the only black
girl in the company.
And I had a customer who
was a little bit mentally
unstable and he came in
and would hit on her and
he was like,
Oh no.
He's like,
I had a vision.
Oh no.
That.
I had a
Premonition.
He's like,
I had a vision that
my father Odin was
going to give me the power
to free all the blacks.
Whoa.
I need a movie.
I want a movie about the
mentally deranged comic
book fan who
frees all the blacks.
Well,
technically there is a
manga that you can read
called In a Yashiki.
That is about
an old man.
I ain't reading,
I ain't reading no
nip shit.
backwards ass black and
white fake comics
from a fake land
of fake people.
And
Digibro would like
it.
He probably
like In a Yashiki.
Digibro is being
converted.
Digibro loves American
excellence.
That's good.
That's horrifying
and good all at the same
time.
Did you see Luke Cage?
I have not seen
Luke Cage yet.
I did see Daredevil.
I did not care for the
second season of Daredevil
at all.
Neither did I.
I cared about
the first half of
the second season of
Daredevil.
And then it just goes
into this downward
spiral.
It went into this
like electrical hole.
What did they
fucking do to
Punisher?
Oh my God.
He didn't do anything
in the last episode.
The whole season
is about like
Daredevil vs. Punisher.
This amazing
philosophical budding of
heads between these
two diametrically opposed
brilliant characters
who are have so much
pathos and
characterization to them.
This whole season
is about these two
characters budding heads.
And it's the greatest
thing ever.
And they jumped the gun
at the hands shit.
They introduced it too
early.
And they just
the whole thing
went down into this fucking
ninja hole.
And fucking
I don't I didn't
like the actress
who played
Electra at all.
I don't like the accent.
Why can't they just
have them talk normal?
Why do they
cast these fucking
charisma vacuum women
as these fucking
characters?
They want everyone
to care about these
female superheroes.
They want representation.
They want little girls
to love Wonder Woman
and love Electra.
So why don't
they cast people
with charisma?
Why do they
cast these girls
with these like
weird accents
that sound ridiculous?
They don't want to talk.
They talk like
that fucking anime snob.
Fucking
I want to see the Wonder
Woman movie.
She's wrong about
sort of online
and he doesn't understand
he's a bad guy.
I am a 35 year old bald
man.
Wonder Woman is going to
be a 35 year old bald man
who reviews anime
badly on the internet
because she has a
stupid fucking accent
because they cast these
fucking emotionless
charisma devoid
broads as these characters.
Electra sucked.
Wonder Woman is going to
suck.
She already sucked
in the Batman v Superman
movie.
Electra sucked in
Daredevil season two
and they focused way too
much on her at the end.
She's boring
like this queer love story
between her and Matt Murdock
that nobody fucking
cares about.
Electra serves one
purpose.
The character of
Electra is only there
to die.
That she's not
interesting.
She's not cool.
I hate her.
She should just fucking
die and come back evil
and then die again
and get it over with.
I don't want to hear about
her.
I don't want to see her
falling in love with Matt Murdock.
I don't want to fucking
that weird scene
in the last episode
where there was like
100 hand ninjas
just patiently waiting
outside the door
to finish his
20 minute fucking
I'm in love with you monologue
locked in this broom closet
before they go out and fight.
The ninjas were just
waiting there.
They were just fucking
standing there.
Are you done?
Are you done falling in love
yet?
Are you done having
your big emotional fucking
the notebook scene?
Can we fight now please?
And then they have this
fucking tepid fucking
this this this soft
fucking penis
soft penis battle
on the on the on the
rooftop.
The Punisher shows up
and shoots like one bullet
and then fucks off
and does nothing.
They fucking
stuff.
Yeah.
They goofy like
yeah.
That thumbs up.
Oh man.
They they screwed the pooch
on that one.
Daredevil season two
started strong and ended
poop.
I'm like
traumatized right now.
Anyways.
Oh my god.
Luke Cage on the other hand.
Yeah.
How is that?
I hear good things about it.
Well,
Daredevil started strong
and then sort of went
got a little bad
at the end.
I thought
Luke Cage
was consistently
okay.
mediocre
for the entire run.
I mean like
there were parts of it.
There were certain scenes
in Luke Cage
that I thought were some
of the coolest things
I've ever seen.
Some of the best scenes
ever.
There were like
moments where
it came close
to greatness.
But for the most part
I kind of
was spacing out
and I think
binging is an unhealthy
way to watch
those anyways because
you get bored by the
seventh episode.
No matter how good
a show is.
So that could be part
of it.
But it didn't.
There were some really
like the scene where
he's you know
wearing the bullet hole
hoodie and Method Man
writes that cool rap song
about the black power
and that
that part was awesome.
You know,
it's funny too
because there were a lot
of people complaining
online
that Luke Cage
was a little
too black.
No,
fuck that.
That's bullshit.
And you know,
I just want to sit there
and I just want to tell them
like,
do you even know
what Luke Cage is about?
Why would you say that?
Like enough.
I want him to be the blackest
niggest ass,
fucking
bufarest
jungle bunny,
fucking
tar baby.
What's another one?
This is Trump's America.
I can say these things now.
I want him to be
the niggest of all
possible nigs.
The big nigg.
Yeah.
I mean,
yeah, he was good.
The show was definitely
sufficiently black.
He could have even been blacker
and I would have been happier.
Yeah.
You can't fucking take the blackness
out of Luke Cage.
The whole point of the character
is being black.
Like,
that's...
They were like,
it's just not credible
the way he's acting.
He's not acting.
It seems a little
scary.
And I was like,
stop.
Stop talking.
Read the old comics.
If you're kind of shit
on Luke Cage
for how they're
presenting him now,
you're not going to like
the old comics.
Yeah.
The inclusivity thing
that I've complained about
and that everyone can play.
It's not just about,
oh, they're taking
white characters
and white men
and turning them into
girls or black
or minorities or whatever.
It's just that,
regardless of race,
let the character
be who the character is.
Yeah.
Like,
Luke Cage is,
he's a fucking,
he's a fucking
70s exploitation.
He's shaft.
That's who he is.
Yeah.
And that's who he should be.
Which anybody,
if you're not reading
the new Luke Cage comics,
I do recommend them.
They're fun.
They're only,
there's only going to be
four of them
and it's drawn by the same guy
who did Samurai Jack.
Like,
making Luke Cage less black
would be the same as
making Thor a woman.
It's equally retarded.
It was definitely,
there was a lot of good scenes.
The scene where fucking
Cotton Mouth gets beaten up
by the girl,
I don't want to spoil it too much,
but that scene was fantastic.
That was like,
had me gripped.
And the scene,
like right at the beginning,
where like he,
the guy holds him up
and tries to mug him
and he says,
you know, you see that
police across the street,
let me give you a history lesson
about why America is great.
I love that like,
the patriotism aspect
of his personality
was really cool.
He was like,
he's a great character
and I liked the actor.
There was one thing
that really bothered me
about Luke Cage.
The actor has a fucking mole
on the back of his head.
And I mean,
like he's bald
for the whole show.
He shaves his head,
but that fucking mole,
every time I see it,
it took me out of the show.
Like,
can he get that removed,
please?
If he's going to play
a beloved character,
if I'm going to have to watch
Luke Cage forever
for years and years,
and it looks weird,
like you can see it
from the front.
It's a mole
on the back of his head
and you can see it
from the front
because it sticks out weirdly.
And I'm just looking at it,
the whole show,
he's like,
I'm Luke Cage,
I'm really strong
and Black Lives Matter
and I'm going to beat
the bad guys
and I'm going to have a fight
and the whole,
I can't even fucking
focus on.
All I can focus
is that weird mole
on his head
and I just want to take it.
It's like Austin Powers.
I'm just looking at
Luke Cage,
the whole movie.
Mole,
we talked about Steven Strange,
we talked about Luke Cage,
we talked about Daredevil.
Now we can finally
talk about comics.
An hour and a half
into the panel cast,
we can talk about comics.
The new ones from this week?
Yeah, the new ones
from this week.
Oh no.
I know, I know.
You see it on my notes.
Yeah.
I mean,
so last week
wasn't really that great.
This week is equally
unimpressive.
And that's not to say
that comics are generally,
so they released
Spider-Man Renew Your Vowels
number one this week.
And I have been
so excited for this one
because I really like Mary Jean
as a superhero.
I like Mary Jean in general.
Yeah, she's interesting.
She's fun.
I think taking her out
of the Spider-Man mythos
was one of the worst things
they ever did.
No, like,
Mary Jean is fun.
She's great.
She's Peter Parker's fucking wife.
And she should be.
Yeah.
But Spider-Man Renew Your Vowels,
which was a title
that they released
during Secret Wars
as, like, just a few issues.
And now it is an ongoing series
starring Spider-Man,
Mary Jean, his wife,
and their daughter, Annie.
And I'm just going to say this
right now.
I do not give a fuck
about Annie.
I don't give a fuck
about anyone's daughter.
I don't want to see anyone's kids.
I hate kids.
I'm tired of,
like, it's a consistent thing
in Marvel.
All the kids in Marvel
are really fucking smart.
We get it.
Yeah.
I mean,
she's sitting in her room
and she fucks up her dad's shit
because she's trying to make it
better and she's crying
and she's trying to make it better.
It's like, I get it.
Here's what I hear.
Here's how I feel about, like,
about kids sidekicks in general.
There should be one
and his name is Robin.
I like Damien.
I mean, all the Robins.
All the Robins.
Batman can always have a Robin.
Batman always should have a Robin.
Mm-hmm.
Nobody else,
no other superhero should have,
like, a younger sidekick.
It only works for Batman because I think like the character of Batman kind of needs a Robin
But um
You know, I hate kid flash. I hate Donna Troy. I hate fucking all the little teeny boppers. I hate them
They shouldn't exist
Fucking if you're if you're if your name isn't Robin, then you shouldn't be a fucking sidekick
You should be I hate them superheroes don't need little sidekicks
Robin is the sidekick
Yeah
Either way renew your vows like I was really looking forward to this one and it and how did you describe it insipid insipid?
Yes, yeah, that's I think that's a pretty good. I just felt nothing. It was yeah
Well, it did not leave an impact on me like I feel like it should have like the artwork was really good
I loved the chemistry between Peter Parker and Mary Jane, but anytime they brought in Annie
It just fucking ruined everything for me. I'm a little spider. I pooped in my web diaper
I have to have I have to wipe my butt. Watch me catch this this item in the most fucking
Graciously a elaborate way at the kitchen table. I get it. You're a fucking spider girl. I get it. You're a fucking genius
So you heard me talking about spider-man 2 and you and you heard in my voice
How much the character of spider-man means to me?
I'm gonna go here. I'm gonna I'm gonna go go for it. So about 10 years ago
Everything about spider-man was
irreparably ruined forever
They took it all they took everything that was good and pure about the character and they flushed it down the visitors crapper and
The character of Peter Parker to this day has not recovered. I think I feel like the entire Marvel universe
Has not recovered. I feel like this decision in a lot of ways
ruined the entire Marvel universe
There was this storyline 10 years ago called spider-man one more day
infamous
infamously hated for for good reason, but you know what?
No matter how much people hate one more day, they don't hate it enough
They don't god fucking so
Civil war
The original civil war a huge plot point was that spider-man revealed his secret identity. Yep
He joined Tony Stark side Tony Stark assured him that this would be the safe and right thing to do
Yep, and because he's spider-man it immediately backfired
Of course all of his enemies
Because like one of the great things about spider-man to me one of the great things
about the character of spider-man is
His greatest flaw, which is that he's a bully
Spider-man's supervillains hate him
They want him to suffer like
Fucking
Killer croc doesn't hate Batman. I mean he hates them because he foils his crimes
Yeah, Batman's just an inconvenience
But like on a personal level because spider-man doesn't just beat up his supervillains. He mocks them
He makes fun of them. He belittles them because spider-man was bullied as a teenager and
Like I feel like an un-talked-about aspect of his character is this big flaw of his that he's internalized it and
He's always projecting even trying to be responsible and trying to be a good guy
Spider-man is kind of a dick. He is a bully
He'd be you know and so his all of spider-man's villains doc-ock green goblin electro the shocker
They all have this personal fucking hatred of spider-man and they want to make himself for so much
So in that way, you know spider-man
He creates his own problems
Because he makes these these two-time criminals these would be
Nothing criminals he kind of elevates them to super criminals just because of how much he makes them hate him
Yeah, that's a really good example. Yeah black cat's a legitimate super. She was like a cat woman kind of a vigilante sort of a
On again off again girl things have definitely escalated and now she's like an evil kingpin type. Did you ever read superior spider-man?
Yes
Great
But that's kind of what I like about spider-man is that um, I think that what makes him
Possibly the best superhero or the best superhero character in his own way. I think every
Comic book character is the best comic book character in their own way
But um, I just like the fact that of all the superheroes
I think that spider-man has always been the most corruptible the most human he will always make mistakes
He will always be corrupted by his by power or like delusions of grandeur
He'll always have moments where he loses his temper and does something stupid and he'll always create bigger problems for himself
And that's kind of the character struggle and what makes him interesting to read about so
He he gets assured by Tony Stark that removing his mask and revealing his identity
Will be an okay thing but because he's spider-man and
Everyone fucking all of his supervillains hate him so much
immediately it backfires and everybody starts gunning for his family and
eventually like an assassin hired by Wilson Fisk shoots Aunt May and Aunt May is gonna die and
Because he has a guilt complex. He feels like it's his fault even though Aunt May is a thousand years old in any ways
He's gonna fucking croak any day now. You know, he's desperate. He goes to everyone. He goes to read Richard's
He goes to dr. Strange. He goes to even even supervillains like dr. Doom desperate
Please someone who's good at science or magic save my aunt aunt
How do you say aunt? I've always said aunt. I think I'd say aunt. I don't know you're from Texas. Yeah, I
Don't know it always trips me up. It swings. It does swing, you know, please
It depends on their personality somebody save my aunt. She can't die. It can't be my fault
I will be a sad panda if that happens. I think she's an aunt may for sure though. Yeah, but um
Everyone says no for whatever reason
Even though like, you know, Reed Richards could have cured cancer a billion times by now
I don't buy for a second that Reed Richards couldn't have cured a bullet hole in an old lady
I don't believe for one second that dr. Strange couldn't have solved it, but
Yeah, Magneto
But um, yeah, so everyone tells him no no one can
Solve this dilemma finally Mephisto. He goes to the demon lord Mephisto the devil of the Marvel universe
And he says you're my last hope. He signs a deal with the devil to basically
redo this and
So Mephisto uses his powers in exchange. He says, I don't want your soul. I want your love
I'm going to take your marriage and you're not married to Mary Jane anymore the weirdest excuse for a retcon ever
I mean the real reason they did this is because they they wanted they didn't want spider-man to be too grown up
The editor-in-chief at Marvel. He said this publicly
He wanted spider-man. He thinks that spider-man should be relatable to younger people and he should never be too grown up
He didn't want him to be married. He just wanted him to be like a poor struggling bachelor again
Which you know, which now if you look at the
Opposite yeah, I can't they've gone too far in the opposite direction now, but um
So he makes a deal with the devil to retcon all this horrible stuff that happened
And a lot of people dwell on that they do they dwell on the moral implications of it
Like spider-man would never make a deal with the devil. That's not my problem with it
That's because like I spider-man his whole thing is that he's a very corruptible. He makes mistakes
Of course spider-man would make a deal with the devil. That's who he is. I mean, has anybody seen the new spider-man Deadpool?
Yeah, I just go on. Yeah, sorry. I'll get that but um
Yeah, so I don't have a problem with that on like a moral level
Of course spider-man would make a deal with Mephisto. That seems totally in character for me, but
The problem that I have is the ripple effect of this
Retcon throughout all of spider-man continuity and all of Marvel continuity it ruined everything
Nothing for the last decade has made any sense because of this one moment in time
That was clever. You hear what I did there because there's another comic
Clap for me, baby because of this one story fucking
so I
Guess the continuity became that like he did unmask during civil war
But nobody remembered it for some reason and people were like aware that they didn't remember it
They just didn't care
like
Like he was not an Avenger anymore
No, none of the other superheroes even knew who he was which really grinds my gears because that like takes away character development
For so many like different characters and aspects like there was always this like weird budding friendship between him and Wolverine
That I always loved reading that was gone because nobody fucking knows that he's Peter Parker now
Nobody ruins everything this like this like weird bonding moment with Jessica Jones and that one issue were like
Hey, we went to high school together and I had a crush on you Peter in high school and Luke Cage is like nigga
What and that was a great moment that I don't know how that fits in anymore
It doesn't make cuz nobody knows he's Peter Parker
They got fucking comics now to this day
Nothing about the Marvel universe makes any sense because the ripple effect there's so many tiny little things
So many little stories that you now have to wonder did they even happen?
Did they do how do they fit in anymore because because nobody knowing his identity it ruins everything like um
Like in the new Avengers comic nobody trusts spider-man. They're like who's this weird spider-man guy?
We don't trust him. We don't know who he is. Everybody thinks that spider-man is like a weird guy
Even though he was an Avenger for like a decade. He everybody lived with them. They knew he was Peter Parker fucking Tony Stark
Meets Mary Jane and he goes. Oh, who are you? I don't know who Mary Jane Watson is Mary Jane lived in Stark Tower for like 10 years
Holy shit, but it doesn't make any sense
I read and it just blows my fucking mind like every fucking thing having to do with spider-man blows my mind
None of it makes any sense. Nobody. How does Tony Stark not know who Mary Jane is?
She lived at his house does she just not remember living at his house for 10 years
Does he does he not remember this does he remember like someone lived this you remember that like do they remember that like?
Yeah, spider-man was an Avenger, but maybe we didn't see his face and we didn't we never paid attention to that to his wife
And his aunt who lived here. What wife what aunt we don't know what?
Like even though spider-man has been like
Like it's back to this like weird old status quo of like none of the superheroes knowing if they can trust spider-man
Even though like he's been like an Avenger. He's been like the best superhero for years and years
X-Men he's been on the fantastic for future foundation. I'm sorry. Yeah, like spider-man
His tangled web is a part of everything spider-man is the lynchpin of the entire Marvel universe
Red conning that one thing about spider-man had ripple effects that ruined everything and made everything goofy like
Like spider-man's power his real power in like a meta sense
Not not that he can not that he's agile and can shoot webs
The real power of the character of spider-man his place in the Marvel universe is that in an unspoken sense
He is the best superhero that is the purpose of spider-man. He
He's been around all these years. He's the most fucking, you know
Resilient the most, you know the most tenacious
Every superhero he doesn't have the best powers
But every superhero secretly knows that a spider-man got pissed off enough. He would kill all of them spider-man
His place in the Marvel universe is that he's the best superhero
He could kick anyone's ass no matter how powerful they are fucking Thor Dormammu fucking
Anyone nobody can beat spider-man. That's his power as a narrative device. Do you agree?
Sure
Sure, do you understand what I'm saying though? Yeah, I do. I do. He's the most important superhero in the Marvel universe
Anyways, there's more spider. So because so because the one more day storyline ruined everything forever
It ruined spider-man comics forever it ruined the Marvel universe forever. Everyone hates it
Marvel kind of has to every once in a while. They released like a what if or a what if we didn't ruin spider-man
What if we weren't the most a comically inept comic book company literally comically inept company that ever existed
What if we actually appreciated and valued our characters and knew how to write them?
So every every couple of years we get like this alternate universe just to like just to tease us of like what if like he was still
Married to Mary Jane and what if the spider-man mythos still made sense?
Yeah, they did that after seeker invasion
Yeah, things like that. I know you're talking about. Yeah, so this is another like sort of Elseworlds kind of thing
Yeah, where it's like what if spider-man was Mary to Mary Jane and they had a daughter and she had spider-man powers too
What if that?
And like I don't see the point of it
I don't see the point of an out of continuity just to sort of like tease people who want this who want things to make sense
Again, it's kind of it to me. It's just kind of like just pouring salt on the wound
You know, I did kind of see it that way like at the tease. Yeah, um, but I mean
I don't know. There are things about renew your vows that I still enjoyed
But I think I already explicitly like yelled about them the chemistry between Mary Jane and spider-man are perfect
Annie ruins fucking everything as usual. She ruins it all the way up until the end ruins it literally
Ruins everything. I hate it. I hate her. Why is she in this?
Yes, and that's that's it. There's nothing really to say about it
I mean, it's just the first issue and it's just setting up the dumb bullshit
It's just gonna be like a fluffy meaningless out of continuity
Salt in the wound cluster fuck up. Ha ha ha wouldn't it be funny if spider-man still made sense, but he doesn't we'll never fucking fuck you
We'll never actually do this
Right, so it just kind of annoyed me greatly everything about spider-man sends me into a blind frothing fucking rage
The new spider-man in general has definitely been that way for me like have you been reading clone conspiracy like actually reading?
Yeah, that was next on my notes. I was gonna get to that, but I mean fuck spider-man is so weird now
They've taken him in such a weird direction. They've just made him into Tony Stark
Yeah, he's just a rich guy now. Like I liked Peter Parker
Spider-man who is so broke they had to run after the bus like stay on the back of the bus like yeah, I'm like
What is the point like wasn't the whole point of one more day the reason that you that you through this?
Wrenching to everything and ruin spider-man forever was so that you could have him like be a relatable guy
Yeah, supposedly, but like now they've gone the opposite way anyways, so now we have the worst of both worlds
He's not relatable and his continuity makes no fucking sense it so now he's like he's in charge of this billion-dollar corporation
He's just Tony Stark now. He's not even Peter Parker anymore Tony Stark isn't even Tony Stark isn't Tony Stark anymore and fucking
I've always hated I've always kind of disliked like genius Peter Parker where they kind of elevate it
Like I don't think that spider-man should be a genius
I don't think that he should be like Reed Richards Tony Stark level. It's okay for him to be like smart and sciency
That's part of his charm, but making him out to be like oh, I invented ten new spider suits and I invented in the top
Like he's in the top eight smart yeah, get that shit the fuck out of here. That's stupid. That's not what that's not why people like the character
No
He's charismatic. He's fun. He's relatable, but now he's just rich
Yeah, and like you can have him still be relatable and still be Peter Parker without taking away his fucking wife and all of his continuity
Like it's not his his his financial status that makes him relatable
It's not like his marital status that makes spider-man the most relatable superhero to a lot of people
It's his personality. It's the fact that he's a flawed kind of doofy dipshit who creates his own problems
And as always seems to have bad luck, right? And so they just don't understand it
I
People who write comics don't understand the characters only I do
I'm the only person who in any kind of a meta narrative sense understands
I should be writing every single fucking comic
I keep saying that and it keeps getting more true with every comic I read everyone who writes comics is incompetent
I'm the only one who understands shit about fuck
I'm having a vein is gonna pop in my fucking forehead any minute now
So spider-man is like a rich like industrialist fucking
Lex Luthor type basically almost and he has these comics where like the Avengers go. Oh, Peter Peter Parker is
Funding the Avengers now and and we he's like an outsider
Even though he lived with us and we knew he was Peter Parker for 10 years
He's like an outsider and we don't know if we can trust spider-man and also Peter Parker is
Friends with spider-man and we all just buy that for some reason all the superheroes who really should be savvy to this
Because Tony Stark did it for like 60 years this iron man's my bodyguard shit, but somehow they totally fall for it again
Oh, yeah, Peter Parker's just this weird guy and spider-man is like his bodyguard
I guess I guess they're like friends like how fucking dumb how much of a bunch of fucking dipshits are these superheroes now
I have an appreciation for Tony Stark in the movies who's like, yeah, my man fuck it. What of it?
That was brilliant that's like
Don't beat around the bush like I get it like I'm trying and that's totally
That's like this moment of like this aspect of the character that is so right
But like the comics never figured out until the movie like once you see it in the movie like yeah, of course Tony Stark wouldn't keep it
a secret why would he it's just yeah like
Peter Parker being like a rich industrialist and like spider-man being his friend
Nobody's ever gonna buy it. It makes no sense. It doesn't make sense for the character or for the continuity
I hate it. I you know
I was really sad when superior spider-man ended like I knew eventually it would have to because Doc Ock can't be spider-man forever
But it was still
Devastating for him to go from you know that to well now
I'm going to get all of Doc Ock's like riches and his company and it's gonna grow from there in the wow
I'm gonna be great and it's just it's not just this fucking
It takes me out of it
Just the fact that like all of these new Avengers comics that came out like when I was in middle school and high school
Where they relaunched the Avengers and it was like spider-man and Wolverine and spider-woman and Luke Cage
And that that was like the best lineup ever
It was all these cool characters and they live together and start tower and they were like friends
They would like have scenes of them like eating takeout Chinese takeout like with their masks off and like there were scenes like that
Jessica Jones see and I mentioned were like we went to high school together Peter
Wow, you were a spider-man all along like all these great little character building moments like and all like ten years of like continuity of like
The new Avengers becoming friends and like all of that because of the the one more day story was like wiped away
Now the Avengers like don't know who spider-man even is they don't trust him again
It's back to this like weird paradigm of spider-man being the outsider and being this like weird guy who isn't even
recognizable from a character standpoint as the spider-man I know anymore and
like
I'm all for character development, but just like
Taking it in like the weird direction too far too fast is not character development
It's just like a goofy it freaks me out and the one more day thing and it ruined everything forever. I'm just repeating myself
I'm going into a fucking loop. I'm in a loop of madness a loop of sadness because you know there was this you know
Fuck one of my favorite stories of all time
Astonishing spider-man and Wolverine where spider-man and Wolverine they go on this fucking time travel adventure and they become like best friends
By the end of it
It's like this tremendous spider-man meets this girl in like the old Wild West and they lived there for like three years and he gets married and then
you know and
He goes back to the present and she doesn't remember and and so like he's lost this love of his life
And the only person he who knows about this like side of spider-man now is Wolverine and they have this like bonding friendship now
That's gone because Wolverine doesn't know that he's Peter Parker anymore. Did that like not happen now?
Nobody remembers anything about spider-man or all this character development that happened in the 2000s. It's all gone
God why why did they ruin everything? Oh
God oh
Boy
Are you ready to move on to the next spider-man topic? Yeah, and after I get done with mine
You had comics that you read that you wanted to talk about too. He's crazy. This is truly giant-sized people
How long are we into this already? Well, I this is the only one left to have after I'm gonna talk about this next one
At some point I'm gonna get Digi on here and me and him are gonna talk about Gwenpool because he's been getting it
Okay, um
Okay, so the last thing on my list for this week is another spider-man. So I you get to listen to me rage about spider-man more
Um spider-man the clone conspiracy issue number two, I believe um
This has been okay. I'm I don't hate this. I don't hate this now granted
It's still like the you know the modern industrialist genius Tony Stark spider-man that I have trouble caring about it all anymore, but
This is a storyline that is
Steeped in some of the weirder aspects of continuity
I'm just like a continuity nerd. That's I think that's why I hate one more day so much because I
Am a fan of it. I get off on these weird stories. That's what I love about Grant Morrison
he's one of my favorite writers of all time because
When Grant Morrison writes a character he fucking reads everything about them that's ever been written and he like pulls things from like the
50s and the 70s and the 30s and he like reintegrates them. Did you ever read Grant Morrison's Batman?
Amazing what he did how he took all these like different incarnations of Batman and made them cohesive into a picture that made sense as
Like one complete character brilliant
I should talk about that because it makes me happy and spider-man doesn't but I'm gonna talk about spider-man. I
Like continuity and this clone conspiracy storyline is a story that is sort of steeped in like
Weird continuity it all stems from this storyline in the early 90s this infamous
storyline
Called the clone saga and it's this it's a storyline that is
Sort of has become synonymous in people's minds with this like bloated
Overdrawn attitude of how comics are being written in the early 90s that sort of caused like the whole market to crash
The clone saga of spider-man is what people point to because it was this long
Super convoluted storyline that went for like five years and it was all about spider-man
Just getting cloned a million times and he didn't know if he was the real spider-man
And there was a sky called Ben Riley who was a clone, but maybe he wasn't a clone
But then he was a clone and it was it got like way
Complex and convoluted and everybody hated it everybody makes fun of it to this day for being so shitty and dumb
By the end of it after like 15 years of these these clone saga stories that everyone hated
It was revealed that it was all part of the plan of the supervillain called the jackal and the jackal was this like weird
Fucking green furry. He was just like a furry version of the green goblin
And he's just this goofy character who just like he loves cloning like that's his supervillain origin
Like other supervillains have like pathos. You're looking at me like I'm getting facts wrong, but I don't care
Like other supervillains have like this pathos like that that make them like almost as three to three-dimensional as the supergirls
Like two faces a great character or fucking. I don't know Lex Luthor is a great character
Yeah, very underrated. Yeah, Poors and Ivy is a great character
Harley Quinn has all the potential in the world to be a great character
But they just turned her into the new Deadpool Harley Quinn was a great character at one point in time
It's another can of worms I'm so glad you feel that way because I think every day about unleashing that candle worms on this panel cast
Every time I start the panel cast I think it's just gonna be the week where I open up the fucking Harley Quinn can of worms and go on that fucking
five-hour rage tirade
Yeah, so like you know some supervillains are great and they have pathos and character arcs
Not the jackal the jackal just loves cloning
He's just and like even though the clone saga was like universally reviled and it ended and nobody ever wanted to hear about it again
Every once in a while the jackal still pops up again with some goofy cloning related
Scheme and I just love the character because he's so stupid. It's such a dumb goofy character. He just loves cloning
He loves cloning like the riddler loves riddles. It's his thing every time he shows up
I'm gonna clone there's there's a line in this comic because the jackals in this comic is it's another jackal story
It's another big clone story and it's reaching into all the clone history of spider-man and
There's there's a line from the jackal. He's talking to spider-man. He's sort of monologuing and he's like, you know
I've evolved spider-man. I got into a little bit of a rut there for a while
Cloning you and then cloning Gwen and then you and Gwen and then you and then you and then Gwen and then you for 20 fucking years
but um
It was cute, but uh, yeah, so this clone conspiracy issue is it's another
Big goofy clone story which I have a morbid love for I think everybody at this point like the clone saga
Everybody hates it, but it's also sort of become like the room where like people love making fun of it
Like it always gets mentioned in the comics like spider-man if you read comics
He constantly quips like oh, I hope I don't have to deal with any clones today
And it's always like a little wink and a nod like it's kind of like when Batman is always like
Periodically Batman would just be like I hope it's not fucking vampires today
Yeah, or it's like when like a when like a when like a contemporary Robin says like a holy fucking
Yeah, holy rested metal Batman like sort of a little nod to how campy it used to be
So yeah, the jackal always shows up and spider-man always has to deal with clones
And it's become like a kind of like a running gag at this point that spider-man
Half of his problems are clone related
so in this comic um
The jackal comes back and the jackal has been given a redesign which is great, and I love his redesign. Have you seen him?
If he was on the covers in the yes, um
The jackal has always been a goofy character, but I think part of the reason
Why nobody gives a shit about him has always been his design because he just looks like a furry green goblin
He was an uninspired lame character design and they've changed him and now the jackal
He's like a guy in a business suit with an anubis head mask, and he looks fucking cool
It's very a star versus the forces evil is it?
Yeah, well, I mean I haven't seen that toffee. That's what it reminds me of
He's the one of the big villains nut. I love that show by the way, but go on go. Yeah, so he meets the jackal again
He's like he's going around and he meets doc ock doc ock's back. He has a new body
Um shit. Yeah, okay
go on doc ock man
Superior spider-man
Elevated doc ock so much. Yeah. Yeah as like as like a credible supervillain like now
like I'm excited to see that doc ock's back because
Like again, that's an example of like character growth and how continuity is so important because it takes characters that you didn't care about
But they can grow and they can become better versions of the cells and suddenly I care about dr
Octopus I never did before and that's why you can't just have a story like one more day
That takes all that continuity and flushes it down the turlet
You can't do it
So there was a big storyline a couple years ago where doc ock
Dr. Octopus was dying. He was on his last legs and as his final scheme
He wanted to kill like a billion people right and spider-man stopped him
But then dr. Ock had a dr. Octopus had another secret scheme where he switched bodies with peter parker
And spider-man peter was trapped in the body of the ailing dr. Octopus and died as dr. Octopus
Dr. Octopus was in the body of peter parker. He took over his body. He took over his life
He tried to fuck mary jane. He's coming. It was some of the creepiest
It was really creepy. It was really a good well well written. Um, he fucked a midget
You know imagine getting your body back and finding out that you have a gross midget girlfriend
I would be devastated. I would
That was like the most sinister thing a super villain has ever done. He stole peter parker's body and body and made him fuck a midget
Yep disgusting. Wow
They're not in proportion. They've got weird little it's not just that there's okay, you know, I'm gonna get off this topic
All of your midget viewers are
They creep me out. I'm sorry
Look, I believe that midgets should have rights, but you creep me out
Um
So
Dr. Octopus was spider-man for a couple years
It was really good. It was a it was a really interesting story and like
Spider like peter parker. There was still a fragment of him in dr. Octopus's mind and they were fighting for control of his body
And it got worse. Yeah, and uh, but
Like the uh, sort of the crux of the series
was that
The the experience of being spider-man
Changed dr. Octopus and he slowly became more of a noble person until by the end of it
This was so brilliant how they wrote this this like slow character arc. Yeah, where by the end of it
Um, the green goblin is like beating up the whole city and dr. Octopus
He's been calling himself the superior spider-man this time. I'm better than parker
I can be a better spider-man than he'll ever be but by the end of it
There's green goblins everywhere. He's beating up the city and dr.
Octopus because he's become a better person because he's fallen in love with a midget
That's how a bad guy becomes a good guy. You fall in love with a midget and she shows you
the light
He's he's grown as a person. He's become like an actual superhero and he realizes
my god
Parker was always the superior spider-man. I can't solve this problem. I am a villain
And I'm an idiot and I'm a megalomaniacal fuck. I don't have what it takes to be a superior
He had this moment of humility where he realized that parker was the one true spider-man
So he goes back and he just gives in the in this beautiful character arc this moment of self-sacrifice
He gives peter parker his body back
He relinquishes control to the real spider-man and it's a beautiful moment and it elevates dr. Octopus as a character and makes him great
but um
so in this comic
it uh
The jackal has found a way
Not to clone people
But to take their memories right up until the moment of their death
And put them in the clones. So they're not just clones. They're basically
They know everything that the person knows, right? Right
but
dr. Octopus
Because the because dr. Octopus's body died a long time ago. He doesn't have the memories of doc ock
But because the superior spider-man when he did the spider-verse thing
He learned that he would eventually lose his body back to parker. He didn't know how yet
So he did some sneaky stuff and he put his brain in a computer and the computer got out and the computer put his brain
into the clone that the jackal made so
it's
Dr. Octopus the clone has all the memories of the superior spider-man
But not the memories where he became a good person and at the end gave up his body
So he's just kind of so he still has that grudge like spider-man. I took over your body and somehow
I don't know how it happened because i'm from an earlier part of it
I don't know how you got your body back
But you must have done something sneaky and spider-man has this moment where like no
I don't don't you see you gave me my body back
You became a better person and he's like i don't believe you you did something sneaky. I'm still a bad guy
Fuck you. I was the superior spider-man
So he's so he has
Just enough of that character development to be the superior spider-man still
But not enough to have completed his little arc and be a good person again. Oh, no, it's it's sad. It's I like it though
it's
so
So doc ock is back and he's got his body back
And he's he has this grudge against spider-man because all he knows is that he was the superior spider-man and somehow
He doesn't know how somehow parker sneaky sneaked his way back into the body
So now he hates him even more and so this this this this sort of b-list villain
Dr. Octopus has been elevated to like want to like kind of spider-man's arch nemesis more so than the green goblin now
And that's pretty cool. So dr. Octopus is there
Um, and he's beating up spider-man. He's gonna take the crap out of him. Rhino's there
Uh, there's a new electro who's a girl. Electra can't call her. There's already an electro. How do you do that?
It looked Trina. Yeah, um
So
The jackal has brought all these people back to life
He's brought um, yeah, and he's given them a pill
So he's keeping them on a leash because if they'd stop taking this pill their clone bodies will break down
So the jackal has brought all these spider-man villains back to life
But he controls them his his greatest clone related scheme yet
And so he's fighting dr. Octopus and the jackal shows up and says no dr. Octopus. Don't do it
Um, I have to monologue for a bit. Tell him about my plan
and so
the jackal
Take spider-man around Gwen Stacy's there. There's a Gwen Stacy clone, of course
um
The jackal is telling spider-man
About his plan
And he's saying spider-man
Look at what I've done. I've eliminated death forever and spider-man. He's going on that lame superhero. You played god shit
Cry me a fucking river. Yeah jack jack me off
Um, but he's like look what I've done spider-man and he opens up a door and it's every dead spider-man villain ever
They're all back
Everyone who's even like supporting characters like captain Stacy and like, you know all the all these guys all these people that spider-man has lost over the years
Um, he's brought them all back the hobgoblin the green goblin. I don't know if
Norman was actually dead. I have no idea what happened to him after the superior spider-man. Yeah, but he was in the room
So I don't know green goblin was there hobgoblin was there the fucking the the guy with the pumpkin head
What's his name? Oh, fuck. I loved him that punisher killed him in civil war 10 years ago
But he's back. Well, he came back in the venom series. Oh, well, he's back. They're all back
Everyone's back all the super villains are back and also all spider-man's dead friends are back
and um happy reunion
Yeah jackal reveals his secret plan to spider-man and it's actually a pretty
Clever plan and it you kind of as a reader you kind of buy into it. You're like, oh, okay. Yeah
um, the jackal says
spider-man I've brought back
All the villains who've died because of you and I've brought back all of your friends who've died because of you
The reason I've done this
Is to wipe your slate clean all the blood is off your hands. I'm giving you spider-man
Everything you've always wanted. I'm taking the blood off your hands
You can be a free man now free of the guilt, right? But did he bring back uncle ben? Uncle ben? I don't think was there
It's slight oversight on this part
The one person who who actually mattered who who could have changed spider-man's mind
But anyways, he brings everyone back. I guess his plan is to say spider-man
Fuck you. I did something good for you. My ultimate evil scheme doing something nice for you. How do you like that?
That's the kind of goofy retarded villain shit that I love
Um, so yeah, everyone is there
Uh, Gwen Stacy is there and spider-man's like this is crazy. You can't do this
You've brought back everyone who ever died around me. Oh my god. It's a crazy conundrum. But then spider-gwen
Uh starts fighting. Oh, yeah, she's not actually Gwen. She's spider-gwen. Oh, okay
So um, so the Gwen Stacy clone starts beating people up and they her and spider-man escape through the vents
and um
Gwen Stacy says I'm not actually a clone of Gwen Stacy
The real clone of Gwen Stacy that the jackal made fucked off with kane over here and they're off somewhere else. I'm a mole
I'm spider-gwen from a secret universe. I'm blue. I have spider powers. Whatever
Whatever the fuck and then it so they escape
Peter escapes with spider-gwen and then it cuts to kane and kane is in another city. I think he lives in Dallas, right?
Yeah, oh well houston houston houston
So, um kane is in houston and is driving around his spider car because there's no web slingy buildings in houston. I guess
No, well not unless you're in downtown Dallas
So it cuts to kane and
He's got the actual Gwen Stacy clone with him
And that's how it ends. He it's the reveal that the the Gwen Stacy clone and the spider-gwen have switched places
and they've
Yeah, and now they're gonna bang
I do love me some scarlet spider. Yeah
That was one of my favorite like many runs of any kind of off scarlet spider because we keep mentioning him
But I haven't explained who he is yet. He's uh, he's one of the many many clones of spider-man
But he's the best one. He's definitely the best one. I can't recommend scarlet spider enough
Yeah, he's he's he's all the superpowers, but none of the responsibility. He fucking hates the responsibility
He fucking hates peter parker. He's like a misanthrope and he's a jerk
He ran away to houston because there were no heroes there and he's like good
Yeah, fuck it and he's sitting on the couch like getting fat eating cheetos and
Suddenly like his whole life is just ruined by the news
Because he happened to save some old lady who's trying to cross the street and an 18 wheeler almost smushed her
And he was like no fuck her. She can die. I don't care. This is okay
But of course, you know at the last second he saves her but in the process like destroys the 18 wheeler with his body
And hurts the 18 wheeler trucker
um
And anyway, he's like
Getting a fucking home old lady. Why are you trying to cross the street? This is awful
And like he slings off he fucks off back home and the news all of a sudden is like wow
houston has a hero
We don't know what he is, but we're gonna call him the scarlet spider and he's just like
I'm going to mexico. Yeah, I can't I can't live here anymore. Yeah. He's a good old boy. I fucking love him
He's my hero. Do you happen to know uh, what the fuck ever happened to ben reilly?
Does anyone know no, I don't think anyone knows
That it's also convoluted. He was he was an important character for a while
but
That was a long time ago. Maybe maybe spider-man's deal with mafisto got rid of him. Maybe he just doesn't exist anymore
Just lost in the ether. Yeah
Anyways, I liked that comic. I am enjoying spider-man the clone conspiracy
Despite all the stuff I hate about spider-man lately. I'll read it eventually
There's been a lot of offshoots for clone conspiracy. So I've been a little less than inclined to try it out
um
But you know, I'll I'll still read it eventually. It's just it's one of those things
Um because the prowler is now a thing in clone conspiracy is an offshoot and some other shit came out. I don't know
so next up uh
What else were you any other comics? Do you want to talk about this week?
Um, no, not really, but I do want to mention that I hope eventually you do read them and talk about them, but
Um, I've been obsessively introducing people to the legend of luther strode series
Oh, yeah, you gave it to me, but I haven't read it yet. No, you will eventually. I'm sure
Um, I fucking it. It's the fantastic trilogy. It's the best trilogy. I love it. I can't recommend it enough
It's drawn by trad moor who did the all you ghost writer at least the first six issues of it
He's done other things. He's been doing several avengers covers um marvel covers in general. He did the latest
Not the latest the issue the suicide issue for a fucking deadpool. He did that cover
He's done a lot of great covers. He's got great art. I fucking love him. I fucking I fucking love luther strode
I'll touch his wiener. I don't even care. It's it's big and scary. I'm sure or or maybe it didn't grow with the rest of them
who knows um
but
Let me actually talk about what it actually is. So it fans of kick ass or even fans who
You know
Expected greater things at a kick ass. I don't know. Did you ever read kick ass?
Is that's all the movie the movie I read kick ass too and I did not care for it
I don't think anybody did good. There was there were some problems with that one. Um, but
uh luther strode follows a run-of-the-mill nerdy kid in high school who ends up finding a book
That it seems innocuous at first, but
You can derive power from it depending on whether or not you're capable of understanding it
So he takes his book he starts reading it. He starts taking, you know advice from it. He starts working out next thing
You know, he's a big buff dude who has the like the power to
predict
anyone's movements
Like it's interesting. He can look at somebody and he can actually
practically see their future in every sense like all
Like it all means um, and it makes the fight seem so he can look at a flaccid penis and see a boner
Yeah, and he can see which way it's gonna bone
Um, and it actually makes the fight scenes all the more interesting
Because you know, he can predict like bullet trajectories. He can predict them
It's just it's a mess of things that he can do and he becomes so powerful
that
He basically evades death because he can will his body to do whatever he wants it to
So let's say for example, he gets shot in the chest by a bullet
He can actually control his muscles to such a degree that he can catch the bullets with his chest and just spin him back out
He has that much control over his body. There's an entire scene an entire fight scene
Where him and another person just like him just like him in quotations
um
He's trying to kill him and you see them fight and suddenly Luther like jumps over him grabs him by his head
And snaps his neck all the way around like it's dangling between his shoulders
But the guy has so much control over his own body that he defies death and ends up pulling his neck back onto his fucking shoulders
And his find like it's it's an interesting series. That's full of violence and gore
And I love it sounds pretty groovy
It's fucking manly. I can't get over it
Um, that's really all I wanted to talk about if there were other things to talk about
I've already forgotten because these past two weeks have been completely forgettable
I'm sorry DC and marvel image titles have been good cannibal was good
If you haven't read cannibal yet the second issue just released this week
Um, but I'm a baby boy. I only know about superheroes
Hey images superheroes trillium well not trillium. I'm sorry not trillium fucking plutona
I only know about marvel and DC because they make movies and I'm a casual. I'm a little casual baby boy
Fair enough
I'm a little casual baby bitch
That's about the extent of what I had to say though. I mean, there's always more that I could say but how long has this been going on for?
Yeah, it's about two hours and 17 minutes now
Good good, but um
Goodbye
Yes
Hey everybody welcome back to the panel cast it and I I fucking
Woo, I just recorded a fucking three hour cluster fuck goes to the most heinous
Wonderful addition to the panel cast ever, but it's still not over. It's still I'm still here
Uh, I have another guest here's digi bro. Oh, we're gonna talk about going by the second guest
Yeah, I had a first guest. Yeah, I wanted to know who the history guest is
um, so
Uh
Wait, what is this podcast? This is about comics. Yes that one
Fuck they like go through the rolodex of all the podcast. I I literally just like I just just I just like blew my mind
Like raging raging about like everything related to every comic ever written for like two hours
And now we have to talk about uh the new gwen pool. I assume you because I've I've succeeded
I've actually succeeded in swaying some people to reading comics. Yeah in particular digi who's an all comics boy
Yeah, I gotta say man. The panel cast has changed my whole life, man
Now I'm you could you are consuming comics at an alarming rate
I feel like one of these weeks you'll have read more comics than I have I feel like that's gonna take a long time
Uh, you know, I've I've come to realize that you're so much better at this than anybody else
I know who reads comics my my brother shade tried to ask our friend brandon tolantino long time comics guy
Like, you know, what are some good comics and tolantino's just like
I just read iron man
We were like it's so impossible to even talk about or like
Because I was just talking about this before
um
Even complaining about like a comic you don't like in order to get context for it
You have to complain about something 10 years ago that you didn't like and then go back 20 years from there
Or something that like some act some storyline
Like 25 years ago that set into motion this domino effect that led to the bad comic you're currently reading
So everything i'm trying to complain about turns into an hour long history lesson on this fucking show
Well, thankfully you've given two recommendations that I I picked up from previous episodes specifically because they didn't seem like
They needed that much context which were gwen pool and the vision because both of them are
They have lots of other heroes in them
But the stories are pretty self-contained and pretty much about those characters the vision ended you already talked about it
Great run. Um, just bought volume one yesterday got my brother reading it. Um
Gwen pool volume one unfortunately not out yet, but chapter eight came out yesterday. I read it
Uh, it was it was okay. It was very cute. That's the main thing. I took away from it. Um, it wasn't super eventful
No, um, not a whole lot happened. I mean the last issue ended
She was on the subway and the cops are coming to get her in this episode. She fucked around
She ran away from the cops. She did some shit. She was gonna do something to blow up those squid aliens the toothed ins
Yeah, and um at the end of it turns out she fucked up so bad that her employer doesn't want her anymore
Yeah, and so he's gonna kill her but then she shot him
And but then it turns out he's a robot man. He's not even a regular man
Yeah, I mean the thing about this comic is that it's it's it's gotten to the point
Or it's kind of spinning its wheels a little bit in that
We we we kind of get what gwen's big problem is is that she doesn't see this world as a real place for some reason
She just thinks it's a comic that's kind of her big
Hangup and it's it's kind of been reiterating that over and over again. So now I'm officially as of this issue
I'm at the point where I'm like gwen when are you gonna realize?
Yeah, there was a point in this comic where she's like she was doing her, you know
Yeah, none of this is real stuff and it was at this at that point in this issue
I was like hasn't she had like the sad realization twice now already
Like she's already had her character arc twice over and she's just kind of looping it seems like
It's a little odd and
One of the things that I I can't decide if I do or don't really like this about the comic is that gwen herself
Is like adorable. She's like this super cute peppy young girl who does not at all
Look like a psycho murderer like the way she acts
And so I'm wondering like is that intentional because like she just so much doesn't think this is real
That like in her mind
It's like playing a video game like even a normal person would go around and kill people in a video game, you know
But like she just acts so fucking psychotic that whenever her mask is off
I'm always like god. She's way too cute to be this crazy, you know, yeah
Well, like it's kind of weird because I think it might to some degree just be the art style that makes it seen that way because
She was introduced late last year
In uh, howard the duck as like a backup story where she showed up and she's like, hey duck man
I'm a crazy bitch. I got guns and because of the artwork in that story
Um, I really got the sense that she was like an adult like in her mid to late 20s or something
Like because she looked like you know a muscly abs having like a grown-up ass deadpool knockoff
Then in her ongoing series because the art style is so manga-y and cutesy
He looks like she's a teenager all of a sudden and I mean when she went marvels when she came over to spider-man's house
And she like said that she was a classmate like it really kind of implied that she is high school age
But they've never had a good there's never been a moment of like here's exactly how old she is, you know
yeah, um
So I've just kind of assumed that she's like 18 or so
Based on the spider-man part, but it's hard to say. She's she's definitely like a weird mixture of a fucking idiot and
Kind of a genius in other ways
She's good at tactics. Not so good at morals and understanding people
But the most important thing about this issue that I wanted to talk to you about
Is how we finally saw the crazy goth girl without her helmet on and she was mad fucking cute
Yeah, that was awesome. I was just like, whoa
Who's this incredibly hot character? Oh my god, it's the crazy girl
I had so Gwen pool has this co-worker this evil co-worker
As part of her modoc organization that she sort of runs or ran until this issue
Um called the evil eye and she's like a crazy witch lady with a stupid helmet
Who says spooky things all the time and this episode?
She went into her room and the lady was there and she was just like a normal girl and she's like, oh my god
Gwen we've never seen each other out of costume before and like her speech was different and she was talking like a normal person
And uh, she sort of played it up like a kayfabe thing like when the mask when i'm in character
I go a little I go a little too far. Yeah, well that she like I guess the the mask like lets her
See all this crazy information that she can't perceive normally and it just makes her insane
But as soon as she takes it off she's just back to normal and she doesn't like remember what the mask was showing her
That was adorbs. I definitely I just said the word adorbs. Yeah, you did adorable total sincerity
Yeah, um, I definitely I love her supporting cast. I love bat rock. I like that bat rock isn't a comic doing something
He's a cool guy. Yeah. Well, that's a that's the funny thing for me is
When it wasn't until
The evil eye took her helmet off that I realized she's from Gwen pool like
For me as a new comics reader every comic I read there's always like a shitload of characters
And some of them you can tell are new like if you're reading a the current dr. Strange run
There's like dr. Strange. He's got his sidekick the uh, the asian guy
There's the grand mask
You know you can tell which characters are there from older comics
But then there's this new girl who's like an assistant that he picks up to like manage his library
Who shows up in issue number one and like she's kind of an important character now in this current run of the comics
But she's totally new
And now i'm wondering am I gonna start seeing this girl turn up in other marvel comics now that she's been introduced
In this one and then i'm reading Gwen pool and like obviously like you said, uh, what's his name the the french guy?
Uh bat rock zele pair. Yeah, he's he's like they like she explains to him that he's from
Previous comics like he's obviously an older character
I love how they're using him because he's just like this sort of
Kind of forgotten about like old sea list captain america villain
And they sort of like the way he's utilized in this story like even though he's like a sea listener and a nobody
He's a veteran of this world and he's sort of the mentor to this idiotic teenage girl
Would you say this is the most interesting his character's ever been?
Definitely, yeah
And and then but but he's yeah, there's these other two members of the team and like
I have no idea if these these guys are have ever been in anything before
You know or will they be in something from now because like
The vision just ended and now all of a sudden the vision's daughter is showing up in other comics being turned into an sjw
Yeah, I said my piece about that already this week
What comic was that? Yeah, like that was in champions number two
And wish I I literally raged about for a full hour
Amazing at the beginning of this podcast
Yeah, um
Yeah, you always want when you read comics like this that have a cool little cast or they introduce new characters
You always want to see them pop up in other comics, but then when they do
Kind of regret it. Yeah, like you like oh, no
I have a
You know being new to comics and all I read the vision and it never even occurred to me
That the daughter might show up again until all at once jesse said like
She showed up and they ruined her and it was like within the same page
That you showed me. I was like, oh the vision's daughter is in another comic. That's awesome. Oh
I real I have already been introduced to the gross disappointment that comes with caring about anything
It was a it was a sad time
Indeed. Um, yeah, so anyways, I definitely hope that uh
That this series like you know goes somewhere
Yeah, I'd like and I hope that it completes itself or has like an arc to it. Yeah, or I don't know
It's it kind of the the modoc arc felt
Fairly complete. She killed him
And since then it feels like it's it hasn't really gotten its footing on the start of this new arc
But there's still yeah, there's like the plot threads that we need to have concluded are very obvious
It's like we need to know what's up with ghost boy
Uh, yeah, she needs to make up with spider-man somehow and like learn that this world is uh a real place
You know, and I still want to see her origin. Yeah, and that too. We need to know her
We talked about that not on a pipe. We talked about that amongst ourselves. Yeah, I'll like uh, it's cool how like
Because she's been so unwilling to give us her origin because it's so overdone
Yeah, that it's created this like
Weird like reverse psychology thing where now I want to see her origin
And I want to see like how the hell she got here because they keep like slightly alluding to it
Like dr. Strange and that one is she was like, oh, what how the hell did you get here?
And she's like, I don't want to talk about it ever. It's a bad time and I'm like, yeah
Yeah, I want it. I want the fact that she's so adamant about the idea that she doesn't want to talk about it because it's clearly something traumatic
Makes it even more like well now I like what was so traumatic about it
I gotta know, you know, uh, yeah, it is a good reverse psychology. I definitely I want to see her be like
Um a popular character. I don't know if she is or how well
I'm getting I'm getting a nod yes from the person here who is works at a comic book store. Oh really?
Yeah, I just uh, uh, I didn't even know you had a guest in the room. Hi guest
He says hi
Um, yeah at the start of gwen pool eight when she's doing the recap thing
She she describes herself as like surely the best-selling character
And I wasn't sure like when I read that I was like either she's selling really well
Or this is a joke about how badly this comic is selling like it's got to be one or the other
But I'm glad to know it's yeah
I definitely hope that she continues to be
sort of a
Mainstay in the marvel universe. I hope she shows up in other comics
I'm I want to see her interact with as many other characters as possible. That's kind of the best part of it
Is seeing her
Interact with all the all the established superheroes and stuff because she's got such a weird outsider perspective
I want to see her hang out with deadpool because that's the character that she's sort of ripping off
Obviously has to happen right like yeah, surely that's the unspoken thing that we're building up to somehow
Yeah, that's gotta be like the final boss or something
Yeah, because like because deadpool part of his whole thing is the break in the like he knows he's in the comic too
So it seems only logical to have
Them meet and bond over it. I mean surely she's aware of deadpool because that's who she modeled herself after right? Yeah, so
Yeah, it's interesting how they have like deliberately not made mention of deadpool as if
Like in order for her to breathe as her own character like we can't mention deadpool because then it'll just seem like
But then you know, it has to happen someday
So I kind of like that it's being I feel like that's when we'll know
If the comic is wrapping up is when deadpool finally shows up
We'll be like, okay, this means that we're we're hitting the uh the end of this narrative. Yeah
Uh, she's definitely a hot sexy little girl
And I want to fuck her and rape her and the whole grab her by the pussy the whole part where she was doing her
like descriptions of uh each
Like scenario like when she was describing what they were gonna do and the art style gets like really
cutesy and like uh
Drawn with like crayon it looked like and that was fucking adorable. It was I was like man
I want to see this artist do more just cutesy stuff, you know
Yeah, good time not a super
Exciting or eventful issue, but still generally speaking a good series and a good time. Yeah
Thanks for having me on the panel cast
Oh, yeah, that was digi bro, and that was the panel cast. It's finally over
I'm I I'm sorry that I did this to all of you. You could all go home now. It's done
Goodbye