Come on, you fuckers think that just because a guy reads comics, he can't start some shit?
Aw, fuck it, take all you want!
Levi, you ready?
Home again, home again.
Gibbontake, the love!
Class is paying 101.
I guess one person can make a difference.
Greetings, true believers.
It is I, Endless Jess.
Here with the very first weekly panel cast.
I haven't actually decided what to call it yet.
I can't decide between panel cast or amazing comics weekly.
Maybe I'll use them both.
I don't know, I'll put a straw poll. Everybody vote.
Everybody vote for the title of this new weekly podcast here on The Pro Crastinators.
The motherfucking panel cast, baby, starring Endless Jess.
I'm talking about comics people.
The most important thing in the fucking world besides wrestling.
Those are the only two things that sustain me.
I am a life form powered by wrestling and comics, and that's it.
The same way that Digi Bro is powered by, like, lollies and pajama pants.
And Ben is powered by money and depression.
And Nate is powered by being wrong all the time.
I am powered.
I take two AA batteries right up my ass.
And those two batteries are labeled wrestling and comics.
I don't have a weekly wrestling podcast yet, but at least we're getting there.
We're halfway there, living on a prayer.
We're halfway to the promised land.
Who knows, maybe someday I will have a wrestling podcast too.
But at least right now, I finally have this outlet for me to spew all of my undying,
unbridled devotion to superheroes and comics
and all of that goofy man-child bullshit.
You know, if only I had some kind of man-child-centric YouTube channel.
I don't know. I don't think I do. I can barely remember. I don't know.
But this is the podcast-centric YouTube channel.
And that's what it's all about, baby, because I am excited to be doing this.
I recently posted the very first edition of my new series, Amazing Comics, on my channel, Endless Jess.
And you can all go watch it right now if you haven't.
It's a video about Judge Dredd and why I think that he's a cool guy.
And his comics are awesome and everyone should read them.
It's just me explaining the appeal of Judge Dredd as I see it in this first episode of my new series, Amazing Comics.
And in addition to that, I'm also doing this weekly podcast about comics
just to ease people into it and teach people, educate people about comics.
And I'm excited because this is something that I've been wanting to do for years and years and years.
But everything I do takes me roughly 11 years of planning before I can actually get it off the ground and actually get it done.
That's the creative process of me.
Everything needs to stay in, like, a metapod state so that it has time to grow from a fledgling idea
or a flight of fancy in my brain, a little seed in the back of my mind.
It needs time to sprout and evolve into an ill beedrill.
As the great poet me once said,
I'm a cocoon wait until I burst to an ill beedrill gonna kill with words.
So I was thinking about this new thing I'm doing, this new avenue of making comic book videos,
this dream that I've finally achieved in my life of making comic book videos.
And I was thinking that, you know, in addition to the Amazing Comics series on my channel, Endless Jest,
that you should all go watch right now.
I'm not sure if I've said that before, but I'm saying it right now for the 300th time.
You should go there right now and watch it and come back here.
In addition to that, I'll also be doing this weekly podcast to educate people about comics
because every comic book fan, here's the thing about comic book fans.
Every comic book fan secretly wants everyone else to be a comic book fan.
I don't think people realize that.
I think people assume that comic book fans are gonna be elitist and not want anyone in their club like how most fandoms are.
But I don't think comic book fans are like that because every time that you walk into a comic book store,
I swear to God, the cashiers, they all light up like it's fucking Christmas Eve and Santa Claus just came into the chimney to get his comics.
Every comic book store in the world, when you go in there, everybody in there looks like they're happy to see you.
And me especially, my greatest joy in life is sharing the things that I love.
Sharing cool stuff with everyone.
I'm like the end of the movie Ebenezer Scrooge of cool stuff, right?
I started out as this crotchety old man, all miserly, hoarding my stuff like the dragon smough.
I'm totally, I'm mixing my analogies here.
I'm combining them into this grotesque, amorphous Akira blob of metaphors and analogies and references.
I try to keep up. I'm in a Akira blob made up of Ebenezer Scrooge and also the dragon smough.
And I'm sitting under my lonely mountain slumbering on top of this hoard.
I'm a hot mess hoarder baby, I'm referencing myself now.
I've got so many references inside me about cool stuff, the spew out at people, that half of my references are just me because I'm the coolest stuff of them all.
So I'm sitting on this pile of cool stuff that I've been hoarding for decades.
I killed the dwarf king, I took all of his cool stuff and I'm just sitting there in the mountain and nobody can have my cool stuff.
It's my cool stuff.
I don't know the joys of sharing yet.
I'm like the guy in the Barney movie where they went to the island and the guy was living in the tree house and he didn't want to share his cool inventions.
And Barney and friends taught him about the joy of sharing.
I'm also that guy in addition to being like smog and also like Ebenezer Scrooge.
It's all the same metaphor, it's all the same basic idea.
It's the same basic thing that I'm getting at here but it's three different stories, all of them at once happening, all at the same time in my brain.
I'm as miserly as all three of those guys put together and the lesson that I learned at the end about sharing is ten times more heartwarming than any of their lessons because it's all of them at once combined into a fusion.
Like Dragon Ball Z, like all of that like smog, you know what I'm getting at.
So I'm that guy and I'm the dragon smog and I'm also the guy on the island in Barney and friends and I'm also Ebenezer Scrooge.
And then the ghost of Christmas, no, no, no, no, then Marley, Marley shows up.
Marley and Marley, they show up first and then the ghost, you know, how the story of a Christmas Carol goes, you know what happens, you get it.
The point is I learned the lesson about sharing and I run into the streets of London on Christmas morning with a bundle of gifts in my arms, all the cool stuff, all these things that I've loved throughout my life that have made me who I am,
that have influenced me into becoming this unstoppable mass of nerd rage and pop culture knowledge that makes up the entity known as Endless Jess.
I've got it all under my arms and I'm running out into the streets of London on Christmas morning and I'm throwing it at people.
I'm throwing my cool stuff. I'm not even asking if they want it. I'm fucking chucking it at their heads.
I'm taking a box of comics and I'm throwing it at some orphan's head and it's hitting him in the temple and knocking him over and he's bleeding on the ground and twitching and convulsing and dying.
But I don't care because he's got comics now and that's all I care about.
I don't care if you live or die. I just care that you understand and appreciate why all the stuff that I love is great and amazing.
All the stuff that I love needs to be appreciated by everyone and I will beat you over the head with it until you learn, until you either learn or die.
I will beat you over the head with a box of comics and wrestling boots and controllers and video games and sexy naked girls, all of it.
It's all the stuff that I like.
Hamburgers, I'm gonna beat you to death with a fucking hamburger and a hot dog until you learn to show respect, until you put respect on the name of all the stuff that I like.
Anyways, let's talk about comics. I think that's enough of an intro.
Okay, so here's the format of this show.
Real laid back, I read comics every week and I'm just gonna go through all the comics that I read this week and kind of review them, I guess, and go over my thoughts and probably spurred out and go on a bunch of wild impassioned rants and tangents because when you really love something, you also really hate it.
You know, I love comics just like I love wrestling and just like with wrestling, I know how good it's supposed to be so when it's bad, this nerd rage just boils inside me like a thermometer that's about to pop and cover the world with acid.
And everybody melts and dies like that guy at the end of Robocop.
It's horrible, it's brutal, it's violent, it's grotesque, you don't want that, you don't want to see it man.
So this first episode of the podcast is actually going to be a giant sized episode because I'm covering two weeks worth of comics here.
I was all set to record this last week and it took me a week, I had to do other stuff, the idea still needed one more week in the idea cocoon.
And now it's finally ready so I'm gonna go over last week's comics and then this week's comics.
So here we are for the week of Wednesday, October the 11th.
I mean 12!
Okay, so the first comic that I want to talk about that I read last week is Deadpool number 20.
This is a one shot, one shots are always cool.
That means it's not a part of like an ongoing arc or a story, it's just an issue that anybody can pick up and buy.
One shots are usually fun, I always like checking them out, picking them up, buying them.
Because there's no commitment, you know.
Nowadays every story is an 8 issue epic.
A huge fucking universe sprawling event with 11 core issues and 50 backup issues and sticking its tendrils into every other comic in the company.
And if you buy one fucking comic you have to buy the whole goddamn story and end up spending $500.
So thank god that once in a while you can at least get your hands on a nice, succinct, compact one shot that tells a complete story in 22 pages.
There's an art to that.
There is an art that is being lost nowadays when it comes to brevity in comics, especially superhero comics.
It's ridiculous because some of the most beloved comic book stories of all time were stories that were one shots or two shots, you know.
Either one issue or two issues.
Days of future past from the X-Men.
This revolutionary story that everybody remembers, that everybody looks back on fondly, it was made into a fucking movie.
It's like two issues.
It's a short fucking story.
The killing joke, one of the most influential Batman stories ever written.
It's like what, 40 pages, maybe less?
One shots are cool.
Keep that shit to the point.
Don't waste my fucking time and don't waste my fucking money.
So this is Deadpool number 20 and it's a one shot.
And I think right from the cover of the book, you know exactly what the story is going to be.
The cover of this issue is Deadpool sitting on a rooftop with a girl immediately just from looking at it.
If you're genre savvy, if you're comic savvy, you know exactly what they're doing.
This is a parody, a Deadpool version of one of the classic superhero tropes.
Which is the superhero having to talk a person down from suicide.
I think eventually every superhero deals with this story or has to contend with this premise.
Because it's sort of an inherently interesting premise.
You know, you take these larger than life fictional superheroes who are usually punching aliens
and fighting super villains and robots and all this fantastical stuff.
All this outrageous out of this world conflict.
And you put them in a very down to earth realistic conflict.
Like having to talk someone down from suicide.
And it's a premise that if the character is good, if it's a superhero that the writer understands
or is, you know, a three dimensional character with a very strongly defined personality,
then the premise sort of writes itself.
You just take character A, sit them next to suicidal nobody B, and you just let them talk.
You let them, you see what happens.
You see how I talked about this on the plebe and the weave.
One of my favorite things about fiction is just seeing the tropes.
I love tropes because I love seeing, I love characters.
And I love seeing how all of these different characters and different personalities interact with
and resolve the same tropes.
I think that tropes get a bad rap.
I think people say all this stories cliche or, you know, this has been done before.
Well, yeah, everything's been done before, but I think that sometimes the most basic reusable stories
are the ones that you can get the most mileage out of if you're a skilled writer
or if you have a really strong character at the center of them.
So this is that for Deadpool.
And it's obviously, you know, any comic that does this trope
is more or less directly pulling from Grant Morrison's All-Star Superman,
which is probably the most famous example of this in comics.
You know, it's that famous, it's just like one page out of the comic
where Superman is dying, he's got like poison, he's got kryptonite poisoning,
and he's on his last legs, but he's still going around the world
solving crimes and doing good deeds and helping people out.
And it's just one page where he, you know, he zooms up behind this girl,
this young teenage gothy looking girl who's about to jump off a building and kill herself,
and he just fucking supermans his way right up behind her,
and he says this perfect, brilliant little quote.
Let me see if I remember it correctly.
I believe it was,
your doctor really did get held up, Reagan.
It's never as bad as it seems.
Which is such a fucking perfect quote because it's just vague enough.
It like implies this whole story that you as the reader don't know about,
but you don't necessarily have to know about.
It gives, like in two sentences,
Grant Morrison gives this character that we've never seen before
an entire history and an entire personality
that you can sort of fill in for yourself as the reader,
just based on what Superman says in like two sentences.
And it's so effective and it makes you feel for the girl
and it builds up Superman as like this amazing guy who just knows everything
and he's always listening and he's always there for you.
And you just read those fucking lines and you just look at that panel,
that one page with no other context behind it except for what's on the page.
And you read it and you just fucking instantly tear up every time.
It's the most touching thing in the world.
And in like even though it's part of an entire graphic novel,
of like an entire 12 issue story,
all of that is almost totally superfluous
because right in the middle of it,
in the span of all of like two or three panels,
he tells the ultimate Superman story,
the greatest most important Superman story ever told
that you ever need.
Pretty much the only Superman story that you ever need
is told in those two or three panels in the middle of the book
of just Superman, he's flying around the fucking world helping people
and he sees a girl about to jump off a fucking building
and he gets behind her and he says some stuff
and he comforts her and he fucking saves her,
not even with his superpowers, not with super strength,
not with X-ray vision or super speed,
with super compassion, motherfucker.
That's Superman's real power.
That's why Superman fucking rules
and it's the most amazing thing in the world.
You read it, it makes you cry every time.
It's a fucking tear-jerker for sure.
And that's probably the most famous example of this particular trope.
So of course the whole hook of this book right here,
Deadpool number 20,
the whole hook of it,
sort of the satire or parody element of it
is, you know, let's take that incredibly touching Superman story,
let's take that trope that was so famously,
incredibly touching in Superman
and let's apply it to cynical, apathetic,
crass and stupid Deadpool.
It's a perfect recipe for instant comedy.
You know, like I said, it writes itself.
You take a trope that works for one character
and you see how it works with a completely different character.
That's the magic of tropes and that's why I love them.
So you see this book, you know,
you walk into the comic book store
and you see a book and it's a Deadpool comic
and the cover of the comic is a girl,
you know, standing on a rooftop with Deadpool sitting beside her
and you take one look at the cover of the comic
and you instantly know what kind of story it is.
You know what they're doing
and you're instantly hooked because yes,
of course I want to see how this trope applies to Deadpool.
Deadpool, the, you know, the wisecracking cynical jerkass,
the merc with the mouth, the regenerating degenerate,
this ugly perverted bastard with a heart of gold.
Who wouldn't want to read that?
Nobody, that's who. Nobody wouldn't want to read that.
And so now you've heard me gush about the premise for 10 minutes.
You probably want to know what I actually thought of the comic.
How well did it deliver on that premise?
Was I entertained by the final product
as much as I am entertained by the premise inherently?
The answer is yes.
It was a good-ass comic.
It was funny and it felt true to the character of Deadpool
and it even succeeded in being a little bit heartwarming.
You know, it starts out, the girl's on the building,
she's about to kill herself.
Deadpool comes up, he says,
no, don't do it.
And, you know, she immediately says,
ah, shut up, don't try to talk me down,
don't pretend like you care.
And immediately Deadpool, being Deadpool,
just totally throws her off guard
by saying like, hey lady, don't put words in my mouth.
I didn't say I care.
I'm trying to care, but you're making it difficult.
So that catches her off guard
and they start having a conversation
a little bit of a back and forth.
Deadpool's trying to talk her down,
but he doesn't really know how to do it exactly
because he's not that kind of superhero.
Deadpool is not the guy who inspires people.
Deadpool's the guy who kills people
and makes dumb jokes about Mexican food.
So that's what he's doing.
He's making dumb jokes about Mexican food.
He's sort of awkwardly trying and failing
to talk her down from suicide.
His dumb jokes aren't really impressing her.
So finally he says, you know what, fine,
why don't you just hang out with me for the night
and we'll go have some fun.
And if you still feel like jumping off a building
at the end of the night,
then I'll let you jump off a building,
but Parker Industries is down the road that way.
You know, jump off of somebody else's building.
Don't jump off of my building
because I don't need the bad publicity.
So she says fine and they're going around the city
and they're doing stuff
and basically Deadpool is taking her
on his wacky, mercenary errands.
So he's breaking into like drug lords' apartments
and hoodlums and beating people up
and shooting people and killing bad guys and all that.
And she's sort of tagging along
and sort of being his sidekick for the night.
And the whole time he's cracking jokes
and he's playing on his phone
like he doesn't give a shit and you know, all that stuff.
Then at the end of the comic,
she goes, she says like, oh, you know,
that was fun and all, but you didn't change my mind.
I still am depressed and I still kind of want to kill myself.
You know, maybe, maybe I'm not totally sure
that I want to kill myself,
but you didn't exactly cure my depression, buddy.
And Deadpool's like, shut up, baby. I know it.
That's why I'm taking you here.
And Deadpool takes her to the fucking hospital.
And it turns out that the entire comic,
when he was playing on his phone,
what he was actually doing was texting the hospital
and letting them know that he's bringing in
a suicidal person later that night.
So they're ready for her.
And he has this speech at the end.
Of course I'm paraphrasing because I read it a week ago.
But um, so I don't remember the exact quote,
but you know, he has this little speech tour
at the end where he's like, you know,
I try to be a good superhero,
but we both know that I'm not the kind of guy
who can help you with this problem.
So I decided to take you to people
And she goes off and then Deadpool,
you know, he goes out of the hospital.
He's feeling a little bit better about himself.
And then he steps in a pile of poop.
And that's how the issue ends.
And a cute little joke of Deadpool stepping in poop.
So it was a very in-character and very clever way
to handle this premise where Deadpool
has this self-awareness.
And he understands that this is not where his strength lies.
His strength lies in cutting people's heads off and stuff.
He has a great quote in this where he's like,
where he's sort of sized to himself
as he's watching here get taken away by the hospital staff.
And he sighs and he goes,
unkilling someone is way harder than what I usually do.
Oh, that Deadpool.
And so yeah, you have a character
acknowledging his weaknesses and his flaws
and finding a clever way to solve a problem
that he did not expect to have to deal with
by working around those flaws.
It's a great little character moment for Deadpool
of just acknowledging his weakness as a superhero
and making an effort to resolve the problem
the way a non-superhero would resolve the problem.
It was very down to earth and it really is like a special...
It says a lot about Deadpool in the same way
that the Superman story that it's parodying
says a lot about Superman.
And that's why I love tropes
because how these different characters react to the same problems
is a great device for exploring those characters.
So that's Deadpool number 20.
I highly recommend it. Everybody should go out and buy it
and read it or whatever.
I know I spoiled the entire comic,
but you know, fuck it, I don't really...
I don't think a spoiler like that is going to hinder
your enjoyment of the comic if you pick it up.
You know, if you're in the comments
pissing and moaning about spoilers,
shut the fuck up.
Go fucking cry me a river somewhere else.
Go sit in the fucking corner with a dunce hat
and eat your own shit like the diaper-wearing baby you are.
I ain't got time for that shit.
I ain't got time for people...
For any spoiler cry babies in the comments section.
Look people, I will use my own discretion
on this podcast when it comes to
what I think is a harmful spoiler
and what I think is a negligible spoiler
because there is a difference, okay?
There are some things that are technically
spoilers of what happens in the story,
but they will not affect your enjoyment of the story
in any negative way.
Obviously, if there's a comic
that hinges on some huge reveal
that's supposed to be a big surprise,
then that would be a spoiler that I'm not going to spoil.
But I don't want to hear any fucking people
crying that I spoiled this fucking one-shot Deadpool comic
that you ain't never even heard of before this podcast anyways.
God damn it.
You weren't going to buy it anyways,
but now you are going to buy it because I'm telling you
that it's fucking great and you can suck my dick.
Okay, that's that.
The next comic that I picked up last week
was Gwenpool.
We're going from Deadpool to Gwenpool,
the unbelievable Gwenpool number seven.
Gwenpool is a new character.
She was created last year, late last year.
She's been a little bit divisive.
Some people see her as just a, you know,
an unoriginal premise
and a corporate marketing gimmick
and they don't like her.
But those people are stupid
because even a corporate marketing gimmick
can have heart, damn it.
Even an unoriginal idea
can lead to good storytelling.
You dummies, you dumb stupid idiots.
So if you don't know who Gwenpool is,
she is a normal teenage girl
from our world who loves comic books
and has found herself in the Marvel Universe
and is using her comic book savviness
and genre savviness to navigate
the fictional universe of Marvel Comics.
So a very tropey story.
Once again, you've seen this a million times before.
It's one of the oldest, most overdone premises there is.
You know, audience insert character from our world
gets zapped into the fictional world
and their only power is that they've got nerd knowledge
and their genre savvy about what's going on.
And a lot of people see that kind of overdone
sort of hacky premise
and they just kind of write it off based on that.
I just reviewed an anime called Re Zero
on The Pleeve and the Weeb over on Digibro's channel
where we both shit on that show
pretty relentlessly for having
the same hacky, tired premise.
But the difference was that that show
wasn't well written.
We didn't do anything interesting with that overdone premise.
That's why we didn't like it.
Like I said, I'm 100% in favor of tropes.
I love them.
And any trope, any premise, no matter how hacky
can be entertaining
and worth reading
if it's expounded upon in a captivating manner.
If it's written well.
And is Gwenpool written well so far?
You better believe it, baby.
This series does do interesting things
with the premise.
It utilizes it
in creative and clever ways.
Like for example, her name,
right off the bat, is a clever little in-joke.
The joke is that being genre savvy
and being knowledgeable about comics,
the first thing she does
upon getting zapped into the comic book world
is she fashions herself a little Deadpool knockoff costume
and she starts calling herself Gwenpool.
Because she figures
that the only way to survive in the Marvel Universe
is to become someone important
so that people will want to read her adventures.
So if she names herself
after the two most eye-catching names
in the Marvel Universe, Gwen Stacy and Deadpool,
and combines them into a portmanteau of Gwenpool,
then people will be interested and they will buy her comic
and she will survive and be a successful character
in this universe.
So the name Gwenpool is a totally shameless marketing ploy,
but they make it a part of the narrative
where she picked that name
to be a shameless marketing ploy
as a means of interacting and surviving the Marvel Universe.
You know, people see the comic and they go,
who the fuck is this, Gwenpool?
What did they bring back Gwen Stacy
and they made her a Deadpool clone now?
What the fuck is this shit?
Goddamn stupid, I have to read it.
I have to buy it.
And then they buy it and they read it
and they go, oh, it's not what I thought it was.
It's actually a clever little twist.
She named herself that on purpose
to get me to buy it.
She rused me.
It was a clever ruse and it worked.
And now that I'm reading the book,
I see that it's clever and entertaining and interesting
and I'm gonna keep reading it.
It's brilliant, it's genius.
I like it.
And there's all kinds of little things like that
throughout the series.
Little clever utilizations of the premise.
Like for example, in this issue,
this issue starts with there's these
like octopus aliens coming down
and shooting up the place and wrecking up New York
and you know, it's an alien invasion
and Gwenpool is able to fool them
by putting her costume on a little pig
and sending it off into the city
and they mistake the pig for her
because they don't know what humans look like.
They can't tell humans apart from pigs
because they're stupid aliens.
And somebody asks her,
how did you know that that ridiculous
cockamamie plan would work?
And Gwen's answer is,
I have never seen those particular aliens
before in a Marvel comic.
Therefore, I knew that they were created
specifically for me to deal with.
Therefore, I knew that my cockamamie
asinine plan would work.
So unlike a lot of shows like Re Zero, for example,
which utterly fail to deliver on this
genre-savvy protagonist promise of a premise,
Gwenpool actually does consistently deliver
on that premise.
And it's even a little bit feelsy at times.
It does manage to have a little bit of pathos
at certain points.
Because Gwenpool, of course, she comes to this universe
and she's very arrogant
and thinks she knows all the answers
and thinks it's going to be a walk in the park.
This is going to be all fun and games.
And because of that, she screws up a little bit.
She makes some mistakes.
She gets a friend of hers killed at the beginning
and is very sad.
And she slowly realizes that while she may be
zapped into a fictional universe,
while she's there, for her, it's real.
So there are consequences to her idiotic actions.
And there are some moments where she makes mistakes
and has to become sad.
It's good.
She's a good character.
She's, you know, this character could have easily been
one-dimensional and stupid and utterly worthless.
But they've succeeded in making her likeable
and three-dimensional.
There was one issue where she teamed up with Spider-Man.
Not the real Spider-Man.
I'm talking fucking Kmart brand Miles Morales Spider-Man.
Don't get me started on that shit.
But she's teaming up with Spider-Man
and they're trying to catch this, like,
would-be school shooter.
And of course, Gwen doesn't take it seriously
and she's talking all this, you know,
fourth-wall breaking genre-savvy comic book trash.
And it's all going totally over Spidey's head.
And she tries to kill this kid.
She flat out just tries to kill him because fuck it.
She's in a fictional world.
She can kill people who cares.
They don't matter.
They're not real, right?
So of course Spider-Man freaks out.
He's like, what are you doing?
You can't kill people.
And she starts talking all this shit.
Like, no, you don't understand.
I remember this guy from the Ultimate Comics.
They brought him back to the mainline Marvel Universe.
The only reason that they would bring him back
is because somebody remembered him.
He was created just for you.
He doesn't matter.
He's not a real person.
He's not even an important villain.
He's just some random dropped plot line
from an old comic book series that somebody remembered
and decided to bring back to finish off here.
He's not important.
He's not even real.
I can just kill him.
And of course, Miles Morales freaks out
and fucking punches her in the face
and ties her up and says,
holy shit, you're a crazy person.
You can't go around killing people.
And she's all sad because she likes the superheroes,
but the superheroes don't like her
because she's basically a fucking maniac
because she has a hard time accepting
that anything around her is real.
It's all fictional.
And she's just kind of amoral because of it.
And she's basically just Subaru, but done right.
I mean, all of you little anime faggots out there,
you turds who pissed and moaned
that me and Digi didn't give a high enough score
to fucking re-zero.
Well, this is why, because re-zero didn't deliver
on its premise in any interesting ways,
whereas you have a series like Gwenpool
over here in my American comics, a superior medium,
you have a series like Gwenpool,
which is the exact same premise,
but done right, done correctly,
done interestingly and entertainingly,
and they actually succeed
in making a likable, decent protagonist
who is arrogant because of her genre-savvyness
and does make mistakes,
but actually learns from them
and still manages to be somewhat relatable
and fun to read about despite those flaws.
So, Gwenpool number seven, highly recommended.
The entire Gwenpool line so far,
I say is highly recommended.
I think everybody should be reading Gwenpool.
It's a really good comic.
And re-zero gets a zero out of ten.
Fuck you all.
You're all a bunch of stupid whiny babies.
You don't know shit about fuck.
I hate weeaboos.
I don't respect you.
Go to hell and die.
Next up, we have My Little Pony,
Friends Forever number 32.
So, the My Little Pony,
Friends Forever comic series is a spin-off
of the regular My Little Pony,
Friendship is Magic comic series,
which itself is a spin-off
of the My Little Pony,
Friendship is Magic TV series,
which itself is the fourth iteration
of the My Little Pony children's cartoon franchise.
So, it's like, you know, turtles all the way down.
It's just My Little Pony all the way back,
stretching through history to the dawn of man.
When the first Neanderthal stepped out of his cave
and was brutally murdered by the first Homo sapien,
ushering in the age of man,
the Homo sapien he bashed in the Neanderthal's skull
with a rock and he stood over his blooded corpse
and he beat his chest
and he howled into the sky
a mighty cry, a mighty roar
that sounded like this.
So, the premise of the Friendship Forever series
basically just taking two characters who normally don't get to interact with each
other as much and pairing them up for little adventures. Again, another trope
that I love. Futurama did this a lot, especially in like the first Comedy
Central season when it first came back. They had a lot of episodes that were
this premise of teaming up Bender and Amy or Bender and Hermes, you know, or the
Professor and Zordberg and going into their history together. You can get a
lot of interesting stories that way by just pairing up characters who don't
normally pair up together and seeing how they interact. You can get a lot of
clever little stories out of a premise like that and you can get a lot of clever
little character moments out of a premise like that. So it's always
interesting to see and this one, issue number 32 of Friends Forever, struck me
as particularly interesting, so I had to buy it. The cover leapt right at me, right
off the shelf. I immediately took one look at it and said, well I got to read
this. It's Fluttershy and Daring Dew on an adventure together. You should see, you
gotta see the cover for this. It's beautiful. It's, they're flying through
like a, an exploding like the inside of a volcano it looks like or some cave with
lava. This is cool. She's got like, it's awesome. It's dynamic and it's
pretty and it's beautiful and it's cute and it's a character team-up that you
never see. So I had to get it, had to check it out, had to read it, see for
myself. If it was as cool as it looked and let me tell you people, it was
exactly as cool as it looked. I'm not gonna say that it totally blew me away but
it certainly didn't disappoint me either. It's pretty much, it's a My Little Pony
comic. If you, if you like My Little Pony, Friendship is Magic, the show, if
you're a brony kind of person or if you're into it, if you like My Little Pony then
you know exactly what you're getting when you pick this up. It's very funny. It's
well written. Just the first page is sort of instantly sets the tone. It's
fluttershy. She's in her cottage and she's going over her calendar and she's
all excited. She's like, oh boy, I finally have a whole week off with no
adventures. I don't have to save Equestria this week. No, you know, annoying, stupid
bullshit. I'm just gonna take it easy and have a nice, relaxing, adventure-free
weekend. And then Daring do just burst into the door and she's like, we gotta go
on an adventure. Rainbow Dash told me that you're good with animals. Let's go
fucking fight animals or save animals. We're going to the jungle. Let's go
fucking yeah. And she, and she, and she sort of looked at the camera and she
winks and she goes, not again. The studio audience goes, yeah, yeah, yeah, great
stuff. Classic. Can't wait to see how this adventure is going to pan out. So they
go on this adventure and so the main gist of this adventure is that there's
this species of spider that has like a map on its back. It's got markings on
its little spidery abdomen in the shape of a map. And if you find all the
spiders together, then their little butts will combine to form a map to some
treasure or some shit. And Daring do needs Fluttershy's help because
Fluttershy is an animal expert who loves little spiders and this was a very cute
little touch, a very enjoyable little detail because the reason that she needs
her in particular is because Daring do is afraid of spiders the same way that
Indiana Jones is afraid of snakes. So that was clever. That was nice. I like
that. Until they go and they have a funny little cute adventure. Who is Odle is
there. He still sucks. He's still a really shitty character design guy. Why is
his face on the end of his nose? I hate that. It's terrible. He's the worst guy.
I think Daring do needs a new villain seriously because that guy sucks. But
anyways, they fight them. There's spiders and there's, you know, it's
Fluttershy. It's cute. It's funny. It's my little pony. What is there
to say? It's just a nice, cute, fun little adventure. Yeah, cute and fun. Just
like the show before fucking season six came and ruined it. Season six isn't
that bad. It's pretty bad though. Hey, we're not talking about that. That's the
past. You got to put your behind in your past. You got to look forward to the
future. I'm a comic spoi now. Not a horse boy. I'm still a horse boy. Get out of
here. Nobody wants you. Go to the furnace room. Yeah. Okay. Sorry for that.
Little spat roommates quarrel that you all had to witness. Fucking Colt
Corona. He's still a horse boy. Man, I can't blame him. He's literally a horse
boy. Anyways, onto my comic of the week for last week. Teenage mutant ninja
turtles number 63. So right off the bat, I got to talk about just this whole
modern turtles series in general. It's been going on now for, I don't know, maybe
four or five years. I mean, it's on 63. So do the math yourself. How many months is
that? 63 months is a couple years. It's been going strong. It's been very
consistently high quality from the first issue pretty much. It's been a great
series. I've been shouting its merits from the rooftops for a while. It's
probably all together my favorite incarnation of the turtles. Definitely up
there because the turtles have had so many different incarnations and re-
imaginings over the years. It's a franchise that just never dies. It's
always evolving to fit its era. The original comics in the 80s were sort of
a satire of gritty, dark 80s comics like Daredevil and Dark Knight Return. So
they were very dark and then from there the cartoon series that came out in
the late 80s and early 90s was very lighthearted and cartoony. It was a
show for kids and it was marketing all the toys and stuff. Then the
movies that came out, the movie was sort of a nice middle ground between the
serious comics and the cartoony cartoon. It was pretty good. The movies are
and then there was more. There was a live action TV series. There was a
second cartoon series in the early mid-2000s. There was a whole new terrible
Michael Bay movie franchise. Out of the Shadows wasn't that bad. It was okay.
Bebop and Rocksteady were pretty great. The Turtles just keeps on surviving
because it keeps on changing and adapting and it's always different. What I
love about this current incarnation from IDW is that these comics have
achieved this fantastic balance of every incarnation of the Turtles ever. They've
taken elements from the original comics and from the cartoons and the
movies and the 2000s cartoon and all of these different elements from all of
these different incarnations of the Turtles and they've blended them
together into this cohesive continuity and this cohesive narrative that is
like perfect. It's just a perfect, it's the perfect Turtles saga. A
Turtles stew, if you will. They've done a fantastic job and I love it. So issue
number 63, which is my comic of the week. This is setting up a very interesting
story with the Turtles that I have not seen done before. A little backstory
going into this issue. Shredder is dead. They've defeated Shredder. They've
defeated the Foot Clan and in the aftermath of defeating Shredder, Master
Splinter has become the new head of the Foot Clan. So this clan of ninjas who
were their enemies, now Splinter is in charge of all of them and he's, you know,
trying to make them a force for good in the world and having to deal with their
responsibility of leading this massive army of ninjas. And in this issue in
particular, it gets really interesting because Donatello has this scientist
friend named Harold and Harold gets kidnapped by this gang called the
Street Phantoms who are like a rival gang to the Foot Clan and they go to Master
Splinter about it and Master Splinter goes, yes, all according to plan. I used
Harold as bait so that the Street Phantoms would kidnap him and reveal their
location so that the foot may strike. And so of course the Turtles are like,
wait a minute, that's kind of fucked up. You used our friend as bait and Master
Splinter is like assuring them. I knew that nothing, I knew that they wouldn't
hurt him. He's too valuable. His scientific mind, they needed him. I knew that he
would be okay. Trust me, this was all for the greater good. I knew what I was
doing but it's like a Ken, like what's going on here? Is Master Splinter
being corrupted or compromised by his new position? And that's so fucking cool and
interesting. You know, I've been a fan of the Turtles forever. I've never seen
them tackle this story before. I've never seen them come at it from this
angle before where suddenly Master Splinter is in charge of the fucking
Foot Clan and he's trying to make them good guys but you have to wonder if he's
changing the Foot Clan or if the Foot Clan is changing him. You have to wonder
if Master Splinter really knows what he's doing or if he's slowly being
corrupted by his new job. This is so fucking cool. Oh god, it's so awesome!
Like how often do we see like any character development for Master Splinter
at all, right? Like how often does he even factor in as a character? He's usually
just like the wise mentor, but these fucking comics have been so good. Like
Like every character in this series gets fleshed out and has arcs and changes to their personality.
Every character matters.
Everything in this series, oh god it's so good, it's so fucking good, oh god!
So yeah, and there's a part where Leonardo is talking to Master Splinter.
He says, um, look, uh, the other guys are concerned, you know, Leonardo is basically
confronting him about these concerns.
And Master Splinter has this talk with Leonardo and it's so fucking well written where Master
Splinter is justifying his actions to Leonardo and he's kinda right.
Like it's sort of, it makes Leonardo step back and wonder like maybe I was wrong to
confront Master Splinter even though like his gut feeling is telling him that Master
Splinter is making a mistake and you the reader, your gut feeling is that Master Splinter
is being corrupted, but at the same time he's kind of swaying you.
You're like, you know that does kinda make sense because Master Splinter is um, he's
bringing up a scenario from like a little while ago when the turtles went over his head and
didn't involve him in the full extent of their plans and kept him in the dark because they
had a plan to sort of like, you know, re-kajigger the techno-drome without his knowing of it
and he would've disapproved so they went over his head and didn't tell him their full plan
and he's bringing that up and he's like, you know, Leonardo, my son, at the time you
left me out of your plans and you kept me in the dark because you thought I would've
disapproved and you were right, I would've disapproved at the time, but only because
I didn't know what you knew and I would've been wrong so you were right to go over my
head and so now I need you and your brothers to trust me that I know things that you don't
and trust me when I'm leaving you in the dark about the full extent of my plans and trust
that I'm doing the right thing and it's like, you know that using the guy as bait was a
pretty shitty thing to do, but you also, you can't really argue with Master Splinter's
logic there, he's totally right, so Leonardo just kinda shuffles off to his brothers kinda
defeated like, you know, I talked to Master Splinter, I don't know, he kinda has a point
I guess and you're reading it and you're like, yeah, I guess, I fucking shit, so it's so
good, it's presenting this conflict that is so interesting and it's presenting it well,
you know, you could've easily done this badly and had it fall flat and just come off as
try hard and shitty and, but they didn't, it's really well written and it's really great
and so then, so the turtles are going to attack the street phantoms, right, they're going
to rescue their friend Harold and while this is all happening, it's also cutting to Harold,
the scientist tied up to a chair being interrogated by the street phantom guy and Harold's a great
character too, he's like this sardonic, cynical, rude sort of doctor house type character,
like he knows he's a genius and he doesn't have to put up with any shit, he's just some
weak guy in a lab coat, he can't defend himself, but he's tied to a chair being interrogated
and he's just being a huge dick, he's just not cooperating, he's like, shut up, you can't
threaten me, I'm fucking smarter than you, my fucking turtle friends are gonna come over
here and kick your ass, it's great, all the scenes of Harold being interrogated are great
and so then it's the turtles and they're going to, you know, they're gonna break in there
and rescue Harold and all of a sudden they're surrounded by street phantoms, they're surrounded
by all these bad guys and you know, master splinter's there, he's got a couple like foot
clan ninjas as backup so it's, you know, it's the turtles and master splinter and a bunch
of foot clan ninjas like together as a team and they're, but they're surrounded, they're
still outnumbered by these street phantoms, there's too many of them and they're like,
oh god, master splinter, we're surrounded, what do we do, you gotta tell the foot ninjas
to attack, you gotta give them the goat to charge forward and master splinter's like
not yet, wait a minute, we don't need to and then it reveals, it looks up, the fucking
cavalry arrives and who is it, motherfucking Casey Jones, the last page, Casey Jones comes
to back up the turtles but it's not just Casey Jones, oh no, it's Casey Jones and the purple
dragons, in this continuity the purple dragons are like another street gang that like Casey
Jones's father was in control of and they used to be bad guys or whatever and Casey
Jones has been gone for a while but Casey Jones shows up and he's got the fucking purple
dragons behind him like he's taken control of them so it's Casey Jones and it's a whole
army of dudes in hockey masks with purple dragons painted on the hockey masks and so Casey Jones
has created his own Casey Jones purple dragon street gang army of a bunch of dudes in hockey
masks and they're gonna have a huge fucking ninja brawl and it's gonna be the coolest
thing ever and I can't wait and that is my comic of the week, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
number 63, it's fucking cool, it's written by Kevin Eastman, the original creator of
the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, he's still doing it, he's still making comics and he's
making the best comics, the best iteration of the turtles that's ever been made so the
original creator is, you know, still writing for this series and he's still knocking it
out of the park, it's fucking awesome, everybody should read it, everybody should be reading
the new turtles comics, everybody in the world, they're fucking awesome, okay let's see what
came out this week now, we talked about the comics from last week, what came out this
week, I don't actually, I don't really remember what the hell came out this week, a bunch
of bullshit probably, a bunch of stupid bullshit, I don't care about any of it, fuck it, who
cares, this has gone on long enough and that does it for this week's or last week's episode
of this podcast, this comics, that's it, I'll see you next week.
If I remember to do this again, goodbye.