Come on, you fuckers think that just cause a guy reads comics he can't start some shit?
Aw, fucking take all you want!
Goodbye, you're heavy.
Home again, home again.
Give me a try to love!
Class is paying 101.
I guess one person can make a difference.
Alright, welcome everybody to the panel cast, I guess.
This is the first panel cast that I've done in a long time.
I don't know why I haven't done one in a long time.
I don't know why I would do one again.
Fuck comics, I don't care about comics.
I damn sure don't care about my listening audience.
I don't care about The Pro Crastinators fans.
I don't care about a dang old thing.
Joining me once again is the boozy floozy.
Hi.
She's here to talk to you.
She knows about comics too, and so do I.
I know the most about comics.
We know the best comics.
We play the best comics, and we're the best at them.
We read the best comics, and we're the best at talking about them.
And this is the panel cast, and this is the comics that were this week.
What are we...
Well, we didn't really read anything.
I haven't read a comic in two years.
I haven't read a comic in nine on to seventeen years!
Ever since your older brother was born and done,
sent our family spiraling into poverty.
You little shit.
Let's talk about the uncanny Avengers.
Number 18.
What do you think about this comic that you didn't read?
It was good.
It was a good comic.
You kind of read it over my shoulder.
Yeah, I did.
I'm gonna be perfectly honest.
I'm out of the loop.
The last thing that I remember hearing anything about Red Skull
and Xavier is that Red Skull apparently ate Professor X's brain or some garbage.
Yeah, that happened about three years ago or some shit.
And it's just been this long dragged out storyline of the Red Skull
has all of Xavier's psychic powers now.
And they're trying to find him and kill him and get him.
It's Rogue, and it's Deadpool, and Cable,
and it's the Quicksilver is on the team,
and the Wasp is on the team.
That's actually a really good team.
Yeah, it's a pretty good book.
And Captain America was in charge of them,
but he got mad at them and he fired them all.
So now Rogue's gone rogue.
That's like a gamer's tavern joke.
Wow.
Yeah, I guess Rogue is gone rogue.
But now they're not officially sanctioned anymore.
They don't have Captain America's blessing anymore.
It's just a team of fucking pissed off people
who don't give a shit.
They just want to kill the Red Skull.
That's their only mission.
Deadpool and...
Which Captain America?
The real Captain America, the only real Captain America,
the white one.
Not Black in America, not that one.
No, not, not, not fucking, not Jonestown, USA.
Not, uh, welcome to Booferville, population one.
Not, not welcome to the jungle.
We got funny games.
Not, uh, not, not, uh, not Jigaboo of the jungle.
Stop.
Watch out for that tree.
With the help of his friend, an ape named Ape.
Okay, so this is a comic about Black people, I guess.
That's what we were talking about, right?
We were talking about how the Blacks came to America.
The Blacks came to America and they ate Professor Xavier's brain with...
Is that the little mermaid I'm hearing?
Interrupting my hilarious anecdote?
Turn that shit off!
What is happening?
My shitty Let's Plays are playing in the background of my shitty podcast
and it's ruining both of them!
As I was saying, this is a comic about how the first Blacks came to America
and ate Charles Xavier's brain at Thanksgiving dinner with the pilgrims
and then slaughtered all the Indians.
You know, those Blacks, they don't know about their Black privilege
that they got from scalping all those Indians.
The Blacks invented scalping.
Scalping tickets.
I'll have to take your word for it.
History was never my strength in school.
Did you major in herstory?
Because you're such a vagethumping feminist?
What?
You know, there's Bible thumpers and then there's vagethumpers.
Is this because of my sandwich comment earlier?
Yeah.
Are you fucking serious?
This guy, I swear...
What the fuck?
The only thing that's gonna be thumping that vag is the strong right hand of D. Trump's America.
Boy, don't I know it.
Doesn't that happen in January?
Oh boy.
Shit.
Donald Trump isn't even funny to me anymore.
I don't care about anything.
Nothing's funny anymore.
I'm a comic book boy.
Welcome.
So in this comic on the cover, it's got a picture.
And inside the comic, there's more pictures.
And some of the pictures have little word balloons.
It starts with a flashback of Rogue.
But it's a dream she's having.
It's a scary nightmare.
And then she goes...
The Red Skull, he's got brain stuff.
He fucks with Quicksilver.
And she goes to beat him up.
She goes, I'm gonna kill him.
And she goes and gets him, but it's all a trick.
And at the end of the comic, she pulls a fast one.
He pulls a fast one on her.
And so now she's hypnotized, too.
And so this storyline, this storyline is just,
it keeps chugging along.
It'll never end.
They'll never kill the Red Skull.
Yeah, that's...
Like why?
Why even try?
Like why even have the storyline?
Why even start a storyline of like,
we're gonna kill one of these big villains
when you know that they're never gonna kill any of the big villains?
Well, nobody thought that they'd kill Wolverine,
but look at that.
I mean, that's kind of why characters like The Punisher
don't really work in comics as much.
I mean, The Punisher works on his own,
but like when you add in like,
like when you start thinking like,
okay, why is the Kingpin still alive?
And Kingpin's getting his own comic.
Yeah, it's just like, you know,
if you're not gonna have the balls to kill off these bad guys,
then I guess fuck everything.
It's all worthless.
Well, I mean, didn't technically he kill Kingpin
and Punisher Max,
but the Punisher Max series is his own entire different universe.
Not even in the canon.
It's a different...
It's a different universe.
Well, anyways, that was Uncanny Avengers,
and it sure was a comic.
What's the next comic?
What, how do I...
What the hell is this?
I don't know.
What is this website?
I don't know what else you read.
I mean, what is this stack of comics
that I purchased legally at a comic book store?
Ooh.
I like, I like some of these comic books.
Which ones?
I like comic books.
Okay, here's Rocket Raccoon number one.
Yeah.
And he's a little raccoon boy.
Oh, he looks sad.
He's stranded on Earth because the Civil War II,
their spaceship got blown up.
So all the Guardians are having their own solo adventures.
They're all stranded on Earth or some shit.
Yeah.
He's eating a pretzel out of the garbage can.
And he fucking hates Earth.
He doesn't like Earth because he's a raccoon boy.
He's scratching a man.
He's killing him.
Good.
He's pissed off.
And then he goes, oh man, this is a really shitty episode
of the panel cast.
This is a real clusterfuck.
This is a train wreck.
But anyways, that's Rocket Raccoon number one.
And he's, you know, he's, I guess the human torches in this.
Johnny's, oh, I clicked on the wrong thing.
And I, oh boy.
Oh boy.
What is happening here?
But anyways, you know, let's just go to the last page
and see how this story resolves itself.
Dog butt.
Let's see.
What's the, I guess it would be page 22 here.
Let's see what happens, Cyril.
Um.
I don't know what that is.
Yeah.
I don't know what the hell that is.
But you know, so he's got a comic.
So that's, that's something.
I don't even know what, what came out anymore.
Oh, Spider-Man.
The more of this.
Nope.
That's not the Spider-Man I was thinking of.
Black Spider-Man.
I know.
Miles Morales.
I like Miles.
Niles the Niglet.
Oh my God.
I clicked on it thinking that there was a new Spider-Man,
but it was the wrong Spider-Man.
It was a little black baby.
I thought we didn't care about Spider-Man anymore.
Hey, did you read the new Venom yet?
I thought you were going to say,
I thought we didn't care about race anymore.
I thought, did you read the new Venom?
At all?
The new Venom.
Yeah.
There was an issue, like there are only up to two issues now,
but it was actually really good.
There's a new host for the symbiote now,
and it kind of seems like they're going the ghost wrap-wrap.
How many new hosts does there have to be for?
There's only been like three.
Well, maybe there's been more.
There was Eddie Brock and there was Flash Thompson
and there was probably 10 other guys.
No, there's a Scorpion,
but we don't talk about that.
Oh yeah, Max Gargleballs.
Don't fucking talk about it.
Max Gargleballs.
I like that.
Yeah, I actually really like the new Venom comic.
They are going back to the roots of the symbiote
working for evil again, I guess, basically.
And they're kind of taking a...
For those of you who have been reading the Old New Ghost Rider,
they're kind of taking that route, the symbiote, now.
I don't want to give away too much.
I don't want to spoil too much, but...
I don't know.
There are only up to two issues,
and I've really liked both of them so far.
I can't stop farting.
Oh yeah, this guy.
This guy.
Did you...?
No!
Did it squeak?
I'm shitting my pants!
So there's All Star Batman number five.
I think this is the last one of this arc.
Yeah.
It's by Scott Snyder.
Scott Snyder, who is a wonderful writer,
but goddamn it, I don't fucking like the art.
I don't know.
I don't know if I'd go that far.
He's a good writer?
I...
What don't you like of Scott Snyder's?
All of it.
All of it, really?
I hate the...
Everything he does is just a hackier,
lame-er version of what Grant Morrison did.
The Court of Owls is just a lame-er, black glove.
His Joker is just like a homo, a gay.
He wants to suck Batman's dick like blatantly.
He ruined the fucking Joker.
By making him gay, it is homophobic.
And I don't care.
It's gay!
He writes his little Batman comics,
and he draws a little word balloon.
He draws a Joker.
He says, hey Joker, say something gay.
Then he writes in the little word balloon,
I'm gay!
I just like to imagine that all of Joker's
word bubbles are shaped like wieners.
And they're like, you gotta stop doing that.
Yeah, I hated all of his Joker stories.
You know, I don't really remember the Joker stories very well.
I just remember them being really fucking gross.
Actually, that's a lie, because I liked Endgame.
See, I thought that one was kind of anti-climax.
So of his two Joker stories, I hated one of them.
I liked his Bloom story.
Well, yeah, that was an interesting character.
I liked Bloom.
But I hated the whole Gordon Batman thing.
We're just talking amongst ourselves now with no context
for anyone who didn't know how to even give a shit.
But anyways, this is All Star Batman.
This is his new thing.
And, you know, it was a cool story.
Some shit about Two-Face, you know?
I feel like this comic took a while to come out.
So by the time you get to the end of the story,
you don't remember what the beginning of the story was.
Two-Face put a head out on Batman.
Yeah, basically. There's more to it than that.
But, you know, it's, you know...
Tweedledee and Tweedledum, what the fuck?
But anyways, at the end of the story, you know,
basically, Two-Face has this cure, this little thing.
And it's gonna either make him all Harvey or all Two-Face.
You know, whichever side of his personality is the strongest,
that side is gonna take over.
But at the end of it, Batman says,
fuck you, and he breaks the cure,
because he says that, you know,
everybody in the world has to make the choice every day
which side is stronger.
So I'm not gonna give you the easy way out,
you little punk-ass bitch.
That's fine. No, I don't like that.
You don't like that?
I don't like that.
Well, Batman explains it better than I do.
I explained it bad.
That's fair.
But, um, anyways, you know,
that's Batman for ya.
That was a good story, I think.
I don't remember it with perfect clarity,
but you know, you know, video games,
I mean comics, this is comics.
Oh yeah, The Dark Knight 3, Master Race number seven.
That only took a million years to finally come out.
Yeah, so I didn't actually read this issue.
I skimmed it, but it looks cool.
I've been reading up to this point,
but I've been so I don't really give a shit.
I don't really give a shit.
So I've been reading comics sometimes,
and when I was a little boy,
and I'm a comic.
And so in this comic,
so this is the third in The Dark Knight trilogy
of, you know, the Frank Miller man.
Frank Miller is, you know,
I guess you'd call him one of the seminal
comic book boys
of the 80s.
It was like him and Alan Moore and Grant Morrison.
They all made comics cool.
Some kind of triad, I guess.
Yeah.
Wouldn't Warren Ellis be in there somewhere?
Wouldn't Warren Ellis and fuckin'
Bill Gaiman and all of them.
All the old boys.
But, um, yeah.
You know, Frank Miller, he was a great writer.
He's one of the best of all time.
You know, a lot of Frank Miller stories
are my favorite stories of all comics, you know?
Yeah, Daredevil born again is fantastic.
His Wolverine,
which he didn't write, he just drew it.
Claremont wrote it, but, you know,
the original Wolverine was great.
And The Dark Knight Returns is still a great story.
It still holds up.
It's a great version with fucking
RoboCop
as Batman, which was the coolest thing
Peter Welling.
And it was amazing.
It was the coolest thing of all time.
But that's a good story.
So everyone really loved him.
He was one of the most famous comic book writers.
He was very critically acclaimed.
His stories are, you know, among the most influential
and widely adapted.
If you've seen Batman v Superman,
you've basically seen,
you know, it's
it's Batman v Superman
is just a bastardized, crappier version
of everything that Frank Miller ever wrote.
Yeah.
But, um,
he sort of stopped being
so critically acclaimed at a certain point
and everyone kind of turned on him.
And they started saying, you know,
he's gone crazy. He's racist.
He hates Islam. He's a misogynist.
He's a misogynist. He's, you know, the whole thing.
So people stopped liking him
and they, you know, his
his stories started getting
worse, I guess.
His art got a lot more stylized.
I don't
really care that much for Miller's art style.
Well, people have always said that his art
has gotten worse
and they're right
looking at it.
I was going to defend him, but then like
I'm looking at it right now and I'm like, yeah.
I've never been like a big fan
of Miller's artwork and I've never really been
of a John Romita Junior's artwork.
At least not any of the more recent
I like John Romita Junior's art style.
I don't like John Romita Junior's more recent art style.
He had a different art style
like when he first started and then it
progressively started changing and now they're all sausage fingers.
Well, that's how you, that's sort of how it is
with Frank Miller's art. Like you can tell that it's still
his style, but like he's just
it's evolved in such a way that like
it's gotten more and more stylized
and cartoony to the point where it's,
you know, the anatomy is very
weird and a lot of people hate it
and I hate it.
But um, yeah, it's not so bad.
But anyways, you know, so
he wrote The Dark Knight Returns a million years ago
in the 80s. It's a story about
old-ass Batman.
He's old and he's retired. He's
bitter. He comes back
to kick more ass for one last hurrah.
Then like, you know,
years later and like the
year 2000 or something, he wrote The Dark Knight
Strikes Again, which was like the second of that
series. And in that series,
everyone hated it. It was
poopy. Um, I have it.
I've never actually read the second one because
everyone's told me it's bad, but I know what happens
in it. It's, it turns out that like
like Dick Grayson
turned into like a spooky
bad guy man and nobody liked it.
But anyways, the point is nobody liked the
second one and nobody likes Frank Miller anymore.
So, but he's come back to do The Dark Knight 3 now
the, the, the third
in his trilogy, I guess, of this
saga that he started way back in the 80s.
Which honestly has sold like exceptionally
well, but I, but
it's had some issues with
you know, being churned out on time.
The last issue
I remember specifically it getting canceled
for resuscitation at a later date
when I was dealing with it
at least twice, I think.
And you know, that always kind of puts
a wrench in things, honestly.
Well, yeah.
The big question going into this
from everyone is that like
does Frank Miller still have it? Can he still
tell a good Batman story? Because
you know, everybody hates him
now. He's, he's not, he doesn't
have the same, his name doesn't carry the same
weight as it once did because
so much of his recent stuff has been so critically
panned like his All-Star Batman and Robin
from a couple years back.
I remember that. Which is basically a meme
because it's so
weirdly aggressive and cynical and
out of character. Like out of
character, even for Batman, it's
like way too cynical. It reads more like
Rorschach as Batman
and it's a really
weird, like hilariously
bad comic. It was so bad
that like
when the first few issues
of All-Star Batman and Robin came out, everybody
hated it so much and said it was so terrible
that like by the
fifth issue, Frank Miller had to go
oh, no, it's
it's a parody, it's campy.
Like he had to like go, he had to back
pedal and play that card. So then like from
issue five on, he tries to
make it even more extreme to make it seem
like he was trying to make a parody of Batman
from the get go, but he's not fooling anyone
so it just gets weirder and dumber and weirder
and crappier.
But it was not meant to be a parody.
That's bullshit.
He screwed the pooch on that one big
time and everyone hated it
and nobody likes him anymore
as a writer. But
he's gone back to the
storyline that made him famous in the first
place and
I've really liked this so far
The Dark Knight 3. Have you been reading it?
Yeah, and
my customers have really enjoyed it too.
I have some really avid
fans of this particular comic
primarily because they really enjoyed like the first Dark Knight.
But much like you said
earlier, a lot of people didn't seem to enjoy
the second one very much.
I think everyone's just kind of patiently waiting
to see how this one concludes.
I've yet to have anybody actually like go out of the way
to cancel it or anything.
Nobody has actually said anything like
you know, oh well I don't like where this is going, just take it off my sub.
So
I...
Was it only supposed to be a seven part series? I can't remember.
Is it eight parts?
Seven's a weird number to me. This one definitely ends
on a there's gonna be at least one more
part. Okay, so it's an eight part series.
Okay.
Yeah, no
I think it's good but
you're also talking to somebody who
doesn't really, I'm not
really that big of a Frank Miller fan.
Really? I, you know, a lot of people are
always like the Dark Knight is one of the best stories of all time
but you know, anytime I go back and I talk to people
about my favorite Batman stories
the Dark Knight's never there.
I don't know
if I'd call it like one of my favorite
Batman stories of all time
but I mean everything in it
is clearly important
to like the pop culture
mythos of the characters. And you're right
about that. There's a lot of people that really like
the Robin that's in that particular Dark Knight
even though I don't like
Carrie that much. I have
conflicted feelings about her. It seems like she was never really
trained at all at any point.
She was, even in the movie, she just kind of
puts on the outfit. Like she just shows up and she's Robin.
Yeah, and like even in the
movie at the end when she's like running up next
to Batman's tank, she's just like, she's there for
moral support but she's wearing the costume. I don't
know.
But I did, I have an appreciation
for the whole like Batman vs Superman
thing in the Dark Knight. I thought that was
really good. Yeah.
But it's like you said
BVS basically bastardized that.
Yeah.
The great thing about the Dark Knight 3
is that it really seems like it's
coming from like a place of catharsis
from Frank Miller. Like it seems like it's
a little bit more optimistic
in tone than some of his other
stuff because he garnered such a
reputation for cynicism
and like a lot of his philosophies
about Batman and superheroes in general, I
disagree with too because he always
talks trash about
Batman shouldn't have a Robin
that's gay and that's kid stuff and Batman
and when superheroes
Superman shouldn't
be dating Lois Lane. He should be dating Wonder Woman
because they're both strong and they can have sex
through a mountain.
And there's even like an entire series
about Superman and Wonder Woman being together
and breaking up.
If you really want to get into
the philosophy or the mind of
Frank Miller and how he feels about superheroes
and things like that, I feel like Sin City is
probably one of those books that you need to read
even though I didn't care that much for Sin City.
I've always
gravitated more towards
like a Grant Morrison
sort of philosophy. Like the stuff that he says
in interviews and stuff. When you understand him.
I always feel like yeah, this guy really gets it.
Like
because like
because Grant Morrison's whole thing is that
he has zero cynicism about superheroes whatsoever.
Like he goes into every book like
well yeah, of course Batman
would have a Robin. Of course he would have a best friend
who's 12 years old. Why wouldn't you
if you were a billionaire and they've got a billion dollars? Why wouldn't you fight
crime with a little boy?
He's your best friend.
Like he's always talks like he loves everything about
superheroes and like he goes into every
comic like wanting to talk about like
he wants to incorporate like the entire
mythos and like the whole continuity
of like 70 years of Batman into it.
Grant Morrison's my favorite. He's a good old
puppy dog boy is what he is.
Did Grant Morrison do the black mirror?
I don't know. I don't remember.
I just remember the black mirror being like one of my favorite titles.
Um, but yeah
going on. Yeah, Grant Morrison's great.
Yeah, but and so I guess
they're sort of opposites because Frank Miller has always been
more cynical it seems like. But in this
in The Dark Knight 3 he seems like he's
he's writing it from a place of like
wanting to be more optimistic again because
the whole story of this one is that
um, you know
Batman and Superman are working together again
and they're really kicking ass and
and coming together and saving the day there's
there's this like religious sect of
assholes inside the bottled city of
Kandor who breaks out who they're all
Kryptonian so they're all strong and Superman
so they break out and start raking havoc and trying
to destroy the world and Batman says
you know I'm a hundred and seven thousand
years old but I ain't gonna stand for this
he walks his rickety ass up a mountain
and he he he goes to like the fortress
of solitude and he and he thaws
Superman out of his block of ice because
Superman he's just been hanging out in a block
of ice like he doesn't give a shit anymore
and he goes to the block of ice says hey hey Kent
get your ass out of that ice
we gotta beat people up and Superman
he hears them and he's like what we gotta beat
people up yeah
and then Superman and they just they just
beat people up and there's this great scene
where like you know they're fighting
all these Kryptonians so Batman he
arranges to have it like he does some
shit and it's like raining Kryptonite
rain and it's weakening all the Kryptonians
but then they're still beating them up
because there's so many of them or whatever but then
Superman shows up and he's so
so like the the Batman armor
from like the first book
where Batman wore that like super powerful
armor to fight Superman it's in Batman
v Superman the movie the same armor yeah
they he did he does like a call back to this
where because it's raining Kryptonite
Superman gets in like
his own Batman armor to help
beat up the Kryptonians
and just punching them with his fists
and stuff it's super cool it's the best
it's my favorite comic everyone
I think this is a good one
yeah and then the
and then the the latest issue there's
this great scene this shit yeah
yeah we're looking at the scene right now
I'm sure Jesse will put it up on the
spoilers I guess but yeah
yeah but it's
it's just this great moment that
Bruce and Kent both share together
towards the end of the other latest issue
but yeah um
I will say one thing about Frank Miller's artwork
like I know I already said that I don't really like
it I'm really
emphasizing that with the way that he draws Wonder Woman
oh god
it she's
there's that vagethumping feminist coming out of
you again no it's not feminist
I actually agree
I don't like
I'm gonna get reamed for it
I just fucking know it but
she's just so aesthetically unappealing
to me drawn this way
yeah he's she's really weird looking in this
in his style
he kind of draws her like
like a spooky person
yeah I mean she's got that like spooky
bulky yeah
like fucking
she looks like she's like
she looks like she needs to be wearing pants
she's like a fat soccer mom on steroids
in a bikini that's like 10 sizes
too small for her
she's like the soccer mom from the earlier seasons
a family guy remember
he punches
this guy that he assumes is a man
and then everybody starts screaming
he's like oh my wife
and then he's like what you mean
your husband and then you start hearing
like crying he's like yeah
she wanted to labor she had a baby
that's kind of what
that's kind of what it reminds me
of the way that she's drawn
it's just it's really not
it's not good looking I'm sorry
it's shallow but I don't care
I don't like it hey man there's nothing worse
than a woman who ain't pretty
yeah I go
that's your best quality you know
that your hashtag not fat oh my god
Civil War 2 came out
the last one of that finally that's over
okay so once again
with Civil War
they announced that this was only going to be like a 7 part
series
and before this they did the same thing with Secret Wars
but then all of a sudden they were like
we liked this so much
that we're gonna tag on an extra
issue that's gonna take forever
to fucking release
and you know Civil War 2
when it first released like it
I was into it
I may not have been as into it as I was
in the original Civil War
in fact I feel like the only reason why they even came out with Civil War 2
is because of the fucking movie
but
but it's taken so long
for them to actually conclude
this fucking storyline that I just
I've stopped caring
I really have
you know especially since like previous already
came out with stuff saying you know
here's our next storyline here's
Monsters Unleashed about to happen
it's gotten to the point where the events
are so bloated and so long
that the next ones are already coming out
by the time they're even over it
yeah they did that with Infamous Iron Man
like I remember a ton of people going
wow spoilers much
for Civil War when Infamous Iron Man 1 came out
like Avengers
or X-Men vs. Inhumans is already coming out
and this one has been
so that's the next event and it's already done
it's already done
I think IVX is already done
well
I've already ranted about Civil War 2
so I think AVX only had like
issue number one is out
no IVX
IVX definitely has two issues
same thing it's the same shit
you're kind of right
wait no no no I'm thinking of
no it's not IVX
I'm thinking of there was another one before
where it's all about it's like a four part series
it was all about like
I guess the X-Men getting wiped out or something
I already forgot
I don't know what I'm talking about
is that Harley Quinn I see
yeah I guess this came out too
Harley Quinn's Little Black Book
issue number five didn't the first issue come out last year
Harley Quinn has like 10 different series
I don't even know what I'm looking at here
but the cover is clearly
it's a nod to the old Muhammad Ali vs. Superman cover
Ben she's in a skimpy little thing
hey look it's Obama
I hear Obama you're not
you're not relevant anymore you're just another black nigger
Obama
welcome to
panel cast the most racist podcast
on the internet it's supposed to be a
family friendly comic book show
and it's just an excuse for me to say the N word
50 times every week
Obama
so I didn't read this comic
I don't think I need to read it to know that it's
garbage oh yeah we have
we both have
an issue with current quality
Harley Quinn comic books
I have a lot that I could say about how much
she's designed alone this is like wait
what is that
wait a minute
I don't even think this is a recent comic
I think someone just uploaded this
because this is
maybe no it says February yeah
February 2016 well that's number one
yeah maybe it is a recent comic
no number one was I mean she's
because in this she still looks like she has her
this is still her new 52 design
but they've since redesigned her again and she looks
a little bit better now but still shit
she's a pre-designer to make her look more like the
Suicide Squad version from the movies which
but she still has the
crappy bleached skin
look at the wall eyed
who hired this artist
I don't like it
the black and red thing is terrible too
I mean the hair
okay so
again this is
another thing that I'm probably gonna get reamed for
because everybody loves Harley Quinn
is like one of the most subscribed comic books
that I know of that DC has released
it is the Deadpool of the DC
universe everybody wants
every single Harley Quinn fucking anything
when it comes out Harley Quinn
and Poison Ivy Harley Quinn and Power
Girl Harley Quinn
her little black fucking book
god what else Harley Quinn's little gang
or whatever you know there's so much
fucking Harley Quinn the gang of Harleys
actually I don't think there was a Harley Quinn and Poison Ivy
the gang of Harleys which is basically Deadpool
and the Mercs for money
yeah again this Harley Quinn is
DC's answer to Deadpool
for Marvel like I just
which is
she shouldn't be because that's not
what the character is
okay so Bruce Tim was the one who created
Paul Dini created her
but Bruce Tim was the one who designed
her character I think
or at least he drew her
I think he finalized the design
if I remember right I think Paul Dini
Paul Dini to this day is still
the only person who
writes her correctly
like the only time I enjoy
every time I read a Harley Quinn comic
if I enjoy it without
fail I'll go I know who wrote this
Paul Dini and I'll look at it and then sure enough
because he's the only one who gets her because he created her
I think for the past two years
the person who's been writing for her
um it's been a mannequin
or somebody else and you know I get
that a lot that look you just gave me
I get that look a lot when I say that
you know oh well Amanda Connor is going to be
writing this comic
and you always see the same look from everybody
they're just like oh
she's writing for something
not drawing it
well that wasn't why I gave that look I gave that look because of course it would be a woman
ruining Harley Quinn
well fair enough
of course it would be some wannabe
empowered fucking Tumblrina
who
God
they don't want to acknowledge
what makes the character special because they think
it's like derogatory now
DC
either they don't want to acknowledge it
or they just don't get it DC doesn't
understand why people
love Harley Quinn they don't understand
why this character who
was created 20 years ago
is as popular and as important
to the cultural zeitgeist as
Spider-Man and Superman and Batman who were all created
70 years ago they don't want to
acknowledge the reason why so many
women relate to this character
why so many men can relate to her
why there's so much cosplay of her
why everyone loves this character
so much it's not because she's a
wacky zany deadpool knockoff
it's not because she's an amoral killer
who goes around and commits crimes
and stuff it's not because she's a free spirit
or an empowered you know take no
shit does whatever she wants
badass suicide girl
people love Harley Quinn because she's
a sad damaged human
character she's relatable
the whole the entire basis of the character
is that she fell in love with
the wrong person and she knows it
but it's ruined her fucking life
and everyone's been there that's
why the character became so popular
in the first place she's not insane
she's she's not a wacky
crazy person like the Joker the only reason
that she's acts like that is because she's dating
the Joker she has moments
anything from the old animated series
that you watch anything that Paul Dini has ever written
you can see she'll always
the thing that humanizes the character is these
little moments where like the Joker kicks
her out on her ass and she sits there in like an alley
and she goes how did how did it get
to this how did my life become
this you know she she
she's intelligent enough
to understand how weak she is
and how flawed she is and how fucked up
how badly she screwed up her own life
she's smart enough to realize it but she's
not quite strong enough
to change things and that's what people
relate to because everyone in the world
is this you know everyone relates
to spider-man because everyone has guilt
everyone relates to Superman
because everyone feels like they don't belong
sometimes everyone fucking
relates to Batman because everyone
their parents got shot
watching Zorro that happened to everyone
in the world all of these characters
everyone relates to Bruce Banner because
everyone has a side of themselves they don't like
everyone loses their temper or like
you know everyone can see these flaws in themselves
and that's what people love about Harley Quinn
she's a flawed fucking person
she doesn't have to be
an empowered
wacky Deadpool knockoff going on
these crazy mercenary adventures every week
she just has to be a person
trying to be better than she is
and I don't really touch upon that anymore
like any of the Suicide Squad
comics even the movie
it's just Mr. J
and I'm crazy
and he he I'm cute
but I'm kind of ballistic
am I gonna kiss you?
am I gonna cut you? you never know
it's just terrible
it's accurate and it's terrible
like it and you know
it's so devastating to me because I really
I really enjoyed the character back then
and you know if everyone does
she's a great character
she's a character that didn't exist
before in comics like that specific
moral struggle
yeah I know like that specific
moral struggle that defines her
of just being in love
with the wrong person
everyone ever has been there
everyone has felt that pain and everyone has gone
fucking insane from it
her whole origin
is just that love can make you crazy
not that she's crazy and so she fell in love
that's the misunderstanding
that I think is the basis of all these
crappy new comics
it's just
incredibly frustrating that none of these writers seem to get her
or that they don't want to acknowledge
I think they don't want to acknowledge it
because people have it in their heads now
that it's like somehow derogatory
to women
to acknowledge the fact
that the basis of this character is that
she's weak
but it's not derogatory to constantly throw her
into that situation time and time again
she's weak and she's in love
she's a hopeless romantic
and she's
and she's abused
and no one wants to
it seems like they're trying to move away from that
because
it's not a good role model anymore
well
as if her being like an insane psychopath
serial killer is any better of a role model
right and you know actually
it's a funny line that people
ride upon when it comes to Harley Quinn
so if you haven't seen the new
Suicide Squad movie or any of the
interviews with Margo
Robbie whatever
you know she explicitly says that
that she really wished they had touched upon
the whole
the actual abuse because so far it's only been
glorified
that movie Suicide Squad
was weirdly romantic
like
they seem to really love each other
in that movie
he loved her a lot
he was obsessed with getting back to her the whole movie
which isn't really that much like the Joker
I guess
I haven't seen the Suicide Squad movie
if you didn't know
well the whole Suicide Squad movie is that
the Joker is so
in love with Harley Quinn
that he's on a rampage trying to get back to her
and he's like
there's this scene where
he is so broken up
about Harley
not being there that he goes in this room
with all these knives and he lays on the floor and cries
like a fucking like a 14 year old emo kid
he's crying over not having
his boo with him
the whole Suicide Squad movie
is about the Joker
he just wants his girlfriend back because he's
really in love with her
that's not very characteristic
of him
this is coming from the character
who has actively
gone against Harley Quinn because
she went out of her way to try and do something
to appeal to him
to please him such as kidnapping Batman
and trying to
you know kill him in a way that would be funny
to both her and the Joker
but you know he
fucking gets angry at her for it
he's like you know how dare you do this
and throws it out a fucking window for it
this is coming from that relationship
this is coming from the relationship where he's like time and time again
like trying to kill her over and over
what the fuck
are you serious at Suicide Squad
I'm not
as against the
Jared Leto Joker as everyone else is
I know it looks fucking retarded
but to me
I think a big aspect of the character
the Joker specifically
what makes the Joker such a good character
is that he is inherently
open to interpretation
like I don't think there can really be a wrong Joker
that Young Justice episode was pretty bad
Young Justice
episode is it the
oddly young looking Joker
he looked like David Tennant
yeah oh god he did
don't do this to me
so there can be a wrong Joker
nevermind forget what I just said
anyway
so rewinding back to the whole
abusive situation that Harley Quinn has been in
so there's been tons and tons and tons of stuff
that's touched upon that have you ever read Gotham City Sirens
that was another
mini series
I say mini series kind of loosely because it was like two volumes long
but that was
two volumes long I guess now
nevermind
anyway
wasn't that ongoing of a series
but they touched upon Harley Quinn trying to
overcome what she dealt with the trauma
of being in a relationship with Joker
and Poison Ivy and Catwoman both trying to
support her through it
and injustice even though that's not in the same universe
they touch upon that a lot
in fact I remember there was a scene
specific to Harley Quinn
god he's like one of my favorite characters
starts with an L
he comes from outer space he kicked the shit out of Superman
Lobo, thank you
god I don't know why that left my brain for a second
he's one of my favorite characters
the original not
the new 52 redesign
I don't want to talk about that
but there's a scene
an injustice where Lobo like backhands Harley Quinn
if I remember right
and you know she like spits for a second
and like looks at him and says you know
if there's anything that she's learned
and like her long line of being Harley Quinn
is that she's never gonna take shit from anybody
ever again and of course she's specifically
talking about Joker
I actually really like the injustice comics
I think that's
I swing between liking it and hating it honestly
to me the injustice comics for being like
an else worlds
the characters in that still seem like more
in character than in most mainline DC
publications
they've definitely gone some dark routes with that one
but yeah Harley Quinn
specifically says you know she's been abused long enough
she's never gonna accept this again
and I guess she ends up throwing Lobo out the window
or something something absurd for like
Harley Quinn level strength considering Lobo
is who he is well Harley Quinn
is super strong or she was
before the new 52 I don't know if they changed it
well Harley Quinn but there was a long time where like
Poison Ivy had given her a serum
that gave her like Captain America
ooh I remember that
oh god you know
I think they only remember that when it's
convenient to the plot but that was a thing
you're not wrong probably
but um
yeah the thing about
like to me the core of the character of Harley Quinn
and
remember I'm right
so objectively the core of the character
is
just that
she's a good person who surrounds herself with bad people
bad influences toxic influences
if not for
you know she could be
she could be a force for good in the world
if not for the fact that
her boyfriend is a bad guy
her best friend is a bad guy Poison Ivy
her boyfriend
the Joker is you know a mass murdering
psychotic terrorist
her best friend Poison Ivy is
a man-hating eco-terrorist
you know
even Catwoman is a fucking burglar
and not that there's anything wrong with burglaring
well she's what they would call it
anti-hero I guess
but um that's like the core of the character
like everybody has someone like that in their lives
everybody knows someone who you know
is better than the people they surround themselves with
who has bad influences
and does dumb shit and gets
becomes a burden on everyone they love
you know she's just
so much about the way
the character was originally written and originally conceived
is so human and so relatable
and that's why she took off
she just like skyrocketed immediately
she's only existed for 20 years
and she's like one of the pillars of comic book media
and that's why
one of my favorite episodes
revolving around Harley Quinn
was like the one I think where
where it's just Batman and Harley
like I don't know if you remember that from the animated series
but I really liked that episode
the one where she kisses him at the end is
you're not a bad guy B-man
there's so much that
I think that episode is actually in the opening
of the panel cast it's when
home again home again
yeah no
yeah
Harley Quinn is just it's
it's complicated like I understand that
you know DC has to
have an answer to Marvel regardless
and they have to have some kind of balance
to the dark and grittiness that is
DC comic books because if you look at Rebirth
and you look at New 52
it's prominently like dark it's dark
it's scary it's violent
and then you have Harley Quinn
who yes it's still violent but
they have all this bubbly
wacky shit going on
it's just
yeah and like they
she has too much of a sense of humor
she's too wacky
she never takes anything seriously
even Deadpool has
his moments where he like steps back
Deadpool is a more serious character than modern Harley
holy shit the
the issue of Deadpool
Deadpool comics the one of the more
recent issues of Deadpool is where he is
trying to help out this girl who
he finds on top of a on top of the
Spider-Man's fucking I talked about that
in the panel cast that's right
that was a really great
did you yeah there was a there was
that whole arc from Brian Postsein where
Deadpool and Captain America
and Wolverine went to go fight some weapon
ex-bad guys and he was looking for like his old
girlfriend yeah was pregnant with his
daughter or whatever and you know
Deadpool finds this like mass grave of bodies
and in the mass grave he finds his old girlfriend
and
it's like a really sad he's like crying
and like yelling and Captain America is like
nooo
Deadpool has had some very intense moments like you know
yeah it's like they're trying to make her Deadpool
but they're also making her a worse Deadpool
because she doesn't have the
they're not giving her any of that pathos
they're not giving back the depth that she used to have
Deadpool still has depth and you know
I still get upset when people will be like
oh another Deadpool coming he's just another
wacky zany piece of shit and it's like
like it's not the characters fault
it's really not
and you know I guess you could say the same for Harley
it's not really her fault she is totally
marketable sex sells
even the Deadpool movie you know had
it had a core to it it had like an emotional
core there was none of that in the Suicide Squad
movie and well if in all fairness
Ryan Reynolds really has like a passion
when it comes to comic books and I know
that I know a lot of people will like look at the Green Lantern
movie and be like are you sure about that
statement it's like but that's not really his fault
he did not have he did not have
a great hand in the Green Lantern like he did
in Deadpool but anyway
it's just sad to me that they've you know
they've taken this character who had
so much depth to her and was such an interesting
character that you could write stories about
forever and
due to you know
marketing or misunderstanding or whatever they've
devolved her into this like
warped perversion this parody
of what the character once was
of just like
I'm gonna kill everybody
and I have a talking squirrel
for my best friend and
there's poison ivy and we're just
lesbians now we're just lesbians
I don't you know
it doesn't bother me and she's a wacky
crazy person and that's another
thing like the constant like the
the masturbatory I'm so
crazy shit
it's so it's so annoying
because she's not crazy
you can't hold me against what I do
because I'm a little
crazy
I'm a little loony toon girl
it's shit
she's not supposed to be
crazy she's just
dependent and she's
she's a thrill seeker I guess but she's not
psychotic like they had
an episode in the animated series a whole
episode written by Paul Dini we're like
at the beginning of the episode
she passes a test
and she's certified sane and she's
released from Arkham yeah and the whole
reason the only reason she ends up back
in Arkham at the end is because
she can't acclimate
to being free again to society's rules
again because she's been in this fucked
up lifestyle for so long it's
kind of like a commentary on like people
getting released from jail and stuff and
going right back because they can't acclimate
to society anymore right but
you know that's how
the creator of the character always wrote her
she's completely sane
she's just retarded
you know
it's one way to put it
she's just a flawed human being
and she's interesting and I know what
I know like the comeback to everything
I'm going to say is
well why can't the character evolve
why can't there be character development
why can't she move on from the Joker
money money money
I'm my opinion
it's marketability
I'm not saying that the character can't evolve
I'm all for character development
I've made many videos about how much
I love character development in all media
but that's no excuse
character development has to be natural
and logical you can't just
rewrite everything about a character
and like try to fit a square peg into
a round hole and that's what they're doing
with Harley Quinn they're taking a character
one thing and they're constantly trying
to ram it down our throats in a way
that the character shouldn't be
and was never intended
I mean you can't deny that
you know they won't let her evolve
I mean they just they won't
yeah she's going to be fucking
this crappy Deadpool thing forever
and you know every now and then you're going to get
like these glimpses of hope
just like these moments of clarity from her
and that's all you're ever going to get
from DC when it comes to Harley Quinn
right now you're not going to see
like any like true redeemable anything
coming from them because it's all about
what sells and Harley Quinn right
now regardless of how
we feel specifically you and I
because it sells
this new Harley Quinn
fucking sells do you know how I'm like
when the Halloween party
you went to how many Harley Quinn's did you see I'm curious
and this year's Halloween party
yeah I don't think I saw any
but I know what you mean there's always Harley Quinn's
like the new Harley Quinn and that's what I saw a lot of
and this is oh you know what yeah you're right
there might have been some suicide squad Harley Quinn's
yeah no again
marketability like DC needs to make money somehow
and if Harley Quinn
is going to be like that little golden
goose fucking egg layer
than whatever fine and if this
if this system works for them that's fine
but I don't I will never
actively read or encourage
Harley to anybody if they say
hey I've never read
the new Harley Quinn comics what do you think
I will always put into the older stuff
that's what I mean is that like because in the comics
you know she's not like the Joker's girlfriend
anymore anything she's like a strong independent
woman who needs no man and like yeah
so so that's like their
answer to all these complaints is that like
well no she has developed
as a character because she's not
just she hasn't developed you've just
changed her changing her isn't
developing her yeah
like I don't like
if you she had already developed
and not been the Joker's girlfriend anymore
she was like that before the new 52
and it was fine she developed naturally
well it's also been an on and off again thing
honestly yeah I think
it's only like recently like
post Gotham City sirens that she's finally
been like if you ever touch me again
Joker I'll fucking kill you
yeah which we know will never happen
and like the whole like crazy like
in the movie
in the Suicide Squad movie there's like a
brief flashback to how she became Harley
Quinn and it shows the Joker
literally giving her
shock treatment to make her
crazy
are you serious
yeah are you serious
like could you get it
more that wrong that's like
that's not even just wrong it's like a
perversion like to weigh everything
that's cool about her origin no
no god he's so much better than
that like I get okay so first of all I know
Joker is not beyond torment
but he's also like the thing
that makes him scary is that he can make
you fall in love with him he can make a normal
sane person fall in love with him
with just talking that's
like his power he is a true
psychopath exactly um not
sociopath mind you a fucking
psychopath yeah there is no remorse
he does what he does because
if it works it will work in his favor
and he knows it works electrocuting
somebody's brain to make them crazy like
you no that's not
that's not interesting that's not scary
well don't kink shame him
are you sure it was to make her crazy it wasn't
just like that's what they heavily implied
that he okay okay to make her
crazy well then I'm okay
that's disappointing
yeah um
well what the fuck so like yeah she's
not she's not like
a person who was
seduced to the dark side or
or lulled by the Joker into
becoming a worse person
she's just a person who was
basically you know just cattle
prod me yes she was
just made crazy and I guess that's how
shock treatment works you just become a serial killer
I guess so
I guess I've been doing it wrong
I read a suicide squad comic recently
that pissed me off so much it was this um
it was called it was like
there was like a riot at blackgate
prison or whatever
or whatever the prison is called
blackgate marvel okay so
rikers is marvel I'm just gonna have to take your word
for it because I have not actually read
a
suicide squad comic since kingshark
oh god and I
that's another conversation for another day
because kingshark I fucking
love kingshark but
let's let's not
I fucking love kingshark
I had a friend the other day he was
like hey um
you know I just saw the suicide squad
movie but but I heard that you know that it wasn't
supposed to be croc it's supposed to be kingshark
what what do you know about kingshark
and I just imagined myself like running
across the United States of America
to to blast
down his fucking front door all the way
in California and slide in
like a like in a baseball game
home base and be like let me tell you about kingshark
motherfucker
I but I have not actually
actively read he sounds pretty jossim
god
I will never forgive you for that
just so you know
um anyway
but I'm just going to have to take your word
for any kind of suicide squad beyond the new 52
original new suits and squads there was a
suicide squad comic
recently we're like it was
at the prison all the suicide squad bad guys
were there or whatever and there was
something
released into the through the vents or whatever
some gas or something
and what are you doing
what are you doing
keep talking keep talking
you're distracting me what the
I get it I see she's just
googling kingshark I see him
I'm trying to find something god damn it
go on
oh yeah I guess you was on the flash
kingshark I've never watched the flash
no one has I don't like
all those fucking WB
I hate them all thank you go on
but um
suicide squad comic that came out recently
there was something in the prison in the atmosphere
in the vents that made everyone
go insane everyone went crazy
right all the inmates
lost their minds and started becoming crazy
people
but
because Harley Quinn
is already so crazy
it made her
sane again
that's what the storyline is called it's called sane again
so now that she's sane again
Harleen Quinzel can
get to the bottom of this
and solve this crisis
because that's her superpower
she's insane
she's wacky
this isn't
this is
ladies and gentlemen this was the day that
Jesse left this earth forever
I must go now
my planet needs me
oh my god
I remember you telling me about that
and I was like what the fuck are you talking about
are you serious I've never
I've never
I just
I've never been more disappointed
DC is like
a child that has disappointed me
for the last time I have to disown
my I'm like Jackie Chan's father
in drunken master when he
when he gets drunk and he causes that big
fucking racket in the town square
I have no son
I disown you and Jackie Chan has to
fucking go and drown his sorrows
alone and cry
and then he has to redeem himself by fighting the guy in the
foundry with the lava you've ever seen drunken master
I haven't but that sounds amazing
drunken master is a masterpiece
welcome to the legend of drunken master
podcast
where we talk about the greatest film ever made
that's it
we just talked about it
what was I saying
yeah but that's me talking to DC comics
I'm Jackie Chan's father disowning them
god I don't like that
I don't like it I don't like it one bit
no sir I don't like it
I need to like regain my
composure here I'm
I'm kind of wired from that
you're all hopped up I'm Harley Quinn hate
I'm kind of tired but then again I'm kind of wired
what do you say we go home and I eat your pussy
what are you talking to
that's from a movie
I forgot what movie I think it's like Nathan
Filion he says that in some
in some thing
okay
Nathan Filion
I'm kind of tired
but then again I'm kind of wired
what do you say I take you home and eat your pussy
some of you are gonna realize
very quickly that I'm not really
I don't really watch that many movies
or TV shows I sleep a lot
okay how do I move on from that fucking
you don't you can't fucking
move on from it
they took something good they took a diamond
and they squeezed it into coal
it's what they did they managed to reverse the process
I don't know yeah but they did it
that's why she always had that's why her old costume
was a diamond pattern because that's what
they that's what she was she was a diamond
she was my diamond she was America's
diamond she was America's sweetheart
and they took her
and they raped her
and they ruined her
they turned her into shit
and now the only place she belongs
flushed
down the visitors crapper
flushed her right down the
turlet that's what they ought to do to her now
she's ruined
your sons of bitches
you broke my heart
and you're ruining me
doing foley
is a three year old boy
you tore my heart out
and you threw it on the ground and you just don't do it
do you want to hug
you people wanted cactus jack
well I gave you cactus jack
come here it's okay
it's never going to be okay
but
wow
that was really emotional
and it should be
it should fucking be emotional
you know I'm sorry if there's a ton of people out there
that really like the new harleen quinzale
that's fine
I'm not going to berate you for it
but this is just this is just how I feel about it
this is how we feel about it
I'm going to berate
anyone who's listening to me for this long
and still doesn't know that I'm 100% objectively
true in this case
then you can go take
a long walk off a short pile of shit
into a bigger pile of shit
because you are a pile of shit
we all have our guilty pleasures jesse
yes
hey
jesus
how long has this been going on for an hour
you want to keep going
I don't know that was pretty good
this is a good brand
this is a good shitting
well it's even came out this week
I don't fucking care anymore
a bunch of bullshit it looks like
I don't fucking care I guess IVX came out
whatever
no that was number one I already read that
oh
I like the punishment
but I haven't read the new one yet
that's all that's all last week
justice league vs. suicide squad
boy I can't fucking read
to read that I can't fucking wait
oh yeah justice league vs. suicide squad
let's read that let's read that right now
let's see how they portray harleen quinzale
in the new justice league vs. the suicide squad
this is issue two I think I read issue one
well I don't remember it
yeah there's nothing to remember it's just
they're fighting okay no I do kind of remember
batman hires lobo
to be a good guy because that's what lobo does now
he's paid
to do what he's fucking told as long as he's paid to do it
so batman has paid him to be a good guy
holy shit
bonus though it is
the old school
lobo that we all grew up with
oh yeah
however
what the fuck
did you ever read the new 52 lobo
I did not
nor will I ever you don't need to
okay so for those of you who
haven't read the new 52 lobo
or even if you have
you know it doesn't matter I'm gonna say it anyway
the new 52 lobo
when it came out
they basically tried to say that the old school lobo
that we all knew and loved
you know the one from the superman animated series
you know a big bully voiced by brad garret
that glorious
hound of a man
he uh
he was an imposter
he was never the real lobo
if you didn't know that
the real lobo was
basically the model for the front cover
of a romance novel
he was this handsome
muscular like pretty boy
something had a final fantasy almost
and they decided they were gonna make him
the new lobo
he was gonna kill the old lobo if I remember correctly
if I don't remember correctly fuck you I don't care
this new lobo
has me all sorts of discombobulated
and the new lobo
um
he so he could basically
do anything that the old lobo could do
except he if I remember correctly
had like super ridiculous
regenerative powers like
Deadpool level regenerative powers
like if you cut off his head he'd probably be
fucking fine in like an hour or two or something
fucking no
and you know
there was already a lot about the new 52 lobo
that I didn't like
but I read all the way through it anyway
just so that I could try to you know understand
it and DC
and why people read it
and I'm not saying that there were a lot of people that read it
I did not have very many
sub customers that had it on their sub
I'd say maybe like three or four tops
and there might have been more at one point
but you know they all dropped it
and a whole lot of people tried to subscribe to it to begin with
they just kind of like picked it up one day and were like
yeah I guess they'll take a look at it
maybe it'll be good
and it just stayed on their sub for whatever reason
there's like you know fuck it I guess I'll just finish it
um but
there's this entire scene
where lobo, new 52 lobo
is pitted against the red lantern core
and he
fucking kills all of them he kills them
he kills the red lantern core
he tears apart
atrocidus, he tears apart the cat
I'm going to fart again
look out
nooooooooooooo well
nooo
oo I'm shitting my pants
ouch
oh
that's how I felt
I shit myself
We're gonna keep going anyway, so
That's that's basically how I felt, you know in all fairness though. They did renege on that later. They they basically
Now who's saying the n-word?
Tell me more about how they reneged. I I have an excuse
I've been drinking is um when everyone's injured and your basketball team only has white people
Do you need to renege before the big game?
Suck my balls
suck em
In all fairness they they did to go back and they basically said that oh just kidding the red lantern course still lives
Do you think that after four years of Trump in the White House America's gonna want to renege? Of course they are
You know did you know that Obama actually said that if he ran for president again?
He'd win again. It's like against Trump or whatever. I don't fuck. He doesn't matter
You're not allowed to run. You're not allowed to have a third term. No, you're not. It's an American thing
Does it matter I don't know anything about politics welcome to the politics cast and now we're talking about you know
What else pisses me off about Harley Quinn the whole the whole bleaching her skin thing
How the Joker now her new origin is that he bleached her skin to look more like yeah, hold the fucking phone
When did that happen? It was not a new 50 that was a new 52 thing. Yeah, I remember now
I did not like that. Okay. She used to be such a cutie pie
She'd take off her outfit and her makeup and she'd be normal
So before before new 52 Gotham City sirens actually ended right as the new 52 started it and in Gotham City sirens
She did not have bleached skin. She was a she was an adorable little
Harling Quinzel and I loved her. I loved Gotham City sirens. I love Gillum
What's his face is artwork even though he didn't finish the series he started it and it was wonderful
And then he started the Catwoman series from new 52, and I liked that series while it lasted but anyway
Um
Yeah, why did they bleach her skin? You know what's the point? You know what's cool about Harley Quinn?
I'm gonna drink some more is that she's not she wasn't just the Joker's girlfriend. She was his number one
Lacky she was his bottom bitch
She was based she was like his Robin and she could do things that the Joker couldn't like for example
Walk into a place like a normal person and like be in disguise because she doesn't look like the fucking Joker
She looks like a regular person. That's that's that's like what that's like her superpower
That's her asset to the Joker as a lackey
It's not just her glorious tiny little pussy that he loves getting inside with his nasty green tongue
It's the fact that she can that she can take the makeup off and sneak into places for him and like mingle and shit
So isn't the Joker supposed to be like an evil genius isn't he supposed to be smart?
How fucking stupid is it for him to like make her look like him? That's taking away that asset
I think okay, so I have a theory already on that
I think they did it to try and emphasize the whole abusive situation
I think they tried to make it to where he was marking her. Yeah, no, that's how I feel to you
I don't yeah fucking jerk it off. Whatever jerk it off
But that makes sense, right? I like they want to emphasize the abusive part of the of the relationship
I think it all just came from wanting everyone to have edgy new hot topic. He redesigned in the new 52
Yeah, I wanted her with the black and red pig tails and the white skin. That's probably an even better
I think it was purely idiotic marketing that did that. I remember that scene
I remember it was kind of rapey to like he dips her in there and like when he takes her out
He's like holding her like firmly by the chin and she's like sucking in her bottom like like nervously
He's doing his little like Joker grin. I remember. Oh dear god. I tried to forget and you reminded me and now I'm gonna drink some more
Yeah, yeah
Fuck
I
I'm just gonna say I hate new Harley Quinn. I hate I hate it. I've I can't bring myself to
I'm not again. I'm not gonna
No, I am I'm gonna kink shame people
Clarify trying to be a good person, but Harley Quinn in this current era does not make me a good person
Helps me in any kind of way. I don't like it. I don't think she has depth. I don't like the way she looks
I don't like anything about the new Harley Quinn. It just needs to stop
And I and I hate how much how much they push the whole lesbian thing now with her and poison Ivy
Like they really ram it down your throats in these comics, you know Tumblr loves it
You know
Like Paul Dini always hinted at it. It used to be like a oh, yeah, you make me so thorny. Yeah
Yeah, like it was always like okay. Yeah, we get it there. They're probably munching some carpet behind closed doors
That's that's cool. That's cute. We get it, but now it's just like okay
We fucking get it like every other comic is then like hey
I think you want a fucking finger me in the puss
You want a finger my puss?
Yeah, I want to finger your puss. How about you finger my puss, baby? That's my poison ivy. That's a pretty good poison ivy
I'll come here to kill all men and finger some puss. That's the Megan Fox poison
Megan Fox poison ivy. I can't wait
I
Can't wait with her. I guess you'll have a green thumb
Cuz Megan Fox is known for her gross thumbs. I've never seen her thumbs. Is it like is it like Danny's that's like a meme
Megan Fox has toe thumbs. Oh
Like short thumbs like their toes
So not is it on the same level as like Danny sex being thumbs
What's wrong with any sex banks thumbs, oh they always make fun of Danny sex veins thumbs Megan Fox thumbs. Oh
Yeah, I guess she does have kind of stubby thumbs. Yeah, that's really gross
Oh
My god, it's worse than I thought
God look up Danny sex banks. Oh
It's like if her thumb was a person it would have no knees
Oh
Still like cotton from King of the Hill
Did her thumbs kill Fiddy man? Yeah, she's got cotton thumbs. Oh my god
Stop doing oh good for you and how was it? Oh
No, they can Fox discusses her wonky thumbs
I
Don't want to look at her ever again
Well, you're gonna because she's they're talking about making her the new poison ivy
Mmm, don't do it. I like it. I don't don't do it
You know who was a good they made her April O'Neill too. That was a mistake
What that whole movie was a what is it with what is it with like perfect beautiful redheads being ruined by Megan Fox?
You know, one of my favorite things that I remember you saying about the TMNT movie when it first came out was you know, like
splinter
Learns karate. Oh, yeah through a book
Yeah, and I'm like yeah, and you're like well
It's good to know that there is no God. Yeah
That's the that's the the the turtles the 2012 one
Splinter finds a karate book in the garbage and that's where he learns to be a ninja
You know what you know what's been oh?
Jesse what what did you read any of the Batman TMNT comic books? Of course?
I did I have it have you wrote the new one the one that's based on the new cartoon. It's actually it's the Batman animated
And the TMNT like the current generation I guess on Nickelodeon. I did not it's actually good
It's actually fucking good. Okay. I don't like the new TMNT like cartoon for the most part
Like I'll watch it and kind of humor myself with it every now and then but I can't like watch it consistently
But thankfully with comic books you don't have to listen to voices. You only have the voices that are in your own head
But the the new Batman TMNT adventures are actually really good
So if you haven't read it yet, I do recommend it
I do feel like a lot of people are like oh well
It's not going to be as dark and gritty because you know
It's Batman going into their universe as opposed to the TMNT going into his universe
But it's good like I want to say trust me, but you know to each their own. I enjoyed it
I
Can't think of anything else to talk about. Yeah, that's comics for you. They're all shit. They're all bad
I don't like them. That's not true. Did we like some of them? I don't even remember which ones we liked
We oh, yeah, I read all the new Doctor Strange recently
You did tell me all about it caught up on that. Oh, I haven't read this one yet
So I haven't read the newest one. Okay, so you read up to 14. Tell me all about it. It's really good. I like it
It's um, I like the artwork a lot. So did you ever read Jason Aaron's?
Original Thor run his God Bomb arc
No, I was never really a big fan of Thor. I love Thor. He's a good boy. He didn't do nothing wrong
You know, you're probably right
I've just I've never taken the time out to actually like actively read anything by Thor again
Same with the movies like I enjoyed the movies, but they're not my favorite. I don't know
Thor was a good boy. He didn't deserve to get replaced by a woman. It was wrong
Whoa
Oh
Massagerist over here. Shut up. What's wrong with a woman for?
You guys can't see it, but I'm trying to do the trout mouth that the trout mouth that a that
Tumblr social justice warriors do what's wrong with Thor being a woman
So um, so this is Dr. Strange Jason Aaron wrote this he also wrote Thor for a long he's been writing Thor for like seven years
Stop it
So are you are you saying that all social justice warriors are ugly
I'm sorry go on saying that all people are ugly until proven innocent
Jason Aaron wrote a Thor comic and his Dr. Strange comic is basically the same comic
It's the same his first arc in Dr. Strange is like the same as his first arc in Thor
We're like in Thor it was this guy there was this guy called gore who hated gods and he wanted to kill all the gods and
In Dr. Strange
There's this guy who hates magic and he wants to kill all the magics. I can relate to both of them
But it's really cool
He like you can tell that he's really you know
It's it's for because of the movie and they're trying to make Dr. Strange like a lot more relatable and down to earth and stuff
So Dr. Strange in this is like a regular guy who has to deal with a lot of magical bullshit. He has to eat gross food
He hates it. He's always sick. He uh, he has to see his fight monsters. He goes into like this a special bar
That only magic people can go into
Like Dr. Voodoo was in there
Eliana Rasputin is in there and like Scarlet Witch and they all hang out and do magic stuff together. They have drinks
Yeah, yeah, and they and so these guys are killing all the magic. They take all the magic out of the world
And Dr. Strange has to fight back
And it's cool and they really they try to like I don't know if I'm too far from the mic
I feel like I'm scooting away from it. They they they introduced this concept or of like all magic
coming from somewhere like it um like
You know every time that Dr. Strange uses magic unbeknownst to him. There's always a price somewhere
so like
There's a bunch of people and a and a so like Wong has a bunch of dudes in a secret temple somewhere that Dr.
Strange doesn't know about like taking all the pain from all of his magic that he uses what the fuck
Yeah, and it's very it's interesting and it's cool and he fights the guy
But then at the end of it um
At the end of that story arc. It's like it's taking all the magic out of the world
Or like it's taking a significant amount of the magic out of the world
I was gonna say that might explain the new Dr. Strange versus the punters
Well, it's not like just a punter sure which it it seems like you know
That's like a big shift in the status quo
But it's such it's so vague that it's not really a shift at all like oh you've taken out most of the magic in the world
Well, what does that mean? He's still using magic. Yeah, like every like now in the in now
It's like oh ever since the magic was taken out of the world doing this is a lot harder
And then he does magic and he doesn't so it's kind of a pointless not really much of a shift in that
It's not much of a shit status quo shift in all fairness that may have tried and attempt was made
I was gonna say you know fairness it might affect other characters in the long run. I'm sure we'll see it
We'll see some of it later
But go on. I'm sorry
Well, that's basically it. I mean
Then the second story I picked up and right now he's in a car
It's driven by the orb the guy at the eyeball for a face and I haven't read this issue yet
But I'll get to it. I really like the new Dr. Strange. Yeah, I like it. It's been good
You know, I think Dr. Strange is kind of an interesting character in the sense that
You know, even though he's in the Marvel Universe and there's even a movie out for him now
Which you and I both saw and talked about a little bit on the last podcast, but
You know
You know, he's not exactly the easiest character to just kind of slip into any Marvel comic book
It's like constant teen, you know, yeah
like you can't just throw him in with anybody and I say that of course after they immediately throw him together with a
Punisher but
There's just so much to Dr. Strange and his abilities that it almost feels pointless to try and get him to team up with anybody else
because
You remember Civil War, you're a member like the first Civil War run where punish your killed like five guys
But but you know spider-in's like hey, Dr. Strange. I need you to do me a favor. I need you to
Help I need you to get everybody to forget that I ever revealed my identity to anybody. Yeah
And you know, Dr. Strange like I'll carry you got one and the spider island happens and spider. Oh, no, Dr. Strange said
No, that's impossible. Even I can't do that, but it happens. Anyway, maybe if you if you if you strike up a deal with Satan
Yeah, maybe that maybe that can do it
Yeah, I don't god I do remember
He did something I could have swore like up and down that he fucking did something in Civil War along that vein
Because I remember in the amazing spider-man's run of spider island where spider is like hey
Dr. Strange, can you do me? Can you do me another favor and Dr. Strange like no, and he just like fucks off forever
You know whatever maybe I'm getting things mixed up
but anyway, I
Really like the new Dr. Strange run. I like the artwork. I like the character. I like the way that he's written
I like the dialogue. I like
There's a lot about the new like Dr. Strange
There's very few like Marvel comics and I actively like sit and go. Yeah, this is fucking good
Dr. Strange is one of those titles
But this is also coming from the same person who says that full killer full killer is fucking fantastic
Which I stand by that. Holy shit. It's a fucking fantastic comic book
Totally underrated for anybody who hasn't been reading it. It's great
I know Jess hasn't been reading it, but you know, I don't did you even read Merck's like the Merck's for no
Merck's for money, I guess it's called. Nah, I'm looking at this DC holiday special right now
Oh with Harley Quinn more Harley Quinn all the Harley Quinn hey the suicide squad Harley Quinn
Hey, she looks pretty sexy right there with your legs spread open open in that present the present
That's in front of her box the box that's in front of her box. I'm uh, yeah, I like that I
Like Batman sipping on the tiny cup of tea
That's my fetish
But anyway, I
Don't if you're not reading Dr. Strange, I recommend it
You know, there's so very few Marvel titles. Like I said that I actually actively read
Dr. Strange is actually one of those titles that I currently read and
Fool killers another one that actively read before that was vision
Which you know, Jesse and I both talked about vision already
But I'm just gonna fucking say it again. If you didn't pick up vision yet do it
There's only two volumes and they're both fucking glorious
That's right and that's is that it is that that's the panel cast everybody
Comics suck and we hate them the end