Come on, you fuckers think that just cause a guy reads comics, he can't start some shit?
Aw, fuck it, take all you want!
We're violent, we're heavy.
Home again, home again.
Gibbontake a lot!
Class is paying 101.
I guess one person can make a difference.
Welcome to the panel cast.
I am the Wolfman, baby.
Woooo!
Does anybody get what I'm doing?
That's Wolfman Jack.
He was a radio DJ a million years ago.
That's what I am now, cause it's Halloween.
I'm a Wolfman, I'm just like Wolfman Jack.
Only I'm not quite as powerful as Wolfman Jack.
I'm a Wolfboy, I'm a Wolfman in training.
Though I do share his lupinous condition.
It's a lupinous condition, not a lupus condition.
It's not lupus, it's never lupus.
It is in fact lupinous in origin.
The curse of the lichen flows through my blood.
Every Wednesday when the comics are released,
I transform into a comic devouring Wolfboy.
Ready to run out into the streets
and read comics and scare people.
I'm not quite as good at howling as the original Wolfman.
Though I do suffer from Lycanecticus.
I also suffer from a rare and debilitating form of Schifilophagus
that makes me unable to howl with the same level of strength
and force and power and gusto as the Wolfman
so I can only manage to croak out a barely audible...
What am I talking about?
Welcome to Panelcast, true believers.
I am your host, Endlit G.
I'm just stealing that true believers catchphrase from Stan Lee completely.
I'm 100% ripping that off.
I can do that.
That's within my rights as the most important person who ever lived.
I have sold a minion over the legal right to rip off, steal, and appropriate
any catchphrases or turns of phrase spoken or uttered by anyone who has ever lived.
Ah, like an absorbal off, absorbing the most powerful traits of all great men.
Because I am them.
I am everyone and everything.
That's why I am the endless boy.
Bitch.
I don't think Stan Lee will mind.
If I drop an Excelsior every now and then or if I open my podcast
with a true believer, if I so choose, he doesn't mind.
Me and him are tight.
We go way back.
In fact, me and him had a running contest in the 80s to see who would get the most girls.
Last I checked, I was way ahead.
Besides, that dude's like 500 years old.
He'll probably turn to dust or go back to his home planet at some point pretty soon.
And then, where will his essence go, if not to me?
I'm like Shang Tsung.
As long as someone is dead,
I have the power to harness and appropriate their essence, their visage,
their form to disorient my opponents in combat.
In the combat of the mortals.
What the fuck is happening?
This is already week two of the panel cast,
and it's already just a complete train wreck spiraling down the drain.
Eat your debris.
It's already turning into a...
Oh boy.
Ah.
God damn it, I'm the motherfucking wolf man.
Okay, let's talk about comics, people.
That's what this podcast is about.
That's what life is about.
It's the only thing that truly matters.
The only thing that brings me any real sense of peace and tranquility
in this rotten, miserable hellhole of a planet.
It's the only thing I trust anymore,
because comics are the only safe activity left
for a psychotic man like myself, okay?
I've been eagerly anticipating sitting down here
and recording another panel cast for everybody this week,
because comics, reading comics is the only time I feel safe anymore.
It's the only safe activity left.
Going outside is not safe.
It's not safe out there for a man like me.
Chaos follows me.
Conflict follows me.
Everywhere I go, I just want to live in peace,
but nobody wants to let me.
Everybody wants to fuck with me.
Everybody wants to take shots at the champ.
So everywhere I go, I end up in some fight,
or some huge brawl,
or someone fucks with me,
or I become the center of some swirling tornado
of chaos and violence.
Happens to me every single time I go out.
Just the other day, in fact, I went to a party,
and of course I ended up at the center of a huge fucking brawl,
because everyone has to fuck with me.
Everybody has to start shit,
and nobody expects that the guy they're fucking with
is gonna fuck with them right back.
Nobody expects that somebody in this world
still has the balls to stand up for themselves.
So of course I end up in the middle of a huge fucking catastrophic brawl.
I'm fighting people off me from all sides.
I'm throwing bitches left and right.
I got guys hanging off me.
I'm punching, I'm kicking, I'm scratching, I'm killing.
Oh god, it was chaos.
I was just like Brody in my intro.
Come on, you fuckers think that just because the guy reads comics,
he can't start some shit?
I'll fucking take all you on!
You know, it's the same old song and dance with me.
Everywhere I go, this happens.
I'm used to it,
but I'm also getting pretty sick and tired of it,
and it's all because some people just can't take a joke.
Some people just can't comprehend
or wrap their minds around the intricate concept of humor.
It's like rocket surgery to some people.
You know, it seems like you can't even show up in a Trump hat
and start slapping bitches anymore
without everybody losing their sense of humor all of a sudden.
Well, I apologize if my satire was too high-brow
for you Neanderthals to understand,
but I thought this was America.
Anyways, I'm sure I'll get into the gory,
hilarious, awesome details of that story
at some other point on some other podcast,
but this is not the place for it.
This is the place for comics people.
I'm talking about all the wonderful, wacky, wild,
and exciting comics that I read this week.
And also, I am the Wolfman.
Don't forget that.
I'm gonna quiz you on all of this after the podcast is done.
Who is the Wolfman?
What are comics for?
Who likes them?
What country is this and where's my America?
All important questions that you will be graded on.
Harshly.
One other piece of news that I forgot to mention
in the pilot episode of this podcast,
and last week's episode, I didn't mention this.
Wasn't sure if I wanted to mention it,
but as I go through and talk about all of these comics,
if any of them peak your curiosity
and you want to check them out and you want to read them,
there are comic reader websites where people just post them
and you can read them for free all over the internet.
I guess I'll put one in the description box.
Obviously, it's not legal, but you know, who gives a fuck?
I use it and I still buy comics.
You know, usually what happens is if I read a comic on there
that I like, then I go out and buy it.
So I think that sites like these actually drive sales.
I think that piracy often has just as much of a beneficial effect
to sales as any negative effect that anyone says it has.
So if I talk about comics and they sound cool to you by all means,
check them out and then go fucking buy them
if you feel like it or if you don't feel like I don't fucking give a shit, man.
I don't give a shit. I'm an easygoing guy.
Until someone fucks with me and then I become the motherfucking wolf man, baby.
I'm just gonna make sounds.
Noises.
I read Wonder Woman this week.
Yeah, how's that for a smooth segue?
So this Wonder Woman series is part of DC's whole company-wide
rebirth branding thing.
And what the rebirth thing is, is a couple years ago,
DC did this big retcon.
They called it the New 52.
They were sort of, they were trying to simplify their continuity
by saying that like, okay, the whole DC universe now started five years ago
and that's the new status quo.
But in trying to simplify their continuity for new readers and such,
all they actually managed to accomplish was
they made it a million times more confusing and complicated
and accidentally totally screwed the pooch and ruined everything
because when you take, you know, 80 years of continuity
and try to squish it all into five years,
suddenly nothing makes any fucking sense.
Like everywhere you would look, there was all this weird shit that you couldn't,
like saying that like Batman, for example, has only been around for five years,
that does not work in any way with all the different Batman stories.
You know, the fact alone that there's been like six different Robins, you know,
like Dick Grayson has gone from a 12-year-old boy to like a 25-year-old man
and then you had Jason Todd and Tim Drake also growing up into grown ass men
and then he has this son, Damien, who's like 12 years old,
whom he's sired with Talia Al Ghul when he was still Batman 12 years ago.
The very idea of squishing all this continuity into like a five-year span
inherently ruins everything and makes nothing sensical or coherent in any way.
And there were so many weird plot holes that arose from this decision,
from this rebranding, you know, like the Teen Titans were totally fucked,
the Teen Titans are still fucked, nothing, nothing can save the Teen Titans now
because of the continuity and how badly it's been fucked.
The Teen Titans make no fucking sense and I don't think they ever will again.
Nightwing is in his 20s, but Starfire and Raven are still somehow on the Teen Titans
and still I'm supposed to believe they're still teenagers,
even though Damien's now also in the Teen Titans and he's like 12
and Cyborg now was never a Teen Titan, he was just a Justice League guy
like what's going on, I don't understand any of this shit anymore,
none of it makes any sense anymore.
So they just totally ruined everything and it made it really hard to get invested
in DC's stories for a long time, but the great thing about DC is that at a certain point
they finally looked at all the fan response and they said, you know what,
yeah we did kind of fucking ruin everything for a couple years though,
let's go back and try to fix it, let's try to smooth things out a bit.
So they went back and basically this rebirth branding thing that they're doing now
is kind of like DC's apology to fans, it's their way of saying,
alright we admit it, we fucked up and they're kind of like slowly reintegrating
all of the old continuity that was lost in the New 52 relaunch.
So they're, you know, trying to get everything back to basics and get back to the way it was
and getting rid of all the weird, hokey, New 52 bullshit that nobody liked,
like for example Wonder Woman and Superman being like romantically involved,
which is like a weird like leftover idea from Frank Miller in the 80s
that he had a boner for but doesn't really make sense to anyone else,
but they did it anyways, like what the, like it kind of ruins both characters
to say that, you know, they're this like Brangelina power couple
lording over the world in their fucking watch tower.
I mean like the main thing that makes Superman or Wonder Woman relatable and special
is that they both date regular people, like Superman's girlfriend is Lois Lane,
she's just a regular chick because Superman is a regular guy.
If you take Superman and you have him fucking Wonder Woman,
suddenly neither of them are like regular people anymore,
they're just larger than life gods who are sitting up on Olympus licking each other's assholes
and lording it over the rest of humanity.
It's dumb.
So anyways, this issue of Wonder Woman starts out with Steve Trevor,
Wonder Woman's old boyfriend.
Steve Trevor, if you don't know the character, he was the guy who first,
he was like a fighter pilot who first crash landed on the island of Themyscira
and discovered the Amazons and discovered Princess Diana,
not Princess Diana the one that you're thinking of.
Not the young woman who died in the car crash and her beanie baby is worth like $50 million.
I'm talking about Wonder Woman's name as Diana, she's...
So yeah, Steve Trevor is the guy who discovered Wonder Woman
and he's pretty much always been her boyfriend or her romantic interest
or her best buddy or her human compadre.
He's always been sort of integral to Wonder Woman.
So this comic starts out with Steve Trevor
and then a bunch of stuff happens in the middle that I don't understand
because I haven't been reading this series, I haven't been keeping up with it.
There's some stuff about like Diana can't find Themyscira anymore,
like it's hidden from her for some reason.
She's trying to find her way back to Themyscira and it's like off the map.
I have no idea what's going on.
I have not been reading this series, I just jumped into issue number nine.
But near the end of the book there's a scene where Steve Trevor is hanging out on the beach
and Wonder Woman goes and joins him and they have like a conversation on the beach
and they have this come to Jesus meeting, this sort of
we used to be boyfriend and girlfriend kind of talk.
They have some real talk and they're talking about Superman
and he's like, you know, I can't blame you for going out with Superman.
I mean, he's fucking Superman, man.
She's like, yeah, maybe it was wrong, maybe it was more convenient than it was.
And Wonder Woman kind of goes into the speech about her motivations for having been with Superman.
Kind of like retconning some purpose into that weird fucking
corporately mandated romance, right?
Trying to retcon some, I guess, character motivation into it that makes some semblance of sense.
And Wonder Woman is going on this speech and it's a good speech.
And I feel like for once Wonder Woman actually came off like a person with a personality.
She usually doesn't for me. She usually doesn't do it for me.
But I think it was pretty well written and they're having this conversation
and yada yada and blue bitty blue and long story short, they kiss and so they're back together.
So that's what I'm talking about with the rebirth line and why it's been so great and so satisfying
is because the entire rebirth line that DC has been doing all year has basically
just been them kind of getting back to basics and saying, yeah, we fucked up
and slowly putting all the puzzle pieces back together the way they belong together
and putting everything as it should be in its right place.
You know what it feels like to read these rebirth stories
and see them fixing all these mistakes and rectifying all these weird directions
that they went on over the last couple of years because it's been hard to read DC comics
for the last couple of years ever since the New 52 began.
Even good comics, it's been hard to read just because the continuity got so fucked
and there were so many weird things going on.
So in order to understand what it feels like to now read these rebirth comics
and see them one by one fixing everything and putting the puzzle pieces back where they belong
or at least back into a shape where they make sense again,
it feels so satisfying to see these things like Wonder Woman kissing Steve Trevor
or Green Arrow being back together with Black Canary and they're on an island or some shit
or Superman and Lois Lane having a house and a kid together
and his kids got superpowers and he's teaching his kid how to be superpowers guy.
It's so fucking satisfying. It feels like all's right with the world.
Like God's in his heaven, Superman is fucking Lois Lane and all's right with the world.
I read it and I feel warm inside. I feel like I can feel electricity in my blood
and I can feel endorphins shooting off into my brain and making me feel safe and secure again
in a way that I haven't felt since I was a child.
I can feel the pages of the comic growing larger and enveloping me
like a warm blanket of security and it's like I'm just melting into it.
My body is breaking down and I'm melting into the pages.
I'm becoming part of the comic.
I'm seeing my world in ink and color and separated into panels.
I'm being drawn into a realm of pure imagination,
a realm of comics just like the Sega Genesis game, Comic Zone.
I'm becoming one with the comics and I'm soaring through a vast and beautiful universe
like the Silver Surfer.
I'm seeing colorful nebulas and a technique color of different galaxies and star systems
becoming one with the hopes and dreams of all good little comic boys and comic girls out there.
I've obtained the Power Cosmic like the Silver Surfer,
only it's even more powerful than the Power Cosmic because it's the Power Comic.
I'm surfing through the galaxy on a board of the Power Comic.
A storyboard, if you will.
Ha ha ha ha!
That's me sucking my stogie because I just told I made a brilliant play on words.
You know what it's like? It's like the video game Res for PS2 where you're like a wireframe guy
and you're flying through this like crazy techno cyberspace scape and it's like a shmup.
It's like Res. I've become Res.
And I'm seeing all of these beautiful heartwarming images flashing before my eyes
as I soar through a beautiful brilliant galaxy of colors and shapes and memories and feelings.
Witnessing all of these pieces fall back into place the way they belong.
All of these puzzle pieces coming back together to form a cohesive picture once again in my mind.
And I'm hearing Tom York from Radiohead crooning like an angel.
Everything in its right place.
That song is playing.
Look up everything in its right place by Radiohead because that's the soundtrack of this journey into mystery
that my soul, my essence is undertaking through the universe.
Yesterday I woke up sucking a lemon
That's what it's like. Feels good man.
Anyways it was pretty good and I don't even like Wonder Woman that much so you know that's good.
The next comic I read was fucking um fuck.
Suddenly it's really fucking hot in here. Oh my god. Oh god get the sweater off me. Oh god!
I'm done. I'm taking a nap. Going to bed. Finish this one. Finish it later.
The next comic I read which is probably the most high profile comic that came out this week
was Civil War II number six.
And let me tell you this comic can go fuck itself. This is a piece of shit.
It's a fucking, it's a pile of fuck. I don't respect it.
I don't respect it. The fact that it exists.
And it's not even a bad comic. It's fun.
I get it. I get why comics like these sell because it's all the superheroes in one book.
And I guess to normies who have not seen that every year who are not sick of it
because normies do not have this event fatigue that comic book fans get.
That's why these event comics continue to sell.
Because if you don't read comics regularly then of course you want to see all of the superheroes fighting each other in a comic.
But when it's every single year you're reading comics and every fucking year Marvel has some new goofy gimmick event comic
and it's always some new ridiculous conflict of characters acting out of character
and you know personalities being stretched so far in order to meet this corporately mandated battle
where we have to have side A beat up side B and vice versa
to the point where the characters aren't even acting rationally like themselves anymore
and the stories don't make any sense and they just bleed into all of the other comics
and stick their dicks into every other story currently going on.
And nothing can make sense anymore.
No storyline gets a chance to breathe on its own.
No comic gets a chance to breathe or stretch its wings
and see what it can do with its own universe and its own storylines and its own characters.
Character development is thrown out the window all across the board.
It's all swept away once a year to make way for some huge goofy clusterfuck event comic
that's usually bloated and takes what fucking half the year to come out
with 50 fucking tie-in issues.
God damn it! I hate these fucking event comics!
I cursed them! I'm sick of them!
Oh god.
You know you've got DC over here with its rebirth shit
and like yeah you could make the argument that it's kind of taking things back to the status quo
but not really. It's not getting rid of character development or anything like that.
It's not putting things back exactly how they were.
It's just putting things back in a way that fucking makes sense.
It's putting the characters, it's making them like themselves again,
making them recognizable again.
It's not getting rid of any character development
but these fucking Marvel events every year.
Holy shit!
Marvel is all about the illusion of change.
You know every year we're gonna shake up the Marvel Universe with some crazy new gimmick.
The fallout from this event is gonna be so catastrophic
and universe changing.
Nothing will ever be the same again.
They say that every fucking year and it's always bullshit.
It's like they think they're shaking up the status quo
but there's no status quo to shake up anymore.
The events are the status quo
because every fucking year there's an entire year of like weird fallout
and goofy gimmicks that don't make any sense.
And then by the time anything starts to make sense again
by the time the stories start getting back on their feet
then by that time it's time for the next year's stupid event
that's going to shake things up in some other recocculus way.
Oh this year fucking the X-Men are outlaws
and mutants are endangered
and then the next year mutants are not endangered
but then the next year they are again
and then this year there's a registration act
and then the next year Norman Osborn is in charge of the government
so the maniacs are running the asylum
and then the next year there's Skrulls.
Some people are Skrulls in disguise
and it's a hole you gotta figure out who the bad guys are.
You can't trust anybody.
And then the next year Peter Parker is now a fucking billionaire
on the level of Tony Stark, a genius inventor for some fucking reason
and then the next year you've got fucking, you know...
Fuck! Fuck!
Enough! Enough already!
Nobody can keep up with this shit.
It's all goofy. It's fucking retarded.
Civil War II? Are you fucking kidding me?
Who asked for that? Who wanted it?
Oh because they made a Civil War movie
they've gotta fucking have a comic that says Civil War on the shelves
so Normies will buy it.
They had to concoct this recocular Civil War II story
which is even more nonsensical and retarded
than the first one was ten years ago.
Somehow it's even more ridiculous.
You know by the grace of God
the Captain America movie Civil War
fixed the Civil War comic story
which was a fucking retarded comic book story
that everybody hated because it didn't make any fucking sense.
Oh god I hate it!
Oh god!
So the story of Civil War II
is that there's this inhuman.
The inhumans are a group of fucking assholes
who live on the moon.
I don't even want to fucking get into them
because I fucking hate the inhumans.
They're the worst thing ever created
but they fucking unleash a poisonous gas cloud on Earth
and it's making more people into inhumans.
So more people are getting inhuman powers
and there's this fucking kid named Ulysses
and he gets these pre-cog powers
where he can tell the future
and so since he can tell the future
he has visions of these horrible catastrophes, right?
So all the superheroes get in a room
and they go,
what are we gonna do about this kid's visions
of the horrible catastrophes?
And fucking half the people
are led by Captain Marvel, Carol Danvers,
who says, oh, we should use the kid
to stop crimes before they happen.
And then half the guys are led by Tony Stark, Iron Man.
And he says, no, that's crazy.
Haven't you idiots ever seen Minority Report?
And Carol says, no, I haven't seen Minority Report.
I've never seen this trope before
and therefore I'm a fucking moron
and I think it's a good idea.
Sorry, I'm sorry, not Miss Marvel.
She's not Miss Marvel anymore.
She's Captain Marvel now.
You can't call her Miss Marvel.
It's regressive.
The little brown girl is Miss Marvel.
She can be called Miss because at least she's brown.
At least in some way she's inclusive and diverse.
You can't have a white girl.
You can't call women Miss.
So Miss Marvel is not Captain Marvel.
Oh God.
So Captain Marvel takes a bunch of guys.
She takes War Machine and She-Hulk.
She assembles a team and she goes to fight Thanos.
Thanos.
Thanos or Thanos?
I feel like Thanos sounds better.
She goes to fight Thanos because the fucking Ulysses kid
had a vision that Thanos was going to beat everyone up.
Really bad.
So she goes to Thanos.
She finds him in his fucking house and starts a fight.
And what do you know?
Thanos beats everyone up.
Really bad.
She just barges into his fucking place.
He's mining his own business.
And he's sitting in his best chair.
And she busts through the wall like the fucking Kool-Aid man
with War Machine and She-Hulk
and starts a fucking fight.
So yeah, the kid's vision came true.
But only because she fucking, you know.
And that's how the trope works, right?
That's how this trope always ends up.
Seeing the future is what locks the future
because they see it and by trying to avoid it
they cause it to happen.
That's like the plot of every That's So Raven episode.
How has nobody in the Marvel Universe
ever seen an episode of That's So Raven?
So that's basically what the Civil War II divide is about.
It's about the superheroes who have seen That's So Raven
versus the superheroes who haven't seen That's So Raven.
And don't know how this fucking trope works.
So Thanos kicks everyone's ass.
War Machine is fucking dead.
She-Hulk is in like critical condition.
So Tony Stark is so fucking pissed off
that his best buddy, Rody, died
in this ill-conceived cock-a-manie pre-cog battle idea
that he basically says, fuck you Carol, we're fighting now.
Everyone's fighting.
Meanwhile, Carol also has to go and find Bruce Banner
and tell him that his cousin She-Hulk
is in critical condition because of her.
And nobody wants that job
because if Bruce Banner gets mad,
if he finds out that we fucked up so bad
and got his cousin hurt,
he's gonna hulk out, he's gonna throw a big fit, right?
Even though Bruce Banner has actually been cured
by the Hulk in continuity for like a year,
they're still paranoid about it
because they're a bunch of fucking idiots.
So they're going to confront the Hulk
and tell him, you know, what's going on.
But then also, the Ulysses kid has another fucking premonition
and he has a premonition that the Hulk
is going to kill everyone.
So here's what Carol does
because the only way that this story can even happen
is by making one of the characters a complete retard.
So they made Captain Marvel a complete fucking retard.
Everything that she does in this series
defies all logic and rationale.
It's all completely insane.
Her actions are the actions of a fucking madman
and it's baffling that anyone would even take her side at all.
So the situation is that they have to go tell Bruce Banner
that they got She-Hulk nearly killed
and they have a vision that says the Hulk
is going to fucking kill everyone.
And they already know from the first vision
that trying to prevent the visions
is exactly what makes the visions happen.
So you'd think the answer is pretty fucking clear.
Leave Bruce Banner the fuck alone.
Instead, Captain Marvel shows up on his doorstep
with like an entire army of pissed off superheroes behind her
ready to like intimidate Bruce Banner
into coming with him quietly.
What the fuck?
You don't intimidate Bruce fucking Banner.
You don't even try that.
That's a goofy idea.
So they're basically antagonizing Bruce Banner
into becoming the Hulk.
And he's saying,
what are you fucking people talking about?
I haven't been the Hulk in like a year, okay?
I haven't had, you know, a Hulk episode in a while.
I'm totally okay.
You're telling me that you got She-Hulk all fucked up
for no reason.
Clearly I'm pissed off,
but as you can see, I'm not hulking out.
So why do you have a bunch of people here
trying to intimidate me?
So they have this fucking, you know, conflict.
And long story short,
they're so worried.
They're so paranoid that Bruce is going to hulk out
and kill everyone.
That Hawkeye, who is sitting over in a tree,
lets loose an arrow,
flip, and you know,
shoots Bruce in the head,
and Bruce Banner's dead.
They killed Bruce Banner.
So then there's a whole big thing.
It's like the trial of Hawkeye,
you know, trying to, you know,
and Hawkeye reveals that Bruce requested him
to kill him if he ever was going to hulk out again.
And Hawkeye says that, hey, in good faith,
I'm Hawkeye.
I have better eyes than you.
I saw a little flick of green in his eyes.
I thought he was going to become the Hulk, you know?
I had no choice.
He told me if he ever became the Hulk again
to fucking kill him, so I did what he asked.
So, you know, it's a whole big trial.
And Hawkeye is found innocent,
I think.
I'm a little hate.
I'm pretty sure he's found innocent,
but you know, there's another point.
Fuck, what else fucking happened
in this Godforsaken story?
Anyways, because of everything that's fucking happened,
Tony Stark and Captain Marvel fucking hate each other.
And yeah, and it's Civil War II.
All the superheroes are going to fucking fight each other
again over stupid bullshit.
And the conflict is so stupid,
because, like,
in the first issue,
Captain Marvel's side is proven
to be objectively wrong.
Right?
Like, she gets the pre-cog,
she gets the vision of, like, Thanos
beating everyone up,
so she goes to attack Thanos
and gets beat up by Thanos.
In the first issue,
the dilemma is fucking solved.
Well, okay, now we know that this is that
Surraven rules.
We know that if we fucking try to prevent these visions,
they're just gonna be forced into fruition.
We're going to make them come to pass
by trying to prevent them.
That's how time travel stories always work.
Have you never seen a fucking time travel story in your life?
Holy shit.
It literally happens in the first issue.
Like, the dilemma is over.
The problem is solved.
The issue is complete.
Nobody would be insane enough
to still be on her side
after the very first vision that they saw
proved that her side was fucking retarded.
Beyond a shadow of a doubt.
Like, it's one thing where it's like
in the first Civil War,
where people can argue both sides.
Like, you know, some people have been...
Some people read Civil War I
or they watch the Civil War movie
and they're legitimately on Tony Stark's side
with the Registration Act.
Some people watch it and they're legitimately on Cap's side.
I can't imagine anyone being on Carol's side
in Civil War II
because the story itself
goes out of its way to expressly show
that her side is objectively fucking wrong.
Holy shit.
This is fucking terrible.
So anyways, it's Civil War II
and all the superheroes are fighting each other
and eventually the kid gets another fucking vision
and this time his vision is of Miles Morales
who is the little black Mexican Spider-Man.
There's two Spider-Men now.
I don't know why he couldn't have just had it like his own name.
But he has a vision of a little baby Spider-Man
killing Captain America
and that fucking sends everyone into panic mode
and so that's where this issue starts off
with them dealing from the fallout
of this new vision that they've had
of Miles Morales killing Captain America
and it's really stupid
and it's really fucking shit.
It's shit.
God damn it.
God fucking damn it.
I hate event comics.
I'm so sick of this shit.
I'm so sick of Marvel's bullshit
every year with this shit.
Oh my god.
I need tea.
So they get this vision that Spider-Man's going to kill Captain America
and so everyone's freaking out
and Carol is doing her fucking minority report bullshit.
She's like,
okay Spider-Man you're going to come quietly
we're going to arrest you.
This is like a 15 year old kid.
She's basically gone full supervillain at this point.
She's arresting children
on account of some fuckboy in humans
goofy nightmares.
So she's about to beat up Spider-Man
and arrest him and all that
but then Captain America's like Carol shut the fuck up
sit the fuck down you crazy ass bitch
and Miss Marvel
remember Captain Marvel used to be Miss Marvel
but she bestowed the name Miss Marvel
onto Kamala Khan
who is a teenager
and so she is Miss Marvel
and she was like Captain Marvel's protege, right?
Captain Marvel gave her the name Miss Marvel
Captain Marvel is about to, you know,
arrest Little Spidey
but then Little Marvel, Miss Marvel
she grabs her with her giant hand
she can stretch her body
so she's got a giant hand sometimes
she grabs her with a giant hand she says fuck you
this is crazy
you've gone bad man
so you know Miss Marvel
so they all jump ship
all the little teeny bopper Avengers
jump ship
the Iron Man side
and Captain America
has a talk with Spider-Man
he says okay son don't
don't freak out
and then Thor
not the real Thor, the fucking woman Thor
Jane Foster, she flies
Little Spider-Man out there
God none of these fucking superheroes
are even the actual superheroes anymore
every fucking character's name
that you talk about when you talk about Marvel
you have to put an asterisk
next to every fucking thing that you say
it makes everything you're saying
take ten times longer
because you have to add the caveat of
and then Spider-Man, not Peter Parker
the little Spider-Man, the black Mexican Spider-Man
does this and then Thor takes him
and flies away, not the real Thor that you know
I'm talking about the girl Thor
Jane Foster, she used to be Thor's girlfriend
she had cancer and now she is Thor
because Nick Fury whispered a secret into his ear
that made him unworthy of Mjolnir
so now fucking blah blah blah blah
and then Ms. Marvel grabbed Captain Marvel
because Ms. Marvel is the Ms. Marvel
because Captain Marvel used to be Ms. Marvel
and god damn it Marvel I fucking hate you
fuck
just give these characters their own fucking names
if you want to be diverse
then create new superheroes
don't fucking co-opt
names of superheroes that already
fucking exist
these two Spider-Man swinging around
it's fucking confusing
you piece of shit
I hate you Marvel
I fucking hate them
so Captain Marvel is off on some
shield, helicarrier
sulking like a little whiny baby
because her crazy weird
evil supervillain plans are falling
through and everyone on her side is
abandoning her cause
Black Panther
abandons her side and he goes and joins
Captain America's side
Black Panther has one of the goofiest
lines I've ever seen in this comic
where he's saying
I'm sorry Carol I can't be on your side
of this conflict anymore
because you know
when you're on the
opposite side of Steve Rogers
you're usually
in the wrong
Captain America is usually a pretty moral guy
so when it comes to moral issues
I want
to be on the side of Captain America
well mother fucker
if that's how you feel
then why weren't you on his
side from the beginning
what the fuck kind of a
what the fuck
kind of a revelation is that
it's not like he saw the carnage
or saw what was going on
and said you know what
I'm starting to think that maybe Carol's ideas
about this whole pre-cog
you know
kind of justice thing
I think maybe she's going off the deep end
it wasn't like he slowly saw what was
happening and came to acknowledge
this he just suddenly
remembered oh yeah
Captain America's on the other team
well he's usually right
how could I forget
what the fuck
and then at the end fucking little spider-man
goes to the fucking
capital steps of
Washington and he stands there
some shit
I don't fucking know
oh fuck this is
terrible this is so fucking
bad
why do they do this
I'm looking at this fuck I'm looking at these pages
right now and every time
I keep remembering other things
about this comic that are so fucking weird
like at this point the only
people still
on Captain Marvel's side
are
Storm for some fucking reason
Jean Grey
not the real Jean Grey
not the original Jean Grey
the new Jean Grey who is actually
the younger Jean Grey from the past
transplanted into the present
from Beast because he made a time machine
to bring the original young baby
X-Men to the present
that teach Scott Summers a lesson
because the X-Men were fugitives for a while
because of all the fallout from one of their big stupid
events Avengers vs X-Men
in 2011 so Beast
hated Cyclops and he wanted
he had some weird goofy plan
that somehow bringing Jean
Grey as a teenager back into
the present with oh Jesus
so she's got fucking teenage
Jean Grey there on her side
she's got Storm there who
Storm has a fucking Mohawk because she had
a Mohawk in the 80s and some
Jackass at Marvel decided to
retro and bring the Mohawk back
for some reason even though it looks
fucking goofy as hell so she's
got fucking she's got fucking
phony teenage teeny
bopper Jean Grey from the 60s
she's got stupid looking
Mohawk Storm and she's
got the Guardians of the Galaxy on her team
but the Guardians
of the Galaxy are so fucked up
the rock that's like like okay
Groot's there Peter Quills there
and Rocket Raccoon's there
Dora and Drax so everybody that you know from
the movie but also I don't know
what the fuck is going on in Marvel
Ben Grimm the thing is now
part of the Guardians of the Galaxy
Shadowcat is there Kitty Pride
from the X-Men what's going on
I don't know what's
happening with the Guardians of the Galaxy
I don't know why fucking Kitty Pride
and Ben Grimm are currently on that team
but they are and so
that's basically all the people
who are left on
Captain Marvel's insane
supervillain team
the Guardians of the Galaxy
featuring Ben Grimm and Kitty Pride
stupid looking idiot Mohawk
Storm from the 80s and
stupid looking teeny bopper
bitch face mindrapes
people without permission and turns them gay
Jean Grey from the 1960s
Jean Gay should be her name
because that's all she does
she's a bad she's an evil little girl
she turns people gay
as the great philosopher
me once said
you so gay
you're making me gay
why is Kitty Pride
in the Guardians
why is she one of the Guardians of the Galaxy
what is happening
you know there's this weird panel here
where Carol is sulking
because nobody wants to be on her fucking
supervillain crew anymore
and fucking Peter Quill
comes up behind her
and he says you know what
fuck them you're right
you're absolutely right
about this whole thing
if you can prevent anything bad
from happening then you have to try to do it
you have to do everything you can
to prevent disasters and tragedies
from happening
well you know
that's a great speech there Star-Lord
except for the fact that she's
causing the things to happen
she trying to change the bad
things is causing the bad things to happen
this was established in the first issue
so why the fuck
did this conflict even make it
to six issues
it should have been over at the first issue
you're all crazy you're all idiots
you're all out of character
fucking badly written fanfic
idiots
oh god
you know these are beloved characters
everybody loves Star-Lord
why is he suddenly a fucking idiot
why is he on this team of supervillains
why are any of these
beloved characters on this team
of supervillains why is Carol
a fucking supervillain
okay they're gonna have a fucking
Captain Marvel movie in a couple years
they're gonna be wanting
they're gonna want a push Captain Marvel
as a hero they're gonna want everyone to
fucking love her right
so why are they making her a fucking crazy
tyrant who arrest people
for future crimes
you know Marvel's all about fucking diversity
everyone's all about
we need female superheroes
there's not enough female superheroes
for little girls to look up to
so we gotta make a Captain Marvel movie
hey little girls
do you want to
be like Captain Marvel when you grow up
remember that she's a fucking
tyrant who arrests
children for future
crimes that they haven't committed yet
wow what an inspiring superhero
for little girls to emulate
thank god we have all this
diversity now
so that we can have
female superheroes and then
ruin them with terrible comic
book stories that make no sense
and make them seem like irredeemable
monsters and idiots
holy shit
and I could almost understand
why Captain Marvel would feel this way
about it and want to be
you know misgovernment
arrest people for future crimes
because she does come from like a militaristic
background
she was like an air force military lady
but fucking star lord
I mean you know
star lord he's basically Han Solo
he's a
galactic scamp a space pirate
a scoundrel a scruffy nerf herder
a fucking rogue
he's a guy in a goofy red jacket
and a weird looking bug mask
who flies around the galaxy
fucking green alien girls
and who defeats super villains
by dancing like an idiot
to 70s funk pop
it makes no sense
for him to be on Captain Marvel's side here
and maybe I'm wrong
maybe there's some aspect of his
personality that I don't know about
because I haven't read enough guardians of the galaxy comics
I've only seen the movie
something that sets some kind of precedence
for why he would be down to clown
with this insane fascist
ideology of arresting people
for future crimes which seems to go
against like the very basis
of the character I don't know
but personally I don't fucking buy it
imagine the movies
trying to get away with this shit
like turning all of these beloved characters
and superheroes
into a bunch of bumbling fascists
as though the audience
is still somehow supposed to find
these characters likeable
like imagine that this is guardians of the galaxy
2 star lord is going around
with Captain Marvel busting into people's
houses and arresting them
for future crimes
try and put a Jackson 5 soundtrack to that shit
see how fucking heartwarming it is
a fucking montage
of star lord breaking into people's
houses and swatting people
A B C
it's as easy as 1 2 3
as Batista's power bombing
your fucking grandma through a coffee table
because she might
shoplift at some point in the future
she might be at the
she might be at the self checkout
and forget to pay for an apple
so we
gotta fucking Groot Stomp that bitch
in the spine
grandma can't get away with it again
this is a job for the guardians
of the galaxy
candy girl
you are my world
god every fucking Jackson 5 song
is the same
I'm just picturing this movie now
of just nonstop
horrible brutal
fascist violence
it's all in black and white like Schindler's
list but still set to the
soundtrack of the first movie
I
hooked on a feeling
it's just like a slow motion
nightmare of the guardians
of the galaxy busting into a
kindergarten class and shooting up
the place because they got a vision
that one of the kids might push
another one of the kids off a swing set
at the playground so the guardians of the galaxy
are bursting into a kindergarten classroom
and just shooting up the place
you know the hot kindly teacher
in her early 20s rocket raccoon
puts a fucking bullet in her head
Drax is Batista bombing
kids all these kids are getting
mangled and crippled and killed
massive bloodshed
and once again
the day is saved
thanks to the guardians of the galaxy
fuck this comic
okay
god damn
I think that's enough Civil War 2
talk
Christ this podcast is going long
I definitely do not
intend for every panel cast
to go this long
because Jesus it's been fucking two days
I've been recording this now
what's next
I still have a couple more comics I want to get to
that were cool this week
fucking uh okay
so the next
comic that I read this week
I'm fucking sliding all over the place in this fucking chair
why do they make chairs
with wheels on them what is the point of this
fuck
Jesus
oh lord help me Jesus I'm
tipping over I'm tipping
come on
fuck it
okay
ugh
and I wonder why these things go long
okay the next comic that I read
was Miss Marvel
Miss Marvel
number 12
and um this was actually
this was a good comic
this was a nice little
heartwarming a good
decent little kind of one shot
in the midst of this
you know epic retardation
of Civil War 2
that is sort of fucking up
every other comic on the stands
in the midst of all that there is
still room for
little character stories having to do with it
uh you know branching out
from this conflict that
in and of themselves
are decent
so uh Miss Marvel
this character is another
relatively new character
she's only been around for a couple of years
um Kamala Khan
was a little
Pakistani teenager living in New Jersey
and she got superpowers
and her hero was Miss Marvel
and she idolized all the superheroes
but particularly
Captain Marvel
so Captain Marvel said you can call yourself
Miss Marvel I can I'll give you the name
she she earned the name
Miss Marvel and so
her role in the Marvel Universe
is sort of like the forefront
of the next generation of superheroes
even though the problem with that
is that the next generation of superheroes
will never be
the current generation of superheroes
so they're kind of an eternally
unfulfilled promise because of the way
the comics are you know
Spider-Man and Iron Man and Captain America
and the main guard they're always going to be around
so when you have characters like this whose
purpose is that they're the younger generation
of superheroes
it's kind of an inherently
unfulfilling idea because
it's never really going to come to fruition
no matter how much time passes
they're always going to be
the younger generation of superheroes
you know that's how you end up with a teen titan
situation where
nobody knows what to do with like Beast Boy
and Raven and Starfire so now it's
they've been around for like fuckin 80 years
but somehow they're still teenagers
because you know they get
stuck in that next generation
teenager hole
and not the kind of teenager hole I like
HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA
HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA
Ben, one of the more successful ones, she's one of the few of that type of character that has
succeeded in being her own character and feeling like she has an actual personality and a reason
for being, and she's popular. People like her. Um, her and X-23, who's currently Wolverine,
those are the only two, I think, of the diversity Avengers that have been well-received, that seem
like they are actual characters with their own stories and their own, you get what I'm saying.
So the story of Ms. Marvel, number 12, is that this whole Civil War 2 event thing has been going
on and all of its ramifications are ruining everything. Um, Ms. Marvel has lost faith in
her idol, Captain Marvel, because she sees that Carol is turning into a fascist lunatic with this
pre-cog shit. So she says, fuck you to Captain Marvel, she strikes out on her own, and also she's
feeling bad and down in the dumps, because her best buddy, whose name I forget, best buddy,
Buddy Buddieson, is his name, is um, in the hospital, he got hurt in some superhero battle,
he goes, I don't want to hang out with you, we can't be friends anymore, because I'm sick of
getting sucked up into your superhero bullshit, or something like that, I don't know, but basically
she's feeling real down in the dumps right now, she's taking her lumps right now, she's
turned her back on her idol, Captain Marvel, her best friend don't want her no more, she's got nowhere
to go, she's feeling lost, she's feeling vulnerable, so this issue is sort of like a little one-shot
finding herself issue, she's traveling abroad, she's trying to find the real America in Pakistan,
she's getting on a little plane, and uh, she's going to her ancestral home of Pakistan, all by
herself, she's going to spend a few weeks hanging out with her grandma, and her extended family,
and just try to find herself, gotta find the real America man, you know that's the problem with all
of these event comics, all of these superheroes, you know, the civil wars, the Avengers versus X-Men,
all of these goofy manufactured conflicts, it just comes off like all of these superheroes and
beloved characters have forgotten the face of their fathers and lost sight of the real America,
and I want it back, we gotta bring the real America back to comics, that's my platform, that's what
I'm running on when I run for president in a decade or so, or a couple decades, when I'm old enough,
when I'm fucking 89 years old, that seems to be the minimum age for a presidential candidate in
this country, make comics great again, find the real America, put it back in my comics, so Kamala's
going through the airport, she's having a shitty time, you know, she's getting hassled by airport
security, she's looking all glum, she's looking all sad, she gets to Pakistan, she meets her family,
and it's so, it's so heartwarming, you know, seeing this reunion with all of her extended
relatives and stuff, I mean, we the reader, we've never seen these characters before, we don't know
these characters, we're being introduced to them, but it effectively feels like a sort of homecoming,
like, oh I haven't been in Pakistan since I was a little girl and I'm back and I'm with my grandma,
my abuela, that's a Pakistani word right, abuela, and it's a really great little character story,
because as she's hanging out here in Pakistan and she's trying to get her head straight and
ruminating on all of this, you know, tragic stuff that's been happening around her with all the
superheroes in America fighting each other, it's really going into, like, her character and her
personality and her unique little struggles, and she talks a little bit about, like, when she's
conviting with her abuela and she says, in New Jersey, I always feel like I'm a foreigner,
but here in Pakistan, I feel like I'm too American, so she's got that whole, you know,
ethnic American, caught between two worlds thing, you know, I can sympathize because I myself have
always felt caught between two worlds because of my ethnicity, I'm half Irish and half French
Canadian, so part of me just wants to feel white, but the other part of me just wants to feel really
white, and I feel like I don't belong anywhere, if only I had some of that minority privilege,
that the blacks are always lording over me, oh, look at me, I'm black, I feel like I belong to
a community, you don't know how good you have it, we whites are alone, damn it, we're cast into the
world, derelict, and without a place to truly call our own, there's no white superheroes anymore,
there's no representation for my people, there's nowhere for us in today's America,
and that's why we gotta find the real America, that's why we gotta make a great
again, that's why I'm voting for Trump, okay, the next comic I read, oh Jesus,
I just ate, I took another break and I ate a shitload of ramen, I ate so much fucking ramen,
the most ramen that's ever been put into a growing boy in the history of the world,
oh god, let me lay down, I need to lay down on the couch, oh Jesus,
oh, I just, I recently discovered that my microphone, the cord on my microphone is long
enough that it can reach to my couch and also my mattress, so this is gonna change my fucking life,
people, this, I can already tell, this is a revolution in podcasting technology right here,
you know, I'm sorry, I can't bring the pop filter over here, so there might be a little bit of,
you know, that going on, but aside from that, this feels, this feels good, I could definitely
get used to this, oh god, oh there's so much fucking ramen in me, oh, okay,
just a second, let me fucking get my brain back,
it is recording right, that's the one bad part, I can't see if it's actually recording or not,
so everything that I'm saying, I mean, I can't see the computer from here, so for all I know,
for all I know that I could just be talking to a microphone that's not even,
that's not even on right now,
what is going on outside, I hear thunder and lightning and motorcycles or some shit,
god damn, the wind is howling out there like fucking sleepy hollow, it sounds like the,
the sounds of the planet screaming in Final Fantasy VII, I swear to god, I can hear that exact sound
effect outside my window, okay, so next up is my comic of the week, the best comic of all the
comics that came out this week, it is, none other than, I'm gonna make a drum roll with my feet on
the coffee table over here, this is my drum roll, the comic of the week, this is a bad drum roll,
the vision number 12, yes, the final issue of what has been a momentous run, a story for the ages,
a tour de force, a legend, a saga on par with some of the greats, this has been like consistently the
most impressive comic coming out recently and it just finally had its last issue, the story has
been wrapped up and what a story it has been, so if you don't know who the vision is, the vision is
the data of the Marvel universe, he's a robot man who wishes that he could be more like a man man,
he is the Avengers resident robot dude, he was created by Ultron, oh my god, I'm gonna shit my
pants, oh my god, I'm gonna have a baby, a shit baby, oh, so the villain of the second Avengers
movie, Ultron, the big scary robot guy, in the movie he was created by Tony Stark, but in the comics,
Ultron was created by Hank Pym, the original Ant-Man, one of the founding members of the Avengers,
Hank Pym was in the Ant-Man movie, but he was not Ant-Man, Scott Lang was the Ant-Man in the
Ant-Man movie because he's the current Ant-Man, the Paul Rudd character was like an apprentice of
Hank Pym in the movies, there's little tiny differences in the movies in the comics, but you
know you can wrap your head around them if you really make an effort to, if you read the shit,
I don't know if I can, but so Ultron was created by Hank Pym, he was like the first like real
artificial intelligence, but Ultron turned out to be a fucking asshole, he was he was a petulant
entitled bastard, he wanted to destroy the Avengers, destroy the world, he was a villain,
he fought the Avengers a million times, eventually Ultron made a robot of his own,
this robot would go on to become the vision, and so in an ironic twist of fate, Hank Pym creates
Ultron who turns out to be evil, then Ultron creates the vision to further his evil agenda,
but the vision turns out to be good, and the vision joins the Avengers and becomes a superhero,
one of the most beloved members of the Avengers and saved the world 37 times over his career as a
superhero, as he often reiterates throughout this series, I am the vision of the Avengers, I have
saved the world 37 times, 37 in a row, the vision is not totally a robot, he's not technically an
android, he is what's called a synthesoid in the Marvel universe, so I think he's a you know
kind of an android, but he does have some human characteristics, you know his skin is that sort
of metallic pink color, but it is skin, um he does presumably have a penis, I'm guessing, I mean he
was married, he was married to the Scarlet Witch for a number of years, and they did have children,
so I'm assuming he's got a dick, fucking robot dick, fucking android dong, give Wanda some of that
swinging android dong, android dong, android dong, android dong, android dong, android dong, android
dong, android dong, android dong, android dong, android dong, android dong, android dong, android
dong. Synthesoid winner, he's more like a sexazoid is what he is, he he goes all night, he makes the
He makes the ladies scream!
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhh
So that's who the vision is and what he's about, basically.
He's a peace-loving, philosophical, you know, compassionate, stoic robot guy with an Android
DONG!
Personally, the character has never connected with me that well, because, you know, it's
hard as a reader not to just see him as a robot.
I think the movie did a good job of stressing how human he is, but up until that point, you
know, it's very easy to play the old Avengers game on Sega Genesis or to see him in a comic
and just go, well, yeah, I know Captain America and Iron Man, but who's this, uh, he's just
a robot guy, right?
I don't get it.
Like, well, it's very easy to not understand the character vision, and I didn't really
understand the character of the vision for a long time.
I mean, like I said, he's basically just the Marvel Universe's version of data, but
there's already a data in my mind, so there wasn't really enough room to love another
android character, I guess.
It's already full.
I've got data up there.
I've got Android 18.
She's a babe.
And I think what it really comes down to, the reason why the vision never impressed
me in the past, is because he just never had his own series that was good or interesting.
He never had any.
There never seemed to be any interesting stories about the vision.
He was always just kind of there.
He always, he's always just the robot guy in the Avengers.
He never came off like a flawed character before.
He never came off that three-dimensional.
He always just came off to me as, you know, he's stoic and he's calm and he is super
powerful and he's just there.
My point is I was a fool.
Like so many before me, I was caught up in my own humanity.
I was so arrogant about humanity, I could not see the pathos of a robot man, blinded
by the outside, judging a book by the cover, judging a synthesoid, not by the content of
his character, but by the, the robots, the parts of him that are robots.
You, you, whatever.
Fuck this.
Abandon this whole joke.
You get what I'm saying.
I'm abandoning this bit.
Get to the fucking point already.
You're yelling at your fucking computer screen.
I hear you.
So, so what this story has been about.
It's over now.
You can read the whole thing.
It's a self-contained, it's 12 issues.
It's a, it's an, it's a complete story and it's so goddamn good.
It really feels like this character, if you didn't appreciate or understand the character
before, read this and you'll have a totally new appreciation for the vision because he
finally has like a defining quintessential story, you know, like it's so easy to point
to Batman and go, if you want to understand Batman, here's the Dark Knight Returns or
here's the killing joke or here's year one or RIP or whatever happened at the Cape Crusader
or if you want to understand Spider-Man, there's Craven's Last Hunt or the death of the Stacey's
or, you know, all these characters as iconic as they are are only iconic because of the
strength of their stories.
They've all had those definitive runs.
Ven is never had one before now and this story feels like a definitive run for the character.
It starts out, the vision has created a family for himself.
Hank Pym created Ultron, Ultron created the vision and now the vision is creating a wife
and kids in his own image.
He creates a beautiful vision wife for himself named Virginia.
He creates a beautiful vision son, Vin.
He creates a beautiful vision teenage daughter, Viv.
So the vision has created a family for himself in his quest to become more human and live
as a human and understand what it is to live on this planet like the rest of us.
So he creates his cool, synthesoid family and he moves into a house in the suburbs and the
first issues are just, you know, him and his family, you know, this family of robot people
hanging out in the suburbs, getting into their neighbors and stuff.
So the vision is trying to live with this family in the suburbs and trying to be like
a regular person and of course it doesn't take long for all of it to go tragically awry.
An old supervillain of the Avengers called Grim Reaper attacks the house when vision
is away and so in self-defense his wife Virginia kills the Grim Reaper.
She murders him.
He's dead and she doesn't know what to do.
She's worried that there'll be repercussions or she won't be tried fairly because she's
a synthesoid or whatever.
So she hides the body and she's trying to keep the secret and unbeknownst to her, you
know, a neighbor saw her do it and filmed her doing it.
So now she's got to confront him and she's got and so anyways long story short, all kinds
of shit goes wrong.
Just to confront him, another, the neighbor dies, the neighbor's son dies.
Just every worst possible way that this wonderful little life the vision is trying to carve
out for himself could horribly fall apart in the span of like a couple months.
You know, this one unfortunate act of Virginia in self-defense killing the Grim Reaper spirals
out of control and next thing you know there's a dead kid and a dead neighbor and it's like
what the fuck is going on and like the Avengers become suspicious of him.
So they send this guy, Victor Mancha, who is sort of like another like vision, synthesoid
robot themed hero.
I think he's like also an Ultron creation.
So maybe he's like the vision's brother.
I don't really know much about that character, but he's like a guy with robot parts.
Anyways, they send him to spy on the vision and that goes wrong too.
So next thing you know, Victor, the Avengers spy who's sent to see what's going on at the
vision, he accidentally kills the vision's son.
So now we've got a fucking dead supervillain, we've got a dead neighbor, we've got a dead
kid and we've got a dead son.
The vision's beautiful, synthesoid son, Vin, is dead and now Vision is so pissed off.
He's on a rampage.
He's going to fucking, you know, he's going to beat up the Avengers, he's going to find
Victor Mancha and his little cell and kill him.
He's going to commit a murder because he's grieving and he's angry.
The, you know, it says right there, right in the background of this panel cast, even
an android can cry right in the upper right corner.
Nobody knows the grief and rage of an android and his dog.
So the vision is just kicking everyone's ass.
He beats up all the Avengers at once and he goes to kill this guy in the fucking cell
to seek vengeance for the death of his son and that's where issue 12 begins.
With the question of will the vision commit this vengeful murder from which there can
be no going back.
And you know what?
I'm not even going to spoil it because you got to read it for yourself.
You need to read it for yourself.
You need to understand.
You need to witness this story and all its glory.
It's so good.
There's so much pathos.
It's so fucking well written.
It makes you feel for this character in a way that you never would have thought before
that you could feel for the vision.
It makes you, it really fucking grabs you and you're like, yes, I understand now vision.
How could I have been so blind to not see how great the vision is?
This is a story that asks the big questions, folks.
What is it that really connects us?
What is it that truly makes us human?
What does it mean to be human really?
And it really drives home the point that the vision is more human than he realized for
better or for worse.
And that's all I'll say about it.
Ain't going to spoil this one.
You should all read it.
It's your duty to read it.
It's your sworn duty, all of you.
I'm giving you a fucking homework assignment.
Everyone has to read the vision.
All 12 issues.
It's the best fucking comic.
It's the best story that I've seen come out in comics in quite a fucking while, a good
number of years at least.
I can definitely say that for sure.
And it's written so well.
Like the fucking, the narration and the dialogue is so rich and heavy.
It's not written like a comic book.
It's written like literature.
It really takes itself seriously and it handles the telling of this story with all the gravitas
that it needs to.
And it's really effective.
It feels like a hugely important story.
It's so non-comicbook-y.
It doesn't feel like the other Marvel comic books.
It doesn't feel like a typical superhero bullshit.
It's not bogged down by the stupid event comic.
It has nothing to do with Civil War II or any of that bullshit, you know, that corporately
mandated cross-company horseshit that infects every fucking comic with these retarded continuity
politics.
It's self-contained.
It's not out of continuity.
But it's also not bogged down by the current stuff that's going on.
But it definitely is nothing like any of the other superhero comics that you're going
to read right now.
It's not a fucking story about, oh there's a bad guy and we're going to go fight him
and punch him in the nose and that's how we'll defeat the bad guy.
It's a totally different kind of story.
It's just like this character-driven, suspenseful thriller.
And it's so down to earth and human for a story about a fucking Synthesoid with a robot
dick.
Oh god, it's so good.
Oh, it's the best thing I've ever read in my fucking life.
Oh god.
I think laying on this couch is messing my head up.
I need to get back to the fucking computer.
Ah, shit.
Oh fuck.
Anyways, I hope that I've sufficiently sold you all on that without spoiling the last
issue.
You know, it's a 10 out of 10 baby, it's the kind of thing you read it and once you're
done reading it you're like, yeah, that's why I like comics right there baby.
That's what it's all about.
You know, you take a character like the Vision who is like this weird sea-list Avenger in
a lot of people's eyes.
You know, this unrelatable sort of robot guy who's always just there as part of the team
but nobody really cares about him.
You take a character like that and you take your time telling a story about him that like
delves into what really makes him tick and sort of touches on these very human things
that everyone can relate to.
You know, stuff like family and loss and grief and rage and you take this character that
nobody suspected could have this kind of pathos and you imbue it, you imbue this captivating
complex characterization into this character that maybe he had all along it just took the
right writer to show us what a great character the Vision could truly be.
Vision number 12 people, comic of the week.
Everybody go out and find Vision number one, go to the fucking comic readers, I'll link
them in the description box.
Star with Vision number one, read the whole damn series.
That's your fucking homework for this week.
Everybody go enrich your lives with this piece of fucking literature that ought to be studied
in schools for the rest of time.
This modern masterpiece.
Okay, so, I've talked about a lot of comics this week, some good, some bad, some fantastic,
but there's one more comic that I wanted to talk about this week, one more comic that
came out that I think is worth a mention and that comic is...
Your fucking wolf cop number one, baby, I told you on the motherfucking wolf man, baby.
Everybody forgot about the wolf man, but the wolf man is here to stay, yeah, let me tell
you people about the wolf cop.
If you've been following the Ramelama Ding Dong on my Patreon feed, then you've probably
seen the wolf man talking about the wolf cop.
You've seen me praising the movie, you've seen me doing a review of the movie on my
Patreon and what a fantastical little piece of happenstance right here, that the week
I happen to see the wolf cop movie, there just happens to be a wolf cop comic coming
out to continue to franchise on this very eve.
That's what I call serendipity, baby, that's what I call a Ramelama Ding Dong.
Now in case you don't know, in case you ain't seen the movie, in case you ain't seen the
light yet, in case you ain't one of the chosen few enlightened individuals who know the saga
of the wolf cop, in case you do not know, I will inform you.
The wolf cop is the wolf man alter ego of Officer Lou Garoo.
He is a small town cop in a spooky town, he gotta fight shapeshifting witches and warlocks
all day every day, but luckily he happens to have the power of the wolf man on his side
and when that full moon rises high into the sky, you know it's about to get hairy up in
here, awoo!
The man turns into the wolf man and the wolf man turns, I said the wolf man turns into
the wolf cop daddy.
The wolf cop he kills people, he cuts their faces off with claws, he rips them into shreds,
he rips the entrails on, he feasts on the corpses, he takes his police cruiser and it
modifies it into a bad ass spooky wolf cop mobile.
And he goes out into the city and he solves crimes and he brutally viciously murders
criminals left and right, and he drinks like a fish, and he smokes cigarettes, and he fucks
beautiful women.
The wolf cop is a Trump supporter, he grabs the girl is by the pussy, cuz he's the motherfucking
wolf cop, and the wolf cop don't take no for an answer daddy, oh no, woo!
The wolf cop is a rapist, aw hell yeah, ah!
So wolf cop the comic issue number one, it opens up presumably after the movie, wolf cop
is driving around the road in his police cruiser wolf cop mobile with his best buddy.
Now right off the bat this part confused me a little bit because I gotta spoil the movie
for you right here, I gotta give a little spoiler right here, and I'm giving you a fair warning
because wolf cop is a masterpiece of film that everybody should see ten times and commit
to memory.
Every single frame of that masterpiece should be burned in your memory for all time baby,
but in case you haven't seen it I'm warning you right now, I gotta spoil the end of the
movie just a little bit to tell you what confused me about issue one of this comic, okay, so
at the end of the movie it is revealed that wolf cop's best buddy is actually a shape
shifting lizard man, and he was one of the bad guys, and wolf cop had to kill him.
That was a twist in the movie, a movie takes twists and turns that you don't always know
about going into it baby.
But I gotta admit if there was one flaw with the wolf cop feature film it was that I was
a little disappointed that his buddy turned out to be a lizard man who had to be killed
because the buddy and the wolf cop they had a wonderful chemistry together that really
made the film something special, their scenes together were funny and charming and wonderful
to watch.
So I was a little bit disappointed that it turned out to be a bad guy in the end, but
anyways wolf cop the comic issue number one it opens up and wolf cop is driving around
in his wolf cop mobile and there's his man right there.
So I gotta wonder man cause this don't make no sense something here don't add up.
How can he be there, how can there still be buddies, how can he still be alive when he
was a lizard man at the end of the movie wolf cop had to kill him last time.
They did not explain how he is somehow back from the dead and somehow they are unspeaking
terms again.
Don't get me wrong I am glad that he is back from the dead and they are buddies again.
It warms my heart to see because they have a good chemistry.
They got a buddy chemistry.
I like a buddy movie.
I like a road trip buddy movie.
I like a road trip buddy wolf cop movie.
I am not complaining but I do hope that at some point over the course of this comic book
series they do explain how this boy came back from the dead and why wolf cop in his
infinite wisdom chose to forgive him for his vile betrayal.
The wolf man is turning into the Babadook spook a little bit.
Sometimes the characters bleed into the other characters and I turn into Captain Barbosa
now.
All the characters they all start from the same voice and they branch out Miss Turner
and sometimes it gets a little confusing.
You best start believing in stupid podcasts Miss Turner.
You're in one.
But anyways back to the wolf man baby.
Now this is just issue one so I can forgive him for a lack of exposition.
Clearly they wanted to get right into the nitty gritty and right into the meat of the story
with an action packed first issue.
No time to sit around a diner table and talk about what led to these events.
I understand that but I do hope at some point they explain this glaring plot hole baby.
I'm the fucking wolf man.
Anyways the issue starts and he with his buddy going on a road trip into wolf cop cruiser
and he going down a road and suddenly a gang of bikers they come up and they're looking
for a scramble.
They're looking for a tussle.
They're looking for a rumble.
They're looking for a fight.
But of course they picked the wrong time daddy because once that moon gets up in the sky
you turn into a motherfucking wolf man.
And that wolf man ain't just a wolf man.
I've been telling you this whole time he is a wolf cop daddy.
He got a gun, he got a police car, he got boots and a shirt, he got a badge, he got
a bad attitude and he got a lot, a lot of whiskey to drink, he gonna drink all the booze
you got and he gonna do it with all the ladies too.
He drinking beer and his smoking cigarettes.
Do he like to party?
The answer is a yes.
Now I'm the crazy taxi guy.
It's time to pick a car and driver.
Wolf cop are you ready?
Here we go.
It's time to check out how you did the day.
Now let's take a look at class D lessons.
I can't believe it.
Is that your best come back and try again?
But anyway let me tell you what I was telling you before I was interrupted by the crazy
taxi man.
I was trying to tell you about the adventures of wolf cop baby.
Wolf cop he come and he fights him and then he takes those bikers back to where they came
from and it turns out they're working for a scary cannibal man and the cannibal man is
eating people so wolf cop got to fight the cannibal man now but it turns out he ain't
just no normal man he got a secret of his own.
The cannibal man turn into a giant were pig.
I said a were pig man and let me tell you this were pig is even bigger and scarier than
the wolf cop.
How can wolf cop defeat an enemy as big and vicious and large and in charge as the cannibal
were pig.
Quite easily it turns out wolf cop kicks the crap out of the were pig it kills him dead
real easy it only takes like one or two pages man.
So then after wolf cop killed a were pig that unsaved all the damsels in distress they open
the door and they save all the pretty girls and they run off to be somewhere better and
wolf cop he's a little bit banged up but he gonna be okay ain't nobody tougher or
meaner than the wolf cop and his buddy come up and he say we did it now let's get the
fuck out of here what we gonna do now wolf cop and wolf cop says drink and the buddy
give him a thumbs up he said god damn right buddy and that's the end of issue number one
of the motherfucking wolf cop and I am the wolf man daddy
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH