Hey, it's Digibro here. This big group decompression chamber was recorded by me, Tom Oliver, Best
Guy Ever, and Ben Saint a few nights ago. Originally, it was going to be a decompression
let's play video. The entire thing was recorded set to Ben playing a game called Dungeon Crawl
Stone Soup, which is this really unbelievably complicated and difficult to sort of parse
dungeon crawler roguelike game. We were just watching him play it while having this incredibly
lengthy discussion. Unfortunately, the video component of that was lost. All the footage
of Ben playing this game was lost to the ether, which is really unfortunate because a lot
of what Ben says in this is him reacting to things that have just happened in the game
when he speaks up every once in a while. We also addressed the game kind of explaining
it and what it looks like early on. This game is so esoteric and the visuals are so incredibly
minimal and bare bones and sort of difficult to even parse if you're watching from a distance
as I was while Ben was playing that losing the visuals isn't as big of a deal and most
of what Ben is reacting to he explains since it would not be even interpretable in the
video anyways. So yeah, I don't think we lost too very much. I hope that's the case anyways
and that you'll enjoy listening to this even without the video component, but if you want
to just maybe look at some videos of what Dungeon Crawlstone's Stone Soup looks like,
you'll be able to get an understanding of what we mean when we talk about it in the
few times that we do. But yeah, mostly this is three hours of totally unrelated discussion
about a broad range of topics and it was really fun and I hope you like it.
Hey everyone, it's Radcon2 and everyone else fell asleep before getting the Pleeve and
the Weeb done, so me, Ben St, best guy ever, Tom Oliver, and Digi Bro, we're all up in
his room and I'm showing them my favorite game of all time, Dungeon Crawlstone Soup,
the coolest game ever that I spent a year and a half trying to beat and I'm going to
be playing it and we're going to just... How long is the session of this game? Are you
going to lose a bunch of time? Okay, there's no way I'll win. Winning takes like 20 hours,
so I will just see how far I can get in however long we feel like going. Alright, so in this
game you pick a race in the class and I'm going to go with a favorite, I'm going to be
a gargoyle Earth Elementalist. I bet. Just out of curiosity, you haven't played this
game in a while. Yeah. Have there been major updates? I haven't, yeah, I mean I don't know
what they are, but I'm sure there have been some. Okay. So yes. Ben's plenty loud, we'll
turn that more towards us. Okay. Alright, so I've got my, I've got down in the bottom
right, I've got my equipment and shit up in the top right and my stats here in the middle
is the map. It's black, missing pixels. This looks completely incomprehensible. See, I'm
exploring the map. Wait, you're playing? I am playing right now. This is, this is the
major game. This is the game. This is the game. What the fuck? Emphasis on the gay.
I just have to, okay, I'm going to sort of have my spell situation. I really like retro
aesthetics, but I have my limits in terms of how primitive you can get before I just
kind of feel like- I think we're going to have to lean up, Tom, to be heard. I feel
like this is so old it predates my interest. This is an old ass game that has been continually
in development. It's not even that it looks old, it just is minimal as fuck. It just reads
as archaic to me. I mean, minimal. Ben played a lot of dwarf, whatever. I mean, what, what
era does this make you think of, Tom? I don't know, it just feels like MS-DOS era. It makes
me feel like 95. I'm trying to remember what my- Maybe it's a win 95 port of a DOS game.
Yeah, I guess so. I mean, I'm just thinking of video games that came out in 1995, most
of which are far more advanced than this. Right. Well, that's why I said DOS. I'm thinking
like something that started development in like 89 or something. I got a port to Windows
95 when DOS was like dying. Like Doom was a DOS game, right? Doom was a virtually a DOS
game. I feel like in 95, I played a lot of games that were out long before 95 because
we had a shitty computer. I didn't play any computer games ever again. And we didn't have
a console until, well, we might have had like a Super Nintendo at that time, I guess. My
history of video games was stupid as fuck. Yeah. I actually forget how to cast spells,
which is going to be a real problem for me. Shameful. Wait, what's that? Explain to me
what your role is, what your class is, and how you plan on winning. He's a man made of
rocks that throws rocks at people. Well, I don't just throw rocks. I'm an Earth Elementalist.
So I have a collection. I have, down here, I have 20 stones. I'm going to consume these
stones in order to cast stone spells. Everything you just said. Throw rocks. Whoa, what the
fuck was all that? That was auto-exploring. Okay, I found a goblin. What is this? The
game plays itself. Okay, okay. What is this nightmare reality you've sucked me into? Is
this door fortress too? Oh, I don't even, I don't actually know those spells. Oh my
god, how the fuck do I learn spells? The mouse is just sitting in the middle of the screen
and he doesn't even care. No, I left him. He's asleep. He's asleep. What, the mouse?
Oh, wait. The goblin, dude. Oh, the goblin. Oh, wait, is this picking up the cursor?
Yeah. That's fine. It's no big deal. Yeah, for this game, that makes sense. Okay, I have
to figure out how to learn spells. Well, the meantime, I am out of my dev. Hold on, I'm
going to take the cursor from you for just a second so I can put this. Go ahead. I want
to put this on top so I can see the game because I can't see much of it through you. The audience
doesn't know what I'm talking about but you can have the cursor back. Okay. Spell casting.
I mean, so the main deal with this game is that you're in a dungeon and you get to new
floors and you basically just explore until you encounter enemies and then you just deal
with them and you try to get stronger and level up so that you can face increasingly
hard hordes. Activate a memorized spell by pressing Z. Okay, but how do I memorize the
spell? I assume that the appeal of this is that it's hard to ship. No, no, that's how
I activate a spell. It is very hard to complete successfully. And so there's two main goals.
The first goal is to get the orb of zat and emerge victorious from within the place. I'm
too inexperienced. But that's the bitch way to beat the game. There is a much, much harder
way to beat the game. We just collect every single rune and then you do the same. You've
got to collect 15 demonic runes. Okay, so here I'm coming up on this. Oh shit, he woke up.
All right, all right. I'm going to cast the sandblast. Is this like a roguelikes when you die,
you're fucked? Oh, absolutely. All right. It's a brutal game. It is a roguelike. The mere
comprehension of the game is the most brutal part of it. I mean, there's plenty of text on the
bottom left that shows up to tell you generally what's going on. It looks like it's written in
fucking code. It kind of is. It's kind of the aesthetic. It's definitely going for DOS. The
trend is right now. This is a game for math nerds. Oh no. I wouldn't say math nerds. Ben
does have a degree in physics. True. This seems out of my depth. I'm an art guy. I'm out of
magic. You have to just stab this newt. Okay, okay. There's a certain brand of PC game that like
that that I've seen people who are into that kind of game and they're like a lot of them. And when
I look at them, I see nothing. I literally don't get it. Do you like binding of Isaac,
did you? No. No? Okay, because this is that, but way harder and way more complex. I fucking
love binding of Isaac. Yeah, Ben and I both love binding of Isaac. This seems a lot more like,
like binding of Isaac is considered like a rogue light. I was just wondering if you liked it at
all. It took me a long time to even get a grasp on what the term roguelike meant. I'm going to
explain something that's really interesting. In this game, in this game, you have to eat to
survive. Right. So right now you can see at the bottom, there's my inventory, but then down at
the very, very bottom right, I step over this goblin corpse and I can see that I'm at bottom right,
I'm standing on the goblin core. So I'm going to hit C to butcher it. And now I have meat in my
inventory. And I love to scale. I'm going to do the same to this newt. Okay, so I have meat. Now
that meat will go bad if I'm not careful. So I need to like continually be exploring. This sounds
like Ben describing his everyday life. This is why Ben's good at what he's doing right now.
This is just training for real life. If I'm not careful, it will go bad. I'll eat it anyways.
That's right. All right. Now let me, let me see here. I got to decide which like weapon. Oh no,
I want to be, I want to be, you want to throw your rocks at people. No, no, no. I want to be
casting spells, but I do want to be. Just know that the gargoyle is too dumb to throw a rock.
I played, where is that right now? I played this game a few times on Ben's suggestion and, and just
hit a wall of there being too many fucking menus and buttons. There used to be a thing. Okay,
there are cursed weapons in the game. And if you equip one, you cannot unequip it until you find a
scroll and cursing. Oh, that sounds awful. Well, here's the real kicker about that. Early on,
if you get cursed, you need, if you get cursed with say a club, you cannot equip a dagger in
order to butcher an animal. So if you get cursed with a bludgeoning weapon, you can't hold a
cutting weapon to butcher corpses and you will starve. And you don't know. If only we had another
hand to use something. They actually changed it. They actually, that used to be a thing like you
had to have a cutting weapon in order to butcher corpses. Now they change it. So your character
always has a knife and it doesn't actually stop you. But it used to actually kill you early on
in the game. Pretty interesting. I'm looking for. So to explain in brief to Tom what rogue is
rogue was an entirely text based game. Okay, that was like, you know, something like this, where
you're in a dungeon exploring us. Yeah, but it was, but it was randomly generated each time. And
and it's like, you know, you, you. Yeah, the main point is that if you die, you lose and there's
lots of traps, like you have to try to make it through the dungeon without, you know, getting
killed in traps and losing your weapons and shit and make it to the end. Okay. And so anything
that's like that in any way, which these days mostly means a hard game that you die, you know,
if you die, you go back. Yeah. But like the idea essentially is that each run is different
because you pick up different shit. Right. And it's like, it's usually randomly generated.
Right. Yeah. And so you, you never know what kind of powerups you're going to get on your way to
the end. And binding of Isaac sort of like, like there's, there's a newer genre that people call
it rogue light, where it's stuff that's like, it takes some of those elements, but kind of
yeah, it's a little bit more pick up and play. And binding of Isaac was such a huge hit that
there's a lot of those now like FTL is another one and shit like that risk of rain is kind of one
of those, which I was the biggest fan of risk of rain. Yeah. But you used to be too glitchy to
even play risk of rain is aesthetically beautiful for sure. Yeah, that's true. Mechanically deep. I
have a follow up question that might be open up a can of worms. I'm going to regret, but I'm
going to, I'm going to go here anyway is, is to, to you guys were both involved in this
conversation and I observed. Yeah. Why are you okay with the term rogue like, but Metroidvania
pisses you off. I feel like they're kind of both. Don't look at me. I'm fine with both of them.
Because I, I listened to your argument about Metroidvania and it felt like kind of what you
just said is the same thing with Metroidvania. Like the idea when you say, because I don't play
rogue likes, I do have a very specific concern with that. And it's that he likes two very
different things about Metroid and Castlevania. And he finds the term, you know, the only
muddling, the only real problem with it is the fact that I really love Metroid games. And the
Castlevania games that are called Metroidvania are, I mean, I don't even hate them, but they're
just they're a different kind of game from Metroid where Metroid is really just Metroid has no
RPG elements really. It's just an action platformer where every once in a while you get a new
ability. Most of those abilities are not just for combat. Most of them are for exploration.
Well, there's some of that in some Castlevania. Even, even like the, even the beam upgrades,
you know, like, you get an ice beam, it lets you free enemies to walk on.
Everything has a purpose aside from combat. Combat is very secondary.
Whereas like Castlevania, Ario Sorrow, for instance, has like, it has a leveling system that is
like, okay, I played through about half of Ario Sorrow. And there was one part where I got to
death, and I couldn't beat him. So I ran back to the start of the game, because there's an item
shop there. So I could buy potions. And then I ran back. But in the time that I made that run,
I went up two levels, and I destroyed death. Okay, like I couldn't beat him before. And then as
soon as I gained two levels, I just fucking destroyed him. And the only reason I gained two
levels is just the process of going to the game. RPGs have that quality. I get that 100%. And I'm
totally with you. But my only counterpoint would be, because I think everything you just said is
100% valid. Metroid and Castlevania are completely different games. I just think when someone just
like, well, I mean, in terms of like, how combat works and how progression and stuff works, there's
definitely different kind of mechanics there. But when someone says a Metroidvania, I think,
just like you said in a roguelike, they're talking about permadeath and stuff. I think when you say
Metroidvania, they just mean an open and connected world with a grid-like map. I think that's all
the term really means. Axiom Verge is a Metroidvania, and that describes it. But it also is a
Metroid game. Well, there are some that lean more towards the Castlevania side. Right. But the
upsetting part to me is that I want to play all the Metroids. Would you rather have a Metroid-like
and a Castlevania-like? I would. Would that make you more satisfied? I would even be satisfied
if like Metroidvania can stay. Just also, if a game is just Metroid, just call it a Metroid
clone. You know, like Axiom Verge, if Castlevania didn't exist, there would be no reason to put
vania in the title of Axiom Verge. It's just a Metroid game. If Castlevania didn't exist, well,
sure. It does. I think the thing is, is that I think a lot of people who play Castlevania probably
enjoy that exploration and like progressively unlock the world. And we'll go to Axiom Verge
because of thevania in it. Maybe, but like the thing about Metroid is that like so much of it
is about the environmental design and like learning your way around is like learning about this
world. There we go. There we go. I finally killed the worm that's been dogging me. You're exploring
this alien planet that's got all this kind of personality to it and like there's distinct
worlds in there. You go to Norfair and that's like a fireplace and you explore there and you get
an ice beam which lets you freeze these molten lava things. In Castlevania, there's no connection
between any of the fucking hallways you go down. And it's all hallways. That's not true. There are
clearly themed areas in Dracula's Castle. In Aria of Sorrow? Absolutely. The clock tower.
There's the clock tower and that's like it. It's not it. The clock tower is the only place that has
like environmental challenges in the whole game. I'm not even interested in arguing about it,
but there are definitely different areas with different features. I would pretty much every
Metroid is probably more thematically distinct in terms of its locales by nature of because it's a
castle versus a planet. They are less different from each other. In Castlevania, there's times
where you'll be going down a hallway that's like a courtyard and you'll fight a couple of
skeleton dogs or something and then like a giant Medusa that has nothing to do with the environment
you're in and then you'll go through another door and now you're just in a totally different place
fighting totally different enemies that again have nothing to do with the place you're in.
And I'm not saying this is like makes it a bad game or anything. It's just not like Metroid.
The enemies you fight would be relevant to that spot and it would be like it's about exploring,
whereas Castlevania is really about combat. It's really about the leveling and the hit
sparks and sound effects and the pleasure of it. I absolutely agree. I think again I'm not to
read it myself, but I think the only point that I think the only distinction Metroidvania is trying
to make is it's talking about how the world map is laid out and nothing more. This slug is shooting
darts at me. Now there is one game... He's more than he appears. I will say... I can get behind a
door though and he won't be able to follow me. I will say that Dark Souls I think just is Metroidvania
because it is in every way it embodies both games. In fact it embodies all of them. It completely
embodies Metroid. It completely embodies original Castlevanias and it completely embodies the new
Castlevanias because it also has that combat system. So it's not that I think it's invalid
to suggest that there are games that are legitimately a combination of Metroid and Castlevania,
but like when people say Metroidvania it can either refer to these games that are exactly
like the Castlevania games. Like what's that one called Abyssal City? It's Valdestoria Abyssal
City is a game that's described as a Metroidvania and you play it and it just plays exactly like
the new Castlevania games. Axiom Verge is described as a Metroidvania, but it plays
exactly like Super Metroid. You know so to me there's kind of two genres here that are being
called the same genre. I think it's just supposed to be referring to the way the games laid out and
it's up to you to use like your brain to read one or two sentences and make the rest of the
distinction yourself. Well how am I supposed to know just based on like the description on the
Steam page? There's these really cool things you're probably kind of familiar with them because
you do it for a living but it's called videos and they really kind of clear that up pretty
quick. Further reading is just the only thing. Yeah. But you know what? If you make a purchase
decision based on one word. But I only buy impulse. I'll tell you that. Well then that's a personal
problem and you need that. I do think that I mean I haven't played all these games but I've played
massive amount of Metroids and Castlevanias and to call Axiom Verge a Metroidvania as opposed
to a Metroid clone is kind of just wasting everyone's time. Yeah. Just call it it's just a
Metroid clone. It is literally Metroid. That's what it is. There's no Castlevania element to it
at all. Yep. Well except in the elements that they are shared but you might as well just cut that
out and just say it's a Metroid clone. I think that's what most people mean when they use the
term. And the same is true. I guess that's my point. It's just that the term is a meme and people use
it a lot. I guess. And there's also the game Zio Drifter is also just Metroid and like it was
what made me kind of come to this realization about Metroidvania. It's why it bothered me
because I made a video about Zio Drifter and Axiom Verge and how each of the like it was called
Ways to Clone Metroid and like I at one point I had thought should I call this like you know
like Metroid like different kinds of Metroidvania but then I was like but there's novania. They're
just Metroid games. Yeah. You know and I think someone had even said like in the comments like oh
you mean Metroidvania and I'm like no these are just Metroid. It's just a Metroid game. I think
I still stand by my original argument and that it's just to describe the way the maps laid out
but I will grant you that a Metroid like and a Castlevania like would be more useful than
Metroidvania. You know I mean when I made my video in response the point I was trying to make was
like you're saying Tom that I think what they're trying to convey is that when they call something
in Metroidvania they're specifically describing that overlap. It's the overlap that is being
described by that term which does leave out things. I think it would be fair to keep that
Metroidvania is not a term that has to die but it would be nice if people distinguished
between the two more. It makes sense to me. Mostly like fans and reviewers who just throw
around Metroidvania all the time to describe games. Well we shouldn't we shouldn't we shouldn't be
listening to them at all anyways. You just told me to watch reviews to find out which one. No no I
didn't mean reviews I said like you go to the Steam page and you can watch your video like oh this
is what the game plays like. It's clearly Metroid versus Castlevania versus a mix of both.
I definitely played Axiom Verge because it looked exactly like Super Metroid. I just I just I just
don't I don't even think you on your at your worst would look at it look at the word Metroidvania
like I'm buying this because I saw this word I was doing any more research. I mean there's I have
had plenty of times where I saw the word and then watched the video and then determined which one
you see then you solved your problem but then I got autistically mad. Well you know we all have our
things. What's what's going on here Ben. But there are a lot of people who are very up in arms
about the proliferation of Broglie. I've encountered a unique monster that I've never heard of before
and I have no idea how strong he is. Robin? I don't know what he does. He's gonna steal from you and
give to his god monster friends. He drank a potion and became more agile. See that's over there that's
a magic amulet on the right and I want that but I'm scared of this guy. He's coming for you. But
it's okay because I've just learned a new spell. What is it? It's on a way fast. No it's um I have
stone arrow which is a much stronger version of sandblast. This guy's got a whole fucking goblin
cadre with him and that makes me nervous. Understandably. You know Tom actually now that you've made me
reflect on this I do I hate myself for being up in arms about the metroidvania term and here's why
because I'm realizing that the reason I feel strongly about this is the same reason that people
complain about the term roguelike. It's a reason I hate which is a fear of evolution because there's
people who a lot of people have their niche and they just want things to fit into that niche
and when that niche starts to evolve and no longer have like all the elements they want it to have
then it's like they feel this disconnect from it where other people might like you know some people
might like the rogue lights for the same reason they like rogue but then there's other people who
are like uh it's not actually like rogue it's it's more dumb down you know. It depends on what you
like you what you enjoyed about rogue. I mean it's a lot like and I can make two music comparisons
the the most obvious one would be new metal which is where you know metal the only reason that the
term new metal literally means not metal and it was invented by metal fans because when like Slipknot
and Lincoln Park and all those bands came out metal fans were so mad that people were calling it
metal that they came up with the term new metal so that people would like say like you know this is
not metal because we don't respect it even though like like there's there's certain like okay I would
not consider Lincoln Park a metal band even though there's there's a lot of metal influence there
I think it would be more fair to call them like uh like a metal hip hop fusion as opposed to making
up a term that is clearly intended to slag off the genre like new metal but like I don't fight
segments there's certain Slipknot songs that are indistinguishable from metal there is no
reason they should not be considered metal other than that metal fans don't like Slipknot
and therefore yeah yeah you know and the same goes now for Prague where you know progressive rock in
the 70s there's like a there's sort of specific kind of way it sounds but then with 2000 stuff like
all of it's considered Neo Prague or New Prague like Kohit and Cambry and the Mars Volta and stuff
like that like nobody will just call it progressive rock even though the Mars Volta is every bit as
experimental as any 70s progressive rock band like hang on hang on one second let me let me explain
what's going on right here this Sigmund is really bad yeah he's all he hangs that he's pretty strong
and he hangs out on low level floors it's his character description is specifically that he
hangs out on low level floors because he's a dick who likes fucking with weak adventurers yeah and
those words all in the description dick who likes fucking well oh let's let's see his description
um an elder the elder of a pair of brothers who came for the orb no one knows what Sigmund saw in
the dungeon to drive him mad but his shrewd magical status and wicked scythe and i'll leave little
time for his his what okay this is not what yeah he changed it they fucking changed it let's both
shit i hate when they change things he used to be just an asshole okay anyway anyway so he just cast
a spell on me and confused me which is absolutely terrible and i'm really scared right now so i think
my only hope my best chance is i have all these scrolls that i have picked up and they're unidentified
i don't know what these scrolls do the only way to learn what they do is to either use a scroll of
identification on them or just use them and see what happens so i'm going to just start using scroll
totally at random oh man and just hope that one of them is a teleportation scroll that will get me
the fuck out of here and what are your odds on that oh no i can't i'm too confused you're too confused
he confused me and now i can't do it now you can't read oh he cast a spell and now i'm more confused
oh god just get to the upstairs okay you know if i get up the if i get to these stairs a puff of
flame i'm really fucked that really oh god oh god don't go that way oh god oh oh he's coming for
your butt please hold so close if it doesn't teleport okay can i get up there yes i fucking got away
thank god okay that was that was intense that was the first comprehensible thing that's happened
in this game well i have wanted to take the time to explain all right i think i'm gonna skip that floor
i don't want to fight that guy i want you to on your channel sometime do a playthrough of this game
where you just narrate everything you're doing that'd be interesting maybe i will that'd be pretty
cool maybe i will because so far i have had literally no idea we're talking about like a 20
hour process though yeah i mean he doesn't have to beat the game in one video yeah yeah but think of
all the mid-roll ads you could have on that now we're talking oh dear i don't have enough magic
but yeah so i think i think the people who the people who are calling games like uh like like
ftl or and all that stuff rogue light are just people who don't want their niche to become mainstream
and for those people like like because it's kind of a rite of passage to like be i'm into something
so extreme like rogue you know like right i'm i'm i'm into this thing that like takes effort to get
into and these people who would probably never play rogue who are playing binding of isaac because
it's more accessible like they feel insulted that those people are saying they play roguelikes you
know when roguelike used to mean something so hardcore but digi isn't your criticism of the term
metroidvania uh just contingent on the fact that it it simply is what happened he's oh he threw a
he threw with the goblin at you he threw a goblin at me badass because the goblin thrower
yeah this guy's new this guy's new i'm just gonna i'm just gonna take some potshots at him as i run
towards the staircase yeah that's fair to try and like weaken him for later you were saying oh i was
just saying isn't your criticism of of the the metroidvania specifically based on the fact that
if for you it makes it harder for you to find what you're looking for in terms of you know
specifically metroid which isn't so much an issue of stopping evolution or anything it's just that
it's confusing on some level it's yeah it's just i'm upset at the idea of polluting this genre i care
about okay so that's that i want more metroid and instead i'm getting castle metroidvania and i'm
i'm sort of afraid that like when like for instance uh you highly recommended me shantae the pirates
yes i did and you said it was a metroidvania but then i stand by i started playing it and it is
identical to a castlevania game that's correct that's correct there would be no reason to call it
well metroid well castlevania itself is a metroidvania right yes but that's what he's talking about
if in the same way that i said that if axiom like if castlevania didn't exist there'd be no reason
to call axiom verge a metroidvania yeah or a metroidvania rather this you can call shantae
exactly like there'd be no reason to say it's anything other than a castlevania game i'm gonna
for the term yes ben what's up i'm gonna put on this magic amulet and see what happens let's find
out it's a cursed amulet of inaccuracy that that should be all right that's not that's not the
worst thing in the world it's still not good you know but the thing about shantae though is that
there are a lot of elements i'm just i'm just gonna start identifying shit it's probably a good idea
shantae specifically does contain a lot of things that are quite metroidy specifically you get
you get major power upgrades like you do in a metroid game that increase your mobility
in you know major steps along the game which i would argue are very there's stuff like that in
aria sorrow like you gain a double jump that's true that's true and you gain a little like uh the
thing that slows your descent little wings yeah the bat the bad thing and i'd say there's there's
more environmental challenges i guess we're talking about an issue of degrees
i think the problem is is that you just want to play more one of those scrolls with a scroll of
remove curse so i can get rid of the amulet well just like i feel like castlevania games the appeal
of them is very grindy and i'm not as into that whereas i agree whereas like like like with aria
of sorrow i realized like i made a video about that game ben ben's probably the only person who's
fucking seen it in the world i'd watch that i love aria of sorrow what is it well it's a very
critical critical very critical i will not watch it i just i just drank a potion and turned into a
tree into a tree yes you're fluttershy right now we went there i was i was gone up i was like no i
know that's gay i had to like process what you went by that oh really i'm so far out of wow
that's never gonna leave me i'm in too deep um anyway yeah a lot of my criticism is the same
thing that uh egoraptor talked about about like what the problem is with ever like castlevania
2 and and all the newer castlevanias which is just fascinating it's a game about running back and
forth across the world fighting lots of guys and the reason it's fun now as opposed to how it wasn't
two is because as he put it there's lots of hit sparks and sound effects and your weapons feel
good and it's really crunchy and awesome and you fucking slash these big guys like
it's it's yeah i fucking killed that guy and you gain like a thousand different weapons and a
million different ghost spirits and stuff yeah it's awesome and like you know i played through
like half the game and i just kind of got bored and stopped and then i watched like a video of
someone getting a hundred percent or no you know maybe i beat the game yeah but didn't do any of
the extra stuff because like i remember oh there's so much to do i remember getting really far and
maybe even beating it but then i looked at like a video of someone doing a 100% run and there's like
whole stretches of the castle i had oh so much i hundred percent of that game myself a couple
times there's so much there's all these secret bosses there's a thousand million weapons the ultimate
super mega boss oh and it made me realize that if you were someone who played this game in such a
way that you just kind of casually wander around and fight shit like forever and like tried to do
all the secret stuff it's a totally different game from the game that i was trying to play yeah
which is i'm fighting a snake right now one is kind of blow through one of the best perks of
being the gargoyles that i'm immune to poison so this guy is not that threatening oh actually he's
he's doing some kind of bad damage i don't like that i don't like that wait what's happening again
he's fighting a snake he's made of rocks so we can't be poisonous he's poisonous though he's a
poisonous serpent he's hitting hard dude i'm just gonna drink this potion of might a lot of the
castlevania games are our best played from a completionist standpoint and i got a lot of
enjoyment out of them doing it that way i mean i've i've i've been asked about this on these shows
before like why am i so bad at video games and why do i never beat them yeah and the reason is
that i with any media i am extremely impatient about it because i want to consume it and move on
yeah like i always feel anytime i i'm like working through one thing i feel like it's distracting me
from other things that i could be doing like like you know i just want to make a video i just
want to go do something else and and work through all this different stuff so when it when something
takes more than a couple days i get really antsy about it and i don't even if it's like even if
it's amazing you know and there's very few times like dark souls 3 is one of the only games that
like i beat it in two days and then i immediately started playing again you know i immediately
went on new game plus and made another character uh i beat it in a different way you know like i
think i beat it twice there's an altar either beat it twice i got most of the way through in a
second there's an altar of sif muna here sif muna is a pretty good god for a spellcaster but i'm more
i'm a sif muna is a god who just gives you lots of access to lots of spells cool i don't want to
worship her though because i'm going to worship vehumet who is specifically the god of destruction
magic he doesn't give you access to as many spells but he does like power up your destructive spells
and reward you for destroying things with magic so i'm not gonna i'm not going to start worshiping
sif muna can you is there anything you can do to unworship if you start worshiping someone
if you start worshiping someone you can renounce your religion but your god will um declare you
an affustate and curse you and take divine vengeance on you until they eventually like just
forget about it and they're like well whatever it's that's enough i see except for except for the
good there's three good gods well whatever that's enough there's three there's three good gods who
won't take vengeance on you unless you join an evil god and then their wrath will fall upon
how dangerous is the auto explorer you keep doing oh it's not dangerous at all because it stops when
literally anything of note happens yeah it's great so it just saves you time yeah digi i was gonna say
i think that's interesting how uh we we consume media differently because even just today i went on
a crazy tirade of cleaning the entire lower half of this house because i felt compelled to to make
sure it was all done and even when others told me to stop i simply could not bring myself to do so
i had to follow it through to the bitter end and uh yeah i just think that's all right the way we
play why are they telling you to stop well tom was cleaning i just felt so guilty he was cleaning
up all of our dishes as was victor as was victor and victor here's the thing victor and tom both
have the same kind of guilty conscience uh of like like if no one had done it that would have been
like like they would have felt a little guilty because they wanted it to get done but as soon as
someone's doing it it's like well i should have victor specifically mentioned that yeah it's my
good Samaritan nature like fighting against my inherently this is actually horrible i'm trapped
between nobles and a snake i just i mean if i was the snake i guess to me it's like well you guys
obviously wanted it to be clean more than i did because if i actually didn't want it to be clean i
would have cleaned it right well i'm not i don't even care about that the the point was just that uh
i i play games the same way i tackle other tasks because i do it as fast as i can as hard as i can
but it's the exact opposite you're a quantity and you're a quantity guy yeah quality quality yeah
yeah that's true yeah i mean this is true of everything okay check out these pro straps i'm
gonna try and use passwall and just like pass through a wall all right do it i have like never
fucking done this before you're a rock guy that's why you can do it right yeah passwall lets you meld
with stone oh you're like pika from one piece i like i like never use this okay this it's uh c
okay so z this is exciting c i feel like if this has not worked this did not work wasted my mp
damn okay okay i feel like if this had like more like advanced graphics i'd be totally enthralled
right now you guys are a bunch of babies this is fucking fascinating i'm completely no no no i'm
i'm enthralled but i just feel like it'd be some of this i don't know you guys are cowards is what
you are god damn weak cowardly i play fucking dungeon dragons or have my imagination yeah that's
your problem i can step on computer science major that's why i'm interested yeah i gotta scroll
of teleportation if i can survive for a couple more rounds i'll be safe the shimulinsky family
yes oh he won't let down a family of science a family of science that's true even though you're
both artists now you approach art from like you're the kind of guys who would make a game like this
that's true me and tom would probably make a game that looked absolutely beautiful and played
like generic dog shit some of the games i've made exactly i'd rather take the little more travel so
i can focus on making it look cool exactly the game i was trying to make uh with my buddies before i
started tbap which actually we stopped working on the game uh to work on tbap stuff man horses
ruined our and the world and the world was robbed and the world was robbed of this game where we were
playing as i was working on a 3d animated series with my friend before this was a this was a 2d
technical platformer that was all about being synced to music and we had the engine running
properly what and and basically is this the game you played is that a different game no totally
different game totally this was one we constructed ourselves out of unity instead of using rpg maker
yeah it was fairly pro you considered suing crypt of the necro dancer for stealing your concept
they kind of did steal our idea a little bit but ours was a 2d platformer instead of like a dungeon
crawler there's is a roguelite incident it is a roguelite it sure does let me just say i fucking
love uh crypt of the necro dancer that's the game on my list to play that is i never played games
anymore i don't yeah me neither but that one is really as you sit here playing by the way i just
want to take a moment to point out how ben's survival in that situation is is fairly pro
shit thank you ben says he doesn't play a lot of games but in the time he's lived with me he's
played more games than i have in like the last three years it's about how you approach things i
guess okay pokemon is not i don't view playing pokemon as a part of his life i don't play that as
playing what about just the the amount of prep work for the pokemon contest the well yeah that
again again that doesn't feel like playing a game to me well i mean it is objective okay shut up
it doesn't it doesn't feel like it though oh oh god oh sweet a published name invisibility
wasted i don't know yeah i don't oh crypt of the necro dancer i am right right i was re-watching
my end of 2015 video like stuff i loved in 2015 the first thing i commented on was crypt of the
necro dancer and i described it as uh um the game i've spent the most time playing out of all games
that i'm absolutely terrible at because i was never able to beat like like like the third floor of
the first dude i couldn't do that either it was too fucking hard yeah it's i mean i played for
probably 13 hours oh wow like the third floor that was that guy there that sings to your music right
yeah you can put in the middle of that that is probably a hard game i can actually get to read
a limel yeah it's my problem right now who is a god no kiko bakuga who's the god of death magic
specifically okay but i don't destruction not yeah yeah he's not yeah i want to subtle difference
that who meant the god of blowing chip up up with fireballs and such are you gonna be a still
an earth guy are you gonna switch to i yeah yeah i well i am gonna branch out a little bit like i'm
gonna learn magma bolt as soon as i can okay but uh which is fire earth cross class but um i am gonna
i am gonna specialize in earth the whole game okay what's your problem with uh trying to get
well it's not even blood just because gargoyles are really good at earth is that because i'm
like so self-critical when i die in a game i feel like that's a personal failure when you when you've
died in a game do you feel like you die for real a little bit inside yes every time every time
every every death in a video game is is a personal blow to my ego because i shouldn't i if i was
better i wouldn't have played a game like i want to be the guy that game will make you i don't want
not give a shit about dying a thousand times okay that's true i can leave rapid deconstruction
is a great fucking spell but right if i learned it right now the failure rate would be really high
and it's a pretty powerful spell so if you miscast spells really bad things can happen you can get
contaminated with magical energy that can actually mutate you like physically mutate you that's the
good thing about simple games like this is that they can implement crazy concepts without having
to like yeah that's where there's so much better than bullshit big budget shitty 3d games the first
time i ever won this game i was a crusader of oh i was a merfolk crusader and the reason that i won
was really early on i found an altar to the slime god whose name escapes me and all through the slime
god all through the game these slimes were always following me around they spawned on every level
and ate all the equipment like so like i didn't get any good drops because the slimes would eat all
my shit but the god would continually just fuck with me and mutate me and like by the time i like i
got the orb and i crawled out and i crawled out like i was colored in like iridescent scales and i
had like glow like glowing gold extra eyes like poking out from under my skin and i had extra arms
and shit it was fucking around do you win the game yeah like some of those were good like the extra
eyes give you an accuracy bonus and stuff like that fuck yeah so sometimes they're bad all right
well you convinced me this is the coolest game ever made it is yeah it is the coolest game ever
this is like if dnd were fun and good yeah you could play dnd by yourself and you didn't have to
worry about oh dear so much are you fucked no wait yes oh god the coolest game ever that we're
gonna have to restart right now um are there no save states that's a fickle mistress of course
that's for pussies never i've never played rogue or any rogue like so well just know you are not
no one's played rogue like no one has actually played rogue well i'm gonna be the first the reason
that rogue like has proliferated as a term because everybody wants to play rogue without playing
no one's played rogue everyone's played i mean there's a whole like the thing is this this is
really these should be called mystery dungeon games to me because that's what they're called in
japan there's a gigantic like you know pokemon mystery dungeons that's just a spin off of like a
huge fucking thing yeah but there's there's like well there's just a thousand games that are like
that because there's i mean there's dungeon crawler games and then there's like tons it's the word is
nariki dungeon so like there's there's like there's tons of games that are just spin offs of other
franchises that are just mystery dungeon versions of that franchise and then like and then there's
just like a million of them and they're like uh izuna legend of the unemployed ninja my sister was
a big fan of that i i fucking she bought it because there's a cute ninja on the cover well and i
bet you did too my friend i bet you did you gotta understand man oh i understand izuna legend of
the unemployed ninja is a game that i saw in the store yeah i'm unemployed and i want to be a ninja
i was immediately i was immediately the most captivated i've ever been with anything in my life
because that's so it's okay it's this ninja what the fuck tits and pink hair and she's got a big
smile and she's super cute i've never seen this altar before it look honestly looks like a god of
juggalos what does it does it not look like a tiny clown face to you it kind of does actually see
up here to verify us uskaya an altar to uskaya the reveler it appears to be the reveler sounds
clowny uh i'm gonna fucking go pray at it just to see oh man you're gonna throw your whole
don't join that dark carnival just sit ben okay i don't know usaka the reveler is a god of ecstatic
dance oh my god uskaya appreciates many forms of worship but in the dungeon most worshipers
stick to the dance of combat uskaya appreciates the passion rhythm of combat rewarding followers
for each strike they deliver and for the damage they deal their foes the longer the dance continues
the greater the path okay so it seems like he's like a melee god he's like a melee combat guy all
right that's cool so i'm not i'm not gonna join him pretty fun i that's awesome just like you get
up you don't say any prayers we just give him a nice nod and like a thumbs up as you walk away
the carnival you want about izuna the unemployed ninja yeah god so yeah i saw this game and it was
so beautiful and captivating because it's called the legend of the unemployed ninja so i was like
this is the greatest name ever of a game plus four plus four ring of intelligence just put it on
perfect for you feeling good going good i desperately need one of those so oh yeah dude i didn't buy
the game immediately because i looked at the back and it's like you know these very simple pixel art
kind of graphics and i was like this looks like it's probably a pain in the s rpg tactics game
or something uh so then i i i read reviews of it and all of them just assured me that the game is
hard as fuck because it's a dungeon crawler they're all hard as fuck um so i was like okay well i'm
probably not gonna play this because it's it's too hard uh and then it but i but i always wanted
it every time i was in the store i just never had the money for it and then they made izuna
to the unemployed ninja returns and that was always in the store and i was like i fucking want this game
still unemployed um yeah i don't want to factor this girl so bad and well here's the other thing uh
do you guys know about the character bico who's that okay she's a character who's famous on forechan
probably know her then she's she's got um she's got white hair and an eyepatch and she's the one
they made the comic for yeah this is the same b she's like five times yeah yeah she's missing an arm
and a leg and she plays guitar and anyway yeah i don't know tom knows the story i tried to get a
comic made of her but the artist who drew her is the same artist who drew the izuna art oh yeah so
me being a fan of bico also compounded my desire to buy izuna at this point i i need to remember
this part of the story yeah so i finally bought izuna 2 the unemployed ninja returns and i played
like 10 hours of it and it was too fucking hard so i'm gonna die i'm gonna die the terrible end
to that story of passion what's happening what's happening the fucking bee caught up to me i can't
run him i died bee you died that same bee that same bee got me a bee yeah well like a magic
bee i assume this mighty gargoyle was felled by a bee he's probably big he was a red bee no this
was you don't understand this was a red this is like a red bee like in donkey con they're invincible
you can't kill him so you know all right i'm just gonna fucking i'm just gonna rush through
and he'll understand this is a big bee really big guy well we're on run two now all right well you
know like you got yourself out of a lot of sticky situations so i'll give you props for that this
game is all about sticky enough to escape the honey though this game is about threat management yeah
as you're crumb across this game is about never taking any risk i feel like as you will deal with
so much shit in this game that if you even take risks that have a one percent chance of killing
you eventually you'll take so many of them that they'll kill you i feel like this is this is a
captain Picard game which is why it's a good game exactly you know what like a game he would enjoy
but he'd be good at i feel like he'd be good at it like he takes lots of risks though oh yeah but
you have to take risks to survive in this game so you know of course you would but yeah you do have
something there never need to say where you have to be adamant in your assertion that there are only
four lights that's such a cool scene it is a great scene there don't think i've seen this shit man
oh it's a good one oh i think i'm gonna die to this cockroach i feel like to explain it would be to
really die at least at least right away i barely survived i barely survived the cockroach all right
wow well that's a sentence i've said many times in my life and completely meant it
yeah and the thing about izuna too is that while it was hardest shit yeah it also just is like it
didn't have as much story as i would have liked like it's the kind of game kind of like uh like
diskaya or the niponichi games what always shocked me about those games is that like you'd go through
this gauntlet of like hours in a dungeon like this long incredibly hard dungeon that takes you like
fucking 50 tries to beat a level and then you beat it and you get like maybe three minutes of cut
scene that's mostly characters just saying dumb shit and the story makes no progress and then
you're right back in another dungeon that always frustrated me immensely about that yeah like
because i was used to you know rpg's like final fantasy 10 yeah you know good games yeah we're
gonna sit down for a fucking yeah yeah it's funny because some people like there's a lot of people
who really hate like the final fantasy games because of this reason that there's so much
cutscene but like to me i was kind of conditioned i grew up with those games and i like this condition
to expect that if i just beat a giant boss i'm going to get a sizable chunk of story for payoff like
i did not play those games because i thought it was fun to fight bosses the people who hate final
fantasy probably people who grew up playing stuff like dagger fall which is like the exact
opposite yeah it's a huge fucking big world well meanwhile like the make your own story essentially
the nipponichi games like the reward for that is some snarky dialogue and then they waste like 15
minutes of your time with bullshit conversations no one gives a fuck about and granted i like i didn't
get this at the time and god i fucking i bought an amulet of faith now that's not that might that
might really help me that'll really help me if i can survive to fucking get a god this time yeah
i makes gods really like you that's sweet i fucking i fucking bought like every nipponichi game
they released here because because i i the aesthetic appeals to me so much yeah like i'm so oh they
look so good dude that's so that's the disappointing part because you get drawn in for the aesthetic
and they don't really do anything with well i was also i'm gonna just like make you bought the game
i was also way into that was for i was full full heartily this is this is pure hubris pure
pretension and hubris yeah i was from well yeah i don't i don't think of myself as being
that pretentious because pretension means you're pretending to be something other than what you
are i am a leader on with your body i am elitist and biased but i don't think i'm pretentious but
as you don't you don't make any excuses this this was a matter of pure pretension that i was really
into tactics games the only reason i was really into tactics games is because i thought that because
i'm smart i should yeah i told i totally get that i'm smart dude i thought i was wicked smart
like i'm looking all the i'm feeling like playing chess for years over here exactly with all these
old anime boys like i i think the first one i played was probably fire emblem and i sucked at
it i could never beat level 15 uh x uh and like because you know i would restart if i lost a guy
so me too i just played the level like a hundred times i couldn't beat it and said fuck it and
just because i'm literally not smart enough to think of a fucking whoa whoa whoa i just drank
a potion of beneficial mutation my fingernails lengthened and now i feel fantastic is that like
a combat bonus i've done that before it is um i yeah i think it would give me a bonus to unarmed
combat so it's like it's a really small but hey that's zero point two points of death
yeah like i might be able to make off hand attacks like it's like make super power in that episode
of family gather they all got super powers you got the girls grow yeah yeah oh i remember that
but yeah so like over the course of like five or six years i really had it in my head that i was
way into tactics games it would buy like all of them and then play them for like barely any time
because i was so bad yeah you know i think the one i played the most of was the original diskaya
and then like but i had phantom brave makai kingdom fucking lapus l tactics all the way that one
that one sucks that one sucks shit uh i tried so hard to play that game for so long i thought that
it only sucked because i was not good enough and then i grew up like there was a time that is the main
girl was so hot the main girl lapus l tactics was like my my skill and my my personal preference
dude where does that divide it's super hard to find sometimes well the thing about lapus l is that it's
it's the the way that the combat system works takes forever like i don't remember that like you
have this okay it's all based on positioning where you have to like basically uh there's like a line
of colored blocks i do remember that and remember that like your character stands on that line and
whichever way they're facing the line faces that way yeah right like if there's a line cutting
vertically through the stage you'd have a character standing in it and turn them to the left and the
line breaks to the left right and so you want to position all your characters in such a way that
yeah you want to position them all in such a way that you get as many enemies in in this line as
possible and then when you attack it'll go down the line and hit all the guys but then like there's
also like uh like cutscenes for like you know hitting someone yeah and those like they load in
and they're slow and they load out and you can't turn them off so every even like the tutorial
battles are like 40 fucking minutes just because of how much shit you have to watch in between
attacking and like you know as a kid i just thought well i'm garbage at this game and i don't
get it so this is a so i so i'll play it later and then like you know like two years ago i busted
it out and i was like i'm an adult now i'm gonna play a lot of self because i love the aesthetic
of this game the characters look fucking great and i put it in and started playing it and i was like
this game fucking blows the characters all have generic anime personalities it's slow as
shit and the tactics are boring and fuck this game i'm never playing it again i really hate
tactics games i i played a lot i play fire only because my friends do i don't even like it i don't
know why i play it i don't think i would like it if i played one today and yet into fire he loves
fire but final fantasy tactics is one of my favorite games of all time and but that has a great
story it has a fantastic possibly the great story in all video games uh in terms of drama as i
understand the tactics system is complex and rich and wonderful as i understand it final fantasy
tactics is like like like the story is on the level of like the wire or game of thrones or
something it's like it's like it's like an epic political just like exponentially increase my
desire to play yeah it's it's have you played vagrant story or do you know it's the same writer
i want to play that they're they're both known for like these this is why i need to start late to
the party i'll have no yeah so i'll do all this shit tactics it would be a great late to the party
especially is a wonderful wait wait wait um i can kind of infer from the name but what is
late to the party uh basically it's an excuse for me to actually do all the things i keep saying
i've been wanting to do for the last like 10 years huh yeah like it's a good name it's all media
it's media that everyone else cares about that tom hasn't gotten to yet right i can i can be the
sole arbiter side of your nostalgia is bullshit or totally valid this is an alter to my club which
just be careful with that just be very careful i would tread lightly i would i would approach it
very from a very casual and um lighthearted opinionated project i would never i would never
deal in absolutes yeah only a sif does that by the way i think that i'm kind of more of a sif guy
the best way to describe final fantasy tactics is like a cross between the real life war of the
roses and berserk that's how i would describe it it's awesome that sounds fucking great it's great
the drama between deletha and ramza is right up there with guts and i think it's really played
final fantasy tactics advance and i was like this must be like oh shit i wasn't a huge fan of that
game well you know it's a little hard to get into it at first kind of wrapping girls were kind of
cool viara yeah oh i played all the uh the other games but uh only the original is really truly
great and worth playing well tactics advance is like i kind of wish this story is not the same
kind of story it's totally different and it's still fun but it's goofy and not as serious and the
game is just less complex and less fun um yeah so all those fucking niponichi games man i it took
a long time to come to that realization that they're not like that like that you're not the problem
yeah that oh yeah that i'm not the problem and that they're not that they just weren't what i wanted
you're into them for the wrong reasons you're looking for something out of them they don't
deliver well jesse's video about fucking the witch in the hundred night was fucking perfect it was
captured all of my problems with those games it was so great that they have these these these
short weird vapid cutscenes and terrible voice acting and then if you like and if you try to
like you like you have to press x to advance the dialogue which causes them to talk at an unnatural
rate but then if you try to like mash x and you keep hearing the beginnings of sentences there's no
winning yeah there's no victory over the cutscenes and a lot of games would do well to to manage that
yeah and it's it's infuriating and it took me a long time to realize it and like thankfully i stopped
buying the games in like 2008 because i was never playing them so like i have i was like i'm not
going to buy any more until i get through the collection i have i did that too la pucelle and
i've got like three disguise sequels that have just sit in a box because i thought i would play them
it never did you you see over there the audience can't see this but do you see how there's one rack
that's just ps2 games i think so i've beaten maybe four of those and the rest of them are i went
through this period where i was really obsessed with jrpg's but i kept buying them and like i kept
like there was a there was a point where i had a cutoff and i said i'm not going to buy
any more until i beat all the ones i have it's crazy you one by one as i try to go back and beat
the ones i have i realize oh these suck like they mostly suck i still love final fantasy nine
final fantasy nine is fantastic everyone loves final fantasy that's one of the final fantasy
nine is one that everyone who sucks final fantasy seven's dick and just like but nine is so charming
well that's fine i mean i haven't played seven so i'm totally biased but like nine just like
tickled me in all the right way there's okay there's two different levels here like there's the
ones that i never beat that i played like five hours and gave up and thought i would do one day
and those are mostly the ones that i came back to later and went oh i only played five hours
because this game is fucking boring whereas there's other games that i actually almost beat back then
and the only reason i didn't is because of shenanigans yeah in final fantasy nine's case i adored that
game it was like the greatest game ever i made it to disc three uh and then natasha the cat has
nine lives you have to you kill her but she just disappears she appears somewhere else on the level
oh is she uh any stronger when she reappears no she's just the same that's kind of cool farmer
uh you can oh she summoned a demon oh well that's that's not good she summoned a demon
the demon oh i'm out of magic the doctor shows okay it's actually bad 1399 with hd
graph i have fucking read reviews for that shit oh no i have stars right now and has 3598 reviews
if it's got good reviews then it's worth it i mean if you like playing on a fucking mobile
well you know i have like a psp or something it's got to be on that i don't psp is gay i don't have
oh the psp war the lions version is i think it's better like if you just want to play it on the
computer i don't know if dude just fucking pirate it or something i guess you like to buy games so
well he's just worried about whether he's gonna play it on the phone or on the computer that's
oh well the whole thing is that like it's one of the i don't sometimes i spend more time on this
a day than i do on my computer i'm not like that so i'm slowly moving i find sitting at a desk to be
very uh limiting not even limiting just like physically uncomfortable these days yeah i don't
get one of these you'll you can't afford one of these never mind oh god you fuck well i mean this is
a five hundred dollar chair you're sitting in bed this isn't the first one he can't afford this isn't
the first time he said that and it won't be the last no so i just come out and check the privilege
and feel like a victim and i've been in this culture that's a good thing that's true that means i have
privilege over you and soon you'll be paying me well the point is i can sit in this chair all day
and it never becomes a problem i don't know like for some reason i like a couple years ago when i'd
sit down at my desk like all right it's work time now when i sit down at a desk i'm like this is so
gay and i just don't want to do anything well just be aware if if you're i mean the music is great
and if you can appreciate the game fully on your phone feel free to do so i might just wait until
like a new laptop and buy it on windows and just play it on that fair enough um which could be kind
of cool it should be given that it's it's due respect when i don't want to over hype it i mean
it's not perfect i'll sell my final fantasy nine yeah and why i stopped yeah i got to disc three
do you remember the part where kooja is the bad guy of course kooja captures your whole party
and he's he splits you into two let me guess you got to the place where you can't use metal weapons
or something essentially yeah you can't use magic that's right he says like i'm gonna send you to
this uh this castle you get to take two people all of andre the castle all of andre you pick two
people but you can't use magic yep and i didn't like process what that meant so i sent zadan and
vivi oh dear that is not a good call both useless uh that's pretty good my zadan had lots of magic
though uh and and and i was like slightly i was like one level under leveled like i'm never over
leveled in these games i'm always like right hang on that doesn't make any sense zadan doesn't use
magic we're talking about zadan yeah i mean yeah i'm just saying i always call him zadane it is
actually supposed to be pronounced zadan but who gives a fault air well air zadane it's supposed
to be air it's not magic so i don't know what the fuck you're talking about well does he in the game
they never pronounce his name i mean i'm with yon vivi that's totally true he'd be useless without
magic but zadane are you sure he doesn't use magic yes okay well maybe he has some skills
he has skills but i think he could still use those i don't remember i don't remember the points
you got fucked i got i got there the enemies were like a level higher than me yeah and i could not
do any well no it wasn't just that i couldn't do anything i literally could not progress
because there was only two rooms in this place and i kept uh i kept having to run away from
battles because i couldn't like fucking kill anything right so i just kept running away and
i kept going back and forth between these two rooms and of course i had saved the second i got
there and of course i didn't keep multiple save files back well i mean because i was just i would
have done the same thing what did i did do the same thing so i got through this for some reason
i would chose tiner because i wasn't done i kept going back and forth between the two rooms going
like what the fuck happens here and it turns out there's like a specific enemy you have to kill
to make the next area open and i literally could not kill it with the characters i had like because
i couldn't level up i couldn't because i wasn't strong enough to kill anything and there's no
way out you can't leave the fucking place yep so it was just like i was literally completely
fucked my save file was done well and i just didn't i didn't have the fucking wherewithal to play
do it i got to the last kudra fight and my memory card got corrupted i lost all my series
for all my games that's tragic that's tragic i've actually my memory card dies twice and it killed
my final fantasy nine progress and my chronocross progress well you know the ending of nine you know
like the good guys win i mean i never felt like great ending i feel i still feel like i've beaten
the game because i grinded a lot so i was crushing everything at that point so i was confident you
still couldn't beat oh you i never got a chance to actually fight it but you would have won i'm
pretty sure i would have i have a question for each of you and i suspect that for a lot of the
answer will be never but how many times have you given up on a game towards the end because you
couldn't beat a boss never because i couldn't beat a boss i don't think i've ever done that
why is this guy so strong holy shit you know i probably have done it once or twice i did that
with final fantasy 12 for a while but then came back and defeated it and fucking raped that game
and it was awesome i just wanted to do that but i my tism is that like at that point i'm just like
i can't let this game be better than me it's not even real yeah like that yeah and i'll just scream
and i'll use racial slurs and i'll snap controllers in half and i'll get so pissed but i'll eventually
do it and i won't even feel good i'll just be like i just made myself die two years earlier from
all the stress i have it i haven't made everything in some cases i give up because it would take to
like okay here's the thing about me as a kid and this is probably also why you guys are better at
games than me because i just growing up i thought side quests were just a waste of time oh you fool
like i did not think that side quests were worth doing or that there was any reason to do them i
was like people only do this if they're fucking like weird or something right like i just well
you're not wrong i just literally well the thing is that a lot of japanese games expect you to do
all the side quests just to beat the final boss like like okay yeah shadow hearts covenant for
instance is a game that i absolutely loved and i played it all the way through to the end and i got
the final dungeon was pretty hard but i was still beating everything in it yeah and then i get to
the final boss and he's just like curb stomping me like i can't do anything to it and i realized
like i i think i looked at a strategy guy there he said i had to be like it's fucking vehumet
it's fucking vehumet time all right i just happened to find an ulcer to vehumet usually you don't
find the god you want until you get to the ecumenical temple but here i am and i found it all right
the game's trying to turn in your favor uh what what did you do the environments change it's all
randomly generated it is all randomly generated but it doesn't ever look like something different
yeah yeah there are different regions okay i've i've just been fucking around in the early game
right now this is like the baseline yeah normal dungeon yeah okay now now that i'm worshiping
vehumet i just got a and a book but it's probably not anything i want because it was next to this
altar of kikubakudga it is kikubakudga's kikubakudga's disquisition on evil and the only spell it has
is pain which is garbage so i won't be drinking it should i drink from this fountain oh oh oh and
sif muna fuck that um should i drink from this fountain of sparkling water sure why not um how
do i how do i do it speaking of old there probably is an answer to sure why not but yeah
i didn't give it oh yeah yeah it can do terrible things to me um i had to do it anyway i'm gonna
do it anyway i just fuck how do i real man boys take risks give a yolo or two of this fucking game
i mean you're supposed to be going on this card but you can't kirk it every now and then to keep
to keep the analogy going um yeah so at the end of shadow heart's covenant yeah i looked at the
guide and it's like you should be like level 67 or something to beat this boss and i was like
level 59 and i was like like because again i didn't like process side quests is like an important
thing i was like so am i expected to just grind in this final dungeon for like 10 hours well no
yeah because what i eventually realized i mean in your situation that's what yeah well what i
unless you want to go on the side quest were not locked locked out in this game and it's actually
pretty easy to travel around because that game is uh basically you go to a bunch of different
cities yeah it's like each city has a dungeon in it but you could travel between the cities pretty
easily um and it takes place in the real world and in the in europe and so i was like i like
eventually it occurred to me oh like they expected me to have done all the side quests to get all
the ultimate weapons for the characters and that would make this boss a cakewalk that's my shit
but like jam i had not you know i had not done so that was like so rewarding and so i just kind
of play zeno saga yeah zeno saga was my favorite that was that game was my jam i got stuck on a boss
10 hours in and gave up dude i did i was right there on my shelf among games i will play one
game zeno saga 2 it's sitting on my shelf i never finished they changed the art style dramatically
and i got super turned off i didn't like the look of it nearly as much exactly zeno saga 2 is pretty
fucking panned by fans but three is apparently a return to form the problem is that three is i guess
a convoluted mess story wise because there were supposed to be six entries and spend 10 years and
they got canceled so they had to do everything it's four games worth of content in one so it's just
yeah you can't you can't fucking quaff from fountains anymore what the shit man oh you used to be
able to like mutate and stuff but you drink this like irradiated magical water but now i guess they
took it out what's a bummer they take out features sometimes so this game just got less cool because
the mutant was like half the intrigue well no i mean there's there's other ways to do it but yeah
you can no longer drink from fountains i guess they thought it was extraneous which it was but i like
that uh that's kind of the whole thing this phenomenon you were talking about about hitting a
wall i actually fucking love it because it gives me an excuse to go do yeah to go do all the side
quests that i've been putting off to that point because a lot of the time side quest those that
will i mean it depends not me anymore but it depends on the game like like okay the most recent
example of me giving up on a game at the very end was persona 2 eternal punishment which i played
about seems like a close to five years ago now and uh the game it's like 50 hours long you know as
as rpg's tend to be and like i do like i love persona like shin megami tense is the the like
still how like how i got over niponichi i haven't gotten over shin megami tense even though i should
because the games are just so perfect they tell you about persona or the all of them persona and
the rest because the aesthetic is just everything i ever wanted like they look exactly what like
what i want they look how you want to look they fuck how you want to fuck but but atlas is infamous
for making extremely hard games so it's like everything about the game is what i want except
that it's so fucking hard yeah and like the persona games in particular i love the characters i love
this the way that you like go back to the same town and everyone has new things to say every time
you beat a dungeon i love that shit right so i'm playing do persona 2 and the thing is that as the
game goes along the story gets kind of retarded and like the second half of the game is just so
much less interesting than the first so in the first half i was doing a lot more like you know
like extra bullshit yeah but then as i get grew less interested in the story then it would be like
you know i just went through this grueling dungeon and did all this fucking shit and then i come back
and i get a cutscene that is not even interesting i'm like oh this fucking blue and then i have to go
to another incredibly grueling dungeon and when that happened i was like but i still want like now i
just feel like i want to rush through this to find out where the fuck the story is going yeah so in
the second half i just started yeah the second half i just started rushing did you see those fucking
orcs i just came i just came up some stairs about a bunch of orcs and an orc priest um priests are
really bad yeah it's this weird shift in proportion where it's like early in the game the story is
really interesting and the dungeons are pretty short but then later on it's like the dungeons
are super long and super difficult and the story is like nothing yeah so i just feel like i'm in this
endless gauntlet when game is doing a yield turn it's not cool yeah and so the final dungeon in that
game um i was so fucking sick of the game like i just wanted it to be over i was i've been playing
for like probably three days and i just wanted it to be done because they're like non-stop for three
days you know and i was like i gotta fucking finish this game and they're telling me like you know the
final boss if you want to beat him check this shit out what this is that altar over there is an altar
of trog the god of rage and for barbarians and stuff this moth in here is a rage moth or like
wait he's called uh yeah he's a moth of wrath so he's gonna like sprinkle his rage powder on these
fucking rats and send them into a berserk fury so i'm gonna get the fuck out of here get out of there
it sounds like the worst day ever it's pretty bad i mean the the rats are not particularly strong
so it's not like sounds bad it could be it could be dealt with dark souls has taught me that rats are
not to be trifled with that's true i don't want to be hard wearing bloodborne i don't want to be
trifling all right one in isolation is fine i got embarrassingly murdered by a gang of rats it
happens i was i was in uh in maybe you feel less bad about your failures in bloodborne if you watched
other new players because well i felt a little better i felt a little better when i watched when i
watched hippo's uh live stream of bloodborne where he was still dying even though he's like
mastered that game yeah all right yeah yeah i feel a little less no one just makes it through
you know and that's your the whole thing is like i never even talked about dark souls until
i started talking to you guys and the first time i heard anyone talk about dark souls was when
gib was saying i just fucking destroyed dark souls on my first time and i died like twice
i was like oh is that a weirdo exception so okay the thing is that hippo hippo played
not only extremely cautiously but he violently overleveled in his playthrough like i think i'm
doing that in bloodborne right now he was so unbelievably OP that he did things in his first
playthrough that i've never heard of anyone doing yeah because he did artorias in his first try yeah
but but he said that artorias he said that he was taking a drink uh like of estes and artorias
hit him and he did not stagger out of taking yeah yeah which means that is like for that to be possible
he would have to be like like 10 times the level that most people finish the game at like he was
so over leveled it's unbelievable that's crazy so yeah i grinded for like four days to get leveled
before i kept playing the game i just felt like that's a good idea it's it's so boring though grinding
that game is grinding is not great in that game it's what in dark i actually i i i saw my tweet
about dark souls i wrote an entire script in my head for bloodborne i was thinking of dark souls
you're talking about bloodborne yeah because i enjoyed grinding in bloodborne really i just
enjoyed i hate grinding in all those the act of playing bloodborne is the appeal of bloodborne
well here's the thing like bloodborne the only reason i can stand playing bloodborne is because
every time you hit something it's like having an orgasm the blood yeah exactly that's why it's
grinding is fun if that if that wasn't there i couldn't play this game i don't give a shit about
that shit i just want to fucking grind my exp and get up as fast as possible do things repetitively
over and over like that it gets numbing like the only like i had this whole like thing planned out
was like because i was i was comparing it's like action games i like that are hard like ninja
guide and a devil may cry it's a different kind of game completely sure like the the appeal of
devil may cry and stuff is like magic how you kill the guy and the the fun in bloodborne is if
you'll kill the guy that's true you don't know if you're going to be able to make it like that's
why you're co-incostrously and like the thrill is like when you have like less than half a life bar
and like you're just kind of getting by by the skin in your teeth well the thing is that you feel
like a fucking winner once you once you're great at the game it shifts to the other one because
like the way that my friends who are really into souls games play it's all about how fucking much
can i gimp myself and still beat this boss i guess you know like how can i play this game at level
one with only shields yes i can that's kind of that's kind of my big problem with with bloodborne
right now is that like in order to like blew it effectively you have to like treat it as a game
and that sounds really fucking stupid and i'm trying i've i've been like thinking about how i
want to make a video about this and explain this concept and i don't even know how to describe it
in words correctly yet is that like i like kind of not passively experiencing a game but like
kind of getting lost in in the the world and the idea of the game like when i played mass effect
like i was in space like i wasn't sitting at a computer playing a game you know with bloodborne
it's like you have to actively be aware of all the mechanics and i don't believe in immersion i i'm
so i believe i'm the biggest boner for immersion ever i'm not immersed i'm not having nearly as
much fun i don't believe in it i don't think it's real i've immersed many times in my life at least
i think i have and i wouldn't trade it for all your patreon bucks in the world you know oh i just i
don't get it okay i traded for a majority of patreon i don't i i wouldn't be happy about it if you
never get immersed in anything then what's the point of experiencing any story i don't i don't
get the idea like i've never had the moment where i stopped believing that this is a story no i don't
i don't see everything in don't believe it's a story you see it becomes so like you just forget
in it you're not thinking about anything else like um when i'm playing something like mass effect
like i'm not even like conscious of the fact that like there's i'm sitting in a chair and i'm
holding a troller it's just like you're living vicariously through those characters and those
events and so it's just like like if someone the only time you remember you're holding your
troll is when someone like bitches at you like oh fuck you have to pause it you know about this
forgetting shit but like uh like when when ace died in one piece that emotionally devastated me
and i couldn't do anything for a few days i mean that's getting immersed to me it's the totally
if that's what immersion means then i've been immersed but like i don't i don't i've never
forgotten that i don't think you ever think it's real when people when people talk about immersion
the way that like they mean when people say like you know i'm not even analyzing it i'm just immersed
in it like that doesn't happen to me i don't have a moment where i don't think about it i don't think
your autism never gonna let you get to that level no it's just like i mean when i'm watching a great
movie i'm constantly thinking about why it's so great i'm always thinking like oh my god this scene
is constructed so well you know i have to like i have to like flip a switch in order to go into
that mode and i feel sad sometimes because i have such a dip like there are times where i'm i'm
seeing a movie and like i feel bad that i'm thinking so much about why it's making me feel
emotions as opposed to just feeling the emotions someone who can flip the switch i will say that
when i do flip the switch and then and i like realize the flaws of something it just makes me
feel stupid for letting myself be so retarded i've had that i've had that before but i'm more
i usually am more devastated by the fact that i can't just feel something unless it is so
unbelievably powerful that it's like with your personality if you could do that you'd never
let yourself do it anyways you'd never be like well i'm just not going to analyze this because
the immersion was so great right well shit i mean you're just saving yourself a step right
this is this is sort of why your brains optimized for your fucking yeah well i keep i keep telling
people like uh i've had this problem that i've been talking about in the decompression chambers
and stuff that like i need a 10 like i am so desperate to watch another 10 because i've been
trapped in this world like like all of 2016 not a single anime came out that i would give
above a nine not one and all i want is a 10 because even a nine a nine to me when i watch it i'm
thinking wow this is executed so well and when i watch a 10 i'm just thinking oh my fucking god
i love everything like and that that that leap i need that like when i watched speed racer for the
first time i wasn't thinking about the like like oh my god it's a ghost of my last character
he's here with a fucking vengeance oh man that's super cool i don't think i can beat it run can
you just say hi maybe do you say the ghost of your own character yeah yeah the one that just
died he's i just saw it but i'm but i'm getting off forget i'm getting out of here i'm getting
the fucking that's pretty cool that's awesome as shit yeah you can like you you just will
eventually have like this is definitely the coolest game ever made yeah i'll say i'm gonna
fucking and now i'm gonna die because there's a fucking ant that did the the the the the what
she's like that right there that would just i don't have anything to heal with can you go back to the
other floor can you go down the stairs the ant will follow me that's so gay see it's it's important
you stairs he's so small take him forever take him a month to get down i'm gonna die i'm gonna
die heal i don't have anything to fucking heal with let's do something i'm dead oh there was
no there was nothing damn it i couldn't i'm sorry i'm sorry everyone i used stone gargoyle
i i feel bad that i just don't grow i just want to make it to level two i haven't even been able
to make it to the ecumenical temple shameful which is like oh my god i'm getting gang bang all at
the gate but whatever whose phone keeps fucking doing that noise mine made a noise just now i think
that sounds like an iphone sound effect so the fact that every your android phone does it is like
sending me into a frenzy it's like only me and munchie have them anyway would it really disturb
you if i had an iphone uh no i just the fact that you don't and it's making iphone noises
is kind of freaking me out that killed me that's fine nope no biggie the first encounter yep what
the fuck don't worry about the the the downsides of random generated levels there there were just
there were just like three dudes they're waiting for me okay i think i'm probably gonna die to
this hobgoblin too oh no oh no i made it okay sweet all right well so so so that moment that he
had just now with the other guy it's unfortunate because i wasn't playing the game and i never
would because i don't understand this game yeah but that was a 10 out of 10 moment for me that is
that which one which one when you find the ghost of your own self oh yeah at no point did i think
about like the possibility why why is that cool or anything like it's just it is so obviously amazing
that that is that's what i that would be immersion for me like not that uh not that i'm like lost in
the world but that like there was just a just sounds like you're so fucking jaded that you need
something exactly i am extremely fucking jaded and it takes something being like like i can't believe
this happened and i never would have expected it and it's like blowing my mind that it's real
that's what it takes to make me like feel anything that's that's not being a youtube man is this you
just that's the downside to your obsession for quantity you're just kind of like blowing through
your wow factor way too quickly it's true and it happened all at once with anime i mean why why
why would you be why would you be satisfied with anything less yeah exactly like anything less
is good but it's just not you know but the thing is that the only way i can find
i'm sorry he's looking one of his old videos the college graduation video i just got a comment
he's looking at a comment i saw i just had to i had to give him kudos for the music choice on that
video yeah great he learned it from watching me all right well but bonita that's not true that's true
that's true um anyway uh yeah you're right that i'm jaded but the problem is that i never find those
10 out of 10s by chance i only find them by seeking them out well and like by watching at this point
i feel like that's kind of just the nature of the beast you've become you i mean you can't watch
everything to try and find those that's digi's goal that's what i've been doing he's like he's
being audacious like the problem is that admire your drive well the problem is that the stuff that
i end up loving the most is never stuff that everyone else loves the most and so i have to go
find them like i can't look at a list dude you know oh my god magic rings it's made of bones
have you find it have you consider that it's finally time what to learn japanese and dive deep into
that whole other cool shit the the level of manga that i will like like i've been saying this
imagine all the light novels you could read that like should have been published instead of
instead of fucking sao well light novels are inherently bad like that's i'm about to disagree
that rule you're you're not necessarily writing a light novel oh i will like if it's not bad then
it's not a light well if you're defining it like that then i think our case is already complete well
well you're you're too old to be a new light novel writer they're all like 18 and shitty that is
like really depressing actually i think about it i'm an old man that can't be right why is there
like some cadre of older better writers we're like well look at these retarded kids making
bank on this shit why don't we get on it my point is that like what is considered a light novel is
like the necessary element of it is that it's a shitty novel it's just like young adult fiction
right i yeah but it's it's young adult fiction that is like deliberately of like like like you
would describe it as a light novel because it is not of the heft of a real well how different is like
a story online from like a hunger games they seem pretty comparable to me they are and hunger games
is terrible so that's exactly the same thing it's entertaining in its own way yeah so i would uh
i don't know a 30-year-old 30-something-year-old american women wrote that two years worth of
semen float in a blopping sound and float endlessly into opera that was not any of the
published versions i don't think i don't think you're gonna find a line that i don't think you
have to be kind of dumb to write a book like like okay or maybe i'm under arrest to make them
i'm like the biggest i used to be like the biggest light novel guy in the world like like when i was
reading them before well because light novels before they became something that everything
in anime is yeah uh i was reading them in like the mid-2000s but nobody knew what they were uh all
that shit right there you see on that shelf that's all light novels is anything worth reading
yeah a lot of it okay well i'm i'm looking for stuff to read boogie pop boogie pop was my world
is that gonna turn me into you because i don't know if i want to go down that road
no i mean if you if you read if you you know you read some of my book a little bit i read a little
i need to read more it's it's like people who like the one the couple of people who read my book who
had read boogie pop were like you just cloned boogie pop like that's all it is okay um because
the well it's like it my book is just boogie pop meets bakano that's like and gunslinger girl like
if you combine those three you've got my book but uh it's not a terrible combination yeah and like
bakano okay bakano great example phenomenal anime um okay you might be explaining a point
i was just about to raise but keep going bakano is a phenomenal anime um the light novel took
four took almost 10 years to finally come stateside it came last last year uh they released it in
only in a 20 dollar hardcover because they knew how badly people wanted it so they released it only
in a 20 dollar hardcover now here's the thing what you have to understand about both manga and light
novels in japan is that they're like five dollars like a light novel is like this this little tiny
fat book that ring of protection of magic baby that they put out in like all right finally getting
stacked i i hope okay okay there's a race in this in this game that is the octopode it is literally
just a sentient octopus nice and it's cannot use like most equipment but the one thing it can do
is it can wear eight magic rings at the same time uh so if you find eight magic rings you're just
fucking you're fucking set because someone captive planet all by yourself isn't that good to get eight
rings well rings are wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait ben what ben i have a
question for professor sains what i can wear 10 magic rings what are you talking about the rule in
dnd and in much fantasy is that one ring per hand that's fucking gay is doesn't make any sense is the
thing in but an octopode has eight hands if you get a mutation with a new arm you can wear another
why is it just counted as one hand they're all coming from the same central appendage um stop ask
jesus two questions anyway keep going yeah so so so light novels in japan are these little five
dollar rinky dink little books that they fucking shovel out and they come out like every three months
like like if you're if you're reading a series speed yeah that'd be nice i mean look i have nothing
but respect for white light novel authors because they're so fast yeah but the stuff they're writing
is fucking dog shit so like like rekkie kawahara for instance you either understand about soren online
and excel world is that each one has at minimum two books a year at minimum both series are running
at the same time two books a year usually they edge towards four books a year okay so he's writing
these like every month to three months okay these are cheap disposable fiction they are meant to be
things that young people can buy you know for the cheap read quickly get the next installment
in a couple months read a whole bunch of them and they come out like constantly the ones that get
made into anime are the really successful ones but there's a ton of light novels they're really
oversaturated in market so there's just shitloads of these crappy little books coming out now when
they release these stateside because the market for them is so small here and there's such high
demand from people who really care about them they jack the price way up so right now the average
price of a light novel is 14 dollars bakano because it was in demand for so long because it's this
niche that people have wanted it for you know all this time 20 dollar hardcover so i bought it
because i had to of course um you know and i was hoping they were gonna like only do that for the
first book and maybe release like cheaper versions later of course not you said you set the standard
on that you jumped on it oh no i drank a potion of mutation well i feel frail my feet thickened
and deformed i feel the magical essence link to my wands what the fuck does that mean i have no
idea what that means that's you expend magical power to strengthen your wands or whatever frail
is terrible cloven feet is actually pretty shitty because it means i can't wear boots okay i need a
potion of cure mutation wow that's that was that that was a good luck with this third run that's
so good that the the real bad thing is the frailty like by the time i'm finding good boots
it's not unlikely i'll have found a potion of cure mutation yeah um boots yeah i mean your
goal eventually is to get kitted out with like a good piece of equipment in every one of your slots
and then your fucking like every game ever made yeah so so anyway i only bought bakano because
i knew i could write it off of my taxes because i'd make a video about this exact concept i'm
talking about but um have you done that yet yeah i did uh i didn't watch it uh it was called
have have manga and light novels gotten too expensive was it on after dark yeah it's on
after dark i'm not subscribed after um if you want to be polluted with videos every single day then
by all means that's why i'm not subscribed uh so it's too much they're all fantastic everything
i've ever made you know anyway bakano i bought this damn book and i started reading it and
it's it's not well written like that's my huge complaint yeah i was so fucking stoked to check out
oh you read it too no i didn't read i haven't watched bakano another thing on my list to do um
but like i really enjoyed no game of life and i was like oh read the light novels they're terrible
they're so fucking i like flip through one in the store i'm like this looks like it was written
by like a five year old yeah and i wasn't sure like is it just translation or is it like they
actually written by retouch because they're written like i said in like three months but here's
by like a 20 year here's what i don't understand okay um because i just recently read the entire
series of animals which is it's kind it's not the same thing but those came out once a month
there's 12 books a year but those are like okay apple gate is a beast they're smaller books but
like the concepts in there are like fucking great like it's one of like the best like books talking
about like the the psychological effects of war which i mean it's this probably better maybe
exaggerate no no it's not not like okay not not like the best ever but like it's like it it treats
it really realistically and like goes into a lot of things that you wouldn't expect for a book written
for that like age demographic it's fucking great that's like the coolest it's the coolest thing
it's i would do not regret spending 60 on all of animals all right that's cool that was well
worth it but it's just like why why can't like a quote unquote i guess like young adult write
something of like just it okay you have to understand as well that part of the thing with
light novels is that they come from they're very edgy yeah a lot of the a lot of the concept behind
them like the people who did it in the beginning we're kind of like no no this fucking priest won't
leave me alone like some people let's talk to you about jesus some people credit boogie pop with
having been like yes got influence light novels to happen like as as a thing right yeah and boogie
pop the whole idea was that the the guy who wrote it cohe kodono um his writing was too weird
no one would publish him because his writing was too weird um he described it as boogie so he decided
to fuse it with pop sensibility hence boogie pop yeah we've heard this a thousand times yeah yeah yeah
i'm explaining to tom who doesn't watch after dark all right i think i i have heard you say this
before well anyway that's not that important i don't think i can do it not here that he tried to
make you know a pop just found a pizza just found a pizza in the dungeon right yeah threats most of
what's unique about boogie pop as a book is not really like that it's a great story it's the it's
the format of it that it's like five different characters each telling their own part of the
story which is you know it's like there's a lot of like gimmick elements to it so it's like it's
basically just like anime characters in an anime story but it's presented in this very obtuse
strange way with like a sort of rambling stream of consciousness writing style interesting and
that's what some like a lot of the early light novels all of them are like these very um outsider
art stream of consciousness kind of shit but like you when you look back on them as an adult
you can feel the fact that you're older than these authors were when they wrote them and you really
feel that like they're not geniuses they are just like writers who gotta start early you know and like
yeah like i read boogie pop now and even though i still really appreciate it and how like you know
where it innovated and how interesting it is like the actual writing is pretty immature and that's
true of like all light novels and the thing is that most of the people who are writing them were
influenced by the old ones and there's just a degradation over time it only gets worse yeah
new light novels are only worse and worse and worse than older ones so if you read a lot of
those ones on the shelf for the original generation if you read new nicoe scene i hear the sound of
rushing water that means there's a special portal on this level that'll take me to like a hear this
game well no it says what it says i hear the sound of rushing water anyway that means i need to
find a portal and get there because there's a secret level um that will probably have a nice
treasures for me read but yeah if you read the writing of nicoe scene or kohe kodono or any of
the people in foust which is those two volumes there that say foust those are like compilations
cool and it was like it was a magazine that existed in japan that was half like mostly like
light novel authors writing short stories and then they also had manga stuff in there and like
everyone in there has like a very distinct like dark edgy kind of teenage like young adult style
but those stories were very like even though they took a lot of influence from anime and video games
they read more like young adult fiction like it was they took place in like you know urban areas
and they had like real stories and some drama but then over time they like light novels just
became anime and it just became like all the tropey bullshit and uh and now they're just garbage
they're all fucking terrible and and it strikes me as odd that that happened why could you just
write fiction for you know young adults and not have it devolved because they're they're they're
being like the problem is that those guys who wrote the original ones were probably influenced by real
books writers yeah right of course like like uh catcher in the rye they all owe a lot to to that
you know they all owe a lot to the catcher in the rye they they even in one of the foust volumes
there's like like a few of them nerd out about it you know really love that sure not be catcher in
the rye is you know is something that young adults love sure you know it's written in a way that that
audience can appreciate it but it's a real book but if you only read stuff that are influenced by
that that's a little worse and then those people are the right you know and everyone keeps writing
worse and worse stuff yeah and if you're writing like i want you to imagine that someone because
this is something that happens all the time and it happened to me as a kid we probably all experienced
this no no you watched sort art online or something like it some shitty show that was your favorite
show and you immediately decided that you wanted to be a writer and your only influence is that one
shitty show you watched so you try to write something exactly like that yeah and if you're
successful at writing something exactly like that shitty successful show you also have now
written a shitty successful show it's just that it strikes me as particularly strange that the
market would come to support like shittier products instead of rewarding the what i would assume is
better quality stuff you know what i have a theory on this because it's easier to make it's easier to
make but i think we're just talking more to the who's buying it right yeah it's the same people
the dude here's the thing we can tie this all back together it's the exact same mentality is why you
bought all those fucking games because the aesthetic of the book itself yeah and the number one thing
you remember it's all marketing it's the it's the producers the most important thing to remember
about light novels is that the writing doesn't matter the cover matter exactly because every
novel is a two-man team it's a guy who wrote the book and then the guy who did the illustrations
and those guys are equally important exactly they are of equal importance if not the character
designers even more you know and these character designers like like whereas the the art the the
writers are all these you know these young dudes who are probably submitting to contests like you
know dengueki bunko probably has a contest like every month hey who's who wants to be a writer
you know you do your story shit let's publish it and then they farm artists off of like pixiv
you know pixiv yeah so they'll just go on there and find someone who's popular and be like let's
hire this fucking guy makes sense super underpaying yeah exactly and slap that guy's fucking art on
this guy's shitty book and now you've got a product and now you've got the asterisk war you know uh
or or like like with the in the case of the asterisk war the guy had previous who did the character
designs had previously done a series called uh what the fuck is it called is some other bullshit
fucking shit and it wasn't shit great yeah it was a bullshit shitty show that was really popular
because of how hot the girls were and it's like there's no reason that asterisk war would have
gotten an anime if not for the fact that the same character designer did that novel and like they
probably just like some novelists came up with the story and they said oh let's put a let's put
this guy on it and they put that guy on it and now that novel regardless of what it is has a future
because that artist drew two you know life is successful because she was on the cover but the
people orchestrating all this are the people at these companies that choose to publish these books
written by these people they're the ones who get in touch with these artists because they don't have
to pay anybody a lot of money it's because they know they'll sell a fuckton yeah and and they see
soulless fucking scum sucking faggots who need to be executed well they're picking out a day
they're picking up the story as well going to japan it's daytime there it's these people we can take
them out it's these people whose responsibility it is to support the company they work for and
guarantee the return on investment through these books and these light novels and these artists
and whatnot it's it's that need to produce and get a return on your investment that's really driving
artistry out the window and bring in bullshit but here's the thing and i mean people can look at this
and be like uh like how is it that all these bullshit things keep getting successful yeah but
that's the thing is that only a small percentage are actually successful but they're paying for all
the failures because like because like i said before whereas only some of these are getting
anime adaptations there are fuckloads of light novels getting published and most of them just
died i know nothing about this market so i don't either i've i've most sure for manga i've tried
googling light novels constantly for manga yeah i've never gotten anything like like how many
times have you started this in any medium how many times have you like a print something not like
anime where it's all made at once like a season is made all in one sitting but like how many times
have you started reading a series and then after like a few chapters it just dies it happens all
the time you know it's tragic and that's like that's what like like light novels they're just
constantly making them and some of them like one comes out nobody buys it it's done but the one
that actually survives that gets the anime it pays for like yeah right exactly so they just
they turn out as many as they can in the hopes that one of them is going to be the golden goose
makes perfect sense the people are dumb enough to buy one of these right and that's why why i hate
a one picture so much the sora online team because it's very clear because they make like
fucking four shows a season because they're just hoping one of them is going to be the cash
they're doing the same thing yeah they're doing the same thing and they just turn out constant
shit and like you know every once in a while one of them sticks and they make a billion dollars you
know but uh somebody has to stop your madness yeah so anybody cares the only way to stop it is
these are just pure market forces driving the entire thing the only way to affect it is that
there has to be the the individual people running these things have to have a guiding light within
them that tells them artistry is what i'm here for and that's what i need to do but here's the
question yeah where's the money come from well how do you define artistry yeah because like
sordot online is unbelievably successful yeah which just means people like it yeah so like
whatever people saw in it is not what you know what we saw in it and the only real way like
the reason that people like us like critics have any importance at all yeah is i mean this is
self-serving but we can affect the way people perceive these things that like i have convinced
hundreds of thousands of people that they don't like sordot online and shouldn't support it
you know and like that's the only way thing you've ever done in your life yeah like how else am i going
to affect the market to make less people want sordot online and more people want log horizon
other than to like convince them that they want one and not the other yeah right and uh and if it
works if enough people like me say it then like it might change something but yep that's what my
hope to do to convince people to do things that are better than what they're doing right now yeah
by your standards by but yeah and i would never say that it's anything other than my personal
our job is the most self-serving in the world in that regard yeah that's entirely true oh god it's
a fucking centaur oh my fuck our centaur is being in tough he'll kill me he'll shoot me full of arrows
and i'll die what the fuck got us on this light novel tangent is there something else eventually
planning to loop back to that i forgot probably but who knows yeah no game no life i haven't bought
specifically because the volumes are 14 dollars a piece i'm just so depressed because i want to
know where it goes it's so it's so interesting because like here like in the top side of the
books are shit though right they they i've only read like one half of the page but it was enough
to tell me that that's even if there's shit like because that's the thing like no game no life might
never get a second season and there were only like i thought it was getting something it's getting an
ova it's been a while that hasn't been here isn't it i thought it was maybe i thought i heard something
about that well the thing is that the the anime like the really popular too wasn't it yeah but the
novels were very new at the time so like there was only four when the anime came out it only adapted
three or it adapted three out of the four so there was there was not enough material for another season
and it was publishing slower than most light novels but uh but yeah that's one of the good ones
when volume four came out in the u.s i was like i kind of really want to know where this goes but
i'm not going to pay 14 dollars for what i know is going to be dog shit writing you know it's not
going to be eloquently written gotta get the uh pdf rip from oh no no no no but so many i'm fucking
bees i love the bees and a demon but that was where you're playing nick cage yeah the swarm of bees
and a demon but that is what i was faced with oh well if you're wondering at all ramp if you're
wondering at all why i'm still behind no the bees are fast and worse please inform and lighten me
because i don't know because the one great thing about light novels is that not unlike this game
crazy fucking ideas get into them like even though the the writing is dog shit like okay a certain
reason i like animorphs there's a lot of cool shit going on yeah a certain magical index is the
perfect example of a series that's like it's full of dumb tropey bullshit just just drink a potion
that permanently made me um weak stupid and clumsy now you know it's like to be me
oh so a certain magical index yeah nothing but like dumb tropey anime bullshit yes it is
it's only sales are driven entirely by waifus right because misaka for some reason is the most
popular waifu of all time and i don't know she's she still wins best girl contests like on both
reddit and on like in japan it's this it's the spats dude it's gotta be this bad it's this girl
named misaka also known as rail gun and her power is that she's like one of the strongest uh espers
in the city and it's there's an academy city it's a city that's all schools that teach people how to
use espers magic and she uses she controls lightning uh and she her thing is that she'll take like a
coin and flick it and it fires like a rail gun and so they call it pretty cool it is cool and she's
just kind of like a sundae girl or whatever who has like she's really strong but for whatever reason
people fucking love her like she's like one of the most popular characters ever and i don't know
why i don't get it either that's special the public continues to baffle me i mean i like her i don't
dislike her i just don't understand the she know i want to just like saber like what yeah i don't
get that even better character design but i don't get the overwhelming love for saber it's just
because i don't know man strong women think about this dude we can't even sit here and complain
about them we just faffed to uh fucking to be downstairs and she has no person i other than
like we can see up her to be is way more interesting inherently than i have any players like you have
some connection i guess but that doesn't do much for me in terms of endearing me to a character
like i don't like my bloodborne guy at all look to to be is in a whole new world there's time to
explore whatever it doesn't we'll find out if she's interesting with the game yeah we'll find out
we'll find out but like i feel like she's going to be a stereotypical i'd have no emotions and by
the end she'll have some sort of like emotional i don't know i don't know i don't know you have to
understand near as off the rails off the rails it could be anything well i would love to be mistaken
because i really like everything else the game so i can't wait to play that fucking game because the
twists are going to be legit but yeah the guy who makes the the near and draken guard games is a
psychopath and his games are full of weird off the wall wait speaking of psychopaths did you
did i haven't talked to you about the fucking godzilla movie coming out this year have i
no but i'm excited you know of course you're fucking oh my god i'm so ah it's like two of the
coolest things yeah uh i've wanted a godzilla animated movie forever before we go down to godzilla
let me finish my point about that i just i'll put my boat away for just that just that index it's
waifu driven it's full of you know anime cliches and dumb bullshit is it worth reading no it is
because it is it is so fucking unhinged with ideas like index has the most detailed
like series of rules and like like things go like every book basically is just to introduce
as many concepts as the author can think it's super interesting when like things like that
happen because like you can it's very interesting when you find pieces of media that are doing so
many extraneous things just to like you know like the author or whatever has like one specific
goal they want to do like this is what they actually care about yeah but you can't just do
that no it's like i can't just make up rules and publish them online and people yeah the man i mean
it's basically a wiki the book is like a wikipedia like like you know if someone just wrote a wiki
for a show and then just like loosely turned that into a book that's kind of what it is i do enjoy
those it's it's just and he never stops coming up with shit and it can lead to amazing shit like
for instance um accelerator is a crazy dude yeah no like the concept of the story is that like
there's there's the academy city which is built built around science and they have to teach people
to like use powers so it's kind of an x-men city like like it's all young people learning how to use
superpowers and they only believe in science but then in like in the beginning of the story the main
character meets this girl named index who is with who works for the church and the church is entirely
governed by magic and it's but it's a secret world it's a whole secret world of magic so basically
the story is about this secret world of magic colliding with the city of science which both
have totally different series of rules like the way that science works is really deep and complicated
and has tons of rules and the same is true of the church and magic but they're totally different
from each other it is cool but meanwhile the main character his only power is that his hand can cancel
anything it can cancel all magic it can cancel all science and it constantly cancels his own luck
it can cancel all science so everything for like anything he touches everything will go wrong for
it of course the first thing this is used for is uh the the girl index i'm wearing a protective
magical garment but it's but it's genius how it's done it is because because index her outfit is the
walking church right and it protects her from all magic and she she like brags about it it's like
super powerful or something yeah it's like the most powerful armor in the magic universe and he
touches it and it explodes off of her immediately lol naked yes but but it is a clever it works no
it works in terms of like it totally works totally objectifying the female lead that's one of the
better ways i've heard she's garbage anyway she gives a part she's a retard yeah a literal retard
and she doesn't matter after the first book uh but i got my tits in the first book you're all
fucking yes she's a she's a lol yeah but uh well this for people like but that's the thing about
index is that like the like the what happens in the story is just dumb tropey anime bullshit but
how and why it's happening is this really bizarre series of crazy i really wish we could get something
like one punch man for these books like someone just like this is good ideas i'm gonna make it not
below dick well the best okay here's i'll give you one example because this is something i was
watching season two of index and like the first arc of season two was kind of boring up until it
got to this point where like there's there's all these combat nuns right like like that show up
and they're having this huge battle oh i did it and there's and they're fucking did it what did you
do i killed the orc wizard nice orc wizard yeah i was playing a fucking game are you playing i was
fighting an orc wit yeah i know usually i deal with things like bees but um i just meant that orcs
wait are we in the second level orcs and wizards are not i'm like ford i'm like ford
floors deep all right well done level two or level one well this is this is the first zone
okay i just saw a lot of trees are you going down floors or up floors down you gotta go down
okay you're going deeper into the abyss i wasn't sure if you're already in the ow are you getting
yes i'm being harmed i just like the screen is flashing i'm like usually that's a sign oh god
was a fucking iguana oh my god why is it you defeated i can't deal with this shit
i really don't understand okay i think i can get away ramp up yeah it looks like at all
oh thank fucking thank thank guanas do thank mock lab
so anyways there's all these combat nuns and they're fighting on the roof of this building
and like there's just one girl this game is a fucking clusterfuck i'm getting like i'm having to
like flee every floor like back and forth because there's all these things that i don't want to deal
with but then they keep pushing me back you can't keep running away from your problems then there's
just no end to the stupid shit look that's life okay well i have to run away from my house in six
months well sure okay okay okay combat nuns yeah all on the roof finish your thought fighting fighting
this building and like there's all these people running around with all these different fucking
powers and there and all the combat nuns have different weapons everyone's got something unique
every fucking character's got some completely different crazy shit with its own rules and
there's one character who's like singing this uh this hymn and like it's like permeating through
this this whole area and like it makes it so people can't use like certain attacks when
there's this hym's going and they really need to use those attacks so all the nuns pull out chopsticks
and just stab themselves in the ears so they can no longer hear the hymn and it won't disrupt their
magic and so they go in and start fighting and i was like like when you see something like that it's
just like everything's justified all the dumb bullshit is justified because that was awesome
it is pretty awesome we need we need some lots of stuff like that they just someone who rents
do you know how they make a bajillion dollars it's super edgy by the way one of these light
well there's a lot of fun well the thing about index is that it has edgy moments but it's really
goofy like i've seen a bunch especially like the anime i mean the anime is goofy itself but the
narration of the book is really like sarcastic and silly and like doesn't take itself seriously at
all like you can tell that it's which is what i like about it it's not that it's well written
but it's very silly it doesn't take itself seriously and it's fun to read and uh and there's lots of
there's just so many like random comments like the main character will be running down a hallway
and he'll like there'll be talismans all over the walls like because of some you know something to do
with some magic and then he'll like make an observation about like hmm and i noticed that
like it says this thing which means this and like um oh yeah that's why those are there and i'm just
like there's this is so much like it's so much shit um and did you remember when we bought those
rambutans yes i just found some rambutans yes this game is why i know about rambutans although they've
they've generousized the fruits into just being fruits but they used to be you could find like
black currents or like lentils or stuff or just just like okay i found an artifact robe
it's gonna be wait i'm gonna identify it just for fun oh before i put it on every time you do
something it is a plus two robe a tuam oh it prevents me from casting but it's really good
oh you have to cast spells this is it oh my no it's so fucking good but it prevents spell casting
that's the worst possible so fucking good that's good if you need to fucking run away from something
because you're not going to be casting you can buff yourself you'll have it the thing is it takes
it's the robe of ben sainth kind of the thing is it takes a pseudo realistic amount of time to put
on things it doesn't just take one blip it takes like several rounds to put that is that is the worst
thing i've ever heard maybe here's that here's that secret here's that secret entrance i was
looking for before but it's long since rusted over oh yeah it did not work out that's okay it's
just the sewers fuck the sewers no i was i was saying like what if they want to like make a bajillion
dollars they need to one of these companies who publishes all these light novels they need to
just get that one successful thing we get like a trillion dollars and use like
half of it just like we're gonna hire a team of one get like all the gay step one get like a trillion
dollars well i'm clearly it's not that hard i'm sure these books have editors they're just very
lax they need they need better editors editing editing is is the thing but yeah like like
but the sad thing about all this is that like like something like index um is probably like at
best a six out of ten and it's still one of the better light novels well here's here's the thing
i can just hear you describe that i'm thinking like what if um jeez what if they just like decided
just cut the bullshit and they just just they wrote the book like you just described it's super
conversational so you're not even reading it with the expectation of reading a book it's just
like i want to hear some guy tell me what's cool of shit that would be great and some of them are
borderline that i mean that would be so i would be so much more down to read something like that
than someone attempted to do pros badly oh yeah i mean like that's every time i get stuck writing
s l i literally just turn into a valley girl and i'm like and then like they did this thing and it
just it comes out so much easier you don't have to like that's dude for years i was considering um
like abandoning writing books and just writing wikipedia's like i was just going to write wikis
for my stories because though they existed but not actually write the stories and so i mean i
don't know how i'd monetize that but i just like it was the only way i could think to just get the
fucking ideas out there without having to write shitty like like because the uh the the index guy
that's what he should have done that's what he wanted to do yeah well he he just works out well
yeah he's extremely famous no i'm talking i'm talking from a and also puts out integrity standpoint
and also has put out four books a year for 15 years by the way impressive work it is pretty
i will i will not and he runs like several extremely successful series want to do there is
impressive no matter how bad it actually is there is a quote inconspicuous book over right here that
sounds incredibly such incredibly conspicuous um so i but i need to be able to fly to get to it so
oh wait wait wait i have one i have a potion of flight well so i'm just gonna touch this clearly
fuck me in the butthole thing it is a sif moon is compendium of the frostbite uh which is honestly
not that useful so whatever it's a shame oh well that's fine yeah uh god the guy who writes index
he also writes heavy object which also got an anime adaptation last year and like several other
like he'll he will have years go by where he has written installments into like five different series
and multiples of some of those how do you even keep your brain organized like that
clearly he just doesn't he just needs to have a mental like orgasm every now and then just get
these ideas out of him i mean he's just he's he's one of those guys who's described as like you
know i don't want to do anything but be writing you know like a steven thing or something yeah
nissi always seen is also i gotta get to that point um and he's fucking unbelievably successful
but nissi always seen is another one where it's like in his case it's that he writes such his
okay i would describe his dialogue as so stilted and awkward that it's its own style and it's awesome
like it's it's it's full circle i'll give you the better have you ever seen any of bakemonogatari
or katana gattari or any anything with the gattari in the title oh yeah um
yeah he's known for those and and for some other stuff but his his like his characters all just
have the most bizarre like thought processes and like reasons for thinking what they think
and they just talk that's all they do his novels are just non-stop dialogue yeah it's really
none of which is natural at all but it's so fucking weird that it's really my books
are nothing but dialogue but it's done well not to to my own horn no no go ahead to your own horn
i mean nissi always seen is famous for amazing dialogue it's just that it's it's like amazing
in that it is so out there that it's really amazingly confusing um it's it's so interesting
because like this whole discussion we've been having like this entire time it's basically
saying like we live in like the post-talent era like you don't need to be terrified to be successful
why do i stress myself out so much about being good and yet and yet like like i i it freezes me
in place not be able to do anything because like it's not good enough but clearly being good
is does not matter anymore no well it's not the primer i don't think it ever mattered it's i don't
think it ever mattered well i think it matters significantly less now just because like the
volume of stuff can be done oh dude i found a store well i don't i don't think being good was ever a
thing i think it's just that there was a taste that that was that was calm you know i kind of i
kind of agree with you just because like shakespeare is so renowned and he's basically just like
trash back in his day well like it's just that like the reason taste gets made is like let's say
there's only let's say we're back in the day and you can only publish one book a year like you just
don't have the technology to publish more than one book a year you publish that book everyone reads
that book it's everyone's first exposure to art so their taste is that book it's true now if you
write another book that's nothing like that book people are going to go well that book was good
this is something different i don't like it as much this is bad and then if you write something
that's exactly like the previous book but you know a little different that people go oh this is like
that this is what good is you know and then everyone just takes influence from the same book
and that's what good is and then eventually there's people out there it's a gross simplification but
then there's i can't argue but there's some people who read that book and they go well i hate this
i'm gonna write my own thing yeah and i'm gonna write my own thing and then they write their own
thing and nobody cares about it because it's not good you know to them but then sometime in the
future we now have the internet and you can publish that you can publish that thing and
everyone goes uh like everyone's like well this isn't good until that one guy finds it who's like
this is exactly what i wanted and it used to be that you could only show whatever book you wrote
to the people in your village or to some publisher who doesn't want it right but now i can go like
like imagine your village is the entire world yeah your village is everywhere and like as long as you
can just get it into the hands of those people who want it then you're good and that's the hardest
part that's the entire struggle of publishing on the internet it's not about being good it's not
about anything it's about finding the people yeah finding your tribe exactly exactly what it is and
it's like where is my tribe are they on reddit are they on fourchan are they over here are they over
there i just gotta spam it are they on tumblr please tell me they're somewhere you know is it the guy
who inspired me is he going to like my stuff as much as i like his stuff let me send it to him
maybe he'll post it on his twitter you know like that's you're desperately trying to find your
tribe it is a struggle for sure this makes me wonder what the end goal of all this is
what's it what's what are we all getting at with this are we talking about humanity oh no
no you got this barely survived all right well barely survived that fucking centaur what are you
talking about the point of like of the creative struggle yeah the point of art in general why
it's consumed i think it's i think the why really why we should give a shit but the point i don't
think anyone needs to give a shit i think the only people that give a shit are the person making it
for themselves i think i like making it and i need to justify why well to me the purpose of art
is to let people contextualize themselves and the world around them people don't like when you when
you are just like let's say you're just working all the time yeah all you do is work and at some
point you take a step back and realize i don't even like doing this why the fuck am i doing this
why is living a thing why am i alive why would i be doing this and then you read a book and you go
oh that's why that's why that's why it's this thing this makes sense now and then you're like
i i want another and then you read another one and you go and this is how people sustain themselves
through working these like to me the most important thing my videos do is make it so someone who can't
do what i do uh and is working some shit job somewhere doesn't kill themselves today you know
like if my video sounds melodramatic but it actually is i've got lots of comments to this
effect in the past that like you know uh like your video came out today i felt like dog shit and
wanted to die and then i watched the video and now i feel okay like that's the most important thing
my videos can do is make people not want to kill themselves because the simple act of living sucks
you know um yikes something feels off about that like why what is their justification for not
killing themselves by being entertained just feeling just feeling like someone like whatever
you've never been working at your job and just being like this fucking blows balls imagine if
you'd went and worked at your job no i know i came home and did nothing but like stared a wall
and jerk off yeah you just didn't have the artistic spark but what but what am i giving that that you
can't like i think what you're asking is more philosophical it like like okay um why don't
you give an answer here's here's a great what do you think it is i think he's trying to figure it out
here's a great example from uh from how i have an answer how i've kind of understand this from a
lot of people like um you know i spend a lot of time on forums in the mid-2000s yeah and i would
continually see people uh like like uh this one forum called otaku boards obviously an anime board
and there there'd be threads about like why you're on this board oh god it's prince fucking ribbit
it's fucking prince ribbit guys it's the ultimate frog man he is the ultimate frog there would be
people who say things like you know in my town which is small town bumfuck know where you say
real bad um like i would get beat up for even saying i like anime like like because it's just
not something that anyone else in the community wants any part of and they think it's devil worship
and faggotry and you get beat up for being well they're not wrong now now let's say let's say you
live in the middle of bumfuck know where and you're gay right no one around you understands
and no one around you to talk to and you don't understand anything and then you watch a show
about being gay or that speaks to you even it's not even about being gay but it's the same kind of
thing right and you watch it and you realize oh like this is a thing this is not i'm not a fucking
demon i'm not a literal devil i'm not going to hell uh god isn't real but art is you know and then
you you you find something to to like to connect with and be like oh i'm a fucking human other
people feel this way you know but then you can't talk to it about talk about it with anybody in
your town because they still don't understand you so then you find the internet and you go wait a
minute there's a bunch of people watching this shit and there's there's gay people everywhere
i'm going to be gay with them and then and then you watch my analysis video so you can be gay with
me you know i see the point you're making and that is interesting and i do see a value in that
but you know what's funny is that the way that i think about my videos is they're kind of constructed
with an inherent assumption that of course anime can have intellectual content that is valuable and
should just be accepted but you know what's really fascinating is that my some of my closest friends
in life uh the guys i went to college with um even just recently i was talking with them about just
you know like gurrenlog and just because they watch have seen my videos and stuff and they just
do not accept that initial premise that there is anything good about anime and that there can be
intellectual content with it they don't even get past that and this shocked me i wasn't even able to
process it well you need to remember that was that was the nature of our entire disagreement about
why i even like the show in the first place they just don't understand that remember how it was
when we were all my little pony guys yes the same thing i mean it's the same thing we still to this
day we have people in the pcp oh my god will not acknowledge that like like like like jeff and monkey
both of them anytime pony comes up like they don't seem to like actually think that the show is
like probably any good you might like they really think we're all just fucking crazy yeah they're
like well that show is obviously gay and we tie him up at night and we force him to watch
i think monkey is in the place that i was before i watched the show and realized that there it really
can't be good oh god it's a bear it's a fucking bear guys for the record i don't think monkey would
like the show oh he gone berserk don't think it would be we need we need to have money watch the
japanese i just don't know then you can appreciate you'd appreciate that more yeah i'm honestly
surprised he has not done i'm honestly surprised he has not done an anime review of my little pony
like before i mean he's planning to do that would be fucking hilarious it seems like an obvious choice
he's he's planning to get bigger plans i think the next fucking uh what's it called anime spectrum
podcast is supposed to be about it really i don't know what to say like you know there's like 17
documentaries so i don't bother going down that route but like yeah like i don't think in in his
or jeff's mind like they even process the idea that it's possible that that show is actually
as good as one of their favorite shows like i don't think they even think that that is a possibility
i wouldn't you know i guess that just shows that people we really do have barriers within ourselves
that a lot of us have to overcome everybody does i mean i we all had to kind of get through that
to different degrees before i saw the my little pony show i thought it was bullshit
and soon it was terrible you know because like i i had to watch all the old ones with my little
sister because she was like five and i was like this is the gayest shit in the world so it was i
just think it was totally there's nothing that baffles me more and this is this is also true
of stuff like kaon and other stuff i like that people anything people treat this way what baffles
me is what you're about to make people will say things like digi bro you you seem like a smart guy
how can you like this thing and my response is shouldn't you shouldn't you reverse engineer that
and think that because i'm a smart guy the things i like probably have something going on you know
what do you think i just like lapse into insanity every day you watch my little pony for no reason
and this is like the thought process that inevitably got me to watch a show and like
anything else that initially was hesitant about was that it's like here's like the
primacy that happens i can either continue to assume that this thing is bullshit or i can
actually give it a shot and i can either a be completely justified in my hatred and nothing's
changed or b i've opened myself up to something new that i like i want more things in my life
to like well you know my friends this was the exact point i raised to my friends and i said well
how do you how do you rationalize the fact that i like the show and get all these things out of
that i have explained in this massive long video that you have seen how do you rationalize that
and their answer was very simple they say nate we think you are just projecting what you want
onto the show and that it doesn't actually exist i don't understand how anyone can think that it
doesn't make sense i don't get it all it is is people who don't make they're giving me so they
don't make art and they don't understand art we went over this in the fucking in the uh the the
intentions of the artist podcast that like everything that's in something had to be put there
you can't just like there's nothing i killed prince ribbit i am the champion of the dungeon
speaking of art art has just been created but wait dead frogs corpse but wait no but but but low
dear viewer look at this it is a human corpse that was left behind by prince he was a human prince
transformed into a blink frog oh my god just kiss him eat him anyway eat him anyway why didn't he just
ask me god you know i guess i guess he can only croak you know he's croaked the dungeon the dungeon
just corrodes our social functions and turns us into monsters well the real monster that's an
interesting point though yeah now i really it's well i okay i kind of want to play devils advocate
in the fact that i think you can project some things well sure it is possible you can project
but like but there's some stuff to there have to be degrees there's definitely there's definitely
agree you know okay for instance in uh in kill luck hill yeah like um some people have said like
what makes you think that like all the like there's all these themes that are that are supposedly
there about like um like japan versus the west and like how things went after world war two
sure and people will say like aren't you just projecting what you want to see onto the show
and it's like why would they choose to like recreate the exact three cities that obu no
odonobu naga went to on his conquest and have the like parts of the show take place there why would
they have like these certain names that refer to all these ancient gods who stand for all these
certain things and like like there's all this symbolism in the show that is that is objectively
there like those things are in the show and like you can very clearly extrapolate that these things
symbolize these other things and like people will say like how can you think that it's like
because none of this is here by accident they didn't they didn't just happen to write you know
the same cities and the same gods into the show and it knows not much more of a stretch not to
diminish the artistic integrity of of doing that but like it's easy to think like oh there's no way
they could have planned all this from like a viewer's perspective but when you're writing something
and you just have to you're inspired by things then it just it just gets in there people who create
or people who don't like think about art have a hard time realizing yeah because that everything
is intentional yeah you know it's just like every word is intention i could explain every single frame
of every video i've ever made and exactly why i chose to put it the way it was you know and in
another thing oh boy and this might this this might i don't know if you guys will agree with this yeah
but i think that the creative part is and like the ideas is by far the easy part like i could i
can make a show and stuff it with every fucking metaphor in the world the hard part is making that
work agree you know like writing that oh organizing the ideas yeah like like like i mean we could
right now i could just ideas i mean i think this is a great example ideas being easy and structure
being like look i could just pick up this can and be like all right this strawberry to can uh in in
this i'm gonna make a short film where i drink the strawberry to can and i place it on the back of
this couch and the couch symbolizes all of society and the strawberry to can symbolizes the atomic
bomb and i'm donald trump and this is what i'm gonna do to the world you know and i'll wear like
i'll wear like a trump mask and all this will be very obvious when when it comes out you know
so i'll just take a drink of the can and i'll say like fuck the world and i'll put it on the couch
and it blows up the world and you all understand right and like like i just came up that's all
stream of consciousness that's how a lot of creativity is like the actual ideas is just oh and
then this happens and this happens and this happens and yeah and then like actually making
that into a coherent a coherent narrative that anyone would get that's the hard part yo check
yo check this out check this out i got this sick ass spell called lee's rapid deconstruction and
it refers to the fact that it rapidly pulls apart ie explodes rocks and so it lets you deconstruct
walls so i'm gonna i'm gonna tear a hole in this wall to get at to get at that altar of vehuma
and pray to my the god that i want however another thing you can do with it is you can use petrify
which i also have i haven't done this yet but i may do it you use petrify and then explode them
but so because it's re it deconstructs rocks right petrify an enemy and then explode the stone
statue also it like does shrapnel damage to everything around it hey that's pretty cool i'm
gonna try and use this more because i'm finally getting to a level of spell casting you're turning
into a cool guy i'm finally getting to a level of spell casting that the spell isn't gonna be
misfiring and contaminating me with mutagenic energies every time i tried to do it only several
times but oh yeah only only maybe 10 percent of the time which is acceptable we're gonna be 10
percent muted instead of 40 yeah i've got a line for you that you should that you should have used
on your friends and could use in the future let's hear it it's it's just simply why do you think that
i'm smarter than the people who made this show that's exactly what i was thinking when we were talking
about this why would you think why would you think that i can get all this out of the show
but they can't i was going to say that's giving me a ton of credit yeah like that i just like i
just really am the best guy yeah i just creatively made up all this crazy stuff that the show can
symbolize just because i'm writing for tv yeah clearly yeah like if i'm if i'm projecting all
this i'm clearly a fucking genius and i have great ideas and i should have written this story myself
well okay i'm gonna i'm gonna say something else and and i agree with your statement completely
and i'm not gonna try i'm gonna try and like add an addendum onto it even if you come up with an
interpretation that wasn't uh supposed to be there i don't think that invalidates it no no at all
like there was an interesting uh there was an interesting uh interview with um uh jeff smith who
made the comic bone yeah sure yeah and he was talking about like because they one of they asked him
like like anything like that's like crazy thing that happened with bone like one of the weirdest
experiences you had with like interacting with people who read bone and he was describing experience
where uh there's the the whole like end like end of the story they're going to the series this um
this city called athea and they're they're trying to get there and they need to get some shit it's
been a while since i don't remember those specific i just remember they need to go to athea and um
they're traveling to get there and this guy comes up to him at a convention and they're talking he's
like gets the book signed he's like i really was fascinated by athea and like the way that you kind
of um because like athea meant atheism right so the whole thing is a metaphor for like the the
crumbling of like religion and going for like humanistic interpretations of things and and he's
just like what the fuck what the fuck just happened what the fuck just happened what do you mean
just like 50 turns past and i died uh did i sit on yes you fucking sat on the keyboard and killed me
i'm sorry wait how did that work though there's a button there's a button what button
s or space or whatever the space bar then that sucks too the f for the fuck you button it was an
accident oh my god i was gonna make it that time i was gonna make it to the ecumenical temple
all right pee break i'm sorry i'm gonna piss away my tears oh my that's that's terrible um i'm
i'm embarrassed that i'm not making it further on these runs but yeah the reason that was at your
fault the reason he called the city of thea is because it was just a play on the gold on
the reason he called the city athea it was just like he just like took athena it took out a letter
athena it sounded cool yeah but like this guy took it and totally ran with that but like
that doesn't technically make it like invalid like it's because like here's the thing how you've
never talked to the guy who made it yep so how do you know what he was thinking yeah you can only
infer you can only infer so varying degrees of even if it's like super obvious like maybe it wasn't
like maybe this guy like clearly like that was i mean as long as he doesn't like like okay there's
a difference between saying i got this out of it and saying like this is what it means yeah yeah right
the story is not about that but you can have that interesting take on it sure like like how i
have like made sordot online better for myself by believing that kirito is a new type and like
like to me that's canon and i know it's oh well i don't know that it's not intentional but to me
it's canon and it makes the story better and as far as i'm concerned it's true does anyone want a beer
we have some right here yeah this um yeah with this pass oh you brought it up okay
yeah i was gonna i will take one i'll take my actually i won't i don't know why i want
i have my cup of water not sitting right there i'm too late for beer
yeah a little bit it's too late i can't i can't fucking believe this dude i was on level seven
i was doing so good ah yeah drow new sorrows it's all my fault you can punish me with your
pee pee
dear viewers apparently did you saying i'm gay over and over is this is a new verbal tick
that's the meme well it's it's the best it's the best meme me and ben have both been doing
i've just been doing it more excessively we've been we've been subject to it since we got here
and uh when you guys like okay like me and ben just walk around the house like looking at each other
and going i'm gay dude me too man yeah i'm so gay yeah have you seen how gay i am
and the answer is always yes not to be funny it's just fine we admit it it's just i guess we've
been admitting it where have you been we feel a certain camaraderie i'm sitting in general
by by sharing our gayness that's good that's good it's healthy yeah you know it's grow and live
together this is the coming out cast yeah so i think the reason we live together but not in a
gay way they're not yet i'm sure you guys feel the same but the reason i'm so adamant about this
whole thing of like everything in there matters is because i know that there are a million things
that everything i make means that no one picks up on and that are like like yeah way more thought
was put into this than anyone realizes you know i'm making making something you know making a story
is it's a lot of fucking work and a lot of things have to go into that i don't feel like a lot of
people miss the things i put in then i tend to make things pretty obvious i guess i don't know i mean
my videos have too fucking many things i disagree in my videos not much is missed other than like
references that nobody would get or like just weird personal in jokes that i like like for instance
the phrase it's all a rich tapestry i work i'll work in the phrase rich tapestry all the time
because it's something that an anime blogger i was a big fan of was like his catchphrase
this guy called anime critique and he would always say it's all a rich tapestry and like
so any excuse i can get to work that into a script i will and like it just sounds like a it's it's a
pretty normal phrase it's pretty innocuous on its own it's only when you realize that i've used it in
so many fucking videos that you'd go that's weird people don't say that all the time yeah yeah but
like but for me it's this in joke that i'm making like this reference to this this anime guy who's
not even around anymore for the past five he might actually be dead he was he was in like thailand and
there was like he disappeared during a time of political upheaval in thailand oh dear nobody's
heard from him since he was killed on the australian brush fire i really hope not he was one of the
coolest fucking guys on the internet man it will be a real shame if he's gone but hopefully he's
just been in the gulags for a while yeah uh but anyways you know there's there's lots of stuff like
that and then the rap lyrics like the reason i did the whole three hour analyzing my own
raps video it's just because like almost every line it means more than first appears but sometimes
it's just a fucking like the the first word that came to mind that rhymed with the last word is why
that line is there it's interesting how like your creativity has like it has peaks and valleys in
terms of like how invested you were in things well it's just that like i i really enjoy serendipitous
connections i say this all the time like i really enjoy when something just happens to work out and
it is perfect more so than when i really set out to make it perfect like i find a lot of joy and if
i can if i can write lines that just spiral into one another and it brings me to somewhere cool i want
to carve out my fucking victories from the block of marvel in which they're in case i have found
i am trying to become more i go first but it was gonna say in in art i feel like learning to just
not learning to just kind of draw whatever and just sort of deal with it like like i used to save
all my late i used to save everything on different layers and now i'm a lot more as i
combine layers just put it all in one layer if it doesn't work out they're just like i'll you know
i'll correct it yeah i think it's a more healthy way to do it because it is less sacred and you
get more loose and the other thing is like like okay the one of the reason that champion has taken
so long is i had a real shitty um work method before where i i sketched all the it's normal to
sketch all the pages and then you go back and ink them but i've been doing nothing but inking pages
that have been sketched for like months now and i've like i'm right i'm right on the cusp of
finishing that and after it's done i'm never gonna do it again i'm never gonna pre-sketch i'm always
just gonna just draw it as i go because that's how i do with brunswick and it was great yeah and i'm
gonna just just not fucking just just not fucking i'm just well it's not that i'm not gonna sketch
it's that i'm gonna sketch and finish all the same in one go um and and just do a video on how you do
that so i can just you have to figure it out maybe i will actually maybe i will actually that will make
for better fucking uh speed draws because you'll be able to see the entire process yeah okay just
give me the the not speed draw version because i have just watching for like six hours i would do
it too that's how i absorb information slowly hence my whole problem that's why i'm still done
all right um anyway so yeah a fucking fucking whatever let the chips fall where they may that's
all that's what i'm saying the way i write raps is the ultimate in the serendipitous stuff because
i go into every rap with literally no plan i write the first line and like let's say for instance
well here's the one i had like the most plan for was uh i'm mortal and like i was listening
to the beat and it kind of reminded me of chrono trigger and then i thought about how
like in a game like chrono trigger you beat the final boss but ultimately a thousand years later
they're just gonna come back and and all the people you're saving are just gonna die anyways
everyone dies like saving the world is really just prolonging the inevitable for everybody in it
the only way to actually save the world is by creating the singularity and we live forever
you know so yeah everyone else is just a temporary bad guy look at this fucking shit this is an
altar of vehumet right here surrounded by a matrix of fucking spontaneous fireballs well that's
annoying it's it's a bit i'm vex i'm feeling a bit vexed right now but i want it really bad
i'm gonna brave this fucking fire you made it i could die any second oh god oh god i'm all right
let's just i want this okay vehumet welcomes you now let's see if his holy fire eviscerates me
before i go yeah you made it thanks no it looks like i was i'm i'm i'm chosen i was i was chosen
by he something i wanted to i wanted to mention about like like creative process and stuff because
i'm becoming more comfortable with the fact that like pain is right and not wrong yeah because like
i like punished myself for not having it come easily where like yeah if you like want to fucking
kill yourself that means you're on the right track and not on the wrong track well let me sort of
it's sort of well depending i mean the whole thing is that like it's not it's not gonna look
just like usually like you said it's carving it out of the marble you don't you don't just look at it
and it appears you know one of my favorite lines guys is uh i forget which bodybuilder said it but
nothing but a peanut yeah ain't nothing but a peanut ronnie colman ronnie colman the classic
it was uh this is it's about weightlifting but it applies to art in general i think it's um
man is both artist and canvas and he has to chip himself out of the marble in which
is created to sculpt you know whatever you get the idea it's a good line it's a good line yeah so
so anyways that i'm mortal song so that that whole concept i had i came up with the first
three lines based on that concept i would love to save the world but i know every everything dies
we know the cycle never ends but we continue to try if i miss the singularity within my life i'm
fucked and so i wrote the rhyme scheme so then it was just what rhymes with fucked oh no oh jeez oh jeez
so perfect so getting cut by the universe my favorite line in the whole song just because
fucked rhymes with cuck so if i miss the singularity in my full life i'm fucked getting
cucked by the universe now what rhymes with universe verse uh uh it's a little a little
cheap but okay sure yeah well i also do lots of internal rhymes in my songs so i usually am not
as worried about the end and end rhyme but um what if i pull a sing about me and get shot by the
end of the verse which sing about me is a song by kendrick lemar where a character gets shot in the
middle of a verse it's super dramatic and it makes me cry every fucking time i hear it because he's
he's saying like uh he's like um and if and if this meets you for your album or if i die before
your album drops i hope you and then you hear cucko co and it just stops fucking i never understood
what the hell is going on there but now he's he's like kendrick's reading a letter like the whole
concept of that song is he's reading letters from people from the ghetto who are who are still there
like talking about his music and what it means to them so the one guy's like really you know like
yeah man you really got out there and you're saying something that means something you know i hope that
one day i can make it out but as he's saying that he gets shot and dies it's brutal it's really
fucking horrific um anyways so i'll pull a sing about me and get shot by the end of the verse
the real curse is not knowing yet feeling the need for their goal towards which to continue growing
and never slowing even when it hurts and it's just me thinking like what word rhymes with slowing
and how does that relate to this theme and then i just keep building more rhymes on yeah there's no
fucking plan and any of them all of them are written very fast and uh and i feel bad about it
because my rhymes are the weakest part of my songs is that they're they're not creative they're all
just like the first word that came to mind that i could work into fitting the theme somehow but as
a result that's how i do it too i have like four or five songs where i have the lines um uh uh uh
stacks tax uh like i keep rhyming tax and stacks and health and wealth like i'm always talking about
how i'm trying like like all i really care about is my health and wealth and so i keep bringing it up
over and over again throughout the album because it's such an easy rhyme yes it is that uh that it
just always comes up but yeah i like that that kind of uh just just run at it as hard as you can
and let make things come out of it out of the uh out of the out of the bullshit i've been in awe
recently being around jesse again it his is almost uh unbelievable ability to spontaneously rhyme on
command yeah it's it's uh it's above what your average human being is capable of it really seems
to me everything that's good about jesse's art comes from a place of just being a literal artistic
genius and like that one certainly seems that way at the very least i i feel like most of what's good
about him has less to do with forethought and more to do with just raw ability to come up with shit
yeah off the top of his head out of nowhere he has good he has good creative it's it's so interesting
for me to be around that it's like a you know it's like a stat balance thing right yeah like he has
all of his points taken out of competence at basic human function and all put into creative ability
yeah um that's the only that's true i mean when you i want you when you look at jesse if you ever
feel jealous about his creative ability just consider what cost it has come at and ask yourself
if you want to live that life yeah that's true that's true do you want to live that life remember
just remember what it took to get him here remember you know another remember how he
actually feels about his own life which is pure misery and ask yourself if you want if you want
the talent at that cost and it's also important to reflect on how capable is this person of enjoying
the spoils right which is really not at all what you're saying and then no matter how much
he makes on patreon it doesn't matter because he hates his job you know because he'll just never
forget that girl in high school he knew who i don't even know but something happened and it'll
never forget it well apparently he's now uh like he's now officially i won't talk about this on the
show but i'm curious well talk to him later no i hate it well he's he may or may not be actually
like hooking up with boozy flusie she might be his real girlfriend she is his real girlfriend is
that a fact well you know i i didn't want to get into that i was just saying they're gonna get a
place together and everything whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa well he's busy moving out of the basement
i think so i think we're gonna get a place together up there in michigan i'm actually like
really happy to hear that yeah it sounds cool pot potentially positive positive thing uh but
anyways yeah he can't be happy because he hates youtube and he doesn't respect the medium at all
yeah uh but it's also where he makes his money yeah the problem is i hate everything i do yeah so
that's that's not fun that's a challenge it is mentally let's let's go get him he's downstairs
he's sleeping he's vulnerable let's fucking get him guys like like like kill him yeah yeah like kill
him you know what's our motivation again i don't i don't know okay whatever he's finally started to
be happy we can't why are you asking me about motivation it's time for action question good
boy good boy this is this could be our only chance to do something we gotta find out if you're
killing artists you gain his powers oh god it's segment i don't i don't know if i want if i only
get the powers it's only the powers yeah the rule states the powers not the deficiencies yeah that
just wouldn't be fair that would be nice because you you because that wouldn't be fair because you
only know his powers and you don't really know persons deficiencies i know jesse's deficiencies
well you do i experience jesse's deficiencies all the time such as when i'm trying to get him to
radcon and he hasn't bought a fucking plane ticket until two days into radcon yep yeah it was a very
port city and is what i would consider a deficiency i i wouldn't argue that fact
i'm gonna fucking have an ulcer oh i have one i don't recommend it oh no i think things will
actually have an ulcer i actually do have an ulcer holy shit from stress yes i've been in the
hospital seven times in the last six months because of stress jeez that sucks yeah good times oh no
have you considered taking a chill pill um well good idea good idea i've there they
i've talked to three therapists they've all said you probably should be partially committed that's
how fucked up you are i'm just like no oh dear fuck that that is scary so scroll teleportation
oh please activate is there a way to be partially committed there we go it's you do like a nine to
three thing on weekdays and you just go there they try like a full-time job how do you make money if
you uh how do you survive you don't do you get welfare if you're partially committed no you do
well then what the fuck why would they yeah what a shitty recommendation it's a week long program
i guess only do it for one well i guess that's not the end of the world i work on weekend so it
wouldn't fuck with me well why not go for it is it expensive i have no idea i never as soon as as
i said i'm like well i'm not talking to you anymore i'm fucked we're not that fucked i refuse to
admit to myself that i'm that bad well that sounds like a healthy way to go if i had if i if i have
any problem at all i'm gonna go seek help that's my current policy even like if i stub my toe and
it hurts for more than an hour i'm going to the hospital that's that's i mean my problem is like
i'm like a hypochondriac so like already like freaked out about medical things too much already
yeah but they told you to go do it well it's not like you're just making this up in your own mind
that's true i guess i guess part of my anxiety and depression is feeling anxious about my anxiety
so it's just it's a fun little like stacking effect yeah synergy anxiety is uh is synergy yeah
it's pretty bad it wouldn't recommend it you know how a black hole like splits you in half over and
over and over again forever is that true uh well it's a theory if you get sucked into a black hole
it keeps dividing you in half over and over forever wait along what line i don't know about that man
what does that mean okay whatever all right sounds cool i like it i heard it in a thing one it compresses
you into an infill i think it might happen in a junji ito but oh yeah all right that's about right
no i think throw that out the window i have heard it in something but it was sci-fi so i don't know
yeah all right how true it is i don't think i don't think that's true um well i don't think we
we're going to assume it's true and that it's a metaphor for anxiety all right that's good so like
like an intentional one i'll accept it i'm in a black hole of emotions right now that sounds
fucking emo every every every everything you're anxious about like doubles it does it creates a
second anxiety it's really fucking annoying and you can't really do anything about it well you
can't really do anything about it right i can do something about it well i'm glad you're better
me in that way too i guess uh you just have to now i feel anxious about being inferior to you
oh no way well i i just like when i hate when people say you when they mean themselves
because it's like like it this is everyone does it all the time but you know people people people
people say like like when someone's telling a story about something that happened to them
and they keep saying you like like they're describing that they walked into a club and
saw like these like like a beautiful light and that's like and you walk in and there's this beautiful
light and you're just like oh my god and i'm like no none of that happened to me this is your story
this happened to you you know do people tell first person accounts in yeah all the time i've never
personally done that if you if you listen to enough people talk you're gonna start now now that i've
i gotta i gotta say did you this is not something i've experienced you've just you've just ruined
conversation now that i've put it in your mind you'll notice it forever i did i did i told my mom
this problem and like it suddenly bothered her more than anything in the world for years that
she i feel like as long as you like frame this with like picture this that would solve the whole
problem i mean oh god it's my ghost it's my fucking ghost he's back he's back with my dad like that
that exact example i used of walking into the club is one that i remember my dad that is so weird
i've never heard anyone tell you know what maybe you probably have dude it's probably the first
time it happens i'm gonna call you up and just say faggot and then hang up your phone and you'll
know why this is so terrible i'm fucked i'm gay i'm just gonna drink all my potions pray for the
best and and hope something good happens read all my scrolls scroll of identify really helpful
the worst part about what i just described is that i also say you when i mean me sometimes uh and yet
i complain to other people when they do it well we're all hypocrites but because i especially the
fact that i put it in my mom's head anytime i do it around her she immediately correct me
i'm just like uh but but she my mom's passive aggressive and never just says what she means
like so i'll be telling that and she'll just start going you yeah and i'll be like what what do you
what do you fucking mean you she's like you like well at some point i have to like realize oh i must
have said you and that meant me yeah i gotta have a twist the knife a little bit on that
she's she's i'm gonna be okay i'm gonna get away my mom has an interesting way of communicating
which is i'm gonna shoot him before i go it didn't work say things that make sense to her without
consideration for whether they make sense to you in the moment
oh god i'm so gay so gay what time is it it is like four or five in the morning oh my god
this is like the best podcast we've ever done it's a really good podcast i was i'm surprised
wide ranging it's it's it covered a lot of bases everyone except ben said a lot but ben
i've been having a great time over here ben ben said the most emotionally charged things
is a good way every time ben freaks out and dies we need to put a mid roll add in
that's actually a great idea why not i ask you this is the segment this is the ultimate
decompression chamber i'm just gonna call this like the procrastinators decompression chamber
it's everything works for me this is why we all need to be in the vicinity so we can do
shit like this all the time yeah this is exactly what i want everyone patreon.com slash all of us
fix this problem this could be a bi-weekly series if you people got off your ass no it's more ghosts
it's more ghosts ben because that you buy this ghost constantly that's those are the only ghosts
the only ghosts are you that's enough that's deep man granted like 50 percent of everything i said
is stuff i've also said elsewhere that people probably be like yeah we know yeah we hear you
say this every other week don't assume that everybody
that's why that's why it's good that like yeah like you know i i personally hear myself talk so
much that i get really paranoid about telling the same stories all the time and it drives me crazy
because through the process of having made 1600 videos yeah everything i have to say has been
something interesting like i've been i've been just looking at stuff in journal like blogging
and vlogging and stuff and people recycle content constantly yeah it's a good strategy well the thing
is i think the problem with me is that most people recycle because they don't remember like like i've
seen yeah really like i don't know okay there's definitely an intentional recycling of content
for some some people are like uh like almost like bernie sanders i have this i have a problem with
bernie sanders which is that one time i decided to actually watch him talk and then i did another
time and he said all the he said the exact same thing he has like two thousand points the entire
which is both the strength and a massive weakness yeah and well it just makes it it makes it so as
soon as i've seen one of the sauce like oh i'll never watch him again yeah the only thing the only
reason it worked is because the two things he was saying nobody was talking about yeah well there's
some there are some like internet personalities who are like really hammering this one point
that they want like everyone to accept and all their stuff is about that like the guy who does the
the ten universes theory he's got like fucking a hundred fucking videos on his channel all just
explaining the same theory like more and more in depth uh i mean i think he's probably on some
level insane yeah probably but like there's a lot of people like that but then there's
ones like dan avidan from uh game grumps where he'll tell the same stories like over and over
because he just has a shit memory and doesn't realize he's told them before and erin who's too
busy playing video games doesn't stop him yeah you know uh or kasey nice that in the process of
watching all his vlogs i've heard him explain certain things like dozens of times just because
he obviously doesn't remember everything he said in a vlog yep uh but i remember everything i've
said so like i start telling a story and i immediately know i know i've said this before
and i'll i'll say it often in the chagas i know i've explained this before but but there's only
like two people who've actually heard me explain everything yeah i'm sure that's true like i think
if i could help explain whatever you're doing at that time or even if it's just if it's pertinent
to the topic at hand it's worth repeating if it's especially when you have a cajillion subscribers
like you do well most i mean like if this was a main channel content i wouldn't count on those
people having heard anything i've said yeah because the only people who i really think of as my audience
are the people who watch all the other shit the procrastinators is a fucking cult and we know
that you all suck our dick i like i almost i'm at a point right now just suck our patreon
dicks a little bit harder and you'll be even cooler i'm honestly at a point where i really
don't think of digi bro as like my channel it's just like a repository for my high effort content
yeah like like the stuff on the digi bro channel sounds like you're a brand now dude well like
pretty scary the procrastinators channel and digi bro after dark ink oh no like like digi
bro to dark and procrastinators these are channels that i manage like out of like a personal need
to make this kind of content and to and to have a conversation with this audience like like the
people who are watching this stuff i'm expecting them to be watching like a lot of shit that i make
and to be like following this ongoing narrative of who i am and the people watching digi bro like
those are just videos that are constructed to be like a piece of information that i want to share
and those people like anyone who's not also following all the other shit i don't expect them
to know anything about me you know so like the presentation of videos on the digi bro channel
is in a vacuum each video is presented as though the others don't really exist whereas the videos on
the videos on after dark and procrastinators are presented assuming that you know literally
everything about me if you're watching on digi bro you're a fucking normie if you're if you're at
the procrastinators level you're now a cult member yeah i mean to start selling robes because the
problem by him this channel like i think one of the weaknesses of this channel in terms of growth
is that it's very assumptive because it totally we all assume you know all nine of us you know
there's nine members and we just work from the assumption that you're familiar with all of our
because we it's not even like if you're in a niche you know all of us we're all scared you know
it's not like the horse days when we all kind of did the same yeah we're all over the math now
like i mean here's a sentence that comes up in nearly every procrastinators is in my video that
came out today it's very and and like we say it all like like like if we're talking about the lucifer
in the biscuit hammered video you'll say something like you know well this video i just put out the
lucifer one you know and like if you know anyone who doesn't follow your channel or hasn't seen that
video has no fucking idea what you're talking about and if they're listening to it like 20 weeks later
in another videos out then it's no longer your latest video and so like yeah every like we do this
constantly on the show yeah we always talk about using like cards or something to start like back
linking to yeah i mean that takes effort it does like we'll do stuff like like make a like a joke
reference to something that happened in an episode of a monkey jones let's play yeah and we will all
laugh like because we all think it's funny as shit and it's like how many audience members
have watched a monkey jones let's play at the same time though would we really want to make
professionalism or anything else we would not want to dumb it down no yeah we have to like the goal
is to suck more people in to make them watch all this shit we want we want you to be cult members
that's really the if you feel like you don't know what you're doing that's your fault i mean we have
to just be here yet format changes have come up about ways to make the content more appealing to
wider audiences i don't know how to solve this particular problem here well like we hope that
people will eventually love us more if they just watched all of us it wouldn't be a problem so
just do that i mean but like when we make because some of this stuff like horseshoe heaven yeah that's
got like a hundred subscribers like a couple hundred and it's my fucking it's my favorite of
jessie jessie's channel of course it is the one that i would unsubscribe last if i had to cut all
my channels if i am speaking correctly the only way to find out about horseshoe heaven yeah was like
like hey it was a secret link it was a hidden link in a video yeah and the channel it actually
has like 300 subs i think well i think it has like 700 or something yeah it had made a hole to do
about passing it has like 500 i think yeah yeah but like it was literally a hidden link on one
endless jess video yeah so if you haven't watched that one video and found the hidden link and
actually sat through yeah all of horseshoe heaven then you probably don't know what alien boy is
that's true and so when we all start laughing about alien boy or making a reference to like
kid i be in this video like these are all jokes that no one gets no one knows what we're talking about
we must sound like mad men but we're not you're the mad man for not being cool enough yet yeah
but like like even if we just said like go watch all of our videos on all of our channels like that
still is not gonna lead you to horseshoe heaven no it won't think about this though how fucking
mind-blowing would it be is say like two years from now we go to like some random convention or
something yeah and people come who are like fucking on our level and just like die we can talk to them
like we know them i mean there's people that would be like eerie that would be interesting that would
be that'd be really fucking i don't know if i'd like it that's really famous i think i would think
it was cool if people i think there's people i can like lachlan still uh who's a frequent commenter
like he knows like i have never really spoken to him but he knows literally everything you know
this means some people's tizm is us yeah it's interesting like lachlan lachlan i mean he makes
his own videos now too but he knows yeah he's he's watched everything i've ever made and everything
anyone in the pcp has ever made and most of what we've ever made reference to and like like you know
if you want to cheat i mean it's not just us he follows a lot of people but like he knows
everything there is to know about us and he can come into like a thread like like on my Reddit
and just like say some shit and i like to me it's like yeah like i don't even i don't even stop and
think i've never talked to this guy because just knowing that he's seen all my videos i already
have an understanding that like this dude knows me yeah there's nothing that i could say you want
to show cuts getting on this level the reddit is like a very well updated compilation of everything
we do in reverse chrono it all gets posted there and one that we've been kind of meaning to like
make a bigger deal out of we kind of should i guess it doesn't have many subs i just i just i never
read it i don't read it any that's on you guys i go on this the procrastinator subreddit just to
see what you guys have been posting oh really yeah i don't check your individual i just subscribed
everyone i need a good reason to use reddit i haven't found one yet someone made me a reddit for
rebel pixels and i've touched it like twice and i feel like the biggest shit lord who ever lived
because that was like such a nice gesture and i'm just like well i don't fucking know what to do
with it i don't i don't think i don't think like all of my stuff gets posted that channel but all
of it's it's posted to my personal subreddit for sure yeah yeah well i mean there would be like
three times as many posts and no one can find any of it my subreddit is like shockingly very
active like like not just with my content like people post like there's there's like a whole
community on my subreddit that's cool yeah um just of people who i don't know will be asking
something or other or just talking to one of like some people come in there because they hate our
anime so much that they will just have conversations about shows on my subreddit because it's like
people who are kind of like isn't that nice you know that's i mean that's what you need you just
need wouldn't it be great to be the our anime alternative one day i would i would love to
have an all our anime alternative not necessarily for it to be my board because we do like me and
Lachlan who's the mod we do remove like stuff that's not at all relevant to me okay but we'll
leave up like if it's a discussion of like a show that everyone knows i love then like yeah we can
discuss that here you know yeah obviously i'll have something to say that is a tough balancing
act for sure because if you let it go too unfiltered it the original purpose yeah i'm fairly strict
about that i don't want people posting bullshit because yeah it does it gets out of hand immediately
if you let it happen right so it's it's not a good not a good short leash um but i think the the
procrastinator subreddit like the problem is that none of us go on there so no one feels an
incentive to like yeah like i don't i don't know who's reading it it's well updated because rival
steven is fucking you know always post all our shit there and uh and duvou has at some points
paid him to continue doing so really has he wow he's like he's like just thrown him like
ten fifteen dollars just like as a kudos saying like hey well that's nice okay that's that's
different than saying like please keep updating this i'll pay you that's that's how i interpreted
that statement that's on him though i do not endorse that activity no do do it for the love not for
the cash i mean patreon i mean i won't that that guy is pretty dedicated i mean to do it at all
even you know it's super cool yeah he's some he's one of the people who sometimes there's like
there's like a small cabal of people who post all my stuff to my sub because i don't post anything to
my sub it's all my i just don't want to get into any territory we're expected to be paid for this
sort of thing you know absolutely i don't think it would be that way yeah all right uh so i mean
my personal subreddit there there was a guy oh shit i just remembered there was a guy who was
posting all my stuff to my personal subreddit yeah and then he was like i can't do it anymore i was
like cool no problem but then like a week ago or two weeks ago he even he messaged me and was like
i can start it again and i just forgot to ever reply so i should probably tell him yeah i'll
make you a mod again because that was fine i mean i was i had been letting it lie completely
i am in a constant state of feeling bad about people i ignore it is the worst yeah you can't
you can't you can't communicate with everyone that wants to talk to you when you're when you're
this fucking popular bro you can't you can't please everyone you know what i'm saying like it's
not even just everyone who wants to hear from me there's a lot of people i legitimately feel like
i like if i respond to this person i will be happier for having done so and i just don't get
around there's too many fucking people and eventually if like like you sometimes if you
ignore someone enough time is there and they're just gonna stop yeah you're gonna take it the
wrong way yep it's true like we should just make a statement right now it's like at least 70% of
the time i made it i made it to the fucking ecumenical temple you did it ben you did it oh my god
it's level two well it's green not really all it is is just a place where all the gods have altars
except for the one if your life really sucked you didn't find this is actually every single god of
the ready excluded uh actually yeah the ones that aren't here are the ones that are in other places
in the dungeon such as behemoth the one that i wanted which i already found so this is totally
pointless and just symbolic that i'm making progress but how are you at level two yet there
isn't a level two there's only a second area no i'm still in the original area okay would flurry
one of the ecumenical temple is debatably a second area but like there's very little actually there
yeah are there any like actual dividers or just all kind of yeah there yeah there is there's like
special portals that lead to different regions and different regions have later regions will
like each have a rune in them right yeah so you should alter to an unknown god oh
you cannot you cannot tell which altar this god belongs to convert to them anyway
actually you know what i just realized i'm glad like i was getting worried because the problem
that i've been having at rad con so far and have had in the past uh with everyone forever
including me and ben working out is that uh it's really hard to schedule around people who
sleep at different times yes like because you're thinking of it as like we'll do this tomorrow
but my tomorrow is very different from your tomorrow and for a second here i was worried
because i was like oh fuck it's already like uh it's already like five in the morning i'm
gonna wake up so late but then i remembered that the main people i'm watching with tomorrow
are you two so it's perfectly fine oh is that true okay yes i'm mostly scheduled around you guys
like like i gotta do that one fucking movie with jeff right and jesse and then i'm gonna watch a show
with you and then i'm gonna do some of you know i've got you for two episodes as well yeah okay
i feel a little bad when when jeff when you and jeff came in and were like everybody quiet down
i i don't know i didn't like jeff's tone and i kind of gave him like a scathing look uh i feel
like maybe i just don't know the guy and didn't read his tone the way he meant to be read i felt
like he was being a real dick but i don't know i don't tend to be funny what okay well it did
not come considering he said hey fuck heads shut up for a second we gotta take this show maybe i
should have just assumed it was a joke when you when you get when you get cross like maybe you
should say something just to clear the air well i didn't i didn't like say anything i just looked
at him like what is your deal man i don't know well i should have us i don't know i'm being i'm
being cool i i had told him to go like i said uh we gotta like i said we gotta go make those guys
shut up so we could do this show yeah so don't worry i'll take care of it it was did you tell
you to shut up be a he was he was probably just joking and i just like wasn't in the mood to hear
he might he might be overestimating the uh how impressed we are by his uh by his presence um
he is a famous youtube guy you know he's he's quite active on the youtube he does quite well
be on that point and yet you're still making videos make your novel i don't it's not that i
don't care about youtube i'm saying i don't care about youtuber oh yeah no i do care about youtube
it's uh i thought you were done with youtube i i make a bunch of videos about that you were
done with youtube i make a bunch of i'd say a lot of things that i know i see i actually it's funny
i just recorded a um a sort of solo uh decompression video it's all about my inability to make choices
is it for rumble pixels it was going to be for procrastinators okay i did it last night
everyone's just done this but like yeah i i'm still resistant to doing it you don't have to do it
i would rather put a video like that on my own channel feel free to i don't know if i'm going
to post it at all because i did it when i was like still like really not feeling well so i'm not like
super energized about it it's just really funny and it might just be like super fucking gay just
like it's weird because when i made the decompression chamber i expected it to be a video
that none of you guys would watch yeah because it's it's totally very similar to my afterdark
videos that most of you guys don't pay attention to but weirdly everyone seems to be into them
and like everyone seems to listen to them it's it's the it might be because it's on procrastinators
i can absolutely explain why this is happening it's because when you go to afterdark you're
presented with so much fucking shit you feel overwhelmed that's just the way the human mind
if it's just one video a week where it's just like i'm going to be a faggot now
yeah we can we can deal with one one dose of fagotry but if you just like literally take
a shit on the channel constantly i mean like it wasn't it wasn't too surprising that ben listened
to just just so everyone knows i have butchered a human and am currently eating them good good
to know that's all i wanted out of this we've crossed the threshold like i wasn't survival mandates
certain uh extremes uh wait wait wait wait wait look uh yes this uh this raw flesh tastes terrible
it says well you know yeah it's it's you it always tastes terrible it's hard to eat raw meat you can
only eat raw butchered meat when you're really hungry unless you find an amulet of the gormand
which lets you just fucking stuff yourself on everyone's carcasses until you're like
you're actually a really good item because spell use casting spells like takes food energy
okay how do you how do you prepare cooked items you can't cook them you you can i you either you
find like permanent prepared food that lasts forever or you just eat raw food there's no cooking
this has brought me to an interesting thought uh which is that there's a big difference between
consuming and engaging with content right yeah for sure and and it's interesting to me because i
when i think of people who watch all my videos i think of like people like lachlan again who
who know everything about me and know all this history but there's plenty of people who do watch
all my videos and just don't care that much and ben is one of them because uh well i mean i care
you care sometimes why would you leave a comment when you could just go upstairs like that video
was gay and just go back well i mean it was before that ben ben consumes a lot of my content while
like drawing yeah just like having it on in the background and like i mean you watch like most of
the after dark stuff right i not recently but in the past i have and like like victor watches
everything i put out just because he's bored and sits on the couch but he plays 3ds do the whole
thing so he like kind of vaguely like victor's response to the vast majority of my videos forever
has always been well i hear you talk about this stuff all the time in real life so uh so it doesn't
that's a fair point so um so so like on the one hand you've got like davoo who will you know who's
actually way behind on my videos and has not listened has not listened to most of the after
dark or decompression stuff he basically doesn't watch youtube at all anymore like all he does he's
too busy working i guess all he does is watch anime and edit yeah um i mean like he's dedicated
dedicated himself to the cause the way it's it's really interesting to me because he thinks of
watching anime as work yeah like he thinks of it as i have to watch this i feel like my comment
in response to that guy who told you that you watching anime can't be work was very yeah that
that summed up all my thoughts on but but it's funny because like i don't think of watching anime
as work even though it's like it contributes to it because to me it only becomes work when it's
directly contributing to a video whereas davoo thinks that all anime he's watching is work and
therefore he yeah he has mentioned on many occasions how he wants to see every anime so
that he is more capable of making these videos fast but but in the way that like you and i've
been watching for a long time how dedicated he is to that because yeah all the time that he's not
editing for me he just watches anime well you know you know what that's because we live that's
because we haven't made the big move to the city yet and we're all still fucking we're all we're all
boring here and there's nothing else to do well because he gets part of it he he sees it it's like
i'm not like okay um he has all these other things he wants to work on video games and the reason he's
not working on them is because he's working by watching anime sounds like procrastination
to me it seems that way but he doesn't treat it that way like he thinks like watching anime is more
important to his career than doing those other things and then like doing those would be procrastination
realign your uh your interests and your priorities yeah i'm not the one to say that but i mean he's
doing good work he's he's he's doing great because like because the thing is that like uh close to a
year ago i gave him like a google doc of like every show i thought there was a chance i would talk about
at any point in the near future it was like probably a hundred shows and he's most of the
way through that list and he's made it out like you know i'll stop watching anime constantly
when i've broken this list uh with the the ironic part is that i actually he didn't even notice this
and i forgot until like like a couple weeks ago that uh it was an alphabetical list and it just
stops in the middle of the letter s because i just got tired of making it and never got back to it
so he's been like watching all these shows all this time and i looked at it and i was like
devu this list could be like you know like this is like two-thirds of what would be the list you
know so uh you know i can't i don't know if he wants me to write out the rest or if he'll just
be like well you know you gave me the list i'm gonna do that list if his goals have a thorough
understanding of anime in general watching a hundred shows or so is a very good start so he's
probably watched over 150 in the last six months you know what his secret plan is he's just training
under you right now and then like this time next year he's gonna start digivoo and just fucking
uh i've offered to have him put videos on my channel in the past yeah like to just do his
anime videos there um make sense try to remember why i was talking oh yeah the engagement thing
right that like devu's way behind on my content but when he watches that he's extremely engaged
like he soaks in every detail of it that's the most valuable thing you can whereas like like
ben watches most of my stuff hippo watches almost all of the stuff i put out like he always has
consumed like just about every single thing i put out but doesn't really care about much of it like he
doesn't really care about the things i'm talking about so like he just kind of goes in one ear
not the other and like every once in a while he picks up some intriguing things victor watches
all of it doesn't care but like but with the decompression chambers it's like everyone seems
to be listening to it and like uh you know why you know why because i live with you and i hear
yeah it's because we might hear about ourselves that's a big element i've never gone in thinking
i'd be talked about i've definitely done it all the time it's just weird because i definitely
watched the pcp to hear myself how fucking dumb i did or i'm so used to nobody being engaged or
really caring and then like i've been like people keep talking to me about the decompression chambers
and being like oh yeah what you talked about in this one and i'm like wait you listened to me
for an hour and a half i'm the boring like i think of myself as the boring guy in the pcp
really really because i'm not funny everyone else is funny i'm not funny i'm the boring guy at all
i mean i don't know man i mean you're not ha ha funny my main channel content in particular is
not funny well yeah like like like like you guys all like you and nate jesse and hippo who are like
the trifecta of extremely funny people like i feel like you guys really value a video being funny
true and my videos aren't funny so they are not valuable you know like my videos have always been
like i feel like everyone kind of thinks like yeah his don't really matter they're just fucking his
random thoughts that he puts out there i don't know so people tell me like i listened to an hour
and a half of you just literally talking about yourself usually like this strange mix of self
aggrandizement and self peril uh i'm like what you listened to that twice like you know like
more like more than one episode yeah and then everyone just started making their own and and
like i guess we all liked it like did it it's interesting because like my my channel like
talk about engagement is that like i did all these like videos on reviewing tablets i was like
there's people telling me free stuff why would i not do it yeah yeah but like the channel is
written is on to be just like art sucks and this is why like don't do this and like and those are
the ones that get way more engagement i'm just like they don't get a lot of views but everybody who
watches them gets something really like important out of it yeah so i'm just like they're very personal
for people they're so hard to make though because i feel like i'm just a bitch every time i make
i can't do that it's so hard i gotta tell you what what your channel reminds me of more than
anything um i know we've talked about this scene before and welcome to the nhk it's one of my favorite
scenes which is have you seen welcome to the nhk i've seen the first two episodes watch the whole
thing you know the general concept it's about a hikikomori uh you know and there's a part later
in the show there's this one arc where he meets another hikikomori yeah and it's like through
like it was like a girl what was his connection to that girl how did he know her she was i believe
a classmate who he met again later like it's like a classmate that he that he had in high school
and she's become like a part of a pyramid scheme she tries to like rope them in and then you find
out that the reason is she's she was the class rep i think yeah whatever she's trying to make money
like because she has to take care of her brother because her brother's a fucking shut in and is
and is a hikikomori in her room and um there's a scene where they go up to the brother's room
and he's like saying like there's no way out of this and he says i've read every self-help book
there is you can see them all on the shelves i could write one but i can't get out of it
and that's what your channel is to me it's a man who has read every self-help book knows all the
advice and is literally giving it to other people in spite of the fact that you cannot follow it
yourself and are dying yeah i mean no i'm like literally dying yeah he is literally dying he has
an ulcer in his fucking stomach and he's dying yeah uh out of just stress from art from this
exact thing there's nothing physically wrong with me and your channel is like here's how to get out
of that even though you are not out of that but it is all the right advice it's all the correct
the idea behind the channel right now and like what i want to kind of do more than if i can stop
being a little baby about it is that i don't want i wanted to be like being very honest in my
presentation like i'm going to give you advice i'm not the best artist in the world in fact i'm
probably like the lower like 25 percent if i'm going to be realistic true and that you're definitely
wrong being being publishable puts you in the upper 25 for like the the highest 25 i mean you
people have paid for your art that puts you in the upper 25 percent people paid for Reki Kawahara's
work would you put him in the upper 25 and all these ways to lower your value people aren't
really paying for Reki Kawahara they're paying for abec's character design that's true that guy is
the brother of the woman who designed kaon which means he has royal blood in his veins
no but like the idea is like i'm not well put together and like i wanted to kind of be like
you don't have to be a dude with like a bajillion subscribers and like supremely like god gifted
talent like that's just like emanates from everything you do right in order to to be successful
yeah it's amazing to me that you understand that what you cannot make yourself that's the whole
thing is like it's like everything i understand logically exactly what i need to do and how to
do it but like it's an emotional reaction that's beyond my control right so i literally like
with people like oh you need to need to just like get better like i go to therapists like well
you understand all these things i'm like yeah but like that doesn't look you just need to start
thinking more positively i'm like i have the same conversation with my therapist every week for like
two months like you just need to start thinking more pros like i get that yeah but i you you
you have clearly shown that you understand how to fix these problems because all the advice you
give is great yeah like the rebel pixels channel i've shared those videos and been like everyone
should do this you know you just haven't done it i just need a partial lobotomy and then i'll be fine
that might actually be true you know i mean i i felt when like that that what inspired me so much
about that particular chapter and like what happens in that the only way he gets out of it is that
eventually his sister just fucking leaves him and like he literally can't survive in his room anymore
dude so he has to get a job so funny because i did the video i just made about the decompressed
thing about choices saying how like it started like a i had like a self-help book i talked about
how people are more happy when they feel they're in control even if they're not because they did
the psychology experiment where um they they designed the most mundane game possible and brought
a bunch of people into play it was basically a number between one and ten would come up and they
had to guess would be greater or lower than five that was the entire game they had to do it for
like three hours and they found um that they would test it in two ways the first way was that you
hit a button for a higher or lower and then the second test would be a computer would decide for
you so you would they would the computer would pick one of the buttons and they found that
when you chose it you're were more excited you're more invested and when you the computer did you
were fucking bored sure then and they they the people were told they were being tested for
accuracy so like you're going to find out how good you are at this then they stopped they
touted the results and they told everybody who participated we lied to you everyone got the
exact same pattern of right and wrong there was no way you could beat this pattern and then they
sat them down and did it again and they still got more excited having the choice even though they knew
it was total bullshit their primitive dumb fucking animal brain got fucking psyched over like the
possibility of being right like having that control over the situation even though there was none and
so that was like the thing it's just like people are fucking stupid and you have to make choices
and then i go into like i don't make any choices like i'm so reactionary at this point because
i'm like a people pleaser that i don't do any of that like every time i even make a choice i just
like caught myself like did i make the right choice and then it's like i'm like thinking like i need
to i'm getting kicked out of my house now and i feel like maybe i secretly wanted to get kicked out
for years because then i have to start doing exactly what happens to the character he i'm literally
an anime by a way of getting by way of his fucking sister just like being like i'm sick of this and
abandoning him like one day because he would like bang on the floor to get her to bring food and like
he's begging on the floor and she's not coming and like a whole day passes and he's just like
i'm gonna die if i don't leave my room and i'll get food and so he leaves and he gets a part time
job and it's implied that he uh is happier having done that um but like for me that was a huge eye
opener because i watched that show when i was in the middle of you know fucking half a decade of
depression and i was like fuck me like what's clear like what became clear to me at the tail end of
being depressed was like again i read all the self-help books i heard all the advice and none of it
was working so i i told to my parents like i need medication because i i like my dad is the type
of person if you tell me you're depressed he's like well if you just gotta think of it this way
you just gotta do this i'm like i know i know i did the research i went online i typed how do you
cure depression none of that worked so clearly there's gotta be something else here like there's
i'm i'm fighting as hard as i can i'm doing all the things you're telling me and it's not working
so we need to kick this up a notch you know this needs to be different and maybe getting kicked out
would have worked for me i mean it wouldn't have put me in this situation for sure so i'm very
glad it didn't happen uh but like you know like i eventually they took me to a psychologist i got
medicated i got better you know like that's kind of what all the fucking people are saying to me too
just like your brain could just legitimately be fucked up yeah like and i mean i'm i'm lucky that
it worked for me because like victor who went through you know the same kind of depression
went through like six different medications and none of them worked some of them made him way worse
and he eventually just gave up and said i'm just gonna be depressed for the rest of my life
you know uh and his depression only finally stopped being like a constant force when he hooked up
with his current girlfriend and now he's like like the first time i've ever seen him legitimately
happy um he used to be so angry like he was angry all the time he would snap on you for anything
and ever since he started dating he's just been like fucking blissed out all the time i guess when
they just say you need to get laid it's totally true that's more than that it's i mean he was in
love with joke mate he was obsessed with her for a long time he has uh victor was telling us about
this uh this amazing book idea he has and i want it's so good it's so fucking good really his book
idea ever which is just the title it's a coffee table book that folds out into a coffee table
the book the book is called um how to find the love of your life in seven easy years no it's how
to get out of the friend zone in seven easy years right either way that's a very clickbaity titling
i love it that is that is like a buzz people are gonna like that shit seven easy years though
yeah no that's great that's a great title because that's how long it took him to get out of the
friends i i imagine all right all right everyone update update i am being i am being rampaged upon
by an ogre and a herd of yaks a herd of yaks are coming out oh god this dungeon has no fucking
chill no no this this is this is escalated what's that golden man there that is an ogre that's the
ogre okay he just has some yellow are you just fleeing for life i'm just looks like my only choice
is to go down these stairs and just see what see what happens um all right what the fuck is that
a purple ugly thing all right oh god they put me in the game you know uh i i also experienced
some tough some feelings similar to this at one point uh when i had when i had finished my four
years at school and i was back home and was doing these shitty media labor jobs while uh just like
taking like one class a semester and dreaming of one day finishing my degree and leaving i would
kind of like antagonize my parents every once in a while i really think i was trying to get them
to kick me out and like occasionally i would say that like if i'm fucking up so bad why just kick
me out and uh i think i was it was a cry for help i cannot imagine you saying that at all
that seems really weird you can ask dad i i like i would bring it up sometimes about like well maybe
if you kicked me out it wouldn't be a big problem uh but of course i was terrified of that notion
because i've never done anything by myself in my entire life i'm like half freak out mode half
like just whatever complacency i think is the biggest problem for our generation it's horrible
and like that's it's exactly why i talked about this in the decompression chamber that's why the
decompression chamber exists is because like i i hate the idea of like my content always being
the same yeah because the second i fall into a cycle of doing the same thing all the time
everything falls apart like mentally that's when i because i just become like i'm not even making
progress and it's so easy it's so easy to just be like well this makes me a baseline amount of money
so let's just keep doing that forever and then like nothing improves that's how everything gets
shit you know that's literally how everything gets shit like i feel like i have to constantly
challenge myself to come up with something new and it always pays off like you know the only way
to make something like grow is to like if things aren't getting any better at like they're just
staying the same and you want them to get better something has to change you know you can't just
do the same thing forever and hope that it's gonna change by itself you know it just feels like like
to me i don't know how often i talk about it but it's just whatever i think about how in like like
three years ago when i started doing the thing that actually interests me making videos i just
found this well within myself of an ability to do shit that i had never had before in my entire life
and an incredible drive to do it that i had never experienced before and i feel like that was me
finally being a real person for the first time like i always had an ability and i just you know
there it was i just needed something to do that hill giant could very easily have just killed it
truly was a hill giant in my life that i put against such eloquent terms what what are we talking
about i know the feeling just because like you know i've said i've said everything before yeah but
uh like for for so long i thought i was going to be either a filmmaker or a writer or all these other
things that like that like i that i wanted to do and the reason i'm not those is because i just didn't
do them yeah i would talk about them all the time i'd said like every single day i would like give
myself a pep talk about how i was gonna be a director and how i was gonna like run away from
home and make movies and like become this renegade director homeless man i guess and like like i talked
about it constantly and i directed nothing yeah i never made a fucking movie you know and like
quentin tarantino and fucking uh what's his name robert rodriguez had like this book or um well
robert rodriguez had a book about this but tarantino and him talked about this at a panel somewhere
yeah where they were like tarantino like very clearly laid out these rules for how to become a
director he said every day of the week i'm on fire every day of the week write scripts and on the
weekend shoot the scripts that's it that's all you have to do right every day and on the weekend
shoot the scripts you just wrote you're done you're a director just do that for several years you'll
be great you'll eventually get great right and i read that and i was like yeah wrote no scripts
directed no movies continued to talk about it for years yeah um you know and i did write a novel
but i immediately abandoned it when i realized that editing it would be a chore um so like that's
funny because editing is my favorite part of writing that's when you you're gonna be a successful
writer congratulations you take something that sucks and you make it less sucky i wrote my novel
in a month and then i never looked at it again the best part is when you find a sense like i can make
it better by doing this and then you get instantly erect and it's like i know i love that in my analysis
writing and that's the thing like like all this time the whole we are completely opposite about
writing because every time i write a script i do like one pass i'm like meh it's fine the whole
the entire time that i was talking about being a director that saw him up being a writer that whole
time i was writing an anime blog in the background just because i wanted to do it yeah right just for
fun didn't think it was going anywhere just hey yeah oh i watched the shot let's talk about that
it'll be funny i think about this all the time because all the time just like because i'm like
i really want to just write i want to just tell stories i wanted to be a son of a little kid
and like i've just everything has been like what medium do i want to do it in because like i've
still written it's like i'm gonna make fucking video games and that didn't work because i was
fucking complicated so it's like i'll do animation and like i don't like that and then like it's i've
been going lower and lower and lower down to writing and like my mind has always been like i
can write easily so that clearly that means it's not hard it doesn't doesn't count it's a lesser form
that is the absolute worst way you could have interpreted exactly because i'm fucking retarded
so even now i feel like i'm not living up to my potential by just writing um which is dumb cut that
shit out because i personally i like i feel like i have more core respect for writing than anything
i do too because like all the other like even if you're your favorite fucking like tv show or
video game would suck dick if the writer didn't show up because it's like look at these pretty
graphics sitting there like jerking off got them i mean i think like i think that uh like you know
a just an image can convey an incredible amount of storytelling and like or just an animation
could um but like the level at which you're like doing a 22 episode animation uh 12 times right
like yeah you need something like like like the only way that's gonna have a deep meaningful thing
to it is if someone spends forever making those images perfect the thing that like to change my
my mind said like i think i just need to write is that every because i would do comics and stuff
and i would sit down i'd write the script in like two or three weeks tops it'd be super because
there's not a lot to it it's just like this is the picture i want and this is what i want them to
say it's basically what i mean i mean i'm not gonna not to say that that's easy but like the writing
part always came easy to me and then like it'd be like three months of drawing it and the entire
time i feel like i'm not doing anything it's just like well i already know what's supposed to happen
yeah that's that's how it feels when i'm just inking in the pages i've already sketched i don't
feel creative at all doing it it just feels like busy work and a fucking chore i actually really
enjoy inking just because again it's the same thing with editing it's like it's taking the shitty
drawing and making it look fucking cool hey but ben's stuff it's satisfying in a way but ben's
actually a good artist so miss sketches don't look like a mess of retarded no my sketches look
horrible my sketches are like garbage well the thing about ben's inking is that he basically
just redraws it he does you can you pretty much just like completely redraws do it all in black
yeah that's what i that's what it's it's not my my sketches are just like like literally like
everywhere and then i just take it and i take that mess and just make it one nice clean line
and then he gets me nice and nice and tighten the pants because it's fucking it looks cool yeah i
i guess i do something like that but the the penciling's the worst because i have no like
understanding of like perspective or form so i just sit there and just like
i just want to have the hand out what the fuck they're selling me some books dude they're selling
me some fucking books is my book there is in the future no is your is yours book the fen folio
that was the sequel is it perhaps the papyrus of beguiling
uh well i really there was this one undertale thick i wrote all right i got it i want magma
bolt i'm gonna see if i'm gonna have to fucking consult the way for you undertale thick no it said
papyrus i wasn't sure no uh anyway for me writing an analysis video like the only analog for it
for me it is literally the same feeling as jacking off and then just like arnold described
for me it is exactly like what arnold described with the pump is one to one how i feel writing
an analysis script and it's really easy for well i will make a comparison sort of like that when i'm
editing a nuzlocke specifically i feel exactly the same as if i'm just sitting there passively
consuming a video like editing a video that i made to me just feels like sitting and listening to
my video over and over again which is something i love to do is listening to my own videos and looking
at my own drawings is like my favorite activity that stimulates me more than anything else it is a
lot of that's how i feel about all my vlogs like i make i make it and it's like it's kind of fun
and then i watch it back and it's like yeah okay that's a fun video i'd watch it if somebody else
made it you know and uh i did yeah and i watch it like six more times because i feel like it uh
and then forget about it forever but like with with writing the like and i guess this is why
because it so something i've been struggling with lately is the idea that my main channel
content is not really worth more than my vlogs like in terms of like people are getting almost as
much out of some not all of them some of the blogs are fucking retarded but like i need to
there are certain videos i've made that like and i get people telling me this all the time like
people come onto my reddit and are always like did you write to dark is your real main channel
like i care way more about the content on there than the main channel because it's way more videos
covering way broader subject matter and i've gotten out like so many fucking opinions on what you're
doing right now is you're basically doing a sales funnel with free content yeah it's yeah exactly i'm
just like i'm just fucking throwing it out like all the stuff that could be i'm making like ten
dollars a piece on these and they could be like uh every week i could just have a patreon post that's
just a compilation of a bunch of logs and i don't know if people would value it any less than the
main channel content you know the thing is like like people don't want to lose like whenever i bring
this up people are like well i don't want to lose the main channel content because i still value it
but that doesn't mean that i don't also value these as much well i think like you have to understand
like the levels of people like uh your your your top level is you have digi bro yes that's like your
267 000 retards you follow yeah and they're that's them well that's that's that's like the the most
easy to find shit like that's why it's so successful is because it's it's searchable it's you're playing
the game like we've talked about this before and then you have after dark which is like people want
to go a little bit deeper and then but like the people who are like the most hardcore yeah are
patrons yeah exactly they are the ones who give the most of a fuck because they're giving me money
i only have like 500 patrons like you should be 250 000 subscribers right 500 those are the
people's dicks you want to suck yeah and and none of them well i don't think i don't necessarily
agree with that i don't i don't think it's good to only appeal to your core no i'm not saying only
appeal to them or i don't i don't think it's good to to to to i mean prioritize them a little but
yeah not well i mean like like jesse makes as much money as i do on patreon practically like well
okay no never mind please forgive what i just said that was true once i make i make a lot more now
than he does but but only because i mean because he's still charging weekly no i charge per video
like oh my god you must make a killing i change everything monthly i only put out like three
four videos a month and then sometimes like a fifth bonus thing i feel like anyone starting
patreon now you can't do that anymore uh i don't know about that man i don't like i don't know about
that attitude because like patreon had already been going for a while when we jumped in everybody
who's no because when we uh when we all started you couldn't do monthly things yeah you could
not not in the beginning it was always there no it was not really no when i made it i don't remember
monthly it was only per creation that was added later oh i hear a distance snort that means there's
a labyrinth here with a minotaur and the uh the thing is everybody's doing monthly and that's what
they expect like all the big channels that run patreon i despise monthly because to me and monthly's
games fuck to me like never to me the whole point of it is that i have to make videos agree you know
and i have i get paid for exactly how much work i do and that's like what incentivizes me to make
more the problem i'm gonna die people get scared when it's per video because i don't know how much
they're gonna pay for and then you have to put that bigger shoes not gonna put you can put a cap
and blah blah but if you say month it's like oh i'm making 12 payments a year i'm extremely careful
and i'm very clear about what you're gonna get if you pay for per video you know but like um i think
but at the same time i feel like that's like kind of in some ways i'm throwing like i make these posts
at the end of like every other month where it's like all the unpatroned videos in one post and
it's like 40 videos that i'm putting in one post some of which are my favorite videos i made that
that month you know and i'm like am i really like considering this like all like all 40 of these
are only worth as much as one main channel videos some of which are like six minutes long and not
that interesting you know compared to some of these blogs it's really dumb but but the reason
i feel that way the reason this distinction exists is because the vlogs i like i make it and it's
just like yeah that was fun and the videos are literally masturbating it's like this is this
is oh no this is what i want my life to be you know snorke snorke killed me while i was trying to
run up the stairs to get away from him what it sucks oh that was really dumb i thought i could
take i had been i had been i had been wrecking shit because i got a ring of magic power that
gave me extra mp and i had finally gotten enough piety with that who met that he had started to
do the best thing he does which is restore your mp every time you kill something with magic so you
can just kill kill kill kill and it all just it all just you'd become like a steamroller of
magical death so i had i had kind of been having that going for a while but i got overconfident
and i find snorke fucking snorke man what a dick yeah he's someone draw a fan out of snorke
he's just like a really he's just like a really strong troll and he's also really fat and ugly
he's particularly ugly i think that's in his description he must go on youtube
yeah but yeah uh i guess i guess the long and short of what i'm describing is that i am making
the mistake of putting like like basing how much my content is valued like like what value i'm
putting on it in a public sense of like what people are charging me based on how much i value my
content and that's the mistake i'm making yeah it's not i'm not basing it on how much my content
is valued by other people but just strictly like i think writing a post is fun and the feelings it
gives me are like i've accomplished something right you know like if i write if i write something
like that that flying witch video which is like you know six and a half minutes and i wrote it all
at once like in one night it's not a thought i'd ever really had before and i just came up with it
all but the process of writing it was like oh yeah i'm fucking coming and then it's like yeah
that's a patron video whereas there's like vlogs i have where i'm like summarizing the whole fucking
universe and like all of anime history and it's like this is life changing for some people
and and i'm like yeah throw it into the the fucking pile with the 40 other vlogs you know
well would you want to improve the production values on the vlogs of vlog type content if you
were going to make it a main channel thing i definitely am going to do that but i don't think
i'll ever i don't know if i'll ever be able to bring myself to patron it you know like like maybe
the yuri on ice video that me and victor recorded which is going on the main channel
it's basically like a plebeian the lead discussion it's me and him sitting chairs we discuss yuri
on ice uh i'm even gonna have devout edit it and put a bunch of footage in so it should be
patronable but even then i'm just like but it's not written you know like what value could there
possibly be in something i didn't write there's a few moments where i say um in this like how
could anyone pay money for something where i say the weirdest fucking comment and it blew my mind
and i was just like it changed the way i'm gonna do videos on rebel pixels and because i got a
bunch of thumbs up too because i i did these last two videos that are about um why i think you like
youtube is a symptom of a bigger problem and shit yeah yeah that was a great yeah and and someone
said to me i really like this video but i can't get into it because it's scripted i hate your
scripting voice it sounds super unnatural i'd rather you just talk and like it got like 15
thumb ups like we were just like weird well i mean i i do understand that like i can there are there
are normies the idea normies want you to be a normie uh yeah and sometimes you have to appease
them i guess it's so weird like all the videos that get the best responses in terms of engagement
not in views but engagement are always the ones where i'm just like uh i mean fucking i guess like
dick sucking sure like that's that's the kind of language that people seem to really resonate
i mean i mean if that's if they knew what my dick looked like they'd want to suck it for sure
if that's the truth then i guess it makes sense to go for that kind of content because like i think
on rebel pixels this year i'm not gonna script anything real real quick can we all appreciate
that for like how long has this been going three three and a half hours now tom has been non-stop
shitting on his appearance and abilities but when it came to his dick he was like i mean if they saw
my dick they would definitely want to suck it so i think this man must be a monster i think yeah i
think we can say that tom has something to be confident about i just have the opinions of other
people who are very clear yeah see that's exactly the kind of thing you'd say if you had a fucking nine
inch dick i don't know put your hand up to mine for a second oh my god it's a pretty big hand it's a
pretty big hand it's a huge hand i don't i don't know well that was a diversion it sure was sorry
what were you saying tom um before i got out i was i was saying did you hear what i said when you
left yeah youtube uh sucks so the value to i gotta tell you that people want your your something about
the owl something about the owl i've gotten the same thing i've gotten the same thing that people
people tell me all the time like i really need your unscripted content because it feels like
i'm having a conversation with somebody you know but do you think about that that's the entire
fucking reason youtube took off in the first place because it wasn't all like this fucking production
and like we kind of are forgetting that because we want to be cool all the big guys are vloggers
all the biggest youtubers are fucking vloggers that doesn't mean well i mean what about guys like
PewDiePie vlogger now i'm not talking about doesn't play video games anymore just vlogs that's true i
meant guys like uh best guy ever dammit i can't remember the fucking name of these guys what's
the guy who made the the thing about the politics videos about the animal kingdom that guy cgp
like cgp gray's content i think is really good generally and it's scripted and i'm just saying
that there is a market no there's absolutely a market but i i think there are lots of people
out there who appreciate shit like we're doing right now i guess so i think here's the thing
about cgp gray though like his main channel content which is phenomenal yeah and is very
successful um but like i don't think he'd have a patreon that's as successful as he did if not for
the hello internet podcast because people know him damn like that's a good point yeah like i don't
know the history of that but you could be right he i mean he uh well it's hard to like put dates on
this without looking into it but like you know he was running that channel for a long time and i
always just thought of it as like a guy who makes really informative videos and then i listen to
hello internet and he's a fascinating character like he has a really interesting personality
and i love him and it's him and uh and brady from numberphile and they have great chemistry
and it's a good podcast it's the first podcast i ever really listened to actually yeah never was
never big in a podcast until recently i'm getting big in a podcast now too yeah and now and that's
that's a thing like the pcp kind of came about like none of us were into podcasts yeah like when
the pcp came about that's not that's not i have way more that's not true i was not gonna lie i have
way more fun doing pcp i was then i do making my videos i was hugely into this is the most fun
i've had making anything like in the last like three months i was i was hugely into the ricky
jervais show which is um which is based on the ricky jervais podcast so that was like i was actually
a huge influence on t-bap and like the way that the t-bap was presented t-bap is pretty podcast
pretty much a podcast yeah yeah like the true it always was in the in like the later episodes the
reason i drew them sitting at a table is because that's how they are in the ricky jervais really
even i didn't know that i i well i feel like i definitely mentioned okay maybe i just forgot
yeah fair enough i mean like back when me and tom and jessie first started talking we were all
like pretty harsh on the idea of like podcasts and unedited content like we all thought it was
total bullshit and that like no one would care about it and like like when fucking poor neil x
who like at the time that he made elements of brony like we all thought this will never take
off unless it's a super highly edited thing because they're so long yeah and so we put so
much if that came out now it could just be like and i told him this over time like you
should like like like once it got to the point where like this is now what kind of contents
popular on youtube and in his series was just the visionary i've told him a bunch of times like
dude just put out parts five and six as podcasts because in the current state of youtube it will
be exactly as accessible it might be more successful because then you can just put that on behind
something else yeah as opposed to having to look at it for two fucking hours yeah and like
it's such a shame but like we were all super anti-podcast until like literally up until
we started like um like biggest problem in the universe convinced me and jessie like oh my god
podcasts are cool i could have fucking escaped that last life if i'd remember that i had fucking
past wall i always forget about past wall the best spell in the universe it just it just
sends you through a wall and nothing can fucking fall you did they fail the one time you tried to
use it well it failed because i use it in the it's because i use it on the wrong spot you can only
go through like the wall the wall can't extend into infinity yeah okay like you can only move
through relatively thin move through one square essentially uh so there's some there's some limit
forget how it's determined anyway seems like something you might want to figure out anyway yeah
we were all like oh no we were all pretty i mean even before that like we were fairly anti let's play
until we got into game grumps and then we were fairly anti-podcast and then we got anti let's play
again i'm still trying to do it i never i'm doing a let's play right now oh no ben's doing a let's
you know what i guess i guess that's technically true it feels more like a podcast if i was playing
the game i'd be really mad that's that's why we got like because the re like i had this perception
that let's play meant like you know something shit yeah until i found actually you know it wasn't
okay i was into game grumps for a long time but what got me into the idea of doing let's plays
and podcasts was uh yacht sees one uh let's try it out oh yes and like just like realizing that you
could just have a video game just be there while you just talked about whatever it was like oh
this can be a let's play or podcast i guess i guess that's and that's where digi bros came from
you know maybe i'm still just in like 2010 i mean have you ever watched digi bros it's just a podcast
we don't even talk about the game i never watched digi bros never really i don't think i well maybe
i watched like one or two but i i just my stigma for let's plays runs deep a lot of people's does and
i think that's the only reason that channel's never gotten bigger because it's it we were talking
about this on a lot of you changed the name to something that said it was just like this really
doesn't have anything to do with let's plays well i've been meaning to like we've been talking a lot
about this because for the longest time we were putting no effort into it deliberately because
it was just for fun but like it started to really baffle me that for money well like digi bros was
started before i had like before after dark became a vlogging channel that's posting all the time
right and then it slowly became really weird to me that like my vlogging channel has like people
who watch all these fucking videos like they'll get like 10 000 views per video you know and it
could be the most inane weird random shit and yet the digi bros channel which is the same content
just with a video game overlaid which to my mind makes it better there's something to watch other
than me half shaded in darkness gets no views and i'm like the only reason this is is that people
think it's a let's play yeah it's really not it's just a podcast it's no different from the pcp
or my vlogs when i think let's play i think some really obnoxious motherfuckers screaming at a game
right yeah even though you know it's me and i would maybe you're sitting at the game maybe you
finally sold out it's always victor who plays the games well that makes it better off this right
off the bat um i am incompetent at video games so it would be unwatchable if i play victor's
barely competent but at least he can play and talk at the same time and i can't uh i can't do that
either but yeah i can never stream streaming is something i'm gonna be able to do but yeah it's
really funny to me how like how we can go through these phases of like thinking it's thinking podcasting
is totally lame until any of us heard one podcast that we liked and immediately wanted to do that
seems weird but it doesn't seem weird at all like if you see nothing but shit about a format it's like
oh this format shit and they seem to go it's like oh it can be that i felt like what i felt that way
about vlogs until uh until i start nice dad or something no um max landis a plus three oh yeah
these vlogs yeah those are pretty great yeah and like what inspired me to start doing all the vlogs
in digital after dark was how shit max landis's quality is so shit and yet decent quality i would
be watched like like like my what do you mean so shit me a decent quality well like he feels like
a laptop yeah like the actual quality of the microphone audio and video is more respect than
that he writes movies he doesn't you know make doesn't he care about the fucking cinema well
that's the point it doesn't matter it doesn't matter that's the whole point here well yeah that's
the thing like i for the longest time my policy has always been i won't make a video i wouldn't
watch and then like i always thought i won't watch stuff with shit video and audio quality
but i start following max landis and he has videos where it's like he's you know traveling
and he's like in a hotel room and he just like clearly whipped open a laptop and hit record and
started talking into like the shittiest camera ever but what he's saying is interesting so i was
watching these and i started watching and i'm like wait i'm willing to watch this i could make this
like in 10 seconds i could flip on my phone and have better image and audio quality there's a lot
of videos that ideas have that fall through the cracks so i'm just like i'm not willing to just do
this yeah and well i bought a gorilla pod buddy so that's how you do that no no no what happened
i had a fucking ring of wizardry from the first room and i fucking died well man well that
you're a wizard i would have made all the fucking difference that's so good to get early because
suddenly you don't have you barely even have to level up before you can cast your dang spells
just cast them right off the bat because it's fucking your aptitudes through the roof
incidentally here's here's my advice on how to get into lower quality content how to get into it okay
how to get into making like like lower quality making that's real i'm always looking to make
low quality content did you tell me more how to get yourself low production value how to get
yourself mentally into the idea of making lower quality content all right is to belt out a ton of
it all at once like what got me like what i did do that one time and it was great what launched the
digi bro after dark vlogging like thing like this this happened just all at once because you know
we're talking about this channel's been around for years yeah it's been around for like three years
and it's uploads at like maybe once a month maybe twice a month sometimes a vlog sometimes a podcast
like whatever was like something that didn't have a place right in one day i put out three vlogs
like like filmed back to back and just released them as soon as they were done and then it was just
like this is now a channel where this can happen and therefore and like i didn't stop all week i put
out a video every day or two videos a day all week and people were like digi's lost his fucking mind
what's happening but but then also people were like this is epic this needs to be my life now
and i was like this will be your life and then i didn't stop for six months and this is where we are
now um yep yep the three videos i did that day the first one was called losing my mind in a room
full of naked anime girls and it was it was just about how when i look at these posters all i see
is their flaws because i look at them so often that all i can see is like how shit the art is
in almost all of these and i'm just like running around my room with a camera pointing at posters
and going look at how her neck does this thing it's so fucking weird i hate it look at this one
her crotch is in the wrong place and i'm just like going around screaming at the camera
losing my mind literally and uh and that started it all and now it seems like such a fitting way
of thinking it looks like we are now it was beautiful
there's a lot of a lot of my vlogs i should be running around my room pointing at posters
and those are my favorite ones we should all just resolve to just make shit i have been meaning
i have been meaning to make more of the of the you know those two like essay videos i did i just
i just don't fucking i just it's just thinking of those are really good you should definitely make
more of that i do i like them it's just thinking of like what do i want to talk about i just want
i want my video comment i would recommend just just effort as possible try to consume the media
that you want to make videos about in general i guess i think it'll just ideas will just come
another way to get yourself into the mindset of like making worse content is just think about
how much of it you like like for me it was that maxland is thing but we are all no fans of the
gibbon take channel sure which is just random bullshit like weird fucking esoteric ideas that
just spawn out of the ether and i enjoy that channel no no no the only thing about those it's
not that i have anything against the idea of putting out low low quality low effort content
it's just that i don't i don't have ideas for like things i actually want to talk about fair well
that's there's a difference between you and nate i think nate is just a verse to the idea of making
something he's a paragon that has no like i've thought about it and i i can't do you do it on
fucking bestie boy bestie boy you fucking do it right so what are you talking about that's fine
the point is that it's not bad content you're thinking of it wrong like would any of us accuse
jump cut jack of being a bad video i love jump cut jack it's an amazing video and it probably took
15 minutes to make probably like i haven't seen jump cut jack why it's like it's like 30 seconds long
and it's wonderful four mags in size hey guys welcome to another fucking video yeah that's it
it's that's it that's it just given saying hey guys welcome to another fucking video but it's
through constant like every letter is him in a different position in the room it's magical he
just turned on a camera and stood in like he stood in somewhere in the room and said the whole
line then stood somewhere else and said the whole line and then he just edited together so that he's
teleporting everywhere constantly while saying this one look look i thought about 15 minutes
give me such a low key genius i can't i'm trying to fix my problem and i've already got it starting
got it started while i was making the lucifer one i had another one that was being edited by this
other guy that's like a similar scope to the one punch man one which only took a long time to get
done because the editor guys are fucking incompetent piece of shit that is the problem when you
upload the videos yeah outsourced is no fuck you buddy you piece of shit i hit two rings you gotta
find yourself a divu i i do we all need a divu this guy is not my divu the key to do to having a
divu is to have somebody who's just so in love with your content that they would they would die for
i get people who tell me that they love it and some of them are content creators the problem is
you need to find someone who's actually good this is fucking the guy i work with is good but he's a
little bit unreliable and he's got other things going on that's a cardinal sin it's a cardinal sin
yeah when is the divu collective actually gonna be a collective so we all get one yeah that'd be
nice that's an important question it's such a shame divu does not like that meme and doesn't
understand why it's great it's hilarious wait it seems pretty innocuous it's just
i thought that was his idea no jesse came up with it oh what like there was one episode he needs to
embrace it there was one podcast where jesse and divu got into an argument about something yeah and
jesse felt that he had been steamrolled in his argument so he edited in segments into the video
where he argues with a straw man of divu that is the divu collective just trying to assimilate him
and change his opinions to match its own and it was fucking hilarious it was amazing and we all
like everyone immediately wanted it to be a meme and like divu was like you know i'm not he was like
he said uh he was like i i don't get it and i don't think it's funny and like i don't care for it
but i'm not gonna stop it because like you know you can't control these things yeah like it's just
what you're it's a thing revolving around me now i think he just doesn't like the association he has
with someone he didn't even like at the time the fact that jesse kind of like went behind his back
and edited in like an argument but like it well yeah we should just strike back he should he should
strike back in a new in a new video or so in the next pc page he should argue with jesse about
something right he should just become the divu collective they already have our own horrible
jesse meme he doesn't approve that's true that's true we all we all need to we all need to drive
a stave through jesse's heart in some way only then we hate us all equally you know you know about
his revenge plan have you heard about that i did hear about that yeah that he has like a really
elaborate like he as he put it because he was like this isn't because someone was like why don't
you just like explain it to someone he's like it's not like that he's like it's not like a video
revenge plan it's like something i would have to actually spend like years staging like this is
like a really elaborate like a film like like a movie idea plan for all we know boozy floozy is step
one of this plan it's very possible well he said he said that he had relented for now that these
plans should never see the light isn't that exactly what he would say if he was trying to get us you
i don't i don't know if i can it won't work we're gonna betray him tomorrow i'm ready to betray
anyone at a moment so when jesse's video steps into the ring we're all dead
speaking of when should we wrap this up i don't know i guess i don't think i can i don't think i
can play anymore in this fucking game all right well we've got four hours recorded i don't have a
lot of space left i don't think we have enough i don't think it's enough and we should all go to
sleep so we can actually make sure there are things to be done tomorrow it's true i'm kind of awake
now though that's okay i hope you all enjoyed the ultimate procrastinator's decompression chamber
yeah it was uh it was a doozy this has been your host ben saint and my friends who are the other guys
the other guys signing off i don't know them i don't want to know them and neither do you i was
playing video games if you were smart that was you did too uh bye bye take these guys
okay and scene and scene okay and john sena
uh
that's good shit that was fun yeah it was