In the beginning, God created the heavens and the earth. The earth was without form and void, and darkness was over the face of the deep. And the spirit of God was hovering over the face of the waters, and God said,
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm the best guy ever.
Yes, you are. Pause. You guys ruined my dramatic pause.
Oh, you want me to clap?
Yes, that's what I wanted.
Best guy ever!
Good. Let's do this every time. Let's see, who's here today? We got Mumkey Jones.
Hey, what's up everybody? I'm Mumkey Jones. I am the monkey with the Jones. The Jones is the monkey. The monkey is the Jones you ever know.
What's up, Munchy?
They said I couldn't fit all my electrical wires up my urethra.
Hippocrit, once again is here.
Nothing's worse could cause me physical pain.
Hey, hey, you interrupted the man's interest at Baron right there.
Now it's depressed given. No intro for me.
And back after a long hiatus, Lethal Aurora Mage graced us with her presence.
Hello, I'm here again.
Wait, Mage, you brought us all presents?
Can I have my present first?
You're not listening to me. You're not. Things are going out of control.
So today, we're going to talk about creators. Creators that we love and hate.
Hate.
Oh, I forgot about hate.
I'm too full of love, you see.
Well, I mean, you've got a podcast full of creators you hate, so you're covered right there.
So, alright.
How many Christmas podcasts are we just going to say that we hate each other?
Yeah, I mean, that's most of them.
I have a list of four and Ben is one of my four.
Of course. Let's just go round Robin style, I guess, and everybody's got their things.
We did homework this time, actually, right?
Yeah, everyone's ready.
I have a huge list in front of me.
So here's a huge list. Why don't you go first, Munchie? What do you got?
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
So first of all, what I look for in creators...
Enough!
Excellent.
What I look for in creators is how similar you are to Andrew Hussey.
The more similar you are to Andrew Hussey, the more I like you.
Yes.
So meaning that I look for comedy and class.
The more like Andrew Hussey you are, the better I like you.
So vaguely kind of an asshole, pretty funny, conducting yourself with an air of mystery and class and being gay,
like fucking over your fans, not having any respect for the people who support you.
Dude, let me tell you, I love the level of class he showed by pausing his work for a year to get work on a project.
They got totally fucked.
Oh, fantastic work.
Yeah, and it's still not out, even though he said it was going to be released.
Love that.
First of all, he said it was going to be released in 2015, then it was going to be in January of this year,
and it's still not out yet.
Class.
Who is Andrew Hussey?
Andrew Hussey is the creator.
He undertailed. He made Undertale.
He didn't make Undertale. He did not.
He's the creator of his finest work, Riska Circuit.
Yeah.
Andrew Hussey is on both my love and hate list for this.
Of course.
Sometimes.
He made Homestuck and the MSPA website, where he just posts a bunch of comics.
He used to be really good at art, now he doesn't do anything.
And he's also just a fucking hack in every way.
He's a regular, bensome, mashed.
Max revive problem sleuth.
Bring it back, it's time.
The people need it.
Believe me, I have another property we need in Max Revive later.
Good.
I wonder what that could be.
Should I go through my entire list?
I think we're gonna do one at a time just to mix it up. We're gonna go around definitely
Okay, so Andrew Hussie my favorite guy his use of colors as being garish and weird and awful
And and his general aesthetic is is everything that I love
I told that informed your art a lot. Yeah, definitely the colors. Yeah
Everything in Homestuck like like if I didn't read Homestuck, I would be I would be like I would be just like George Washington
So it set me on the right path
Hero a creator of nations a nation-builder. That's bullshit dude a white supremacist a racist
All right, and I just like it was pretty good
There you go. It's pretty good. Okay, monkey. You're next on the thing. I'm looking at here. What do you got?
Folks I've noticed an unfortunate new trend on our little website. We lovingly call YouTube
Thanks to the popularity of people like nerd writer one. We have a whole new wave of these
analytic genius 16 year olds
Who want to show us just how smart they are by analyzing like a Marvel superhero movie and shit?
It's disgusting, but from this new wave of filth
There is one there. There's a there's a piece of cream that rises to the top. Is that what that saying is?
Yeah
Like cream I think what it would be in this situation would be a poop a turd rising to the top like a
Not a turd. I think he's really good. Oh
You can't touch them if they're if they're littler than you're then then like five feet tall. That's eat
That's the same you can't touch it
Don't know about that
So there's this YouTube channel called lessons from the screenplay as have any of you seen this one
No, no, I don't know that one. So what I really like about it is it's not just he's not just gonna watch a fucking movie and say now
I think that this is just he actually does a little bit of homework and work
What he does is he'll read the original screenplay to the film and compare it to what the final film is
So between writing a screenplay and then the final cut of a film
There's a thousand hands to go into it and fuck with the movie and it
Max Landis would be all about this shit. Oh
Yeah, and what I really like about it is that of he's only done like nine episodes so far
It's a fairly new channel, but like half the movies he's done are some of my favorite movies
So it's really great for me
He's done like nightcrawler and X machina and what's really interesting is how he'll show how
Changes made from the screenplay to the final cut. He'll explain how they improve or
Are less than the value of the film ultimately for example with exposition and X machina at the beginning
What's great about X mocking on the first 15 minutes is you have no idea what the hell is going on
But in the original screenplay, it's just fucking exposition city
So as a writer and somebody who likes, you know, how films are made
It's really interesting to me and I'd say of all these weird new trend, you know analytical faggots. He's one of the good ones
That's pretty interesting. So an X mocking his case the actual director or whoever was in charge improved upon the screen absolutely by just
Cutting 90% of the beginning out. That's a very good movie. That's pretty cool. Yeah, I
Do like a lot of some of those. I mean, I think no writer is actually still quiet kind of one of the better
I
Still think he's pretty good. I think he means
That's true, that's true
But yeah, yeah, I agree the most most of that that crowd is just
And it's nice to know that there are some good ones
Yeah, so that's mine like
Your guy. Yeah, okay. Yeah, let's go to the next one then mage is next up. What do you got for his mage? Oh, okay
Okay, um
So I have a little artist and giving out that I absolutely adore the arts of and it's kind of like rare for me to like
Be really into someone's art. Just like so so much. I am right now. Like I haven't had like a little
genuine
As you put it
They're called unknown spy and I have found they're giving a target like all a long while ago back when I was into ponies
But it's only like in the last year or so. I really went through their gallery and
So I'll how really creative the their characters are and the designs and they have like this comic
That I absolutely adore when I read it like all in one go for one day and I'm just I was just like oh
Man, I need more of this
How how do I cope with the lack of this?
It's just like absolutely amazing just their style is kind of like cartoony
It would really work like as a as an actual cartoon on TV show and stuff like that and it's just oh man
I can't even put it into words. Just how much I adore
They're just so creative. I just look at each one of their character and design and just stories and personalities
I just just so do they do primarily like OC stuff or is it specifically for comics?
They they they do
They do a lot of original art, but they have a few fan art stuff in their gallery
Yeah, they have like a comic and they have like this concept thing called media controls
It's basically personified media controls and they're kind of like set in a world
That could be like a fighting game or something like that and it's like it's quite popular a lot of people are quite into it
And they're making their own characters
I'm included and the people who made their own characters for the universe and they don't even have the comic for that
Yeah, they just had like the few characters and the few characters were so a well made that they inspired other people to
Make characters and in that universe like remote controls or like that's what I was wondering. Yeah
Okay, you know copy paste play cuts is like those
Okay
Interesting. Yeah
It's really really good. I could link a few
Okay
Things weird, but also quickly cool. That's right. You have neptunia a little bit
nepotog
leon
I
Linked in the press me. Oh, okay. Let's see here
Save okay, okay incognito. Hey, that's cool. I like the guy. I was just gonna say cuts the coolest one bar
Incognito reminds me of metaton for some reason
Believe a ball
Seriously like like fuck dude
Fuck you up not joking
This shit is just a reaction
Real alright, did you learn this from the Undertaker?
No, I just I just was raped by metaton
Oh
Okay, let's move on. That was it cool
Okay, hippo crits. What do you got for us? Oh, yes, I have
Anish Kapoor who is a is a modern artist sculptor kind of guy you may have seen
The thing he made in Chicago this giant mirror bean thing
Sort of that people can walk under it. It's like a massive. It's called the cloud gate if you Google that and
the thing about this guy is
that he
like he is the guy that set me on the path of being cool because
You know, I was just I was in art school
You know doing stuff and the teachers always said now you need to look up some artists and get some inspiration for the thing
You have to have inspiration. Fuck you and I'm like, oh
Whatever and then I looked in this book and there's this thing and they had all these cool pictures
And it was an ish Kapoor and he had and basically what he does is he makes sculptures and their big weird shapes the huge colors mirrors
You know huge metal monstrosities, but they're always like really nice looking and you can you know
I've been to a few of his art exhibitions to see them up close and it's like whoa like you just build a huge big weird
Curvy metal thing and it's great and the thing that I really like about him is that in this book. I was reading
People say to him, you know, he was he was saying the the the way he he approaches meaning
And he says I just make stuff because I like the way it looks like it's something to that effect
like he makes these cool amazing sculptures and he's such a talented craftsman and
He doesn't have any of the pretension that you would have expected of a you know a modern artist sculptor sort of person
And he's sort of like I didn't realize that you could be
making
Loads of money being a famous sculptor artist modern guy and
Also, just just do it because it looks cool and for no other reason
And I just really love that about him and his ethics and his work ethic and is
I was just gonna say what are his yeah
That's what really really need to talk about he's an old guy, so I doubt he's played any game
That's
We can only talk about
I had a good old
No
And you got a you got a gamer
Gain is the most heartfelt topic there is dude. Come on. Okay. Okay. Well, I Google this and this is sick
This is sick. I I understand like like
Like like like you always just think the artists are just like weird fucking assholes
But when you find like did you like like yeah, obviously
And then we find someone that's like genuinely cool. You're like you're like me. Oh, I can keep my soul when I when I when I make
Yeah, like that the the reason I get mad when like the general consensus on the internet among like basically everyone is that modern art and
Artists are pretentious and stupid and everyone gets overpaid and they're all bad and lol
Let's laugh at modern art as a whole like like that's a meme. It's basically it's basically yeah, it really annoys me though
It's literally a trigger. I get I get all worked up because it's like saying, you know film lol so gay
Can you name one film that isn't gay though?
Like broke back Mountain
Yes, American Psycho
Yeah, that's pretty straight
Yeah, that was definitely gay dude
Okay, well that was a great suggestion
Go look this guy up. What was his name again? Could you say over time? Anish Kapoor if you type in cloud gate
You'll you'll get the image of that that famous
Or just type in Gamergate and go to the important shit, but okay
Albrillo prince up. He assassinated the Archduke Ferdinand since the world in World War one. I really like his work
I really like that all those people died. I'm for it. Hey, you cut I have a thing
I want to say I have a creator. Okay, so so okay, so there's this guy
I don't know if you've heard of him. His name is Richard Spencer
He's an American writer and what he's creating is a future for the white race
That's what he's working on and I gotta say I'm a big fan of his work
Nate to live I'm glad I'm glad we started up a council and allowed him to prosper
Okay, let's move on a bunch. Yeah, it's you again. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay back on like analysis thing
Cuz I think we're all kind of in that circle
There there's there's a guy that that that he was talking shit on in the chat
And I agree that he's pretty bad, but also I like him a lot his name. You know a little birdie
named my night mind his name is night mind and like he keys like
He's like kind of long-winded and has it like super eyepatch wolf dr. Wolf whimsical weird delivery
That's like that's gay
But but but he's cool cuz he talks about like like horror internet ARG things like like marble Hornets and shit and
No one that I know is doing that and I just like to learn about horror
They are like I really like ARG is just in general and so just to learn about like like like really
It's just like a jumping off point like like he'll analyze something then I'll be like, oh, that's a thing
I'll go check that out and then that's
He's good. What's the guy's name night mind night mind
I don't remember shitting on a guy called that
Did he do a did he do like a video analyzing the Zanya cat
Which was prefaced by I literally don't want to do this, but everyone's asking me for it shut up
Oh, well, that's my favorite kind of video. I just don't like the fact that it's a thing. Oh, yeah
I agree. I think I think I would rate. I would rank night man as like a six
six to a seven
By the way, I while you were talking I just made the connection that
Dr. Wolf and super I patch wolf are the same guy. That's probably dr. Wolf's anivate channel. Okay, glad okay
By the way, I just want to throw out my favorite content creator of all time is dr. Wolf. Yeah
Retarded obvious shit, all right, I'm sorry to waste everyone's time with that. Okay, let's let's move on monkey
What's up? Let me take you back to a simpler time
Way back before, you know, 9-eleven way back before World War two we're talking the economic crisis of 2008
Love it. Monkey was a young child and he was really into a in a YouTube series called stupid Mario brothers
Has anybody heard of this? No, I love it already remember that. Yeah, so it's actually quite I love quite good
It's by this guy named Richard Michael Alvarez where it's like they had these cosplay Mario costumes
And they decided to make skits out of it which branched off into entire episodes and seasons with like an overarching story line
And it got really intense towards the end. There's there's tons of cool fights with like really good special effects
It was crazy for a YouTube series
but then but then this is when Richard Michael Alvarez goes down the road of
Disgust the road of fuck you see supply person for the first person because he
This is the type of guy, you know, it's the story that we've seen over and over again with your your bojaks and your
Your best guys ever as you know these types of people
Yeah, where they were once really big and popular and then they made a change or their show ended and now they live in obscurity
And they're sad about it and they they thirst to regain the fame and the love that they had before
So like six years after the the stupid Mario Brothers show ends rich
Alvarez comes back because he'd been doing shitty stuff on YouTube for six years stuff that nobody wanted to see he has like
120,000 subs in his videos on average get about 600 views. So I'm guessing it's all dead account baby. Yeah, so it's like, okay
I should have monetized this shit when it was popular. I'm gonna try it again
So what he's doing now he made two new seasons of the show and now he now he's putting it up on a ransom
He says listen up fans. If you want me to make season three. I have to hit this
$1,000 patreon goal per month. Okay, so instead of doing a Kickstarter to fund this season
He's using the excuse. Here's a patreon pay me for content that I'm not making and you'll only get the content if I hit this
Goal so pretty much throw your money away for no reason
Forever because I'm never gonna hit this fucking goal and you're just gonna keep paying me for nothing
I didn't think that went through so is this a creator you like I used to when I was a kid and now I hate him because he's
He's doing this bullshit on patreon if you need money to film the season do a kickstart
So let me ask is he right now like getting paid money. I assume as a you know as a part of this campaign and it's just not making anything
Yeah, yeah, he's not do he's getting money for the stupid Mario Brothers series that he's not making is he making other shit
I'm just wondering he he's making like let's plays with his girlfriend. They get 500
Quality that's the saddest thing I've ever fucking heard for my entire
No, I haven't checked this channel in the last month, so maybe something's changed
But this went on for like six months and then I got that's a long time. Yeah
Somewhat related monkey. Have you ever watched Super Mario brosie?
Hell, yeah, no, what is that? Yeah, it was an ant worm dude. Come on
Come on. It was like it was like a retarded like flash animation
Where it took fucking like the Mario sprites from the RPGs and like Sonic sprites
You just had them like duke it out and this weirdly like overly complex plot that was
Fucking sick. Yeah, okay. All right. It was
Well, yeah, that's my guy actually seen it you should you Google it
It's still around and then like the guy came back and he's like making new ones now, right? Yeah, I
Haven't kept up with that though
Same are they still I mean they were still good like the first I watched like the first of the new ones that were coming out
And I think they were still like just as good as they always had been
It's just that like it's not as fresh a formula because it's been like ten years or something. I
Don't know
We just hijacked monkeys though. Oh, yeah, he's gay. No, I was done
Please feel free to take the reins
Okay, mage you're up
Okay, so this is my second and last creator that I like and there's no creators that I hate
So I'm probably gonna stay silent after a new van. You can take my Ben from me
No, it's okay. I'm not greedy. I'm fine. Well, like mage says she doesn't like to discuss people that she hates
Okay, so the second one is a youtuber kind of
Like they do animation memes and they're probably one of the people who actually influenced me to make my own
And I wish I wish I guys I could like tell you the full saga of the banana goat because it's like it's it's it's just the best thing
So this guy scotchy
He he he uses this purple gay goat for for his animation videos and there's there was one
Where people were really complaining about
The goat being too sexy or something like that or too gay
And so in response the guy made a video
Where he kind of interacted with his
Goat persona and he was like, hey, dude, you need to be more heterosexual and and that that kind of that that kind of backfire
I should link you guys the actual video because it's just absolutely priceless. I got removed from you too hot for YouTube
it's just I
The amount of fucks this person does not give is just
Amazing and they have the talent to back it up. They're actually a quite talented animator as well
They have some original content some memes and stuff like that and it's just
Everything they do like some of these like little shitty posts. They're just like the best
I I just I just want to link everyone some of the videos because they're just priceless and I just adore adore this creator
Just for their attitude for their for their art and for for their talent and just everything
Sick sicker than syphilis
I
Save me or save him. I forget whose meme is who's these days. I don't even remember a save me
Max I'll do that. I'll get there. I'll get I'll get to write we're building up to a me because I am one
We always
Shut up everyone shut up. Have we even like introduced why we're talking about just random people
Is that is there a reason I feel like we've just started talking about people and we've gone in a circle like people watching like
Are they talking about like creation?
What I look for in creators and and and and shit
I'm looking for a future for the white race, which is why my list is as it is so all right
I just feel like the
Why you chose the people you did please feel free who are my senpai's that's awesome. Yeah, that's true
Well, I mean the the the thing is I've always had like a problem with recommendations. Yeah
In that I never ever look at anything anybody ever recommends me unless they do it for like months and months and just fucking just
Just do it. Yeah, like I I didn't I refused to get into Game of Thrones until
Season five was long over because
I don't like being into the hip things that everyone is talking about so I just
And it was just it was just one of those things like a whole podcast of like. Oh, yeah
Look at this. Look at that. Go google this and and stuff. You know, you know what I feel like for someone like me
I would just
Hippo, I hear what you're saying, but I don't think this is a recommendation podcast
I think if there are creators in the audience, we're explaining why these ones are good and why these ones are bad
So people know what to do
Well, that was you munchy. Well, yeah
I suppose so but I suppose so but like and
I guess we'd have to be very specific about why these fucking sheeple will listen to anything we put out who cares
That's true. That's true
Okay, well, uh
Hey, if the naru cast got 3000 views, this one's gonna hit 10,000
Yeah, I'm really mad. Well, actually, I'm not really mad, but that's it's did we beat the podcast?
Absolutely. Well, potty cost the potty cost gets uh from a thousand to a thousand
Major we did it a moment to point out how you guys made an ironic parody of the potty cast as soon as we moved it off
The pcp channel and you immediately like doubled the viewership
To say about that
I think part of it was people knew what the potty curse was and knew not to click on it because they knew they didn't like it already
This new thing this new thing with mage and monkey like whoa, what?
Everyone's gonna click on that major good friends people don't really they don't realize that because we're never on the podcast together
But me and mage go way back. We've actually I was talking to her before the pcp even started
We hung out a few times over in uh, slovakia or wherever the fuck she lives
Nice
Major's our token black
The token black and the token girl. Yeah, we did it other than did you I'm all of the tokens
I'm gonna take you to an arcade. Can you give me some shucky cheese tickets in exchange for those tokens?
I want to get I want to get some gum and and melt it all right
I want to be taffy and melt it all over my body so I can turn into a clay monster. No, they're my tokens
No, they're fucking mine. Give him here. I want to get a tiny finger trap. So I never have to leave ben ever again
Do you think
All right, my next my next guy my next guy is is a youtuber
He's very funny not any of us and he goes way back to he goes way back to to newgrounds days where he did nox's corner
Which is a plasticine stop motion animation
Comedy thing which is still hilarious. It's sort of like an adult swim sort of strange comedy sort of thing
And he has a youtube channel. His name is robert benfer
and he
does uh skits and music videos and it's it's all weird comedy that is like very
Very dry very awkward like cringy sort of like, you know awkward pause sort of comedy, which I really like and
Yeah, he does he does a bunch of cool things that he's good and I like him. Oh, yeah
That's my in-depth. Yeah in-depth analysis of robert benfer
He's he's he's awkward and clumsy and uh his adult swim humor there. That's what he is
People got me into him by posting animation. It's really good. Yeah by posting bbw lover in the chat. It's quickly become my favorite song
lover
That's my license plate number
Okay, um, okay, I'll take one next. Um, so this one, uh, I I'm not
I do like their work. I wouldn't say that I absolutely love it
But what I kind of love more is their lifestyle and this person might be contentious. This is shad man
Shad man the porn artist. You might be familiar
Come on munchy. Get get with the times. This is shad man's time. Okay. Oh, is he the guy who draws violet from the Incredibles over?
I'm sure he does. Yes, among many other things. Well, what literally I was I literally have a huge ramp playing for shad base
Really?
Here's what I like about shad man. Shad man is not afraid to make like
The most disgusting like guru loli porn just because he feels like it and he is continuously hounded by like the the internet police
To like take down his website and like demonetize everything he does
And fuck with him on every single level and he had to like go out of his way to like build an independent website
Which you know these days is really hard and it's just been like a really long journey for that guy to like be a viable content creator
Of the porn that he loves so much that I don't even really like that much
But uh, you know kind of like in general and I he's just kind of uh
He's like an internet pirate and that he went out into the world and he made his own way doing what he really cares about
And he has fucking succeeded. He's got a huge following now
And I just really respect that and I'm also big into uh people being able to make whatever kind of porn they want
So he checks that box too. So shad man that this one's for you, buddy
Uh, I okay sure respectable respectable that that he carved his own uh, yes his own part of the internet
He's the most god-awful person. I've ever had the displeasure. I'll make your case viewing what what so ever
Is it because he made hill loli clinton? Yeah, well, that's my favorite thing he's ever done because I love hillary clinton. Yeah, me too
obviously
Okay, okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. The the main. Oh, he's the guy that made that thing. Oh my god. Sorry. I'm a bit
That's him. He made some really hot art of the uh pokemon trainers from uh pokemon go. Okay. Okay. The main the main problem
This is a good issue that his art is fucking abysmal. It's not. Why does everyone say that? Why does everyone say that?
No, it's not
Then why is he the most rich man in the world based solely off everyone?
What I would say what I would what I would say about shadman's art style is he's like the narrow hoe
Yes, and I love narrow everything. That's right. Yeah, and you love narrow. I don't like narrow hoe. It's it's sort of like
Let's just draw the
Let's just draw the boost like way bigger and just round and that's right. It's not it's not artistic
So I mean it's not artistic. Oh, fuck yourself. It's not as artistic as something else. That's so stupid
It's it's it's not I don't I don't dislike it. It's like in the mcdonalds of porn. It's like eating
You're looking the mcdonalds of my dick. Fuck you. You don't know
It's like you took mcdonalds and took out all the mcgriddles and you just relived with all the greasy horrible shit
The thing about it. All right. I'm not even defending yourself. Is that I have
None. Well, I mean the art is like like I've I've enjoyed some of his art though
It's it's it's just that I can recognize that man
You know, I like other things that like have a bit more anatomy to them
Okay, you know what? That's totally fine. You guys can hate his art
But the the thing I like most about him is his like campaign to survive and struggle to make it during what he's doing on the
I that that's what I really like. Yeah, I do. I do like he seems like he's been on the the sleepy cast
which is like a podcast for
for um, you know, uh psychic pebbles and
And like all those and yeah animators and he's been on that podcast and he seems like a really funny cool guy
Um, so I like him as a person. He's German. So I know he also cares about the arian race. So, you know, we've got
You know, there's a theme here. There's a theme. I just don't like the attitude that comes through like his art
I've never listened to him and I don't want to but just like I I I hate I hate
I I hate porn artists in general who did like who just draw porn and and because why
Because okay, it's like this every piece of art. You hate sex, right?
Sure, sure, but but but but more over it's because every every one like every piece that they make
Just feels like like they they just really really want you to get a boner
And there's well, yeah, they're really really pushing for it and it feels so forced. It feels like great. That's great, dude
Most porn artists suck
This is my problem. Let me ask you this munchie. Are you do you allow yourself to touch your own dick when you're taking a piss?
Is that allowed in your house?
Is that too gay?
I have to open up my pants with my teeth and then and then use my teeth to aim. It's hard. Okay
I can understand that struggle. Okay
Okay, it should have been just like a tryhard edgy asshole. What does that mean?
Oh, he tried so hard to give me a boner with his porn that he draw to make me jack off try hard in the sense of like
It's gonna be Hitler guys
Yeah, I love that. I love Hitler porn
Like like what if it was like, all right, I I get what munchie is saying though. It's it's like, um
You know every sort of drawing is basically the same. It's just with a different character
In in a sense like he's not he's not like creating an an art piece
He's just like taking something that already exists and giving it big tits. Yeah for the most part
I mean, I'm not gonna say that's all he does and and and yeah
It's all to for the purposes of giving people, you know a stimulation is porn
That's what it's for but I guess that the munchie is having a problem with
Being a porn artist as opposed to being an artist who can do porn
Not not like there's a difference to me for from like an artist who does porn exclusively and a porn artist
But the man is
Okay, go ahead. Yeah, like like like an artist who does porn is like, okay
How do I make this like like a visually cool image? How do I make this look nice?
How do I make this look stylish?
But he's just how do I get to manipulate people's emotions the best sounds?
Please let me know it's porn. You're trying to achieve the same thing every point. I get it
I don't like cold. I don't like shitty products, huh, Nate? How about you?
Twiddle my clit, huh?
I maybe I will munchie. Maybe I will twiddle your clit
Uh, okay. Well, yeah, the case has been made people. There you go. That's that's why I like the guy and there's there's he's a he's a hot topic
Just like we're a favorite store. Yeah, that's right. Okay, munchie. What's next?
Okay, okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
Uh
We're gonna have a guy who who who Gibbon knows to and he's probably
Like like like youtube was once dominated by like by like gaming gaming channels where you would talk over a game
Beedly funny jokesmith right and this is
The only jokesmith from that era that that I genuinely like still like the dark side film
Yeah, it his name is germa nine eight five. Oh, yeah
Yep, uh, he's a youtube guy that does like video game commentary videos
Like like it's basically like a like a let's play but he edits it like edits it down to like the best moment
Since it's like seven minute video and all of them are fucking gold like like all of them are great
I was going to recommend star because he was like his friend who like it wasn't a bunch of videos but start like
Just streams over watch like like that's all he does
Yeah, and he doesn't like make videos anymore. And well, I mean, I think he does occasionally, but it's overwatch
Uh, oh, yeah, yes star star is germa's friend who I used to like more because he was like
Exactly, but but then he just it became very obvious that germa is the only one that's actually funny
I think star is funny, but it's just he has to like have a game to riff on
Yeah, germa is a comedian with a gaming channel. That's basically
That's you know, he knows how to make it make you make you just so that the all the pcp fans out there
No, germa's the one who inspired the multi-man pcp world. Yeah. Yeah. He's the guy. Yes
germa rumble is is a series of videos that he's made which are
Basically him just commentating as a wrestling, you know pundit over his shitty characters that he made in a wrestling game
And it's it's really really good. And he eventually made like a live-action version
Which was crazy. He gets used to all the characters from his like videos over the years and have them duke it out such as the
bad boy
Man, I have my t-shirt. I think I roared. I think I worked red con. That's yeah, you did. It was awesome
Yeah, okay, okay
He used to post all that stuff on like on on germa germa 985
But he's since done that weird thing that some youtubers do where he like
Saves his main channel for like big content and then you post like his normal content on the second channel
Which I don't understand at all
But so if you want to find his like actual normal content go to second germa
Is that the name of the channel second germa? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, second. Okay. Yeah
He named it that like temporarily and couldn't think of anything and now it's just cool
I
It's great. I reckon I recommend him if you want to get started go to like like the recent past
And and there'll be something like like the shortest cowboy in the land or some shit like that. It's fucking hysterical
That sounds like my aesthetic. Yeah
Cowboys and short people he's down
Uh, and yeah, it's pretty good. It's a compact. He's come back. He's come back
Uh, take it away from me. Take it away from me. It's gonna bite me
Munchy it's your okay, monkey your turn. All right, folks
Here is somebody who does not need my praise
Somebody who we should all know and love somebody who I am convinced is
Impossible to hate as a human beings donald trump say what you will about some of his recent content and his movie
But as a human being I think it's impossible to dislike james rolf
Yeah, I do it. Oh, yeah
And here's why you know, even if you don't like, you know
Video game shows where the guy just screams cuss words and that's you know, most of the jokes
His passion as a filmmaker is what makes me so enthralled by him as a person and a creator
And I'll watch I mean, I don't watch lots of his let's plays
But anything that he puts out that was made with you know
A modicum of effort. I'll watch he makes weird little projects sometimes like he made a short
Film trailer for dr. Jekyll mr. Hyde the game the movie
And he's not even in it
But I love it because I can tell are all the hard work and the craft he put into it
And he has the behind the scenes any behind the scenes video he does you should watch even if you didn't watch the original thing
Because watching this guy makes stuff makes me want to make stuff so bad because he loves it so goddamn much
Yeah, yeah, I will say the if you've watched uh the avg in movie
I haven't watched it because I've heard that it's bad and I don't really want to ruin it
For myself the idea that james could make something bad
But his making of vlogs of the movie was so cool. So I I assume those are like better than the movie itself
The vlogs of just him going through like the process of writing and making it and buying like
Hiring a tank or whatever like it. He's such a charming guy. I love James Rolf
And his his basement is like my favorite character
Is that better than jesse's basement? Oh, can we compare them? I would say yes
Even jesse's basement is very characterful, but james rolf
Avg and basement is probably I I feel it has better
You know, I I am not uh, I have not seen a lot of avg and content just for whatever reason
I just haven't really stumbled into his shit though. I like I got into jon tron who I know is like inspired by him
I really love his content. So I mean to go back
Um, but just like today I went to youtube and saw that he uploaded a video yesterday james rolf of like episode like
I don't know like 150 of uh, you know angry video game nerd show or whatever
And it had like 800,000 views and I just thought like how cool is it?
This guy's still making this fucking series and so many people still love it
And he's successful at and he's like being able to keep doing it for selling and he's made all these other projects
And like it's gone past the point where I don't some people feel like demo has uh, he's made content
It's getting kind of samey and it's dipped into like the boring part
But like if you persevere and making something like that for like, I don't know 10 years or whatever
And you just keep doing it at that point you come back to like totally
Respecting that kind of effort and dedication to the craft and uh, that's what I feel for him
Even having not seen a lot of his content. My committee is better. He is a huge dick
Mike mate does have a huge cock. It's true
My fair thing to do is to build brown bricks in minecraft
Minecrafty
I think one thing that really makes james stick out to me is that I spend a lot of my time now
Just talking to you pcp people and you're all artists who who hate what you do
And you complain and bitch about it all day. So to see james
Be happy and to enjoy the art that he's making it's a new turn for me
And it's nice to see somebody who isn't a whiny bitch
You just don't get to see him whine and bitch. He presents himself in a certain spin as we all do
We all wear different faces a certain hedgehog spin video
So that's my I used to like his I used to like his content a lot back back in the day
I used to watch it quite often
Funny like the what the first video of his that I saw was about like, um
These video games that were sort of kind of not fit for children. I think or something like that. I don't remember the exact time
Yeah, yeah
I stumbled on that video and that was the first one
You just stumbled upon it insert clip of major feverishly googling pornography video games
I know what happened. I understand
Yeah, that's a real
It gets real, please
Okay, well mage, uh, doesn't I think she's there tapped out. So let's just skip to get to hippo, I guess
Oh
I like james rar
Well, I guess we've said enough about him. He's got something else. I want to hear
Well, I just I just love his his
Is charming like if you've watched like some of his recent videos like about power rangers
He does like a like a 20 minute take and he does the entire video just standing there just talking
Supernaturally like he's so good at it. He's like the best a lot of time
He he's he's the funniest. Well, he's I would say he's uh debatably the funniest
But he's definitely the best video maker in the gaming review circle. What about peanut butter gamer? Come on?
What about necrus?
Peanut butter gamer and catechorus are
Real quick, that's all I will say about I forgot one thing about james rolf is that on his channel
He has these weird documentaries of like there's one from 2002 where somebody made a documentary about him as a college student
Who is like
In aspiring movie guy and he's he's very shy and he's like his teeth are kind of fucked up
And you can tell he doesn't really have like a lot of friends and he talks about that all the time
So it's really inspirational to me that like this guy who just had a dream of being a movie maker and had like
You know little prospects in college is now one of the biggest internet pioneers of all time
Yeah, yeah, I think in terms of like internet pioneering. He's bigger than
He's probably bigger than ara hanson who is also pretty big. Well, sure
I think he was like he's up there with maddox is one of the guys who started a whole new
Genre of of thing on the internet. That's right. Oh, yeah. Yeah
Like
Nostalgia critic was kind of around but he's he's not as good in any way. That's true
Though he did inspire a lot of people. I'm the nostalgia critic. Welcome to the new episode of the pcp. I'm
Oh, he should be our new the pcp membrane fit right in
He said the same we will deign we will we will deign to give him an invitation
And he will he will accept. Hello. I'm a nostalgia critic. It's not true. I didn't I didn't I didn't I didn't hit her
I I'm I'm innocent
Did he turn into tommy we so
Okay, so munch. I mean I mean gib. I mean hippo
Oh, yes, yes
Tommy we so well tommy was out for sure
I
I guess I have a few but I don't know. I mean I have I put Andrew hussy on here, but
His soul. I already said this thing. My joke for that was that he made brisket. That's it
Oh, I got elbow, which is a band a british band who I like and liken to a modern day Beatles in the term in the
Sort of like late later Beatles sort of experimental cool
Sort of interesting melodies and the lyrics and stuff if you listen to a lyrics on an elbow song, you'll be like
It's like real good like pros going on there like real thought went into every fucking syllable that guy's really smart
I like him. He's good and the the the songs themselves are very like
uh
It's hard to describe, but they're very they're very um, well, you know in a way. Yes
Because they're they're they're not like heart
they're sort of like uplifting
and um somber it's very emotional very emotional music
uh, lots of slow builds and and uh, you know, not a lot of like
Dernar nae nae nae guitar. It's just it's just cool. It's just like it's like nice good stuff
And I like it. It's really good and I like elbow and elbow is like my favorite band
It's like real good, you know, and it's like really good and it's like good and I like it sounds good as kneecap
That's true. Kneecap and the superior band. Nya nya nyan cat. Nyan cat is that what you said?
That's my favorite that actually I changed my mind nyan cat is my boy
Nyan cat's my favorite. Say I I'll let him into my catflapping. I'll let him into the pcp
Yeah, make him the banner
Excellent, uh, I want to I want to go. I want to go. Let me go. Let me go. Let me go. Let me go. Let me go. Stop
Stop touching me. I'll unleash that
Oh, is he done?
Well, I mean there's not really much I can say because it's music and you'll have to listen to it
Sing us their entire discography real quick if you would just
Hamtaro when we work together. It's much better my best friend. He likes sunflower. So he's grub grub grub
I'm so glad you guys know the words. I'm not the only one
I fucking grew up on hamtaro that was my favorite show in the world
I'm not I'm not gonna sing
When we work together it's much better my best friend
You have to sing little hamster's big adventures
Uh, that's uh, when I was a young boy
My father took me into the hamtaro to see a
Son of a man
He said son when you grow up
My father took me into the city
Enough
In enough enough
I'm trying to think of the lyrics that I make of skipping between songs
Uh, one will we be singing? I can't do it. It's just bad. Let me let me google the limit
Cut my life into pieces. This is my last resort
Suffocation no breathing
Don't give a fuck if I cut my arm pleading
I think we're gonna get a lot more comments about munchies ear raping this episode. I think that's true
I've been working on a cocktail called grounds for divorce
Whoa
I already like this start
And that's part of it. That's already a good line
Yes, I think that makes them a 10 out of 10
Okay, good. Let's move on. I don't want to embarrass him. I'd be singing on live streams
I know munchie wanted to go but he's gonna have to wait because he uh, interrupt it and it's very rude. Um
Uh, okay, I've got one. Uh, this is a real life one that a lot of people will probably know uh, elon musk
I am a big fan literally a big fan of elon musk and I actually are you are you a fan of his musk?
Absolutely, I would I would sniff that man all day. What about his elon? Do you like his elon?
It's just pretty good. I mean I'm more of the musk guy than the elongated
Well, let me tell you why that's his full name elongated penis month musk
I was not actually a big fan of this guy. Uh, I don't know the big level until like I believe two days ago
Might have been yesterday. I want to happen to read this article. Um, I don't remember the like I retweeted on my twitter
So you can go see there if you care. Um
And uh, so it's this article about so he's starting a new company. So, you know, he's got uh, tesla
And which is like an electric car company and spacex, which is like spaceship program company
He he just made a new one. Um, or maybe it's been around for a little while
But like they're they're starting to get things rolling. It's called neural link
And what neural link is doing is they are developing a bmi technology and that is uh, body machine interface body mass index
Not quite. Uh, it's it's uh, sorry. It's actually brain machine interface. So these things already exist to some extent
They're like, um
They're like chips you could put in someone's brain
Uh, if like you're an amputee and you can give them a prosthetic to make them gay not to make them gay
But to make them uh able to be gay fully as they would have been if they hadn't lost their limb or whatever
Uh, and that's that's just like one example of what you can do with these
Wait, what?
You put a chip in their brain to make them think they have you put a chip in their brain, which uh, you know, which uh
Can read your brain signals and can like send information to like electronics that are contained like a prosthetic. That's cool
Yes, I do like yeah, that's like would bmi's are in general
but so
So what's what's most fascinating to me about this is elan musk's intentions in doing all these things with all his companies
And the way he's going about doing them and I had a whole I had a whole
Time the other day thinking about this and and I realized that he's the smartest man in the world
For by for by a lot and it's it's because of the way that his uh company
Like is structured what it's designed to do and in the article go check out the article really because it's absolutely fascinating
It talks about the way he sets up like his business model how there's like a uh, like there's a goal of the company
And uh, he sets up the like he realizes that he wants to achieve something like elan musk's goal is to uh live on mars
He wants to colonize mars and you know live there and die there. That's his goal for his personal life
So elan musk wakes up in the morning. Yeah, it is pretty cool
So he he wakes up in the morning and he thinks to himself
How am I going to achieve this goal of not just me personally getting to mars and dying there
But starting a colony on mars and realizing that he lives in america in a capitalist system
He then he realizes the only way to do that is to create corporate entities and incentives for average people to get involved
So what he does as his solution is he forms a company called spacex
Which is going to do all the hard work and get government grants in order to do so and shit by by figuring out
How to make this happen how to make this easy to get people to mars, you know relatively easy
And uh, and he's going to do all the work of establishing the base setting up trade routes to mars because he knows once there are trade routes
After that it'll be much much easier to make people even think about the idea of actually living on mars once we are
Are doing shit there period
But who are we trading with them?
We're not trading with anybody. Well, if there's anything there, we'll fucking beat them up because we're america. Um, but uh
We'll we'll just you know mine for resources or do whatever set up, you know, maybe we'll find that
It's fucking the arc of the covenant or something. I don't fucking know
Uh, but we'll go there and we'll do cool stuff, but he wants to live there because it's like
Step forward to space travel
So what i'm trying to say is like so he founds a company, right?
As a way to establish trade routes because he knows that's the only way to get people convinced in their own minds
He knows already that this is a reality
But in order to convince the stupid sheep out there in the real world
You have to do all the hard work for them present them with a plan as to like
Hey, I did all the work involved in making this thing happen
All I need you guys to do is agree that it's cool and then you will just want to be involved
And that's when people will start doing things that are in line with what he wants
And that is how he is a genius who is manipulating people to get things
They didn't even know they wanted by giving it to them almost for free
But doing all the hard work and that's the same shit with this neural link thing
People don't even know that what what what would be great for humanity is to be able to interface our own brains
with things like external memories or
You know super computers that can do the intense calculations that human brains aren't really well set up for
So what he's going to do is he's going to start this company
He's going to go figure out everything and eventually in like 20 50 years or whatever
He's going to present people with hey, I did all the hard work to make this wonderful thing that will revolutionize the world
Are you interested and as people realize that it works and they're getting great results
They'll say absolutely and that's the way that elan musk is fixing the future and making the world better for everyone
By just doing everything and then people will realize later how awesome it all is
and uh
And it's like ghost in the shell neural link is like ghost in the shell. So that's cool. So there you go
It is sugoi, isn't it? He deserves a clap
He deserves the clap
First one first one first one for one clap for elan musk. There you go now. Nate
Here's my problem with elan musk. Okay, sure. I read that he is an immigrant to the us
So he's probably a terrorist
You're right, dude. I didn't anticipate this twist. Why didn't we build a wall to keep him out?
We should have built that damn wall. God damn it. We should build a wall to keep him in
Build a wall around earth so we can't go to mars. Yeah, I hope we do
Uh, that reminds me of an anecdote about elan musk actually. Yeah, I was calling up the other day and he says
It's it's just like what you guys are doing online
You make one false move and everyone turns on you even though you made a great product
And then and then I says to him I says
Listen elan. I I know we gotta do I can support you if you just back me my nigga
You my nigga and he looks at me and he looks at me and says, you know what much you're my nigga
I've been with you since day one dog. I fucked with you heavy
That's how we started together called uh, space x
Nice more like space. It's it's it's space x right. Yeah
Fantastic. All right. Thanks
I didn't realize
Well, okay. Why don't you tell us uh creator yours?
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
Uh, another lee analysis legai is is is text talks and I think I think you subscribe to this channel
Oh, yeah him. Okay. He's a friend. Oh really fuck. I want to be a friend. Oh, well, no, no wait
No, no, he's his his his his his a thing munch munchie
Text talks is the name also of another person who used to be a brony analyst
So you're thinking of someone you're talking about someone
Good thing you explained I I I I know both of them. I don't know both of them, but I know of both of them
So I I got okay. Are you sure they're different people? That just seems weird. There's two people at the same name
Yes, the text talks. Uh, the brony is the guy with the the red oc and he's like angry talk and and
Oh, I remember him now. Okay, right. Yeah. All right. Yeah, it used to be called text
It was the guy who had the the fake unicorn horn that uh ben ripped off that ben stole the idea from I remember that
Yeah, yeah
And and and then and then yeah
I'm talking about specifically a guy who who makes who made a like like a homestuck analysis series
That's huge and and and great and super in death
One episode hasn't come out in a while, but it says he's working on so so I trust them. They're super cool. They so far
They've covered uh
Like the relation between computer science and like the world beginning of homestuck and they have also talked about how like
Gamze's character is bad on purpose. So it's like it's okay guys. Do you agree with that muchy?
Do you agree? No, no, I think he's a fucking sheep and I hate him. Okay, okay
But but but other other than his like bootlicking to hussy I I like him a bit and
I think is I think he's a smart guy and I like his content
He recently came out with like like an analysis of like doda2
And uh, I I don't give a single fuck about doda2
But he talked about tf2 for like three seconds and I and therefore yes
nice
One interesting thing about that guy
Uh, I linked his well, I I noticed that he
I think he talked to me about it or
Or sent me a message saying please show this to Nate because Nate your your analysis of grun lagann is like what inspired him
I think I hope I'm remembering that but yeah, he's like he likes your stuff
Which video are you talking about is like, uh, is the one you want me to show
No, no, I mean which of his videos, uh, did you did like he say to show?
No, he uh, I think I
I liked it
I linked it in the chat a while a long time ago when he posted it. So
Well, cool. I think yeah, he's he was doing good work
And I just wanted him to make more because I'm sure he'll improve like everybody does
I forget whether he made the the episode about risk or being important
I think I watch I'm looking at a channel right now and I see risk in a thumbnail
What yeah, probably probably I only only I remember is the one with rocks in the thumbnail the computer science one
Which was oh, broxy
Yeah, oh my oh my god. Nate. Did you see that one tweet? I said that was completely serious
We're one night. I just dreamed that I was fucking rocksy all like all night
It was great. Did you wake up and like, uh, you know skin yourself raw because you thought of that. Yeah
Yeah, that is a sin. It was awful. I went down like like two levels of crazy conscious and I think but but I made
I made it back. I I drank like 50 cans of of nick loading gag. So that's
That's great, dude. Seriously though. I love rocksy. She's the only thing good about homestack. Uh, yeah, she's she's pretty good
Uh, but yeah, uh, text talks pretty good. Like like it go good. Good job. Good. Okay. Yeah
I I can't remember whether he actually made that episode about brisco. He was going to and I was excited
Maybe he has made it and he's just not like titled as brisco
I don't know. I I watched all his videos
Worst anime ever brisco. That's gonna be good
Oh, yeah, I'll watch it. It has the the the right word in the
He's got the key word. Yeah the key word anime. Fuck. Yeah
That's what I type in I type in key words the key word ever because I want to live forever because i'm afraid of death
What hashtag don't let me die. Okay, uh
monkey
Let's move on
Okay, folks. You ready for a real problem? No. Yeah, biggest problem in the universe this week
Toe nail clippings. No digi bro. No, okay. I got I got somebody, you know, I
I don't remember the username, but that's not what's important here. We're just gonna talk about what they're doing wrong
Because we're here to learn a lesson. We're here, you know, you me us in the viewers want to know
How do I be a good content creator rather than a bad one?
And here's an example of one of the worst ones I've ever seen
So he makes these pokemon let's plays. Oh fucking. Oh, okay. All right. They're not very good
Because here's the problem. Sai has suffered enough. Sai has suffered enough
Come on. If this podcast could go on for three hours, I would include Sai, but it's not
So what this guy does instead of doing, you know, the typical let's play format like a 10 to 15 to 20 minute video
This fucker thinks, you know, I'm gonna put out an hour and 20 minute video once a week
Because everybody has time to watch a full movie instead of like watching it a couple times a week on their lunch break
But then
Then this is when this faggots laziness comes into play because it's not enough that he just records himself
And throws up an hour long video once a week
He'll get busy or sidetracked or forget and the fans will have to go
Two or three weeks without a new episode now when you're playing pokemon
It's important to know what the pokemon are and to feel attached to them so that when they die, you know
It's sad
But if you haven't seen an update in literally two and a half or three weeks and suddenly a new one pops up
I don't remember what fucking pokemon he had. I don't remember when he caught that. I don't give a shit when it dies
It's a shitty format. He's a lazy
Content creator and I really hope he actually suffers a painful death and dies
And his name is monkey jones
It's a gaming expectation
Well, you know, uh one one thing I noticed about that is uh one one thing that I do like about that
Is that he didn't lose and die in his pokemon sun nuzlocke? You know that I gotta say that's a strength
That's a strength of the series. That's because he cheated. I mean if you want to watch him, you know, look up everything
I'll blind nuzlocke
Max revive ben saint. So, you know, we're we're over that hurt. He's cheated in two different nuzlocke
So I think it's okay that I lost one
I don't think he's cheated at all. What is he?
Except for the max revive. I saw on the max revive episode. I saw some weird comment that said oh
Oh, these nuzlocke's are like professional wrestling. We know it's fake. I'm like, what the fuck you talking about
My heart's fucking fake. What the hell are you smoking pokemon? Not real
I don't know why he would say that but some some weird retard
As far as I remember it the the max revive thing was because he was the max revive thing was a bit of a meme
It was not real. It's not. Yeah. Yeah, it's not really like an actual cheat
But he did make his pokemon faint on purpose. So it should have been
discarded
I I guess I was I don't know for training purposes. I mean I for me. It's perfectly acceptable and I have no problem
The thing is the thing is
Uh
I do agree that the episodes are spaced too far apart and too long for me to keep invested in the pokemon themselves
But that is also probably because I just don't like nuzlocke's in general and I can't watch them
Well, let me well as somebody who loves nuzlocke's and somebody who sort of revived it in this little small gay community
I hate his long ass videos
I have to open another tab because I can't sit there staring at it for an hour and a half like a movie
I can't even watch movies in here. I mean
Okay, well, let me raise this point
I find ben's nuzlocke about a thousand times more interesting than yours and I watch both of them
And I think it's because a I actually really love how long the episodes are
I watch all I watch everyone's because I love all nuzlocke's
But uh, ben's are by far my favorites and I think it's because a I really like
How long the episodes are I I actually enjoy that and I it is annoying
I watch them all
It is annoying not to get them, you know frequently
But I understand it's a consequence of this and you could argue what's more effective in terms of like audience
You know retaining your audience
But for me I look forward to them more than any other video every week
I mean every month every well when they come out
They're my favorite thing and it's because of the gravitas that uh, he puts into them with the with the little artwork and the
I don't and I think the length of the video actually has a lot to do with it because you know
You're getting so much, you know, and I really get invested in I will I will say that I liked I liked the last nuzlocke
He did especially by the end because it was like oh look at all those drawings
He did all those drawings and next to him. It's like all those all those guys
The
I I I paid like zero attention to like what was going on because I had in the background just listening to it
But by the end I was like, oh, that was a nice
Remember when Ben went out with bananas and took bananas on that death date. That was like the coolest thing ever
I love that. It was the greatest fucking thing ever. He cares. He cares. Oh, that was good
There's a lot of classes a lot of attack. There's a lot of attack
He's going to attack me because I'm a terrorist and I'm going to bomb his city
And I mean Ben Ben has been working on this Pokemon hell angle for a while
And I I just I know that there is something to come at the end of it
And I'm like I'm really excited about that as opposed to being a normal nuzlocke
You know, I'm always excited for the elite four
But there's something extra going on here beyond and you could argue if it's worth the effort
But I do I gotta say it's my favorite nuzlocke. I've ever seen
I mean, I would argue in my original fire red nuzlocke. We put in lots of live action skits
That's probably the same amount of effort
He's putting those were great and I absolutely loved all of them, especially the manual stuff
That's true. That's true
Now they're shit. Well, yeah, I don't have an animal anymore
I don't really want to like compare you guys. No, I do. I want to compare myself to Ben. I do it every day
Well, if that's what you want to play I would just have to say that I think Ben's
Has a little bit something extra and it you know, you are way better in terms of getting them out on time
which is like kind of the most important thing I guess but uh
His his are his are I just think it shouldn't take anybody literally six months to play one game of pokemon
I agree. I agree
Well, ben and I you see you don't understand because ben and I spent a year doing let's plays of this game called
What fuck equestria bound. Oh my it's fucking god. I everyone's
No, let's play of all time. I need to maximize something. Max delete
Max delete t-bat. No t-bat plays will never die
We're still going the episodes are coming for uh equestria about
Oh, well, okay. I mean, you know, I don't want to criticize you in your opinion about
I want to say I want to say as someone who just generally doesn't care for no
I did a nuzlocke on on my given gaming thing and I blew through it in like five
You know 10 minutes. Everyone was dead. I was like, oh, well who cares and um
I don't like nuzlocke's I find them annoying and difficult to watch
And I have only watched ben's one. I couldn't watch anybody else's
So like as a person who by default hates a nuzlocke's
The fact that I am still watching ben's is is probably indicative that he's putting something
Something little little extra into it that makes it good. I like ben's nuzlocke's too
I kind of like I like the idea, you know drawing the the pokemons and and stuff like he's on little art
The main reason why I want to do a nuzlocke is because I want to do art like that
Well, you're welcome ben. I turned my hate circle jerk into a love circle jerk. There you go
patreon.com slash ben's
Oh, what have I done? I should have brought it in like a real thing. You fucked up, dude. You fucked up
Hey, who wants to bring in a creator? They like named monkey jones. I want to hear monkey jones one
Like I went to Africa. I saw black person. I left
That's why I don't like monkey jones content. Not a fan. Oh real quick before we move on
I am contractually obligated to say my favorite content creator is sheep over go check out sheep over on youtube
True everyone go play. Uh, what's that game called the sheep over the game game sucks game sucks
It's not a real gamer game
Gamer girl, dude, you don't even go have sex at kfc. You're fucking pathetic
Game
Yeah, we should we should start into a pcb speedrun of the sheep over game. We should I beat it but game
Hippo, what's the point of telling a person who's a huge fan of you and who was hoping you would like the game
Just spouting off that their game sucks. It's kind of mean
He wants to break spirits
Silly evil. She made the sheep jumping sound this the sheep from spiral because she thought you would like it
That's why that's why and you're sitting here shitting on the fucking game
You are a monster game. I just got frost. No, you're a bad person. I don't actually hate it. I just got I just got
This hole is just getting bigger and bigger
Um, no, I don't actually hate it. I just died a few I died a few times
I died a few times. I got annoyed
Then I beat it. Well, he didn't beat it. That's a something sheep over pcb race one
Sheep over pcb race to kill her sheep over race war. Ah, you said it first guy
So fucking racist
Come on. All right. Speaking of speaking of speaking of gamers. Yeah, cool gamers. I have another good guy
Um
Gamers tavern. Yeah. Yeah
Gamers tavern. Gamers tavern is a let's player who
Uh, is the most uh underrated word. Um
No, well, he's underrated, but you know, uh, he's the very the the word to describe his
The way he talks is very uh monotone monotone. He's the most monotone
Uh
Punmeister gamer in the world better than me at puns
He just he just he just
his let's plays consist of him playing a game and then
Uh, either I don't know whether he records it during or afterwards. Maybe afterwards
But he just recites puns about what's going on on screen one after another with no, you know, just long awkward pauses in between
Like no emotion in his voice. Just the same tone like it is absolutely masterful dry humor. It's the greatest
It's the greatest the dryness of the humor is so good. That's the word dry humor
The driest humor you will ever find on youtube so good
I love him. You guys brought quite the list of artists. I only had two
I I really I have like five more. I yeah, I've got a couple. I'm gonna
I I assume I assume we're all gonna just like, you know, two or three and so not to prolong this but you guys
Yeah, me and maids don't have
I thought of some of the
Yeah, me and maids are gonna go hang out and wait wait wait wait
I I I have I have another one like right right now. I have I need to say it
I I hate all right. Whoever made the the video on youtube racist mario the animation
Whoever made that fucking video. I hate him so bad
He it's got like 17 billion views and it's just mario kart and he says fuck you and there's peaches tits everywhere
It's the worst video I've ever seen
I hate I hate animators that are just super successful and awful at the same time
You know what?
You know what? I'm gonna throw another one. I just thought about youtuber. They're called jaden animations
They do little animations while they talk about their life and they're kind of like she's kind of like a like a dork
But a nice dork. I like her a real gamer girl at last. Could she be my future wife?
Ha ha ha ha
heart heart a fair maiden who plays li games
My god. Look at her mouse control truly mlg
Those are the genes. I want to pass to my son. Okay. Yeah. She's gelatin. She's she's quirky. She's funny and and I like her content
Gorky
What's her name?
Jaden animations. She's quite she's quite popular. Is she single?
I don't know.
That's what I want to know.
I'm not going to get caught by watching the video.
Monkey, just send her pictures of your ears.
That's your turn, Zemon.
I know gamerheads, dude.
Okay, but, uh, give what's saying.
Speaking of, uh, sick animators,
I just like to give a big shout out to my most beloved, uh,
YouTube animator of all time.
Zoe Quinn.
Uh, close.
It is, uh, Aaron, quote,
if I ever make a let's play, please kill me, Hanson.
My absolute favorite.
Uh, you know, that's really all there is to say.
I hate people.
Do you actually like him?
I actually, uh, as a businessman, I respect him greatly.
I think he's done all the right things.
Yeah.
As his opportunities have come along.
But every day I lament that he is spending so much time
on Game Grumps content I do not enjoy very much,
uh, as opposed to working on just like anything else
that I like more.
Well, the thing.
And I get business wise why he doesn't.
I just, okay, go ahead, go ahead.
He does have that, that business, like the business side.
I actually like that.
Um, I, I, at the time when he just, it was like clear
that he was not going to do animations anymore.
It became a bit sad for a while,
but then I remembered his animations were pretty good,
but it's basically just the stuff he says on Game Grumps.
But even Sequelitis is like a thousand times better.
If he just kept doing those.
Well, yes, Sequelitis I would like more of.
Sequelitis I would like more of, but I,
I don't begrudge him for, for making Game Grumps
a huge thing.
I just find it sad that also now Game Grumps
is not as good as it used to be and is boring.
Well, hey, there you go.
So now there's no reason for me to watch anything that he does.
On the PCP topic, please.
Don't we have Aaron Hansen as its own topic?
I believe we do.
We need it.
We need a cooler.
I guess I'll save that for later.
Okay.
Uh, needless to say, he's not even a dinosaur.
What the fuck?
You go raptor?
Oh, I want to, I want to quickly,
I want to quickly plug two of my favorite
actual animators who are still animating animations.
Okay.
I mean, yes, ma'am, you have made animations,
so that counts.
But I'm thinking more of a hot diggity demon.
I don't know what that means, but.
A butt plug, I would assume.
Yeah, right.
Sure.
Yeah.
Of course.
Hot diggity demon and, uh, Yotam Peril,
who are, who are buddies, who are animators.
Hot diggity demon recently has been doing.
Brain dump.
Yeah.
Which is like a little review show,
which is way over produced, animated.
Yeah.
And the thing I love about Max is he,
he works way too hard, but it's great.
The product that comes from,
from how hard he works is like really like
the best animation on YouTube at the moment.
That comes out semi-regularly.
Or regularly at all.
It's just like really good.
And Yotam Peril is just an adorable,
um, animator guy who's very funny,
and he does like really adorable voices
and has a really cute art style.
And he's just, but it's like cynical content as well.
Like he's, he's, he's a cynical guy,
but it's just like really happy little,
little guys going, oh, oh no, I'm really sad now.
You know, it's, you know, I can't really do stuff
in that sort of.
He's ironic, cynical, a nerd, and a lesbian.
Deal with it.
He's a, he's a nihilist.
Wait, wait, let, let me, hang on.
I got a, I got a wholesome, it's wholesome cynicism
is what I would describe as, is that guy.
Yotam.
Now do you think that, do you think that the ghost
on Brain Dump is funny?
Not funny at all.
It's the worst.
I hate that fucking ghost.
I hate him.
Yeah, but the, the, the grandma's
chunker, bunker, wonker junkers,
that, that, that was great.
I love that.
That's the coolest.
I unironically think he has some cool opinions.
I know that's a dumb thing to say, but like he,
he has some angles in his brain dumps
that I wouldn't have thought of.
And I'm like, oh yeah, he's got a good point.
Yeah.
He's a sweet cookie.
I, I, I like hot diggy demons animations,
but I don't like bring them for the most part,
but it's fine.
Oh well.
I enjoy it.
I, I, I just, I, I like that.
I like his talent, but I'm not really
so sorry to his sense of humor.
Yeah.
Everyone, everyone seems to say that.
Like, I think his humor is hilarious.
When it's on point, like in the fucking
invaders in one, fucking love the invaders in one.
But who's the sassy cat?
Who's the sassy cat that I really enjoy that part?
Oh yeah, that was great.
Oh, where's the Spyro video?
Wasn't he like a little hell once?
He went to BronyCon conventions,
that's what you're asking about.
He was, yeah, he went to those.
Speaking of which, a quick shout out
to Isle of Compossible a lot,
my favorite YouTuber.
Oh my God, my favorite.
My favorite.
Hark, a true gamer girl, over the horizon.
Yes.
Can I just give a shout out to every gamer girl,
every real gamer girl out there,
just the best, just the best.
Please bear with me.
My dear same maiden, may I fancy you
a candy that shaped like a Nintendo
entertainment system.
I keep them to my breath, minty fresh.
Would you like a shirt that says
I heard Star Wars?
Yeah.
My other car is a millennium falconess.
With a Batmobile scrapper.
I want to give out one last real shout out,
and this is very different from what you guys,
what we talked about so far.
So I am actually a huge fan of ASMR in general,
and I watch it like all the time.
Yeah, I know it's weird, right?
But I'm big into it.
I'm literally gay.
And furthermore, I don't even like female ASMR,
I only like male ASMR.
Yeah, not a joke, not a joke.
It is so gay that he's straight.
It has a lot to do with the fact that I get a boner
when I listen to female ASMR and have to jack off,
so that's just annoying.
So I listen to mostly males.
This one guy is by far the favorite,
he has proven himself over the years
as the standout champion of the ASMR community,
and his name is Ephemeral Rift.
He is very popular, and he is the best.
He does all these weird creaky-cookey things
that some of them are hit, some are miss,
but in general, I love most of what he does,
and he's consistent, and he's fast, and he's great,
and he also does, I don't know,
he just talks about his views on life,
and they're pretty in sync with mine,
so I don't need to hate him,
like I do every gamer girl who I marry.
So there's that.
And yeah, he's cool.
So if you like male ASMR,
Ephemeral Rift is by far the champion.
Everyone else is shit.
I used to love...
Is it legal to be married to two people at once?
Is that legal?
In Utah, I think.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
That's Polly Ganey.
Polly Ganey, yeah.
Hello, my honey.
Pollo Gamy.
It's it.
I'm a fucking asshole.
Polly Propylene.
Yo, let me tell you real quick, just one,
just because I'm sure nobody who knows
who the fuck Ephemeral Rift is.
Like, here's an example of one of the things he would do.
So like, he'll do like these role plays.
Just get close to the mic.
Well, yeah, he'll be fucking close to the mic.
I mean, that's always assumed.
Like, this guy, he does ASMR,
which is all, you know, kind of the same shit,
just like quiet talking and shit.
But Nate, though, isn't it a separate topic on the list?
Yes, but I just wanted to tell people
what I like about this specific guy
in regards to this.
And it's so like, just one example is,
he did one video where it's like him
in the post-apocalyptic world, right?
And he is like, he is pretending to his son,
which is you.
You're like his, or I guess his kid.
It's gender non-specific.
And he is like pretending that in the apocalypse,
no, he's pretending to like be a fancy restaurant.
Okay.
And so like, he's got like cans of spam
and he's pretending that it's like really high quality food
and he's eating it and like,
like the premise here is that he is pretending
that it's really fancy and nice and delicious.
And he's also talking about how like,
like your mom died and she,
or she like ran off when the apocalypse struck.
And like, this just gets woven into this like ASMR video.
And he's talking about like, yeah, you know, son,
I loved your mom, but she was dumb as a stump.
And she's probably out like fucking a,
like a warlord right now.
That's just what your mom is doing right now.
I hope that, you know, if you weren't here,
I would have blown my brains out long ago,
but you know, I care about you.
And that's just the kind of shit he talks about.
And that's, that's very much my aesthetic.
I like spam.
He's deep as fuck.
Yeah, spam.
I like watching many spam.
That's what I'm trying to say.
I'm gay. I'm literally gay.
Welcome to the Munchy ASMR.
Today I'm going to be cleaning up the remains of my ex-wife.
I, I, I, she, she's all over bits in my room.
I'm going to have to clean her up before the police call.
That's not even, that's not even unrealistic for things
that some of these guys would do.
I want an ASMR of Munchy peeing on, on his face.
Someone may, someone needs to go out there.
A piece of defense needs to go make the Munchy peeing supercut
and put together all the fucking piss shots.
Please.
The piss shots.
The money shots.
Oh no.
Okay. Well, I'm, I'm done.
I got more, but that was all the important ones.
Let me go.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Okay. This is another guy that, that, that hippo,
the hippo knows.
Uh, trainer tips.
Oh yeah.
Train, trainer tips.
He's pretty cool.
Is, is a vlog of a guy named Nick.
And he really, really fucking likes Pokemon Go.
Like, like really.
He really likes Pokemon Go.
Like, like faithfully.
Like, basically every video on his channel is about Pokemon Go.
But it's like, like, like, but it's not, it's like,
a lot of people like come like to him to like,
oh, how do I learn the strats?
But it's like, his channel is really just like a vlog.
Like, like, like most of the video is just like,
like him, like doing his, his, his normal day stuff.
But he also just happens to like Pokemon Go a lot.
So he's, he like, he gets into mechanics and shit.
And he like teaches the kids, but it's mainly a vlog.
And the reason I like him, most, most of all,
he feels like a cool guy and shit.
But you know, the main reason is that his editing is fucking,
it's great.
It's, it's really great.
It's super high production.
And, and, and the way he like, the way he cuts his like,
the way he cuts his scenes by like, like,
like I'll put his hand over and it'll fucking take it away
and it'll be in a new scene.
All his transitions are great.
Everything about him is fucking cool.
He has like drone footage in.
So he'll like, he like lives in like Long Beach.
It was like the prettiest fucking city ever made in humanity.
North Side Long Beach.
Yeah.
He'll just like fly like his drone over and get like a cool
shot of like above Long Beach.
He's, he's, he puts way too much effort in shit.
And he releases videos every day.
So he's like Nate, but better.
He's like Nate, but every day.
Yeah.
But every day.
Every night.
Every day.
Best Nate ever.
Number nine.
Get out.
Oh, by the way.
Okay.
I like, I like trainer tips editing as well.
It's, it's that he used to be like, I mean,
he still is like inspired heavily by Casey Neistat.
If you've ever seen Casey Neistat vlogs,
where it's like, you just going around,
I'm rich and I got a electric skateboard and I'm going to woo.
And that, you know, that's Casey Neistat.
I'm on a plane again.
It's stuff like that, except intercut with Pokemon Go footage
and him talking about Pokemon Go and saying,
Oh, look at this catch.
And recently the other day, which is like really cool.
He went to Australia to catch a Kangaskhan because he has money for that now.
That's awesome.
And, and he, the whole video was basically literally a documentary of him as a,
you know, like a, you know, that famous Australian guy that would go up to.
Guy who like finger and punch rain died.
Yeah.
Steve Irwin.
He did a whole like video where he was like sneaking up on a Kangaskhan to try and catch
it.
And he, and you know, he edited it.
So yeah, he had the, the, the accent go in the whole thing.
And it was like, it was like a real like production, like a, like a little,
and he was just him with his camera and Pokemon Go.
And he did all this in Australia.
Yeah.
Australia is like, it was really cool.
It was really good.
Even though the action was kind of cringy, but it was a good job.
I like him.
He's good.
And you know, just speaking of Pokemon Go, I'd like to give a shout out to my favorite
meme creator of 2016.
That would be Hillary Clinton.
Pokemon Go to the polls.
There you have it.
Now, I don't know who made this shitty joke.
I want to figure out how to make them fucking die.
Okay.
I do have one serious actual YouTuber.
I just, I just thought of this person as a side note.
The, the biggest problem with them is that they haven't uploaded and got almost three
years now.
It's, it's, it's really shitty.
Yeah.
Best guy ever.
No.
Yeah.
Best guy ever.
No.
The, the last one they called was something about how life's really unfair about being lonely
or something.
Big shout out to Elliot Roger, my favorite YouTube, YouTube content.
I hope, come back soon, brother.
Come back soon.
Make more.
Nate.
Nate, didn't you hear what happened to him?
No.
What?
No, he got a movie deal.
He's not doing YouTube anymore.
I mean, I'm happy for him, but I feel like it won't be the same as the content that we've
come to expect from him.
Yeah.
They're making a, they're making a Columbine retribution movie and he's starring in it.
Mix feelings, dude.
Mix feelings about that.
It's, it's a revolutionary film technique because they're actually going to kill real
people.
Yeah.
No, no.
They're just going to record him shooting people.
It's going to be cool.
That sounds good.
I was actually sleuthing around myself because, because I'm a big fan of his work and like
I, I found like a YouTube channel that's like basically I didn't come so it's a little
bit of conspiracy theory, like a little bit of elite, but I think I found like like a secondary
channel of his.
It's called like Monkey Jones.
I don't know if you've ever heard of it, but, but I think.
Wait, Munchy Jones?
You see Munchy Jones?
Yeah.
What I'm saying is you guys should subscribe to Munchy Jones.
It's a real channel.
Look it up.
Yeah.
It is.
And I think, I think he's doing God's work.
I think he's doing the Queen's work.
Yeah.
All right.
I have, I have, this is the last one that I actually have any preparation for.
Okay.
Niga Higa is, is a YouTuber.
Oh, I remember him.
Yeah.
He was like way back in 2005 making videos, vlogs and stuff and he grew huge and, and
stuff, making funny videos, funny skits, you know, comedy stuff and yeah, how to be a
gangster, how to be a nerd, how to be an injured video, I think.
Yeah.
And maybe that was somebody else.
But the thing about him, which I feel, I feel among all the like 100, like billion trillion
subscribed channels, like he's really high up there.
The thing that I think compared to everyone else is just that he, he deserves it more
than anyone else because his videos are just so consistently well done.
Like he writes so much, like twists and turns into his scripts and executes them every time.
Like really like, it's funny because like every video just looks like, oh yeah, it's
just another big video from a guy who's a big YouTuber and it's like whatever, it's
just him saying, hi guys, I'm gay.
Like, you know, it doesn't look like it's going to be good.
But every time I watch it, because I know by the end I will be smiling.
It's always, it's always got something good in it.
And it's nice.
He does, he does some things that like, he made a Rube, a Rube Goldberg machine.
I think what, that's what it's called, right?
Yeah, a Rube Goldberg.
Rube Goldberg.
One of those, yeah.
He made one of those just for a short like two second clip of a thing in a video and
it was like a really extensive, like in his garage, garage, garage, like a whole big thing.
And the, you know, he had like bloopers of it not working the first time and he had to
reset it up.
And it's just, I really appreciate the amount of work that must go into every video he does
because it's good.
Thanks for reminding me of him.
I want to watch some of his videos now, then it's going to, yeah.
But also watch his new stuff, like anything, anything he's made is like, it may seem like
a dumb thing that's like, you think, oh, well, the obvious joke is this, he's going
to make something that isn't the obvious joke.
That's how I would say about all this stuff.
Tee hee.
Yes.
Yep.
Well, with that, are we, are we done with all our creators?
No, no, why?
Oh, please, can we go to questions, please?
No.
Okay.
You got, you got one more, dude.
You got one more.
Like a cow.
Like a power round.
It's a trio of people.
It's like the Eric Gontrich show, it was just the skits and also better and it has really
tight editing and it's really like fucking like crazy, weird comedy skits, but the new
shit is like weird, like political and like kind of weird.
Their old stuff is like it, like if you had like a fever dream, but instead of taking
Nyquil to treat it, you took a black pill, green pill, and down it with some Nickelodeon
Gac.
It's pretty good.
Watch, watch all the stuff around Charles bombshot 9-11 video and before that, then we
have Wisdom Gun, that's that's Parkour dude 91's creator, Ran Runkowski's new channel,
after Fall of the Eagle Nation.
It's pretty similar to old, like millionaires extreme stuff, except like more Parkour dude
91.
Pretty good.
I haven't followed Wisdom Gun very, very often, but it's, it's, it's, it's pretty,
it's pretty good.
Go, go there.
The last real one, Temple of Rigs party.
It's a really good band.
It's like, it's like 80s.
It's like, it's like a vapor wave was like good and not a horrible, awful dribble.
It's like 80s rock synth wave.
And now the thing we've all been waiting for, hashtag, say it with me folks, Max Revive T-Lag.
We need to get T-Bap back on the front lines.
We need to get them back.
All right, all right, all right, you kids don't, you, you guys don't even fucking know.
There's these two horses, right?
And they're getting all their sludge on when suddenly these bitches come up and their
motherfucking grill bitch.
So they have to ward off these smelly, extravagant bitches while still doing their horse homework
on horse time.
What the fuck?
Get them on the phone.
They need to come back to you.
Hang on.
I'm going to call cake standard right now.
That guy's a busy man.
Who knows if I'll answer.
All right, say something for this stream.
What?
Who's calling me?
Who is this?
What's going on?
Is that you, Gibbon?
Yeah, Keg, fucking where are you dude?
What happened?
Oh, you know, I went back to college.
I dropped out for 20 years and then I went back.
It's, you know, that's just, I'm trying to get my GED.
Oh, did you go to the college where KP did that song like you were in the background?
No, I can't afford to that.
I had to make my own college in my own house.
It's cake standards, a university of Puss.
The UP, yeah, that.
That's where I go.
I'm learning how to sex myself.
I'll have my degree soon and then I'll have a lucrative career ahead of me.
Thank you, UP.
Do you know what the phone is?
I'm sitting in a drone.
He's going to be gone in a couple of seconds.
Get him off the phone.
Okay.
Goodbye.
All right.
Bye.
That was the last thing we ever made here.
Keg's fucking done.
Keg's done.
That poor bastard.
Keg is over.
Now he's got a fine phantom on wherever he is.
Is it like Siberian caves?
We've got to send us a drone his way too.
I'm looking forward to that.
Okay, let's do the questions now.
Okay.
Here we go.
I got a couple assembled here.
Okay.
What was the first one I saw?
Here we go.
At Spacko 306 asks, if Kirby absorbed you, what power would he get?
Depression.
Good one.
Very good.
That's similar to like the sleep power where he's just immobilized for a while.
No, no, no, no, no.
When Kirby has depression, you can't help.
But whenever you press any direction, he walks closer to the edge.
Yes.
And he's about to break.
He's one step closer to the edge.
Oh, you got it.
And the only difference between Kirby's depression and Mumki's depression is that Mumki's never
goes away.
Mumki can't just press a button and make it turn to a little star and get rid of it.
Well, no.
Has he ever tried it?
No.
Press select.
I haven't tried using the Mumki cheat codes yet.
I'm trying not to cheat.
Okay, that's fine.
Well, then you're not like Ben Stain at all.
No.
Okay, let's see.
I'm not like Ben Stain.
No, no, no.
If Kirby nailed me, hmm, let me think.
Well, here, here.
Jack.
Kirby's right next to me.
Why don't you inhale me?
Get on the ground!
You fucking nuisance!
That's like the megaphone power.
You have like a racist variation of the megaphone power.
Yeah.
That's perfect.
Oh, you know what he'd get?
He'd get the Ku Klux Klan hat and a megaphone and would just, you know, go to town with
that shit.
Perfect.
Yes.
It's like, you know, you know how the megaphone power gives him like, first he's got like
the radio announcer with like the headphones, then he gets like the one with like the Mohawk
with like the guitar or whatever.
And then like the other is just like a little megaphone.
Like you would have the fourth step.
That's like the Ku Klux Klan hat and a big megaphone shouting at a Black Lives Matter
rally.
That would be, uh...
Exactly.
Guys, okay.
Take this voice apple right here.
Mission body and like make a mod of Smash 4.
Make the end place high with that.
Just replace Kirby with that.
Make that Kirby Smash 4.
Wait, we say it again?
Like mission body.
Take that voice slip right there.
Like isolate.
Download this video and isolate that.
Then make a Smash 4 mod where instead of Kirby saying hi, he says listen buddy.
Oh yes.
As is taught.
That's that's genius.
Somebody do that.
Uh, monkey.
I mean, sorry, Mage.
Go on, go on.
If, if, if, if Kirby inhaled me, he'd get an edgy OC.
Oh, shit.
Are you as Sasuke?
No.
Like edgy.
Don't you know lethal?
Lethal, Mage?
Yeah, exactly.
Make a personification of self-loathing, which is a very edgy OC.
Yes.
Nice.
Uh, what about you, Gib?
It'd be the power to shit on somebody who made a game for you.
Yes.
Uh, yes.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
No.
Kirby, Kirby would get the ability to, um, not make main channel videos.
Exactly.
That's, that's absolutely perfect.
Um, God, I don't know what he would do if he ate me.
Uh, he get like a thousand, he get like a sunglass to, you know, generating and throwing
power.
Yeah.
I was going to say something with sunglasses.
I'd do it.
Uh, okay.
Here we go.
Before we go to the next question, can I make a clarification real quick?
Sure.
Uh, okay.
I don't want to, I don't want to make it seem weird.
So earlier in this podcast, I was very hard on Ben and I just want to clarify that I do
actually hate him and I hope he dies.
I didn't want anybody to get confused by, you know, kind of the jokey nature earlier
on.
I'm not kidding.
I actually hate him as a human being and I want him to be suffering, being pain.
That's understandable.
Monkey, you have never not ever, you've never like gone back on that.
Like even like one-on-one conversations, you stick to it.
I don't know how, how jokey it is.
It's too real.
We made a few vlogs when I was at Digi's house last time and I was at least civil with Ben
in those videos.
Okay.
So he's able to package his, you know, his hatred away at least temporarily at times.
I'm only nice to people when they're within distance of hitting me.
Understandable.
Makes sense.
Okay.
Next question.
Here we go.
Uh, at Janiz Makudomaru, our old buddy says, uh, I'm getting a new comp in a few weeks.
Should I get the protection plan with McAfee or not?
Um, I'm gonna have to go with a, I'm gonna have to go with, yeah.
You want to protect your shit, dude?
You should get McAfee and Norton and have them fight.
See, make them both claim that each one of their, like each other is a virus.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Yeah, you compete to see which is more powerful and you take the winner.
That makes sense to me.
Well, they, they should get a vast because it annoyingly likes talking to you.
So you'll never feel alone.
I just want whatever plan has that little paper clip come up is like, Hey, uh, can
I help you?
Uh, how do you use Windows?
You don't seem to know what the fuck you're doing.
Let me help you.
I have a really great, uh, antivirus program.
It's called Bonsai Buddy.
I use it all the time.
I have a couple different versions of this all right now that they're talking to me.
They're trying to sell me like hamburger helper right now, but it's just really helpful
because I often buy it.
Do you actually have that?
No.
Okay.
I would have really loved you to actually have it.
Serious suggestion.
I use AVG because it's free and it's kind of okay.
I actually have no idea if it does anything at all.
I don't even know.
I have no answer to this.
I use spy bought search and destroy.
I just go to download more word.com.
Whenever I have any problems and just hit a couple of minutes more.
All right.
Fucking.
Oh, Nate.
Can I pick a question?
Yeah, go for it.
Uh, at monkey away wants to know, and I wanted to ask this because me and did you were too
scared to talk about it, uh, who of the PCP, who likes the insufferable social media debate
podcast and who hates it?
Cause we said half you hate it and half you love it.
I like it.
I, I, I, I, I think, I wouldn't, I wouldn't pay for the bonus of doing right now.
I, I enjoy it, but I wouldn't pay for the bonus episode because I don't pay for things,
but I do like it.
It's, it's fun.
It's like, it's like a new dynamic that I've never seen Digi try to be and succeed at being
funny ever.
Like he's actually funny and I, no, no, no, it's a backhanded compliment.
Digi is generally not funny, but in this podcast, he is very funny and I like it.
I, it's one of those things that I actually liked the idea of a lot, but I never watch
it.
I've seen like one, I think, and, and liked it.
And then when there was a bonus episode, I like had an instinct to want to see it.
But as soon as there were any impediments to doing so, uh, lost all interest.
So, uh, yeah, that's, that's where I'm at.
That's where I'm at.
We didn't have any of the real haters on that podcast is how good the person who made
the thumbnail spelled in the first episode fucked up and changed it.
Yeah.
He didn't raise.
It's fucked up.
Dude.
Nobody seems to dislike it though.
Nobody seems to dislike it.
Well, I think the people who dislike it aren't here today.
That's probably true.
Uh, let's see here.
Digi.
Uh, okay.
How about, um, Digida, oh, at DSI Benji says, this isn't a question, but says this isn't
a question, but I want you guys to talk about giving to raise amazing rap rap dog.
And I also want to talk about rap dog.
Yeah.
It was awesome.
I was in one day because I felt like I've always wanted to make music and I don't know
how.
So I just did that.
It was great.
Your dad was successful.
Yeah.
Wasn't your dad in that?
My dad was in there.
Your dad was the main character.
You got a dad.
You seem.
Uh-oh.
Shouldn't have mentioned it.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
But you see, Munchy, you're implying that it would be easy to steal my dad.
It's not.
It's in fact very difficult.
He's unstealable.
We'll see about the unstealable dad.
My worst nightmare.
He has like sticky shoes.
He could stick to the floor at any time.
Oh, no.
That's the one thing I didn't account for is goop.
Even though all I think about every day of my fucking life is goop.
No.
That's the one thing I didn't account for is goop.
Even though all I think about every day of my fucking life is goop and sludge and ooze.
I didn't account for it.
Shit.
You know, I meant to actually mention this question in response to Munchy's last one, but I forgot
to.
And it was just, um, by At Admired the Tire said, uh, thoughts on Munchy thinking his
opinions are worth $1?
No opinion is worth spending on money on, in my opinion, especially people just spewing
shit.
Any, any response to that, Munchy?
Yeah.
I think he doesn't know what the show is if he thinks it's my opinion show.
That's fair.
He might just be retarded as most, uh, as, well, I mean, to be fair, as everyone paying
money for that show, if I could say something, it's really weird.
All these people are commenting, complaining as if it's a big surprise that there was a
bonus episode.
But in the previous free episode, we talked about the bonus episode the whole time.
So they're complaining about content that they don't have access to, even though they're
not utilizing the stuff that's free and right there for them.
I'm curious how many people, like how many money do you have from that so far?
So far today, this is the date it came out, we're rounding up, I think about a hundred
right now.
So about 50 bucks each.
It's pretty good.
So a hundred people out of how many, like a 10, how many people usually watch the podcast
is like two, three thousand?
I don't know.
The first one has like 11,000 and then the second one has like eight.
So they're rounding up about like seven or eight.
So yeah, yeah.
It's not bad.
It's like a very small amount of the eight thousand, but still that's a hundred bucks.
I feel like I should do this.
And I think I can.
Yeah, we should all.
I looked into it while we were setting up and I think I can charge for something.
I don't know.
That's a lot dollar once.
Maybe I should put up a video that says don't buy this and if people buy it, I will laugh.
I can see that on the Gibbon Take channel.
Of course.
That would be good.
Okay.
Here we go.
By at stewing in Susumu says, what is really the worst pizza topping because they're sick
of this.
Well, okay.
They say, do you believe in pineapple being seen as the worst is a meme that needs to
die?
I think pineapple is fine.
Pineapple is fine.
It is a shitty meme.
I don't know where this meme started.
It probably comes from that one, you know, picture that girl from like her yearbook.
That's like, if you like pineapple under pizza, then your bloodline is weak and you will
not survive the winter.
That's good.
That's a good meme.
But at this point, it's drifted into real life where people actively don't like pineapple
because the meme's gotten too real, but pineapple didn't do nothing.
Pineapple's good.
Yeah.
What are we talking about?
The worst pizza topping is probably Doritos.
There's like a taco pizza and it's like 100% Dorito fucking chips in its dispensers.
It might not taste the best.
Stealing your dad.
It might not taste the best, but it does elevate your Christ consciousness substantially.
Who here likes olives under pizza?
I like it.
I do.
I do in general.
Why?
Why not?
Because I like olives.
Olives are, you know, like little salty things.
You know what I like about olives?
I like that they're kind of a vegetable and I can eat them and feel slightly better about
the pizza I'm eating.
That's on my mind.
I think about that.
The only pizza I can get is meat lovers because it's the best I want pizza.
The only thing I like about pizza is when the bread is nice and tasty and fluffy and
squidgy and not too thin.
If it's thin crust, get fucked.
I love thin crust.
Thin crust is fucking sick.
Thin crust, get fucked.
That's what I say.
No.
We're going to have a problem, Jim.
B-B-W, like crust.
B-B-C, crust.
I like bread more than I like pizza.
And pizza is like mostly bread.
Thin crust for life.
In fact, in fact, I would eat a pizza which is just bread.
Bread and nothing else.
What about cheese?
That's just called bread.
No cheese.
Just the...
Okay.
No, I get it.
I like it when pizza has like nice like stretchy cheese.
That's the best kind of cheese.
Except for when it stretches down your fucking throat.
Yeah.
That is gross.
That is nightmare.
There's like a semi-local place near my house.
It's like California, a thing.
It's called Fleet Bay's.
And the cheese, they put like seriously like three normal amount of pizzas on the cheese
and they put clogged your heart.
It's fucking insane.
It's great.
I would outlaw cheese if I could.
Whoa.
Cheese, it's gotta go.
It's gotta go.
I hate cheese also.
Have you ever considered what it would be like to have a hole in your chest?
Because I'm about to inflict that upon you right now.
I don't like cheese in anything.
I don't actually...
I do like cheese, but...
Do you like nacho cheese?
No.
Oh, shit.
That's the best kind.
I don't like...
It's just...
I don't know.
Do you like nacho cheese Doritos?
Hell yeah.
Not on a pizza though.
I mean, that's like cheese powder, you know, that kind of shit?
No.
I don't know.
There's something about the taste of cheese that I don't like.
That's crazy, dude.
You guys are making me hungry now.
That's my God.
Yeah.
Do you like Crab Rangoon's with cream cheese in them?
They're called Crayon Goons, but yeah.
Oh my God, guys.
Crayon Goons.
Clam Chowder.
Dude, haven't I told you the story of Crayon Goons about how there was a typo on my fucking...
Thin crust, get fucked.
Go, Crayon Goons.
You're dead, you're dead.
What's the next question?
Next question.
This is my new first name.
This is our next and last question.
Given takes, you made a mistake.
We're in the same continent.
Oh shit.
Same country.
Oh my God, she's rapping.
Oh, that's...
Yeah, she's coming for you, dude.
She's coming for you.
She's got a...
Is the pizza blue...
Are you flying away soon?
Dude, she's got an NGOC and she knows how to use it.
Exactly.
Why the fuck out?
Okay, last question.
How much...
Oh, by Michael3041.
How much is too young for sex with the young?
I don't think this guy understands the question here.
I don't think he's really aware of what we're talking about when we're talking about sex
with the young.
My favorite, my favorite, is when you're...
They're so young that it's like nine months before they were born.
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
I was gonna...
I mean, there's a couple adages I like to use in times like this.
Let me see.
Grass on the field, play ball.
That's one.
And the other is old enough to crawl.
Or enough...
Oh, they're already in the right position.
Yeah, that's the one.
That's the one.
Yeah.
I think if they can count the right amount, that's my policy.
If their age is on the clock, they get the conch.
Yes, that's right.
But what does that...
Like one second old, I guess, would technically be on the clock?
No, it means age one through twelve.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, you can't go younger than one.
What are you talking about?
You can't use it.
Sicko.
You can go younger than one.
Oh, you're disgusting.
Yeah, you're disgusting.
I'm five fucking infants.
But come on, if they're like one second before they hit one age-year-old, then come on.
Let me ask this though.
Does it count as sex with a young if you have sex with a very pregnant woman?
Does that count?
I want to say yes.
That's the first thing I said.
According to Maddox, yes, it does count.
I agree.
Should you be arrested?
It's like your only way to have sex.
With the young, with that young.
That's legal.
That's legal child sex.
The youngest person to ever have sex was me when I abolished slavery.
Sex slavery, a.k.a. the ability to have sex.
Yeah, that was well done.
Okay, that's the end of these decent questions.
They were all garbage.
Do better next time, as always, everybody.
All right, thanks for asking enough of a message.
Make sure that you're around next Saturday and you send us more questions at tpcrasnayers
on Twitter.
Follow us.
And thanks for watching, everybody.
And we'll see you next time.
Monkey Jones is going to break your mom.
The games will never stop.