Ah, fancy meeting you here. Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm the best guy
ever. And let's see who we got here. We've got Gibbontake. There you go. In and out. We've
got Ben Saint. Yes, technically correct. Accurate. That's the best kind of correct. Tom Oliver.
I did it. I'm here. I made it. Just in time. Just in the nick of time. Nobody's ready for
breakfast. Mage, what's up? Apple's motherfucker. And that's it. And that's the last one. Apple.
It's like that Apple Pokemon. Like I do like them apples. I mean, I'd rather... Oh, you
know what? I love oranges. There was a big debate about oranges versus apples the other
day, but I gotta tell you, oranges, apples, they're dodging. Let's not revisit the juice,
debacle. What the hell happened? Let me just tell you, the best thing, one word, grapefruit.
Grapefruit is the greatest fruit on the planet. You're right. And no one appreciates it. Nobody
appreciates grapefruit. Literally no one else in the entire world likes grapefruit but me.
What the fuck? Don't be one of these hoity-toity motherfuckers with your grapefruit scissor
and your spoon, putting sugar on it. Yes, that makes it like a fucking bowl of sweet
cereal. No, you peel it like an orange. That's so fucking yucky. That's so fucking gross
that people will put my fucking juice. Yeah, like a grapefruit's fucking sweet already,
you fucking coward. It stinks of the bourgeoisie and I'll have none of it. It's something fucked
up's going on here. If you're like, sugar would add something. Pure sugar would add something
to this experience. I fucking hate sugar in most foods. I feel like sugar is like to
have like sweet chili or like sweet and sour food, like sugar in like a savory food, like
a main course. It just feels wrong. I hate barbecue sauce. It's disgusting. No, I don't
agree with that. I read a recipe. It's the worst fucking shit in the world. I read a
recipe on r slash keto recipes. That was for crustless keto pizza. Funny thing about this
pizza is that you just fucking put cheese on a pan and bake it and the cheese just becomes
the crust. It's really funny. You know, that's like a weird take on the fact that... Just
get rid of the middle man. You're only there for the sauce and cheese anyway. That's all
you really want. Yeah, it's like if you don't do this complicated thing where you use all
these alternate almond flour for the crust, call it... No, just no crust. Cheese on the
pan. Just bake the cheese. Just eat the cheese. But then this guy, who was like, if you want
to do like a fancy sort of sweet pizza, sprinkle a little stevia on top of the crust. Oh yeah,
stevia. What the fuck? I don't get that. Like are you fucking kidding me? Who on this fucking
God's green earth has sweet pizza? That sounds like a nightmare. I mean, I understand like
Hawaiian pizza has pineapple on it. That's not my thing, but like I get it in concept.
But to just take like some fucking like sugar substitute and just sprinkle it on top of your
pizza, you must be fucking high, bro. I mean, what's wrong with you? Some places have like
cinnamon breadsticks. You can get like, and they're very similar to like the normal garlic.
It's like that just is the crust of the pizza. But we're not talking about making a cinnamon
pizza or like a dessert pizza. This is just a regular pizza made with like cheese and
fucking pepperoni. Just sprinkle some sugar on top. No. Yeah, the combination. The combination
of sugar and savory is what annoys me the most. Like I love desserts. Everyone can enjoy
a good dessert. But like having a sweet thing in something that is otherwise savory really
annoys me. I turned my nose up. I'm a savory boy. I'm a spicy boy. I'm a savory spicy
boy. You're being very elitist right now. That's all. Guys. What? Have you ever had chocolate
pizza? That sounds just like a pancake. I've had like Domino's. I've had like the like
dessert pizza, which is just like an Oreo fucking frosting thing. I had a chocolate ice
cream sandwich where I just got two slices of white bread and put chocolate ice cream
in the middle. It's actually really good. Bread goes well with it. I had I had chocolate
pizza for Mazda and it sucks and I'll never have a chocolate pizza again. There's this
place nearby that looks like the Buskin Baker or something. They have a food truck outside
that is it's like ice cream donuts and they have they have like these they give you a
warm like freshly cut donuts. They cut it in half and in between they put like a layer
of like pizza. I think I had like raspberry ice cream. It was fine. It was okay. Oh damn
and ice cream and I was not overly impressed. Sounds all right. Yeah. I also made another
recipe from r slash keto recipes. I made keto brownies and I don't know what the fuck is
wrong with them. All right. I don't know. It said it said use xylitol. Use erythritol.
Don't use stevia. I don't understand why you can't make this in the fucking lab and concocting
with magic spells and tinctures. I don't know why you wouldn't be able to use stevia if it's
like it's just as sweet if users are but apparently but I use so I was like that's stupid. I made
it. I used stevia and it's not sweet. It's fucking these brownies are the textures mediocre.
The flavor is fucking like bitter. They're awful. But I can't throw them out because
they're made of fucking butter and almond flour which is too precious and I can't waste it.
So I have to I'm still shocked to this day by the fact that when you like when you what's
the word cook. I don't know when you fry onions they turn sweet which is which is truly stupendous.
I guess so. I guess so but I don't know. I guess I fucked up. I guess I did it wrong.
My brownies are terrible. They're they're a nightmare. Well that's so I took the pizza
idea and I sprinkled stevia on top of them and I don't know. It's a little better. Hey
here's a fact. Here's a fact that makes me mad. The main ingredient in stevia the zero
calorie sweetener that's not sugar. Do you know what the first ingredient is bread dextrose
it's sugar. But they remove all the bad strokes and they only leave the decks. Wrong. You're
super speedy. They just use they just use little enough of it that according to the
round serving size which is like a one packet's worth it's under five calories worth so they're
allowed to claim that it's zero. In fact it is. It is almost as bad as this regular sugar.
Don't use the powdered kind. Is it just like the percentage that like they have a large
percentage of nothing on top of the sugar. So it's not it's not even that large but yeah
some of it is just it's just got like bulk ingredients that just like bulk it up and
don't add anything. So what's the difference between the liquid and the sugar. Liquid doesn't
have the bulk. The stevia the stevia liquid is just like the extract from the plant which
you know. Okay. My my friend bought a stevia plant and you can actually like pluck a leaf
off a stevia plant and chew it and you can taste like a sweetness like as though it's
got sugar in it because it just has like a naturally sweet like fucking I don't know
oil or essence or something in it or whatever the fuck. Makes sense. You can just put stevia
leaves in your tea when you're fucking cooking your tea or whatever and it'll sweeten your
tea. Isn't that interesting. I'm interesting. I just thought that was interesting. Yeah that
people die in car crashes all the time. Speaking of things that are interesting. Let's get this
out of the way right now. In fact the Pokemon is out. Right. Okay. There you go. It's out.
Me and Major played it. It's you know. Here's my one minute run down. Wait. Wait. Are you
going to talk about it on content in like a week or two. I think. Okay. I'll close my ears for
now. I don't want to get spoiled on Nate's opinion. You know. Oh okay. Sure. Sure. I will
surely not go into full detail here but here in brief. It's pretty good. It's not like awful.
I kind of feel like I feel bad a little bit because I felt I feel too like I was kind of
swept up into like wow looks like this game is total shit for reasons I I don't know like there
are technical limitations that do annoy me as I play when I just like actually I mean one of the
annoying the only technical thing that's bothered me so far is that the like render distance of
enemies is of people in the field is very short and you can see them pop invisibly and it like
makes the world feel way less real which is unfortunate but that's that's a technical thing
that you know it's not like they wanted to do that so it's overall when you mean a technical
thing you mean they fucking couldn't do that on to on current hardware I mean there's no way they
like wanted to do that I'm assuming that was a concession for you know I mean it doesn't even
look that frame rates that like in graphically intensive it looks like a fucking ps3 game well
I mean what's the argument here they like they chose to do this for whatever engine to make the
game whatever engine they've designed was not optimized it's not a well optimized yeah okay
criticism for that but like all this all the oh my god it's like the worst game ever it's like it
doesn't bother me that much no it's not the worst game ever it's just technically unimpressive okay I
don't mean to lump your points in now with the the group anger that I was just like because like I
I have seen a few clips here and there I clicked on an arlo video for like five minutes because he
was talking about it and was like yeah what do you think what are you talking about models models
are the same okay there's controversy whatever it's pokemon well that's the worst like the game the
game just looked sort of like yeah yeah the game it looks like a ds game but on on a bigger screen
the field looks kind of neat the the only someone was telling me on twitter that the field is really
cool the the only thing about the game that I don't think is either a lateral move or shit is the
field um how do you what do you think about the field the fact that pokemon are physically
visible in the field and you run up and hit them I think is a is we have low expectations for pokemon
right but considering that it's a massive jump up it's a it's way better than it used to they already
did it in in this is this is like the closest this is the closest they've ever gotten to a pokemon
mmo and I've always wanted a pokemon mmo so they are they are wow wow we almost got what we wanted
cool um they already did they already did that in um Pikachu Eevee whatever the fuck well I'm
glad they beta tested it in that game for this one the real one I'm sure I'm talking about like
max raids and stuff that's the mmo thing uh because you you you get with friends and you
battle giant pokemon that's I don't care about that at all you haven't tried you don't know you
don't know the joys I've done a couple I mean what I hate organizing things with people I just want
to go do it so you get a bunch on my own so you can like specifically join up with your friends and
the people you want to play with I think so or do you just get randomly cued um you're cutting out
I think you can do either I believe is how it works I'm saying do you get randomly cued and grouped
up with random people or can you be like I want to raid with this guy like my friend I want to
raid with my friends um if you if you have friends uh and you say like a far far fetched possibility
but people can can join uh you quickly but other but but but strangers can join too so you can so
you can choose to do it with your friends if you want to yeah but like I mean okay that's all fine I
appreciate that you're in the past how they do it because I can't I can't go into the uh I can't
I can't cook curry with my friends it's very troublesome uh to to get sort of things I don't
care about at all I I only care about the like main playthrough of the game and then like the
larger meta game uh of like people the I don't do competitive fighting like at all but I am very
disturbed by the fact that so many pokemon and moves are removed which will impact like the
overall scene because I like watching false swipe gaming's review of you know how a pokemon did
through all the ages that's my main connection I haven't I have I have a lot to catch up on
but that guy makes a lot it makes a lot over there uh well there's a lot there's a lot of pokemon
to get through this is a lot of pokemon not as many as there would have been can't wait for 20 20
the year is 2036 and it comes out how was Eternatus competitively really I honestly
am very excited for that video one day I can't wait but uh okay in short this game is a pretty
okay game it's actually better than sun and moon I think I was gonna I was gonna say how to use the
compared to sun and moon the fact that there's no sun and moon all pokemon aren't in is such a
massive blow it's it's traumatic and it's very distressing they might extremely maybe that maybe
when they do the ultra maybe when they do ultra sword and shield they'll fix that I hope so I
because like it's obviously just because it's obviously like a fake a fake limit that they just
made out I heard I heard a rumor why the limit actually exists if anyone cares to hear okay so
like they originally wanted to import the models from like sun and moon and and you know update them
what not for for this game but they realized too late uh that like uh whatever they were using to
import models uh failed so they had to recreate the models from scratch to make them like identical
and uh they ran out of time and instead it wasn't gonna let them extend the deadlines so they had
to definitely definitely I am sympathetic I am sympathetic you know I don't know maybe that
yeah they're gonna they're gonna recreate they made every they made fucking 700 pokemon models
for the last gen and they're just like whoops can't use them gotta make them again no well
I mean as the as the only person here who does any 3d at all I can say that is that sounds patently
retarded to me even to someone with like baby level 3d like there's no like there there are it's like
saying oh I started making this game and I realized all these jpegs I made won't import into this
engine it's like it's a fucking jpeg there are 3d equivalents from that export it as an fbx and
import it into literally whatever you're using like nintendo is assumedly like game freak has
probably made their own proprietary game engine to make this game so like they would know what works
with it like it's their engine well okay there's no way you can't just export a model and import it
in just because like not only is is there just like standards for models like an fbx and shit like
that but like these models in the game have identical geometry and there's no way you can
recreate a model with literally identical geometry it can be similar you can have like
basically the same topology you know it's not gonna be identical it's like saying that was brought
up and arlo talked about in his video briefly about like the models are literally the same
okay like that seemed to be based on I didn't do further research that seemed to be based on
the fact that they put up like the mesh models of characters from like sun and moon versus in this
game and they visually look the same to us but I mean I didn't see any kind of like technical
explanation that proved that these weren't recreate well you can just look at them and see that they're
all identical wouldn't it make sense if they recreated they'd look really really similar
because they're the same no they would never they would never look identical all of them no
creating a 3d model it's not real life creating a 3d model is not like like you don't type in a
bunch of code and it just makes all the points you have to draw it basically in 3d it's like it's
like saying you draw like a like a picture on like a piece of paper and then you try to draw the
exact same thing it will never look exactly the same right exactly I don't believe you okay well
I've done it if you could just copy paste if you could just fucking copy paste the code to have it
identical that's the same thing as just importing it from this from the last generation like I can
believe guys if they're saying like the reason the models are they had to redo the models was like
they had to redo the texturing because they've went from like a qvga display on the 3ds to a 720p
display on the switch and the textures were too low resolution they had to redo them because they
did they redid the textures and they redid the shaders because the shaders and the textures
are higher resolution and look different that's one thing but they definitely from what it looks
like and we're gonna know soon because like now that the game's out people are going to be able to
start ripping all the models from it and do like point for point comparisons but like the models
the geometry like when people are talking about models we're usually talking about the geometry
not the textures and the mapping data the geometry looks completely identical as it was also identical
in let's go Pikachu to the 3ds models because Game Freak themselves had said we're going to use
these models long term that's why we made them as good as we did on the 3ds and why we're running
its performance issues because they're gonna be forward they're forward-facing and then a couple
years later uh we forgot how our own engine works we can't import standard models back into our engine
I agree I agree guys here's the thing like maybe I'd perhaps be willing to hear some of these excuses
but here's the thing it doesn't matter because I'm totally 100% with you I don't care what happened
to them in development I have no interest because the as the kind of person I am playing these games
my number one most important issue for me playing these games is this is top priority get all the
Pokemon okay I don't care that is great that is completely fine and if you were arguing that
point I'd be like fine but you're not arguing that point you're saying I don't believe you and
saying I don't believe you is different than saying I don't care so say I don't care from the start
and we can skip 20 minutes I still don't believe you that it's not possible to recreate a 3d model
no that is fucking impossible to do it identically if you overlay the points you know that you know
that artists make these models right not just like programmers like it's not just about like
punching numbers into a code look we've we can see what the models look we see the mesh why couldn't
you just use that image and like recreate it you can image it's not an it's not a 2d image it's a
3d model that was created by a fucking 3d render modeling artist or whatever the fuck you call him
like someone like like like someone created it someone someone made all the creative decisions
involved in like how does it move where the joints place what is the fucking geometry I'm just
considering all the like versions of these Pokemon that have existed throughout time I just have a
tough time different in every generation uh you slightly yeah I yeah I have no idea how you can
like you yeah you're talking to Tom is a person Tom is a 3d model man he's done a lot of this he
would know more than you why can't you just accept that you probably don't know what you're talking
about here I don't accept that I don't accept that okay well you're welcome to be overly ignorant
in a public space it's totally fine anyway anyway this was just a rumor I heard so yeah yeah yeah
it's fine it's fine let's let's let's let's move on let's move on to something else please
well anyway the point was I think this game is not as horrible as everybody was getting all
in a tizzy about but does have many flaws as you sure it's a perfectly serviceable Pokemon
experience I I expect a Pokemon I got Pokemon I'm pretty happy honestly like my standards for
Pokemon are quite low so like they didn't surprise me in a bad way and actually like they build the
only real everybody feels it's funny how you guys are you're saying exactly what I expected as though
like it's good I like I'm sorry I'm having fun but I am I am not upset that you're having fun
but like I still think everything they did is bad I don't I'm not arguing you're focusing on all
that stuff because you haven't played the game and experienced any of the good stuff so how would
you there's no basic like it's like you can you can say that like there's this is a fun game it's
another good quality Pokemon experience and also be like game freak were kind of cunts for lying
about all this shit yeah like those are two things like I can I can make the wrong decisions and they
have the right priorities and stuff I mean I agree with all of that like I I feel like
that this attempt like I don't think game freak were like oh we can't physically do it I'm sure
they they have the you know the capacity to copy files over I think this was just like Nintendo
and game freak probably realized that the amount of Pokemon there is is too big and they want to
like curb like Pokemon what do you call it creep creep that's exactly what Pokemon creep okay so
like like they just want to in the future they want to set a precedent that not all the Pokemon are
gonna be in every game yeah obviously everybody hates that everybody does not like that that is
a thing but they you know they're just go they're introducing it now and they're probably gonna
do it in the next game it's like we've got new Pokemon we want you to care about these new Pokemon
and um I don't know like I I mean they probably should have just done that from the start I mean
they probably would have saved them because like they they really should have I've been saying ever
since like third gen that they're making too many new Pokemon every generation I think adding
hundreds of new ones every generation was inevitably going to lead to this point I would
rather they add like 20 to 30 each gen and focus on building out features because that's more interesting
yeah I like there's already because every generation we just have functional replacements
we got the bird we got the two bugs we got the fire water I mean that's true but you know what I
heard as they're just do I absolutely agree we have so many Pokemon new Pokemon are fine and all
but like yeah we don't look it's it's the core development decisions that are impacting a
large part of this because another theory I heard as to like one of maybe the main reasons they
didn't do this because there are several Pokemon that have appeared in the game's code uh that
was like the gen one the gen seven starters something like that and uh some of the discussion
that I heard around was that because they didn't want to make specifically Gigantamaxed models
of these and like you know potentially all the Pokemon who aren't in the game it was that
development decision I mean again this is just one of the competing theories we don't know
Gigantamaxed models are just the same model well not all of them Gigantamaxed models are scaled up
not every Pokemon Gigantamaxes right like some some have a special Gigantamax and
others just Dynamax but Dynamax models are just the same it's like it's like a mega form is that
true I don't know if that's true or not I believe right mage you've done you've done the rates and
stuff you would know the difference right they I mean they're definitely they look the same they
get bigger right I mean when Pikachu doesn't have a Gigantamax model it's just a big Pikachu
isn't yeah well okay Gigantamax it well Pikachu actually does change I've only seen the one uh
the the special boy you get from from let's go Pikachu which becomes the fat Pikachu
yeah so it's like slightly different I mean the tail is definitely different all the all the Gigantamax
Gigamax I don't fucking know which ones wait all the ones I've done have just been the same we've
seen Dynamaxed and Gigantamaxed Gengar and Gigantamaxed Gengar is like the weird one with a big
mouth and then there's Dynamax Gengar who's just Gengar but big and he has like a red texture
overlaid on him yeah as far as I understand it yeah red like specular lighting or whatever right
I haven't seen much of this in the game in any case I I feel like it's it's most likely they're
going to try and like make it so that in the future they don't have to put all the Pokemon in all the
games and people won't be as upset next time because they've expressly stated that's their desire for
people to be prepared for that but you know what it feels like it feels like that decision went into
like like laxadaisical designs for these new Pokemon knowing that in the future some of them
they can if they're not popular they can just you know easily not you know continue to use them
some of these designs are very stupid looking they are the new ones I'm just you know I guess
on some level I can sort of understand why they want to set a precedent of not every
past Pokemon is in every new game I don't think that's completely ridiculous I'm just
concerned because I think that like gen one is going to get like super overrepresented
and it already is yeah it's that's going to continue it's just when you consider the full
context where there was much discussion about how in the last gen or whatever they hired a company
to future proof the series by making high quality models that could be reused and now we're learning
like the next generation they've dropped I mean I just think it's not surprising that many of us
would be frustrated really yep yeah um I mean yeah like like what the Tom was saying I would
rather just have a few new Pokemon ever Jenna and focus on the features we don't need fucking we don't
need impudence for fuck's sake hey no actually you know like he grew on me no I won't fucking hear it
it's unacceptable we don't need ice cue for fuck's sake yeah ice you can go but impudence and it's
evolution I like them I big grown on me no you don't understand you don't understand I had him I had him
from him when he was a small baby boy I got him in a max rate so I got him early on and he was a
small baby boy and now he's a big big buff boy and and he has like your maternal instincts are blinding
you to raw but you don't understand I don't accept I don't accept his validity he's he's like he's like
my two favorite types in one I can't hate him I can't hate the boy what is he's ghosts fairy no dark
fairy dark fairy yeah fine that's all fine and I can't I can't prove it but I feel like the dragon
quest monsters models have been like exactly the same since the ps2 era mm-hmm like look they look
like they haven't changed at all through all the games I'm not familiar with the series so I wouldn't
know but it's just because they got like really strong design sense like updating the models
wouldn't make much of a difference anyway but like I don't know it's a different it's a different
thing because it used to be in 2d yeah it doesn't matter I guess dragon quest used to be in 2d as
well I want to remind people of a story we're gonna get 4d pokemon look at this horse dude okay
apparently there's only like seven there's eight pokemon that have a gigantamax form
sounds about right eight of them here's the lit oh look at that they're all gen one and and four
okay charizard butterfree pikachu uh meowth eevee eevee corvanite dreadna and alchemy alchemy
this just reminds me of like the the pathetic display of the amount of a lowland pokemon forms that
were there's like 13 or something are there more galarian forms than there were no i feel like
there's more but not well maybe well let me well let's see there might be like nine there's wheezing
there's farfetched there's mr mime i was arguing with um kazi and munchie the other day that like
to me an alolan form is basically a new pokemon and i know and i'm willing i'm willing to give them
that um oh no i mean pathetic and the like the amounts that they didn't change from gen one like
there's so many gen one pokemon in sun and moon oh the alolan pokemon were like they were cool
and there was only like 10 of them forms ivo yeah uh like a lot of them are bad like alolan meowth
and is pretty shit i i love alolan puritan puritan with his wide face it's it's better but like
alolan meowth is literally just meowth with fucking a different expression there's a
fucking galarian meowth too oh yeah that was the whole door galarian meowth is better because it's
more different yeah i like it like fucking fucking uh snowy volpix is like beautiful like this yeah
yeah i wanted i just wanted more alolan forms i didn't want to see magic herb again i didn't
want to see goldine again goldine is back baby i hate her so much why is goldine back we don't
need goldine replace it was just like really fun it was like a red one when you watch the show and
every time misty would throw out goldine would just flap around on the ground she'd get pissed off
yeah goldine is shit okay what if they made like galarian uh goldine and seeking that were like
fucking awesome what if i would love it what if they were like fighting steel type and they were
just like super bad i would love it because it would be it would be new and it would be fresh
and it would be something it would be fucking anything yeah i mean that's kind of what they
did with farfetched and maybe meow yeah that's right because like every generation like we said
they have the three birds that's basically piggy but again but like different and like it's it's
fine and it's different sometimes the the the bird pokemon of the day is like lame but sometimes
it's really cool i like the galarian was pretty cool yeah i the talent thing was cool i like the
galarian far farfetched because he's like looking down at you like your scum it was funny i love
galarian farfetched man bobapedia doesn't have images up of all the different galarian forms
yet it's kind of disappointing you know what you know what call me when pokemon is like at a point
where goldine isn't there and then i'll buy it immediately of all the pokemon to keep i you
know it's i mean they don't keep miscellaneous forgotten fish actually they do keep some of them
from other like basculin he's in there what does he evolve into i don't know something else
it doesn't it just has like two then why the fuck is he in this game what do you want that
pokemon what do you mean why is he in the game just because he doesn't evolve a lot of pokemon
done sparse does anyone gonna use basculin does anyone want basculin what's basculin okay but
whether or not he's basically a magic problem not well okay okay the evolution true like scarmery's
good scarmery doesn't evolve but i mean that's just one piece of the puzzle here it's that it's a
basculin is uh i mean is basculin's not the most exciting pokemon no it's true
i'd say he's the most exciting pokemon well i've never seen anything that's pretty funny
he's better than goldine i get excited about how unexcited i am when i see basculin um i don't
know but at least basculin's got something going on with the red and green it's got the red and
blue forms sort of that don't have any meaningful difference between them whatsoever how exciting
okay i don't want to i don't want to go to bat too hard for basculin
even though we had that's the legendary banana banana if galarian basculin looks like this image
you just link give here that's in the show notes i would be fully on board or maybe evolved into
a basculin form eval fighting fighting water we need we need less less anthro less anthro pokemon
please i want all anthro and the end i want everyone to be my choke
that'd be good okay guys i want i've been wanting to say like uh this whole controversy with pokemon
and i like i'm not people aren't wrong um but uh what it reminds me of um is a little game called
fable and how it absolutely messed up initially at least from what i heard like it made so many
promises that it couldn't keep and people were really angry about it but me when i was when i was
little i didn't know anything about the controversies and i played fable for the first time and i loved
it it was such a good game and it still is and i i have it on my well i'll tell you why i'll i can
tell you why that happened it's because stiff that's a stiff and malin you uh peter peter malin you
he endorsed peter malin yeah pokemon and it was all downhill from there yeah um no peter peter
malin you right the the okay peter peter malin you the guy who made he made all these fucking games
and peter malin you is just like a chronic over promissor and he just hyped up the game and said
like how realistic it was going to be how many features it was going to have what a diversity
famous you can plant a seed and come back like years later and it'll grow into an actual tree
crazy shit like that shocking um so it was it was it was it wasn't that the game was bad
it was that it was overhyped and overpromised and the developer made all these promises
didn't keep it's basically the same it's the same thing that happened with no man sky
same thing that happened with spore um it's not that the game it's not that the game was like
necessarily horrible it's that it was supposed to be something different the developer set the bar
too high like you have to control your pr or you're fucked like you can make a nine out of 10
but if you promise an 11 out of 10 it's gonna be a two out of 10 in everyone's books because like
fuck you you lied to me yeah it's like i bought this game because i thought i could do x y and i
can only do right because like you're only gonna focus on what isn't there at that point because
it's like oh you hyped up and told me i could do this and now i can't do this so fuck you like
you're just you're just adding extra baggage to your game that doesn't need to be there that was
that was the case that's shit on the dl until you know it's gonna be and peter mollin you apparently
he'd just like he'll do this with every game that he makes so he'll promise the moon and then he'll
the game will come out and everyone will be like where's the fucking moon asshole and he'll be like
and then he'll go silent for a while and come be like hey guys fable two i'm so that was embarrassing
dog shit it was going to put fable three like this is where we're gonna really realize everything
that i said i was gonna do and ten times more but you know that all being the case that's all
even though like while it's being developed be like guys we fucking nailed it like we're fucking
nailing it it's everything i said i don't know why he's everything i said and more and then as soon
as it comes out ah it just not it fucked up a responsible game developer who has like any amount
of information on like how games are made and like what contemporary games can do like should never
have promised the things that peter mollin you promised in fable it's ridiculous to think that
your game would have those features but uh uh considering this game it's just the fact that
i know how pokemon is developed lately i.e. disappointingly and with tons of flaws and
just the whole world is talking about all these bad things about the game that are all bad but
slightly less than everybody i don't know seem to be expressing i just feel like there was so much
criticism that now that i'm playing it and i kind of feel like the promise that was given to me by
gamefreak was a new pokemon game it has you know dynamax that's it that's no they definitely
definitely did not over they definitely did not over promise with sword and shield it and that's
why i think i feel relatively satisfied my disappointment is just from the lack of evolution
the series has shown perfectly over a million billion years do you think that um uh like uh a
natural a backlash against the backlash is allowing you to enjoy pokemon whereas otherwise you would
be like yeah this is yeah but i mean you're enjoying it exactly as i think it doesn't make
just as much sense as someone being mad at fable for being over promised like is one valid and the
other isn't valid i think i'm not talking about i'm not talking about valid i'm just wondering like
do you think um the backlash like the overwhelming backlash against pokemon is making your mood
playing the game better than it would otherwise be at the start slightly yes because i was expecting
it to be so bad uh and it uh wasn't that i've never i've never assumed that pokemon is going to
like the children shield is going to be a bad game i just assumed it's going to be technically
unimpressive and not have my favorite pokemon which is all the outrage really has ever been
not and not do anything too new or interesting i mean the playthrough so far is straight up
better than sun and moon so like and i didn't expect that and so i'm just i'm you know happy
that that is the case it's it has many of the same flaws as sun and moon but it's slightly less
annoying moment by moment and there's like more gems which i'm happy to have back there's eight
instead of you know whatever the weird thing they were doing in elola and uh and yeah i don't know
i mean the everything about the pokemon not being in the game that haunts me i hate that but that's
end game that's after you beat the elite four and i haven't done that yet so it hasn't impacted
the experience yet so just my moment to moment playing is uh yeah i like i like the characters
and i like the story so far they're all just terrible i mean they're not bad it's not it's
nothing is there um is there an is there like a team skull like or like an edgy gladeon or whatever
his name is uh team yell and bd can you um can you can you ride can you ride on your pokemon
nope no sadly zero out of ten yeah sorry there's no following pokemon there's no i
they literally put that in in fucking go go let's go pikachu or whatever the what
what game am i talking about the one that had the let's go let's go oh i was right yeah they
literally had the ability to ride your pokemon and let's go pikachu and let's go evie and they and
they why why would they make a good feature and then they just throw it away i mean they did the
same thing with heart and they pulled it out so it has always been about i guess like adding great
features that improve the experience and then forgetting about them because they were the
gimmick of that one generation yeah yep i mean that that's the only thing they keep
is pikachu and that's it well i cannot believe that mega forms have just been dropped it is
beyond belief personally so much are they i never like mega forms so well neither did i
but they made it a main thing i was forced to accept them under protest and now they just remove
what are they just completely dropped like you cannot do them that's correct yeah are you sure
because you couldn't do them in alola until end game so like is it an end is it a thing maybe you
can access once you get to the end no i'm pretty sure like there's there's nothing in the game yeah
there's nothing in the game indicating that you would be able to link there's no no now it's all
about the like six pokemon that you can gigantamax look you can dynamax and there's a new mega there's
a new form of mega forms and it's just worse and there's less of it but you can dynamax like
literally any pokemon only some of them have fancy and this is talking to somebody who there's like
now godzilla mecha godzilla and mothra essentially in pokemon and even i'm like maybe this was not
the best use of your resources it's literally eight pokemon have a special gigantamax form these are
the things these are all six of the traumatized five of them are gen one five of them are gen one
three of them are gen what nine are we on nine now we you shouldn't even consider the dynamax
thing like like okay mega evolutions functioned as like a new evolutionary form these aren't
basically not like that at all it's just no they can get big i don't think you understand what a
mega form is because a gigantamax is way more similar to a mega than to a regular evolution
well i mean mega forms were nothing like a regular evolution they were just like a thing you could
activate in battle i'm aware of how they function in battle but they give you like a new form to
the pokemon and like new types and stuff shout out if every pokemon had a like specific
changed form if every pokemon had like a specifically changing form when they dynamax
or whatever like then it'd be like kind of like a new form but because only like eight of them
i mean what's butterfree's dynamax or it just gets really big wings and its body stays small
it's not that's nothing bro what are you talking about like literally what are you talking about
i'm i'm just trying to compare the the distinction between why i found mega forms to be like like
mawile mawile didn't have an evolution but it got a mega form that basically functioned like
sort of like it was an evolution in how it looks and how it fights and that stuff okay okay where
it doesn't mechanically function that way how is how is gigantamaxing different exactly let me
explain okay so like because no one is a new form yeah like okay let me talk go on then mega forms
so like they change the typing of the poke most most often as i don't remember if there's any that
don't change the typing uh sometimes they get new abilities as well and you know they get like a new
a new uh look to them like and so it's almost like a new evolution for them in in in a way
it's a temporary one but yeah whereas dynamaxing they just get big and stronger um but like with
the exception of those eight but even those eight that do look different they still have the same
abilities and typing and stuff they're just big so is there what's the what's the difference between
dynamaxing and gigantamaxing uh dynamaxing is like everyone gets big like literally any pokemon
can get big that's all yes i understand gigantamaxing they look slightly different when they get big
but it's but it's um like it's visual it's just visual it's only a visual difference as far as i
know i could be wrong but as far as i've observed it's just a visual thing this is the this is
the fucking worst i mean we could all agree it's shit it's it's dumb and whatever whatever it's
but i just i'm such an abused fan i hated megas i thought they were dumb i didn't want them but
you know what eventually i was like hey man we've moved on everybody we were doing megas now it's
time to accept it my argument for megas is that they add they do add some like strategy to like
like they do increase the fucking possibility space of like choices you have to make in battle
and i think they're defensible in that way so gigantamaxing it's like that it's like megas but
they don't do that well imagine gigantamaxing and pokemon showdown it just fills the screen you
can't see them anymore it does make a difference it's basically just you just power up one pokemon
for three turns that's yeah that's the okay that's it yeah so i guess i get i get i get that like
yeah like dynamaxing and gigantamaxing um um is uh you you've got to choose when to do it so it's
it's like a mix between a z move it's like a mix between a z move and a mega form
basically yes that's true that's that's true uh do i have to have an item do i need to be holding
an item to do that nope i mean technically but you get it in the game like in a cutscene so like
you don't you don't even know you have it yeah it's not something the pokemon has to be holding
in place of like a leftovers or a no no no no okay what were you saying gabby you were saying
something now it's just like reminiscing on on my favorite gimmick my favorite gimmick of the
fucking pokemon contests which which allowed um like pokemon that are not fit for battle
to still have a role in in the game and you could like you could get a tiny cute thing
and if it knows some cute moves you can win the cute contest and you can get a ribbon
i miss those that's true are they existed i never liked them i thought they were bullshit
wait i'm glad they're dead i have an idea and i don't know i don't know if this is like a good
or a bad thing but what if literally the point of dynamaxing i don't even want to say dynamaxing
and gigantamaxing because they're literally the same thing yeah what if what if the what if the
point of dynamaxing is that it is pointless and a a like like non-feature or like like a what if
we made a bad game on purpose guys what if what if the point is that it is like a stupid throwaway
thing that did not require a lot of thought or effort to incorporate into the game specifically
because they intend for it to be a throwaway feature that is like specific to this generation
and will never be used again and they're like wait we we worked so hard we made all these like we
put a lot of energy and time and resources into building these new features for these old games
and then we just even though they were good we just threw them away so we know we're gonna
just throw away whatever new features we make for the next game so why don't we just make it some
bullshit i mean i wouldn't blame them for thinking that way it's what's happening well i would almost
not blame them except that obviously it's like they're so close so close to the revelation that
maybe they shouldn't fucking make a good make good features and throw them away but they come to the
opposite conclusions like well let's just make our features worse so that it's not bad when we throw
them away i'm pretty sure they just got inspired by pokemon go when it's success
what the fuck are you fucking high what are you talking about like like like the the raids the
the pokemon are just real big yeah that could fucking be it that could actually be the reason
like people who play pokemon go they used to sing big pokemon we should put that in the new game
that's silly i see and then you go up with friends and you get battle the giant pokemon
i don't have any fucking friends mage okay i'm not getting the fucking game sorry it's fine
you don't have to i i literally don't mind people not getting the game maybe you know what maybe it's
maybe at some point i will get the game i'm not taking an ideological stance on like do not buy
this game i don't care that much uh but i i don't feel like spending the $60 right well now be the
time where people go as such as myself and seek out those mythical fan games that i've heard so much
about that they say it's time i mean yeah i mean to i just have been too lazy yeah i don't know
some some good some good stuff out there just use the fan game known as your imagination
i have to go take an angry piss okay i have one small gripe with the game i just very tell you
one uh among all the things that people are saying like um i've beaten five gyms so far
and like the choices for clothes you can buy is a bismuth so far with at least like sun and moon
you had like like very themed sort of shops throughout the town like oh there's like the
cute shop and then there's like the sporty shop and then there's like the the hipster shop or
something like that for clothes well this one is like do you want this sporty look or that sporty
look and i'm like where are my cute frilly dresses god damn it this is an athletic game for athletes
such as myself off i don't want to dress you know mage on this subject though i think that just
touches on kind of one larger point this is this is something people have said in general about it
and i wonder if you wait wait wait the looks are sporty i thought this was like in scotland i thought
you were going to be wearing like winter coats and stuff and mittens not really no like so far
all the gloves that are available uh look very sporty biker like like not biker but like biking
that's so lame gloves i know so far i've only beaten five gyms so i don't know maybe i'll be
proven wrong after the next gym and i'll get my frilly dress and i'll be happy but so far
like i had to i had to beat so much of the game and i still don't have my cute dress i am very
disappointed well okay so the issue i feel the boys wear kilts i i don't know i mean that's in there
i don't know uh so the this issue of like not a lot of clothes fair okay perhaps this touches
just into the larger issue that kind of touches all these issues that's like like okay on the this
is on the switch right this is like a console game i don't game for a small company whatever
but like when you just compare when you compare i mean i don't i don't know how many
fucking development staffers they have those those things matter but whatever like when you just
compare the other games that are like on the system i mean it's not hard to just be like wow this
game is like you know developed by babies compared to some of the other games that are on there and
then it's just it's reasonable to be like this is like the most profitable franchise in the
fucking world ever okay okay that that's not fair because why why is that not fair uh because uh
because the small development team game for a bigger team hire more people why doesn't get
that much money as people assume it does that's what no issues i okay but but mage mage that even
even if that's true the pokemon company does so why is a pokemon company not like hey game freak
here's some money i don't know why they don't do it i don't know okay i don't know which of these
companies is to blame but some combination of these companies should have said to themselves
hmm we have probably too few staff members i agree i agree i just don't i don't like people
saying like oh they have millions and millions of dollars they do though mage they do they literally
do well game freak is co-owner of the pokemon company someone at some point in the chain failed
to allot the necessary resources to fucking make i mean we can all agree on that they they fucking know
they don't need to though people still buy the game and they sing as praises and they defend it and
that's just how it will always be not me uh well i i do wish they would improve well i mean it's
really funny to compare this to like uh like what is it like xeno blade chronicles or some of those
games that just i mean like they look a million times better dragon quest and the render distance
is more than like 20 feet and you know i think things of this nature i still say even town looks
better than than pokemon i believe that aren't uh aren't they coming out with like a another pokemon
mobile app that they're gonna make millions upon billions of dollars already didn't they the uh
what is it like pokemon masters i think yeah masters which is by the way not a good game don't
play it it sucks i i've played it well i got my ham doom i stopped playing there you go
eight pokemon go eight billion can gigantamax
well not gengar is not one of them at least they cut half so it's not less than one percent
not according to bulbopedia well then it's wrong we've seen it's didn't we see it's you literally
saw the giant gengar that's stuck in the ground with its mouth open i mean is do you think is
bulbopedia just not up to date probably it's possible some information is let me all right well
let me let me let me check i mean and and i'm not sure if it was in bulbopedia but in one of those
pokemon uh sites it said like you can only get galarian ponita in pokemon sword which is not
true you can get it only in shield so you know yeah see i feel like there's been some things like that
that are maybe just straight up like incomplete or inaccurate that wait and we'll have a rosier
picture to a degree i don't know the things i'm complaining about but you know oh no okay bulb
i'm sorry bulbapedia is wrong okay the the list is still not that impressive but i'm counting one
two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen
seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twenty one twenty two twenty three twenty four twenty five
twenty six twenty six pokemon have gigantic max four so that's something and let me count
how many of those are not new pokemon or first gen um zero yes it's literally none yes literally
every single one is either a gen one pokemon or a um really but the cake pokemon is new and i know
that's a new one that's what i said either gen one or a new pokemon here's the here's the here's the
list gengar charizard meowth eevee pikachu butterfree corvanite alcremie dredna garb oh wait no garbador
garbador is the one exception because he's the trash man yeah he's the daru daruladon daruladon
hatterine copper raja kingler sent to scorch oh it met oh and mel metal of course everyone's
favorite fucking mel metal uh oh right that legendary from yeah so okay so two are not of the
appleton gamers appleton grim snarl flapple sanaconda uh col colosal orbital toxic
toxicity terrible name by the way snorlax lapriss machamp what the fuck is with meowth who likes
meowth that is meowth turns into long cat bro long cat yeah yeah i guess it does bro
skinny is objectively better than i want i'm so disappointed they don't have skinny
meh i'm not like shitty hey
fuck you know you oh that's life baby read them in weep so all right that's that's that's the
spread this has been an hour of pokemon discussion this number this number actually makes it even
makes the uh the gen one bias like even worse and even more agree well do you not think going
forward it's going to be gen one plus whatever we made for this game and that's going to be the
focus like that seems like definitely sure fire away to make the box yes and then every and then
each one of those features that only include so don't get attached to any new pokemon and sword
and shield because they will be gone next yeah the next next generation all the special features
none of them will get none of them will get anything but luckily it's shit and i won't miss
gigantamaxing so i feel blessed luckily we made the features bad on purpose so you won't miss them
when they're gone wouldn't it be interesting if they made a game that actually had like a huge
amount of scope for some console like the switch i'm like you could go to all the regions in each
region had its gimmick but it only worked in that region that would be cool i mean that could happen
you know it it won't fucking happen it won't happen but someone could make that potentially
oh 100 it could be done pixel on minecraft oh yeah that's right page you're gonna have
page giant imagine to to to fucking pixel mon not not yet but i'm sure you already kind of have
that with pokemons having various sizes i suppose oh yeah you know we can gigantamax our uh or you
know our big our boofalons and we can also min max them by making them so very small you can't
even see them down there so really minimize minimize we've got the we've got the gutch coming in going
on the peace be minecraft server so here you go what happens if a gigantamaxed muck uses minimize
he just turned back to regularity that's a fascinating question it's a small but red
we'll see that happen i don't know like i because well i mean just when you're dynamaxed or whatever
like your moves change so i wonder if you don't have access to minimize when that happens to like
change the thought of it ahead of time they may have they may well have man imagine if
fucking mucks in real life could minimize then we wouldn't have so much pollution oh that's how
we get rid of pollution we just you know um we sent in ties tm minimize sentinize the the
landfills it turns into little pokemon we have to just bombard landfills with radiation in hopes
that they evolve into muck and don't do more damage to the environment we need we need to go there
and wheezing because yeah we do oh that's true that's what we really need yeah yeah that's um it
which is basically carbon tax the pokemon i feel i feel like i feel like um like this gen
has has something to say about about like global warming because of like that stupid penguin
and then like the dead corsela and uh the wheezing well hang on you know i heard that was a little
bit of fake news about that corsela wasn't that like a isn't bleached coral just like a natural thing
or was i wrong is that it's ghost type i yeah i could be wrong so what what's this what's the
relevant implications it's dead yeah uh there's a variant that's a ghost oh maybe okay maybe i
kind of need a little more than that if the point is just the the coral's dying okay cool got it
but uh i don't know yeah like i i i could be wrong i don't mind being wrong i i'm just if i may i
would like if i may i would like to change the subject permanently please okay let's do it and uh
and uh to elia czar please at the beginning as soon as we start talking about pokemon put on screen
click that click this timestamp to skip from the pokemon discussion to the politics discussion
yes yeah change my mind let's go back to pokemon i want to follow up on on the thing i was i was
looking into yeah or talking about like a labor and general election in the uk please uh the bbc
website has this little thing the the manifestos aren't out yet which is annoying this i really
want to read up and see what the fuck they're actually talking about but the things they've
all been saying on their campaigns have been like tallied up and and put into like little a little
drop down menu so you click on what party and it will tell you like based on health and economy
and education like what their policies have been like spoken okay and i was looking around and you
know uh labor seems to be the one for me um conservatives are you know i policy i'm not
really going to talk about but the one thing i wanted to mention is that i checked out the brexit
party and obviously they are like generally not for me but there was one thing that really annoyed me
yeah it's that break the brexit party want to abolish the first pass the post voting system
and implement majority or you know the the better alternative the one that everyone wants that
wouldn't make democracy a lot more fairer okay so like so like and labor and conservatives the most
likely parties to win don't promise that at all so it's just sort of reinforces the idea that the
better voting system is not encouraged by the parties who win all the time because they know
that if they allow that to happen they would stop being in power and it would stop being a two-party
system and i hate the idea that if i want that fucking thing i need to vote brexit party i i'm
not going to do that it sucks you know who want you know who wants voting reform
bernie sanders but also yang and i think a couple of the other democrats in i mean okay like in
america we vote for a congressman obviously like separately from the executive branch and stuff
whereas okay actually to be fair i don't actually know how it works who are you you in english you
vote for the party you want right and then they get x number of representatives in the parliament
is that there's there's the country is split up into constituencies and you have members of parliament
people who stand to become members of parliament and you vote for them in your local area they get
elected and then they represent the the party that part of okay so that's pretty much like it works
it's the same okay yeah i'm sorry i just missed so are you voting for a person are you voting for
a party you're voting for a person okay um and who rep who is part of a party yes okay got it got it
i assume it's the same in the the u.s but with senators or something like that yeah the senate
and uh the house representatives someone okay this guy um i was talking about lula the the
brazilian uh former president who uh got uh who was put in jail on like a lot of people
say they were trumped up charges of corruption we got it again that we're taking down the brazilians
these were trumped up charges he this is how i get my legacy like the supreme court voted that
that was that he shouldn't he doesn't have to be in jail anymore um so he's out and uh bernie's happy
about it and this uh this guy tom tom thanks tom tom for this heads up let me fucking read he said
he he he messaged me on discord like tom but there's two of them he said to tell me about like dude uh
hell yeah lula uh and he said i think this is impossible for me to try this is just too funny
i had to read it i think it's impossible for me to translate this to you but lula is not only cool
because of what he represents he is absolute peak commie swagger he got a new girlfriend while in
jail and on one of his first videos out of jail he said quote i am this is a translation i am a
74 year old man with the energy of a 30 year old and the hard on of a 20 year old i want to fight
um pretty cool if true i mean you know death to commies but that's pretty funny
that's funny it's a funny joke um okay so that's all i have to say about politics other than that
it depressed congratulations lulu i loved your appearance in final fantasy 10 it was a great
uh it was a great time yeah so who you voted for hippo you voted you voted in labor um well
my constituency is just based on the name of the party i feel like labor is probably the one for me
but that's really all we need to know at the end of the day that's not what i that's the opposite of
what i was gonna say i mean yeah labor is jeremy corbin is seems like in a many ways a bernie sanders
sort of guy which is why everyone hates him yeah uh that's my impression they don't want to him
they don't want him to give money to people who need it no so what the fuck yeah so uh i'm
probably voting for him hopefully like the the the moment my constituency is conservative but
it's only by a small number of people so hopefully that can be switched we can fucking we can really
don't i really i really have doubts for like labor having a large enough majority to make
a serious like difference that they can actually implement the policies that they want to yeah
like it no matter what happens everyone is still like split in the country nobody's
really talking and and and you know caring about each other and each other's problems i went to
i went to tasty burger uh with kazi and munchie on friday or i don't know whenever i went i went
the other day and uh i went and i got the i was drinking my i was drinking my bullshit piss water
light beers low carb ha ha i was i drank i was drinking at the bar and there was this guy this
guy next to me was talking to the bartender and i realized they were talking about politics
and this guy next to me he was like he was like a he was a good boy bernie bro and i and i my
heart bled for him he was talking to the bartender and the bartender was just like the bartender
was arguing for why we were for why we should keep trump in office and his argument was like
politicians all lie the government is corrupt and trump is the worst of them all he's the biggest
liar and the most corrupt of them all but like that's good because it'll expose the bad things
that was his argument and he like i mean he's he's steadfastly stood by it he would not be
just waited from this government is totally evil then i suppose putting an incompetent at the
head of it as a way of dismantling it is not the craziest idea as opposed to someone who's it
good right at perpetuating that you're correct you're correct nate accelerationists are psychotic
freaks and shouldn't be allowed to vote well his argument supposed to be that because trump is
outside of like the system that his the reason for his corruption is for exposing the bullshit
or just that he's operating for his own gain and not the the system's gain so therefore
like his motives are different no i just wanted to think of a way to say trump is all right i think
he didn't i mean maybe if i'd gotten more of a more of his take he might have elaborated but
all i heard him say was that like trump is it seemed to be the idea that trump is the most corrupt
and the worst and therefore like having him in power will mobilize people against the government
i think me or or will like expose or will will like it was me my impression is that it's basically
uh let's make things let's just make things as worse as they can be things if like they'll make
things really bad like things are bad now but they can really bad and then people will have to get
angry and do something about it or yeah it's like it's it's like i kind of see where he's coming from
but it's just it doesn't make sense because when obama was in office all of the you know the other
side were like trying to get rid of him the whole time here's my question and they didn't do anything
here's here's my question is like well okay if you think that trump being a thing is gonna like be so
bad and so upsetting that it will inspire like a counter movement then like okay so here like
for example we are we somewhat like an opposing party comes along as like hey let's swing the
pendulum the other way and do something different why would you then be like nah though keep trump
like shouldn't you be in favor of the counter movement well i think i think the the again i'm
just putting words in this guy's mouth obviously but if you if you think the entire system needs to
be torn down like a party solution obviously is not going to fix anything like this guy clearly
wants like violent action i guess that's true um i don't want violent action personally i don't know
about but he might just want i mean this based on the little detail we have it sounds like he
probably wants smaller government if i had to guess this guy's desires for how the world should be
maybe violent actions putting too many words but clearly he wants a solution that's not government
based because it sounds like the entire system is not he has no faith in it anymore yeah i guess so
yeah like it's like even if trump like being the president people aren't gonna think you know
because trump was a bad president therefore presidents are like a bad idea and then if the
democrat comes in next they're not going to be thinking that for them because they're a different
person yeah if it's not it's not going to dismantle anything i mean if any like the the
attitude is bad because it like people hate trump so much that they'll fucking be happy with some
fucking idiot like joe biden just because he's not trump and it's very distressing very depressing
i'm very upset i can't even think straight uh i can't abide by that i just found out that devolve
patrick's apparently gonna run now too yeah that's right our old governor of massachusetts are more
people declaring oh yeah yeah hurry any day now man any day now no oh yeah oh yeah it's her turn ben
and i want to have you mansplain her out of the race stop it's too late the fucking debates are
already going are you kidding me well i guess i guess the crackpot theory right now with devolve
patrick is that because these friends with obama he's gonna have obama basically backstab biden
and like come out and support devolve because devolve patrick was basically died obama here in
massachusetts he like had basically the exact same kind of like leanings you know what you know what
him as obama too to have to have obama withdraw his support from biden and back someone else and
split up biden's constituency sounds wonderful so a change i take back everything i said i love
you devolve patrick thank you for running thank you for doing this are you at all concerned that
devolve patrick could theoretically be worse than biden in some way that i don't um well i mean i
have no i mean okay fair enough but probably not i mean probably not if he's if he's he's probably
just he's probably similar he's probably similar to biden he's probably similar to biden if obama
is gonna back him um but also like not senile and also just we gotta split that voting block
by the way just slightly here um uh gib on the on the subject of you uh you know in your your
discussion of labor i was just curious because i had heard recently everybody's favorite political
commentator sargon i heard him say the other day that labor expects to take a some some some
serious hits something like losing many many of their boys and i have no idea i don't know
british politics at all but i'm wondering if you are is that is that do you know of this is this
something happening or is it foolishness what do you mean hits like i mean like half of them will
be voted out of office in the upcoming election is what is what the fear was sargon would say that
i mean i haven't heard that i've been watching mostly bbc news and this liberal media back at it
again like well bbc is generally impartial but they they do skew to the left um but uh i think
that the people have been like saying that labor has like thrown out so many big numbers like i'm
going to do this and this and this and all this money is going to come from uh taxing the giant
corporations and the super wealthy and it's like yeah but if you do that the amazon and google will
leave you can't you can't expect them to actually give the money um so it's like oh how could you
possibly like he said the other day um by 2030 we're going to have superfast fiber optic broadband
cables uh uh like owned by the the people rather than a company and it's going to be called british
broadband and we're going to give it to the the entire country and it's like that's going to cost
a lot of money um but it would be nice but like people were like hmm how are you going to do that
it's like i don't know money i don't know economics or like what the amount of money we
have at the moment is in order to spend on that and of course brexit is going to change things like
with trade deals and all that stuff so yeah i don't actually know much about how how feasible
most of these things that are being said by any party are all i do know is that the conservatives
have been running the country for a long time like a decade and they fucked it up in many many
ways and i don't like them so any change is good yeah labor is pretty pretty it's pretty good
pretty good to me thanks man thanks for that thanks for making me feel a little better
well anyone else got away in elizar feel free to drop a timestamp here to skip the
politics discussion yeah we it's like that's a good show everybody we touch on everything everyone
wants to hear about oh wait no wait one one last little small topic um i went to uh the royal
albert hall a few days ago a big place really big uh very cool um i was up in the gallery uh and i
was seeing snarky puppy the jazz oh you showed me that my favorite streamer yes my favorite
streamer on twitch.tv yes uh she was streaming live in the royal albert hall uh no like the jazz
fusion prog rock cool guy band full of uh you got the the three piece brass uh virtuosos and and
like the super like percussion maniacs and the and the drummer he was insane and the they were all
going nuts playing their music and it was really fun and i was up in the very very top and it was
like 20 pounds for that ticket it was a standing ticket and if you see pictures of the royal
albert hall you can see you know there's chairs and there's boxes and stuff but right at the top
there's like this like big open space of a ring but just like a like a a ledge you just lean on
and it was so cool damn that's a big ass zone i'm looking at in this place uh here posting an image
over in the chat over here uh it's it's like if if if anybody has an opportunity to go to a place
that has like a standing room at the top i don't know how many places have that but i really actually
prefer it to having a seat because when you have a seat it's like a cinema you can't you can't like
really your legs are stuck you don't have anywhere to actually put your drink without kicking it if
there's no cup holder um and every time somebody anywhere near you needs to go to the bathroom you
have to stand up and shuffle through but when you're up at the top you're just sort of standing you're
like you're you're like on the balcony basically just looking at looking down you can walk around
there's bars right behind us you could just go and get a drink and these guys are like a they're
like a jammin ass fun boy kind of get up on your feet and move a little bit kind of group yeah so
you know what he's sitting down for this bullshit yeah they they were grooving they had a big old
bit where um they were having a the half the Royal Albert Hall was clapping three four and the other
half was clapping four four it was like drum beats it was like whoa yeah clapping it was like clapping
and tapping my feet and moving my head like yeah this is really fucking good i love snarky puppy
i've been to some concerts where like you're sitting down and it i feel bad for the performers
because sitting down and watching feels like i mean i bought my dad tickets for his birthday
wants to um uh oh shit what is it uh fleetwood mac we saw fleetwood mac once and oh yeah it was uh it
was cool and all that but uh like we were sitting down in the area and i just felt bad like i wasn't
being into the performance enough even though it was totally sick and uh it was awesome um i forget
the the guitarist but he's a fucking shred master i only know albert hall because i heard a like
world war two like fight song one time that goes like hitler has only got one ball the other is in
the albert hall his mother the dirty bugger cut it off him when he was small why i don't remember
where i heard that that that is a that is a fun like i think it's a football chant it's just or
why would you chant about hitler at football i mean he's not he did it during world war two
or something it's a sing it's a sing song thing that like that like melody would be sung at a
football show can you just like insert anyone in place of hitler it's the sort of it's the sort
of thing i heard when i was a kid in in in the playground like you know edgy kid would say about
hitler has only got one ball he's with the batman the christmas uh what was it uh just uh yeah um
batmobile lost a wheel and a joker got away yeah very edgy very edgy yeah imagine the joker
winning that's making fun of hitler was a really fun past time for for young school boys now we
take it for some reason now i've made that hobby into my career and let me tell you it's going great
we didn't really do that as in america growing up because we didn't need to have kicked his ass we
weren't we weren't we weren't concerned about the whole hitler question it was pretty much a settled
question i'd say uh yeah you know what another grounded tread uh just to finish the the the
story i i put like a snippet of that on instagram oh and it was like really fucking sick and like oh
yeah people are gonna love see like people are gonna be impressed that i like this kind of music
put it on instagram uh and it got muted within a few hours well because i copyright yeah but like
it was a live performance but i think the reason was was they were they were recording it and
um they said the guys said at the end uh this recording was actually like a live album so you
know you're all gonna be in it and it's like oh i'm gonna be in a live album what if i yelled
really loud the whole time so i get like a little what if i what if i yelled really loud onto the
album uh patreon.com slash tpcrastinators oh that'd be good is it tpcrastinators it's the
procrastinators for the procrastinators whoops whoops that's what i said oh no those assholes
at tpcrastinators are gonna see a spike damn it i think like that night they made a mix of it and
then it got copyrighted and it got fucked so that sucks i don't like that that happened so quickly
but uh whatever yeah that's too bad i mean just as a competing theory perhaps i mean that okay that
all makes sense but like some events like this they just say no recording allowed even if they're
not making they they didn't have anything like that up there and i don't know but it was it was
i only recorded right at the end it was muted by instagram right not by um like this company or
yeah yeah just well i it i didn't get like an email saying it'd just been muted it was just
this video has no sound like a few hours later it's like oh i have such a strong sense of deja vu
about this conversation had happened but i know it couldn't have happened but my god deja vu
major dream powers are getting out of control they're bleeding into the waking world we're
seeing the future no that's the thing like it's always i always get the sense of deja vu only
after it starts happening i'm like well what good is that if i can't even tell if it's gonna
happen in the future because deja vu isn't real it's an illusion it's uh just a minor trick on
itself you know i mean i did talk i may have talked a while ago about a similar thing where
um i had films uh like a record player playing a led zeppelin song and i got muted i don't know
why i would have talked about that though maybe because like it sounds very similar to the point
of all like what nate was saying as well is also very similar to it's your brain it's tricking
itself i hate my brain it does shit don't we all uh time to time to take that that brain out behind
the the the bike shifts and kill it speaking of killing it uh let's get to the voicemails what do
you say las wait wait wait i got a i got a funny i got a funny story so i believe it or not i'm
going to be on uh i don't believe it i'm gonna be on the next or it'll be the it'll be tomorrow
after this episode release of this saturday this upcoming saturday i'm gonna be uh me and mumke
jones are gonna do an is it kino uh on on twitch is that all i guess he'll be streaming it and
and florian i i guess is it kino is a twitch show now um i guess i think most of the stuff is twitch
yeah so he they they those two invited me to do uh what will you be reviewing uh uh well they asked
me if there were any underrated or unknown movies and and i was very excited i immediately was like
turbo kid have you guys seen turbo kid i heard i know what i heard about turbo kid is fucking
awesome okay turbo kid is sick as fuck so i'm wicked stoked to expose turbo kid uh to an audience
it's really good uh so i guess me and mumke and florian aka game squad i guess he'll be streaming
it i'll be streaming it on my twitch as well and i think it'll probably be like one or two p.m
on saturday so i don't know twitch.tv slash st comics whoo um and also everyone should watch
turbo kid it's really fucking cool movie it's like a see it's like a low it's like a low budget um
like canadian it's sort of like a mad max kind of thing but like the protagonist is like a
kid who finds like a magic glove that makes him into a superhero is it quite graphic it is like
comedically graphic like there are like jesus is going to like this there are like blood and
guts but it's like it's kind of silly i think i remember uh red letter media giving it a favorable
review back in the day if i wait really did red letter media review turbo kid i believe it might
have been like a wrap up or i know they talked about the sequel not the sequel but like the next
movie that those guys did in like their 2018 wrap up i'm gonna google it which was i think the summer
of 84 was the next one they did i can't remember okay yeah here we go we're half in the bag episode
95 the visit and turbo kid i must have watched this uh in 2015 holy shit i'm fucking old
muck yeah dude a year in the past that i remember it this is four years ago and i've been watching
the whole time you know that's like t-bap era that we're getting to this point where like i'm
starting to be like oh yeah that analysis video i just watched was really good let's check when it
came out 2011 dude yeah yeah yeah no i feel the same way like i i still think of like um i still
feel like all the controversy about like the ghostbusters remake as like recent controversy it
was like three fucking years ago yeah that's yeah that's an ancient yeah so i know as we get older
time begins to accelerate our perception of time gets faster and we're gonna be 40 tomorrow
it's very distressing it's the worst we most of us are like rounding the corner 30 if not 30
already i'll be 30 in uh you know seven eight months or so that's the end of my life it's a
fate worse than death let me tell you i i believe you i believe you you're you're officially entering
the not cool period because like if you do something before you're 18 you're a prodigy if you do
something like in your 20s you're pretty cool anything from 30 to 60 it's like well of course
you're an adult it's just you're normal you're just you're at the age where you should be doing
things but then it swings back around if you're still like doing cool shit at 60 plus then you're
a badass old person so prepare for three decades of like nothing you do is anything other than
expectation and three decades of everyone just rolling your eyes at your bullshit and then of
course take the fact that you're a white cis male and then add that and it's just like so it's just
like it's a real you'll be lucky if you don't get the fucking guillotine the next 30 years
yeah by the by the time i'm an old white man old white men will be illegal and i'll be killed
immediately you know i was just saying the other day gib that you reminded me of a man who's
simultaneously 15 and 75 or something like that uh in the best way yikes wait wait i remind you of
that you you young at heart old of old of skeleton body riddle of bone and weak of mind
is the boomer mantra is that a fucking t-shirt i hear is that a fucking t-shirt i smell that's
good oh how about like a like a yes i'm a boomer and then it's like and then on the back it just
says big bold words brittle of bone weak or ask you about how i'm a boomer maybe with like the
word like censored because it's a bad or like like that sonic meme where it's like the letters
vertically and it's supposed to spell out an acronym it's like yes i'm a boomer brittle of
bone weak of mind all the other letters are empty something one of these will work yeah get back
to us artistic designer people with but wait wait what do you actually mean though i don't know you
just simultaneously you have the air of someone who's both 13 and 75 at the same time you just
restate it but what does that mean it's because you're explain yourself i don't know because you
have like a a slow gentlemanly disposition about you like an old man but also i don't know you are
a small because i like minecraft and i'm stupid uh yeah you're a 15 year old that talks to the
british accent so you must be refined that's definitely that's definitely an advantage in my
in my favor uh i i do i do enjoy being stupid and young at heart that is my favorite thing to be
so i'm glad that that comes across but also being smart being smart and being smart is really good
you talk like a man of a wizened uh disposition i guess i hope when i am 75 i still seem like
that that's my goal you'll be full uh hey fellow kids check out my skateboard no i'll i'll i'll be
playing the the hot new game minecraft patch minecraft 2 will finally be 50 years from now
what if everything was a sphere in minecraft 2 instead mine's mine's fear we finally have the
technology to make rounded corners yeah instead of crafting you sphere things
all right let's let's get to these voicemails over here it's we can't delay the inevitable
any longer um all right link down below people speak pipe you know what to do leave us quality
voicemails uh we'll we'll be kicked to the curb if it's some bullshit uh but we've got our first
boy up here uh it's just statistics uh let's let's hear what manner of statistics he has for us
okay go so nate definitely has something going on when he talks about the idea of one night is
and that being a big problem because let's say you have a question on someone and you wait
like a month to ask them out or whatever that's a month so you could have asked out a hundred other
girls right so what i did as a social experiment as a meme that's what i say but you know obviously it's
is i well when one week i asked out every single girl i had an interest in i socialized for like
one minute and then asked no are you single kind of thing and i got 20 rejections and four yeses
in one week and statistically there you go eventually they'll say yes you know if you're
on like a stupid like whiny bitch like oh please be my girlfriend i'm so sad that's not gonna work
if you just act like a human being and you're just being cool then eventually people will see it
people will think you're funny you know i i didn't take rejections like a big deal i was like hey
where's the shot and i like made flirty jokes because that's what funny people do and that's
all you have to do all yeah to get a girlfriend is this make yourself available and like tell
everyone i don't i don't know fuck maybe this isn't a good advice i don't know see there you
pretty good advice probably and i wait so this guy got four yeses does this guy have four girlfriends
now he's spinning plates like a good man should he sure indeed he should be these are not i don't
think they're full-fledged girlfriends i think he got four like sure i'd like to hang out yeah
something like that yeah yeah wait well that's not fucking worth anything just because they
say yes they're single i don't think he's saying that like i did it i bagged a girlfriend from nothing
i think he's saying that like he's crossed the threshold of being too afraid to even make that
step and now it's not a big deal anymore so i can go out and do it exactly exactly this way
it's making progress okay i'm just a little confused that like the goal of this exercise
was not to like ask someone to be your girlfriend or even to ask for a date but just to ask no are
you single no no no what he said was that he asked he was talking to a bunch of girls he asked 20
girls or whatever and most of them were taken but four of them said they were single and so he
proceeded to ask them out and they all rejected him that's what he's saying what he's saying oh
with this method no no he said he got 20 rejections and four yeses i thought the rejections
were four being single should we play it again real quick just to clarify can we play can we hear
that part again as i rewind this we're we're gonna skip okay just i have to play the beginning part
but just give it a second we'll get to the thing you can cut this out ellie is our the beginning
part if you want and i got 20 rejections and four yeses in one week and statistics okay that
he asked them out got 20 rejections but four yeses four people he asked out said if he would
have continued i think he wouldn't like what he said was like um and they can turn into girlfriends
or they can turn into like maybe he hasn't he's not going out yeah yeah you don't you don't start
with a girlfriend instantly you go out a few times okay but he got four he asked them out and he got
four yeses correct correct that's like four date equivalents four dates yeah something like that
yeah and then he and then all on the same day and he says hey girls and they were all like what the
fuck and and then you're part of a social experiment he had to he had to do a fucking uh mrs
doubtfire routine of running back and forth between each one okay but i think the takeaway here is
clearly boys uh man up and just don't just give it a shot man no one's gonna you know it's fine
it's cool just i'm wondering where like he sounds like he's in school still yeah yeah young and plenty
of access to 20 girls that yeah yeah under what sort of being strange when would there be like 20
girls around that is like hmm these are 20 out of all the girls i know i i can narrow it down to
these 20 that i might have some interest i would guess it's almost him it's in school but like better
to break the ice on a girl you don't want to go out with because when you get rejected you don't
feel bad about it it's like all right i just did it it's real it happened i i didn't die from the
question in the biz game started bitches yeah but why would you ask out a girl you don't want to go
out with because what is the idea is that if you're afraid don't if you're awkward around talking to
people like this is a way of like pushing you out of your comfort zone on and growing as a person
on the one hand i get that but like if she does say yes then you would just stand out with a
fucking shad look there's nothing wrong with going out with a girl and then saying to her later
like yeah you know we went out a couple times but you know i think that's okay but if you know
that you're not interested okay why would you even if you even if you get a yes doesn't that
it's not improve your confidence like if you're if you're someone who's in like in your shell like
in your bubble you you feel like you have no value whatsoever and that's why you're afraid to talk to
women and you talk to a girl and even if you're not interested she does want to go out with you
does that not like to someone in this position like wow maybe i'm not a complete fucking lost case
it does make it does it's not about the fucking girls like no one's right this is about training
your brain like test dummies or anything i'm just saying what isn't it weird it's weird to ask out a
girl that you're not interested in well it's the same way that people sometimes they apply for jobs
they don't want because it improves their like ability to uh do interviews and stuff and like
they become more confident as a person okay it's the same idea is it you get something out of a job
even if you don't like it you still get paid no like people will get accepted for jobs and
then not take them because they don't want to take them they're they're doing the interviews to get
better at yeah and and in that situation you're not hurting anyone's feelings yeah okay so you go
out and then you just say it doesn't work out what this is like the issue here what's the this is
like such a one in a million shot anyway because if you're like still trying to like struggle through
even making the sentence because you're socially awkward the chances of someone like yeah i like
autists let's do it like it's not it's small i mean even if it does happen that'll a give you a
confidence boost and b you can go out on one thing i have a weird coffee date and end it
awkwardly after that or maybe something good will happen who knows the point is that you're trying
to grow as a person and get better social skills and become more confident yourself how okay this
is a net positive it's a net positive for you i'm just i'm just like maybe i have too much confidence
in myself that i think it's not in one in a million like there's no chance that this could go wrong
like i think that there's there's a chance that if i talk to a go that i'm not interested in
into it for reasons of practice and she says yes interested in what do you mean by that what does
that mean well i don't want to go on a date with her okay don't do that that's dumb why would you
do that that doesn't make any sense well that's what i'm saying that's what i mean yeah there are many
many girls who okay well i guess i would just if that's what you're saying tom i disagree if you
like you you shouldn't ask someone out knowing you won't want to like some like someone you are
like have no interest in i don't know if you have nobody around you and you're just trying to develop
the social skill i think it's worth doing no well just just go out just like literally go walk outside
like to the supermarket there'll be a girl there just like sure but this is a this is a fucking small
case that probably won't all right if you're in that situation let me let me it's better to do it than
to not do it if you're fucking that socially autistic i suppose i'm saying that if you do
that if you if there's a girl that you have no interest in you do not want to go on a date but
you're lacking in self-confidence and you're like i'll ask her out and see if she says yes and you
ask her and she says yes i don't know if that isn't a positive because then you just i mean it's bad
for her because you're maybe she likes you and you're gonna stand her up you're gonna have to
reject her but like leaving that aside then you are just you just have this like weird social
obligation now that you have to meet you don't you won't enjoy it you don't want to do it and
are you is it really going to boost your confidence to know that you got a date with a girl that you
didn't even like it's about it's about getting i i guess like it's not a good thing to happen
but it's like it's a small bump in the road to getting to a better place mentally in my opinion
feel free to disagree i think i mean i understand you going to a place lying though tom isn't that
like telling a lie kind of asking a girl out who you don't yeah i guess it kind of is yeah
i guess it kind of is the thing the thing in my mind is just like if like she's the only girl in
the entire country sure but like that's my whole point is that like like this is like such a fringe
case that will probably never happen so i don't know why it's not hard to like find an attractive
woman i mean it's almost like it's a hypothetical thing it's like where are you gonna go where
there's like there's just nobody that you have any like interest in even like on a surface level
like it's that's my life okay well that's me your standards are pretty high then
that's my daily circumstances well i guess i stay in your house where there's just dudes okay okay
yeah that's right in case aside practically speaking like women exist around you you can
you can find one around that you have at least some desire to spend some amount of time with
and i would recommend trying on those correct correct just get out there and do something
please god yes that's the real takeaway okay next voicemail here we go this is from quality voicemail
oh right this person i put a note that they're the voice of the people uh this person is here to speak
on the subject of getting into voicemails uh okay i forget exactly do we need another one of these
well i remember this being decent so let me uh i don't know if i'm wrong let's judge me physically
all right let's let's here go so i create quality voicemails for you
and the mostly real stories for my life and you'll never play them ever
all right i remember this insane fuck you dude what me
oh you did you hope you're okay tom oliver you too oh hell yeah
yeah great that was awful that was okay i'm sorry i thought it was great in
was because i want to laugh at this person you are you are weak you are pathetic i have no
sympathy for you i put you on to be ridiculed i'd throw you in voice jail for something like this
no he's weak and and suggestible that's exactly the kind of people i need to go to patreon.com
so it's polystation too donate double what you think you can
bring me you're tired and you're hungry and i will take what little you have
you think that just because you are living a life and taking time out of your life and
sharing it on our voicemails we have some obligation to play your terrible sounding voicemail with your
shit audio quality shit personality and shit life uh nah nah you can you can go you can go take a jog
you can go jog well unless unless uh you know it does happen because nate wants to do this
well i mean this is the exact have any of his life stories i feel like you've done a number of
these things to to to bring something shit on so you could shit on it you set the precedent that
shit is a okay as long as you want to do it ironically i mean are they are they do the people
want to be on to be told how terrible their lives are i feel like some of them might get
some of the attention is good attention if you can't have fame you might as well have infamy
fair enough how many how many more voicemails do we have i think like four uh all right let's get
to the machine gun let's go go go go go here we go this is uh harlock aznebel uh he's called
oh yes all right let's uh let's let's here uh go hey guys guess what i just lost my virginity
yeah and you want to know how i did it uh how i did it i took nate's advice i went to anime club
no joe yeah i'm a great girl she can fucking speak fluent japanese oh yeah so she's essentially
perfect and then like we started hanging out and obviously i'm a shy little pussy bitch so i didn't
say anything but she essentially seduced me that's and it was just great it was great and you know
what else is great is she's bisexual so we both appreciate how awesome women are it's fun i like
cool it's so cool so cool i'm not i'm not a virgin anymore munchie so i can leave voicemails now
man you get lady anime club let me tell you there's some desperate hoes in there let me tell you
harlock harlock i just want you to reckon with the fact that you will go to your grave carrying
the shame of knowing that you lost your virginity during no nut november shake my fucking head
i just it's wrong it's tainted i i have difficulty wrapping my mind around the point of no nut
november if not to like pursue like okay i know i said this last time but like to me it seems like
the point of not fapping is to like encourage you to socialize no i think a lot of people do it
just spread the bragging rights of like self control i suppose it's to be it's to be morally pure
and to defend western civilization against degeneracy that's what it's about yeah okay sure
but wouldn't one component of the jews want us to fap tom but they want us to fap so that so that
black men can steal our white women and miscegenate the white race out of existence damn it i hate
you don't fucking believe me you've been fucking co-opted by the pedophile billionaires okay the
satanic cult all right bernie got you what about bernie though wouldn't having sex with someone to
you know be like child light or to you know be in the sphere sure obviously you're probably not
gonna have a kid but you're you're like closer to you know doing that than fapping know what i'm
saying i don't know no what i wasn't listening oh whatever who cares all right next voicemail here
we go please okay we're just checking in on uh this guy saying uh why no radcon for all right
let's let's let's hear his question okay i'm trying to be quick for just for nate so okay why isn't
there already a kickstarter for radcon for i mean it's been fucking millenials since the last one so
why give me reasons i need fucking reasons yeah quick update on that you you can blame me it's my
fault oh i mean is it yeah because i because i've been crippled and i wouldn't be able to go to it
so we weren't we're not sure when it was going to be able to be held i'm sure we would have fucked it
up and not done it anyway well the tom involvement was was one factor that wasn't everything or anything
but um beyond that you know we got it was the tom there was the tom factor there was the munchie
factor yeah the munchie and then there was the the location factor and also nate's moving potentially
to virginia i mean there's no hard plans so we could like that could be totally worked around in
many ways that we don't mean that doesn't matter that much but i mean we don't have a location
picture anything for it um we just we just haven't put uh any like real mental energy into picking
making any of the tough decisions that need to go into the thing like i mean i the the the current
status is there's there's a slight update which is just like at this point i i don't know if we
talk about this recently or not but like all the main obstacles of like we know people's availability
now we know the windows they might be somewhat limited and maybe take a little bit to get to it
but we know that we just need to like sit down and and hash out what we want to do where we're
going to do it you know how much money is going to be involved and if we kickstarter or any of that
stuff um and um also um there's there's a potential for kickstarter fatigue because digi said he was
going to do like a kickstarter for his uh light novel printing yes yes uh and you know oh he didn't
do that yet did he said he's gonna do that yeah i don't think he has we should beat him to the punch
maybe maybe they're not they don't have to do with us and not the other way around there's i mean
when it comes to kickstarter fatigue also part of the conversation of the of the can tent uh business
was there there is discussion of a can tent kickstarter to fund my move to virginia now there's
no we should just roll them into one and then have radcon forever you know we talked about why
that wasn't that maybe we talked to i think a while ago or not a while ago but like about
the idea of consolidating can tent kickstarter and um radcon for kickstarter but i think it was
unfavorably looked upon in general was it just like it was because i don't know how much it'll
fucking cost to move you well i mean the main expense over that yeah sorry sorry but like it's
just the main expense of that would like for me like i i've just been looking over like the numbers
and i think it's gonna cost me like roughly four thousand dollars what the fuck i don't even think
i own four thousand dollars worth of stuff i have to pay off my current lease well i mean like that's
how much money would be involved i have to pay off my current lease i have to then get a new lease
with the money down on that so like that's already like i thought you meant you just had four thousand
dollars in moving expenses i'm like how in god's name i'm trying to consolidate like all the fact
one number for that and then also like movements maybe buying new furniture or something like
four thousand to five thousand dollars is my estimate for that so like we've been talking
about like if we did like a kickstarter for content or mixed in with the pcb or whatever
like like a four thousand to five thousand dollar chunk i mean i would sure like to be
fundnates moving expenses and it's like how much sense does it make to put like that much
in a large pcb is it fair to put your moving expense on the people in the first place
well i mean that all depends if we can convince them that it's worth their money to make live
content i suppose then you know that's the pitch yeah that the idea was content would get its own
fan base and people would want nate to be able to move to digis quicker and so they would pledge
to that and once that's like locked and loaded then a radcon will be much easier to fund because
nate will already be wherever digis and if we do it there that seems more like a go fund me thing
than a than a kickstarter thing well okay we're just haven't discussed the old the other big factor
here which is how we will come up with like many specific productions that will be an integral part
like if you give us this money you will get these can tent productions i mean we just you and i mean
you know we haven't come up with that plan as you can see voicemailer there's a lot involved
in just like the logistics there's a lot that we haven't come to any agreement on like we might
want to it might make more sense to do it in boston as well but like you know who knows i think so
because three of us are here and only one or maybe two of us are going to be in virginia the x
factor on that whole thing is just like do we want to like could we theoretically cram ourselves
into digis place and like minimize costs by doing so would that mitigate the fly i mean i don't i
don't know i don't yeah i mean yeah obviously we should do wherever we can do it for the cheapest
we should do that's totally what i think that's all i care about like the the thing i was thinking
is um if nate is in virginia we might not you know i don't know how you would feel about people
sharing your house accommodation ways but like digis definitely fine with people staying over so if
we have you know that's like a few people at digis house maybe a few people at nate's house i mean
most of the expense of radcon three was renting the house right yeah the house itself was a large
part of like the production too though and uh i mean like how much i mean i've been to digis
house a bunch of times well like literally once in a while do you think it's big enough to host a
radcon four like theoretically yes but like to is it bigger than the place in brain tree was yes uh i
think so comparable sized maybe no it's smaller but there's a good amount of space there it's it's
comparably so it's smaller comparably size really because did you was saying it was bigger
well i don't know it's fine it doesn't matter it's just pretty big i don't know this is all
insider baseball that doesn't matter the viewers next voicemail go go go right okay well no that
they probably would love to be hearing all this radcon ideas oh shoot that was the best way to
get another get a radcon quicker is to give us more money that's not even alive yeah basically true
basically sure i mean in general uh all right we'll go to the next one uh what do we got here
this is from uh tio tio why tio oh i know tio tio yeah okay there you go i already i don't know how to
say it it's like it's like tio's the gif of my patrons it's just not happening okay and go so
listen to the last episode uh and uh nate starts talking about content you know the thing between
him and jit didgy and then he starts saying that uh he's designed to uh bring in as many as the pcp
members as you know they want at that at that rate why not just use the pcp channel it has a
oh right audience already there that's it all right that's enough of that i put that on because i
i don't know this i've heard some discussion of why is it just on the pcp there's i just for all
time here's the answer to that question it's because doing things on the pcp can sometimes
be a nightmare when you need to get everybody's permission and like you're putting videos
financial stuff it's all mixed up so fuck it we just split off new channel we're in charge of it
we'll do all the money managing ourselves no need to worry about what anybody else thinks
there's that's it there's your answer whatever uh good done out the kate next voicemail
this one oh okay my favorite voicemail of course here we go uh calling out ben saint
ooh it's time at long last uh we've been waiting for it he's been on a bunch of voicemails right
calling out ben saint or maybe or maybe it's just lots of people who want to do it i think i don't
think this is the same one as before but uh let's see okay okay go i'm not mad just disappointed in
you ben you were the one who introduced me to andrew yang this is all your fault yeah i knew it
you unfollowed him on twitter i can't believe you ben i unfollowed bernie too
ben ben sorry bro what the fuck i have i i think i've already explained that i was excited about
yang for a hot second there and then i fucking got my head out of my ass then unfollowing someone
is like a death sentence how could you do such a thing wait ben you unfollowed bernie as well
were you feeling the burn so hard you burnt out i just unfollowed all the politicians i was
fan that's a great idea it really don't i don't i don't need it i just it's fine i don't need it
oh my god i'm so i'm so proud of you're on the road to recovery no i've actually worse than ever
but it's always darkness before the dawn as they say i simply agree with what you and john said
in your uh in your podcast long ago that i just think having too much politics now there's maybe
more that i know is is better than what i'm doing but too much is probably a bad thing in my in my
humble it's yep every day yep any of that mm-hmm very upset very upset constantly uh okay next
next image all right next one next voicemail okay here we go this is the last one and i think you'll
all be happy to hear it this is uh from uh by uh asha a m and uh let's just let it speak for
itself from the yeah yeah from drawings and whatnot you see around let's let's hear what she used to
say pcp dating sim oh there we go who won a funnel gives lost main again well i have good news for you
with over 30 wacky characters nine main routes around 20 possible endings and dozens of unique
locations the pcb dates sim is real and releasing on valentine's day 2020 as if you fucking losers
have anything better to do on that date the pcb wait no we've confirmed one person will have
something better to do girlfriend from anime club confirmed oh no do you think the last until
february you're never know you're fucking you don't understand this isn't a relationship uh there's
no emotion there they simply fuck that's this one yeah so in japanese they're getting on that
disney plus and thrust as it were the new hotness was that asha or was that the person's voice i
assume it was from her is asha like seven years old uh no she's she's a she's a uh a female yeah
you didn't know just as just as bad a lowly moid as we call it in the biz but i forgive her she's
one of the good ones uh she'll be spared in the first she does she does those art things i saw the
tweets i saw the tweet from uh the pcb dating sim i hadn't thought i hadn't thought about it in a while
i was excited and happy that it would have not become vaporware uh while i wasn't paying attention
it's coming i guess it's really cool about three months until it comes out so do you hear that i mean
like 20 endings nine routes or something it was really fun how damn playing it the the demo was
really fun so i'm fucking stoked i only played and hopefully i'll actually be in the game i wasn't
even in the demo it was a demo it was a demo but whatever no it's fun yeah no it's fun not mad so
they said never mad 30 30 something characters something like that yeah so it's uh i mean so it's
like the the pcp endless war a few other like miscellaneous you play as pcb guys like axinger
rough uh yeah it's gonna be good i'm excited the school may or may be not by a shot up by a surprise
special guest character uh of the pcb verse we'll see we'll see um it's gonna be good i hope that's
one of the end oh yes i certainly hope so what if you can join him on his epic quest for uh you
know vengeance against society you know endless war would be in favor of that maybe that's how you
get endless war by engaging in endless war in the yeah school you know would make sense hell yeah
you gotta get you gotta get some slime first though no doubt no doubt that's an integral part of the
something all right well there you go coming valentine's day 2020 look forward to it everybody
by the way we've done nothing we deserve no credit it's all these guys asha and and chip and uh we
inspired them and that's worth most of the that's worth i'd say all of the earnings all of the earnings
most of the credit i'd say yeah it's only fair uh hell yeah is that the is that the last one
that's the last one we're all done we're all wrapped up very exciting very fun very cool very good
times well that's it boys patreon.com slash uh the procrastinators bonus episodes oh we filmed
the new bonus episode early this month so it's already recorded it's uh it was a good one it was a
very good one it was actual quality it is well every episode brims with quality you just the
definition we use for quality in each episode just not all qualities are created yeah not all
qualities are created it uh uh what's the word i was looking for oh wait there's i don't know how
much it's the word you're looking for is it slap it does slap i think you guys are up on the meta
of like what we call topic episodes versus non topic episodes this was a topic episode game
development and we all had quite a bit to say on the subject and personal history and you get to see
some of our old projects which we've linked in the in the video when it comes out so uh look
forward to it it's a good one so five dollars on patreon.com slash the procrastinators gets you that
and literally 31 other episodes of the bonus episodes so it's well worth it at this point
you're welcome and uh follow us at tbcrastinators on twitter updates etc where we retweet things
like the pcp dating sim updates and whatnot um and speak pipe link down below more voicemails
keep them coming boys appreciate the effort also before before we sign off i just want to let
everybody know who didn't see my tweet about it uh procrastinators is now on spotify after popular
demand it is there i don't know if it's it's indexed yet it wasn't like the day i uploaded it and
haven't checked since but the short link is bit.ly slash pcp spotify it'll bring you right to it
every episode is up there have a ball oh and that's great that's that's wonderful and also
there's like apple the itunes feed and the google play store there these are all now in the description
right below like the the main thing there so all that stuff you'll now be able to reach out so
there's no longer going to be issues of i can't download the mp3 from google tribe hit our download
limit just go to one of these podcast apps if you want to listen to it on there i don't think we
make any money so stick with youtube if you want to pay us for it that's uh in fact we are maybe
losing money by doing this probably not probably to some degree but hey that's so we're we're banking
on brand loyalty so if you're not a patron yet wink wink be a patron bonus episodes that's the way
you sport the shows all right there you go that's it for this week everybody we'll see you back next
time bonus episode fuck yeah have a good time bye good night bye bye