Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast, the only podcast
with me, the best guy ever, and nobody else. I am the best guy ever. Welcome to The Pro Crastinators
Podcast. We're the best guy ever. Yeah, I'd say Munchy's here. What's up Munchy?
Um, um, hey, hey, everyone. What's going on in here? I just came in off the street where
I slept last night. How's it hanging? Oh my god.
That madman, that trickster god Ben Saint is here. We've got Mumkey Jones.
Hey everybody, I like video games. Also Tom Oliver.
Sup beautiful bastards. Hope you're having a fantastic time now. Welcome back to the Tommy
Oliver Show and let's just jump into it. Tom, these come out on Sundays, not Saturdays.
You already fucked it. It's a Saturday when I'm recording it and that's the only day
that I care about. That's true. That's true. We're men who live in the day, the here and
now, we don't live in the future. I live in the present. I don't concern myself with petty
things like the future. Yeah. Fuck that. So if you remember a way back to episode one
of the procrastinators podcast, we talked about the best game ever undisputedly undertale
as we all agree. And it's time to revisit that issue by talking about the greatest game
console of all time. We're talking consoles people of all of all makes models and builds.
And let's let's check in with our friends over at Urban Dictionary to read what a console
is. Okay, actually, these definitions are terrible. These people are not my friends.
I just want to disclaimer that I do not associate with them. Oh, Urban Dictionary. Yeah. Oh,
here we go. My enemies console definition number two on Urban Dictionary, a computer
intended for limited user interaction, such as the NES or the PlayStation. Such computers
are intended only for loading single programs in one session, although newer consoles are
able to perform such feats as getting on the internet networking between other consoles
of the same type. I'm a fucking nerd. Even I hate this guy. Holy common input devices
for consoles include controllers also called paddles sometimes joysticks or arcade pads.
Who calls a controller a paddle? What is that? Okay, doesn't matter. I wrote this, aka retard.
Maybe the same people that call levels boards. What the fuck? Is that a real thing? Yeah.
Yeah. Danny on game drums would always call it if he would get a free man and he would
clear the board. I mean, I love the free man thing, but I've never heard this. Dude,
when I would play fucking brawl with my cousin, he would be like, oh, dude, oh, dude, I love
this map. I love this fucking map. It's a stage. You know, the map on a little bit more
sympathetic. No, the game specifically calls it a stage. Yeah. It says choose your stage.
Oh, I love this map. Oh, get fucked. Yeah, you just get reamed in the middle of an IHOP.
Like you do. I read in your mind. I know you want to. Okay, fair point. Fair point.
To start us off, now we, this whole topic was suggested by our dear friend, Tom Oliver,
rest in peace, who suggested that we discuss the greatest. Has he killed himself since
we recorded this? I'm always thinking about it, man. You never know. Check out a monkey
and Tom's suicide packed video or whatever. Yeah, that's what it's called. That'll be
the last episode. We'll be called then. Right, of course. So Tom was just talking about how
great the GBA was. And I believe that takes his spot for the greatest game console of all
time. Indeed. It's a tough battle. You know, a lot of people, Tom, oh, sorry, go on. That's
all I was going to say. It's a tough battle, but GBA is number one in my book. Now I'm
sure a lot of people, when they hear you say that would immediately jump to the fact that,
but, but Tommy, it can't even play fucking Halo while I'm downloading terror flops of
child porn at the same time, like my PS4. What is your defense of this position? It's
baby shit console. Look, there's, there's serious Sam on the GBA due to course. Actually,
quite a few 3D games on the GBA, surprisingly enough. But no, I mean, the problem is like
the new new consoles, the kids these days, with their fucking multimedia consoles,
consoles have like jumped the plot and forgotten what the point is playing fucking games,
all right. PS4 had all these goddamn channels, you could watch YouTube on it. But how long
could you only play Bloodborne and nothing else? It's fucking bullshit.
Long time.
The GBA launched with a fucking kick ass lineup of games and it only got better. And that's what
these, I feel like everybody here is, is not retarded when it comes to gaming consoles. So I
feel like even though I'm sure some of you won't agree, the GBA is the best console. I'm pretty
sure none of you are going to have retarded choices like the PS4 or some gay shit like that.
That's going to be about consoles that play games and don't do much else.
Anything past the PS2, they don't even have identities anymore.
They just became like a weird conglomerate of...
One of the worst experiences of my gaming life was when I bought Metal Gear Solid 4.
I got the PlayStation 3 bundle with Metal Gear Solid 4. It was great. I plug it in.
And then as I'm starting it up, it's like legendary the setup time for Metal Gear Solid 4.
It was like the first moment when it's like, okay, things have gone terribly, terribly wrong
at some point. And this is the point I'm trying to make in general. The big consoles,
like the load times. I'm thinking about Bloodborne, for example. So I played Bloodborne right when it
came out, like Midnight Release. It was fucking great. And that was before they had patched the
little... You know, the loading screens and all the Dark Souls games held us show an item and a
description of a certain item in most of the Dark Demon blood games. So that Bloodborne,
when it first came out, didn't even have that. It just for the loading screens would just have
the word Bloodborne and nothing else. And of course, in that game, you do a ton of traveling
back to your home base. I know. It was absolutely unbelievable. The whole time I was screaming
about why they didn't have this thing from the others, which was just... It was kind of fun to
read the description of items while you waited for things to load in Dark Souls 1, 2, and whatever,
the ones that were out of the time. But they didn't have that. It fucking sucked. So my point is just
like, there's so much fucking loading that you have to suffer through to play these cutting-edge,
so beautiful, amazing games. But on the GBA and shit, there was so much less of that stuff,
because they really prioritized gameplay. And that is just something that's really been
sacrificed in a terrible way. Well, hang on. Well, GBA was a cartridge console,
and cartridges didn't even have loading times. There were a couple games on GBA that had loading,
and there's mostly the 3D ones, but there was only a couple seconds. But no, it's just...
See, that's my point, Ben. The fact that we were so obsessed with creating these big old
experiences where you have to load in a gigantic map and process all this data at once...
I feel like I'm going to get triggered and talk about my realism rant in games and how it's the
most cancerous thing ever made by mankind. It's inevitable. It's related to this. I want to hear
it. It's so fucking dumb. Honestly, because you're saying how everything after PS2 doesn't have an
identity. It's because this realism curse became a thing. How fucking sad is it that in the PS2,
you had Naughty Dog and Insomniac doing Ratchet and Clank and Jack and Daxter. And then the next
console cycle came along. It's like, oh, look at all these polys we can throw around. We're going
to make uncharted and fucking resistance, which are like bland fucking gay games that have no
personality. The kind of snapshot little zinger sentence I would say is, make art, don't make a
tech demo. Because when you make a realistic game, no matter how good it is, all you're making is a
snapshot of the technical limitations of the time. It ages terribly. It never looks cool.
But on the other hand, here's a perfect example of the shit when it started happening in the
PS2 era. Because PS2 and Xbox, the originals, is when they started to kind of like, oh, we can
make games that look super fucking real. Maybe we should do that. Do you remember Lord of the Rings
that came out on PS2? They're fucking dumb little gimmick where they're like, we're going to have
FMVs in the movie, and then they're going to, well, I can't put enough quotations around this,
so I'm going to try, seamlessly transfer to gameplay. And at the time, everyone was like,
whoa, it looks so good. But you look at it now, it looks like ass, like it's a joke. It's like,
are you serious? It looks like someone like with Down's Syndrome made these models. Because like,
it's impossible to make realistic models on the PS2. Whereas a game that came out in like,
the exact same time, I think the same year, the Legend of Zelda, the fucking Wind Waker,
Twilight Princess, Wind Waker, right? That had art direction. So like, that game is just as old,
but it looks gorgeous today. Gorgeous when it came out. You're so right about that.
Not only does it not, does photorealism not age well, because the technology is not there to
achieve true photorealism. So as we like, get closer and closer, like the old stuff will just
look worse and worse. Like, not only that, but like, photorealism is just a poor, it's just a poor,
like, artistic inspiration to work from. It's just a bad thing to work towards. Because
that everyone, like, everyone's trying to make it look realistic. They're all trying to make it
look the same. Like, what makes the game look good is not the graphical fidelity, but yeah,
like you said, the art direction. Like, good art direction is what makes the game look good and
look cool. Something modern now, like Bloodborne, like, it looks good. Like, it looks aesthetically
pleasing, despite the photorealism it shoots for, not because of it. Like, it's the art direction
that carries the game like that. And all the good games that are out right now, like, like,
it's, you're going to be fighting against the realism as it goes on. Because like, when the PS5
comes out, the art direction of Bloodborne still holds up. But man, those visuals, like, that cloth
simulation, we still couldn't re-do real-time cloth sim. It looks really fucking stupid now.
So it's just like, you're always going to have something like that. And it's really dumb.
I didn't mean to shit on Bloodborne, incidentally. Like, I wasn't trying to say it in any way,
like, it's too obsessed with photorealism. Actually, I think that's one of the brilliant
things about Bloodborne. It's sort of like, it is going for a little bit of photorealism in that
just, like, the things are obviously human-shaped and they, you know, act sort of the way humans do,
like, your playable characters and stuff. But like, the, the, what makes that game great is, like,
the, the cool environments around and stuff. And like, so I'm just saying, like, the art design
of Bloodborne is actually great. Right. Because it does all the stuff in addition to just having
sort of a baseline level of realism. But like, your call of duty and your battlefields, they're
never going to look, they weren't inspired to begin with. Like, the reason they were impressive is,
like, whoa, this is pushing the hardware. But as the hardware ages, like, you play Battlefield,
like, remember when Battlefield 3 came out, everyone was like, holy fucking shit. Like,
you play Battlefield 3 now, it looks embarrassing. I remember a string of first-person shooters
coming out that people were very impressed with for reasons I don't understand. Yes, I do remember
that. It was, it was, it was dumb. It was stupid. And it's, I also feel like there's definitely a
business side to this because, like, by, by making photorealism, like, the thing, like, because we
know, like, for some reason, everyone in America who isn't like a fucking nerd is just like,
cartoons and stylizing things are gay, I have to have it look real. So that's what opened up
gaming to a wider demographic and caused this massive commercialism in the first place.
But on top of that, you're also basically low barrier to entry, no taste required.
Exactly. Perfect. Perfect. And then on top of that, you've also set up this cycle that will
never break of like, we need to make games more real. So every couple years, you're going to buy a
new console to get better visuals where like, honestly, if you just cared about art style,
like, look at Wind Waker, you could still make beautiful games using PS2 quality hardware because
like, there are indie devs right now who make games that are gorgeous, but are super low end. So
one person can make it. And of course, all, all like the, the equipment manufacturers, all like
the CPU guys, like, they love this because this is excuses to like, force people to buy the new
shit that comes out that cranks out that little bit more. I think the most disgusting thing now
is that we have the Xbox one X and the PS because like, they're not even new consoles, they're just
like, we're just now they could run at the frame rate that PC's been running for the last 10 years.
It's so fucking dumb. And people just eat it up. Like I was really hoping that the Xbox one X and
the PS4 pro would flop and make me be like, Oh, I guess people aren't that retarded, but they're
selling great. So it's just, I know what this is, Tom. This is, this is what exactly Ben was saying.
This is the normie influx into the normies. These are people. They ruin everything. This is people
not looking for the best artistic or, or game experience. Like all of us are fucking veterans.
We know what makes a good game because we've been there for decades. We've been experiencing this.
We know what makes a game good. These people don't know shit. So they latch onto the most
obvious thing they can find that to them, quote, unquote, makes a game good. And it's how pretty
it is how, how life, and it's not even that like they understand what a good art style looks like.
It's that it looks the most true to life. Therefore, it's the best. Oh, it's infuriating.
These people don't know shit. Normies, get the fuck out. Not only. I say better myself.
Not only do you realize the graphics just look bad. They are just not pleasant to look at because
they always look ugly regardless of anything ever. It also just harms the game. Okay. The only thing,
the only thing I care about in games is, is, is if the aesthetic matches the gameplay and vice
versa. That's the only thing I care about. I don't even care about the game is good. I was red
build on this. I became like this after like, like listening to the developer commentaries and
like TF two, like, like, if you go to TF two, you can like, go like watch like some commentaries
like in game. And they talked about how in TF two was really going to be this fucking like,
like, you know, super realistic, hyper, you know, hyper realistic blood splatter all of your screen,
you know, tails doll behind you, don't look out for Ben drown, you know, like that.
Okay. But, but then like, they're like, this makes no sense, because if we're going to make a good
game, you know, the, the no real people are going to build bases like 20 feet from another, from
another. So this is going to make no sense. Like, like, if we do this in like, you know, with realistic
graphics, you're going to look fucking retarded. And if we want to make it look good, then we're
going to have to like, make the game shit and boring. So they're like, and there are a ton of
like areas where like, you know, a map can't be huge, it has to be, you know, a map that's designed
well. So there'll be plenty of streets and stuff and corridors you couldn't technically go through,
though it looks like you could in a realistic saying, you know, if there's like a fence that's
like maybe one foot high, and they don't want to, you know, completely just wall off, then people
would be like, why can't why can't we get over this. So they're like, well, why don't we just
fucking just make them all cartoon characters, and not just cartoon characters, cartoon characters
that benefit the gameplay. These the game, the T2 gameplay is all about just fucking being an insane
lunatic and fucking killing people and like, and like wartime bullshit and you know, all that kind
of stuff. So they took inspiration from like wartime posters of the fucking like 1940s and
shit. So they got all that, they got insect that matched the gameplay and complimented
and they got to fix the gameplay too. It was a beautiful marriage. Yeah. And that's the aesthetic
The aesthetic totally works in the sense of like gameplay because like the whole idea about
like the spy just like wearing a mask of the thing that he's disguised as, like that's great and
that works from a gameplay perspective and an aesthetic art style sense. It's a perfect blend.
That's I mean, that's that's just what makes that's what makes a good work of art of any
medium is just that all the elements, all the elements compliment each other and become a
beautiful marriage. Yep, that gets on Koensterk, my dog.
And games are no exception. Is Nintendo the only company that hasn't like been
cucked and tries to go for realism all the time? Hmm, it seems that way. One of the few.
They're definitely the biggest one who's like fought off the temptation. I think most of it
was even just because like out of necessity, because like they gave up trying to like do
the highest spec hardware a while ago. So they have to rely on art style to actually
have the lowest they have the lowest right? Yeah, they focus more on making the games all HD
rather than like making fun games. I was just about to say that while they didn't make realistic
games, they still like if you look at the cutscenes for Smash 4, they look like oh Mario's
individual hairs are fucking rendered. I don't I don't care. I don't care. I mean,
you know, Nintendo had Nintendo had lower hardware, you know, power or whatever with its
consoles. But they also they also had that guiding that guiding Shigeru Miyamoto and oh god,
who's the earthbound guy? Who's the earthbound guy who just died? They had they had those guys
like the tone like the tone at the top of that company was like games should be fun, right? Yeah,
so I feel I feel like that probably went away towards keeping them out of this this fucking
ghetto that we're all in of photo realism. My favorite thing about Miyamoto is how he ruined
Paper Mario. I really love that guy. It's disgusting. I think the good thing about Nintendo is that
they recognize their limitations and then that's what makes you creative is to have those limitations
whereas like, you know, Sony and these other people are like, oh, let's let's see how far and
wide and crazy we can make the graphics without yeah, what can we do with them? We'll switch to
discs so we can have the biggest maps and the most and the most the most individual hairs rendered
in the most veins rendered in the bulging eyeballs of our space marines. You know now that now that
Tom said that I really can't help but think that like really the thing that makes the most sense
to me is that guys like Sony and Microsoft like obviously they're wrapped up deep in like the
hardware game so it's totally to their benefit to do things that like like to push technology
forth so that they can sell more of that shit and like it makes sense to them to iterate in
a small increments as possible to force people to buy it so yeah man like this just to me now
that I'm thinking about it this really just seemed like I'm not criminal but just manipulation
wait wait what did Miyamoto do to Paper Mario? Oh, let me tell you. I mean I know that the thing
with Square and Mario fell through and Mario RPG 2 became Paper Mario I don't know anything else
but that was good though that was still in the good days yeah so Paper Mario 1 and 2 are basically
masterpieces they're the best games ever made probably and they are better than any other
game ever made um and then Paper Mario 3 comes out it's like a weird like science one thing but
that's fine that wasn't that wasn't I like yeah I was just about to say I like it as well it was
different but you know what it was it's still a fun game then uh everyone was but but everyone at
the time was like I remember that I remember people saying that yeah that was me me too yeah um
you know I mean yeah I was like yeah I would like that as well and then Nintendo was like well um
okay sure um and then they were making like like like like some like early press releases they were
like yeah we're gonna make a stand at Paper Mario game it's gonna be sick and then or the 3DS as well
yes yeah which we'll get into how handheld consoles are objectively better than home consoles I think
yes we will uh and uh but yeah I don't know if it was Miyamoto himself but something someone said
it was like yeah this is basically just gonna be the thousand-year door again but uh you know
different and on the 3DS and uh so I was like okay and then it comes out and uh it's basically
unplayable it's nothing like the other games it's a game called Mario sticker star and it is an I
played that game my parents bought me that game and I fucking hate it it's terrible I played it for five
minutes you you are you are literally incentivized to never fight a single enemy or else you are at
an immediate diss okay like it sounds like an undertale to me
except that's yeah uh Mario sticker star is truly the greatest undertale of our generation
have you played any Mario RPGs whatsoever yeah I played um I played Mario
like an OG yeah I played the OG the OG one is like one of my favorite games of all time
yeah okay uh I'm assuming that that was just like uh like later Mario and Luigi's I actually I
haven't played it because no it's it's like extremely old school JRPG oh okay well uh okay well uh
it that's actually the first game I ever played in my whole life I think I was like two or three
and my grandma gave me the controller and I was like what the fuck is this shit your grandma was
playing Mario RPG oh my grandma's the one who got me into video games my parents oh holy shit
my when when my when our parents saw me playing Mario RPG my mom was really confused by the like
turn-based battle system because like maria would swing his hammer and it wouldn't actually hit the
enemy just damage would appear and she and she'd be like it's not even hitting him and I'd be like
mom you don't understand your mom would love call a duty five oh yeah visceral military action
then that's perfect then that's perfect okay you swing your hammer imagine if your hammer
had ammo and once you were out of ammo for that hammer you could not use it ever until you got
more ammo that's what every single attack in sicker star was like so dude I can't tell you all
the bosses that I encountered in sticker star that I literally ran out of attack things that you
could use to damage the enemy yeah you just have to lose and like go figure it out some other way
you piece of well yeah it's a resource management sim it's deep and strategic oh yeah all right all
why would you ever get into a bad like if you you can't ignore it's an RPG okay it's not an RPG
but it was supposed to be it's an RP well I mean it's a paper maria it was called paper Mario RPG
it's a really piss game okay everybody should yeah exactly everybody should go watch a hyper bit
heroes video that he made recently about it's got all the details on this not only that but again
where it's slightly aesthetics impact the gameplay in paper mario one and two all this is the argument
everyone always brings up and this happens in a lot of other ways just in this but this is the you
know the classic example the the toads the toads and mario mario one and two were all distinct
yeah like they did so much with the toe care design that I didn't like that is like way more than it's
ever been used ever they gave them all the end of the world they built they built new worlds yeah in
paper mario one and two like like rich like final fantasy style worlds where you can go an adventure
with towns and shit and it was great all that's personality and richness and they just stripped
they thought nope this is terrible this is a waste of our fucking time no one wants this
shit literally everyone wants it so so they just made they just made all the toes the exact same
you know red spots and then just the standard outfit just all of them maybe one of them has
like sunglasses who gives a fuck and all the worlds are just you know new super mario bros we
they're all just fucking you know grass desert whatever the fuck we're in fucking paper mario
two you go to like fucking like like a cortez pirate ship or like rachel mania in the sky
it's fucking sick fucking the fucking glitz pitch the fucking glitz pit the greatest level of any
video game of all time okay you know what let's not spend too much more time on this we understand
where you literally give birth in the middle of having a wrestling match yeah I remember I don't
remember that okay they also in a similar way they fucked up the uh the mario and luigi series
mario and luigi superstar is a masterpiece one of my favorite games of all time uh and then I think
the series has declined since then but like the new one is just I don't know who cares the point is
it doesn't matter like they're they're fucking it up it's just getting worse and worse uh paper mario
one through three is great i'll stand by that all right i'm the third one the one that was on we uh
yeah yeah i actually meant to say the one with like the fez like change your change your camera angle
3d yeah yeah that was really cool yeah it was that statement i just said is true but my brain was
lying to my mouth what i actually meant to say is that mario and luigi one through three is great
and uh fuck oh really yeah i think one is one is a masterpiece greatest game of all time two is
good and then the rest are like i don't care anymore okay we're those let's move on let's move on
enough about mario luigi we're just we're we're superstars on the gba superstars on the gba uh
i think two and three i think i think i guess that's why i only played the first one because i
didn't get whatever the other one you got the best experience you got the best experience
so i didn't play the other ones either and i'm glad that my memory of the franchise has not been
soured uh fuck you as a story time real quick nate um uh do you remember at red con 2 when me and
dad were me and vue just stayed up like all night talking about mario and luigi games like right
next in earshave while you were trying to sleep like three hours in you were like guys
i'm trying to sleep can we please continue this tomorrow i do remember that i remember it very
well i think i was more than the patient with you guys this is muncie's best memory and nate's
worst okay all right we've been faffing around a lot let's get to the heart of our discussion
here all right it's time to talk about the best consoles yeah old consoles are better but which
one is the best that's the best which one's the best i can tell you the story of how the gba
broke my heart okay go for it i was seven years old the gba just came out and i wanted it and my
my dumbass dad said well if you wanted why don't you just buy it yourself excellent good point what
kind of lesson is that to teach a seven-year-old like am i supposed to go get a job am i supposed
to learn about like individual responsibility what are you saving what fucking money i'm seven
allowance i don't i don't get allowance there i don't know about you guys i thought allowance was
a myth that was on tv me too me too me too yeah yeah it's bullshit but i eventually get one
because my mom is not a prick and she gets me and i got i got the oh gameboy color game pokemon
crystal the the big ol see-through cartridge you can you can see the battery it's beautiful
beautiful game card games so fucking good and i'm seven and i don't know how anything works
my first pokemon game so i in the game with a like a level 90 for alligator i beat red
i remember specifically the four attacks of my for alligator were and i shit you not i don't
know how this happened cut slash scratch and hydro pump but those were the four
attacks that's a the top tier threat in the oh you made a game
whatever there was the girl were you the girl in the crystal yeah um of course just wondered
probably i don't remember but probably okay anyway here's the heartbreak we go on a trip a family
trip down to uh arizona and we take a plane ride and i'm playing my gameboy on the plane and i think
oh man there's on the seat in front of me there's this little pouch that you can put stuff in
i want to put my gameboy no i know where this is going and then we finally get to our destination
we're in the hotel and i'm like i'm gonna play some more put oh oh oh oh goodbye for alligator
i have i love gameboy yeah yeah i would buy forever gator
i have i have i have my story that i may have told before when i was running to catch a train
i think i was coming home from college that was in the money episode that inspired this
this very out there you go oh yeah tragic story ben i'll recap it real quick i was running for
the train and i had my ds in my pocket with nate your copy of zelda four swords i think
and it was the zelda the the 3d one on the ds i can't remember yeah it was but but yeah and it
just it just fucking i was running to the train and it just bounced right out of my bag and just
slid right under just fell right off the platform under the train and i'm just staring at it like
it's right there and i can't get it i just had to get on the train and sit on the seat and i just
like it's right there it's like a couple feet below me but there's no getting it now it's like
it's like ben's on the train to auschwitz and he's like i just what can i do i can't interfere in
this this is not my business i don't know about you guys what is he the conductor sure yeah i don't
know about you guys but ben in a train station in a hurry just feels so right to me it's not like
the train was leaving early like it was on time ben's just late it was it was it was it was leaving
imminently it was leaving in the next minute or two the lesson to take home from this is always
make sure that you're on time so you don't you don't run in and you're bouncing your shit and
every you got and you don't and you don't lose your brother's copy of zelda four swords wherever it
was i think it was phantom hourglass you know it was phantom hourglass that's right yeah okay fag
all right the ds light is the best console ever made okay here we go we're getting to Tom why do
you sign because the ds can play game boy game it can but it's just it's not the same it's not the
same yeah you know how everyone knows it has a backlight you fucking retort it's objectively
better munchy so does the munchy i can scientifically prove to you that gba sp is a superior
game boy advanced experience than the ds light do you want me to explain to you how the very the
very simple reason is that oh there it is there it is look don't get hard on the middle of the
podcast rip shape no no the reason that the sp is superior is because the the biggest problem i
have with the ds light because i had a gba original had a gba sp which i went through two and i tragically
broke one that's a good story uh then i had the original ds then i got the psp which was fucking
gay and then i got the ds light sort of and the one thing that i hated about the ds light that was
never fixed is that the d pad sucks and the reason the d pad on the on the ds light sucks he's right
is because it has terrible diagonals if you try and play fighting games which i played all the time
i played street fighter out three played street fighter two played king of fighters to howling
blood you can't do quarter circles on the ds light pad because the diagonals suck but the perfect d pad
ever made is the one on the gba sp because it's clicky and it's super tactile and responsive
it's the best d pad ever made on god's earth and it's perfect it's amazing i would hook it up to a
playstation and play real fighting games with it because it's so fucking good i i i have an objective
uh counter argument to that exact one these diagonals are actually perfect on the s and i
know why i know how because i used to play bows is inside story my favorite fetish game ever made
and i would only walk diagonally because i thought the sprites were cool i would only do it i would
only walk the diagonals diagonals on the ds light work but you have to push and hold it down if you're
trying to do a quick quarter circle in a fighting game they don't register i hate fighting games why
would i play one there you go because i'm not i'm not talking about what's better for fighting
games saying what's the what's the definitive gba experience and i'm saying if you play fighting
games it's better to get an sp than a ds light ergo the argument that it can play ds ergo that can
play gba games is invalid because it can't play them all effective tom just to be fair tom every
gameboy i've ever had the r and l button would like stop working yeah yep same same thing on the
ds though so that's that's that's that's just that's a nintendo problem no i let me okay let me just
say the ds can play five generations of pokemon tom how many generations of pokemon can you play
on your fucking sp fire red and leaf green the only ones that matter that's true that's all you
need all right let me let me make the business argument here okay here here's why the sp wins
in this one category it's because the sp was the first laptop i ever owned i would do all my i would
do all my business dealings on i have my spreadsheets and i would organize i'd flip it open on my lap
and i'd be typing on it uh you know on on a high powered business trip i was a fucking god of 80s
finance and business the sp was so i actually felt i felt like a business dude the sp was so
fucking cool like you had the gameboy advance original and it felt like a toy and then like
you graduated sp and you felt like a man because it was it was such a much more sophisticated
design it was sophisticated and it's not that we have to give credit to the sp i just like the
first handheld console with a backlight dude you know how much that saved my life yeah i know my god
i can't believe it took them that long to back you know jesus christ it's because and you could
plug it into the wall no more fucking batteries oh my god that was so important it saves my wallet
it saved my eyes it literally is the closest thing to god ever made by human genius okay well
while we should give it credit for being the first in those respective categories going back to it
now the backlight sucks on the sp and the yes is way better it has improved that's true i i want to
say that i still on the subject of feeling powerful when you're when you're having your high powered
laptop console i still feel intimidated by my fucking 3ds it's like i feel like it's too powerful
for me like like i need to like like handle it with with with velvet gloves like like like like
it's a delicate button of an atomic bomb and i could fuck i could fuck this up at any minute
like i don't deserve it i actually agree i actually agree ben and i think nintendo sort of
has tacitly admitted that in the way that they've made like the 2ds and they're just like yeah we
had the original 2ds this thing is too advanced for me to be enjoying myself with i know everyone
thinks it looks fucking stupid but the original 2ds is so much more comfortable to hold i believe
it takes a beating and keeps on taking doesn't give a fucking shit it is great and i love it
i mean okay so recently they came out with excel thing i want to get that that's what i was just
going to say so like okay now that it's been like fucking 20 years or whatever since like the original
ds came out they have finally or since the 3ds came out it seems like they finally like with their
very last iteration which no one's going to buy because everyone already owns two different versions
of it there's like it's you know some weird collection of letters and numbers at the end but
it's like the 2ds excel light or whatever it's like the biggest or whatever it's got two
thumbsticks in it it's got the huge screen it's got uh support for everything now that seems like
the defeat and it doesn't have that waste of space that was the 3d technology nobody cares about that
but it doesn't have what me and ben have and nobody else in the world has which is the capability
of plugging it into your computer yeah look at don't you go fucking high rollers over here
you goddamn right that is okay you know what i was gonna save this for later but i on that point
since you brought it up tom earlier sort of discounted the psp i do have to say though from a
from a sort of technical standpoint the psp has been the console that i have most i should i should
on the psp but honestly it like the games that came out on it were okay but the fact that you
could fucking put custom firmware on there and do whatever the fuck you wanted exactly was the
fucking tits the only thing that sucked is that sony constantly tried to like fucking cock
block you with that because every time you want to play the one good game it's like you're going to
upgrade new firmware it's going to break your fucking custom firmware what do you want to do
it's all right but the psp also gave me the ability to watch porn on a console for the first time
and i did that like a motherfucker that was my 3d is right right oh my god it was fucking nuts in
my fucking bed with that shit holy shit it was nuts but also just the psb turned me into elite
hacker man like i became a genius thanks to owning a psb it was it was from a technical
perspective and what it could be done with it it was super fucking cool you like for the first
time you bought like i got a four gig card and you just loaded games right on it and you didn't
have to dig around with the discs anymore you got rock hard you felt like it was incredible it was
it was so empowering and uh it would be i think the only point i want to make else about the psp
is that as like a long time sony guy you know playing like kingdom hearts and um uh you know
all the final fantasy games that were on sony shit like so there was a kingdom hearts game
i had to play it honestly there were two games that matter for the psb there's kingdom hearts
birth by sleep not that i even like that game but i had to play it as a kingdom hearts guy
and there was desidia final fantasy the most important game in my entire life that i played
more than anything else what's that another very important game on the psp that'd be metal gear
solid peacewalker peacewalker of course i love fucking peacewalker you know what was great about
peacewalker the bizarre fucked up control scheme on the psp and it i fucking loved it it worked it
did work it was even found a way to make that single analog not suck i was it was very impressive
you people you use the fucking like uh uh so you know you got the deep and on the left on the right
you've got the buttons instead of the normal scheme you use the buttons to like control the camera
in first person or something like that it was fucking bizarre uh but okay that's all i want to
say about the psb you know what i've always had a deep-seated hatred for the psp because much like
our friend hippo i'm a big fan of the ratchet and clink series and i bought and played every game
and then they announced hey guys the next one ratchet and clink size matters is a psb exclusive
and i said i played it fuck you well you see where you cried like a little bitch i instead bought a
my dad wanted me to buy all my own shit it's not my fucking job get a goddamn job let me take you
monkey when i was 10 in fourth grade and pokemon first came out and all of my god damn friends
had a game boy i was like mom please can i have a fucking game boy and she was like no i'm like
please she's like you can save up for one of like it's a hundred dollars and i'm 10 she's like
you better start saving so i go saving what a dude i large money i don't know i would find
quarters i had a huge fucking cup full of like money i would do for chores quarters that i found
around the house quarters i'd find on the street and i saved up i think 80 out of the 100 i couldn't
even afford the game boy color so just going to get a game boy pocket because that was $20
cheaper i'm like i gotta cut my losses here so i save up the 80 fucking dollars and by some fucking
miracle there was a coupon that i found for like i think it was walmart that like you buy a game boy
you got one free game it's like oh i don't have to save the 30 so it's like all right i'm going
and i'm getting pokemon so i went i went to the store and my dad went with me and my dad
didn't know anything about games so i gave him the money so he could buy it and shit he bought the
game boy color instead which was fucking sick so i got the free upgrade but then i made i made i made
critical error and i was retarded because i was i was 10 and i was stupid because i went and talked
to the guy who was selling the games and i said i wanted pokemon for my free game and he was like
pokemon's really complicated i don't think you'd enjoy that game oh and he talked he talked to me
out of getting pokemon and it was the biggest mistake of my life because the game i got sucked
and then everyone and then my friend let me borrow pokemon and it was the best thing i ever played
in my goddamn life and i was like mom i need pokemon and she's like save up so i had to save up
again to get pokemon and then i did the shitty game was uh it was it was gex gex for game all right
all right and it was it was pretty bad uh because it with all the all the like humor that was from
the playstation one gone nothing in there uh so it fucking sucked but um so i got pokemon i became
the best we should find out who that employee was uh i i would i would absolutely assassinate him
without a second thought if i knew who let's go do it who does that to a little kid say it was it
was it was awful so i i got pokemon red i fucking dominated i was the best kid at school uh
wrecked train uh i didn't i i was so committed to game boy and handheld gaming that when the
pokemon band happened and they banned all the shit and they they literally rounded up all our
gameboys and put them in the principal's office when this band happened what the fuck and i was like
no so i went to the principal's office sat down they wonder why people shoot up schools and had a
discussion with the man for like half an hour through all of recess and convinced him to let
everyone have their gameboys back and for three weeks before someone else fucked it up again we
all had our gameboys and i was a hero but the fucking hero we did it go dude the tragic end to my
pokemon experience was i i was i was working this entire time to get the whole pokedex because of
course that's what you do and this was back when i actually had friends in real life which is a
phenomenon that has not since come back so i could actually trade be a link cable and get the the guys
that weren't in the game that you had to trade for the only one i needed was machamp and it was it was
the weekend i was going to get it on monday for my friend michael and so because he had the he had a
game i had a machoke and he needed gangar so we're going to do the trade and train it back was fine
uh so we went to the movies i don't remember we're going to see but i was playing my gameboy leveling
up my level 96 uh venus or and this is before the rare candycoats so i did that fucking like
legit to this day i remember leveling up till 96 by killing a level two pigi because i never
ran because running's for bitches so yeah so i i i was just playing the game on our way to the
movie and someone hits me and i dropped the gameboy turns off and then i turn the game turn it back
on the gameboy's fine but the cartridge has been destroyed and all of my files are gone
dude no like someone just like they were exing the movie they hit me like they ran into me
and it flew out of my hands and and it and it just the cartridge didn't survive the drop
god they fucking animate you god damn it everything it was the at least now we know why tom's depressed
dude i it's it's something you don't recover from and to this day i've never gotten all 150
because i don't have friends anymore and i can't trade so it's it's it's it's the worst it's the
worst fucking thing of all time um and and and pokmon has never been the same since a little
a little bit of the good news tom that day the the good news is you don't need friends to complete
the pokedex anymore you can do it uh as a lone suicidal boy so yeah but now it's like 800 people
and it's like that's true i don't want to catch 800 pokemon sheep over has a gameboy color with
pokemon blue so if you want to come over here we will fucking trade with you and get you your 150
dude i would honestly make like i if i'd sat down for a week and just like all right i'm doing it
i'm finally making it happen and just fucking did that it'd be the greatest accomplishment of my
life because that's a good idea to this day it's just once you move into the cargo van and we'll
do it i do yeah that'll it'll just dissipate the cloud of darkness that's been over you
that day is that treasure it's all it's all from that one day but yeah mom dad i don't need prozac
anymore i got 150 i don't need 150 milligrams of prozac i have 150 pokemon it's amazing okay
so of course everyone pokemon is like integral to to the the childhood you know
super console experience so did anybody play any of the older it's anyone have any fond memories
of the older consoles than that like ben and i had a super nintendo i had a second say good
genesis was my first console and the first game i ever played in my entire life was when i was in
first grade and we had like a game day at school like you bring in games you play it's the end of
the school year and i brought in like shoots and ladders because i was young and retarded
and oh and my friend brought in a gameboy with super mariland two six golden coins and let me
try below and my life changed forever it was like the big original gameboy and i was like holy
fucking shit this is literally magic i need to kill you and take this home with me and ever since
then it took me three years to get the gameboy finally because ever since then i wanted it and
it just ah it was the worst but i but it finally made happen my favorite my favorite old school
console is magic the gathering hey oh look at that yo fuck mate me and you mate me and you had we
started we started young with the fucking um and the nes the nes i remember when we got the
i think our uncle gave it to us and yes that's right that's right and i remember that i told i
said it was the greatest day of my life and i think i disturbed our parents by insisting
that the day i got this fucking game was the greatest day of my life our parents definitely
had a weird cloud over their heads when like they did we actually kind of fell out of video games
for a while but it was when i was given a gameboy pocket for christmas like a year or two after
that that was when it all came tumbling i'm sure my parents just like their hearts sank because i
had asked my parents to like buy me a new console back then like hey everyone's playing gameboys can
i have one they're like no no you don't need that that's that's not for you it's not good but then
one of my fucking uncle i think was uncle jake gave me a uh gameboy and i man our poor our poor
parents uh i i think i think i don't know about i mean i think i was like fucking obsessed like
all i ever wanted to do was play video games which i feel like is probably why our parents
develop like a bad feeling because i played too much what i do is i get up i'd get up before school
i'd start playing sonic 2 and then i'd leave the console on all day come home and just immediately
pick up and eventually there's like you're too obsessed we're taking it and like well now i have
literally no meaning to like being alive and but then i got the gameboy later and i got an n64
and that was that was some good times i remember one time i was like it was late and i was playing
i was playing donkey kong country 2 and i was like i fucking love this game i want to i would
just want to keep playing it and i think mom was like ban its bedtime you gotta go to bed and i was
like i want to stay i want to play video games and i think dad was like he was like no mom listen
he's a big kid he can do what he wants like if he wants to stay up all night and play this video
game let him let him pull an all nighter and i don't know if he was genuine i don't know if he
was genuinely trying to do something nice or if he was trying or if he was playing some weird
psychological manipulation games but the way it was offered made me feel like like guilty for like
wanting it in the first place so i was just like no never mind i'll go to bed that's interesting
but you know what that's kind of good like parents do a lot of like babying of their parents but to
like force you to make a decision like it's kind of making you mature i guess i don't know it seems
like a good thing i guess i guess i mean if he's really like guilty if he says it like oh no it's
not like your parents lives matter to you at all just do whatever you want no in hind no in hindsight
i think he was genuinely giving me the choice yeah well yeah i think that's good i think that's
kind of good like if you actually stay up and then you like are having a terrible time the next day
and you could just make the prayer like well you know you stay up maybe he maybe he wanted it to be a
learning moment i hope so i want to say my first video game experience because because i hope that
ben i hope you apologize to dad for not learning the lesson he attempted to teach you that fateful
day i know i groveled yes good it involves everyone's favorite resports enthusiast rocky
my first video game experience of all time okay so so i walk into second grade ballers
fuck and ready to fuck up some bitches hell yeah as as you do and then i then and then i see like
this like fucking kid in the back of head like everyone's like like crowded like crowded fucking
around him and i like like like a walk up behind him and like he's like he has like little like
tv screen and he's like pressing buttons and i see lego luke skywalk or just flipping the fuck
around just you know killing some rain cores and uh you know just remembering some ethnic minorities
and then i and then i like have them so i'm like guys guys what is this what's happening
and then he turns around to me and he smiles wisely ever heard of video games
it was that moment i knew that i had to play a video game nothing will ever be this yeah
so if i had to be over to his house and uh he was like uh hey dude check this out i just got
i just got this in the fucking you know i just got this in the mail this is this is the new
shit it's called we sports and i think i'm addicted and uh so so let me play munchie are you 12
yeah it is it is very entertaining to reflect on how munchies experiences are all like vastly
updated game consoles from like what we all got introduced to when we were at least well i mean
you know there's a there's a degree of age here but whatever go on munchie go on yeah so yeah so
yeah i'm i'm i'm a young boy the uh and he was like dude check this out it's the we if you like
move your hand the game moves i was like this is weird video games are weird i guess is how they
always are video games are intensive uh but then he like he like let me like like he had like two
game goes he was a rich fuck he brought to school like he's like normal game boy and then like like
behind like a case in his fucking room like he would just like occasionally bring out for his
like luxury his luxury you know gaming experiences he would have a game boy sp in mint condition
that was yellow and had Pikachu's face on it if he would only use that for playing Pokemon
and and he would he like let me play like maybe two minutes of Pokemon god just just the the the
extravagance yeah he like he like let me play um fucking like a like a little bit of Pokemon
the fucking decadence of that fucking game boy yes please unheard of did you know that in our
country in our country uh one percent of the population has 99 percent of the game so that
was like that was that was that was my video game popping of the cherry and that was like i must
have one so uh so so so i went home my mom i was like mom if you don't give me a game boy i'll
understand but also frowny face uh so please consider i presented with such an ultimatum she
had but no choice she had no options and so she got me she got me a game boy sp and these were
the following games i had pokemon sapphire lego star wars uh on game boy the best game ever made
and also uh pokemon mystery dungeon red and i i i played those games all fucking day constantly
with without any um you know uh respite or relaxation it was only my my my my my soul nine
to five was becoming a pokemon god not a pokemon master a pokemon god and so i played it all time
and when after school every day i would just go to a rocky house and i would beat the shit out of
an brawl because even though i i was a spun mashing he was shit and i was down be his
curvy every single day of my life and i was right down be his curvy that's undefeatable yeah
literally literally impossibly and yeah after i beat him every single time he would like cute
like like like like right before i like star katom he would just like reset the matching
but like that didn't know and then yeah i was just warming up bro i have fun memories of resetting
brawl matches uh at the moment of truth yeah i was like being fucking blasted away on my
did not fucking count we're doing it again yeah i i always loved in in smash like you know that
weird combination of buttons you have to push in order to reset the match you have to push
like 10 fucking buttons at once i always really like that i was fun yeah i loved it so like when
you like like like you always know that moment you always know that moment when you're like
winning the other person's game really fucking mad and then like yeah like as soon as you like
hit them and you know that hits about to kill and they pause even before you match actually as you
know oh shit they're doing it and then you hear that all those fucking like 10 thousand
buttons yeah no yeah fucking and then it's over no contest it's objectively true you guys are equal
in skill there's no delta between these people yeah oh thank you announcer thank you and then you
would always smile wisely and you and you would know that that that your sheer intellect has gone
as your hand shake with the with the tremendous effort you had to press to push all those fucking
buttons at once as ever your soul fucking leaves your body this year effort of restaying that
fucking game i'm not going to play smash anymore that's their game i'm not going to fight them
i'm going to fuck them i proceed to unplug everyone else's controller of course that madman
uh uh yeah okay guys guys we've been talking a lot of shit here is it time to get down to brass
tax time to get down to brass tax we've got to address at least a little bit uh stationary consoles
non-mobile the play station is the best console of all time is it is it just going to be the ps2
are we all going to agree it's the ps2 you know what from objectively the best yeah ps2 is probably
the best i'm you know i think i think for me i have a real soft spot for the super nintendo i think
my favorite childhood memories are with the super nintendo so i don't know if anything will ever
top that for me fucking mario rpg secretive mana the greatest the greatest times you're about the
remake of secretive mana that's coming they're making a 3d remake of secretive mana oh god this
fucking just gag me just gag me i know i know we'll see i'll report back i we should mention this
too briefly before we get into that whole thing what console did you guys grow up with
because i only had nintendo con i only had a gang cube a we and then an sp and then a ds
well well we me and me and nate a year ago me and nate started with the nes and we upgraded to
super nintendo but then but then we diverged because final fantasy was on play station so we
had to switch so we so we switched to be in sony boy's final fantasy path yeah we follow final
fantasy's trajectory through through every twist and turn that it took mm-hmm yeah although there
was a we at some point we didn't return to where i could get my hands on because most of the time
i either had to give up a birthday slot for a console or i had to pay for of course my own money
so uh living living birthday to birthday was how this is how this operation that's how it worked
you had to you had to you had to plan it strategically i have i have a great story of one of my
birthday when i got an xbox for the first time because i was just like me and my friends were
getting big into halo and halo two was just about to drop and okay so halo two came out
november 9th 2004 and i remember this because my birthday is november 8th so on the 8th i get
the money to buy an xbox so i go into game stop i'm like i need an xbox he's like getting ready
for halo two i'm like fuck yeah dude and the guy just looks at me he like looks he looks around the
there's nobody in the store except for me and him for some reason because it's a small game
so if he looks on the story he's like do you want to touch it i'm like what he's like and then he
goes he goes in right he goes to the back store brings out a huge stack of halo two copies that
oh and he just holds it out and i get to like hold it the day before it comes out and he's like
oh my god it's like dude you're gonna come back tomorrow and get it i'm like ah it was so fucking
cool but yeah i got that was gonna give him a hand job so you could have it early uh you know
he was trying to get you back there you know he he tried but but he was close but you know
my my my my desire to to make sweet love to my new xbox console was more powerful yeah than my
desire to please him sexually so you could you could have made it work you could have made it work
that's all yeah that's true i was young a relationship is a two-way street tom it takes work god damn
you have to work out of this i had a date with the master chief that night um yeah incidentally
my my greatest gaming uh triumph of all time was playing the greatest game of all time final
fancy ducidia for psb like a full like it was like christmas night or like christmas eve or
something i was at me and ben's house or our family home and i had just fucking created a pandora's
battery by sawing through my fucking battery pack for my psb i remember that hack it was nuts i had
all my shit laid out i was a fucking wizard i was i was running a thousand bots and fucking linux and
all kinds of i have no idea what you're talking about it doesn't matter the point is i was in
high level hacker mode uh so the the point i'm trying to get to is just that i i there was a
it was a release of the iso for ducidia like seven days before it went live in japan in japan
not even in america it took like another year for it to come out here and i was fucking playing it
on christmas eve a snow fell around and i was literally little finger looking out the world
and i'm like i just made you my fucking bitch i run this shit i controlled this world was getting
psp isos before they came out in america like i remember playing like the bleach game that came
out like two years before it even got like a chapter in america like that was some cool shit
oh it was great and then eventually once i got into the uh the the ds like uh what do you call
ace card just like yeah i have one for gba and for ds it was so fucking for gb legit yeah those
were fantastic again that was the best in playing like metal slug and like all these games are
harder to find i could never i could i always wanted to play yig drew union for gba and it was
like a turn based with like this super fucking sick art style but it never worked on my car and i was
always pissed to this day i still haven't played it i should buy it someday see that that's kind of
the point that i'm getting to right now so the greatest the greatest console ever made is i'm
going to go with the ds light just because it's my favorite ds and it is it has everything to do
with the fucking hacking scene so like did you play wake one on ds i i did not i don't
know i don't play so they remade the original quake for pc on ds with mouse aiming with like
the touchscreen and it had multiplayer multiplayer it was the coolest fucking wireless multiplayer
holy shit it was awesome the reason it was so cool is because uh we had this kid who was like two
years older than us that go went to our school i think his name was paul gibbler or something and
he was like a super hacker man so he put quake on all the pcs for like two years wake all the time
and no one knew how to stop it then eventually they hired someone to get rid of it and like the
exact same time quake came out on ds so we're like fuck you we're still playing quake anyway
bitch that's perfect and it was either that or mario kart ds in the middle of class and they couldn't
stop you because they're just wireless now so it wasn't link cables oh man it was so there were
there were some heroes at my school who installed civilization on like every computer they could
get their hands on oh my god like everyone to be playing civilization in like library class or
whatever the fuck it was but yeah i mean i i uh the hacking thing psp stuff got me into the scene
but it was the ds like the library of the ds is incredible it's so many incredible games and the
fact that you have access to the um to like the gba library once they expanded that capability
and you could run those two oh it was the fucking best did you have i have it right here i have it
right here and i play that shit all the time with all these my ds it's sitting right over there too
did you have the um right i got i got the flash card that i had it had uh the card itself and then
it had a gba slot too so you could play gba roms off the ds slot it just like did a pass through
and then it was flush to the system because you know how would like i did not have that yeah with
the light the games the gba game stuck out because it made it smaller but this one was flush like the
regularist like filler cart they put in by default but it still ran all the gba games so i had like
both of them going at the same time and i was a fucking god that's dope it was super fucking cool
but i mean the whole thing is like i'm sitting here like like preaching like the gospel of gba
but but like it's like there's like a fraction of a percent between gba ps2 and ds they're all
like like so fucking like unstoppable in their own in their own class like it's just uh it's hard
to pick you know gba definitely was like the one that i had like the most fond memories of because
it's like i don't know i think it's because like that was when i had the most money and time for
games so i had tons of gba games and i just like i played them constantly in class like i may play i
loved metroid fusion that was the first metroid ever played and i had no idea what to expect me too
i fucking love that game dude incredible it's so good it was because like i played nintendo games
i wasn't in super metroid people shit on fucking metroid fusion metroid fusion is better than super
metroid god damn you metroid fusion is the best metroid because like it's a crafted narrative
experience all right thank you nobody understands that crafted experience day i'm waiting for
fucking metroid dread to come out and keep that fucking storyline going i still holding
out yes we need it did you see did you see and uh the new metroid coming up metroid samurse returns
for 3ds right when you beat it with the if you beat it and you put you get the fusion suit you get
the fusion suit yeah it's still there i mean it's oh dread is coming i'm not i there's hope
there's still hope oh it's so gonna be so fucking dope you know i i just well on that subject i heard
that like so some guy who know like the director of that game whatever said like yeah guys just so
you know future metroid games being developed depends on the sales of this uh this like 2d
metroid i'm gonna buy like three of them man yeah fuck oh my god the first time my friend
showed me zero suit samus and brawl i got an uncontrollable sadness in your heart knowing
that sadness i thought you were gonna say an uncontrollable boner yeah i was gonna say boner
cuz that's how i felt uh like a sadness because i that was the first time i was ever in brawl when
you can like freeze frame and zoom in on shit you better believe i played a lot of just say
all right uh the the fucking in brawl in brawl you had that you could pause and move the camera
so so i'm sure we're all familiar with peaches uh yes tilt yeah her forward fucking tilt i think
we all know what i'm talking about and they they fucking black hold her panties and the new one
it's a disgrace i hate this fucking god damn it it makes me so fucking mad how could they do that
like okay the fact of the matter is kids uh and and parents at home like sex is real it is real
women are real you can't just like pretend that it's not there and like how are kids supposed to
fucking find out that sex is real if you just like put black holes over vaginas everywhere
they just have that's how actually how does blacking out a pair of panties make kids think
that sex isn't real where are you getting this you know where i'm getting it from okay i'm saying
that's the attitude that these people are approaching these kind of decisions from it's like they want
to just block out the whole concept of like even a vagina from the minds of children i guess male
children but also the penis for every one game panty peaches panty should be the main focus and
she should be the only thing she's fucking wearing i mean i mean they should be there all right
they're they're real she wears a dress god damn it let's not let's not run from the fact that
where you win a dress and you do a badass high kick you're showing everyone your panties that's
real i agree i agree but i i agree that it shouldn't have been censored but not on the grounds that
we need more sex in our video game is on the ground that it should not lie to people i don't think
a parent that's seeing panties should be inherently sexual okay but but it's it's the idea that like
they're replaced with this black hole like like they're they're covering it up you know like
they're ashamed of it and i just i'm like why why you know fucking deal like uh couldn't they just
added more ruffles or something could he's added more ruffles underneath there that's a more creative
solution that i would be more in favor of i i probably wouldn't love it but it's better and
like palutena like you can just see palutena's panties because like her dress doesn't really
allow to make like a black hole so it's okay it's okay for her but not for peach what the fuck
oh it's okay for a fucking uh what's his name sakurai yeah sakurai's waifu palutena gets to
show her panties to everybody but peach doesn't that's bullshit do you like how sakurai waifu
has has like a stripper taunt you like that yeah she literally has a stripper pole taunt
okay fucking sakurai get the fuck out you're done son you're you're all wrapped up uh oh but
okay nobody has mentioned i really i did want to give a strong shout out to the ps one the
fucking ps one that made me yeah the console i ever got for free no strings attached and it was
the greatest day the ps two the ps two is only objectively the best because it's riding on the
backs of the on the back of the ps one yeah because you can play ps one games on it all my
favorite games from the ps one yeah there you go there you go and uh the ps two only wins by
revolution of the disc the disc in the ps one was a big fucking deal you know and it should be
celebrated as such and the concept of the memory cards which i love memory cards are dope um and
come on we all know the okay let's just let's just address this right now the aesthetic it's the
aesthetic of popping between discs in the ps one is like the most enjoyable experience of any
it felt like you got way more game for your money even though it it's question yeah that's
even true like like when i got the first game i got for my ps one was final fantasy nine and when
it was four discs long i felt like a i know i know there is so much here how am i ever gonna get
through all of this it was the best feeling of all time to have like four discs all at once isn't
it great isn't it great the square edicts uh instead they make the base game and then they
basically sell you the other three discs as that dlc packs later i love modern video games
point out i commented on this on that video this morning but i was like i i the comment i just said
was uh i i forgot that metal gear solid two was actually metal gear solid three because remember
mgs one came on two discs that was great that's a brilliant point on my on my new video yeah
it just so you people know what the fuck we're talking about i made a video about like people
are actually making a claim that the final fantasy seven remake because square enix has said
they're splitting it into individual parts that are like individual game experiences these are
their words because of that it's the same as final fantasy original because it has three discs
like this is a real watch my video it's yes it was a period in the world um yeah so the fuck
yeah ps one uh i think i might honestly give it to the ps one is my favorite console i think i think
the ps two is like the best but it's got final fantasy seven eight and nine how can you argue with
that lineup it's it's it's a legend of groon chrono cross don't say the big cross was so fucking
good chrono cross sure yeah i love chrono cross it had it had that awesome remake of chrono trigger
two that's yeah you're absolutely that was in the final fantasy collection fantasy anthology
whatever it was anthology it had four and it had chrono trigger in it i just i just emulated
this very morning before this uh the the ghost in the shell ps one game which has some of the
best fucking animation it is the manga of ghost in the shell come to life like it literally never
has in any other medium it's actually super fun loved it really liked it yeah it was really fun
ps animation is the best game of all time with realville everybody loves thrillville it's super
fun uh playstation playstation only there was a if only there was a let's player that i loved who
was who was like doing videos about thrillville right now while he's drunk off his ass and doesn't
remember what happened he hasn't even watched him back in his upload someone sees what happens
i'm sorry bend i play playstation one had vandal hearts and vanguard bandits to
to two pretty terrible games that i never loved and to be free how much anguish will you have to bear
some head swells around the dead vengeance is soon to come oh my god one of the greatest openings
any video game ever love vanguard bandits just give me some vanguard bandits and some
lincoln park and just let me go back just let me go back to the good old days of 15 year old me
uh the good good times okay uh any yeah go on much what do you say i i i haven't had much to
say about this because the only games i ever played on the ds or sorry the ps ps2 were my cousin's
game so i just you know walked over to his house uh well you know every once in a while and he would
like uh everyone go to sleep and he was like you want to see what a real video game is and you
would pop in like like grand theft auto or like oh some of the most tedious games of all time i was
like i was so paranoid about that shit like i remember i had i had a copy of uh the original
grand theft auto for ps1 and it was the first m rated game i ever snuck into the house my parents
like i fucked that shit and i was so paranoid i actually like took the the manual out of the game
case i cut out a t rating from an ad from an ad and pasted it onto the front so no one could tell
that it was rated m and just just in case i happened to leave it out no one would be the wiser
nate i was thinking with your head nate i might be misremembering this but didn't our dad like
take uh uh grand theft auto san andreas from you let me let me tell you the tale yeah i was just
an adult i i want to say i was literally 18 i think at this time okay but the idea was i was
in his house you know you know what no i wasn't 18 i was i was like 60 this was in high school
sometimes okay maybe you were like maybe i think maybe you were like 16 and he said i'll give it
back to you when you're 18 and then just never did well to be fair i never called the question
when i was 18 but when i was in my 20s you know my my early 20s god i'm in 27 out oh god okay uh
uh uh uh what the fuck was i just i totally lost my train of thought because i want to die
san andreas oh right when i was 20 something like he finally gave it back he was just like
looking through his sock drawer and i was like hey nate i found this didn't i steal this from you
here you go and then why did he take it from you what what was his reasoning that he gave okay i
honestly think that the real reason that he did it was because i think we had had a conversation
about how he doesn't want those sorts of video games in his house and then like i just did it
without like checking with him like he just he watched it on me playing it sometime and uh i'm
sure all this contributed to my deep uh just like hatred of having other people around when i play
video games it freaks me the fuck out i have to do it in secrecy it's like it's like a secret
eater only i'm a secret game player no one can witness my my sin dude i feel the same way i feel
like vaguely embarrassed whenever anyone knows i'm playing video games it's like oh no the shame
you fucked us up you fucked us up dad uh oh but i did want to give my dad credits because one day
i brought home uh devil may cry one and i was really excited play because i thought it was really
cool and i was like oh no is dad gonna be okay with this but what i did was i said dad i got this
game devil may cry one i was hoping that you could just like you know i don't want to do the shit i
did with san andreus could you just you know is this cool with you he's like all right nate tell
you what let me play it and i'll get back to you and i was well okay and i was a little worried
because it's kind of a violent game anyway i came back after a little while he said date i played
this it's kind of fun uh it seems seems fun seems appropriate so you know whatever go for it
weird our dad played some devil may cry one had a little fun that game was fucking great
it is a great game absolutely that was my first ps2 i can i cannot imagine dad playing devil may
cry that is like the weirdest thing i can ever even conceive of it is a bit weird you know one time
ben watching don't take it fucking stabbed by by what's her face in the first cut scene yeah
you just like this seems appropriate yeah holy shit what the what the fuck i don't know man i
guess he he just thought it wasn't that i honestly think it was more of the fact that he felt like
like i had gone behind his back and like betrayed him in some way so he had like forbidden or something
so i get that but uh remember ben when dad came up to us and was like hey guys uh i so you've got
grand theft no it wasn't grand i see you've got a gta now fuck what's that gta grant tourism that's
the where i'm looking for you've got grant tourism over your playstation i like cars uh would you
mind if i played that sometime you know i'm not gonna like kick you off or anything and ben was
like no this is our game console you're not allowed to play our video games defend yourself ben
that is not okay i don't okay i remember that happening but i remember that me and dad were
like we were like in the midst of an art like there was some shit going down that made me mad
him about that and and yeah i remember he i sort of remember that happening if dad had just come
up to me in good faith and been like hey you've got a video game i'd like to play of course i would
have fucking let him but it wasn't that simple if we were there was there was some fucking context
to it that i don't remember but yeah i remember getting mad at him i remember getting no i think
i got mad at him because like he went and like played it like he played it without asking or
something i don't know like i don't think he came up and asked me i think he he just like told me
that he had gone and like played like my like our ps2 because we bought it like he had played on our
ps2 without without and i was mad about that i guess i sort of get that i don't know whatever uh i don't
i don't remember the typical ben hiding behind the the defense of context like a fucking coward oh
it's we've been saying context matters oh it's that it's mattering game way so as the result of
this podcast that the ds light is the best handheld and the ps2 is the best console i think so
super nintendo super nintendo is the best console we all agree of course did you did make wanted to
make sure that i mentioned he he is with me on gba being best console that's true did you would have
been here i think to say that he's a gba guy for life so i was listening what does hippo say
oh that's a good that's a good i also want to throw in that um i don't i never really got into
handhelds i never really enjoyed handheld gaming as much as uh the rest of y'all seem to it just
just felt it just felt like such an ephemeral experience in comparison like such a crack addict
my weird thing is that like when i got into a franchise i had to have it on me constantly so
if there was like a handheld version of something i played on ps2 i had to have it just so i could
have it on me at all times like a fucking like comfort item it was really weird and and honestly
you know i think that shame about people seeing me play video games might be why because playing
video games in public feels wrong and bad to me all right bet you got you listen to me listen to
me on this point this is this is the real deal all right here oh by the way gibb says that he
loves the ds but he thinks he's leaning towards gba himself so he's on the other ally and sounds
like he's leaning towards gba okay but here's the deal ben about handheld consoles every i don't
actually play handheld consoles like out in the world even back in the day i you know i'd play
pokemon stuff but that wasn't the main joy of it the main joy of it was being maximizing my
comfort when i play that's what it's all about so and that's why the espy changed the game because
i plug it in i would plug it in i would sit in my bed put a bunch of pillows behind me i could
lean back in 100 maximum comfort have the backlight on and just play literally forever this is this
is like important beyond words being able to i'm telling you the console experience cannot compare
to the handheld in this kind of situation or i'm just way too poor to afford like a god tier
chair that would that would come close to everyone's got a bed not everybody has a fancy chair you
know the bed experience like even when i had like a semi decent chair like like my my shoulders
eventually get tired sit like because they're you're on sit on like down and like crane your
neck down and like lean forward and shit even if you have like a good chair i've got a great chair
that i'm sitting in right now and i'm telling you i much prefer you can get tucked in your
fucking blankets in your pj's in your bed have a fucking cup of tea if you want it's the maximum
comfy experience it's the best experience which is why i haven't mentioned till now because i wanted
to bring the hammer down because there is an additional console that bridges this fucking
interdimensional gap between the console and the handheld it's the switch the fucking switch is
the greatest console ever fucking made it doesn't have enough games yet it doesn't have enough games
yet but in terms of comfort i've got it right here i just pick it up it charges all the time
i pick it up it's got this huge screen the buttons are tactile and great it's got all the yeah
let me know when the switch gets fucking thrillville then come calling
i will i listen i played i played uh zelda on it which was good then i played shovel knighted
which i rebought and have beaten that game basically 100 percent that game was fucking
great to replay on the switch i'm playing sonic mania right now it's fantastic on this thing i
play it in my bed comfy as fuck you can't beat it this is where this is where the future of the
human race is going in the direction of comfiness in bed with the fucking switch at the end of this
podcast nate will get a knock on his door and shigeru Miyamoto will be there draped in a black
kingdom hearts cloak and he will shadily hand him an envelope full of money here's my opinion on the
subject the only two video game consoles you should ever own is the pc the lace nintendo
console and then of course the dslite just okay but on that on that point can we just say fuck you
nintendo for like being so exclusive with their shit and protect like like what is their defense
for not just being like on board with the pc it's just so they can get more sales they can push
hardware you know yeah absolutely well i mean that's different and we've completely neglected
we've completely neglected to discuss the pc's viability as a gaming console which i will swear
by i don't need any i don't understand why at this point if anyone if anyone is is ignoring pc for
modern consoles i think you're retarded because a modern console is just a pc worse like there's
no reason not to and not to mention though the pc is basically better at old games too because you
can fucking emulate anything in the world so it's got literally everything you can't beat it it's
incredible and it just blows everything else out of the water for me the only reason to even have
like the handheld part is just because because i just don't feel right when i'm playing pokemon
on like the computer i just don't feel like i want to have that experience like having to be on a
time screen and having to bring it around that's the one deal right there like that's why i
prefer playing on my switch versus on my fucking computer because i can't fucking get comfy in my
bed and play my fucking computer but i can on my switch which is why all right the switch is like
the only device i need to smile i'm gonna bring up one of the best like the best like marriage of
this that you've probably never heard of because it just came out a little while ago it's called
is it like a steam box or whatever have you heard of the gpd win no no so it is it is a a pc
that is the size of a 3ds that runs like old games and shit because it just runs windows so
anything you can emulate on a pc that's like not like super graphically demanding if you just run
right on this it has like dual analog and face buttons and little keyboard built in holy christ
and it just you just that's whatever you want on it and it's it's fucking it's pretty legit i will
say that uh as i've i've i've grown up with mostly pc after you know doing the whole handheld
nintendo phase i should also briefly mention uh just before i get into that is that i also did
this like slipped my mind i also did have an xbox 360 and a ps1 however the ps1 uh my mom got me
by accident thinking i want to get a ps2 for my cousin had it she got me a ps1 and she got me rayman
and i just could not get past the literal first jump and i cried and that was also the first time
i discovered i don't like the way baloney tastes after thinking that i liked baloney for a long
time oh no experience then i was just like i don't want this anymore and then i i think i like threw
it away or maybe like i gave it to someone uh and i just didn't like it and also for the 360
the literal only game i played was the simpsons game and lego star wars you and your fucking lego
star wars yeah that's the sound of mini kick makes when you pick it up by the simpsons game
do you mean simpsons road rage no i mean the simpsons game the simpsons that's the 3d one right
oh um right right that's yeah could you play as like literally every character yeah well you can
play as all the main family and then it has like a fucking like we like met a narrative like home
stuck plot it's great uh incredible yeah simpsons road rage is amazing yeah well it is i also play
that on the ps2 anyway uh so fucking back to what i was saying about pc uh just to like like a comment
again on when like i want in tune to go to bcbs if splatoon allow me to play with a mouse and keyboard
it would literally be my favorite game of all time splatoon is so fucking great i love splatoon
it's the fact that splatoon lacks local multiplayer is like the saddest thing it's it's a travesty
it's a travesty for sure that's all to say that keyboard and mouse is probably like my favorite
like way to play a video game other than of course you know the handheld yes people get so
fucking high and mighty about game pads i fucking love keyboard and mouse i will play any game on a
keyboard because it's the right tool for the right job there are certain games that will play way better
with mouse and keyboard and there's some play better with games some games like n64 games don't
really work that well with the keyboard but like like almost anything else like anything that isn't
joystick dependent i beat hollow night just the other day uh and i basically a hundred percent of
it and um like i i at first i was playing on the keyboard and it was okay but then as soon as i
plug in my ps4 and i get my input map or shit and i get it run on there like that's just how it's
meant to be played you know that's i think my best accomplishment ever with the keyboard control was
when i was in college i didn't have a 360 and devil may cry four came out oh shit it was i
literally i had this shitty laptop so i played devil may cry four on my laptop at 640 by 480
resolution and it wouldn't stretch so i played on a little five inch square 640 by 480 on my laptop
screen with keyboard and beat the whole game and i felt like a god because it's so fucking hard
but i played with wasd and like four other buttons and beat the entire game of devil may cry four
and i was just like yep incredible i'm the best person who ever lived your video game has shooting
or aiming in it do not and put it on a console any console it has to be on a pc the other day
i i went to a fucking i went to a friend's house and he had fucking overwatch disgusting on his
fucking uh i can't imagine playing on on game and i tried to play with a game pad and it was the
worst experience in my entire even right now like i love halo like halo one and halo two i have such
good memories of that playing on an xbox but i'm playing right now spv three which is like a
a fan made remake of halo one on pc and it's so much better with mouse and keyboard like like
worlds better you just cannot do first person shooters or you know third person you cannot do
any of that on a game pad it just does not have the precision that you need to play those games
it just does not fucking work it's literally horrible i have no idea how it's lasted this long
you have to play a first person shooter look it's all the fucking norm they ruin everything they ruin
games they ruin control inputs it's before but think about before like like the end of the ps2
and like xbox live and shit all the shooters like we're on pc only like counter strike and fucking
all that shit that was where the shooter then fucking halo two came along and
normalized fucking online shooting and now we have this fucking huge scene where like analog is what
they build these games for so even when you get them on pc they have like aim assist and stuff
that you have to go in and disable oh yeah to take it to the to the meta point on on that like this
idea of like making games to like include the most people are like to make it playable for enough
people like like just the idea of putting a i don't know fucking call of duty on a console as opposed to
pc and just like casually it down like you're you're not making the tightest best possible game you
can make in that pace in that in that way you're just making one that like more people can buy
and uh don't care for it can i say i just just that call of duty is like my not even i don't even
like dislike call of duty playing it like it's fun like mindless kind of pop it's like watching a
popcorn movie but a game i enjoy it what i found really fucking disgusting is just like how like
how blatantly corporate that series is now that when like the ps4 came out and it started selling
better they immediately switched sides from xbox to ps4 is like oh there's a bigger install base
now so now they're gonna get the timed exclusives and it's just like gross you know you know i'm
with you and you know what else fucking pisses me off sports games that come out once a year
like who the fuck does anyone buy these fucking yeah my cousin my old roommate cub
yeah he buys every fucking mad game why explain that to me i i try to ask him and he says oh but
they updated with the new characters just fucking download it download it characters you want the new
because every year you have to ask for the players or whatever yeah that's such a great excuse to
like what does it need like how is the game any different or better it's like because you can pretend
that you're your favorite fucking six foot four that's the whole thing it's like people who play
those games are into like sports in general so like they want it to mirror what they're watching on tv
at the time and that's how they make ten billion dollars i don't get it and why can't that be downloadable
content for like a dollar why do you need a new 60 dollar game i mean because ea this is what ea
does they just want to milk the market as hard as i mean they bought they bought exclusive licenses
to all those like actual that's why like you know uh nfl 2k and i'll like sega had their 2k line that
was going on for a while like they bought the rights to using the nfl ea did so like sega's like
well i guess we can't make these games anymore and they just stopped yeah exactly they fucking
monopolize them shit it's fucking gross fucking um by the way i ea is probably from right here one
of the worst game companies but i can't be too hard on them because every single day i would open
up my xbox 360 which which i also sold later when i realized i was done with the simpson's game
but every single time i'd open it up for the simpson's game we'd go ea it's in the game
ea sports it's in the game i remember i remember that i'm gonna see the funny home of simpson
i remember that from i remember that for there was a sports game i really love it was blades of
steel on the nes the hockey game it was the shit yeah that was i like i like ea you you could you
could fucking fight you could have there you could you could get into a little a little like sparring
match between players and you would have to like time your button presses or some shit and like
fucking punch each other it was a win and that was like that was the only part of the game that
was actually worth playing but it was so worth it tom was blitz the one where like you break somebody's
bones and you can see the x-ray of it um i think they made another one later that did that i was
that might have been like that might have been nfl the league might have been the one that was
called i forget but the nfl blitz was like it was like an arcade it was made by midway it was like
an arcade version of football so like the downs were like 30 yards instead of 10 and like you could
throw like a fucking like halfway across the map and shit it was like super arcadey it was like
nbh it's not a map it's a fucking stage exactly it's they're both appropriate they're fine it's a
board it's a board guys clear that board uh tom brady i'm sorry all my gaming terms came from my
friend devin who played counter strike 1.6 religiously so everything's a map because i just
i still i've ever heard growing up sure yeah fucking do us too i all day every day hey i love
that okay i i want to present a nightmare scenario for you people that will leave you like you know
shaking up into crying at night imagine you were forced to play a video game oh god what controller
do you use game here's past the controller bro giant spider for ps2 ps2 dual shock i
my favorite is still the xbox 360 controller i like the offset dual analog i have big hands
so i play on ps2 with dual analog my thumb is always hit each other so uh yeah i definitely go for
the the classic playstation dual analog ps2 style okay i need that's what i used to play pokemon
like in all my nuzlocs i plug in my ps2 controller into my computer and play it on that i use my i use
my ps4 just because it connects easier for some reason but yeah it works just fine okay so we've
been talking forever and i figure we're probably have to move on to question some point but i
figured we could close this out with something we've been arguing about what's the best console
what's the worst college ship but can we all agree that the worst console is your smartphone
like playing games on that is is by far the worst thing of all time like there are some
decent games that are designed for touchscreen are you a magic harp jump is the fucking pinnacle
of modern gaming i was swear by it you're not you're not letting me finish my point like anyone
like the game loft games where it's like you have the analog sticks on the screen and cover up half
of it yeah oh that is literally the most retarded i've never i think they can that's acceptable
i've never tried to play such a game it sounds horrifying it's the worst it's the worst thing ever
the read the official remake of the ascensors arcade game i used to play all the time i wanted
desperately play the arcade game but i couldn't because i only because i was a little baby
i said i could only play it on my on my fucking smartphone it was the worst of my life because
the buttons were just on the screen and it was just like overlay yeah the overlay was just on top of
the graphics and i just could not see half the i tried i tried like an emulator or something on
my phone but that's how it worked like this it's unacceptable it's unacceptable it doesn't if i can
speak up in favor of it funny colors i and i emulate gameboy advance on my phone and pokemon
and yugioh like it's perfect for that fine it's a game gameboy color works really well too because
like yeah this it's a square screen so it sits at the top and the buttons are under it and right
that's just like yeah it's perfect so if you're playing like dragon quest three or dragon quest
monsters or pokemon like that's fine play well i'll also say totally i hate i have tried that too
and i hate like the the way that you have you know using the buttons on a touchscreen like they're
way less tactile and like enjoyable to use than if you had it on like you know a controller and
shit so it's worse in that way for sure i think that's the definition of not being tactile in fact
i think you're correct which is why i think it only works for like a turn-based thing like yugioh
or pokemon right like if i try to play mega man battle that work it would suck really fucking fun i
don't know if you play that game at all mom game they have specifically for phones they like they
stripped it down a little bit your your decks like 30 cards instead of 40 or max at 60 and there's only
three rows instead of five rows so like matches go really fast but it's super fun can i get marsh
mullen and lava golem that's all i need i have no idea because they they start they basically
started at like the first couple sets and they're adding it as it goes on so they're kind of like
ramping up the the the meta of the game as it goes i haven't played it in months so they're
probably like way more sets now and i probably stuck but that was really fun good way to play
you go on the go my favorite mobile game is grub hub it has really good game i think that's
it's good it has a lot of things to offer is that the thing that you just get food with
yeah no it's yeah i mean it's a great game i mean yeah it's it's like a virtual sim of you
ordering food i know i hate i hate i hate grub hub grub hub has unethical game design it has that
it has that skinner box that addiction it's aesthetics do not fit its gameplay
whatsoever the microtransactions on grub hub are just ridiculous what's your favorite map on grub hub
my house a dust two by by far
for me it's either uh it's either dust two or pizza those are my two oh wait my favorite uh
grub hub map is uh it's blood gulch which is what i call the path from my table to my toilet
hey we got some questions on patreon let's let's check them all right everybody we're switching
over we're going to the patreon remember people if you want to get your questions fast tracked go
become a patron and then you'll be in the chat and you can ask questions when we fucking ask for them
how many times have i just started to say the donkey kong country theme song this like this podcast
and then just stop after hey i didn't know that's what that was also uh yeah and the the url people
no patreon.com slash the procrastinators that's the one okay all right what do we got what do we got
what food have you eaten the most out throughout your entire life anything related to
carnivoreism or meat i eat meat by far the most that's a category so i guess i don't know uh
chicken nuggets it's just chicken nuggets i eat 20 chicken nuggets a day every day of my life
well is that true that that comes into it's been true ever since i moved to north carolina
this comes into an important definition because if you order 20 chicken nuggets but then you also
order one steak technically you're gonna be eating more chicken nuggets than just that sick even though
you get the same amount of like actual food in you so by that logic you would of course get more
chicken nuggets even if you just eat the normal amount of like an order of by by that logic the
food i've eaten the most of is nerds because every time i eat nerds i eat like 50 000 of them
that's true that's true they're gaming the system they're all right i guess
the other day i was i highly i highly recommend going to dairy queen and handing them a box of
nerds and saying make me a blizzard but put these in it instead do they do that one one time i got
them to do it for me it was sick i was curious to see if the candy i liked as a kid was still good
and i bought an airhead and i bought a ring pop and i had to throw them away because they were
just disgusting oh my god this is the most important thing i will ever ask any of you
this will be the last time i ever speak to any of you i'm gonna leave after this question
do okay do any of you live near like a mining town or any sort of like old like frontier s cowboy
situation do any of you definitely not yes i do okay okay well only paint you a rich tapestry of my
daily life on the range as they say so uh i live next to like an old mine town whatever i go there
there would always be like you know some like tourists looking like gift shop and in such a
gift shop there would be the most magical food i've ever encountered in my entire life it would be
in the candy section and it would be just the sack this like old time like like like cartoon
sack and it was like you know like like with the money like the mice have won it but it would say
gold like pure gold and you would buy it for like maybe like like like for like two dollars and you
would open it up and there would be bits and pieces of yellow gum that they were shaped like
gold nuggets and you would just pour that entire bag of bits into your fucking mouth
and chew it all like the fucking slut you are and you would drown yourself in that delicious
fucking i think i've actually seen these before but i've never tried them you have to live in a
mining town to get this candy i i think so but well that is until that is until the other day
when i realized they're going fucking corporate on my it's going fucking ea sports called duty on
me there's some consoles and and i walk into a fucking i walk into a fucking blicks art supplies
and i see what do i see hubba bubba bits and pizzas losing all the gold is that all the
minds are on a sec yeah all the minus that which made the gold good in the fucking first place
now there's bits and pieces of various types of bubblegum fucking disgusting i'm not gonna stand
up this hubba bubba i'm gonna protest you every single time you see you john hubba walks down to
fucking hubba bubba i'm gonna drown in the fucking i'm like melt down his gum John hubba and his man
servant bubba yeah how'd he get his name on the company uh you know he's just really does a good
job he really really he's like a trusted advisor you know no no no relation no relation just used
to happy coincidence why would they be related because their names rhyme yeah that's that's
pretty racist um so anyway fuck you hubba bubba i'll never forgive you i think we answer the question
injustice yeah hey i've got one here um this is i i'm reading also people where we also read
some questions from the uh from the twitter with hashtag ask pcp uh so here's a question for it's
sort of direct to you munchie but really anybody could contribute this uh at ascan2 asks uh can
one of you say something really fucking funny one day i went and looked at my pet and i said oh i
must you be barking and you're peeing and he looked at me and he gave me a wink oh
oh
no he's gonna disobey me once more
that was pretty fucking funny yeah um all right i'm satisfied i'm satisfied
uh i can get another one uh uh okay here we go here we go at suicide sausage asks uh oh
this one's direct to me but anyone could comment on it um nate i'm trying to be nice but people
are assholes what do i do uh who's got some wisdom for this guy kill them what does he do
kill them that's one way to go kill any other suggestions your problem is that you are trying
to be nice that's why people are assholes they can smell that weakness that's true you got you
got to cut you got to cut them before they cut you you've got a hashtag chat it up my dude you
got to chat it up jazz it up you have to realize that by standing for something you inherently
stand against something else as well and those people come for you so you have to tell them the
fuck off that is true that is true um yeah i guess just uh don't be a pussy all right there you go
that's the advice someone asked a retired question uh okay who's the strongest person a fusion of
monkey hey read their name they just have credit get read their oh sorry sorry orca um in the pcp
patreon lounge okay if you too would like to be culvin started go pledge a dollar
this is important monkey who is the person that like if me and you fused together who's the strongest
person he could be anybody you're already the most powerful being in the universe so like i don't
even know why i'm involved in that that's true you just make him weaker don't you think because
yeah i'll just bring him down he would make him try to kill himself suicidal tendencies right and if
once he dies the whole world dies the the way i see it it's a lot it's a it's not like like you
know autocracy versus order you don't like like yin and yang and sort of like uh like like like like
you know honor versus love and stuff like that so if you used to gather like like all all of my
inhibitors that like lessen my power than you know like i i try and you know i i try and remain
honor bound by not having sex and you know right uh you know all i do is have sex so we'll
belt exactly yeah i'm picturing sort of like munchie is like the eva unit one and then if i
fused it with with munchie like the the armor that actually holds within the creature back
from destroying the whole world would come bursting forth and yeah it would be uh it would be the
end times for sure i think we need to come up with a list first of all i want to say any sort of
scientist uh immediately gone off like like immediately like snap my i don't want to talk
to a scientist y'all mother fuckers lying and getting me pissed i don't want to hear about that
we get rid of them for their sins uh nila grass tyson first one to go because oh yeah right not
because of any other reasons not because you know he's an asshole literally just because he's black
that's because he's black of course he's the only black person i can think of
and uh yeah that's it that that's the end of our list hey here's a question on twitter from
at commander incest sounds like my kind of guy he says if you were to make a frankenstein monster
out of the pcp members what parts would you use and why you'd have to use my iron cock that would
be uh you'd have to use my you'd have to use my heart my heart to give us a strong moral center
to remain powerful in this world yeah that's that's good so we've got the cock in the heart
whose brain do we use in this situation we gotta use mage's brain otherwise it's gonna be all
fucked or else we'll be misogynists yeah we need mage's females no matter what they have to use
my lungs my lungs have to be involved so that's true so they can clip the microphone with every breath
yeah this beam will be more powerful than anything else i've ever made it's gonna be my life it's
it's gotta have hippo's hair yeah hippo's gotta have my funny bones so that nobody thinks it's funny
that's a good idea that's a good idea uh well let's just give it tom's skeletal structure in
general so that we're tall and intimidating against the world you know that sounds good
the best thing you can think of about tom is that he's tall is well physically we can also take
his uh his hatch you know his brony curious hat in addition to your ironclad cock can we add on
digi's phymosis foreskin of course that's the only part that's the only part for digi we take
is his foreskin well that's what he would want us to take it's what they should have taken when he
was born he's been looking for an excuse to get rid of it and his flesh golem is the perfect reason
uh yeah incredible incredible one this this batch of patrons are not are not doing it for me yeah
we need we need to cycle them out and get some new one in head on over to patreon.com slash
the procrastinators that's a good hey okay here's a separate question at smith korban or korban
whatever asks uh what did you dream about last night does anyone remember their dream from last
night i never were fucking remember my dreams and it pisses me off which is why i want to read this
does anyone remember oh yeah yeah no yeah i remember it was actually about arm retrieval uh
my favorite podcast of all time go to armital.com well that sounds more like a nightmare than yeah
yeah yeah i was recording arm retrieval and then roxy along walked to my room and i was like oh that's
a first that's the best dreams have sex with me roxy i love you uh and and then i was like i was
reread i was i was rereading act six today roxy i don't you you didn't live up to what i remember i
don't i don't know if you're my favorite character you're out of my favorite characters anymore
i think you need to leave my household and i don't think you're welcome here anymore
and then uh and i and i shoot her away and and that was that was the end of my dream it was a nightmare
you're out of the pcp you don't disrespect roxy even dream for him
yeah dude what if that was like actually real roxy because you were in the dream bubble and you
bumped into actual roxy in your dream bubble oh the sex could be real for me oh it could be real
if it was in a dream that makes it that's how it works that's that's how it works in homestuck
technically i do something uh what do we got hey okay bunchy this one's for you i'm sure i don't
know if anyone else at leo j larkin asks if you had to pick a pre 19th century military to serve in
which would you choose and why uh i love this question i love when did the nazis start
a little bit after that unfortunately yeah a while after that um i would want to be a
persian slave soldier for sure because that's just the most powerful aesthetic that there is
somewhat similarly i i would go on i would go on g hods all the time i would be an ottoman empire
fucking you know that's not a bad choice i would be one of those i would be one of those christians
that um like like like they just like stole from one of their puppet states and they just like
they're like okay you're our slave now like constantine or something one of those guys
yeah yeah yeah and then remember you're a soldier you're not the emperor you're a soldier in the
military in this example yeah yeah yeah okay so so yeah i'm just uh i'm just going to oh wait did
it say command no no no i well i mean you could you could let's say you could put in command if you
want but you're still a soldier he just doesn't deserve it so yeah i would just be like a fucking
janissary and i just ride around in my cool ass fucking uh horse and just beat the shit out of any uh
unwilling people whine you know i would just force my willum upon like my whim upon uh everyone
who i meet no sex you can only play handheld video game consoles and uh mouse and keyboard is the
preferred method of game and then if they didn't if they didn't accept they would be a dead that's
good hey i think we've answered this question before but someone posted an image that i'm going
to retweet because it's extremely adorable and it just says bug fuck we did answer that before
didn't we i think most definitely that's well well tread territory by this yeah okay all right
just just okay well good uh that's that's all the decent questions everything else is terrible
you guys should be ashamed of yourselves everybody else uh yeah get fucked everybody uh all right
thanks for listening everybody that's it we're all done all right everybody go to patreon.com
slash the procrastinators because guess what people the death note episode is out right now
the bonus episode it's out we're we go we go deep we're rolling in the deep like Adele our favorite
youtube creator uh it's uh it's a it's a whole new world out there so go pledge five dollars to get
access to that and every other bonus death note so please so please pledge so you can see it it's
it's worth uh your interpretation is definitely worth five dollars so if you're not giving us five
dollars already you there's nothing better you can spend it on this month than munchies death note
damn right damn right and uh send us more questions uh you know you also when you're a patron you
get access to the patron lounge you get your questions read and actually talk there a lot we
actually do talk there a lot you can hang out with us and you can go to at uh tpcrastinators
and follow us or for updates and shit they're just fucking tweet us every saturday when we tweet out
we're using uh we're looking for questions hashtag ask pcp there you go that's the deal and you can
go to youtube.com uh forward slash c forward slash tbvap for epic coin reviews uh you know
in case in case in case you're harking for that uh for all the real up to date that that's basically
the procrastinator secondary channel yeah uh pretty much it's it's true it's true all right
thanks for this everybody we will see you next week bye yeah yeah uh i'm supposed to be working
right now i'm supposed to be working right now but i'm not working i'm doing