I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Damn, we should have talked about all that incredibly interesting stuff we just talked about. We should have talked about it on the episode.
No, we should not have.
Aw, yeah, you're right. Now it gets to go on a bonus episode where people can pay money. Money!
Don't talk to me about money.
We're running out of money, Gibb.
It's over.
Yeah, it's over. Time to call it quits.
Time to call it quits. We are floundering. What do you have to say about that?
I say, fuck the police. I'll flounder, even though I'm not allowed to.
Yeah.
All right. Okay, good.
Welcome to the perk-er.
We've got to go all in on the perfect comic party. It's the only way.
The people don't want podcasts anymore.
They've grown beyond podcasts. I don't care about all that podcast stuff.
I'm sad this month.
Go on.
I'm sad and depressed, Sven.
I've been feeling real bad.
Yeah, cool.
Oh, it's so cool. You want to hear about it? You want me to talk about it at length?
That's going to be great content.
No.
I mean, I would love to hear about it if you'd like to discuss.
Well, all right. The annoying part is that it's a feeling that's hard to explain.
How long have you been feeling this way, Gim?
Just this week?
Last few weeks. I don't really know.
Okay.
First off, some basic notes. Lack of confidence that anything will work out with anything that I'm doing.
Increasing pressure to get some shit together so that the bad things will not happen even though I know they will.
Yeah.
And a horrific feeling of nobody understanding me and never being able to express how I feel ever.
That's how I've been going.
You know, well, no, you know, I don't want to make it about me.
But okay, I mean, I understand all those.
Those all make sense.
I put something somewhere.
I put a little, yeah, I wrote it down.
Yeah, I was feeling sad about transience.
Transience?
Transience, the things being brief or fleeting.
I'm sorry. You were feeling sad about the concept of transience in general?
Well, yeah, I mean, everything's got to stop at some point.
Yeah. You know, I mean, I agree with you and I do get sad about it sometimes.
It's just funny to hear you express it so casually.
Oh, yeah, I'm just sad about transience.
Just sad about transience.
Well, that's the word.
But I agree though, but sure, it is sad, yes.
Yeah, I mean, it's most of my frustration is that I don't know how to explain how I feel.
And every time I try to come up with a series of words or like a thing to say,
oh, so what's wrong?
Oh, well.
And then it's like white noise.
Like how do I express white noise in my head?
Like words and language just don't cut it.
You have to feel it.
But it's also really stupid and pointless to talk like that in front of people with language
who can only understand words.
So I'm just sort of like, oh, it's just like that book.
I have no 1984 and I must 1985 or whatever.
Yes, it's not like that book at all.
That's why he wrote that book.
I don't feel like I'm cursed by a robot or whatever.
I'm cursed by the algorithm.
So I mean, okay, what's got you feeling this way?
I think it's just I don't feel like I'm capable of making it in a basic sense.
Like I can draw a little comic and it just takes a really long time.
And you're always going to compare yourself to other people and you should try not to.
It's like just don't worry about it.
Don't worry about not being able to make a living.
Just try your best and keep going.
The best work comes when you're not stressing out.
I'm like, okay, so don't worry about anything.
How do you do that?
I mean, it's impossible.
It's just there's no escape and I don't think I'm cut out for life.
I don't know what I'm doing here.
It's pretty heavy.
I understand.
Yeah, it is all encompassing.
I mean, I get you.
What are you going to do about it?
Well, it's two things.
I want to kill myself too.
Don't do that and persist.
I like persisting.
I'm pretty good at that.
I've been practicing my whole life.
Yeah.
I mean, it's not like on the table or anything,
but it is one of those like...
We're killing yourself?
Yeah.
Okay, good.
It's good.
No, it's not on the table.
I don't want to worry anyone, but it's just,
I don't feel like I can make it.
I don't feel like I can do it.
No matter what it is.
It's just sort of like, yeah.
Are you talking about career-wise, comics-wise?
Comics-wise, career-wise.
I don't know, just life stuff.
Like transitioning.
I don't know.
I'm getting choked up.
Getting all choked up about it.
Oh dear.
I shouldn't have brought it up, but...
Well, that's not good content.
No.
We're hemorrhaging viewers right now.
Crying live?
No.
They'll think I'm going for the pity vote.
They'll think I'm crying for views.
Got to keep those tears locked away.
Ben's secretly...
Wait, no.
Actually, I know tears are good for views.
I got to make him cry more, but how?
I'm going to steal Christmas.
I'm going to steal Christmas gift.
I'm going to come down from Mount Crumpet
and steal all your buzz-wonglers.
Christmas.
Bah-hum-bog.
You know what?
I've watched today.
My brother was here.
This is why the PCP is late here,
because my brother was visiting,
and I just want to hang out with him.
And we watched a movie
called The Christmas Game.
The Christmas Game?
It was like a two-hour-long movie,
and we realized that halfway through,
it was a two-hour-long epic fantasy folklore tale
of one of the Knights of the Round Table
and King Arthur,
and it's some sort of adaptation of a historical novel
by an anonymous writer.
Why would you watch The Christmas Game
when it's April?
I don't know.
Henry put it on.
That's so funny.
When I googled The Christmas Game,
the first thing I find is a board game.
Wait, it wasn't called The Christmas Game.
It was called The Green Night, I think.
Wait, how did you call it?
Wait, wait.
Yeah, I've heard of The Green Night.
Why'd you call it The Christmas Game?
Because in The Green Night,
there is a game called The Christmas Game.
It's Christmas Day during the beginning,
and this Green Night, this big,
made-of-wood sort of guy,
marches in to the throne room of King Arthur's court,
and he says,
fight me, buddy.
This is a Christmas game.
Choose one of your knights,
and there's this clothes,
not Santa clothes,
in this little contract of this game.
We're like, fight me,
whatever damage you do to me.
The person, they have to try and nick me.
They have to try and cut me and hurt me.
And whatever damage you do,
six months from now,
or no, a year from now,
six nights to the north,
I will be waiting in a chapel,
and you must come to receive the same mark again.
And so this kid, like a...
So why would you want to hurt him
if he says you'll be hurt as well?
I know. It was so stupid,
because he's like this young boy,
he's always fucking,
but he doesn't have any cool epic tales.
He's in the brothel,
and he doesn't have any stories to tell the court,
or King Arthur or King Arthur's like,
come on, boy, got any cool stories?
And he's like, uh, no.
All I do is fuck.
And it's so like,
I want to go on an epic quest, I guess.
I guess that'll be good to do that.
Um...
And then...
And, uh...
Yeah, so he has an opportunity
to go on an epic quest,
or to do something cool.
He says, I'll fight the Green Knight.
But he, like, idiot, like real stupid,
he chops the Knight's head off,
he beheads him, because the Green Knight
just kneels back down and says,
hey, why don't you chop off my head?
He presents his neck.
That's a great idea.
Didn't you listen to the thing you'll have to get
your head chopped off? Just nick his arm.
Just give him a little cut on the knee.
Like, what are you doing? And he killed him.
But he took his head up, and he's like,
haha, I'm the headless horseman now.
And he laughed, and he ran away.
And so, like, a year later,
that he just...
He just like, oh,
I guess I gotta go.
Oh, I guess I gotta go, and then he goes.
And he just has, like, little escapades,
little moments
in between, like, on his adventure.
Yeah.
Thinking that, you know, he'll have courage
by the end, or he'll be a Knight
worthy of King Arthur.
And he just sort of... Because I chopped
the head off a guy who let me do it?
Yeah, and, well, no,
now he has to go and get his head chopped off,
and he knows that. And I'm like,
why did you chop his head off then?
That's the part I don't get. Why would you do this?
The clause didn't say kill me.
It says, like, nick me.
Literally, that's what he says.
Yeah.
Anyway, he goes there.
And the film, it looks beautiful.
Acting is all right.
But it's, like,
so overly slow.
It does not need to be
two hours long, and we're getting bored.
Mm-hmm.
It's obviously very thematically rich,
and all the characters and the things are, like,
there's lots to delve into,
but we were just not going to be bothered with that shit.
We skipped ahead.
I remember that movie came out,
and for some reason, I thought it was, like, an MCU.
I thought the Green Knight was, like,
a, you know...
The Green Lantern?
Some little-known Marvel hero.
They're like, oh, they're making another...
They've delved into the depths of...
Oh, they got Moon Knight, and who the fuck is that?
Oh, they got the Green Knight.
Okay, sure. That's what I thought.
But no, I guess it was, like, a real movie.
Yeah, it's a real movie.
Critics love it, apparently, but...
Mm-hmm.
I didn't have the patience.
It was just, like, every scene,
there would be scenes of him walking,
and those scenes of walking would just go on
for, like, 20 seconds longer than they really needed to,
and he goes on a lot of walking scenes,
in between scenes where he's looking,
and then sometimes he's looking,
and then he's scared,
and it's like, shut up!
Shut up!
Just get to the part where you go to the Green Knight
and get your head chopped off.
Oh, he gets his axe.
Oh, he gets his Green Axe
for landing the blow.
I'll give you... Yeah, you land the blow,
I'll give you the Green Axe, and it's a cool-looking axe.
Like, it makes moss and grass
appear around it just very slowly.
Okay.
Like, he puts the axe away in a treasure chest
for later, because he doesn't want to use it.
He doesn't care about it.
And then when he goes to get his head chopped off,
the axe has grown, like,
moss inside the wooden crate.
It's just...
There's moss everywhere.
But I don't think he even uses the fucking axe.
It's just sort of...
He has it.
We did skip around, so maybe we did use it.
I mean, it's pretty cool to have.
Cool to have, even if you don't use it.
I got a magic axe.
Yeah.
All right.
He meets a fox, and the fox is like,
ah, hi, hi, my little fox.
I'll teach you something about yourself.
And he's like, fuck off.
Yeah.
That's what I would probably say.
I'll teach you something about yourself.
Ooh.
You want to learn about friendship?
Fuck off.
Dog.
Yeah.
So, this is not a review, because we did skip,
like, basically from the midway point
to the end.
And then we saw the moment
where he puts the thing and he's like,
all right,
you can cut my head off now.
Wait, I'm not ready.
When will you be ready?
Give me a moment.
Are you ready? Yeah.
Why did he go?
I don't know.
Some sort of parable, probably.
Some sort of story.
To be a great man
is
to get your head chopped off
to get your head chopped off in this epic way.
I mean,
yeah.
It's kind of ambiguous at the very end
whether or not it happens, because like,
he runs away, right?
He runs away and he comes back home
and it's supposedly like a happy moment.
But then
things happen.
A king author dies, he becomes the king,
because he's related by like
sister or something.
I don't know.
Some sort of reason.
And he becomes the king
and then his kingdom crumbles
because of war and he's just kind of a shit king
and he has a
bastard boy son
and the son dies in war
and it's like, oh, all this shit,
this bad stuff happens.
You should have got your head chopped off,
then all that bad stuff wouldn't have happened.
And that was a flash forward.
Premonition did.
And he was back there
and he was like, oh, wait.
I am ready.
I won't run away
like a coward and live.
I will instead die
from a green guy
and the green guy says, well done son.
Well done.
Now off with your head
and then credits.
I see.
And I'm like, I think it's supposed to be
ambiguous. He could say off with your head
as an off with you.
Head of state.
Maybe.
But they don't
show any death after that.
So I guess the idea is
the moral of the story is
do things you
promise you're going to do, like
get your head chopped off.
Even though it's scary.
Your land will be cursed.
Otherwise you'll be a shit king
and nobody wants that.
You'll have like a green aura around your kingdom.
The lighting will be kind of green, meaning bad.
Ooh, green is bad.
Yeah, green is bad.
I learned that from The Matrix.
I learned that from Slytherin.
Oh yeah.
Funny how green is bad, even though green is
gross and cows eat that
and cows are nice.
I made a tweet like that a long time ago.
We should have known Rowling was bad
because she made the bad guys
green and the good guys red.
And that's wrong.
She's twisted.
She's twisted in the mind.
She shoots the...
They shoot the...
I got it messed up. People criticized me in the replies
and I had to figure it out.
I thought that it was...
Expelliarmus was red
and the killing curse, Avada Kedavra,
was green. I was kind of wrong.
I was half wrong.
Okay.
Yes.
It is red though.
Okay.
I think it depends on what you're looking at.
In the movie, maybe,
but in the book,
I think it's usually not described
with any particular visual flair.
There's like one part where
it says there's a red flash
that Expelliarmus could...
One part or no, a scarlet flash.
But what I was thinking of
was the stunning curse.
Oh, it's the other one.
Stupendo?
Stupify.
Stupify shoots the red beam.
Stupify versus...
I think they remember that.
The Ministry of Magic guys do that all the time
after a certain point.
They just jump in and that's their taser.
Yeah, that's their laser
that stops you but doesn't kill you.
The bad guys use the laser that kills you
and it's green.
In the games, Expelliarmus
has no
defined
visual
flair look.
Sometimes it's like a parry button.
Expelliarmus is like in the third game.
It's like a parry that you have to time.
Snape uses it one time
in the book when it's described
as causing a scarlet flash.
There is...
Oh god, no, what was I going to say?
Oh no, it's over.
Harry Potter.
What a film.
What a book.
What a game.
What a tale, yeah.
So basically the Green Knight
is a long, long film that's okay.
RRR is very long.
RRR is three hours
but it's awesome.
We also social in the sheep.
A couple of people
watched RRR after the last episode
and from what I said, they saw it was good
so I thought I was pretty happy about that.
We also saw
Sean The Sheep, the movie.
That's an Aardman, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I've not seen that one.
It's a very funny,
family-friendly...
I mean, they're all family-friendly
but Sean The Sheep, the TV show, is like
for kids.
It's a little simple
but it's nice, it's fun.
So I was surprised.
My mom did not like
freaking, was it called
flushed away?
She thought it was a rat one?
Yeah, she thought it was like too gross.
There is poop.
There's not even poop.
There's toilets and there's slime,
like snails and stuff in the sewers.
That's probably as gross
as it gets, I think.
I know and I just don't think it's that...
It's that gross.
It's actually as gross as the opening of Shrek.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I just didn't get that.
But I thought flushed away
was really good.
Yeah, flushed away, I remember enjoying that.
I haven't watched that in a long time.
I think I watched it like two or three years ago.
What was I going to say?
You know Sean The Titular Sheep?
Yeah, I mean
not really, but
I guess
I can assume some things about him.
Well, what can you assume?
I don't know that he's a sheep.
Oh, okay.
Well, have you seen the other Willis and Gromit movies?
Yeah, well, several of them.
Have you seen A Close Shave?
That's the one with the dog that's a robot
and all the sheep and including Sean.
The dog?
Wait, I'm thinking of
the dog that's a robot.
I'm thinking of the wrong trousers.
The wrong trousers is the one where the trousers
are incorrect and there's a penguin
and there's a penguin in a diamond
house and
that's the penguin one.
The Close Shave is the one where
Willis falls in love with
a lady at the wool, the knitting store.
She's got all this wool
and
there's this dog
that
provides her with the wool but it's kind of
a really weird bully dog,
nasty dog, Gromit hates him
and Gromit realizes that the dog's
evil but nobody believes him
because the lady believes
the dog and Willis believes the lady
and so Gromit
is
something happens
but there's sheep, right?
And it's actually the dog
is evil.
Evil dog. He's a robot
scary dog, scary robot
dog made of robots.
Yes.
It's made of robots?
I think the thing was
her dad was
an inventor and he
invented the dog to look after her
but it sort of goes too far
I think.
I thought I'd seen all the
Wallace and Gromits but maybe I didn't see that one
because that doesn't sound familiar at all.
That is probably
that is one of my favorites
I would say
I've seen the wrong trousers
and I've seen the first one where they go to the moon.
The grand day out.
I thought I'd seen the third one too but
what you're describing
I have no recollection of a
of a dog made of robots.
I mean it's a reveal at the end
but like
I guess this is what he looks like.
Let me
This is where his skin has been torn off in the contraption
and you can see his robotness
I put a gif
Wait a minute
Yes
Yes I have seen
this creature
It's nightmare fuel
I was so small when I saw this one
It's the scariest movie I've ever seen
I agree
And Gromit there's
an amazing like night chase
on the motorway where
Gromit tries to save the sheep
on a motorbike
and Gromit tries to save all the sheep
and then there's another thing where like
Gromit gets a little
Oh it's so fucking cool
He gets a little aeroplane
with a porridge gun on the front
Oh the porridge gun
Yeah
I do definitely remember that
Well it's so Gromit
it's so fucking good
in any other franchise
It's better than the Avengers
Oh yeah
Iron Man couldn't do fucking shit about it
against Wallace
My dad
really liked
My dad really liked Wallace and Gromit
and I
as a kid I accidentally recorded
Pokemon over our copy
of the wrong trousers
My dad was really pissed at me
Why do I have that same memory?
Why do I have that exact memory
of the wrong trousers being taped over
and so we couldn't watch the beginning of it
I guess it's just one of those things
Just one of those things
Everyone has to deal with it
Every father has to deal with their child
taping over their copy
of the wrong trousers
Well that's it for this week
See you later
What do I got in my notes
What do I got in my notes for the week
Oh me and
I bought some more government bonds
I
I indulged in fiscal responsibility
and I purchased more eye bonds
and me and
Asterios
was like super stoked
to see me talking about eye bonds
on the Twitter timeline
He was like aww eye bonds
so much I called my mom about them
It's like cool man
Gotta have a hobby huh
Fiscal responsibility
I prefer video games
You know it's actually a pretty good hobby
because then you have money afterwards
after you get all done with it
I know you said don't talk to me about money
but guess what idiot I'm gonna
Did I think I've probably explained what eye bonds do before
but maybe
They you
you connect
a robot that deals
in currency to your eye
and then you can see the money
You can see the money
I could see this computer
I could sell that for $50
This bottle of water I could sell that for $0.50
I could take it all
I could zap it with my old VR gun
turn it into currency
An eye bond is a government bond
whose inflation
not inflation rate
What's the thing for when you put
your money in something
Interest rate is fixed to inflation
So last year
You know thanks to
Biden, thanks to Brandon
You know inflation was really high
So the eye bond return rate
was an unbelievable 9%
So
A 9% return on an investment
is like
You never get that, that doesn't even happen
But this was on a government bond
which is like one of the safest
and most stable
investments that a person can make
So it was like a no brainer
So I dumped as much money as I could
into eye bonds
And for six months I was getting that sweet sweet
9% return
It's you know and then
just the other day
at the end of April it was going to be
like a new period or whatever
So at this point
the interest rate is not 9% anymore
Now it's like almost 7%
Which is still pretty good
That's still pretty good
So I dumped some more money in there
to get that 7%
And then if it keeps going down
I probably won't continue to do eye bonds
But like for the time being
I'm putting as much money into eye bonds as I can
And just letting it
get as much interest as I can get out of it
Cause it's just you know
9% Gib
9%
It's very good
Considered from another perspective
It's not so much good
It's not so much like oh hell yeah
I'm gaining 9%
It's like if I don't put money in there
I'm losing 9%
Because inflation is devastating 9%
of the money that I do have
So you know
Either way you gotta do it
Conceived of the one way
It's like I got something
Conceived of another way
It's like I protected
a portion of my assets
from an inevitable devastation
So you know
Tomato, tomato
It's not that I feel bad about you doing it
It's a feel I feel bad about me
not being good enough
to do
organizing
Fiscal responsibility
It's never a bad time for fiscal responsibility Gib
It's never a bad time
Never a bad time
Just feel so pathetic
Here's the thing
Maybe I'm just a wacky weirdo
or something
I have gotten to the point
where I find discovering
money loopholes like fun
I like
I don't know I find it like a gratifying thing
to like
look into and learn about
Like I watch
I watch the YouTuber called Patrick Boyle
who is like an accountant or something
I watch Patrick Boyle
and learn about like the latest crypto
scams or whatever
and um
You know I was watching one of his videos
recently
and uh
it did occur to me
It did occur to me
that like really from any
from any rational
um
person's point of view any rational like
financial investor
like all this stuff that I do oh and putting my money
in I-bonds uh churning my credit cards
uh you know
using cash back programs and stuff
all of that is like
at the end of the day it's very marginal
that's me like doing scraping
whatever strategies I can together
to mitigate the effects
of you know like the true
the true horror
the true devastation that I face
which is that I just don't have just like
a real job
like a regular
person just has a regular job and a salary
and like
it's that's just like a million times more reasonable
than everything everything else
that I'm doing so everything else that I do
is just to try and mitigate the effects
of me not doing that
uh and I can pat myself
on the back for getting two percent cash back
or whatever all I want but um
you know
uh
yeah I mean
but like
it's it's good to do if you're in a
situation it is it's good it would be
it would be good to do it would be good to do no matter
what I mean if I if I was making
real money then
getting two percent cash back on all my spending
would be even better it would be an even
better thing to do
um so it's good
but yeah I was I was
listening to him it was listening to Patrick Boyle
and he did a one about he was talking
about the video was about
investment strategies
like
academic people
that recommend versus what like popular
like authors and like
influencers recommend
and how they don't always recommend the same things
and just yeah the emphasis
on the emphasis on like
planning for retirement and on like trying
to like hit a certain like savings
goal by a certain point in retirement
it's like wow
I haven't planned for that at all
I'm literally just
happy to I'm I'm I'm just
happy to have paid my
rent and not have less money
at the end of the year than I did
the year before that's success
to me and that's and
that's bad
that's not good
but
anything else just seems
so hard
like I would have to completely
upend my life
to do anything else
yeah
when I get old I'm just gonna hurl myself
off a cliff
I'm gonna make sure I'm live streaming it
that's my life insurance you've never seen
content like this before
just want to bounce sound
oh no
you know what Gib
I'll tell you this if it makes you feel any
better I wouldn't watch it
I wouldn't watch it I turn my eyes away
and say no I can't look
okay
yeah I don't know like things like
owning property
having a pension in any
fashion oh god a pension
doing like
well being
any amount of success
having
money at all
just doesn't make any sense
doesn't even register as a thing
until I'm reminded about
how I'm not doing it I'm like oh yeah
I understand
I don't know I guess it has become
sort of a hobby for me
looking into how to
how to how to
what's the word
how to squeeze as much
value as I possibly can
out of what money I do have
um
actually a stereos
okay a long time ago
we had um
cheesy just made a funny comic
I'm going to like it
I'm gonna hit like on that tweet
um a stereos
recommended to me
he recommended to me a couple of like bank
things he recommended me a couple of counts
that I could keep my money in
and that would earn like 4%
or like 4.25%
and I was like blown away by that
I was like how can it be
how can that be that high
because when we had um Minerva
Minerva double cast remember
is that her name is that her real name
or does she have a different name now
I remember double cast
we had double cast on because she I guess
is like a CPA or something and she was recommending
I think I asked her
about like what I should invest in and she recommended
like a market linked
fuck
was it like a market linked mutual fund
or something like that
and um I never really looked into that
because I'm stupid
a stereos said he had a couple of like
banks that offer like
4% and like that's crazy
because my bank
of America savings account which I've kept
my money in for my entire life
offers like 0.01%
interest
so nothing
um if I'd been man if I'd been
earning 4% I would have
that would that would be significant
that's a considerable
amount of money that I have basically
thrown down the drain
by using
a bank of America savings account like a fucking moron
so
you know the way I see it
the way I see it right
it's like
you
I can bemoan
that like oh I should have done that and then
I would have more money now like yeah true
yeah true but it's more
productive and a little bit more
what's the word
encouraging to look at it like
you're in a boat
and you're and the money
that you have
is the wait you're you're either
sinking or you're floating
and so if you manage to like if you manage to patch
a hole you know if you're
sinking now that's bad but if you patch
a hole you shouldn't you shouldn't bemoan the water
that's that's come in already
you patch a hole and you stop the leak
or whatever it's like no no no don't
don't get upset about the water that leaked in already
just feel good that you patch the hole you're doing better
now you're on it you're on it you've improved
your trajectory
um that's what I like to do I feel
like oh I can get I can get two percent
cash back instead of one point five bam
I've improved my trajectory because what that
means now is that I'll get
like that's like uh that's like an extra
hundred dollars that's like an extra hundred dollars
I'll get every year for the rest of my life
for doing nothing and then every time I find
a hack like that I feel like
that's an extra hundred dollars I'll get a year
every for the rest of my life well
that's a hundred dollars worth of work
that I don't have to worry about doing
ever again
uh that's why it's so gratifying
when I find a trick or a
cheat or something
uh yeah this is how
this is how it's
I make it fun for me
cheating the system
imagine if I get a job
imagine if I get a job and then I'm gonna get a salary
and I'm like oh to me they'll pay me like
twice a month I'm cheating this system so bad
I hacked it guys wait until
the people online hear about this
this this this incredible
life hack that I found you mean that capital
owners will just will just pay
you they'll just compensate you for labor
holy shit
uh
yeah
um I think I've said this
before I think I should I think I should
probably
I think I should probably look into
some form of real job
it may be maybe later this year
after after I do the
after after I do the the
the slime and punishment kickstarter and maybe
pump out one more lecture at that point I think
I might be like alright
time to start throwing my resume around
and see if I can't find a
a real job with benefits
and you know I can still do lectures
in my spare time I can still do the
I can still do the perfect comic
party in my spare time
uh but yeah
look like look like dental
look like dental insurance for instance
I thought you were gonna go yeah I'll
get a job being a dentist let's do that
no
no you know I could make a pretty good
dentist I've
put stuff on my teeth before I got a
pretty good bedside manner
I got a good old set of chompers
here I got a pretty decent
set of chompers I could do I have a couple
I mean I have a couple cavities that need
that need some work
what if that was how you get a dentist job
you come in you show them how cool your teeth are
how well you've brushed them
you come in and you're like here's my resume
yeah I graduated from dental school
uh I've been
you know interning at dental college
for years
give me a job and they're like hmm
but I see from your record that you haven't
you haven't lived the life you haven't had
enough cavities filled yet we're gonna have to drill
it you have to be on the other side
of the drill before we'll let you
we'll let you be on our side
so you know
open wide bitch
fucker
we're gonna root canalia
how can you how can you how can you trust you
to deliver a root canal
if you can't if you
can't take a root canal
I've just thought about what
dentist school would be like there's probably like skulls
all over the place and it's like alright
now fuck with this skull
alright now measure now measure the
the relative the width versus the height
you know determine determine its ethnicity
determine
determine this skull's ethnicity and it's
likely IQ
uh go do I need to know that
yeah uh for this school
you do here at
here at Hogwarts Dentistry
Hogwarts Dentistry
they just go wibbly wibbly splat
you've got no problems
yes and then it's done
and then so in their spare time
they just do phrenology they just
they just compare
various skulls
stupid most of them probably were
no the Hogwarts school would have a really bad
dental wizard
thing because it's British oh because it's British oh yeah
they would have a better
is there an American wizarding
school yeah there is
there is and it's like it's like
Native American themed I think
it's it's it's uh it's how
it's houses are based on like the
Thunderbird and like Quetzalcoatl and stuff
it's very it's very
strange I like
the Thunderbird just like Zaptos
my favorite Pokemon oh
American
wait let me look up American
psycho
no close
Ilvermorny
yes it is called oh god
it's called Ilvermorny and
it's houses are Thunderbird
Horned Serpent
Puckwudgy and Wampus
what
oh
JK you
JK
were you were you
were you high on Benzos
were you take were you were you
dropping Benzos when you came up with this
were you on Quailoos
were you were you taken
were you taken that that that Ivermectin
were you taken Ivermectin when you
heard it when you thought of Ilvermorny
I think we've I think we've cracked
the case here oh it's in Massachusetts
it's in Mount Greylock
in Massachusetts is that a real mountain
wait mount
grey
oh it is
wait how far how far is it from where I live
you're you're a confirmed muggle
you can't see it you can't see the castle
no that's not
that's not true I just didn't get my I
didn't get my letter by Thunderbird
what's
okay Mount
why is it on Mount Greylock
why that mountain
sounds cool does sound cool
Mount Greylock
Castle Grayskull
yes
from from my house
oh wow
okay it's on like the far west
edge of Massachusetts
so it's a it's a it's about
as far from me as anything in Massachusetts
can be but it's only a 40
oh no it's a 46 hour
walk yeah Lamal
it's a two it's a two-and-a-half hour drive
it's not even bad
America is so fucking big
well now well now I know
it's so crazy that
you you have such a huge country
and so much of your
infrastructure is road based when
that's so inefficient for such
large distances
I saw some
gas this is because you just have
so much gas but like Lamal
this was this was a while ago I saw
someone tweet about like
it was like stop
stop stop stop
comparing the US is like rail
infrastructure to like Europe's
and it was like
placed
and it like placed the like the US
against Europe and it basically the
point of it was it visually suggested
that like the US has more open
space and therefore rail
is more inefficient
and it's like literally the opposite
is true literally the more open
space there is the more necessary
the more if the more energy
like high-speed rail saves
like that's the reason you build it is
you traverse empty space efficiently
you build you're what you're
doing with a rail is you're building
like the most frictionless possible
road
ever have and you don't even need to
like worry about
swerving into a tree
yeah
no guys obviously better
no guys no guys it's it's much
more efficient to have every
in every individual like person or
pair of two people or three people
every every group of like one
person or more has to have
their own little vehicle that's powered
itself and spend its own gas to
individually traverse like 14 states
yeah
it just makes it just makes sense
it's just more
sensible
road trips on in principle
seem like a cool idea and they're
often romanticized
hmm
and I get it like if you just want to
drive to a specific location or just
like a camp
on the side of the road that is
you can't do with a train
but like yeah I don't know
maybe it should be just for road trips
if you I mean if you want to like
stop
like oh I need to get somewhere I have
to bring the car
it's like oh it's a fucking million
year drive
if you want to like stop all over the
place and see all kinds of things then
yeah a train
will not let you do that
or not not as easily
so yeah it's not it's not like I think
it's not like I think cars are just bad
but like yeah as
like as an argument
against trains like hey guys
but there's so much more space is like the worst
argument I've ever heard
um it's literally the opposite
of what you're of what you're trying
to say
um
they build trains all over China
and instead
they were gonna you know they were gonna they were gonna build trains
across California but then Elon Musk said
no no I'll build the hyperloop no no I'll build the hyperloop
I said okay
yeah it's funny when I learned that
is that the reason that hasn't
been plans put in place
is because Elon convinced the governmental
body or something
yeah like convinced enough people
to not invest in the rail network
because of what he was gonna do
and then he didn't do anything he just sort of
quietly abandoned the hyperloop
he's not doing anything anymore
I mean it is he's not talking about it
I mean it exists but it's
like stupid oh yeah
the final well
it was never said that that was the
final project but that is
the car tunnel that
one car tunnel wasn't that supposed
to be some different project
like I'm gonna put a tunnel under the
ground
and that was separate from
the hyperloop which was going to be
a specific motor transport
that may or may not have been under the ground
I don't know
and he had so many terrible ideas
he said 10
11 years ago he said in 10 years he'd put a man
on Mars
and now he's
explode in rockets
now he's exploding rockets and he's charging
$8 for
he's pretending that celebrities paid $8
for Twitter
that is odd
I assume you've seen the drill stuff
some of it yeah
I didn't realize I had been unfollowed
from him somehow I guess
something happened and I didn't notice
because I was following him and I wasn't
he specifically soft blocked
you he didn't like you
but I got back
I'm back and back
better than ever yes good
but yeah for a little while
there
he had a
blue check mark applied to his account
despite not paying for it
by Twitter
or maybe even by Elon specifically
also Stephen King
and LeBron James
and apparently there's a bunch of people with
like more than a million Twitter followers
people that had specifically said
no I won't pay for the blue check mark
Jason Alexander
uh yeah
I think Jacksepticeye
in a weird
stupid attempt I think
to make it look like
it's cool to have the check mark
yes
uh Lamana
see guys it's not
it's not just
weird crypto perverts
and Elon simps
and like mentally ill maga people
it's not just them it's also
people you like like LeBron James
and Stephen King it's cool
I promise
such a like a
if that wasn't Elon I'm pretty sure I would have been
an Elon idea like oh we've got to think of something
to do how about this
and then all the people that he didn't fire
because there's you know
they suck up to him I guess
would be like oh yeah sure
and it's like so short-sighted
he's no
like for such a future minded
you know like
really in the future like tech bro
wizard
he doesn't think very far ahead at
all for anything like he doesn't think
that oh as soon as these people realize
that they're subscribed to twitter blue
with the check mark even though they didn't want that
they're going to say something about it
and then it's going to be revealed
very very obviously
that this is
pathetic on twitter's part
I I mean
I read a think piece the other
day
actually it was like a long twitter thread
but it was essentially a think piece
and it was about
and it was about how elons
kind of like with the trains
in California
how like what the like
the thesis of this piece
what the pieces
if you will was that like
Elon makes money
by sabotaging
public works
and then like positioning himself
to profit off of their destruction
and like that's
what he did with you know
by just by destroying
plans for like high speed rail in California
you know he increased
you know the market value of like
things like electric car stuff
and Tesla and all that
and I don't know I think
this guy was kind of suggesting that maybe he's doing the same thing
with twitter like
by basically by destroying what was
basically
by deliberately destroying what was basically
the public square
of the internet he positions himself
to potentially to potentially profit
off it but I don't know about that because he literally
owns it he literally owns it himself
and has personal stake in it so I don't know
if you can really argue that he's going to profit off
of buying it
and then destroying it and then
somehow I know I think he actually
is just just fucking out I mean
I'm sure that was like
part of the reason he made the joke in the first place
is that
that's how he operates he just thinks
oh you know this car company
this Tesla car company
you know they're making electric cars
what if I was the guy
who was getting you know
I can have a piece of that
and PayPal
or whatever like he's always been
the guy involved
but not really
important to a lot of these
things that he's like
rolled up in but Twitter was a little different
because he got like
he didn't want to buy it
he got legally obligated to buy it
for extremely large sum
and you try as much as he could
you couldn't get out of it
and that is the funniest
I have seen reports
that there is um
I don't know I've seen
I keep hearing about all these like lawsuits
that are potentially being incurred
that Elon's Twitter is potentially incurring
and I just hope
every time I see one I'm like I hope this is real
hope this is really happening
I heard that like you know a bunch of like hate
speech laws in Germany
because you know Germany really doesn't like Nazi stuff
so like the fact that
Elon's Twitter is like so permissive of Nazi stuff
it's like pretty
has incurred a bunch of like lawsuits from like the German
government apparently
um what was another one
I'm sure there's more than that
I don't remember
um oh the
thing with pretending celebrities
bought the check mark is a thing called like false
false endorsement
or something like that
so like that's potentially illegal
which I hope he goes to jail
I don't know
he won't go to jail
I mean as long as the threats there and there's like a credible
like
potential
that somebody could actually file
for something because if there's a bunch of celebrities
they probably have lawyers
some of them will probably want to follow that up
and there's a lot of
like
deceased celebrities who still have
Twitter accounts that have been given the check mark
oh that's so cool
like Chadwick Boseman
Norm MacDonald I saw a tweet
posting them I'm like oh yeah
yeah there are states
so I'm not gonna be happy about that
oh that's awesome
that rules
I say estates but you know
whoever is involved family
anyone
hang on I need fans at least
I need a sparkling water
I'd never needed a sparkling water more than I need one right
okay I'm back
so
what else
what else to have on my list
oh yeah speaking of
being deceased
I got
really sick yesterday
like all of a sudden
I was
also I hope was there anymore
not to change the subject if you wanted to say
anymore about Elon
nah I don't like him that's it I don't want to talk about that boy
that little rascal
that little baby that little diaper man
yeah so I got super sick
like Friday night
and then I woke up in like the wee hours
of Saturday
like
how detailed should I be
well I don't know
I was I had a
I had vomiting and diarrhea
and I was shivering
and I was feverish
and I was alternatingly hot and cold
and I it was like really hot in my room
I turned my heater up really hot because I was shivering
but then I would get in my bed
and I would cover myself in blankets then I was like
like pouring sweat
that sounds like food poisoning
and or flu
you think it might have been food poisoning
I think that can happen with food poisoning
diarrhea involved
I thought it might have been that I ate something
bad but like I didn't
I didn't
well there was that one time
I was diet dumpster diving
for scraps
I didn't eat anything that weird
except I mean I was
I was making
I was doing licorice stuff
I was trying to create licorice
but there's nothing that weird in that
you made some fucked up licorice
I don't think I did there's nothing that weird in it
it's just and I had done it before
with all the same ingredients
and I had been fine
so I don't know why I would get
food poisoning this time
I mean it's just it's corn syrup
molasses
starch
flour
there was a lot you know food coloring
I mean it could just be flu
might have just been the flu
it was um
I'm pretty much fine now
I'm like I'm still kind of like
feeling like weirdly sweaty
about it but other than that
I don't feel that feverish anymore
it was just
all Saturday all Saturday
I was just in bed
I just could not get up
just don't get up
just try to sleep
it was exactly like when I had COVID
only COVID lasted like three or four days
and this was just like one day
yeah so
I had wanted
to get more Biscopades done
I thought I was going to do it on Saturday
Saturday was like okay I'm behind
I'm going to do it
and then I got sick and I wasted my whole day
and I couldn't do a damn thing
I did get some more done
I got a couple more pages done
I'm on page 13 now
I wouldn't count being sick as wasted day
you had to recover somehow
well it's wasted in that I didn't
get to use it for what I wanted to
sure
but I did get some pages done
I was going into Saturday
Friday night I was like
tomorrow
I'm going to spend the whole day
I'm going to get at least three more done
but I did
do more this week
so I don't feel too bad
I'm nearing
a point of being
like okay that's the chapter
done I don't know exactly when I'm going to
I don't know exactly what
I don't know exactly what moment
I'm going to end the chapter
on some like minor
cliffhanger probably
but anyway being sick was
bad felt very bad
didn't like it
I'm trying to think
if there's anything
there's nothing that weird
in the licorice
I mean probably wouldn't
be a licorice if it's like
if you have all the ingredients and none of them
will rancid or anything
it's just fine
it's all the same stuff
it's all the same stuff that I do
that I make candy out of
any other time
you probably just got like a COVID mini
maybe I mean I
I ate a very over right
banana
but it wasn't like rotten or moldy
it was just like brown and mushy
I put it in a pudding
I doubt a banana would have that
food poisoning is like raw meat
usually isn't it
meat that's not cooked well enough
chicken often
I come sort of
I cook all my meat
I swear I cook all my meat
I do I mean I eat
I mean I put bacon in my lentils
but I cook it in the rice cooker
and I think that's fine
I don't see as long as it looks cooked afterwards
I don't see why that would be weird
googling cooking bacon in rice cooker
I mean it's kind of boiling
bacon isn't it rather than
basically basically yeah
so like boiled ham like you can do that
okay odd but like
no no no I'm seeing recipes
I'm seeing recipes
on google that are like
yeah make stuff with bacon
in rice cooker
so
I should try that honestly I haven't tried that yet
it's it's
we got a little rice cooker
do you use it
for rice yeah
you know I haven't actually used mine for rice
so just lentils and
okay yeah pretty much all I use it for
is lentils
because like a protein
I mean what I like to do is
I'm sure it would
you know what's really good
rice
spam and sesame oil
that's a that's and salt
that's a winning combination
half spam
do you have sesame oil
love sesame oil
I had a friend
in California
I had a friend in California who had a
girlfriend
a Korean girlfriend who would make
she would make basically like sashimi
but it would be like rice
and instead of like fish or whatever
it would be a rice ball
on top of a slice of spam
cooked in sesame oil
and they were so good
yeah
that makes me want to make that
I don't even have rice
but I could get some
yeah I just
try to keep my protein up
so I try to
other than my candy stuff
now I try not to eat anything
that doesn't have protein in it
now I'm nervous
now I'm nervous that something I ate
made me sick and it's going to make me sick again
I mean other than like the ingredients
being
contaminated is the kitchen clean
yeah
the kitchen is cleanish
and I mean I haven't
maybe a rat pooped in it
my mom told me that when she was young
she got food poisoning
from like rat poop or something
cause like there were rats living in her kitchen as well
and she got food poisoning due to them
maybe I got rat poop
but I haven't seen a rat
have not seen a rat in several weeks
there's a cat living here in the house now
and I think it's scared the rats away
and somebody found like a rat nest
somewhere and got rid of it
so like the rat problem
while it would be overly optimistic to say that it's over
it's decreased
so you know I'd be
surprised
I'd be surprised if it were rat related
but I guess
you can't you can't
you can never be sure
what a life
hey you know what I did
I did the anime
do you want to see
I realized that I forgot a few
they're like
OVA's there was one about like a cellist
in the woods
and he has like a hallucination
slash little stories
with animals
and he's like the most best cellist
ever
and I liked that but I forgot to put it on the list
and I don't really think of it as like a show
cause it was like
no it was a film
I wouldn't have put it on the list
I wouldn't have put it on the list anyway
but then there was like
Treasure Island
an adaptation of Treasure Island
the Russian one
no it was the Japanese
sorry to interrupt but have you seen
Takashima
have you seen the Russian Treasure Island
I have not
Takashima's Treasure Island
yeah in 1978
it's got
I remember really liking it
I mean it's Treasure Island so I know the story
but like
really cool animation
what's the Russian one
wait no it's not Russian
ah fuck
maybe if I just look for weird treasure island
fucked up Treasure Island
yeah there's one
where the animation is just
so bizarre
oh no
oh it's called Treasure Planet
from 1982
obviously different from the Disney one I guess
yes
but it's funny that
there was another adaptation of Treasure Island
called Treasure Planet
much earlier
I'll just show you some screenshots
Treasure Planet
there's like a
Sakuga in this show the Treasure Island
in 1978
I just want to find a good gift
it's got the little leopard
leopard cub
here we go
anyway that would be high up on the list
oh look at that
wait what's this
oh this is Treasure Island
this is pretty cute
wait
he's not
hang on I'll just post the link
it's so much better in motion
yeah I thought it was a wheelchair
yeah this is a real movie I've watched this movie
if you remember
what was that fucking show
that I did
if you remember
The Fleet Pit
if you remember Live at the Fleet Pit
I reviewed this movie on that
and it's kind of
you know it all
it all looks like this
yeah is the jerky
motion of the arms
but like the face
is like a single image that they're obviously
just shifting around
there's
moving around
making me feel like South Park almost
there's lots of gifts
and I don't know
I could post more
but you get the idea
but anyway
do you want to look at my list here
yes
my challenge list
I actually have
watched a lot of anime
I kind of forgot
I've seen more than
60 of them
I was on my
stream
and I had to ask stream people
to remind me about
anime that aired around
a certain time
of my life
and people just threw out lots of suggestions
and most of them I was like no never heard of it
no never heard of it
and they'd be like oh yeah that one
like oh yeah Cromartie High
oh yeah Big O
oh yeah Steel Angel Karumi
Paranoia Agents
Lupin
yeah oh my god
wow there's so many
yeah
kind of too many
to like go over
I felt bad for
everything that had to go up
against Fuli Kuli like early on
like Barakaman
and Garzi's Wing
and Ultimate Survivor Kaiji
all get knocked out really early
even though those are all really good
just because it's Fuli Kuli
Fuli Kuli did end up winning
unsurprisingly
but in the second to last round
I did have Fuli Kuli vs Gurren Lagann
oh my god Madoka Magica
I did watch that
I forgot that one
Golden Boy vs Madoka Magica
was really hard too
I kind of hated
knocking Golden Boy off
I think I tried to watch the first episode
was that the space one
it's the space one that's like 500 episodes long
I've watched half of it
a lot of the one
that was on this list I've only seen a little bit of
most of them I've seen at least
most of them I've watched all of
a lot of them I've just watched
like a decent amount of
like Jojo Part 3
I've seen most of it I haven't seen all of it
but I counted it
a couple of them
I'd only seen a little bit of
like Steel Angel Karumi
I think I watched like 2 episodes
I don't remember what it's about at all
I've watched this list really fast
did I put Death Note on mine?
I think I did
I don't remember
there were
what the hell is those who hunt elves?
those who hunt elves
I don't know it's like some stupid
like fantasy
show about a group
it's like a weird etchy
like fantasy
comedy about some
you know
it's like a fantasy world where
they
they have to
they don't hunt the elves
I think what they do
is they have to find out who is an elf
and who is not an elf
and it's straight up just like
to see if you're an elf they have to like look at their tits
or something
it's about like stripping people
and like looking at them naked to see if they're elves
because elves have like a magic tattoo
or some shit like that
intriguing
yeah
yeah that one didn't
I don't think that one made it very far
no it was immediately
defeated by kill a kill
oh another one sided
match up there
um
let's see let me look for some other
Azumanga Dio
no I don't think I've seen enough of that to count it
I like Azumanga Dio
I haven't really seen Nietzsche Joe
or that's like that in Azumanga Dio
are like kind of similar
people tell me Nietzsche Joe you should watch
and I'm like I've seen
when it was coming out
or around like earlier
I'm like oh I've seen gifts of that
I've seen when she suplexes a goat
or something
I've seen like funny like
oh it's like a little cute girl
but she is like animated
and over the top fashion
to deliver some sort of
punch
or something and I'm like yeah I get it
I don't need to watch that I get it
that's the joke
it sure is
people always say oh it's so fucking wacky
and I'm like well is it fun
is it nice is it cute is it wholesome
is it anything other than wacky
and they never say anything
because I don't remember just to tell them
oh dear
that's not good
I'm sure it's fine
probably might be a pretty hot take
here but I had
I have
Excel Saga Beats Lucky Star
in my first
I liked Lucky Star but
I don't know what Excel Saga will say
I liked Lucky Star fine
Excel Saga is like a
it's like a parody anime
about like
I don't know
it's
God how do I even
it's a comedy about
these girls
who join an evil organization
bent on world domination
and basically every episode is like
their stupid boss
sends them on some mission to like
here's how we're gonna
it's like pinky in the brain like how are we gonna take over the world
this time pinky
and every episode is like they try to take over
the world in a way that
parodies like some very specific like anime genre
like they try to take over the world
by going to the beach
and being the hottest girls on the beach
or they try to take over the world by
having a
there's a post apocalypse desert
where you have to ride motorcycles around
and do a fist of the north star
type stuff etc etc
and it's just
fucking funny and wacky and you know what
it left a bigger impression on me than
lucky started so it
wins
chris chan famously was a big
excel saga fan
which gave a lot of points obviously
i notice you have
jojo part three but no other parts
i have only i have not seen any other parts
is jojo jojo seems to be one of those
anime where like different seasons of
the show are considered different things
yeah
so like you can say oh i love jojo
part two but if you just
say i love jojo's bizarre adventure
people will always ask
a follow up questions like well which part
yeah i mean
as opposed to like any other show where it's like
a long running show that has
like arcs wait actually
now i might be confused
i might not even be talking about three
i'm talking about the one that has
um josuke and
shining diamonds that might
be four actually i might be i might be on
on weed
but yeah
i know i've heard of like what happens
in the early jojo parts and it doesn't even
sound like remotely similar
to what happens in the later ones
so you know
whatever
yeah what's golden boy
golden boy is
okay it's been a long time since i've seen
golden boy it's an ove it's a six episode
ova about this guy
who like bikes around
japan
like taking odd
jobs
and every episode every episode he
meets like a sexy girl
who he who he goes all like
whoa how about how about how about
who yeah
for um and
and uh
you know he just does like
he acts like a fucking idiot and a fool
and stuff in pursuit of this lady
and uh i don't know he'll usually
he'll like take a job working for her company
or something trying to get
trying to get with her and uh
it always ends with like
oh he he does some he does
some like incredible like grand
gesture to like
for her but then he like loses hope
that that she'll like
him so he runs away in the middle of
the night never to be seen again and then she's left
like oh but he was but he was like a secret
genius though even though he was such a
fucking moron he was such a secret
genius and oh i'm in love with him now but i'll never see
him again um
yeah i don't know
that's that's going boy there's
there's a famous
scene of him like
trying to swim
and he like can't swim
hang on golden
boy
swimming
yeah here we go
how yeah how's my swimming here we go
i'm gonna show you this video and there's nothing
you can do
do about it
okay yeah i'm sorry
here you here you go
oh
that's you unavailable
what video is
not available what
comments are turned off
what okay
are you not seeing it no it's it's
available for me all right well let's try the
different what no fun must be
must be a region
okay okay this this one will work this one this
one will work definitely i'm
seeing it yeah okay i think i may
from that frame
i think i may have seen this depicted
in a video
okay
he's dead
it's the sound
effects
the voice acting is so good
did you uh did you get to the
how do you like my swimming
oh yeah i think you've seen the end
so how do you like my swimming
how do you like my swimming
yeah um
so so that's golden boy
uh and i thought it was really
funny and uh i like
it
hell yeah um
what what else what else
um oh you're you're sort of
robotting on me no
let me close
those tabs um okay
i'll also close those tabs
oh you're fine
wow it worked
it was just just like that
um
sure okay
shin shin chan shin chan
beat witch hunter robin but was
defeated by gur and logan
yeah i i
have um
are there are there any are there any on here that you recognize
that you like had forgotten about
uh other than
i mean i recognize a lot i
recognize zatch bell but i think i was reading
the manga for that for a while and i didn't watch
the anime i never finished it but i like
zatch bell a lot
yeah little babies
little babies and um freaking
uh victorim remember victorim
i don't know
that i do the guy the guy
like the fucking edgy dark
baby no that's um
victorim is the guy
he's the one who's shaped like a
V and he
sings that like song about
like
he's like the ultimate
badass puppet man
but like the way
that they defeat him is they just they offer
him some melon and he's like is so
happy to receive a gift of
melon that he like sings a song about
it and they defeat and he's
defeated oh yeah i don't think i got this far
in that's like
that's like maybe like the the most i've
ever laughed at an anime or like
it's it's it's up there it's in like top 10
anime moments
um
what
have you seen have you seen a chromarty high
is that the one with
the
the walking down the hallway
okay okay okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah we re we replicated
that at radcon one or two
oh yeah but have you seen it though
no that's good
it's very funny
um
yeah there's lots of things i've heard about
watched a couple episodes of on chibi backers
maybe um
oh wait i didn't include s cry
ed no
show that i always say is kind of good
yeah
damn it
ah
fuck no
instead of steel angel karumi
um
the only one that i realize i didn't
put on the list here was medica magica
and i don't have a lot of like
i don't have a lot of like oh
what you thought this was better than
that moment like i don't have that
yeah i guess if you don't know most of these
um i was bummed that
that tatami galaxy got knocked out
like immediately
and i felt a little weird
like having soul eater beat it
you ever seen soul eater
i watched
no no we for chibi backers we watched three episodes
i like so i think
i like soul eater a lot
uh i thought it was really good
i thought the ending
was really the ending is really shit
it has a really shitty ending
it they kind of do the thing how in like
in the original full metal alchemist anime
they just completely change the
ending to something else because like the
manga was still going they do that with soul eater
but instead of being cool like in out
full metal alchemist it's it sucks
um yeah i've heard
lots of things about soul eater's
endings yeah it's just dumb
um but it's a good show
but i like tatami galaxy a lot too
and i would usually give the edge to a
show that's shorter like tatami galaxy is
like a short ova which basically
makes it automatically better in most cases
but i don't know um
what i remember most about tatami galaxy
is just like its art style
and like the the plot
itself i like remember
it but i don't remember it that
well i just i have a lot more
like oh yeah remember
what when that happened oh yeah remember
that character from soul eater
so i had to give it to soul eater
which is very strange
yeah oh yes this one
i've seen clips of this one a lot
tatami galaxy oh yeah
yeah very it's a cool cool
looking show cool looking show
by the way i don't know if i mentioned
uh the last time i had
with with the um the list
i hadn't finished utana
now i have oh
how was that revolutionary
revolutionary girl utana is
um
something that immediately needs
a big long analysis video
afterwards because i don't get it
you don't you're not you're so
fucking thick with
uh insinuation themes
but like insinuation
and metaphor rather than
over like direct dialogue
um so
insinuation of
sex
uh yes i mean there's literal sex
that are there's lots of
it's it's not um
yeah i can't really speak
on the themes even though
i watched some good videos
even trixie's old video was good
on utana
on utana there was a comment
under it it was like oh i always thought it was
like a woman's perspective of utana
and haha turns out i was right lol
pretty funny pretty
drool yeah um but then
there was another one another two or three
that i watched i was like okay
i think i get it but i couldn't
recount it i couldn't like tell you
what utana is about all i know is
uh i loved it
it was great it's very tragic
and very soulful
and um
but like uplifting near the end like
it's sort of like a it's a cliff
hanger like not a cliffhanger but sort of
like a you don't really see
what happens at the very end but like
if you follow the themes and what
you know the show is
telling you oh like how
like how in the green night you don't actually see
him cut his head off
yes
like if you if you take what
the show is telling you
non-directly you can figure out
basically what is what's happened and you're
like okay the movie
um
is apparently like a clusterfuck
of weird shit
takes place in a parallel version
of the the show rather than
simple
like movie that is a retelling of the
show with a bit more animation
uh so i i haven't watched
that yet but i want to
um and yeah i like utanela
it's
very fucking sick
i'm
i'm eating i'm trying a new
recipe instead of
a gummy i'm trying to make like a chew
like a starburst sort of chew
and i'm trying to make
a version of it that does not like
melt you know it doesn't like
deform just from holding it
and
um
i think it needs it needs something
it's it's kind of like
it's kind of like a tootsie roll
but you can't just like pack tootsie rolls into
into a bag they're all like melt together
they'll stick together they might need to
be like coated in something
mirror oil talcum powder
talcum powder
maybe just like a corn starch
maybe just a simple a simple corn
starch powder
yeah powdery something or other
might do it
maybe maybe just like
a little bit of gelatin just a small
amount of gelatin just to kind of make
it hold its shape
that might be that might be like a
gelatin shellac
well i told you
that um shellac is the
thing that they put in starburst right
and oh no you didn't
yeah um i found this
out i was looking at starburst ingredients
and one of the ingredients is
well it's called quote unquote
confectioners glaze
and what confectioners glaze is
is shellac it's
the stuff that they that they that you coat
wood with which if you didn't know
is an excretion of a certain
insect the lack bug
excretes this goo that you
coat wood with and
that they that they put in starburst
but they don't call it that
because it sounds gross in food
in food they call it confectioners
glaze but it's the same bug
goo
well we've been eating bugs this whole time
yeah
and you know what
i'll do it again
i'm okay with it
i like starburst are we thinking of the same
thing starburst
the red and orange and pink and yellow
ones
starburst the tiny little
cuboids with
wrapping paper around each one
cuboids
yeah
and they come in they come in lemon and
strawberry and cherry and orange
uh yeah
i mean in the uk there's different flavors
there are apple ones
what strawberry black
berry orange
no if it's not
yeah
i can show a picture of such a thing
what the fuck
wait a minute
are you sure these are starbursts and not now and later
uh i don't know
i mean i know that strawberries are like the most
the default
starburst
are you sure the okay okay
are you sure these aren't like some like
other flavor
you can get like skittles but you can also get like
tropical skittles or berry
skittles
um i suppose so
i mean i i don't know
hang on
i'm just i'm just i mean i'm in shock and awe
here because i mean
i remember having pear flavored starburst
pear i mean that sounds
i wouldn't i wouldn't really think about being like
i mean yeah that sounds great just
to me to me like
this this this flavor
i mean i would say that's like
yellow pink orange red
is like
this is this is this is starburst and everything
else is a
i mean i would say that's
like yeah more common
i guess
i would always leave the lemon ones i think
i didn't like lemon the lemon it was the orange
i didn't like
strawberry is my favorite
i like the ice yeah but then i also really
like the apple ones i think lemon is the least
good but they're all good i don't like
leave any of them hang on
um
oh my god
uk u k starburst
a comparison
i'm just yeah i think i think
the main ones were like strawberry and blackberry
were the like the two flavors
and then orange
and lemon
so i guess it was just cherry that was the
strawberry and blackberry
so i guess it was just cherry that was different
instead of cherry i had
wait a minute
so british they okay they have an orange
a cherry lemon lime
combo and what's the what's the purple
and grape
blackberry or grape some i think
is blackberry
blackcurrant yeah
blackcurrant okay i'm glad it's not
grape because grape sucks grape is like the
worst flavor of anything
yeah um i love blackcurrant
blackcurrant is my like
i always think of blackcurrant is like the staple
the staple like
confectionary flavor is blackcurrant
wait wait wait okay so your red
is your red is cherry
no no your red is strawberry
our red is cherry and our pink is
strawberry so that's so that's wacky
wow i didn't know this
damn i want to try these i want to try these
blackcurrant starbursts
sounds oh yeah sounds pretty good
actually yeah i think the apple ones
i was thinking of were like the sour
chew-its chew-its
yeah chew-its you know
chew-its no
is it like chicklets they're
they're very similar they're like cuboids
with individual wrapping just a different
brand and
they had a sour
what what's wrong with cuboids they're not
cubes i mean they're not rectangles i guess
they're tech i guess you're technically right they
are cuboids
they are i would call them squares
i'm just gonna say i would call them squares
nah all right cuboids
is funny all right um
chew-its had like
a dinosaur mascot
and it would be like ah i'm
a dinosaur and i love chew-its
so much oh wow he really would eat them
there's another there's another thing
called now and later's
which are very similar to a starburst but
they're really hard
they're really hard and you pretty much have to
suck on them for a while until they become soft
enough that you can chew on them
where is the
the dinosaur
where's the dinosaur
google
where's the dinosaur they have
that like it looks
like a really old advert
over like a
Godzilla looking like live
action puppet dinosaur and then there's
a more recent like
redone like cartoon
it was a specific cartoon
look at look at look at this thing
look at this uh
when i when i'm
doing these searches i keep finding the same
uh google image result
um for
single green mic and ike incredibly rare
masculine shape for female
pleasure
what?
this has popped up multiple times on my google
searches now
mic and ike
an incredibly rare masculine shape
you know mic and ike's
i yeah i know of them
i don't think i had one
okay they're fine
masculine shape masculine shape
for female pleasure so true
so true
uh this is the advert alright
i'm gonna post that
advert hopefully you can see it
you know what
yeah
this is
chew it i like to
i like to chew it chew it
okay let's give it a watch
i like the ChewIt
oh, it is
its the song we were thinking of
in the episode
he likes to share it
and
I
Thought that song was about Chewitt's and then I heard it in the Madagascar movie and I was like what why they put the Chewitt's
Why they put the Chewitt's song in Madagascar?
That's that's advertising this this Chewy this Chewy substance that I've made I
Think it's pretty good. I think it's maybe a little too much cornstarch
The
Consist the chewiness the consistency is about right but it's a little bit like it's firm
But like it like if you hold it it's sort of like deforms and starts to kind of like droop and I would rather
I'm thinking maybe yeah, maybe just a tiny bit of gelatin
Or sh or maybe maybe you can buy shellac in flakes. You have to buy it in flakes. Maybe wax. Maybe carnauba wax
Flavors good though
The first one I made had too much acid. It was too sour
Too sour and not sweet enough too starchy
So in this time I replaced half the starch that I added I press half of it with with a confectioner sugar
Which um I had forgotten about confectioner sugar. It turns out
It turns out that yeah when you just add sugar to a solution sometimes it becomes gritty and crystalline
Great way to not have that happen. It's just use confectioner sugar because it's finely ground and it's and it's powdery
They've solved this problem for me and I had forgotten
I'm a genius
Okay
Candy, what was the other one fruit teller?
Fruit teller was like fruit the non super sweet, but still quite tasty fruit flavored
cuboid snack
Hugh Brits and your in your cuboid snacks
We love cuboids over here. I have never seen a fruitella
We have fruitopia
We got fruitella. We got nutella. Now these ones. What else have we got? Now these ones have you a green apple
raspberry
lemon and
Black blackberry
Looks pretty good
Yeah, oh and then the the box has it has fruit, but the fruits are all square or cube
Yeah, like the products just the product so the product no
No, they only becomes a cube if you combine two of them together and squish them you take them out of packaging
You push them together. They molecularly bond to become one cube of the product. Oh, these are these are gelatin free
Wait, these are gelatin free wait, so what's in them?
Fruit no
No, they're veggie. They're vegetarian, which means they don't contain gelatin wait, okay. I have to know
fruitella fruit fruitella recipe ingredients
it
Glucose syrup sugar fully high okay fully hydrogenated coconut oil
Fruit juices from concentrate wait beef gelatin
Oh
Traitor
Well that other one said it was gelatin free. I mean maybe there's different
Yeah, you'd have to come and buy one find out
Look at the packaging numbers gum Arabic
Gum Arabic
Glisser all
Okay, all right, how to make fruitella at home Wow, I I think I have mentioned this
I have looked up um how to I have looked up recipes for licorice at to make it yourself and all the recipes that I find
involve like milk and eggs and
it's like so
Fucking stupid like that's obviously not what you're buying. Yeah, they all involve like like like condensed milk and
fucking eggs and shit
Like fresh eggs
It's like give me a break
Is that for like the bonding agent or something? Yeah, it's just stick it together
Yeah, probably it's probably like I mean, I'm sure it tastes fine
But it's not that's a cake. They're making there's them. That's a that's a dang cake
I mean the end result looks pretty good
You know you try you it gets this this paste this sticky like paste and you cut it into you know
Cuboids or whatever and I'm sure it's fine
But it's not you know, I want something that keeps on the shelf for ever and that you know make it with eggs
It's not gonna do that
Now hang on
Fuck
Shit, I was gonna look I was gonna look something else up, but I forgot
Oh well, oh
well
Yeah eggs eggs, I guess are just like
something that
Eggs, I guess are like there's something they're a good
They're a bonding agent that anyone would have in their kitchen
Like if you're just for a home cook or just a hobbyist or just someone who's like bored and wants to do make something in their kitchen
Like yeah, a recipe that involves eggs is like yeah, sure just go go nuts use eggs
Just like just like financial
Advice it's exactly like financial advice
Because you know I was watching that video by Patrick Boyle and he said
that like a lot of the like popular financial advice that like authors recommend is
stuff that
is kind of just wrong
But a lot of it is wrong in a way that is designed to like
Sort of account for the fact that like humans are stupid and
Don't behave correctly and what I mean by that is like example a lot of popular
Financial advice tells you to pay down your smallest debts first
Like if you have debts
Find the one that you have that's the smallest and pay that one down first
Whereas like
The right thing to do
By any metric is to pay down the one that has the highest interest rate
But I guess a lot of authors will tell you pay down the smallest one first because it's like
Psychologically if you successfully knock one off the list it like feels better
Right and so it's like
Kind of not
Right, but maybe it might get people to behave in a way that gives
It might you know might get them to stick with it better
Uh or something
even though it's not
Mathematically optimal
Um
Good thing I always do the mathematically optimal thing
I don't have to worry. I don't have to worry about that. Yeah, so true. It is so true. It is so true though
um
Let me look at my let me look at my notes. Let me look at my stupid notes
I played a video game
This week
Oh, yeah, yeah
Did I mention that I found?
phantom's revenge on some other website?
You did. Yeah
I mean, let me let me let me see if I could find it
Wait, no, I don't know if you did
You probably
I vaguely remember this but I think it might oh I might be confusing it for something else
But I don't know what else so maybe I did hear it. Wait a minute
Okay, no, no, I was I was thinking of I was thinking of the pump run away from snakes was found on other websites because it didn't have
It didn't have a link. It didn't have a
My name or charlie's name in the game itself
So there's no way to get like recognition for that. Oh really? Damn. Yeah, let's see. So for for for
uh, the the
Pumpkin alley it starts with our names
And there's names like in the credits
So even if it ends up on other sites and I think it has the little demo we made fridge
Uh, we've still got credit. There's links within the game itself two things that we've done
Yeah, phantom's revenge is like that. It says it's by ben saint and like there's links to like read the comic and stuff in it
So I'm not I'm not worried about
Yeah, it getting stolen or misattributed or whatever. Yeah, it's here on on soft tonic
On soft tonic.com. There is a web page
And yeah, they have their own write-up
Of the game. It's not they didn't just copy paste my write-up. They wrote
They wrote their own. She's kind of
Interesting here. I guess I'll just post the link. Why not?
um
Apparently 68 people have downloaded it from this website, which is interesting
Uh free download. I mean, it's free anyway. So yeah, yeah, it's free
On itch as well
uh
Okay
They are from indie for game developer ben saint. So they do credit you. Yeah. Yeah, they say developer ben saint over on the right side
You know, I mean whatever like I'm not not upset about it
With its content and the variety of activities for you to do phantom's revenge is a
Thoroughly enjoyable experience true for indie gaming fans. So true
Ooh, it is somewhat comparable to mother of many or limbo
Yeah, oh the colorful or more graphic aesthetic to it. I okay. I read this write-up and I went first of all limbo sucks
second of all, uh, I was curious about mother of many
So I went and I go and I and I downloaded mother of many and I played it
and
it was
interesting
But it was not what I wanted it to be. I was kind of disappointed in it
Yeah, I played mother of many and from the screenshot that they showed on this website
Uh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Here. Here is here was the screenshot
And I thought from this that you would be playing as like that it would be like a side scrolling
Action adventure or beat them up where maybe you would like control like a squad of mice
And you're like their mother or something and you're like commanding them to like fight for you
Uh, that's this was wrong. This was not the kind of game. It was at all. It was actually a 3d
um, I don't even know like a horde
Based like first person
shooter
Basically you play mother of many
And you start the game and when you get to the actual game part of it
you're in an arena and zombies just zombie mice just start like
encroaching into the arena from the sides and you have your little scythe that shoots beams
and you have to
You know, you just have to fight back the hordes
And you know, they come like faster and faster and more and more and bigger and stronger of them
And you know, you get experience points from the ones you kill and as you get as you level up
you get to choose this sort of like a roguelike element to it where like
You know, you're choosing which upgrades to get and that that changes your play style a little bit
And basically the the goal is just like, you know survive 15 minutes of
fighting this horde off and it's fine
The gameplay is a little shallow
Uh
Aesthetically, I guess it looked pretty good
It has like an it's you know, the like eastern european
depression simulator
They look cool in this screenshot. There's only there's only one actual mouse
There's only one actual mouse in the game and it's uh, this one
Yeah, it's frankly. There's not enough mice
But she's the mother of many, right? No
She is not the mother of many. She is your sister
And sister of one
I'm not I'm not clear on if the mother of many is like your mom
Or like the goddess of the woods
I think it's both
Anyway, the point is you're bringing your sister out to this like
secret place in the woods to
To kill her and sacrifice her so that her blood will nourish the land and like your crops will grow
And uh, and when you try and cut and cut her, uh, she gets possessed by the mother of many and like summons all these demons
You got to fight the demons
And it's good
Yeah, I'm I'm I'm just noticing on your thing. There's like
Translated versions at the bottom
What?
Like
Yeah, it says program available in other language. I think they just translate the page
Not the game itself
I'm curious if you can tell like if it's been downloaded from another country. Wait a minute
Like on your soft tonic page like at the bottom it's like oh phantom's revenge Korean Italian
It's it says in in the details list that it's like oh, yeah on the Spanish page. It says that the game is in English
So I'm it would be so fucked up if like they had actually like gone into the code and translated the
The game into no no, I wouldn't expect that would be amazing sort of like I'm I'm interested because it doesn't say
On those different pages the number of downloads
But does that mean that if somebody from from korea did download it it would say one
I
think it's probably
quite likely
that
Nobody has downloaded this game from the
Italian
A web web version of the web page
I would be funny though. It'd be so funny
Yeah, because because this
hypothetically is like
Exposing you to so many different markets. Yes that you would never have I'm I'm I'm truly am mr. Worldwide
Hey
Oh, there's a polish page
Ah, no downloads
Oh, Netherlands
It's just so funny seeing like
In in the midst of uh different language texts the things that are state english are like my little pony tonic the headshot
Strong youtuber
Yeah, what is this? This is great. It's the japanese page
Uh
Katana's wayende pony
What and it's never
Oh in in mezlim door drink there in katana's wayende pony meet an attitude
Ha ha ha
Pony with an attitude a katana wielding pony with an attitude. I'm pretty sure is this exactly what the english version says
Oh, yeah
Like what is the a vietnamese?
Sure. Why not a pony a pony slasher with a story
Well, I didn't know vietnamese
looked like that
It's like mostly arabic characters not arabic. Um, I'm thinking of arabic numbers. Um
Like what are these characters called? They're not the they're not like diacritics
You're talking about the ones with the weird like symbols above the letters
No, is there a way to to like
Categorize like types of
text
What like in in asian languages they have like symbols like this but a lot of
European languages share letters like abc
Uh
Vietnamese apparently has like stuff that looks more western
I mean i'm looking at what I think is the vietnamese page and it looks like all the letters are yeah
Basically, you know arabic not arabic. Um, yeah, yeah, I thought that's what i'm thinking. What's the word for that describing that?
Did they did did vietnam just like not have their own like written
language until they
Or maybe they didn't have like an alphabetical language. Maybe they only had like a pictographic language
I don't know. I don't know
Yeah, weird weird that they have
This this is their written
System what's up with that
What's up with that
What's up with that? I mean, I don't know that it's vietnamese. It just has the thing vi
Next to it. I mean, it says what else could that be? It's yeah
What else what else could could it possibly be? I can't think of anything
Okay, french colonial rule of vietnam led to the official adoption of the vietnamese alphabet
Which is based on latin latin script. That's what i was thinking of there we go
Interesting so french are the reason for that
Now we know they strike again
Um, I have let me see have I gotten through my entire list yet?
Mmm illness mother of many anime bracket bonds
Website down the last thing I want to say this week is that my my website is down
Did you hear about this by any chance?
Uh, yeah, yeah, uh jesse dmca
dmca reported uh saint comics dot com for hosting the plebe and the weave
Uh, uh blu-ray vials
Lemau
Yeah, yeah, I just I just I just have to say I just have to say how funny I think it is
that rather than
rather than
make the blu-rays
or
Let me give him money to let me sell them. He has elected instead to pay a lawyer to uh
He's paid paid money to bury them pay money to to prevent them from seeing the light of day
Uh
I know I did you are you aware that I offered him a cut that I said just let me let me give you a cut of sales
And and let me keep selling and he said no
Uh
I wasn't aware of that exchange. I guess it was in dm. So it was it was in dms
It was in dms that would have been like a maybe a month ago or maybe two something like that
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I mean well, uh, so
Yeah, he hired a guy
He hired a guy who does dmca takedowns for 50 bucks a pop
I I looked into the uh, I got I got a letter and I looked into who sent it and it was this this one guy
And I looked at his website and I was like, hmm interesting
uh, so
the website my website's down
I just need a new host which is
Actually the way the way it worked out
is is like
It's kind of good that something happened to make me switch hosts because my old hosting was on like
I had I had picked a really bad plan
The plan I had picked was like month to month and I was paying like $14 a month to host my site
Uh, you know, I switched hosts. That's that is quite a lot. It was quite a lot. It was I
It was not a good I I screwed I screwed up
So I have picked the new plan that I've got I've locked in a rate. It's gonna be like
It's gonna be like $3.99 a month for a while and then it'll go up to like $8.99
In like a year or two
so
That's fine. The website's down for the moment. It'll be back up in I don't know a week or two
Probably not even that long
so whatever
No, no biggie. No problem. And you know, I gotta say
I did
I never really intended to leave the plebeian the weeb stuff up on my store page forever
You know, it's not like
You know, it's not really germane to the content of my personal website
Yeah
So so what I mean, you did also say that nobody was buying it anymore
Oh, yeah, I mean
A couple people bought them like the last minute when I said I was almost out
Uh, so my my you know, I had I had a couple copies left. I said guys I'm almost out
You know a handful more people bought them and now I'm out and so it's all good
the
you know
but you know
I just
After after that
When I said, okay, they're free now
If they're free to download now, it's it's so it was no longer about the money. It was no longer about selling them or making money
Uh, uh, and it's I don't know. Don't you think it's weird?
Don't you think it's weird and wacky that like the dmca takedown didn't come until like
After I'd already said I'm not selling them anymore. They're free now
Don't you think that's weird and wild and wacky and wonderful? I don't know. I mean
Is it is it not
could you
I'm trying to think if there's like a reason a dmca has to be against something digital
Because you're hosting a digital file as opposed to
Having a store where you can buy something and maybe that's different
uh
What do you mean?
Uh, well, I don't know like like a dmca against your site
Would not prevent you from having physical stock that you could mail to people who dm you on anywhere
No, but a file hosting
You can you can you can block that from existing
Yeah, I don't know. Yeah, I mean maybe there's a difference in in something like that. I mean
You know, I don't know all I'm saying is um
I guess I I just I just really feel
That jesse's whole attitude about this thing
is completely irrational and and very stupid and and wrong-headed and like
He seems to have felt from the very beginning
that I am
stealing from him
and and uh
victimizing him
and
I don't know. I just I just think that if you take a step back and look at it
Like the the fact that this is happening now after this stuff was already free
I'm just I'm not even selling them anymore. I'm just offering it for free
I literally just did I did his job for him and I made the blu rays and I
Completed that work for him and I said anyone can have them and it's free now. Don't worry about it
And then he gets lawyers involved and then he sends his dmc a takedown takes my website down
it just I don't know it just really kind of uh
just really kind of uh
Highlights that like
There really was no need for any of this
You really could have just been normal about it and not been a little a little little baby bitch about it
and just and just not uh fucking
Just don't be such a spaz. I don't know. He's been a real spaz about it the whole time. That's that's my opinion
um
and uh, you know
Sorry
Uh
Just there's no point. There's no there's no actual harm being done and I don't really think there ever has been
Uh, and that's my line and uh, we'll never uh, I will never recant it
That's what I have felt all along and I continue to feel that way
Uh, but oh well, you know, I guess none of that matters in the face of 50 dollars
Given to a guy to send a letter to uh to a web host
I don't know what else to say about it
I don't like it
um
Anyway, that's anyway, that's why my website's down
I I know I know, you know, I know my site is like a huge a hugely popular
buzzing hive of activity
I know it's a thousand people a day are like are checking it to read
Beescapades to get caught up on Beescapades so that when the next chapter drops and the perfect comic party
They'll be caught up. I don't know what's going on and a thousand people a day are like, where's where's the website?
I can't read Beescapades. I can't read. I can't
Read slime and punishment to understand the context behind phantom's revenge
And I just want you to know that I'm I'm with you and I'm working on it
And um, the problems will all be solved soon. We will put all this silliness behind us
Okay, that's all I have to say okay, okay
Sorry, I was just looking at my currently operational website and I was just
No, don't look at that
I was looking at my links that I have to from my Clarissa to buy the Clarissa book
I'm like, I can't wait can't wait to add a new link
Well, I guess it'll be the same link, but I guess it'll send the link to like the the page of Clarissa volumes rather than the single one
I think um, I think it'll be like, ah, what if you want to buy one of one of the series?
I think give and take dot site
represents a um
I think I think it's uh
I think it's violating my copyright
I think I think it represents a uh, a uh
You know a a functional market replacement for st comics.com. I think it's uh,
Yeah, pretty much. It's not it's not transformative enough
So I'm what do you mean? I'm gonna have where it's been saying I'm gonna have point point to Ben saying I'm gonna have to take it down
I'm sorry. It's over
Well, it's it's well, they're both because because you know when people see
St comics is down they say well now
What now I gotta go I guess I have to I guess I have to go read
Yeah, I guess I have to go read closer gun smoke instead and then their lust is is slaked and then they
They'll never read
Vapors chapter three. I'm gonna I'm gonna release a new comic called the voopers
No, you wouldn't dare
It's about two teenagers
Um, mints and vagda. Oh, I can't do that. I can't do that one. Yeah, you can. Yeah, go. No, no, no
Don't be a coward go for it. Vagda. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Vagda is the boy. Okay. They're both trans. Okay
fine
Fine if you must
Oh, so papers is well now. Okay losers. They're so
Confident and they don't have any social problems at all. That's
That's awesome. That's that sounds so cool
The voopers I'm gonna ah and then they say I'm gonna go boop. You want to go boop? Yeah
They're best friends. Well
Now they're better friends
Well, shit
Yeah, you can do that if you want
Unless I beat you to it
And then my second comic will be called the loser and they never win a fight
Hey, so in the green night
Is um, is this is this the game?
Uh, yeah, basically. No, no the christmas game is about getting you
getting
I you punch me. I punch you
It's a weird game. I don't why I don't know why it's called the christmas game
So the so the christmas game
The green night says chop my body
And then a year from now next night and he says you have to try and nick me
Is it like is it like sounds like he's gonna be dodging around is it like saint nick?
Like saint nick nick me. Hmm. And then next is it is the idea that then next christmas. I'll come and nick you
Is it like trick or treat like yeah, you you you trick me by slicing my wood off
And then tomorrow. I mean next year. I'll come and treat you to a gouging wound in your body
Uh, yeah, something like that interesting
fascinating
Concerning looking into it. It's a I think it's the they just call it the christmas game probably just because the original story has it during christ's mass
Uh, and it's not to do with like tradition like not traditional but like um more modern
Understandings of holiday season stuff. It could just be like a pagan thing
Well, no, it wouldn't be a pagan thing because it's christmas. They call it the christmas game
Maybe it was a pagan thing. They changed it in the film to be the christmas game because people know what that is
Who cares?
No, it would have been
Because isn't gaue and like one of the knights of the round
So they so they would have been christian
Right, okay. Yeah, I don't know the history. It probably it probably has some pagan origin though
No, I mean
I mean a lot of christian stuff does
It does I don't know when christmas got taken over or the pagan holiday
Of like the wincest sources got taken over by christians
um
Because when christians came and wokeified it
They they they they christified it
um, they christified
um
like
Because jesus wasn't born on december
But like when was that like changed? Um
Oh gee, I just don't know my history golly golly g
Oh
Gee whiz, I guess we'll just never know. I guess only the lord may know such secrets
Gee whiz we jizz
That's true. That's what they said. That's really true
Lamal, um
Oh god, I didn't read the new one piece yet
Oh, is there
It is to 1081 is the new one this week. I think I think I did read that. I forgot to mention it to you. Shit
Yeah, yeah, oh, yeah
I heard it's good
Did we talk about garp in the last one when he does the big punch on the galaxy first? Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, I think we did talk about that. All right
Well, I guess we're doing one piece now. I guess we're doing one piece now
Should I just read it real quick?
Yeah, read it real quick. Um, but I want to immediately draw your attention
to
the
Image at the front of the chapter where sanji is reading a book about caulking. Oh, yeah
Ah, he just didn't uh, I just didn't complete the uh, I just didn't complete the uh the oh
No
But then it would be cooking without the sea
What?
Oh, wait, no cooking doesn't have a sea
I thought he missed out an oh whoops
It is cocking. It is looks like i'm the one who doesn't know english
All right, all right, i'm reading i'm reading
Man
I like scuffed piece
I was i'm going back uh doing I think I I don't I don't remember if I mentioned the one piece book club reading volumes
from
previous
Reading all the volumes from the beginning with a new group people. Yes, I heard about that
and um
scuffed piece kind of was all always there
It's just that there's
Because like I look at the drawings and I'm like, oh, you know what?
You can really tell that this was hand drawn with a like it wasn't I'm sorry. I'm sorry, but like that's just manga
Most manga is pretty scuffed if you stop and you like look at every individual panel
Uh, yes
except for like except for like death note
Or or like berserk, right?
Like some of them aren't but
Most manga
you
It's drawn with the idea that you look at any given panel for like a quarter of a second
It literally like doesn't need to look good
And yet it's so good and yet it's so good and yet it's so good
Okay, i'm reading a few moments later. All right. I'm done
so
All right, looks like blackbeard did not get the ope ope fruit
But just like I thought yeah, he he wants he wants its power for eternal life
Uh, but he would not he would not be able to do that if he stole the power for himself
I guess he would he would have to give it to one of his subordinates
Which I think he could do
I think what he could do is like have like
Like a slave do it like you capture someone forces them to have the fruit and then tells them to use it on him like that
Yeah, yeah
Uh, so if he could capture law he might be able to I don't think he'd be able to do that because law would die
But what does he mean about he says the hundred hearts of people that law stole
Yeah, I I think this has been explained like mentioned a long time ago law
Does that thing where he uses his power to take someone's heart away? He had Caesar's heart for a long time
That was a bargaining chip. Mm-hmm
um
and I think he did that to
Like yeah, a hundred people a rocky part, but I forget where rocky part is or when that happened. Yeah, I don't uh
I don't even remember that at all
Maybe it's maybe it's a new thing. Maybe it's not an old thing that's being referenced, but I think it is an old thing
uh, I mean, but the point is uh
All those people are pirate island, which is blackbeard's island
So I guess law made a lot of enemies and blackbeard made friends with those enemies
If I bring your something
We're all living in fear on pirate. Yeah, I guess so
uh
this
This chapter makes blackbeard seem kind of cool
Oh, yeah, it's it's the funny thing with blackbeard. He's not like a dumb
I'm evil and I want to destroy sort of villain. He's
been
sort of set up as like
A an inversion not an inversion of luffy, but like a different interpretation of the freedom of piracy. Yeah, he's all about freedom
and
but he's
you know
Freedom freedom freedom for himself freedom at the cost of others
At the cost of others luffy's is all about freedom
Uh for himself. Yeah
But also for everyone
For everyone. Yeah
Like he likes sharing freedoms. Yeah blackbeard is like cynical. He doesn't believe luffy sees someone being oppressed
He'll he'll do something to stop it, but blackbeard will be like how can I turn this to my advantage?
Yes, yeah
Uh, so in a way he's a good he's a good um
Smart and thematically
Uh relevant antagonist. Yeah, it's the main villain kind of kind of the main villain
I mean, yeah, see see in them all just like hang out in the bar with kuzan
They're all just like, uh, you know, they're all just vibing. They're all just uh, just bantering
Yeah, they're like, oh, you hate the marines too at that ike acai, you know that piece of shit
Yeah, it's like maybe if if you weren't enemies with these guys, they might be kind of cool to just hang out with
I don't know
I mean when blackbeard when they when you meet blackbeard at
Chaya, he's just sitting there cherry pie
Yeah, yeah
And I I always liked
That luffy hates cherry pie
And blackbeard loves it and that's what they fight over rather than anything else. Yeah
They're like
Yeah, they're they're they're kind of similar
Uh, but
they just
Fundamental disagreement fundamental disagreement on the method. Yeah
Why would luffy hate cherry pie?
Yeah, I know it's such an odd little thing. I also don't he loves I also don't really care for cherry pie
low tier pie
Uh
Yeah, he just he rather yeah, this is
Oh, so okay, so kuzan's missing a leg now from the battle with uh
Okay, you know this is interesting doesn't doesn't affect him at all
Doesn't even bother him, but uh, he just makes a I mean
Prospero also had that like he lost an arm
From pedro and then he turned his arm into a candy arm. Who's who still has an arm. Who's prospero?
the big uh, the number one
Son the first son of big mom the big tongue guy
Oh
Oh the candy man. He literally makes candy
Yeah, this is devil fruit. Um, I'm having trouble picturing him. Let me just google him real fast
Oh pero sparrow pero sparrow. Oh, yeah
Yeah, this wow this guy left like no impression on me whatsoever
Okay, he yeah big tongue sure
Sure, whatever
Yeah, but that's not even his real tongue. That's probably a candy tongue
No, of course, this is real time. He's been he loves licking
Candy well
pooms among us
um
All right, so yeah, there's a few things starting off. Yes
um garb lands with the ship
And he's like, uh, fuck. I'm old and you know, wow
He's so strong
He's so strong and yet he's not as strong as he was. I like that trope. I enjoy that one
Um, and then the the cute girl with the gun gets turned to ice
by by alki g
Yes, unfortunate. This is very unfortunate
And alki g is one of the black bed pirates who is here rather than at uh, we presume egghead
on the ship
Uh, yeah, he says teaches away
So so maybe teach it so maybe so maybe that means teaches at egghead
Yeah, so yeah, that's what I'm thinking. So the teach blackbeard and some other people who haven't we haven't seen
are
on the ship and alki g is not
he's here
and
The whole thing with him joining the blackbeard parts. We were wondering about this
I've been wondering about this for a long time like why would you do that?
Obviously the fight with the the alki g and leaving the marines
Seemed they say it's like over the fleet admiral position
I guess that's been said before
But I feel like it was probably more than just that like I want the promotion
No, I want it and then they fight like that that seems a bit insane. I it seemed like
Uh, I mean it seems like just the the the hierarchy was just kind of in chaos at the time and so
like one of them will probably get it
And
I'm sure it wasn't like an official like whoever wins the fight gets it. It's more just like
All right, we but we don't like each other
We don't want the other guy to become the new fleet admiral
There's nothing to do but just fight about it and like fuck the guy who loses
Uh, uh, yeah, I don't I don't know what to think of alki g because like
Like I said last time
I don't think he's dumb. He doesn't seem like a
Like a hard on his sleeve kind of person. No
That thinks uh after he does stuff
No, but the way he's characterized here is that
You know, he got into a a fight with the other admiral over
Like a position in the military
and then he joins blackbeard's crew
on the
you know
for for like
presumably the protection and the freedom that piracy
allows
Yeah, I don't and I'm like that that that makes sense enough, but then
Well, I guess it just I guess it just does make sense. It just sort of is sad to see him
Do things well that it seems to make to make him look like a villain like turning somebody to ice instantly
Okay, I know he's trying to protect. I mean turn it's turning people to ice like he can turn him back. It's fine
I know for reasons I
Blackbeard says like, uh, you know, we all we all we all profit because uh
Yeah, we all okay the the the
The the you know pirates all wrong. We ain't just a merry band of chums bumming around
We all profit from having our own agendas. That's what makes us pirates
Yes, and the the the vis translation that I just read is different
It says have you got the wrong idea about pirates? Nobody said we're all best friends here
The only thing pirates need is an alignment of interests
Which is you know, it's similar
So, you know, I love this face by the way. There's something so satisfying about this face
Oh, yeah, I posted teach teach his good face good. He's he's a he's a great design. I love his nose and his
face so like he's so his giant face is like so threatening
He's right up in there
So
I mean you're a free man do what you want. So I mean Cousin is
I guess he must see aligning himself with these guys
as useful
to some
end
Yeah, I don't I don't exactly know what his end his goal is right now
But I think well, I'm pretty sure that whatever his goal was
um
Or continues to be is very much involved with the reason that he got into such a catastrophic fight with alkiji
back. I knew I mean
over
Fleet admiral position because like he doesn't seem like he would give a shit about something about being fleet admiral
Yeah, I think either because he believes that um akainu would be a terrible problem
Or I think he that's probably yeah, I think he probably yeah, if my read on him is correct. I think he just wouldn't want
Akainu
To do it. He just wouldn't want him in charge. I don't think I don't think Cousin is the kind of guy who's like
I've got to be freaking king or whatever
Yeah
So I so I think it's like biting his time. I could see how joining the blackbeard pirates might help him in the goal of
Yeah, eventually taking down akainu. That makes sense
Yes, but and then there's the bit where garp he's fighting with garp
And he says your number one protege versus your new favorite. So new favorite meaning kobi
and uh
That implies that uh cousin was the old favorite of garp
Meaning that garp probably also saw goodness in kuzan. Yeah
And I wonder if kuzan is throwing this fight deliberately
Because obviously he has to look like he's defending stuff
Yes, I see because he
garp says he's hesitating or wavering
And yeah
Yeah, and he's sort of letting himself lose to garp and it's not it's not a bad story like garp is such a legend
Yeah, it would happen. Yeah
That's that's true, but I wonder if I wonder if kuzan could have beaten him or at least really tried harder than this
I
Well, he he freezes uh, he freezes him right he freezes garp, but it just like doesn't work
Did I yeah, he just he just breaks out of it or something. Yeah, super hacky super malio
Wavering is a sign of weakness wait
Yeah, okay, I says don't be would you kill your senior apprentice's favorite protege?
Don't be tight and then garp says don't be tied down by this nonsense. I taught you to live in the moment
It's not working on him. Listen up kuzan wavering is a sign
All right, he breaks out of the ice then he
Kicks his kicks his little ass
Throws him into the blue throws him into the blue hole
It's like a black hole, but it's blue because he's a
cop
Yeah, this is a thin the thin blue hole
Um
I think yeah, I think you might be right that he might have uh, he might just kind of be putting on appearances for this fight
It's so funny how black beard
You know, I've been playing uh
Battle network mega man
And it's funny every now and then
Your rival shows up
And your your rival chowd has proto man is his navi
And he's all and occasionally he'll say something like this. He'll be like
Proto man will be like
Me and chowd aren't friends like we're just we're we're just i'm just his now
I dutifully serve him as his program
Uh, and mega man will be like but me and lan we're best friends and and brothers and and our d we share our dna
And we love each other in a platonic way
And proto man will be like, hmm, that's gay bro and chowd will be like, yeah, it's totally gay
I don't think proto man's hot at all and proto be like, yeah, I don't think chowd's hot either
Also, he's like 11 years old. So it's weird to even talk like that. Okay. Bye
Um
Insisting like yeah, we're
Yeah
Me and my co-workers. Yeah, we're not friends. We're just here to get our shit done and make a ton of money
It's like I get it. I get it
I get it
Is a little sad
Is a little sad to be like, yeah, I pretty much hang out with these guys 24 7
We hang out on a on a on a on a ship together
Maybe that's true. Maybe that's not true. Maybe maybe they're not always on a ship together
I guess they have a whole island now. They probably don't even have to hang out together unless they really want to
Well, I I mean the blackbird pirates seem like chummy. I don't think they seem like cold
They can have a beer and they can have a laugh. Yeah, and they can enjoy a victory together, but like ultimately
They're in it. Yeah, not for friendship. They're in it for power. Yeah
Yeah, but they can get power by being together. So it's just it's a kind of
You know, it's not unemotional. Oh, that's what the pcp was supposed to be
Yeah, we were we were supposed to kill the government and and uh
And yet it's still there the government and he's not moved hasn't moved an inch
And now they've elected the real life version of acai new joe biden and there's nothing we can do about it
We were supposed we were supposed to stop this
He's got his magma powers
Yeah
Uh joe
Ah joe
It's joe over. It is joe over
Uh, um
Let's see. Okay. What else to
Well, the next thing in the chapter is that we see that I predicted and it's pretty obvious, but I predicted law
Oh, yeah defeated. Yes defeated. Just like kid. Yeah, just like kid
Damn black beard is defeated law
On winner island, I don't know if that was the name of the island they were at before
I guess it must have been because if it was the it was if it was like
the one depicted before
Where like law was
Briefly turned into a woman for that one panel
Good times. Do you remember that? I vaguely remember that. Yeah
Yeah, it's a little little like haha. We're fighting and this is the result. Was he turned into a woman by
Docky cue with his oh trans disease
I was thinking it was who's the is it Ivanovic is the one that can turn you into a woman
Ivankov Ivankov Ivankov, right
Yeah, Ivankov. Yeah
Fucking doc cue doc cue has freaky hormone fruit. Is that really what it is?
Yeah, the hormone hilarious doc doc cue has like
weaponized like estrogen bullets
Amazing. Yeah, and they say oh, it's only temporary. It's just a freak. I'm out a little just to make a little
Just to make of all weird and shit
So that we can gain me up a hand it was like
It worked shut up. You just wanted to draw a law as a girl. Wait. Yeah, wait a minute. Wait a minute
well
Would that have happened like a long time ago?
Because I mean doc wait
If doc cue shot law
Then I mean was was is that the same encounter that led to his
submarine being destroyed
I mean, I'm assuming that I can't remember. I don't think there's enough landmarks in these panels to determine
Whether it's the same island
Um, all I know is they were fighting. We didn't see the resolution of that fight
And here is a resolution of a fight between black bear and law. I think it makes sense that it's the same thing
Yeah, yeah, meaning this would have happened a little while ago, but not that long ago. I mean if if he was already
getting shot by doc cue I have to imagine that that
was
I don't remember if it was a bullet. It may have been like a gas or something
Okay, but they were because he was fighting a bunch of the crew was like but doc doc cue was there and they were having a battle
So, I mean, yeah, yeah
Blackbeard must have showed up later
No, blackbeard was there during oh, okay, so
So this is so this is they were they were in the throes of a of a fight. It was just we didn't see what happened
Okay, so this is what happened
Okay, so the law got beat
And uh, we we saw earlier that blackbeard knows of the road poneglas
And big mom kaito have won each law has those ones
so now blackbeard and shanks both have
kaitos and big moms a road poneglas
um, but then
There's two more they don't know about one of them. We do know about it's the one inside zoe the giant
Yes, uh, the giant
What is it? It's a it's a elephant tree in the shape of a whale
What on top of it? Yeah, that's the location. There's like the the mink tribe settlement. There's a big tree that looks like a whale
Uh, did I hallucinate that?
Are you know what a tree?
Okay, a tree that looks like a whale. I can't zow is not the elephant
The elephant is could is kashina kashina is the elephant and it has a tree in the shape of a whale on it
And that's zow and that's where the the poneglyph is no zoe
Zoe is wait zoe is the the island on the top of the elephant called kashina. Okay
And then on in so on zoe there is a tree shape like a whale
And in that tree there is a poneglyph
Is it kashina? I'm typing kashina and it's sanguina and I'm like no
There's a glyph in the tree and a tree in the shape of a whale and a whale on the zoe and zoe on an elephant
It's it's zunesh. Okay. Not kushina. Okay. Sure. Whatever
Zunesh, uh, da da da da
One da da da zoe on its back zoe is the island
and
Uh, da da da da da
Where is the thing?
Layout and locations whale forest. That's what it was called
Um
No images
You're fucking me. You're killing me over here. I just want to show ben the whale. Please
I want to see the whale tree
Whale tree
Okay, here is an image of I think I guess it's not a tree. No, it is a tree
It's got it's got leaves coming out of it. Huh
Well
Okay, so that's inside that is a secret compartment where rhizo was hiding
And where the road ponyglyph is
Okay, and so and we don't know where the fourth one is right?
No, the fourth one is hypothesized by the blackbird pirates
It heard rumors that the man marked by flames has it
Who is a mystery man? I can't think of who it could be
Man marked by flames means burnt. I guess I mean
Man marked by flames
It's I mean the only one I can think of
Is luffy because he's got the scar from his on his chest from the from the magma punch
Uh
I guess you could you could say that but I mean he doesn't yeah, yeah
Obviously not who they're talking about they're talking about a mystery man that travels in a black ship
Yeah, um that creates whirlpools around it
Um the man marked by this is the first time we're hearing about that, right?
I think so. Okay. Um
The man might play flames
I had at first thought was like fisher tiger because marked by flames as in like branded with a branding iron
Like the slaves will do so it could be a fish man. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
But I think all the permanent fishermen have been like
Introduced and are either fisher tiger or someone else and I don't think it's any of the other people
Um other than that it could be someone wounded by someone who had a flaming devil fruit
Yeah, I can't think of anyone that would be
But I have heard just by people leave in comments that what if the whirlpool?
um
You do you remember the very beginning of one piece? No
Oh
Uh, well, yeah, no, I remember the yeah, what would you say in?
Luffy leaves on his journey after waiting 10 years after shanks left
He punches that fish that but shanks arm. You know the classic. Oh the um, I'm the the the the sea king
Sea king. Yeah, the the local village sea king tiny little guy
Bit shanks arm off. Luffy punches it and then immediately he's uh in a whirlpool and he'll die
right
He'll in a bit. He's in a big whirlpool and he's like, oh, I'm gonna drown
I guess I hide in this barrel and then that barrel gets found
By alvita's pirates and he meets kobe and all that stuff happens. Um, but the whirlpool
What if the whirlpool was because of the whirlpool guy was there?
What if the whirlpool was because the guy who makes whirlpools behind him with a potential devil fruit the guy man marked by flames
What if that guy was there? I can't think of any other reason why there would have been a whirlpool
It couldn't have been like a sea thing. It couldn't have just been a sea anomaly when you say that
Yeah, I mean, what yeah, what are the uh, oh, so you're saying that like the whirlpool they just happen like the sea just does things
Okay, uh, when you say that it makes me think of dragon
And the the lightning that struck at
rogueport
Remember he kind of like controlled the weather and like uh, yeah lightning struck what when elufi was going to get executed or something
Yeah, I don't know if it's clear what dragon's
Fruit has dragon seems to have some kind of weather control powers and he's got that scar on his face
I don't know. Maybe it's dragon. Maybe dragon is the man marked by flames
Monkey
A D dragon
He does have a big fucking scar although it looks more like a tattoo than a flame
Did I did I show did I show you that image of um, how it kind of looks like
The bottom of the of a shoe
As though garp had just like stomped stomped on his face with like a rubber sneakers
Okay
Abilities and powers
He's the supreme commander of the revolutionary army
um
I love one piece
I do I love scuffed piece. Uh, I love uh, the the retcons
I love when the rubber fruit becomes a magic cloud man fruit. Duh
I eat my slop. I do I unironically do
Okay, it remains unconfirmed if dragon was directly responsible for the wind blast or if he has a power enabling to create them
So we don't actually know if he has a fruit. We don't know anything about his powers
Uh, yeah, if he does have a weather control power
Then his ability to make weather things happen such as a lot of wind lightning potentially whirlpools
uh
I the reason I don't think is dragon is just because
The rumor of the guy traveling around in a black ship. They would just like the black pearl
From the fucking pirate to the cow. Do you think that it's just like a totally new guy?
That we haven't seen before I think
I think it's it's gotten a real
reason to be a guy we know. Yeah
um
It probably has
Like it could be like an old ally of like a famous pirate or a friend of someone who we do know already
Like oh, maybe Ray Lee knows them or I don't know
um, I think the the the
Clue would be the fact that at the bottom of the ocean near fishman island where it used to be
this
red poneglyph used to be there
um
And there's in its place a poneglyph that is an apology letter saying sorry. I had to move this
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Say that again
There's an apology poneglyph
It's just written as like sorry. I just I gotta take I think that's what it was. Wait, wait
Where huh? I'm sorry at the bottom at fishman island. There's an apology. They go from from who?
Oh, we don't know
Do we know what it's I'm sorry. Can you explain this to me like I am stupid? Yeah, I don't understand. I don't remember what you're talking about
I I looked at it a few weeks ago and I need to relook at it just to remember
um
So the poneglyphs we know about
Sea forest yugu kingdom fishman island
All right, nicka robin initially believed this poneglyph held vital information to understanding the void sentry
However, upon finding it she noted that it was different from the other poneglyphs
She had found reading more like an apology letter than a historical text the message was written by a man from the surface known as joyboy
Okay, so joyboy wrote this poneglyph
In the message, he apologized to the people of fishman island for breaking part of his promise
Which involves returning to fishman island to carry out noah's purpose. Okay, so that's not what I was returning to fishman island
To carry out noah's purpose. So he apologized for not doing that or he said he would do that
uh
Yeah, something about noah
Uh, the gigantic no is yeah, I was gonna say okay. No is the giant ship, right?
Okay. No. Yes. Here here it is
At least 25 years ago
This is the fourth
red
Road poneglyph
At least 25 years ago. This poneglyph was located at the sea forest next to joyboy's apology message
At a certain point later that the road poneglyph wereabouts became unknown and it is currently considered lust
And then there's a speculation however, it's speculated to be in the position of
Hino
Kizu who's the head Hino Hino Kizu is the
Oh, Hino Kizu is the name given to a mysterious man possessing a burn sky
It's just the the man the man marked by flames
Hino Iso
Hino Hino Kizu
So yeah, it used to be right next to joyboy's apology message next to fishman island at some point
25 years ago
Yeah, I mean someone like fisher tiger kind of makes sense
I don't know if fisher tiger is even alive, but um
Yeah, it's a mysterious man
And that's all we know
But we know it used to be under fishman island
So if there's any clues it would be some relation to fishman island man marked by flames
I immediately think of the sun pirates, you know the burns the the branding iron turned into a pirate emblem. Yeah
But I I don't know. I don't know how you could make that work
with fisher tiger
Or it could be just some other pirate crew member from that crew, but like
I don't know. Why would he do that? I guess a fishman might have the ability to do fishman karate and make whirlpools
Hmm. Yeah. Yeah, probably the blackbeard pirates were like
Hypothesizing that it was a devil fruit power and it might not be it might be a fishman karate technique
Something that jim pay could learn
Oh, fine. Oh our helmsman. We can level up our helmsman
You can get a power. Yes, okay
all right, so
Probably probably not gonna probably not gonna crack this mystery
No, yeah
Um, oh man, I'm gonna say it's a fishman. That's my vague guess
That it's at least a fishman
Because how could he put a fucking move it from under the ocean?
How they gonna move it?
Well, okay, we don't I mean we don't know that the guy who's got it now is the same guy who took it
In the first place so like a fish even if a fishman took it
He might have given it to some other guy this guy marked by flames or maybe that guy stole it from the other guy
Yeah, it could be a fishman. I don't know seems like it really could be anything
I mean a fish a tiger fish a tiger died from blood loss after being ambushed and shot by a squad of marines. Oh, no, he died. Oh
Yeah fringe
Cringe
Uh, why what a cool white all the good ones die
What a cool guy, you know, he was like, yeah, I'm racist, but
I get that I shouldn't be so I'm not gonna let it
Not was he racist? I thought he was definitely hated humans
He was he there's definitely a part where he's like, I hate humans
I'll never be able to stop hating humans because of what they did to me
But I understand that like a future where humans and fishman can like cooperate
Is like preferable
So I'm I'm not gonna like outlaw them or anything. He there was something like that
But yeah, he himself was like, yes, I cannot get over my hatred of humans
He's I'm reading and it says even though he hated humans according to Hancock
He did not discriminate against them when it came to slavery and liberated every one of them during his raid of marishwa
That's pretty cool. He hates hates humans, but he hates the institution of slavery even more. It was pretty reasonable
Yes, he did not believe in revenge on humans for the discrimination. He just don't like him. Just just is racist against sure
And I mean who's among us
His compassion to humans was further demonstrated when he vowed to take a child who was a former slave back to her hometown
Going as far as to mark her with his own jolly roger to lift the burden of slavery off her back
Yes, I remember that koala was the name of the girl, right
Right
And koala is in the revolutionary army, right? She's like, um, was friends with sabo
Yeah, that's the girl
I remember now sounds right. Yeah
Hey, yeah
Hey, yeah koala
One piece. Let me let me
Oh steam punk. Yeah, that was the girl that fisher tiger
Did something with
He brought her back to her hometown
Despite being a lowly little human the pee human give her watch
Give her watch the english dub
Like the four kids dub
You know that in the four I know in the four kids in the four kids dub arlong calls humans pee humans
Because they stink get it
Uh, he would do that. He would and he did
Oh, you can play as koala in one piece super grand battle x
I gotta buy holy shit
Bro
Check this out. You're not gonna believe this
Si
Oh, she's got chopper aside. Her head is way too big. What's simsie saying?
I
Don't don't understand
What is this
I don't know
Oh, that crawfish is gonna be delicious though
Why did he jump in there?
He didn't know what he didn't know what else to do. Oh poor little that uh, that's actually really upsetting
Just seeing him like I'm just gonna go over
Instant death
Probably not that instant not instant enough
Not instant enough
Unclear if uh mollusks feel pain
Or no, I guess they're not mollusks because they're crustaceans
I think I think crustaceans might not feel pain, you know, it makes me feel pain. That's bad enough
I I see what you I see what you mean
Um
Uh, okay. I mean pretty good one piece this week. Yes. I I guess it was pretty good
Yeah, it was shut up
I guess it was with your your you gotta have blind loyalty. Okay. We have blind loyalty on this show pretty pretty decent
Um, you know, sure it was sure it was scuffed and owed as a hack, but I mean, you know what I I've just I've just grown
Uh, I've just grown weary enough that I'll just accept whatever slop I'm giving. Oh, uh, uh, Cousin join the blackbeard pirate
Okay
Sure thing oda
Whatever you say, you know, he just you know, he just thinks I'm uh, he thinks I'm an idiot
He's gonna disrespect me like this, but you know what? I like it now
Um, oh one more thing one more. Yeah, I don't either one more thing. Um
Um
Briefly to mention is Beppo Beppo saved law. Thanks to chopper chopper giving him
Oh
That uh, okay, okay, okay before un
Uh documented creation of a Soulong ball or maybe it's just a rumble ball
Um that allows Beppo to go Soulong without the moon
Okay, Soulong is when a um, oh fuck. What are those people called?
Is when a mink when it's the full moon and the mink goes like hyper mode, right?
Okay, so
Did did chopper make a Soulong ball for?
Like carrot or someone did he make one of these before? No, no
This is the first time we have seen the idea of chopper using technology to do to put Soulong
I guess this was developed after wano
Before the three crews
Set their you know sites for different islands and left chopper was like
I wonder if Soulong could be like used more than just the full moon. I guess and then he made that little thing
Wow, there's a little panel where Beppo is eating something and he's remembering chopper
Oh, he's he's eating. Okay. I saw the little uh, oh, yeah, he chomps it. He chomps it. Yeah
Cute little chomp. Oh, he's so cute. He is
Beppo
And they turned into this giant
Flaming
Bear beast. Yeah, it's really cool. Actually. Yeah. Okay. I wasn't sure what was going on with the little chopper bubble
I see. Yes. He made a he made a Soulong ball, of course
Makes sense
So Beppo saves the captain
Yeah, uh, finally Beppo has done something
Every instance we've seen Beppo. He's been like he's just standing there
He's just been a cute funny bear who's always scared and and law
Presumably likes him because he's cute
Yeah, understandable
I just remembered because he mentions like the freezing ports of the north blue because he's from north blue
Uh, it's probably just because
Law was in the cold area and he met a bear
And a bear who was like, oh, I'm oh, I'm a little bear and law was like, ah, join my crew
And so they've been buddies forever
So this is this heartwarming
But uh, also the his entire crew is destroyed and his ship is destroyed and law is fucked
But he's not dead. He's not he's not fucked. He's got Beppo. He's got as long as he's got as long as he's got Beppo
there's hope
Yeah, so the new heart pirates are gonna be Beppo and law
um
There is that one guy
You can see it when the submarine is being destroyed the one guy on the left with the with the with the hair with the hair
he's the fishman from
a shabaldi
I remember him joining the the the the the heart pirates crew
After being saved by law during all that hubbub
Man
A submarine is awesome
It is it's awesome to have a submarine as your pirate ship
It's so cool pretty cowardly though. You can't show off your your big flag if you're underwater
Um, fuck off. Uh, he's got it painted on his side. It's fine. It's cool. You know what? He's
He's not he's not bound by tradition. He's think he's thinking outside the box and I appreciate it. Uh,
Yeah, damn now it's wrecked
It is pretty I guess that like there's not more submarine type things. I wonder who built that
Yeah
It does it makes you wonder why
Why does he have a submarine? Why is he the only one with a submarine?
What's going on?
He doesn't need to like coat his ship with like bubble goo to go to fishman island. He could just drive the ship there
It's see it seems like uh the ship can surface like it's upside down in this panel, but it seems like
There's like decks that you could stand on
Yeah, stuff like if it were if it were on so like yeah, it can come up and hang out on the surface if it wants to
I don't remember seeing it before. I'm sure we've seen it before. I just
Oh, no, we've seen it loads of times. Yeah
Yeah, I just I mean that was the ship that was the ship that saved luffy during the war at marenford
Right
You know I just
So hard to keep
Everything sorted in my mind
Uh, I just I see this and I'm like, yeah, okay
I I don't remember, but I'm sure that that's what it looked like. Uh, it's it's cool
I mean, I don't think we've seen it in a while. Yeah. Yeah, I'm just I'm you know
I look at this and it's it's as though it were new to me and I nod and I go, huh cool ship
Yeah, cool ship too bad. It's dead too bad. Oh, well
Um, so yeah, that was a good chapter
I await more
What's what's uh
What's what's gonna happen? I mean, well, okay, we've seen laws fate
Law is yeah blackbird has
two
Do you think we still don't know if law like luffy shared the one from inside the uh
The thing I guess I guess to keep the stakes high. Maybe it was all three
And so they shared all three so now shanks blackbeard and luffy have three of the four
And they're all looking for the mysterious man
Yeah, and whoever finds him first that would make sense would be able to get it I guess
That would that would make sense
um
Do you think
I mean kuzan is seems to have been beaten or is
I think the fight fight might go on but I don't think kuzan
That there's there's two ways it could go one is kuzan could
Ultimately decimate everyone and then kill kobe and that's bad because kobe needs to escape
I think garp might sacrifice himself to save kobe
But I also don't know if kuzan would want to go far enough
To actually kill garp. I don't think so. I really don't think so
Uh, but I think maybe to keep up appearances. He would do it
If it if his if his goal matters that much that he needs to stay
Like undercover that hard, but like I don't know. Well, maybe that would be a real that'd be a real heel turn
Moment for him. That would be really crossing a line. Yeah
Uh, I think I think it seems like he's done and it seems like his powers don't work on garp and like
He hesitated and it doesn't seem like he's he's fighting at full strength. I think
I don't know. Do you think garp is is garp just gonna run wild and just like beat beat the freaking uh
crew
I don't think he he can't beat the entirety of the blackbeard crew other than like
He can't beat like four blackbeard guys. No, I don't think so
Yeah, especially since one of them is the island they're standing on
They're I think they're probably gonna be I think probably because kuzan
Is sort of throwing
I think he's probably just they're gonna get away with kobe
Yeah, I think kobe's gonna survive
I don't know if garp is but I think kobe is gonna survive
Yeah, I could I could see garp dying but not from kuzan
One of the other one of the other guys might
Might get him. Yeah, and kuzan wouldn't be able to help garp without ruining everything for himself
Possibly
Well, cuz um cuz cuz garp couldn't save
Uh ace
Because he had to stand by be like, uh, I couldn't uh couldn't do anything. They were executing ace. I just couldn't do anything
I'm a marine. That's my job. I just had to just had to stand there and watch and kuzan would be like, uh, well
I'm a blackbeard. You know, I just just had to stand there and watch while they killed my old uh
My old master. Well, that was the brakes, I guess
Would kind would kind of be uh
Sort of fitting and for garp in a way, I guess
I mean garp's old
You know what he deserves to die
For being for being old
Um
Hmm
Yeah, so
There's gonna be obviously egghead is probably what's happening. We're gonna focus on again after this
Cuz blackbeard is um his way on his ship
With probably every blackbeard pirate that is not featured in this little garp mission
And they're going to a
They're going they probably have putting in the brig
And they haven't seen egghead in a while. It's been like three weeks. Oh, yeah
Le Mans
Ah, there's so much and then there's the big buster call. There's the
Antony Garcia. What is the fuck?
uh
J garcia sadden j garcia sadden. Are they are they buster calling egghead? Is that what they're doing?
There's something calling. I don't think it's literally a buster call
But it's just like a fuck ton of battleships are coming
Yeah, uh to destroy this island because of information
given to them by
the big fat
vagabonk lady
She eats so much food and poops it out
Nice nice. If I got her name lol
uh
cock is it like
Is it like kato or like it's like a four letter word that begins with k like ca
Uh
impulsive arrow
caro no
Okay, never mind. I'm googling it
Remember remember every megapunk snake york. Why do they think taro? Okay york, right?
um
All right, good chapter very exciting. Shall we go into voicemails?
Um, yeah
Yeah
Yelp
speakbip.com slash pzp voicemails
If you want to die
Okay, the first one. Oh the first one is called beast capades late suggestion
Are you ready? Mm-hmm. Okay, three two one go
This will be outdated already, but uh
Uh
Regarding the beast capades
Uh gift versus
Png release format
I give you wrong ban you right? You should just focus on one type of release. Thanks. Don't divide your small audience even further
Um
Don't rely on multiple people
You're like, oh, I want to I want to be I want to see that again
and just put a lot of effort into something that's
Gonna satisfy two people
Uh, sorry if this is too authoritative
That's fine. You can do that. I don't remember what was the other point. Uh, goodbye. Yeah, um
Um
I was um, I think probably making it as gifts is just like
It's probably better just to not do it because it's like it's like a lot more work
and like
Does it does it increase?
enjoyment
For the reader like a ton
maybe sometimes
But like I can just make the panels look good
In a static format too. Yeah, and that's fine
My my my thing is still like
You may be making two people
More happy, but if one of those people is me the author then I would do it because fuck it
Yeah, I mean, yeah
I'm I'm not I'm not smart
I understand that in in in like a in like a efficiency way, but that's why I draw
I
me
As the author
Yeah, I guess like having it be exactly the way I wanted it to be would make me
Would make me happy, but on the one hand
There's always going to be compromise in anything you do. Nothing will ever be perfect
and
Yeah, having making it one way
If I if I make it one way in static images and then I go back and I make it again in gift form
That
Even though I might like the result that process is going to make me miserable
Sure, because I'm just be like I've already done it. So I think my my happiness would be decreased
So, yeah, I think uh
Perfect comic party static images is what I'm going to do for the time being
Um next one is called slime and punishment book three two one go
Ah, yes, Ben, please
please
release
Slime and punishment as a god damn
A comic already
I've been waiting for a year. I've been sorry
Some people to read it as I borrowed it to them
For a year and they are still waiting
Besides that
I really would like them to experience the game because I love the game
It's the main thing that makes me want to buy this expensive. That's the thing
It's gonna be that expensive
Unless you're foreign
I want to know is the comic doesn't comic make it obvious when
You could just play the game instead of reading the comic version
Uh, please and thank you. I mean
I mean, there's a section of the comic where the panels are
Like game in-game shots. So like yeah, it's really it's really clear what part is the game and what part is not
Uh, it's like I think it's like 30 pages or something. It's like 35 pages
Uh, you know, I just got I just this week. It was late
I ordered from etsy a piece of fluorescent pink fabric to be my green my black light green screen
for that shot I wanted to do for the um
For the the trailer I finally got it on two days ago on friday
And it's hanging on my wall now. So I'm now
I'm gonna finish that beast capades chapter and then as soon as beast capades chapter is done
I'm gonna film that
Uh that that scene and try to make a trailer out of it
Nice and yeah, I have I should have everything I need for it now
Uh pretty cool
Uh, you know progress continues even though
Never as fast as I would like
Next one is called. I am mean at the end. I'm sorry three two one go
Ah about the
That guy that got cancelled because you asked for sex twice
Yeah, uh munchy
No cheeses description of the facts
Made it sound like really not that big of a deal. I don't know the facts either
I would have reacted the same as you've been. Thank you
Just letting you know and I'm sure everybody else would
Everybody's just you know
Latching on just woke to make everybody's just woke. Everybody's just woke around
Plus your balls a bit, you know, just yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
It's fine. Don't worry
Don't take anything. Oh, I oh, I'm not
You know life is a chance
Specifically this guy gets me
Who is this guy this guy's a this guy's a genius
I don't know. I don't know
All right. Hmm. Okay. Next one is called chris lan from prince isolation three two one go
All right, mr. Match. I guess I can do you this one favor. All right. Let me go up to my bathroom and
Son of you jack into my toaster
All right. I'm on the net
What's that mr. Match
One more program to upload to my toaster
Well, I suppose I could I suppose I can do that
I could suppose I can upload one more little little little thing or whatnot in my toaster
Okay, here goes or whatnot
What mr. Match my house is on fire
I think it was a coffee maker. I think it was a coffee maker that
Lipped her house on fire
That's um mr
Mr. Match is a guy from
Uh mega man battle network. He tells you that he's good. He's a bad guy, but then he tells you he's good now
Hey, I'm good now. Hey now that I'm good. Would you go around and
Put all these programs into all these important machines
And then you do it and then there's like, ah, it was bad. Ah, the place is on fire. Ah, everything's on fire
Ah, your dad's in the hospital the mal
Gotcha
All right, next one is called sick new t-shirts 3 2 1 go
Um, you should make a t-shirt with the new pcp like icon like the skull icon
On it because that's true that is hell and uh, it it belongs on a shirt. I think it would work really well
Um, I've noticed that the old tpc logo
Shirt has it as like just a really big image on the shirt, which I think maybe would work better for the skull
I don't think it worked well for that one. I think it would have been better as like a breast
Like the small image on the breast area, you know what I'm talking about
I know exactly what you're talking about, but for the skull, maybe that one would work with both of those formats
I don't know. I don't know. I'm just I'm just telling you what I want to see
I'm just telling you what I want to see so I can give you money
You know what? I think he's right. No reason not to make a shirt with the new branding. Yeah
Okay, can I get a bigger cut because I made the logo
Oh
Next one is called
WTF 321 go
What the fuck been saint?
How the hell did you look at $2,000 for americans and think that's way too much
And chopped it up the stock market some bullshit deficits
He really said fuck your rent and the fact that you're essential in some ways you're worse than
Reagan and Thatcher
Was it we still are two are already dead
2023 only just started and you're already making it worse
I don't know what I did. I don't know
You're seeing a song and I could not for the life of me figure out what song
Was he talking about the covid relief $2,000 for americans when when I say that wasn't that was too much
That's silly. That's silly
Um, thanks for the voice
I don't even know why why would you say these things? Um, okay, uh, next one is called. Oh, it's an image. Okay. Let's take a look
It's an image
Okay
It's jesse serving me a dmca. I'm sure to win because my flange is superior
Well, I mean
It's just true. It's just true
It's exactly how it it it would go and how it did go
Thank you
voice mailman
Uh, let's uh, let's look at the next one
Oh, it's a
anime girl
Of some kind
It sure is sure is it sure is
I don't uh, I don't get it
Next one is called my darkest fantasy
fugitive ben saint 3 2 1 go
So, um, if you killed someone and
There was a dead body sitting in the middle of your room right now
Uh, what would you do with the body and then after that will be your next move?
And everyone knows everyone knows that that person was at your house
Hmm. Oh, did you kill them? That's the important part
If he doesn't say you killed them, so I'm thinking no you didn't
Well, if I didn't then I would call the police and say there's a corpse in my house and I don't know what happened
Because then I'm like, oh, I reported the body. I didn't do it because I didn't yeah
Yeah, if you just if I try to hide it then you could get caught and then
You're obviously implicated as the culprit
Let me let me listen again
No, no, he does it if you killed someone. Okay, so if I killed him
Um or her don't exclude
um
I mean, I guess I would
I think
ooh
Okay
I think
That I'm not smart enough to like get away with it
So so I think the move is
Okay, the move is probably
Hide the body as quickly as I can maybe you know, maybe bury it maybe maybe
Bury it like that night like dig a hole and bury it in the backyard. No, maybe that's even like two
That's a lot of work moving enough dirt to put a human being underground. I genuinely think
Actually that I might just put the body in my closet or something
Like put the like because like people might see me digging people might see me digging
Whereas like if it's just in my room like nobody's gonna come into my room until like a police investigation starts
so I think I might just hide the body in my closet
and then
just like
Get all my money
Get all the money that I have like like withdraw it from all my accounts that I have access to and just like
I put it to bitcoin
I put it to bitcoin. No and just and just flee somewhere and just like flee to I don't know canada or something
You get caught in canada
You got to go like to a small island in the pacific
Yeah, maybe maybe the philippines or something
They they don't have america laws
I don't know how laws work. I don't I wonder if my oh, I might need to renew my passport. I'm not sure if my passport's still valid
Yeah, I think
The the move is hide quick quickly hide the body
Get as get as much of my money as I can
and just
Try and escape
to somewhere and and go off the grid
Because uh, I don't think there's any I don't think there's any like getting away with it
So you're you're resigning yourself to the fact that people will eventually find it and know that you were a murderer
So you can never come back
Yeah, probably yeah
I mean, um
Maybe I could um, I mean, maybe I could try to make it look like an accident it would depend how I killed them
Yeah, I don't know I don't think about this
So I don't know what I would do
If I killed someone I probably I think I think I think about it all the time
I'm always thinking about this
Uh, like if it was premeditated
Yeah, I probably would have already had a plan but I just like yeah, he didn't say he didn't say it was premeditated
He he might have just done it in the heat of the moment
And if that's the case
Like depending on if I already
I don't know
Like right now answering this question. I don't know if there's like
some
lesser sentence I could get for like oh, it was
Just because I was really mad because they beat me in fortnight or whatever or whatever it was
I think they said I was ugly and I killed them
I think you would be I would still get murder charge. It wouldn't be a different type of thing
Unless I plead insanity, but then I'd have to prove that and I can't do that. It's hard
Depending on how you did it. You might be able to get the charges reduced to like manslaughter. Maybe
Like maybe
Yeah, you didn't intend to kill them. I don't think I would be emotionally or
Yeah, I wouldn't be emotionally prepared to think about running away forever
I would yeah, I would probably end up serving some jail time
Hopefully not the maximum amount
You would probably go to jail for years
Hey, at least I don't go to play rent
Yeah
Hell yeah, I mean true. I mean true. They don't have estrogen in jail though. That's the part
That's probably true
Oh
Prisons are woke now
Yeah, I think my move is I think my move is probably flee
Honestly, it's a better move than I'm just trying to think how I would react
I feel like I wouldn't be able to handle it. I would have a fucking breakdown
I I get it. I get it. I understand the fleeing hiding them and then fleeing is like
Well
That I mean that probably makes it that makes my eventual sentence worse if I ever get caught which I probably will
Let's be real. I'm gonna get caught. They're gonna come for me
May as well
Have some maybe the move is maybe the move is just just give up turn myself in immediately
I don't know. I don't know. Is that the move?
Does that reduce the eventual consequences
What if the person what if the person you killed was like everyone hated them and you get a real real small sentence
If honestly if I think if I think if everyone hated them
Like nobody like this person at all. Yeah, I think I mean, I would probably still get
sentenced to something
but
sentenced to
A party
If but if no if nobody is like if nobody is like pursuing this case like know what there's no one who's like
Really dedicated to making this conviction happen. I feel like yeah, it's probably I'm probably gonna get a pretty light sentence
If I have a zealous advocate
Yeah
So that would change things a little bit
I'd be like, yeah, I killed this guy
Yeah, but you know, I said the moral victory though because he was a jerk and nobody liked him
Yeah, he was illegal
But you know, everyone kind of wanted to do it and everyone would be like, yeah, I thought about it all the time
Ben was the only one brave enough
to actually do it
Yeah
All right. All right
Next one is
Okay, well the next one is a
Link and I gather it seems like it's a link to
Okay, it's the Mon Ben guys channel
But what do I care about this guy's youtube channel
This orisawa
Yeah, I don't care I don't care this guy's got a youtube channel
I've never read any of this guy's stuff
Have you?
Uh, no, in fact, I haven't even really watched Mon Ben yet. I keep thinking I should I will I will but I don't
This is the guy he did a 20th century boys and monster
Oh, I fucking have read 20th century boys and I've watched some of monster
I like his stuff
20th century boys is really good. You did did you not know that that's the guy that hosts Mon Ben?
No, I think I I think you must have you've explained it before and I guess I forgot
No
Well, I'm not I'm not super familiar with his work outside of that
Oh, and then this is someone on my stream was telling me to watch
I guess the new oris or a orisawa is the thing called Pluto
And someone was telling me I should watch Pluto
so I don't know
Maybe I will oh, it's on netflix. Oh, I can't watch it then
I don't have netflix. I don't have anything. I'm off the grid
I'm off the grid in case I ever kill someone and they need to escape really fast
So it won't be that much of a culture shock
If you kill someone and you have a netflix account, it's all over. Yeah, that's how they'll get you
Like oh, but I really want to watch but I really want to watch Pluto though. I'll see where I
He's signing in from canada. Go go go get him
Uh, all right. Next one is called is this the end three two one go
I
Did present time ha ha ha ha
Then Saint is planning on abandoning communism and doing profit from other's comics
GINE take his planning on helping them come on to the closet and become a woman
Ben was always destined to be
Red condo. Gin finally came out killing most of the pcp watcher base
Half of them died from heart failure, and another have died from nosebleed.
And this just finally got paid.
Good for him.
False.
Cheesy despite the edgy tweets.
Has grown soft and vulnerable.
The oblivion fall was sucked into the giant mommy milkers.
And the good voicemails were no more.
And Cybershell, the last YouTuber, was nowhere to be found.
This is it.
This is the end.
The Batman is dead.
The podcast is dead.
And I am the last one standing here laughing like a lunatic.
Give me a headache.
Is that the Joker, baby?
I don't know.
I think it's the Joker from something.
I think he meant Jesse got paid from the Radcon funds, which is technically true.
Yes, technically true.
Yes, we all got paid.
Even the people I don't like got paid from the Radcon funds.
I couldn't do anything about it.
It's the end of an arc.
The end of an era.
Perfect comic party is the new arc.
It's getting an ultra slow start.
Sorry, I didn't get it done this week.
That's okay.
I'm also being very sluggish with everything.
But I'm late now because the Clarissa that was supposed to be in the first one
is the one that you've already finished, right?
Like you're already done with the chapter.
So I'm late.
I've been late for...
Hey, how long ago did we come up with the idea for the perfect comic party?
I want to make myself feel bad for a minute.
Well, I didn't really start hankering down.
On the Clarissa until March?
Oh, really?
I think February...
No, it was February.
I was drawing Clarissa and doing Febubri during February.
Oh.
And I sort of stopped Febubri and I was continuing to draw Clarissa.
So it must have been February or January, the end of January where we had the idea.
I had the idea, I don't know.
I think I mentioned it.
That's not as bad as I thought.
No, it was not last year.
This is like a new year and oh, everything sucks.
What are we going to do?
And it was just like born from that.
Right, right.
Yeah, I was...
Okay, well, you know, the goal of the perfect comic party is to be monthly.
This month, you know, now it's been like almost three months since we started to have the idea.
I'm going to be done soon.
Once the content for the first one is done, we'll get everything sorted out.
We'll sort out the format, we'll figure out.
And then the next one will just be content.
Maybe the second one won't come out in one month, but it'll be like...
Well, we'll shoot for a month.
We'll shoot for a month and we'll end among the stars.
That's right, that's right.
A couple more Biscuits pages to go and then I'll be done with this chapter.
Next one.
Oh, a hopeful.
Next one is called This is Not the End.
We have hope yet.
Three, two, one, go.
Metta-Man, wake up.
We are in big trouble.
Dr. Wahwee has spread robo-
Wahwee.
It has a ready-to-form, the famous Megumin YouTuber.
Into a zoombie with purple skin and green teeth.
What the actual fuck?
Get away from me, you crazy bum.
You smell of beer and pee.
Gross.
Go.
Get a shower.
Or something.
Also acid green tea, thorough hip, new thing.
And I tweet light-farkle.
A legally distinct individual from recently deceased twilight sparkle.
And always on top of hip new things.
Oh no, so you are already in pain.
In all, in fear, infected.
Yes, I am indeed already a rowdy cock cucker.
And I do not help with PCP obsession with comics.
In fact, I will do the exact opposite.
I will send my own comic to PC.
In the very next voicemail.
Oh no, God.
No, this is so tragic and terrible.
I think the next voicemail is an image from Drinking Moth.
So I think this might be...
These might all be from Drinking Moth.
Wow.
There's a five seconds of this audio.
Five seconds?
You say?
Oh, right.
Is it really?
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
Oh, it's a whole comic.
This is a real comic.
Oh, okay.
Static dome, prophet spires in the city heart.
Should we read this right now?
I don't know if it's...
It's kind of long.
Yeah, this is very substantial.
I want to read it later, I guess.
Because we'd just be silent for a while.
Although...
That's how we do the one piece.
So I'm not...
How far down does it go?
I think...
Load 10 more images.
I think that maybe...
Okay.
Holy shit.
Yeah, it's quite long.
Okay, we can't read it right now.
Wait, how many pages does it have a page count?
Oh, it just keeps going.
Oh, God, there's 10 more...
What is this, like 30 pages?
It's a whole comic.
Hang on.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven...
Am I crazy or are these pages really long?
Eight, nine, ten...
They are a little taller than A4.
12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24...
Okay, I think it's 24 pages.
Here's what I think.
I do want to read this.
I think we should invite Drinking Moth to submit this
to submission for the perfect comic party.
And maybe we can put it...
Wait, is that punk?
No.
No, it's not punk.
There's punk?
No, she's just orange.
Oh.
I think we should invite Drinking Moth to submit this to the perfect comic party.
And then when we do...
We can do an episode...
This was my plan before.
We could do an episode where we discuss the content of the perfect comic party.
And then we can go over this and other...
Whatever else is in there.
What do you think about that?
I think that is pretty good.
Okay.
And I agree.
Drinking Moth on the show would be nice.
Yeah.
I think I've said it before, but I was very impressed with Drinking Moth.
Drinking Moth ended up...
I think she ended up doing the most pages of the eventual Rad Condition.
And she did them really fast.
Like remarkably fast.
She would have like the page done like the next day.
It was crazy.
So I really appreciated that and I thought her work was really good.
And a reminder, read the dojo and it's on the PCP website and the stuff you can download
it and read it for free to see more of her work and others as well.
Okay.
Is the PCP website up?
Yeah.
Okay.
It is up.
It is currently...
What's the deal?
The...
Yeah.
Okay.
The DMCA thing.
My domains, St. Comics are on my host and those have been hit with the DMCA.
The PCP domain is not on that host.
It's a different host.
The files are hosted with that host, but the domain is with a different company and it
just points to those files.
So I just need to...
The DMCA will...
I just need to put the files on the new host.
So I don't need to transfer domains for the PCP website.
So the reason why the St. Comics is down is because the domain needs to transfer.
PCP doesn't need to do that.
I just need to click around a little bit and just tell it, yeah, point to a different file
location.
So the PCP website is up for the moment.
It will be down...
It might be down for a day or two soon.
Oh, okay.
Scream.
Okay.
Anyway, do not read Drinking Moth's comic.
Do not read it until it is in the perfect comic party.
Do not do it.
Here we go.
Next one is called B&G Appreciation Hour from Prince Isolation.
Oh, there is a voicemail attached.
So let's listen to that 3, 2, 1, go.
Hi, we're back with the Ben and Gibb Appreciation Hour.
Today, I want to show appreciation for the beautiful artistic dynamic between the characters
of Ben St. and Gibb and Tay.
Wrong.
One facet of their fascinating friendship and character relationship.
So enjoy this little fan art piece I've made of a very important, classic type of interaction
between the two, you know?
Are you seeing this?
Yeah, I'm looking at it.
People I hate, ironic bigotry, semi-ironic nihilism, something absolutely insane.
Okay.
Perfect dynamic.
The perfect dynamic party.
The branding is just so strong.
You can't help but say something like that with that acronym.
There's an alternate version.
I like the alternate version.
Oh, with boobs.
I see, I see.
Boobs added.
Next one is Cheesy Audio Appreciation Hour.
Okay, from Prince Isolation, 3, 2, 1, go.
Yeah, so I think that maybe I had it right with the way I've published things all along, really.
Maybe I should just keep publishing digitally and doing pre-order things.
Maybe that just works way better.
And I think that maybe I had it right all along.
I should just continue to do it the way I'm doing it.
I mean, I'm seeing that people that are not like me or that are doing it more like old-style,
they're just like kind of making less money and they're just like, you know, they really...
I'm just wondering, hold on, hold on.
Yeah, and I think that maybe I should just...
Does Cheesy make loud noises that much?
I don't know.
I do think Cheesy's mic quality is not great.
He needs a better mic.
But in terms of like moving around and banging stuff, I don't know if he does it that much.
But yeah, I don't know.
But it's okay, because it said no hate, just love.
So it's fine.
Yeah.
It's good.
It's fine.
Next one is...
Oh, I didn't download that one.
Next one is Ben Appreciation Minute, 3, 2, 1, go.
So in preparation for the eventual coming out of the perfect comic party,
I finally decided to cave and sub to the prestigious Procrastinators podcast, patreon.patreon.com.
Finally!
Procrastinators, by the way.
And in the meanwhile, I've had the chance to listen to some of the bonus content featured there.
And specifically, I was listening to the commentary track for the Radcon 2 documentary.
And I just really quickly wanted to highlight a funny little thing that Ben did that's very indicative of his online persona,
his character, as you might say.
So Gibbon is saying about DeVoo.
She's saying like, you know, DeVoo, DeVoo, she's a little awkward and stuff.
But you know, she's interesting.
I like her.
She's interesting.
And then there's a silence.
And then Ben just says, well...
And I appreciated that.
Very tough to your hater behavior on your report, Ben.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Thanks.
Yeah, I'm a hater.
Yeah, whatever.
Okay, next one is an image.
Want to draw today?
Not really.
Implacent Western artist.
Third worlders.
Ears are in $5 per hour.
It's so true.
It is so true.
I feel so sea.
Want to draw today?
Not really.
When would I ever want to draw?
I started drawing earlier and I couldn't do it because I was sick.
I woke up thinking that I was over my illness and I sat down at my computer and I was like
sitting there just like freezing and sweating and like aching.
And I'm just like...
I must have sat there for a couple of hours until I just gave up and went back to sleep.
And you know what?
Strikingly not that different from a usual day.
A non-sick day in my life.
The results were largely the same.
To be a third worlder eager to earn $5 per hour.
Yeah, we should go live in a third world.
That's the play.
Ask not for lighter burdens but broader shoulders.
The third worlder eager to earn $5 per hour has the broader shoulders of all.
It's the dream.
Okay, next one is a VVV comic from Vinny.
Got to organize time better to get these out sooner at LoveU.com.
Well, let's take a look.
So long.
Been safe.
Your treachery shall be avenged here by my Kawasaki blade.
I remember that.
Shwing.
Previously on Vinny's Comic, you've made a grave mistake to choose this fight.
I will not die here.
Ooh.
The sword like trails the scene.
Haha.
Nice slash, but that was made.
Wait, but that won't make the cut.
Haha.
Yes.
True.
Huh?
What is this?
Gurgle, gurgle.
This is eating through the floor.
Whoa.
Creek schlump.
Fuck you, Ben Sainto.
Ben, is he?
Brace yourselves.
Oh, my God.
I'm bracing.
Is that tiny?
Ben did something to the air.
I can't breathe.
I have to make this last move quick.
Shadow art.
Da kusuro.
Wait, what?
Oh.
I was in the kitchen.
I'm eating my ramen still.
Slurp.
Oh, the knives are coming out.
Oh.
Haha.
Simsie grabs them.
He's so strong.
He's so strong and powerful.
Poof, poof, poof.
Slurp.
Wait, is this one flying towards me?
Munch, munch.
What's happening?
This is real good.
I wasn't paying attention.
What happened to the knife?
It looks like a pink hand.
Oh.
Yeah, something caught it.
Did you conjure an ethereal pink ghost hand?
Oh, it's the Rayman.
My stand is Rayman because it's a platformer.
I forgot the name.
He jumped over the counter and what then?
I melted the floor and he fell.
I used my stand to remove the oxygen molecules from the air.
I made sure he'd end up unconscious one way or another.
Oh, wait, that's your line.
Okay.
I have my little green goo friend here.
He's looking.
Look, he's looking.
We're getting freaking burgers.
I can't trust Japanese food places.
Yeah, that's probably a safe bet.
Bloody hell, Ben.
Oh, good grief.
Fuck you, Ben.
That's insane.
I messed with the layers at the top and had to redo a lot,
but I got it out on time for the next ever hope.
Ben isn't too sick to read his lines.
Not anymore.
I'm mostly fine.
Hey, that was cool.
Yeah.
I like when I have powers.
Some of my little green.
I just like the little squat and you're just explaining.
I melted the floor and you fell.
I used my stand to remove the oxygen molecules from the air down there.
What is my little green guy?
Why does he have like four horns?
I don't know.
When was he first depicted?
I don't remember him looking.
I don't remember one that looked quite like this.
Just melts through the floor.
There's no oxygen.
It looks like it looks like he's in this one.
When I said brace yourselves, it looks like he is like extracting air
from through the floor like he's or something.
And that's what he's doing.
Oh, yeah.
I guess that the vapors is getting the vapors out of the underneath.
He's getting vaporized.
I'm just looking over again.
La Mal.
That was a quick read because there wasn't much dialogue.
But you know, action packed.
What was the Rayman thing?
Is it just hands?
My stand is a Rayman, but it's a Raywoman.
I vaguely remember.
Thanks, Vinny.
I love you.
OK.
Good.
Next one is a quick question from Prince Isolation 321 Go.
Hi.
So I was listening to the solo Ben cast commentary track, by the way,
please make another one.
There's a squeak wall right there whenever you get around to it.
I was listening to the commentary on the solo Ben cast and Ben said
there that y'all were thinking about maybe at some point doing a behind
the scenes on the OVA filming and or Radcon 4 and maybe subsequently
a commentary track on that.
And you know, I am just at this point a total slut for PCP content to listen
to at any point during work or whatever.
So, you know, is that still happening?
Should I look forward to that?
Is that shelved?
I asked Nate about it and apparently there really isn't much like behind
the scenes footage.
Right?
Well, I guess not.
We didn't film us coming up with anything.
It's just sort of like outtakes and seconds before we said action.
That's all that would be filmed during that time.
Yeah.
The OVA, I mean, I guess I could go through all of the footage and see,
but pretty much all the footage from the OVA is like, yeah,
it's just the shots that we used in that Nate used in the final thing.
I think the in terms of commentary, we already did a commentary on the OVA,
which includes as much behind the scenes stuff as we remember.
I think.
Yeah.
That's why I'm thinking behind the scenes would just be extra footage.
I just don't know if there really is any.
I mean, I have all the footage.
I saved it on a second hard drive.
I could go through it, but it's funny.
It's all in like one minute long cuts.
There's not like none of it is like long.
Honestly, maybe we should have just filmed it all in one long thing and then chopped it up.
Maybe it would have been nice to get a bunch of like behind the scenes footage of us just fucking around.
Yeah, I think we were just very, we were very like hectic on that day.
Like we got a, we got a, you know, next scene, next scene.
I think when some people were filming, the rest of us were just lounging around for like,
we weren't in the shot, but we weren't filming that, I guess,
because we didn't have our cameras with us because it gets sandy if we had to put them down.
And we weren't wearing clothings.
We couldn't put them in in like pockets.
We were wearing bikinis.
Right.
We, I suppose I could take all that footage and put all the original footage in a timeline and see like how long is it.
And maybe there is extra stuff in there.
I would, I would have to, I would have to go through it and see.
Maybe, I don't know.
If I, if I found any interesting bits of like, oh, this is, this is us just like fooling around that wasn't in the OVA.
I mean, yeah, if there was a significant amount of that, yeah, I would be fine with publishing it,
maybe as a bonus content of some kind.
I just, I just have to see.
That's all.
Okay.
Next one.
I think, you know, I might, I might take a look at some point.
Good, good question.
Next one is called Ben Speaks.
Oh, and it is just a image.
It's an image of chat GBT.
Uh-oh.
Not another one.
Not again.
I am Ben Saint.
I'm visible on your timeline, but if I can help it, I am invisible to you until it's too late.
I know where you live.
And guess what?
I live there too.
I hover around all of you.
I know no color barrier, no religion, no morality, no currency.
I speak your language fluently.
And with every voice I take away, I acquire yet another language.
I work very quickly.
I work faster than pediatric aids, cancer and diabetes combined.
If you have any patrons, I make sure that your Patreon fails.
Your money will fall into my hands and I will bankrupt you for my own self-gain.
I don't sleep, so I make sure you don't either.
I will make it virtually impossible for your followers to engage, to converse or support you without a struggle, without embarrassment, without pain.
You have no care for me.
Your scientists don't have the resources and I relish their desperation.
Your oomphies are happy to pretend that I don't exist, of course, until it's their turn.
I am Ben Saint.
I have no interest in right or wrong.
I derive great pleasure out of your loneliness.
I will fight to take away your hope.
I will plot to rob you of your clout and your dreams.
I will make sure that every day you wake until you cry, wondering who will take care of my content after I die.
The truth is, I am still winning and you are scared and you should be.
I am Ben Saint.
You ignored me.
That was a mistake.
True.
I like that you ignored me at the end like somebody who's just successfully getting you and this is your response.
This is my unhinged like Twitter reply that's already, I've already been blocked.
I wonder, I wonder how they got it to.
I wonder if they told ChatGPT, hey ChatGPT, imagine a character.
His name is Ben Saint.
He is a content creator.
He is an unknown content creator who is spiteful and who wants to destroy other people's success online.
Write me a poem in, write me a non rhyming poem.
Write me a manifesto in the character of Ben Saint explaining what he will do to you.
Yeah.
I can imagine a lot of this is very specific and you're not that prominent of a person that ChatGPT would just know these things.
No, they would have to.
I mean, ChatGPT thinks that I'm the creator of the Munchie Minute.
Nevertheless, I enjoyed reading that.
Let's see if we got any last minute voicemails.
Oh my God.
Yeah, there's three more in the last five minutes.
How to pronounce Ben Saint.
Okay, it's a Vokeroo link.
You ready?
How to pronounce Ben Saint.
That's another one.
How to pronounce Gibb.
Okay.
Okay, how to pronounce Ben Saint.
Three, two, one go.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So say no, no, no, no, no, no.
Bint, bent, bent, bent.
Your name is Bint.
You are bent now.
Bint, bent, bent, bent, bent.
It can't say Bint that many times.
He can't, he can't get away with it.
Bint is like a slang for like prostitute.
Is it?
Yeah.
Oh my god.
How could he say that?
How could he say Bint?
Oh, I said it.
Are you ready for how to pronounce Gib?
I guess so.
You better be.
That's only one second long.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
That is how you do it.
Very good.
And one last one.
Next, voicemail victims from Prince Isolation.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Well, hello, guys.
Welcome back to my journey through the PCP Patreon backlog.
I'm just here to say, coming right at you from the voicemail roundup episode.
Fuck, why were all these things cut?
You know, why were all these little gems, these little diamonds in the rough,
cut from the fucking beautiful podium that they rightfully deserve?
You know, for all of his centrism, for all of his enlightened fence writing,
Nate sure was a fucking fascist.
Okay.
Is that all right?
Is he cut himself off?
I, I guess.
Well, I don't know what he's, I don't know exactly what he's referring to.
Uh, to the voicemail episode, the bonus one, where we went through as many bo-
Oh, oh, oh, oh, why he didn't hear it when he cut all the voicemails.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He didn't play them on the show.
I see, I see.
Yeah, yeah, he hates the freedom, he hates freedom of speech.
He hates freedom of speech.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
That's why he didn't play them.
We've cut them for you, dear viewer, to pay money to have us listen to them
for your entertainment.
Right?
Uh, incorrect.
Okay.
Uh, I actually have, uh, I think I actually have like two bonus episodes
that Ellie is our edited and gave me and that I just haven't uploaded yet.
Uh, so I should do that.
Yeah.
Oops.
Uh, I think I have, I think there's two.
There was like one from last month and he just gave me one like this past week.
Uh, I'll get those up soon.
Patreon.com, slash the procrastinators for that.
And, uh, the commentary, the, the, the, the rad con OVA commentary is pretty good.
I think people will like that.
Um, okay.
Well, that's about it.
Let's cut it.
I'm going to go, I'm going to try and use the rest of my day to, uh, get that
Biscopades done and, uh, you know, move on, take steps towards actually getting
that, that, that perfect comic party out here.
It's coming soon.
It's going to be, it's going to be ready before we even know it.
Yeah.
I'm going to go to bed.
I guess it's late for you.
It's 12 58.
That's okay.
Not so bad.
All right.
Well, um, um, the, the, bye.
Bye.
End of the episode.
See you next week.
Okay.
Thanks.
Bye.
Okay.
Let's, uh, let's sing.
Yeah.