Hello everyone, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm the best guy ever, and we're all here for you.
I love Bane, and I love memes.
Hippocrit is here.
I'm English, and I got fucking yellow taste, nigga.
Digibro is here, finally, after such a long time.
I really thought that I was going to be the person on here with the worst hygiene, and
then Ben Saint showed up.
There it is, Ben, there it is.
I'm going to, yeah, no need to introduce me, Nate, I'm Ben Saint.
Oh yeah, your smell, your smell preceded you.
I'm Ben Saint.
I'm out of time.
I am here to dispel any and all rumors to the effect that my hygiene is anything less
than impeccable.
We're looking forward to that court case being settled down, okay.
Good luck.
The Davoo.
The Davoo is present.
Hashtag sockless foot lives matter.
Jesse would not agree, and Munchy wears tiny hats, that's all I need to know about him.
What?
No!
Oh my god!
Not the piss!
Instantly!
Press one for Munchy's piss!
One, one, one, one!
He's running off of the stuff for us.
Hey yeah, he's doing number one.
Well, yeah.
That's right.
Wow.
Real synergy there.
I'm honestly a little bit disappointed in myself.
That was not nearly enough.
It wasn't a powerful stream.
Yeah, it was kind of a normal piss as opposed to the like, the fucking intense, wildness.
My fucking kill myself.
If I can't pee good, why is it, what am I good for?
You've run this meme into the ground.
That's right, it's all right.
It's all right.
We're all desensitized to the sound of your piss so much that no one even got grossed out.
Let's help the audience.
Let's get some germics.
Brought to you, PCP.
Brought to you by Jermix.
Brought to you by Jermup.
You guys know the show Monk, the obsessive compulsive detective from the early 2000s?
Yeah, sure.
That show was sponsored by Clorox.
That was, was that really sponsored by Clorox?
Yeah, it was sponsored by Clorox, because fucking Monk always would like, use a wipe after,
before and after shaking anyone's hands.
So.
So much for journalistic integrity, am I right?
Okay.
So much for the tolerant left, am I right?
That's what I was trying to say.
Yeah.
Anyway, we're talking about hygiene.
Hygiene.
So I went to Urban Dictionary.
Yeah.
I told the definition.
Hygiene.
I have a friend named Gene.
This show is dedicated to him.
Urban Dictionary is the practice, to practice the art of cleanliness or to be clean.
So that's really boring.
What was that in Urban Dictionary words?
I don't know.
Just a normal dictionary word.
Wait, hang on.
That's the top definition?
Maybe there's a better one than the second.
The way that it's phrased is like a verb.
Okay, wait, I got it.
Okay.
Here's the second definition.
That's like the second most popular.
Hygiene.
The main factor in how close people are willing to stand next to you in any given situation.
That one I more agree with.
I wouldn't be surprised if a way to, to greet someone named Gene is probably on the list.
I would, let's see how far down that is.
I happen to know it.
I get that joke in, in a fucking X-Men movie and I really like that.
Really?
It's like one of the other ones.
Gene Gray, Gene Gray or something.
Yeah.
Hygiene.
I happen to know a quick and easy catchy guide to how to hygiene.
Okay.
It goes, you gotta wash your ass if you must, you gotta brush your hair if you must, you
gotta brush your teeth if you must or else you'll be funky.
Solid advice.
But I like funky.
I, um, I, I also know a funky.
Here's a, here's a thing I hate about the general concept of, of anything related to hygiene
is that funky is considered gross when it is actually my favorite type of music.
So fuck everyone.
But, but the Beatles, neither the Beatles nor Led Zeppelin are funk guys.
Oh no, Led Zeppelin have some funky tunes.
You just gotta look.
I, I guess that's true.
I feel similarly hippo.
I mean, soupy balls is my favorite kind of music and it's always getting a bad rap.
By the way, I have, I have a second easy guide to remember the cleanliness thing.
And it was George Carlin's method, which is just never clean yourself ever.
Just don't worry about it.
The only things you have to clean daily are asshole armpits, something in teeth.
Fuck.
What is it?
Balls.
Gooch.
Balls and teeth.
Something like that.
Yeah.
It's close enough.
Asshole armpit, balls and teeth.
Balls and teeth.
Ah, no suck a little baby.
Well, so we at the PCP are all like foremost experts on the subject of hygiene.
Like if you were going to come to somebody for hygienic advice, we are definitely the
people you would come to.
So this is going to be the most informed, knowledgeable podcast in the world.
I thought it would be a bunch of blue pill, uh, libtard revolutionaries who are here
to change the game about hygiene standards and smash the hygiene patriarchy that's been
imposed on the world for so long and say, fuck that shit.
You don't need to be clean.
You just need to be a stink boy and embrace your odor and be, you know, as close to like
Ben as possible.
That's, you know, the-
I hate you, Nate.
I hate you.
I hate all of you.
You're all done.
Ben, I really wonder what you were expecting when you decided to come onto the hygiene.
I expected to be treated as a human being.
Before we get started here, I need to mention, uh, we record PCP every week and last week's
recording ever since we decided that it was going to be hygiene, I have elected to not
change my clothes or do any hygienic process whatsoever.
Gonzo Hygiene Journalism, all right.
And I have to say, um, dear God.
Uh, Munchy, that's- I'm real glad that we have time.
The only words that could come out.
The only analysis.
I'm so lucky.
We are real lucky to have a hardcore, deep-covered journalist like you out there in the field,
Munchy.
I'm getting the germs.
Well, that's right.
What has been the reaction of people to you during this time?
Any difference?
I've noticed anything?
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
It got kind of significant.
Like, after the first, like the second day, someone was like, you're wearing the same
shirt as yesterday.
I'm like, get used to it.
That sounds like a personal problem right, you shit.
And then after like the four or fifth day, people started noticing like the stink lines
coming off of me because I was in a loony town.
Right, right.
And then recently, it's just gone, like very quickly, I realized like, even the minimal
hiding that I put myself through, it's still, like, I changed my clothes.
That ended up self is huge.
But now, like, my pants might as well have been peed in.
Like, they might as well have been just completely soaked in pee.
They might as well have been.
The amounts of driblets that build up over a week are not to, are substantial.
My balls are literally like a beef stew.
Like they're literally like beef stew.
Oh my God, that visual.
Oh my God, it's even funnier because I know exactly what he's talking about because I've
been there.
So, like, I know, I know what it feels like to have swamp ass.
Hey guys, show of hands, what is like the, your lowest point in terms of hygiene?
What's the longest you've ever gone without a shower?
And what happened?
Well, I'm going to have to change, I'm going to use a different definition than longest
time without a shower.
The low point of hygiene for me, I mean, pretty much my entire teens, but, like, because
I showered pretty infrequently and I had really long, nappy, shitty hair that I didn't, I
would never brush.
So, like, basically what my hair would do is it would just keep getting worse and worse
until it became such a horrible forest of tangles that I'd have to have my dad sit down
for like an hour and untangle my hair.
Like, like, like great apes.
Yeah.
Or like that scene in the Princess Diaries where that guy snaps off a fucking brush in
the princess's hair and has to, he's like, you're broke my brush, why would you do that?
Hey, Ben, you're a great ape because I like you.
I thank you, I thank you and I love you.
The first time I let my hair get out of control, I was 12 and it got to a point where, because
my idea was I would make dreadlocks because then I'd never have to brush it again.
Good.
But making dreadlocks requires maintenance and effort and I put none of that in so it
just became a huge, like, fucking nest on my head.
And my grandma starts offering me $50 to get a haircut and I didn't take it because I wanted
her to give me $75 because there was, there was anime DVDs I wanted to buy so I decided
I would wait until she offered higher.
And then my dad came up to me and he said, look, I'll give you $100 to cut your hair
because you can't just bleed Mima out of all her fucking money because she was broke
at the time.
I was like, sick.
You're a bastard, Digi.
He said, he said I'll never do this again though.
So I got my haircut, I got $100 and then I grew my hair out again and I started, you
know, essentially letting the same thing happen but now I knew I wasn't going to get any money.
I just was lazy but my dad would just sit there and untangle my hair for like hours
every couple of months when it got to a point where it was just like too much for anyone
to bear.
Why didn't he just stealthily cut it?
Yeah, I was going to say.
There was one time he did have to cut out, like he had to because it was just impossible
and he had to just cut off like a huge amount of it.
But that's not even the worst in terms of like hygiene, like that's aesthetically awful
but the worst that I got in terms of hygiene was, do you guys, are you familiar with Andrew
W.K.?
I don't know.
Only with the name.
He's a musician and general personality.
You guys would probably know him for the fact that he did panels at Brony conventions because
of the fact that he became convinced he was a reincarnation of Pinkie Pie.
Oh yeah.
That's true.
Yes.
Because Andrew W.K. is obsessed with parties and his whole thing is that he just talks
about parties constantly and everything's a party and that's his life.
And so when Pinkie Pie came out then everyone was like, oh this is basically Andrew W.K.
When's the guy with that fucking album, the bloody face?
That's why there's the party hard shirt with Pinkie Pie bleeding out of her face which
is the cool shirt.
Oh right.
It all makes sense.
Andrew W.K. writes all these different weird articles and columns on different places and
he had this one thing, I think it was even a YouTube video, like an analytical style
YouTube video before those were even everywhere, about how you don't need to wash your hair
because he was explaining that your scalp produces natural oils which shampoo are just
washing out of it.
And so if you allow your hair to start perpetuating its own oils then it will eventually be even
healthier than if you were putting shampoo in it.
Right, I remember a cracked article saying that when you shower it removes what is called
the horny layer for some reason and the horny layer does something to your immune system
that's good because we evolved to be apes that don't fucking have hygiene or civilization
or more than two people in a room at the time.
It's incompatible, fuck the horny layer.
True, but we also evolved to be a species that dies at 30.
Yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah.
So this article came out and there is some substance to it.
My brother Victor, he actually doesn't wash his hair anymore because everything that he
was using was just making it worse.
Every different kind of shampoo wasn't working and now that he has stopped his hair actually
has improved.
I tried to do this for probably a month and I have really, really bad dandruff and my
scalp became magma.
It got to a point.
There was no hard surface on the top of my head anymore.
It was all like a mushy layer.
The kill of the first flame.
I'm at that point right now, DJ.
You and me are fucking kindred.
You're dandruff boys, bro.
It's dandruff boys.
If I ran my hands through my hair, it would be like this mushy mashed potato-y surface
that would just have blood and shit in it.
Jesus Christ.
God damn it.
You already fucking usurped my entire lowest point story, which was I went two weeks without
showering in the summer and whenever I scratched my leg, there was this gray goo that scraped
off of it that I thought could take over the world.
I think I was just going to leave because I don't like this stuff.
It wasn't nearly as bad as what you were describing.
Gray goo is definitely how I describe what was coming off of my head as well as like,
I mean, my head, the thing is, if I go like three days without showering, my dandruff
gets bad enough that I start scratching it and I start bleeding from my scalp.
Fuck me.
I'm pretty used to blood coming out of my head.
What the fuck?
Even right now, if I scratch the back of my head, I can draw blood with relativism.
Did you come to get that looked into?
I don't know if that's normal.
Contrary to popular belief.
People always say, like people always talk about how like they joke that I never shower.
No, I actually shower.
I mean, I don't shower every single day, like what some people, what normies do.
But I do have to shower every couple of days to prevent my scalp from turning into a fucking
volcanic crater.
So yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, for me, it's like when my hair, when my hair gets long enough, like as my hair
was.
Is he done?
He's done.
He is.
Yeah, my hair was like six plus inches up until a couple of weeks ago, up until a month
ago.
And like when it's that long, if it's been 37 hours since my last shower, it's like I'm
fucking like planting my face into like the sweaty ass of an athlete.
On the subject, on the subject of hair, here's, here's my thing.
If I go more than like maybe four days without showering, my hair gets pretty greasy.
And the thing, the thing that always strikes me about that experience is if, is if I go
out for a cigarette and I light it up and I'm thinking about what if an ember came off
and just landed on my hair.
And I wonder, and I wonder if the grease on my hair is, is enough and is the right kind
that it would just go up in flames.
And sometimes I'm pretty tempted to just tap my hair with the end of the cigarette just,
just to see what would happen.
But I like, but I like, but I like, but every time thus far, every time thus far I've walked
myself back from that precipice.
I haven't jumped yet.
You need to go full Lord of Cinder one of these days.
Did you, didn't you have someone light your hair on fire once in a while?
That would be, that would be the darkest timeline of the PCP is that one day my hair just goes
up and I'm just, and I look like that guy in the second, and I look like that guy in
the second season, and I look like that guy in the second half of Ghost in the Shell.
Yeah.
Oh right, that guy.
With a messed up face.
Two face.
One of us needs to link the flame, Ben, and I, I nominate you.
Thanks, man.
The most ripe.
By the way, Ben, you and I, when we were young lads, we both had very long hair.
Yes.
Just in contrast to Jesse.
And as I remember-
I feel like I was pretty good about washing it though.
Yeah.
I think we both were.
And I remember spending a lot of time brushing it.
Ben and I both had hair roughly down to our waist in like high school just for various
reasons.
Wow.
And I remember wanting to, I specifically was motivated by a depiction of one character
from the Wheel of Time series, which you might be familiar with.
The Rans like soldier guys, right?
It was one of the Rans like top dudes.
The ones that have the braids.
I forget.
Yeah, there was like some group of men who had long braids and they tied silver bells
to them.
And I always thought that was the coolest shit, but I wanted to do that, never got around
to it.
But it stuck in my mind to this day.
Maybe, maybe one day.
Wait, wait.
No.
It wasn't his organization that had the braids.
It was some, one of the guys-
It was like some ethnicity.
One of the guys was just from some country where they did that.
Yeah, that's right.
Guys, can we, can we just as an aside talk about how great it is having short hair as
opposed to-
So much better.
Down to the ass hair.
I've decided I'm growing my hair a little long, not like crazy long, not down to my
waist long, but I'm going to let it, I'm going to let it get chaggy again.
Down to like, you know, the maybe shoulders in the back is fine.
But like-
Yeah.
God, having long hair is just such a fucking pain in the ass.
Yeah, it's a nightmare.
It's a nightmare.
But first of all, clogs your shower all the time.
Yeah.
Like every time I would have, any time I, a lot of the times when I cut my hair, it's
because my drain has started to get clogged and I go, well, that's a sign that it's time,
you know.
Yep.
You have to start using conditioner so it costs extra, you know, because if you get out
of the shower after just shampoo, your hair becomes a fucking brick.
Yeah, it is an essential thing to have conditioner when you have long hair for sure.
If it gets past a certain point, you got to brush it every day or several times a day.
My friend, I had a friend named Mike, who fucking would brush, he had like hair past
his shoulders.
It was just the kind of hair that doesn't grow super long, even though he'd been growing
it for like five years.
Yeah, sure.
But he would brush his hair constantly.
Like he had a brush on him at all times and he would just like, whatever he was sitting
around, he'd just start brushing at his hair, like maintaining it, making sure it's perfect.
Did you guys ever read stories about like old, old like lords and ladies of olden times?
Yeah.
No, I'm talking about like medieval stuff.
There's always this image of giving your hair a hundred brush strokes every day.
Like Nineve from the Wheel of Time would do that shit with a very long brown hair every
day.
Were you just like on a Wheel of Time?
Yeah.
The Wheel of Time, like the real historical account of lords and ladies.
Well, I'm willing to be credulous of the fact that old women used to, you know, women in
olden times brush their hair a hundred times.
That specific phrase I think is a Japanese thing though, the 100 strokes per day.
Yeah.
Well, this one was, you know, with a bunch of people.
I just thought Sephiroth was really cool.
Yeah, of course.
You were right.
Oh my God.
Bindi Sephiroth, if Sephiroth was real.
I spent a lot of time thinking about dyeing my hair silver, but I never did.
Dyeing your hair silver?
Yeah.
On the subject of having short hair.
So did I, dude.
So did I.
On the subject of having short hair.
The hair I'm at right now is like, you know how like humans, like the one second at the
end of the immortal clock and the dinosaurs were at noon or whatever.
Like me having short hair and the length I'm at right now is that is like the one second
before midnight and like the bombs go off and in my log in my locker.
What does that mean?
It means he needs a haircut in like a week, which is what he's trying to say.
I see.
I have, I have needed a haircut immediately for like years at a time.
I for my entire life, like up until like maybe like a year ago.
I have had the most flowing of mains you shall ever see.
Even more main full than Davos.
Even more main for you see, not only was my hair long, but it was like a curly sort
of like jungle, like like like bonsai, like I'm like going to napalm myself.
What was the actual length because I want to know.
The actual length was down to like like like below my shoulder blades and like above kind
of.
So I'm the person who's had the short, I'm someone who's had a reputation of having
this, you know, big hair for being not female, allegedly.
But I actually have had the shortest, I have had the shortest hair record of anyone in
this call.
It's not that your hair is, it's not that your hair is long.
It's that it is specifically big, that it flows outward as opposed to down and that's
what they would give.
That's kind of a majestic quality to me.
I wasn't fucking done anyway.
Up until recently, I've had, I've had like like long hair and it's been fucking awful
as did you could attest to now, now.
I've had mag, like I think I've specifically like intentionally inflicted myself with magma
brains.
What does that mean?
Okay.
Did you use like weird like volcano brain?
Oh, oh that.
Okay.
So it went like this.
I've had bad dandruff because I would just, like I just wouldn't shout when I was a little
baby boy, which I still am when I was a little, when I was a lesser baby boy, I just wouldn't
shower because it was, I thought it was fucking gay.
And so.
It is, right.
I, I would have a ton of dandruff.
And so I've, like, like it was hard for me to like brush my hair because it was so curly.
Like I just, I just couldn't do it.
So I, I came up with a system where I would, you know, look at on combs, on the little
like points on the, on each points, there is sort of like a rounded sort of nub to,
to make it easier on your scalp.
So one day I cut off all of the nubs.
So it was a hard, rigid surface.
And then when I scraped my scalp, the dandruff would come off and leave a sort of resin,
like a gray sort of like goopy, disgusting, bloody mess on the end of the comb.
I know that feel, dude.
I know, I know about the gray goo.
I know about like dead skin coming off and kind of like, in like rolls a little bit.
But I've never, it's never been bloody.
It's never been bloody in my experience.
Are you ever concerned that if you just pushed on that gray mush too hard, you'd get white
to your brain?
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Sometimes, sometimes I do it, like sometimes I'm bad to do it, like, I'm just like, I
just want to reach and I just want, I just want to feel it, I just want to feel it.
I just want to feel my brain.
Wait guys, is this, is this that thing where like, you know, you know how if you rub the
bottom of your foot, like the cells kind of ball up and the dead skin, you can just,
you can just rub your hands together.
You can just rub your hands together right now and you'll get a little bit of like gray
goo.
I'm doing it, I'm doing it.
Not that much because I just showered because I'm a clean boy, goddammit.
I've been denied fruits of god for a week.
What are you talking about?
Oh, oh right, changing, being clean.
The shower he's probably going to take immediately after this.
Exactly.
I am.
No, we want to hear from you again.
Okay.
Report in.
Right, I wasn't listening to most of that because it was gross and I fucking hate it.
You're the big beard boy, so we want to know about that situation.
Well, first I want to say that my hair was like DeVoo until like I decided to let it
keep growing and then it became heavy enough to pull it down and now if I shaved it off,
I'm not sure that it would grow back like outwards, like big, like an afro, like it
used to be when I was younger.
Yeah.
Yeah, when my hair gets passed like five inches, it becomes heavy enough to start being
pulled down, so then it just looks like a weird like upside down W. It looks like the
McDonald's symbol.
It looks terrible.
Yeah, so the longest my hair has been is actually in my give and take reviews.
It hasn't been before that that I had long hair.
I just sort of suddenly decided to have it and then based my whole YouTube icon iconography
around it and I'm scared to like change that at this point.
I don't know whether, but I have had like, like passing dreams of like, like not passing
dreams, but like fantasies of like, like just shaving it entirely off and then starting
fresh, being able to be bald for like a week.
In his flights of fancy, a give and dreams of being a bald boy for, for, I do too.
I was just going to say I want to see give and bald, but I feel like I have also thought
about shaving off my entire head like very frequently, but I feel like if I do that,
then my, the top part of my scalp would just melt down and I'll just become like a soup
head.
I'll be a soup head boy.
I suspect that give and bald will look like, uh, like a Walter White.
Like yeah.
Yeah.
I see that.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Just be careful.
Be careful how old you are when you do it.
I remember when a Stephen Colbert went to like the military for, to do shows there for
a week and he got his head shaved and it never grew back as full.
Yeah.
And that was sad.
That's why I, uh, that's why I keep growing mine out because even though I don't like
having, like having long hair, I want to savor all the time that I can because a big part
of why I kept my hair long is that my parents encouraged it growing up because my mom thinks
long hair is cool.
And my dad was jealous because he started balding in like his late 20s, so he hasn't
had a long, he just can't grow it.
See what he was doing was he was raising three crops with, for which to harvest hair when
the time was right.
Right.
Yeah.
My dad is bald and I'm probably going to go bald as well.
I've actually started going bald a little bit at the top, like the forehead and it's
annoying me.
Oh really?
It's annoying.
I have, I have fucking hair privileges.
All my uncles, like, like my hair descends from my mom's side and all the guys on my
mom's side have full heads of hair, no matter how old.
My grandpa is like in his mid 80s and his hair is becoming really thin through sheer
force of old, but it's still like he doesn't have any bald spots.
I'm like, yeah.
Fuck it.
No guys.
Okay.
Go on.
Uh, but yeah, you're talking about beards.
Yeah.
My, I think I have the largest, maybe aside from Ben, the largest beard growing capabilities
in this case.
My beard doesn't really get like big.
Like when I grew it long in like 2013 or 2014, it just kind of like, it just kind of grew
down and it would just kind of like, it would, I could just kind of like push it up against
my neck and it would just stay there.
Like it didn't get, it didn't get like big.
It got, I don't know.
Has your beard gotten bigger?
There was like a happy medium of length there.
Mine was at its biggest like a year and a half ago when I had that super long beard.
When you had that super, yeah, I don't think, I don't think it's been ever that big.
I think I've gotten close, but I shaved it away.
And recently I, you know, I shaved the bottom part of it and I had the mustache thing going.
One of my favorite things about give, well, it's just like, I really love that picture
that Jade Maraud drew of, you know, the one of you in the Ryuko costume with like the
hair goes all the way around as one like perfect circle of hair that has no separation
between like a beard and, you know, hair at the top of your head.
I really, really like that.
Which one was that?
The way you described it was strange.
It was, it was the one with, it was posted with the DigiSnow picture.
It was that and then you and the Ryuko cosplay.
And then it's just your beard and hair were depicted so, so, main like in that.
Yeah, unified.
So Nate, have you, have you ever experimented with facial hair?
Yeah, I can't grow it, dude.
I can't do it.
I've tried.
I mean, but by tried, I mean I just not shaved.
Yeah, we don't need to do this too much.
I want to talk about the hygiene of a beard.
Right, that's what I meant.
Right, right.
When my beard got super long, it was definitely a hygienic nightmare because, A, everything
I ate got in my beard.
Like everything.
And it just so happened that I was starting to go through a soup phase at the time.
So I would like, you know, like a little droplet of soup falls off of my spoon and it just
goes all the way trailing through the beard.
I'm just imagining you taking a spoon to Munchie's head, eating that soup.
Yeah!
You know?
Just die.
Stop it.
I won't, I am, I will, no way will anyone get me to edit this particular episode.
I would kill them.
Even right now.
I'm on it.
I'm on it, hippo.
I'm on the cake.
All right, good.
Please, please.
Take this one.
Even right now my beard is long enough that like everything I eat, I have to have a napkin
with me because like I constantly, I feel weird with anything's on my face or hands.
I have to like constantly wipe stuff down, so I always have to have stuff on me.
And there was a point, when it was at the super long point, there was a time where, like,
I would legit just find shit in my beard.
Like, like twigs and stuff, like, I'd just be stroking my beard and there'd be like
a piece of tree that had fallen off when I was outside smoking or something, you know?
I do want to say like, shaving the chin only is, that's the main bit.
If you get rid of the chin, then nothing really falls into a beard.
If you just trim your mustache like it's so that it's like straight, then it's fine.
Like, when I had that, it was really good.
I've never had like a big beard before, as I am a greater baby, however I slam a baby.
Right.
A greater baby.
I love that.
No, he's a dire baby.
Yeah.
I even started to shave my beard recently and I wanted to get it back.
However, even when I've had, like, at the height of my baby beard, I still, like, just
ever, ever so slightly, just the whisk, just a small, tiny little layer, I could feel,
I could feel the soup seeking out.
I could feel it.
I'll tell you right now, my beard drifts as bad as my head drifts and bleeds even
faster.
Oh, God.
Like, get this yourself.
I get some head dandruff if I go a while without sharing.
I don't, I don't get beard rift.
By the way, let me just say that I'm sitting right next to a full wall mirror and just seeing
the majesty that is my beard.
I look so fucking great.
I look so fucking great with a beard.
I agree.
I can see it.
Ben, when I found out that you shaved it after Bronicon, I literally, like, sent you,
like, a few messages saying that I was legitimately mad at you, if you remember correctly.
Yeah.
Well, I have an interesting-
The funny thing is that Ben has spent the last six months trying to grow it back out,
but he habitually picks-
Yeah.
This is-
Yeah, this is the thing.
I'm kind of embarrassed about it, but I was gonna mention it, is, yeah.
The whole time, I was like, I look so, I can't, I think, I don't know.
My face is not the worst, but it's not the best ever, either, in my opinion.
So the whole time, I didn't have a beard.
I was like, man, I wish I had the beard back, but yeah.
I have a nervous fucking thing where I will, like, pick my hair out and I would just pick
too hard and just make, like, a fucking hole in my beard, and then I would have to, I would
be like, I fucked it, and I would shave it and start again, and it took me months, it
took me months to fucking get that, to just hold off on that long enough for the beard
to take shape enough that I could have a little bit of leeway, and now if I pick a hair out
or two, like, it doesn't matter and you can't see it, um, but I'm back.
It's fucking back, baby.
Yeah!
Tea back!
Hashtag, max for five, tea back!
Yes, yes.
Uh, I didn't really get to talk about my general showering and stuff.
There have been times when I have not showered because, you know, even though I hate this,
the stank, I can't ever smell my own, so, you know, it takes a long time for me to notice.
I-
Even though I know it's there, and I can't smell it, I just, like, have it.
I, well, here's, I can smell my own, but the thing is that I don't mind it, and sometimes
I kind of like it, so I'm a monster.
Ben, no, okay.
I definitely mind my own.
BenSaint is definitely, if you know Ben in person, you will know his scent.
Fuck you, buddy.
Hey, you know what, guys?
Ben, it's the primary weapon of a homeless warrior, like, Ben, what else can you do?
We can't not bring this up, because your scent is so specific in particular, and it's
because your whole room, like, it gets to a point where when you open the door to Ben's
room, it just kind of, like, billows out onto you, like, you immediately are hit with his
nose.
We have to talk about Ben's peanut shells.
We can not fucking go to Pugas without being about Ben's peanut shells, we can.
Yeah, that's, that was, I had just really been enjoying some peanuts that week.
They were all over you like a cracker baler.
Well, they don't, they're not gonna, they're not gonna attract ants, they don't have sugar
in them, whatever.
I'll just, I'll sweep them up later.
You go, you go to a fancy country restaurant, a barbecue place, they have sawdust all over
the floor.
It's the same thing, same idea.
I'm dragging on Ben's hygiene, but it's not necessarily complaining, because I was actually
kind of excited when I, when Ben moved in and I realized that his hygiene was as bad
if that worked.
The standards are going so far down, you're in the career now.
He was like, it was exciting to know that my new roommate wasn't going to get on my
case about my hygiene, you know, that like, that we were kind of stank buddies together.
Yeah.
Oh my God, a new variant of the spicy bro pack, the stank buddies.
We have to fucking be stank buddies.
I want to be fair though, like, I mean, the first couple months it was like, everything
he did you was describing was true, but I feel like the last couple of months, it seemed
like Ben wasn't, seemed like he may have been taking showers more often, maybe because
we were, I was trying to not make fun of him about it, but then one time I said, he smells
like a 3D armpit, which I didn't think would be offensive, but that's, that's a really
terrible thing to say.
Whoa.
Here's, here's, here's what I'll say.
Here's, I just want to make this one statement in my own defense.
Okay.
You guys know me.
You guys know me from living at your house and never leaving.
And you know, I love you, I love you boys.
Mwah.
But, but I don't feel any need to impress you.
So yeah, when I, when I, when I never leave the house and I never leave my room, yeah,
my hygiene is pretty bad.
When I go out, generally I shower and I fucking make sure I smell okay.
Not a hundred percent of the time.
There have been times when I've been like, well, I fucking, I let the day get past me
and it didn't shower.
Fuck it.
And I go out smelling like, smelling like, like, like a scrapbook of farts.
But, but, but most of the time I go out.
You nonetheless concede that you do only wear like two pairs of pants in three shirts that
you don't wash very often.
Six shirts, but yes.
What would you say the longest you've ever gone wearing the same pair of pants was?
Is it six months?
I've definitely been wearing those fucking shorts for at least a month.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
I would, I would grant you a month.
Do you mean underpants?
No.
No, like actual pants.
Have you seen his, his orange?
American pants.
His like yellow and orange, uh, like long baggy shorts.
Yeah.
Slums that look like starbursts.
What do you call short pants in England?
Shorts?
Okay.
But not trousers.
But you also call underwear shorts, right?
No.
Underwear is pants.
Those are pants.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well anyway.
Rouses.
What the wrong trousers?
It's not a little bit of cheese, sir.
Well, Ben has this pair of shorts that goes like past the knees and they're these like
acid, yellow, uh, orange.
Oh, I've seen those all the time.
Yeah.
And he will wear them for literally a month at a time.
Well, that shorts aren't like, you know, they're just touching your legs.
Legs themselves don't get too...
I don't know, man.
My shit.
I know people that have worn the same pair of jeans for a year and never washed them.
And it's fine.
You're a fellow homeless people, Ben.
I have to change my clothes, like, every couple of days because they legitimately get filthy.
Like, I get my clothes really dirty.
Well, because I constantly wipe shit on them and, uh, like, just drop stuff.
Like, I'm a messy eater and I eat all the time, so I'm constantly dripping shit on my fucking pants.
Uh, you know, uh, don't clean up your jizz well enough and you got a jizz stain on your pants.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, admittedly, like, despite everything you said about Ben, like, nothing that he's done has ever, like, been in my way,
slightly that's, like, causing me some amount of discomfort.
But didgy jizzing just gets all over the place.
There's a couple of times where didgy's breath in the car became, like, unavoidably felt like I was smelling an asshole.
And I don't know why.
I don't...
He's just eating something disgusting.
Like an asshole.
Hold on.
Let's go to mouth because I have a lot to say about mouth when I think...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I wanted to say...
Yeah, hippo, hippo, go ahead.
Well, I was gonna ask, like, because, you know, what was the longest...
I will say mine, but what was the longest people have gone without changing their underpants?
Because I think I've gone a whole week when I was just...
I've probably gone a week, yeah.
I think four days is probably my maximum.
Sometimes I put on the same ones I was wearing just because they don't get that...
My underwear don't get as dirty as the rest of my fucking clothes.
It gets to a point where it's like, I wonder how much worse this place can become.
You're just wondering.
I would say the smell doesn't get necessarily worse.
It's just, like, the feeling.
There is a definite end to that, like, downward bell curve where it basically makes no difference.
It just levels off.
It just levels off, yeah.
You might as well just keep going.
You asymptotically approach zero hygiene and then you just stay there.
My understanding is that a lot of women just wear the same bra for basically indefinitely
because nothing really gets all that sweaty there.
That's bullshit.
I don't believe that for one fucking second.
I've heard that.
You can basically go weeks without changing your bra because it's like...
Ladies, we're going to need you to weigh in on that in the comments down below.
I'll tell you, man, what made me learn...
I see some women in the comments, I'm going to kill myself.
What made me learn to appreciate...
Women don't have breasts.
Never bring that up again.
Okay, I'm sorry.
What made me learn to appreciate showering, like, because as a teenager, I just didn't
do it at all.
I would go to anime conventions, like, three days of nonstop heat and people moving and
being in cramped rooms and stuff, and I just wouldn't shower because I just felt like I
didn't have time.
Everybody else can do it, but I can fucking muscle through this because I'm a...
I don't know.
I have a weird pride in being able to do that.
But then there was one year where I got a violent case of swamp ass where it was just
like all of the sweat coming from my ass hair had made it just rub my ass raw.
My ass was burning red, and my thighs were burning red, and just everything was swampy
and shitty, and it was like, that was when I learned that, yes, at a convention, you
need to fucking shower in the middle of the day.
Hang on for one sec.
I just heard someone loudly vaping.
I believe that we just have discussed the vaping etiquette on this show.
God damn it.
Please calm your shit down.
I set my audio thresholds that it wouldn't pick up.
Fuck.
You're vaping.
Pretty fucking clearly.
Yes, man.
We get it.
You vape.
Let's move on with our lives.
Can you hear this?
Yeah.
Clear as day.
The fucking icon, the audio icon's off.
You shouldn't be able to hear it.
This is bullshit.
Imagine if it shows up for us, it'll still be in the audio recording on Audacity.
That's true.
The audience can suck it up.
Fuck the audience.
So one time, I think I was probably 11.
I was just like, I think previously, the previous year, just the previous summer, I just,
my butt sweated so often, and it was so uncomfortable.
That's actually not sweat, that's called poop.
There's a difference.
Well, that was a kid.
I couldn't deal with being hot or being sweaty.
It would just bug the shit out of me.
One year, I just thought, I'm not going to wear underwear this summer.
Okay.
And there were pros and cons to that.
I don't remember exactly the nature of it, but I remember concluding, this is ultimately
better somehow.
I guess because my ass is being aired out more.
Because when I had underwear the previous summer, I would just put, rub the back of
my butt crack and to shove the underwear in there so that it feels like there's a cork
going on.
Yeah, I do this.
It doesn't feel like it's like, like, like, you know, sweat that's clamily moving back
and forth.
You put a cork in your butthole?
No, not an actual cork.
Just shove your underwear up into your ass crack to avoid shaving.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I do, I do often, I do, well, walking around, I do, I do get thigh chafed sometimes, and
I'll, and I'll scooch, and I'll scooch my underwear up between the thighs.
Yeah, I do that all the time.
I wear, I wear very soft, I wear very soft, very soft silky.
No, no, no, no.
You guys need to work on your thigh gap.
I've never done it for chafing.
I believe you mean chafing means like it eventually starts to, like, hurt because of, you know,
I've never been fat enough for that.
It's just that it's uncomfortable.
It just feels clammy.
That happens whenever I go to Disneyland.
My thighs get super chafy.
I can't tell what's a joke about Disneyland and what's serious.
I get chafing not from my legs rubbing together, but from them rubbing against my gigantic
balls, and that's what causes it.
You just got to lubricate.
You just got to lubricate with some well-placed piss and just lubricate between the thighs.
My brother Shade has never worn underwear in his life.
What?
The fuck?
He has been free-balling for 20 years.
Holy shit.
That's cool.
He just decided as a little kid that he hated underwear and refused to wear it and has continued
to refuse.
I don't know if he wears it now that he's at work.
I don't know if that's harder to wear a uniform.
I mean, they're not going to force him to, you know?
The greatest fucking fear is that I'll either piss my pants or I'll come across like a dime
bridge and he'll be like, I forgot my pants.
I'm going to a job interview.
You need to give me your pants.
I'm sorry.
You'll see my beanie, sir.
I can't.
I can't give it to you.
It's the worst fear I could ever fucking have.
I get free-ball because of the kinds of pants I wear, because all of mine have just the
one button holding the print together.
And so, I mean, I sometimes have to be underwearless because I'm like doing laundry or something.
And my dick, I have to just like rearrange my pants and wear a big shirt so my dick doesn't
just fly out that hole.
Not to brag or anything.
Not to brag or anything, but I can't free-ball because my fucking bold is just too pronounced.
It's just-
You know, my brother-
I need some-
You have a pretty pronounced bold.
I do.
It's true.
I need the tightness of the underwear to like tamp it down a little, just so it's not completely
obscene.
Yeah.
When my brother was like fat, when he was chubby, he developed a special technique for
the amusement of others where he would stand up, lift up his right leg, and then like shake
his leg to where the fat on his leg would smack his balls and make him kill over, and
he would do it every time and it was super fun.
It was a very specific like martial art move, and it was really funny.
What the-
What?
Ball kata.
Okay.
I want to transition us from-
To female.
To teeth, and here's how I'm going to do so.
Because one of the reasons I have to change my shirts is that my version of quote-unquote
brushing your teeth is that when I wake up and my teeth feel a little fuzzy, usually just
the front six on the top, I just take my shirt and I rub it against my teeth.
Holy shit.
Why don't you just brush your teeth like a human being?
Alright, I'm done.
It's literally a sin.
Did you redo, right?
Yes.
Use like a tissue, at least.
I've done this, I use tissues, I throw them away, I don't have-
Tissues will get up and they'll dissolve and get all on your teeth though.
Yeah, that's why you fold it once so that it doesn't.
I don't know about that.
I just have the inside of my shirt.
Did you secretly do an experiment or a towel?
Did you secretly part of an experiment to have the world's worst possible teeth and
everything he does feeds into it?
We both went to the dentist the last month, but he forgot the appointment just long enough
to where I could go to the dentist, but he had to reschedule for later.
I'm not super scrupulous about brushing my teeth.
I fail to brush my teeth sometimes, but when I do, when I do, I am so intense about it.
I get all my teeth and then I brush the roof of my mouth and the tongue and I fucking gag
myself on the brush because I'm like, I gotta get it all.
I gotta get all the surfaces, all the surfaces need to be clean.
Yeah, that's not how it works.
I've brushed my teeth maybe 15 times in the last 15 years.
Whoa, alright.
I have a little yarn to weave.
When I was a lesser baby, I truly, truly loved to brush my teeth.
It was the greatest pastime I could possibly have.
I had the fucking toothbrush that would play sick jams such as We Are the Kids of the Nation
whenever I brush my teeth.
Yeah, the singing toothbrush.
Sick, dude.
What are you talking about?
You had a musical toothbrush?
Yeah, it's like you press a button and it just starts playing a song and you're meant to brush
for the length of the song, so it teaches kids how long they should brush for.
Whoa, that's cool.
That's a very mid-2000s thing.
I would walk into my dentist's office and I would slap her ass and I would say,
Doc, how's my teeth?
And she'd be like, oh boy, you did a good job.
And I'd be like, sick.
And then I started watching a little man, a little boy, that I had to get my inspective
monoclonal.
I would have to inspect him and he would say, did you bro?
And he was like, are you talking about something like making a fan thick or something about
pink probably brushing your teeth or something?
Oh yeah.
And then I was like, you know, maybe brushing your teeth isn't cool.
And I stopped brushing my teeth.
So my fan thick that was meant to teach kids how much they should brush their teeth taught
you to stop.
Yeah.
I assume, Digi, I know about that fan thick and I assume that you wrote that because
you had at some point learned the value of brushing your teeth and wanted to impart
it to others.
So no, it's meant to be a don't be like me fan thick.
Digi, it's not too late.
You can change.
I don't think so.
Half his teeth are gone now.
That's not even true.
Well, here's the thing.
By the time I was like 11 and I was brushing my teeth as a kid, just not well.
I was doing it like once a day when I got up for school and never on weekends.
But I drank soda constantly for most of my life.
So by the time I was 11, I already had like 10 fillings.
Like I was already just constantly getting cavities.
And then there was a period of like four years where I just like didn't brush, didn't go
to the dentist at all because we had just been changing houses so often that I didn't
have like a assigned dentist.
And I was convinced when I was like 14 that.
Oh, I remember this.
Holy shit.
I forgot about this.
If I didn't brush my teeth, I would eventually build up an immunity.
I thought I would be the beginning of a new stage of human evolution where like the stuff
that would build up would eventually protect me from the other stuff or something.
And you would pass it on to your children?
Yeah.
So I just thought like because you know how like everything else on your body works that
way.
Like, you know, you rip your muscle and it grows back stronger.
So I thought.
Not if you break your bones.
Let's just get weaker.
Yeah.
What about, uh, she's, she's, uh, what's his name?
Fuck you.
His bones kept coming back stronger and he's a real person.
He's not an animal character.
Yeah, he's a real, real man.
DG Browns is going to break his bones.
So yeah.
So and then I was drinking Mountain Dew for like 10 years.
So I ended up with.
That helped.
I'm sure I probably have like green teeth.
I probably have like 20 to 25 fillings in total.
And then I quit drinking Mountain Dew.
I gotta have at least a dozen.
I finally stopped getting nearly as many cavities once I stopped drinking soda regularly.
Like once I switched to green tea, I've gone years without them.
Uh, like, like, like, I don't mean I have gone consistent years without them.
I mean, there have been years where I didn't have a cavity as opposed to every year I have
three.
Um, so yeah, I do have really fillings and bumps in my mouth.
What really bums me out about cavities and fillings is that like at some point, like
I got fillings throughout my life, but at some point they started giving me the white ones
and those are great.
But like the early ones, the ones I got early in my youth are the shitty black metal ones.
Yeah, I've got a lot of those.
Yeah.
And I had like my back molars have these disgusting black fillings and like they're normal because
like my, my dad had them.
So like they seem normal to me, but I think about like to a person that doesn't have cavities,
it must look fucking horrible and I feel so self-conscious about it sometimes.
Who the fuck is looking at the inside of your mouth?
My lover.
She's your age.
Uh, like, I mean, I, all of mine, maybe I don't feel self-conscious about that because
they're all on the inside of the teeth.
Like none of them are on the front or anything.
But yeah, I have a ton.
The smiling is what counts if you ask me.
Even though I've been, I, I, I am, I do have gross teeth and they're all like yellow and
like if I can just, I just touch it like real quick like uh, uh, uh, oh that's, it's fucking,
it's about to fall out.
If I just pull, I just feel like if I just pull it a little bit, it'll fall out and
they're awful teeth and my, my breath could inspire racial riots.
It's that bad.
The thing about, the thing about getting into brushing your teeth.
Fuck up.
Thank you.
Are you finishing your point?
All right.
No, I wasn't.
But I am happy to report.
That through, for my, all my years, I've only had one cavity, even though I literally
never brushed my teeth and I drink soda every day of my fucking life.
Wow.
You don't have to get there.
Give it time.
My teeth are just perfect.
Um, I remember, and I, I, I'm the kind of person who will take all kinds of selective,
uh, uh, encouragement.
Like one time when I was like 15, I was listening to this radio show and this guy was calling
in about how he was like 23 and he'd already lost all his teeth.
Um, but and he had like dentures, but he was talking about how the ladies love it when
he goes down on them.
Cause he could just pop out his teeth and just.
Oh my fucking god.
You see, you see folks, there's a silver loud cloud by every lining.
Yeah.
Um, but like the worst thing about trying to get into brushing my teeth like is that
it is really painful cause my gums can't handle it.
So I just bleed profusely if I brush my teeth.
Yeah.
You gotta keep it up.
It's constant.
And flossing sucks.
Uh, as an English man, I would stereotypically have the worst teeth here, but I think, I
think it's, it's a combination of, cause I don't brush my teeth as much.
I mean, I've been trying to recently, like every day I've been like morning and night,
morning and night.
It's actually been working and the, the first few days it was bleeding and now it's not
bleeding.
So I guess, you know, just keep doing it.
But yeah.
Um, I think it's a combination of, of the fact that I've never, ever liked soda in any
form is disgusting.
And I don't have a sweet tooth the same way that other people do.
I don't even.
And I've just been lucky in that, but I still, I think I have like six or seven feelings
I think, but it's, you know, I, I, I think my teeth, and they're not crooked.
I've never needed braces.
So I'm lucky.
Why, why is the amount of brushing I don't do, they would, they would have been far worse
if I ate like the wrong stuff.
Yeah.
But why is it that, that English men are known for their bad teeth?
Is it just that your culture doesn't care as much or?
I think, um, part of it is probably, yeah, that I think I've explained this somewhere
before, but it's the, the idea that people who get on British TV, they don't need to
have perfect teeth to, you know, to be allowed on.
So people get this, this, uh, this idea that all British people are like, I remember when
a really, I think, I think it's, I remember a cracked article saying that like, well,
they did some studies and British people actually have the best teeth in terms of not having
fillings and, but, but, but they're not great in terms of being white.
Like that culture doesn't care as much about yellow teeth.
So they're presenting themselves grossly, but they're actually really good at tooth
maintenance.
Well, that's the thing.
The thing is that it's not that it's actually gross to have discolored teeth.
It's just that our, like, we just have grown in obsession with the idea that teeth should
be white because it's more aesthetic.
I feel like culturally America really adopted and got into the idea of orthodontia and braces
to like, like, or they were early adopters of that idea.
Cause when I went to Poland, a bunch of the adults that I worked with had like braces
and it was because like the idea of getting braces to fix your teeth was like not a thing
for their parents, but like they grew up and were like, yeah, I'd like to get some braces
and fix my teeth, but it was like a newer thing to them.
Incidentally, my mom got braces when she was like 48 and that's when she finally got her
teeth corrected.
My mom had braces like right up until like right before I was born actually in her mid-30s.
See, the reason I don't care, like people have constantly, like my parents are always
asking me like, are you sure you don't want braces?
Are you sure?
Cause I have, you know, fucked up misaligned teeth and I was just like, have you like literally
everyone I've ever known who has braces, those are like the most miserable years of
their entire life because not only do braces look fucking hideous, like they are the worst
Normal braces look totally fine.
It's only when you get like head-to-head or like the weird shit, like I had some weird
shit in my mouth for a while now.
Braces are the most aesthetically unappealing thing I've ever seen.
No, they're just, I mean, maybe I'm crazy, but when I was a kid, seeing people with braces
was just normal, like just like half the people I knew had braces, it wasn't weird.
Yeah, it's normal, it's just all so gross and shitty.
And entirely because of American TV shows, I associate braces with young teenage girls
and that means I like them.
I find braces hideous and disgusting and also they make it so there's like all kinds of shit
you can't eat while you've got braces, there's like you have to maintenance them or else
they don't even work.
You know what, Shade had braces for like two and a half years and they didn't even fucking
work properly because he maintenance them so badly it didn't take care of them that
now he's got other teeth issues.
Keep crying about braces but here's the deal, you put in the effort, you take the time,
you make the sacrifices necessary, you reap the rewards, whatever they may be, they're
purely aesthetic, they're just aesthetic.
The reward is that you have to wear a retainer every night for the rest of your fucking life.
No, you don't.
Hold on, hold on.
If you want it to say perfect, you do.
They tell you that, too.
I wear my, okay, here's the thing, I do wear my, all right, you guys have been dancing,
you've been dancing with my date, this entire podcast.
Me too.
It's not for me to take the reins over, okay?
Because you guys are a bunch of fucking pansies.
But you're not ready to step up to the plate to be men and deal with this hygiene thing
because I would say that I definitely have the best hygiene of anyone in the PCP.
For sure.
Because I am on top of this shit.
No one would question that.
I am dedicated.
I don't know, I'm not convinced.
Fucking state your case, bitch.
Okay, well first of all, I am dedicated to personal betterment and in a physical sense
and that I'm certain that I have the best routine when it comes to that shit.
And I would argue that is an extension of that.
But every single day, I brush my teeth twice a day.
I floss once a day, every single night.
I do not, I shower every other day at least, generally every single day.
But I'll, the one thing I do that is slightly unhygienic is that I go,
and it's because of my fucking clothing system.
Okay, every day, every week I do my clothes once, one time.
I do all my laundry.
And I don't have many gym clothes.
So I end up wearing the same gym clothes every day for one full week.
And I do not smell good at the end of that week.
Yeah, it's not good, it's not good.
What a disaster.
Are you getting off the topic of teeth here?
Who could bear to be around someone who gets sweaty and smelly in the gym?
Yeah, it's a nightmare.
But I don't know, other than that, I'm perfect.
That's what I'm trying to say, I'm the best person in the world.
The thing that I've always wrestled with as a teenager,
because I had acne and all that stuff,
and it's like, you have to suddenly really pay attention to how you wash yourself.
Because before, as a kid, you're always clean, kind of.
But then suddenly there's grease coming out of you, and you're like,
I don't know what to do.
And I've always had this, like, I know I can be clean, and I know it's better to be clean.
Yeah, I don't care what the fuck that was, Ben.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
What's happening?
God damn it, what the fuck was anyone talking about?
I was gonna say, there's always been this, like, the cool kids were the ones that were well kept.
Right, right.
It felt like, you know, if you weren't popular, there's no reason to be well kept.
Did it ever occur to you that maybe that well keeping of oneself is what makes them popular?
No, no, no, no, this is my point.
I knew deep down that I had to do all these things.
I was just lazy, and it was just me trying to come to terms with the fact that I was so lazy,
and this is the root of all my real problems, is that sometimes I stink a bit,
and sometimes my breath probably is a little bad, and that, you know, I was never gross in public, obviously.
I developed something of a reputation amongst my friends, not in high school, but after high school,
of, like, taking long to get ready for things, because I wouldn't want to do anything until I had, like,
perfectly prepared myself.
See, that right there is the epitome of everything that I find, that is why I don't do hygiene,
because it's just, it's in the way.
It is in the way, that's true.
It's in the way of everything else, and, like, the idea of it is that it'll make the experience better, right?
Like, if you're feeling...
Socially, yes.
It'll make the experience of you better for others.
Well, yeah, which can make the experience better.
I mean, if you don't smell, that also helps you.
You don't want to smell yourself.
You want to feel confident that other people like the way you look, you know?
Yeah.
And so it does benefit you.
Right, right.
But at the same time, the amount of preparation that there is in everything to create this...
It's really, it's a lifestyle, is what it is.
It creates this perfect version of you that, like, you know, that maybe will be, will just have a better time in general.
But for me, it's like, I want to be able to just hit the ground running in everything I do.
Like, I'm the type of guy who, when I wake up in the morning, I jump out of bed and I get right on the computer
and I continue what I was doing the night before.
There's no, there's no moment where I have to, like, wake up, get ready to start the day,
take a shower, brush my teeth, do all that shit.
There's no, like, preparation.
Like, if I want to go out, it's because I'm hungry and I'm gonna go.
I'm not gonna sit around and do all this other shit.
Which is why I have such a difficult time brushing my teeth.
Because, like, my dentist is always like, why don't you just, you know, find, like,
maybe every time you take a shower or something, it's like, yeah, but I take a shower at completely random times
because I've decided I smell too bad to deal with myself.
Like, it's not something I do with this, this, like, preparation formula that I think a lot of people have.
I just, to me, it's not worth the effort because I don't feel like the...
I mean, I totally appreciate the gains you get from it.
Like, I do, sometimes, I take a shower, I put on, like, some well-fitting clothes,
and I go out into the world and I feel more confident than usual.
And I'm like, yeah, okay, this is a cool feeling, but it's not worth the effort to have that all the time.
If I think I smell, but, like, I, you know, on the one hand, mind over matter,
and, like, it's just a confidence thing, whatever.
But, like, if I go out and I know that, like, I'm unkempt and I smell weird,
I definitely act different and I am, like, shy and I don't want to talk to anyone.
I will be more sheepish.
Keep myself at arm's length from everyone.
Particularly if I'm, like, really disgusting and wearing the bathrobe and, like, flip flops or something,
then I'm, like, I will be more, like, yeah, I don't deserve to talk to these people.
You know, I do have good hygiene.
Hang on, I have good hygiene, but I have been known to just wear my pajamas,
throw on my bathrobe and my fucking beanie, and just bomb down the road in my fucking minivan.
See, here's what I do.
KFC to pick me up some fucking golden nuggets.
When it comes to, like, cleaning shit and maintaining myself as a person,
I just kind of weave it naturally into, like, like, like compulsions I get.
I try to, like, reprogram my own compulsions, right?
There's so many times when you have to be doing a thing, like, editing a video,
and you're like, you just want to come up with something to do to distract you,
like, I'm going to go out and, you know, either send them in a roll or I'm going to go...
I set that moment where I realized that, like, the time that DeVue is on this podcast
is taking away from time he could be editing my video right now.
Oh, fuck off.
Yeah, yeah.
We're in a time crunch, as always.
Yes, so, uh, fucking...
Life is a time crunch.
All I did was I just convinced myself that brushing, flossing, and mouth-washing my teeth
is one of the many things I can do to, like, put something off for five more minutes,
or to think about something.
You know what's a key for me?
Fucking don't take my earbuds out ever.
There was one fateful day when I realized I just have my earbuds in all the time when I'm at work,
the whole time when I'm asleep, I'm going to go brush my teeth with my earbuds in.
My brother saw me in the bathroom, burst out laughing.
I don't give a shit.
I never take my earbuds out.
I'm hearing about the history of Nazi Germany for the third time this year,
and I'm going to fucking do it while brushing my teeth, while cooking food,
and I also have a shower speaker that's waterproof, and you can Bluetooth it to your phone.
So anything where, like, I want to hear someone's voice.
I want to, like, hear someone vaguely talking about something,
but I don't want to necessarily hear exactly what they're saying because I can't hear it.
I just put on one of Digi's vlogs, and then you go take a shower that way.
Speaking.
And so that way I never get bored.
That way I can never, as long as I'm listening to something, I can always just keep going forever.
I'm very much into, like, to mood-crafting, and so if I'm going to, like,
if I'm going to go, like, shave or something, I'll throw on some, like, loud masculine music, you know?
Yeah.
Like, when I shave, you know, I throw off my shirt.
I'm, like, you know, getting all ready.
I've got all the shaving stuff around, and it's like, yeah, this is a man's time.
I need some abrasive masculine-sounding shit, you know?
Speaking of crafting your own, like, habits, DeVoo.
Okay, so I have a number of weird, like, nervous compulsions and ticks and stuff.
And I have tried in the past to stop some of them.
But what always inevitably happens is that if I manage to stop one, something else pops up to replace it.
And, like, I have a rotation of them that I sometimes go through.
And, like, specifically I'm thinking of biting my nails.
I've always bit my nails, like, right down to the quick, all the time, my whole life.
And one time I was like, I'm not going to do that.
But what ended up happening is that I stopped biting my nails, but I started compulsively clipping them all the time.
And it was just as bad. And, in fact, it was way less convenient.
And I have, yeah, like, I have the hair-pulling thing, and I have another thing where I do where I'll, like, twitch my, like, abdominal muscles sometimes.
And that's weird. Like, I hate that, because if I do that in public, I feel like everyone's staring at me.
Even though I don't think anyone has ever noticed me doing that, and yet I feel super weird about it.
I used to have a lot of weird compulsions.
And one I'm still not completely down with is scraping my index finger on my right hand into my thumbnail.
And it slowly creates a twitch.
Literally what I'm doing right now.
Right. Now, the reason why I started doing it is because...
I can't even get my index finger to, like, touch my thumbnail at, like, a proper angle.
Well, what happened is that one day I was, like, reaching for the door and I jammed my fucking thumb against it and cracked it in that exact spot, right?
And so, like, it was like, ow, pain, bitch, ass, nigger, fuck.
And then, like, it happened, like, three more times in the course of, like, 18 months for some fucked-up reason.
I think it was just the specific angle that I was grabbing that doorknob with.
Just sometimes I would crack my thumbnail.
So I became so compulsive to have that little trench be there that eventually I started...
I built up this weird habit of doing that.
And you can actually see it.
I was getting away from hygiene.
In the cuticle...
Well, when the fuck...
When top of game, am I gonna talk about my cuticle?
The part of your nail that goes on?
Yeah, it has to come...
Why discuss this at some point, did you?
There's, like, a weird rift in it.
That's, like, weird.
Anyway, well, hey, you know, we were supposed to talk about braces and we switched that top before I got to go to it.
So can we go back to braces?
Yeah, so listen, here's the thing.
But no, I want to ask Nate a question about fingernails.
Because Nate, you seem to be an expert on hygiene.
What is the...
How long do you go between cooking your fingernails?
What do you think is the proper amount of time?
Here's the thing.
My biggest failure in life, in my life, is my obsession with biting and clipping my fingernails.
Nate?
Which fucks me up.
I'm not gonna go into details, but Nate...
No!
Fuck his fingers up at certain points.
Nate, fuck them right the fuck right.
That's not true.
I've always...
You're going over the top.
No, I'm not, dude.
No, I'm not.
I've always been a long fingernail boy because I just don't...
Like, they grow really fast.
I don't know how long after I'm supposed to clip them.
I probably do it once a month, but they're always...
They get really fucking long.
But I always got complimented on them by girls.
Because my fingernails just happen to grow perfect.
Like, they're just beautiful white.
Yeah, they're like, wow, those look like real good hand job giving hands.
You could really, you know, make some money with those.
Girls would ask me if I had had a French manicure, like, all the time.
And I was like, no, I don't know what that is.
But yeah, so I have perfect, beautiful hands and nails.
I'm basically like a hand model.
Basically, George Costanza.
George Costanza.
Yeah.
But, yeah.
But then guys would always say that my nails are too long.
They'd say I was a faggot.
I got no idea.
I would say that a lot of people...
I don't know.
It's considered effeminate to have nails that even show, like, any of the white at the end.
So, like, I don't know, I guess, like, for guys.
Well, I just...
It just so happened that I happened to watch, like, some ASMR video
where there was just, like, a guy's hands the other day.
And, like, a lot of the comments, like, he just had, like, a little bit of the white.
Like, they went, like, to the edge of his finger, you know, like, not really past,
but to the edge.
And there was some white.
And, like, a lot of the comments were talking about how girly his fingernails were.
Dude, guys, you're missing the male ASMR.
You can't complain about gayness.
I only listen to male ASMR because female ASMR is literally gay.
Yeah.
We're gonna have a podcast about that one, though.
Deal with it.
Even though I'm a gross boy, whenever I go out of the house,
like, no matter what, no matter how long it would be outside the house,
I will take a shower.
I'll take a shower and I'll put on a new pair of clothes.
And I often stay in my house, so I'll go every few days without taking a shower or anything.
But no matter what, no matter the circumstance, if I leave the house,
I will take a shower.
I wish I had your discipline.
So here's the thing about nails, right?
Like, my dad, a couple, because back when I was a teenager,
I didn't have the habit of doing it until I built up the compulsion to do it sometimes.
And, like, my dad was like, I don't know why you like growing your nails out long.
And I feel like he was saying it with the connotation of, I'm wondering if you're gay, right?
Are you gay, right?
And, like, because my dad is just, my dad is really great hygiene, right?
So, like, that's how I was able to build up decent habits, right?
Like, my dad brushes his teeth, I think, three times a day.
Okay.
And, like, when does he do the third one?
Just, like, in the middle, like, after lunch?
Maybe it's two times a day, I don't know.
Like, maybe when he's home on a weekend, it's three times a day.
Yeah, so, like, you know, when I was a kid,
I had a big ego about, like, being a good kid, you know,
because this was before I hit puberty and also before it turned out everyone hates me
and I can't finance it with society.
So, when I was a kid, I had this, you know, this big, yeah,
just driven by my self-image of being, like, well-kempt and stuff, right?
You know, back when I was, like, good at math and shit, lol, in, like, second grade, right?
So, like, yeah, like, oh, I brush my teeth, you know?
It's never been about not having good teeth.
It's never been about avoiding cavities, blah, blah, blah.
You don't want to get dentures, you don't want to look old.
It's just, it's entirely been a lifelong campaign of pride for me.
And so, like, my whole childhood never had any cavities.
My brother got some cavities, my sister got some cavities,
because they aren't fueled by ego as much as I am, right?
So, but then when I was a teenager, like, like, it finally came time
to deal with my incredibly fucked-up sharp teeth, right?
I have, um, I have, like, what you call a bonus tooth.
Well, that's what it is now.
But yeah, I had just, like, I had this, like, tooth room.
It was the council of teeth and my tongue could just sit in there
and just, like, rest in this little, little tiny couch of teeth.
It was terrible, horribly uncomfortable.
I had this incredible compulsion.
I have no idea what you're describing right now.
It's just extra teeth. It's like I had multiple rows of teeth, right?
I had so many fucking extra teeth.
My mouth is too small.
How many extra teeth did you have?
I mean, wait, were you Sharkboy and was your sister Lavagirl?
Is that what you're telling me right now?
Yes, absolutely. She also has too many teeth.
I kind of know what you're talking about,
because I grew a, like, a set of canines over my canines
and that eventually got, like, pushed them out and destroyed them.
What the shit, dude?
Is it literal?
Are you sure you're not talking about baby teeth and adult teeth?
I'm talking about when I was, like, 18.
Manchi, what the fuck kind of humans are these?
I don't know.
I long after having lost all my baby teeth,
grew in an extra pair of canines over my original ones
that pushed them out and eventually moved all the rest of my teeth
out of where they were so that they could fit in
and slot into the rest of my teeth.
I thought everyone had the same amount of teeth.
I don't know. I don't know.
Yeah, I know.
People have different sizes of mouths, right?
I thought, like, humans were, like, defined by their number of teeth.
And the new ones, like, grew way bigger than the old ones.
I think everyone has the same amount of teeth.
Wait, wait, wait.
Are you just talking about, like, your adult teeth
grew in around your baby teeth?
No, motherfucker.
I'm talking about, in my late teens, a brand new set of canines
grew in and pushed the old ones out
and then moved all the rest of my teeth out of their way
so that they could fucking find a place.
Amazing.
So, yeah, so, like, if you guys want to know,
like, look, yeah, having braces is terrible.
There's a lot of things that suck about it,
particularly, like, when they fuck up or something goes wrong
or they're adjusting them, you know.
But for some mouths, it is fucking worth it, right?
And mine were.
Like, I have videos dating back to 2008.
Go to my playlists. You'll find them.
Listen to how I talk.
I struggled to speak.
I still do because I learned to speak, you know,
with a fucking fucked up set of teeth.
And I think I also have some sort of weirdly deformed tongue
that isn't long enough.
My tongue isn't long enough.
I can't stick my tongue out very far.
And it ends with, like, a nipple.
So I have a really weird tongue.
My whole weird, lispy voice, it's because of these two things.
Having bad teeth my whole life and having this weirdly fucked up tongue.
That's why I lisp like this.
That's why I sound like a huge fucking nerd all the time.
I've looked it up and what I believe it's hyperdontia,
the condition of having super, super numerary teeth,
or teeth that appear in addition to the regular number of teeth.
I didn't know that was a thing.
So, yeah.
So before they even started with putting on the braces,
they had to pull four of my fucking teeth out.
Four of my fucking teeth out.
And then it was like four years of having braces on,
although it could have probably been like three and a half,
because I got to the point where it was just like,
they weren't taking the braces off because like,
there's really no such thing as perfectly straight teeth,
so you can theoretically have them on forever.
So we had to specifically ask, can we have them off now?
And they're like, oh yeah.
And it was literally only the exact fucking moment
the braces were finally taken off in the clinic.
She gave me the retainer and said,
oh yeah, well how long do you wear these for?
As long as you want to have straight teeth.
I'm like, what the fuck?
I would not have signed up for the whole operation if I had known.
You would have had to permanently deal with bullshit.
This is my whole thing, right?
I don't want to have to deal with bullshit permanently
in any sort of way, right?
I'm fine with doing something as long as it's a temporary thing.
So I had the retainer on for one year,
and I'm like, this is not worth it.
No one I know keeps it in.
I still wear my braces.
I still wear my fucking retainer.
That's crazy dude, I don't wear mine.
I gave mine up in like a month.
I lost the bottom of my retainer though.
See, I talked to Shade and he's like,
yeah, my teeth are slowly going back out of alignment
because I didn't wear retainer and none of it was worth it.
Well, parents made so much money, we got to do it right by him.
I have one fucking tooth that's going out of alignment.
Okay, one of my molars is out of alignment
because the retainer cracked in that spot early on,
which is fucking fucked up,
and I didn't want to have to spend hundreds of dollars
to get it fixed and stuff.
But yeah, over time, I worked for a year, I gave up.
There is one tooth in the front of my teeth
that is being misaligned.
My girlfriend thought that I had just never gotten those teeth fixed.
She's like, when are you going to get bottom braces?
I'm like, but anyway, it is messed up.
Don't bitch fucking slut, god damn.
For the longest time, I've also had this one gap in my teeth
that always has a deposit of food every night,
which is a good-
Okay, great. That's a little snack for you at the end of the day.
Which can be a good survival tactic, you know?
You're like a chipmunk who stores shit in his face.
Can we move on from teeth to-
No, I'm not done yet.
This is not the teeth test.
Well, hold on.
It's not really about hygiene at this point.
It's more about the entire history of your teeth and how they've shaped it.
Well, hold on. I'm fucking doing it.
I'm fucking doing it.
So when I had the braces on, I didn't floss hardly at all
because you can't use those little convenient flossers.
You can't even do the thing where you wrap the floss around your fingers.
You have to fucking sew the food out.
You know, like, where you sew with a needle?
You have to do that shit, but to get food out of your teeth
takes 15 fucking minutes.
Almost never did it.
So, like, I was pretty concerned that I wasn't taking proper care of my teeth
and I could have had a cavity, but, you know,
I brushed them so much when I was a kid.
Also, like hippo, never drank much soda or had much candy.
Or at all, really.
But then, but then, as an adult,
I finally, like, got too old for the youth dentist.
And so my teeth were going un-maintained by a dentist.
I was brushing them.
I was also drinking lots of tea.
I was also drinking some coffee.
And, like, like, buildup was building up.
You know, staining.
And I remember talking about...
That is what buildup tends to do.
God damn it.
Like, I wrapped this shit up.
Where are you going with this?
And so then, my girlfriend was like,
dude, those might be cavities.
And I was like, holy shit.
Okay.
Because I remember saying this, like,
three or four weeks ago on a previous podcast
that, like, when I was a kid,
I was just boasting about how I've never had a cavity.
And my older cousin, Patricia Lepleb, said,
don't get cocky.
I got my first cavity when I was 22.
And I'm 22.
Almost, you know, almost done with being 22.
Might have cavities.
And it was literally the most nervous I've ever been
about anything in my life.
Purely as a matter of pride.
And I finally looked at them.
It was fucking buildup.
I was right.
I sent a huge boasting text to my cousin.
She's like, I don't remember saying that.
Like, I remember everything.
Of course not.
Having you learn how...
Tuesday.
Yeah.
That was just another day when I told people
that they are fucking going to get cavities.
Yeah.
Anyway, that's the reason to maintain yourself.
You'll feel superior over everyone else,
as I'm sure Nate has this whole podcast,
just being like, I'm such a better person.
You know, I do.
I do.
But the thing is, I spend my time in a gym
with people who are way above me,
so it keeps me looking for stuff
to be even more better than you guys.
When it comes to, for me,
I think I just don't like admitting that I'm wrong.
Right.
To admit that I've been, like, wrong
for not going all hygiene
of my whole teenage life.
And I, you know, I went to the dentist recently
and, you know, did all the checkups,
and I didn't get a feeling this time.
But they, you know, they said,
you should brush twice a day.
And every time I'd gone to the dentist,
they say that, and I'm usually like,
okay, like I'm not going to, but okay.
Yeah, okay, guys.
All right.
But this time, I just saw her.
I was an adult, and I was just looking at her.
And I'm like, yeah, you're right.
And now I'm doing that.
And that's just, I just,
because I know that, I know that being clean
makes me feel better than normal.
Yeah, it does.
So it's like, it's, it's,
I don't like to admit that I'm wrong,
but I'm totally wrong for ever being.
Guys, I have a huge branch
that this conversation could take
if you're down here.
Hold on.
Just to finish off,
to go off what Hippo was saying,
one of the recent times I went to the dentist,
she got so exasperated with me
that she literally said, like,
why do you even come here?
Like, if you're not going to take,
and I said,
I come here so you can see if I have cavities
so I can get them filled.
Like, I don't care about the cleaning
that you're going to do.
I'm just here for the X-rays, you know.
That's pretty fair.
When I say branch,
I'm saying it's 100% relevant.
It's just a subcategory, right?
Okay, well, what is it?
Well, I also, somewhere I want to take this,
but I'll hear yours.
We've been talking about like, you know,
like things you do on a daily basis
or a weekly basis, stuff like that.
What about stuff you do on a minute-by-minute basis?
Like, some shit got on your hands.
What do you do next?
Right?
That's a huge...
Well, there's specific ways to do it, you know.
Like, what's your policy on, like, you know...
Oh, I have a thing on this.
You throw it in the general direction of a trash can
and if you miss, it's no big deal.
I agree.
I went on the carpet.
When it comes to, like, small things like that,
if I've got a runny nose
and it's mostly water coming out of my nose,
then I will just get it with my hands if I don't have a tissue
and just rub my hands together until it evaporates.
Yeah, that's not real.
That's not a real thing.
No, if it's like an actual booger with, like, greenness in it,
then I will, like, get a tissue.
It's all booger.
It's 100% booger if it throws your nose.
If it's a runny nose, I will use my hands
and then evaporate it with friction.
No!
It's fine.
Please!
On the onset of the nose, all throughout my childhood,
I was super, I was super, like,
get a Kleenex, I'm not going to pick my nose.
And then, like, one time, I was at my cousin's house
and he was playing Call of Duty and he wouldn't let me play
because he was an asshole.
Fuck you, Josh.
And then...
And then he started picking his nose.
And I was like, you shouldn't do that, bitch.
You shouldn't fucking do that.
That's wrong.
That's immoral what you're doing right now.
Yeah, exactly.
And he was like, you're gay, dude.
You should try it.
It's cool.
Oh, no.
He said you're done in dark.
Maybe I should.
Maybe...
And I only quit picking my nose,
like, two years ago.
Why would you quit?
I think everyone picks their nose at least a little bit, right?
What do you do to get the stuff out of your nose?
I get a napkin.
I pick my nose almost constantly.
Here's my nostril thing.
If it's, like, big, like, goopy, like,
I'm going to die, I can't breathe, sort of stuff,
then I will let it build up overnight.
And then, like, cannon blasts, like, explode.
I do that sometimes.
Yeah.
What else can you do?
I get in there constantly.
And I've got to say that my old chair,
one of my old black chairs,
which you've all sat in on the plebe and the weeb set,
for years, I was just wiping boogers on the back of the chair.
Amazing.
I would just pick my nose and go right to the back
or on the bottom.
And the bottom had sort of that, like,
like that fuzzy stuff on it.
And so the boogers would kind of, like,
hang from that.
No!
It was like all these hanging,
like, like, like the Pokemon Kokuna,
how it hangs from a, like that,
with a bunch of boogers.
No!
Like the Pokemon, not like the actual thing.
Yeah.
There was, like, hundreds.
Much more relatable.
There was, like, hundreds of boogers
all over the back of my chair.
And if anybody sat behind me,
they thought it was the most disgusting shit.
It sounds like some pretty disgusting shit.
But it's all behind me, so what do I care?
Yeah.
That's my retort.
When I finally replaced the chair,
I just took it out back
and just hosed it down.
Burned it?
Okay.
My brother had this.
You've all sat in it.
You've all been in this chair.
Had this childhood friend,
this childhood friend of my brothers
who lived in a bunk bed on the bottom bed,
and it was wooden.
So, like, above him was just this big plank of wood,
and he built up a deliberate booger collection,
which was quite a sight to behold.
But yeah, okay.
Guys, the subject of hands.
How much awareness do you have
about, like, the registry of everything
that's happened to these hands
since its last washing?
I'm like, okay.
Zero.
I make an effort to forget.
Sometimes I look at my hands,
and it's just fucking bleeding.
That's not a joke.
Sometimes I look at my hands,
and it's fucking bleeding.
That's true.
It's happened.
Why?
How?
I don't know.
What do you mean how?
It's just fucking bleeding, Nate.
I just burst my heartbeat.
It's too strong.
It clips the fucking microphone.
Exactly.
It's just out of my body.
What can you do?
I go by the George Carlin thing,
where I just, I mean,
I wash my hands when it's in a public place,
because, you know,
I don't want to look like an idiot.
But most of the time,
I just, you know,
if it doesn't feel gross,
then it isn't.
I wash my hands whenever I do anything
in my fucking life.
I do it at least, like, every 30 minutes.
For me, it's like a sixth sense.
It's like a seventh sense,
where it's like,
I have, like, this, you know,
subconscious knowledge of, like,
what each finger has done,
you know, and, like,
I make compromises
based on what's going on
in my environment.
Again, if I'm in a public place,
I'm like, okay,
if I have to touch a door handle
out in public,
then I will change my behavior
accordingly, you know.
That sounds like some super OCD shit.
No, I wouldn't say that.
Well, it's not really,
because it doesn't occupy my thoughts
that vividly.
It's happening sort of like
in the lower registry of my thoughts.
I mean, you know what I did?
I came up with a system,
sorry, I came up with a system years ago
that whenever I go to the bathroom
in a public place,
when I, you know,
I wash my hands,
I do whatever,
I get the paper towels,
I dry my hands,
I then use those paper towels
to open the door to exit,
because I know people
have been touching that shit.
I just discovered that one day.
I remember one,
I remember one time being in a public bathroom
that had this specially designed handle
that deliberately lets you
just open it with your shoulder or something,
and it had this huge list of instructions,
and it's like being put in there.
It felt like I was in some sort of like
torture device.
It felt like the position I had
to demean myself to assume.
I thought you were going to say
you felt like you were in the future.
Well, what happened was like,
the position I had to be in was like,
if someone were to push the door open
on the other side,
it's going to break my fucking arm.
So like clearly those things
didn't catch on, right?
That is awesome.
I love that.
Yeah, I guess we would pun it.
I have a system,
I mean, if anything gets on my hands,
I'm wiping it off.
I always have a towel next to my desk
at all times for anything
on my face and hands,
or just dripping.
But like, when I,
I basically just wash my hands
under two circumstances.
I just took a shit,
or I just jacked off.
Those are the two absolute
wash hands with soap circumstances.
You know what,
it's going to be real with you guys.
To me, jacking off is not a hand washing activity.
If you take a shower that day,
if you've taken a shower within like
20 or so hours,
then jack off,
you don't have to wash your hands.
If I was a good boy,
I would wash my hands after jacking off,
but I'm big enough to admit
that I'm not that boy.
Nate, how are you not grossed out by that,
but you all grossed out by me
wiping my boogers with my hands?
Ew, boogers are gross!
A man's seed,
a man's seed is pure hippo.
A man's seed should be celebrated.
It's the same stickers.
I don't get any like,
jizz on my hands when I jack off.
Right, yeah, that's the thing.
But just the smell of my dick
like gets on my hand
and it does not get off.
Like, I can smell my hand
from the full length of my arm away
for like hours
if I don't wash my hand after jacking off.
I would probably go longer
I would probably go longer without showering
if it weren't for the fact that
my dick starts to smell.
I just want the audience to know,
if you shake my hand, I just jacked off.
I remember fucking vividly
the first time
I ever like came in my pants
like after a wet drain
and I had to touch
my weenus penis
and feel the
straight up slime
Slime, straight up slime, dude.
Yeah.
I definitely have
I've seen a bunch of you knew that sex was a sin
and to never, you know, go back.
I guess I have a pretty high tolerance
to jizz just because
the way that I jacked off for several years
was entirely by laying on my belly
and doing it in my pants every time.
So I guess my tolerance is kind of weird.
In all my favorite RPGs
I always stack high jizz resistance.
High jizz defense.
Yeah, so I definitely have a hierarchy
of bodily fluids resistance.
Yeah, like cum, I really
don't mind that much.
I think it's pure, man.
Well, the first day I live.
I do because it sticks to everything
and it gets in your hairs and then it's
like impossible to get out once it dries.
I made out with a girl after just coming in her mouth
so at this point, you know,
she swallowed, right?
She swallowed first.
I'm a big snowballer.
You know me.
The first day I lived here
I just like sat down
on Digi's bed.
I was like kind of like laying down on Digi's bed
and he's like, just know I rub my dick
on every square centimeter
of that bed. I don't really mind.
I don't really mind dicks that much.
And then like pee, you know,
I'll compromise if need be.
That's the first step to being gay to boo, just so you know.
I don't mind cum so much at all.
So much for snakes.
He just said pee was next.
I got a bro, he just needs to get jacked off.
You know, it just had to be done.
It's not gay, it's just helping a friend out.
Leading up to moving in with Digi, right?
I'd seen what his toilet looked like.
I knew it was very, you know, pistuous.
But then when I finally saw it
When I finally saw it
Hashtag pistuous!
It was P-I-S-T-O-U-S
Where does T-O-U-S?
T-U-O-S
I finally saw it because it's just that like
The entire
two foot radius of around his toilet
is a layer of pee.
I wanted to get into that.
That's what I've been waiting for.
But we've been so far down this fucking rabbit hole
that we've been only focused on
like self hygiene.
But what about your environment?
Exactly, I have a huge thing about and nose about that.
Oh my god.
Can I just mention the story
at Radcon 2
when I got fed up with the environment
and insisted that we all clean.
I mean I was going to do it myself
but other people felt guilty and joined in
I didn't feel guilty. I just felt like it was a good idea.
I felt like Tom felt guilty, you know?
I guess I'm basing it off of him.
The best fucking moment of my entire fucking life
was when I pissed on Digi's house.
When was that?
It was so fucking good.
When I went outside and I just got to piss on the walls
and I just got to piss on the grass
it was so fucking
Yes Queen!
I pissed in my yard at least once a day
if not multiple times a day.
Yeah.
When I lived in my parents' house
I loved peeing outside. Peeing outside is great.
Me and Ben do it all the time
because we go out to smoke and each one of us
will just go out behind the bushes and be like
I'm going to go piss.
I'm a big peer. If I'm outside
there's a good chance I'm going to have to pee
and I'm not going all the way back inside.
It feels amazing to piss outside.
It does.
This was meant to be given to God before God
out in the open.
I wouldn't be okay with it if not for the fact
you don't have any toilet paper to deal with
some drips.
I was shaking off dude.
It was a leaf all over my body.
Yeah that's the thing.
I don't get much pee drip honestly.
Maybe I'm just blessed.
Well I have an extremely long foreskin
and therefore
I get flung all over the place
which is why my bathroom is entirely
covered in piss.
And the reason that I don't like...
Wait you don't peel it back?
You don't understand how long it is.
It's abnormal. Is it like a meter?
Yes it's exactly like that.
It's basically the equivalent
it's a man equivalent of beef curtains
holding on the end of it.
Yeah it's a beef curtain.
I'm not even joking.
I have an exceedingly long foreskin.
It's a condition called femorsis.
And even then I have an extreme example of it.
Oh yeah.
So yeah that's why in order to get the piss
out of my dick I have to like shake it violently
and it just gets everywhere.
People look at my toilet and will think
this is such a huge build up.
But like it gets that way after
a couple weeks.
That is why I did you.
You have to clean every single time.
Every single time.
You do a little bit.
I'm talking like if you stand.
If you stand.
If you use his toilet and you're standing up
because you're male right.
Any woman has ever gone into his room ever.
That's not true.
Sheepovers had to use that bathroom.
Oh you did that to sheepover?
That's a sin.
So if you stand there.
Whether or not you stand on it or sit on it
you're going to put your feet by the toilet.
There will be now crusted like caramelized pee
on your feet now.
It's not just pee.
The whole floor.
The entire floor of my bathroom is sticky
and it's not just because of piss.
I don't know what else it is.
It definitely leaves me with a disturbing feeling.
I'm just going to use one word to describe the experience
of your bathroom.
The only reason to bother you is because you don't wear socks.
I want to get to the feet situation.
Ditchy's bathroom is like a silent hill.
It is a nightmare.
It was legitimately terrified
the first time I went in.
I mostly use it at night
where I don't notice as much
but when I see it in the light of day
it is definitely horrifying.
It's a war zone.
I have a very specific foot
policy
which I am not able to fulfill
but when I have my own place
hopefully I'm going to get it figured out
which basically is just
I just want to avoid things
that cause bad germs.
Stuff like mold
and mildew.
Like bodily fluids past the giz level.
That kind of stuff.
Not too many foreign substances.
Nothing is past the giz level for me.
Other than maybe...
Are you talking about bloods?
He just considers giz
to be the least offensive bodily fluid
whereas I would consider it to be the most offensive
other than shit.
It propagates life and you oppose life.
I am in favor of life.
That's right.
Because it's a sticky, disgusting substance
that permanently gets on everything.
And it smells, dude.
It smells.
I'm not saying...
I've never seen that.
If you ever giz
and then don't clean it up
watch it for a couple days.
No thank you.
I'm not saying I don't clean it up.
I'm not saying I don't mind it.
I do mind it. It's just the lowest rank
and I will clean it up.
The idea is just have a whole environment
that is clean
and have your feet exist
and you can walk around and you don't have to worry about it.
See, I started developing this policy
because my family started getting dogs.
Right?
We got to the point where we had two dogs at a time
and it was just gross because dogs are disgusting
and I despise everything about them.
And they're just gross and terrible
and they shit and they pee
and they also will lick the floor.
They'll lick fucking food on the floor
and it's five times worse if it's a dog.
Undertale
is an 8.7 out of 10
because it has dog residue in the game.
It would be a 10 otherwise.
So I started wearing slippers
and then when I go into my room
I take the slippers off right outside of the bedroom.
It was a strict fucking policy
for me to never have my bare feet
around because there's dogs around.
So the problem with this house
is that there are so many people that have
a different policy
and it seems to be more like
it's okay to have fucking stuff on the floor
just have socks on all the time.
We have mostly hardwood floors
in this house
or different stuff
and it's just physically
impossible to keep them clean
for more than one minute.
There's just stuff you can't even see
that will get stuck to your foot
and personally I freak the fuck out
if anything is on my feet at all.
With the second something touches my foot
and I have to get rid of it.
So I wear socks at all times
if I'm looking around the house
sometimes socks and slippers
because I would just wear slippers
but I have a condition called
my feet sweat like hell
and if I wear anything without socks
I will destroy it
immediately.
I've had pairs of slippers
that literally fell apart within a week
because the strength of my foot sweat destroyed them.
Fuck.
It's really weird Digi.
I actually have
very weirdly dry feet
to the point like it's like a mummy.
I have mummy feet.
Do you have to moisturize them?
Yeah, I have to moisturize them.
My feet are fucking white.
I think that might be an ethnic thing.
I think you might have ethnic feet.
I have dangerously ethnic feet.
It's the name of a new podcast
by the way coming down.
I want to say that
that's the other reason I wear socks
because I don't want to look at feet.
I love walking
outside barefoot
on hot tarmac roads
and stuff.
I used to as a kid walk
on rocks and hot sand at the beach
barefoot and I just love
walking on
like a bumpy, really
searing hot tarmac road
for some reason it's just really pleasurable
and I enjoy it.
I love walking on gravel
and Legos and all that sort of stuff.
It has to be really fucking cold
to convince me to wear socks.
Only in the dead of winter
am I finally cold enough on the feet
to wear socks because it's just uncomfortable.
I'll wear socks in
I'll wear socks with my sandals
in the 100 degree weather
like socks are just
necessary to make things
not gross.
But yeah, to get back to the environment
like aside from my bathroom
my whole room is filthy
like in terms of
the daylight is hitting my desk
right now and there's just
there's just flakes
everywhere.
Who knows what this is all about.
It's dust.
A lot of it's probably skin
a lot of it's probably food
a lot of it's probably just whatever
is floating in the environment
it's just
has a thin veneer of bullshit
on it in my room.
There's nothing that's just clean.
If you took all the dust in my room
and then like compiled it together
it would be like at least a hamburger
or maybe even two.
It's fucking dust.
There's a ton of
fucking burger juice around me.
It's fucking gross.
It's all covered in fucking snow.
Do you actually wipe it down?
I do.
You see my kitchen it is immaculate right now
it looks great.
My work area I'm less particular about keeping it clean
but I do make sure that
the services are never sticky
and I wipe it down occasionally.
I'm not really concerned about clutter
all I can't deal with is
if there's like shit like gross shit
I gotta deal with that.
The funniest shit is that on my keyboard
all of the keys that I actually
use are like
black as they should be
from the grease of my fingers
So mostly the letters
N-I-G-E-R
They see a lot of use right?
But then all of the F keys
and the number keys and the home insert
are just caked in filth
You can't even read them
because there's so much shit on them
My old laptop used to be caked
the buttons used to be caked
It was horrible.
I scraped it off with a screwdriver
At the very top of the keyboard
with the extra buttons and stuff
All of them are caked except for the volume up
and volume down which have a little halo
of beautiful pristinness around them
because I press them constantly
I use them all the time
Everything else is horribly filthy except for those buttons
So yeah, you can immediately
at first glance
tell what buttons I press on this keyboard
because all the ones I don't are like
It's fucking horrible
Does anyone else do the thing
where they take the keyboard and shake it upside down?
I do that very regularly
Sometimes nothing comes out
and I'm like, yes
For me, dealing with the keyboard
Oh god, my mouse looks fucking
like there's so much
just gunk on my mouse
from my greasy hands
I try to clean my mouse fairly regularly
but it just built
I don't even think about it and then I look at it
I usually have to start cleaning it off
when it actually gets so caked up on the bottom
that I can't move it correctly
Yeah, that happens
I wanted to raise
a different issue
to all of this stuff
because we've been talking about hygiene
in the context of the real world
and the social standards
that we're generally used to
but I wanted to just
I had a whole different way of looking at it
based on one word
and that word is pheromones
If there is any reason to actually be
worried as a society
if we should shift our thinking
to fuck all this hygiene shit
embrace the fact that we're gross
and we get oil on everything
and that we're just animals and shit
because I'm worried
that I'm repressing my raw sexual energy
by not getting my stank out there
via pheromone
or my pheromones out there via stank
and my sexual prowess is being hampered
by not being able to
as a species, we've come to
enjoy the feeling of being very clean
so I don't think that's going to change
I prefer being clean
to being gross
but I know what being gross is like
I feel like people when pressed
are eager to embrace
hygiene and celebrate it
but I think that
almost everyone is nastier than they admit
that B, because we all
have different hygiene standards
and all of us are nasty about something
the other person doesn't think is nasty
like DeVu not thinking comes a big deal
whereas I think it's a
totally gross and DeVu thinking
that my bathroom being completely covered
and piss is gross when I also agree
that it's disgusting
I really fucking hate this piss
shaming going around
I just think that
when it comes down to it
most of us don't care
that much
it's one thing when you're trying to be like
oh I'm out on the prowl
trying to pick up chicks
I'm going to try to look smooth
and confident and stuff
but it's like when you actually have a girlfriend
you probably spend a lot of time with the two of you
you fucked 12 times in the same day
you're both literally disgusting
you are at the worst grossest you will ever be
and that's just natural
that's a natural state of being
to just be covered in your own filth
it's fucking natural
you don't have to bring to piss
piss isn't anything to be ashamed of
it's a thing to be celebrating
what makes the world go round
piss is the only thing that I fucking live for
in my entire life
it's the only reason I work for the money
why I even come on this podcast
it's the only thing I want to do with my fucking time
I feel it in my ears
it's the only thing that I want to believe in
now that's a munchy piss
yeah he's got a lot more piss now
but he did last time
that's an impressive
were you like chugging waters this whole time
all of my DNA is piss
that's all it is
press one for piss
munchy how much did you drink
in the course of this
I just want to fucking live in piss
that's all I want to do
I just want to continue being a piss boy
that's all I fucking want to do
I just want to become a piss guy
I think this is a good time to take some
reader questions
we'll just let him
we'll just let the sound of munchy's piss just be background noise
is it still going
it can't be
well with that
let's address at ken cray
crayley
yeah okay ken crayley
yeah okay he asks
I learned this week that a co-worker of mine
knows about the PCP
what should I do
buy a fucking shirt from
payompaom.com
slash ben saint
buy your fucking PCP guy's shirt
if a guy take him out for beer
if it's a girl take her out for beer
and ask her or tell her that she has nice shoes
tell her that she's young
and that you have sex with the young
munchy literally what did you drink
what do you mean
what did you drink in the last hour and a half
to have that much piss
maybe he drank it before the show
but he pissed right at the start of the show
yeah he did
all I fucking do is
I just drink my own piss
what do you mean
he drank last show's
load
oh no
that's johnny walker
third or fourth harvest
I'll just drink a johnny walker
and then my fourth harvest
after I pissed it out and drank it back again
that's what I'm drinking right now
I'm honestly on my fifth harvest right now
it's getting pretty up there
let's move on to our next question
I'm so fucking pissed right now
the procrastinator's podcast is going to develop
a reputation as the podcast
where a guy pisses on air
that's gonna be what we're going for
what was the thing davoo said
pistachutes
pistuosity
let me give my term next
sponsored by termics
yeah to the
say to that guy who works
where you work piss at him
and then say pistuous and then he'll get it
see if he laughs as you are peeing on his face
okay
at jay kuchar fischer
should I go back to college
or am I too redpilled
from watching this podcast
you're too redpilled don't go back
it's not worth it
oh man you know what um
unless you know exactly what your prospects are
and you know exactly what we're gonna get out of
have a plan find the most efficient way
if that involves college then do it
but if not then don't
yeah do you know what my cousin patricia the pleb said
right after I told her that I went to the dentist in virginia
she said oh hey virginia
I'm applying go back to grad school in virginia
she's like in her early 30s
her fucking life she doesn't have a career
don't follow her don't follow patricia the pleb
she played fucking second life for like years
that's a mistake
that's all you had to say
is it normal for your piss to be like
boiling
usually
that would mean that you haven't
you haven't been hydrated well
it's like
if your piss boils
I feel like it is top ramen juice
without the noodles
oh no
that's salty dude
what question was I gonna ask you before the show
oh yeah tell us the story of you going to the
fucking museum place
oh yeah
if you go to my twitter
bestest guy ever
I tweeted a bunch of shit today
oh my god that picture with the lady
today
April 15th 2017
go back to that day
go to that day and look at my shit
so I was at the creationist museum
so my parents are in town
they were just coming for a visit
and then they were just looking for
shit to do and one of the things
that was like suggested
to my mom which is like at the hotel or something
was doing ziplines and so the place they were
signing up for didn't have any available
so we were just like hey well that sounds like a cool idea
let's see if there's another one nearby
and the second one was this it was called like
scream and raptor ziplines
and we're like okay that sounds cool
so we get there and we realize it's
the fucking creationist museum
I had no idea such a thing existed
I've heard about it a lot over the years
I listened to a bunch of fucking atheist shit
because that's all I think about I much hate fucking god
so I get there and
you just
you just choose to hate him
that's the atheist position
we know he's real we're just mad at him
when you go there do they just hand you
a flyer that just says
carbon dating what
dude the thing about this that was most
fascinating was that the place was covered
in dinosaurs it was like
mostly dinosaur themed
right I couldn't like we didn't buy tickets
to go inside to see any of the
indoor exhibits and shit but I've seen
like pictures because this place is famous
I know they have pictures of like cavemen
hanging out with dinosaurs in that place
obviously it's fucking fascinating
you know because it's like
the humans live together with dinosaurs
on Atlantis I mean before Atlantis
or El and the Mars came
they were hanging out with the necals
I'm pretty sure like four out of five necals
were raptors
let me just clarify right they based
the zipline technology on the necol
technology that's right just so you people know
the creations zipline technology
brought to us from
fucking Mars
just so you know
people the creations museum just to clarify
it is a Christian
biblical like Genesis origin
museum like evidence for
why Genesis is true and accurate
fucking yes like this is a six thousand
years old thing and they like
and
a model of the
like life-sized model of a room on Noah's
Ark that you were at
yeah and that's like
check it out guys we remade
one of the like hundred and sixty six rooms
that was in Noah's Ark
here's the Bible passage that talks about it
here's and this is it this is what
Noah was dealing with when he packed literally
two of every animal onto this Ark
everyone else in the world was killed by God
and he and his family single-handedly restarted
humanity yeah and every other animal
is there a big display all about the
is there all a big display like about the continental
drift and it was like after Noah
continental drift really got its head out of its
ass and made Australia
that's why
not at that part now if I worked for the
creationist museum I know and I worked to like
design a set I know what I do because
it'd be based off of a really good creationist
argument I once heard so this would be
the display there'd be the
the skeleton of like a Chihuahua
and it'd be like uh-huh look at this
Chihuahua you know we you know
using our top scientists you know we can guess
it was like 500 million years ago 700 million
years ago we just make guesses we scientists
we know what we're doing right you know
the fact that meteorologists can't predict the
weather within the next week but they all know about
climate change and evolution sure sure we all
know that right lol then
then right next to it show the body
the skeleton of a great
Dane be like see now look at this
look look at how the Chihuahua
evolved into a great Dane over the course
of millions of years right because this is
hypothetical if this took place 50
million years in the future where all dogs were
extinct and all we had with the bones we'd be like
look see this evolution where this creature got
tall huh see that's evolution
right right guys huh
huh and then like when you leave that particular
place there's like there's like five people
who like rub their their elbows and you'd be
like huh you get it you get it see see
how that looks like evolution
I are you making an argument about how like
I know a lot of creationists make the micro
like they say of course my oh yeah
oh yeah it's like macro evolution
to say and that they're that there's things
that could be mistaken for yeah yeah
and that's evidence against oh man
oh my god oh my god yeah
the whole micro evolution thing is my favorite
argument and having a creationist dad I've gotten
to have a number of times this for like a
Christian well it's so short though it's
a really short debate right so it is
as follows but it's like well yeah I know
speciation where like
you know hair can grow in or shrink in
length and colors can change and I'm
like doesn't that shit stack
yeah and then he's dead he's
dead he's fucking dead it's the shortest
debate I've ever had in my life and yet
they I don't know they cling to it for whatever
but anyway well it's because it's the
species is defined by what you can breed
so even if you micro evolve
the whole fuck ton if you can still
breed with the original species then you
haven't become a new me I love that quote you did
cling to it they cling to their guns and
to their religion Pokemon go to the polls
that's that's that's why I voted for
Hilary got into this museum
and you took this amazing picture where
this this lady looks
really upset well hey let me let me
say there's a couple big yeah the first
one is is me like bowing
in awe of the creationist museum and then
the next one is me yeah so
like so I'm I want there's a dinosaur
there and before we left I wanted to get a picture
of it so my mother who I had
with me I had to her take the picture
by the way my parents are basically
non-religious for the most part I think
my dad believes in some spooky shit but he doesn't
really talk about that much so I don't really know
like we all made fun of this shit the whole time
yeah
the Holy Ghost
all the time this spooky shit
I don't want to get haunted by the Holy Ghost
dad dad dad
except the existence of the occasional
Babadook
yeah that's right
he was off of the bathroom and so I give my mom
this thing and I'm just like I just yelled at my mom
so I had just done the pose in front
of the in front of the thing like like looking
up at the sign in awe and
I was already yelling I'm just like yo ma
I'm gonna throw up some gang signs I say
just like that and I pose in front
of this dinosaur and the just the best thing
was that this this fucking family
was in the picture go go look at the
fucking tweets the best thing I've ever done
and she just she's so mad
she's so fucking mad
she's making a mockery
also you know what this is this is relevant
she was all because that family was black
right they should have like a black guy
who like works there is like yeah you know
when you think about it the theory of evolution
is essentially racist because it implies
that there was this evolution after black
people and white people are a higher
advanced state of evolution that white
people are the superior
races that's what we're talking about here
interesting interesting platform
you guys have yes yes
that's my platform for sure
that's what I was trying to communicate through this tweet
she definitely her face to me
says what the fuck
is this dude and like
her son next to her did also not look
too thrilled it looks to me like she's saying
is this nigga serious yeah it does look
like that like like Tommy like Tommy
and Chuckie I mean I
show of it I was sort of yelling to
people I was
sort of just mocking everybody there yeah
it was great it was super fun by the way those
were tight as fuck and there were
biblical scriptures like on the ziplines
like oh yeah
oh my god
god is god is my wings let him carry me
oh my god this fucking zipline
Exodus 102 from that shit
I don't know
every time you go down the zipline
one chakra aligns
in your body every
trip down the zipline increases your christ
consciousness by one dimension
yeah exactly but walking back
it takes it away
well you gotta find
like an infinite zipline that just keeps going down
at my max what do you think my christ consciousness
was elevated to just by being in proximity
of all this all these normally like like
normal people are at a two
baseline and and I'm
I would say that you like at your
height would honestly get to like
like a hard like five
or a or a or a light six
check those tweets I was
I was feeling I was feeling that crystal and energy
pulsating within me I could feel it
just check that like your blood
probably turned into crystals and like
hard and you can see the fucking Nicole
trying to teach you about stairs type evolution
fucking toad son probably
no toad son came down to the
creation museum and he was like
hey god hey bros doing good
shit I got from
god check it ziplines
and the creation museum
god's real we knew it
got that fucking stairs
evolution motherfucker
and
that's the story
my christ consciousness is not high enough
level to understand what's going on here
yeah you can't even process that shit
yeah we got a couple more here's one
jenny's at jenny's
maku domaru maku domaru
this guy tweets us all the time
says what's up with the hacking
these days
there's trouble with that shit
there's this hacker group called
ourmine
they've got their own wikipedia article and everything
they've hacked everybody in the world
apparently lots of famous
people and shit and now they've
been hacking into youtube
networks and just getting access to
all their channels and changing the
titles and descriptions on the videos
just to advertise themselves
I think they're probably selling something
but you know what they're selling
they're selling like anti piracy
shit like anti
that's being able to hack you
software but uh
they just so happened to
hack the network studio
71 like three days
after I joined that studio
after like four years of not
having joined a network so
get fuck dude
are you staying with that those guys
for now I mean
I signed a contract with them but
the thing about it is that they're
I'll talk about this at a later date
sure but the thing about it is that they're
not exactly a network
they're more of a talent agency that
has a network so that's
why I'm working with them but uh
you know I'll get into that later when I've got
more to say about it
I almost
I got a vibe okay
yesterday I spent the better half
of my afternoon pissing my pants
because I was
I had actually
it's an all day affair
I
I was on google
and this isn't a fucking joke
I was typing in what causes
autism
and I
it's not a joke
oh god
and I clicked the first link
and I went to a page
like I have
since done this on other devices and it doesn't go
to the page that I clicked on so I literally think
it's an autism ghost
page that I found
and I clicked on like I took I clicked on a link
and took me to like this weird like this
weird like obvious porn ad and it was
like a booming face came over and it was like
uh I am from
Microsoft you have been hacked
please dial the snobber
and I'll fucking fix your shit dude promise
and I was like oh I'm
scared of things so I
I close I close
my firefox and I didn't I didn't want to have
anything to do with it but
here's the thing the voice
kept going after I closed
firefox oh no
fuck yeah
they're in the walls now dude
exactly exactly so I
immediately piss and shit my pants
me too
it's a defense mechanism
it's self defense
self defense
no one's gonna want to hack me if I pissed myself
they will be so I called
my friend and I literally just started
trying him like you have to help me
and he's like okay and then and then
like he like the entire time he's like
this is just this isn't real Islamic ghost
yeah yeah I was just about to say this isn't real
Islamic ghost and then like like he gets
like some software to me and like like I run
like like like some like antivirus thing
and I literally like find like some like
backdoor like like like like trojan
horse shit that's like been backdoor
my information and and now like
apparent like like I probably have like
like all my files are on some like
like your wizards database but but I got rid
of that I up and
I know all the munchies secrets
yeah exactly
all because I wanted to know what caused
autism
autism you know I think we if we
could find if we can find pinpoint
if we can use our fucking crystalline
sensor technology to find the one place on the planet
where some persons Christ consciousness has
spiked to unbelievable level
we'll know who has munchies secrets
we'll know where he is
we'll never find out what causes autism
no
he never found out
that's the greatest crime of all
oh tragic
this is like a superfine version too
like the entire time I had to jump through hoops
I had to download a whole bunch of shit
and the entire time
a couple times my computer just
shut off at random
and I relate this to my
friend and this is
my greatest fear
at one time Nate talked about how like
if he had a runny nose and he couldn't breathe
baby shit
here is the greatest fear
I could possibly have not a fucking joke
I get a virus
and then I'm like I'm going about my day
I'm just going about like doing whatever
playing games I have a virus
it's dormant and then like
a pop-up window happens and like
some dude just starts laughing at me and it's like
I'm in the computer bitch
and then he's like he just starts laughing at me
like I don't know what to do because he's
complete control of my computer and then he just starts going
to like gore websites and he's like you like this
huh this is what you like
and I'm like no it's not
it's not what I like
that's the worst thing
that's all I could think about when I was trying to
get the virus off my computer
it's like a black guy is going to show up and he's going to make me see gore
he's going to make me see gore
I think something similar
I mean I haven't like had my computer
completely taken over but there was this one time
when I got a virus and it changed
my desktop background and it would not stop
playing music and I couldn't
do anything so I had to reformat the whole
hard drive I think I was like 12
I remember one time when I was a kid
I was like wondering to myself is it possible
just possible like theoretically
to have a virus that just overloads
the wires and like
mechanizes them and like turn and like
all the wires and fucking systems
they start flapping around in there
making a huge noise and they turn into like a little RC
helicopter or a little drone
that busts out of your case
and stabs the shit out of you
that's basically possible in that show
fucking computers are terrifying
I want more questions man these are good questions
we got two more yeah these were pretty good
I went through the whole list ahead of time and found the best ones
okay here we go
at Zana J
it's like x-i-n-i-j-e I don't know how to pronounce this shit
okay this person has some very important questions
guys jesus man
yeah I don't know man this person
asked what would you do
to punish Ben St.'s crimes against humanity
I assume
this is a good question
it's gotta come up at some point
is it
Ben's Crimes Against Polk?
that's what I was wondering
I would make Ben take a public shit
no
I can't even take a private shit
without running the water so no one can hear it
exactly
we gotta have a toilet
up on a podium in the middle of town
square and he has to take a public shit
I'm just saying
that's one step up from a group shit
that's like a public shit
we should do a group public shit
I'm imagining
I'm on murderers
row
I'm being walked to the gallows and the whole PCP
is prodding me along
and they walk me up a big ramp
up to the top of a statue
in town square and I squat down
and I'm just like weeping
the tears are flowing
and I'm like I can't do it
and then just
munchy comes
and squats down next to me in solidarity
and then everyone looks at each other
everyone looks at each other
and they all come and squat next to me
and the tears just get even stronger
and I'm like I love you guys so much
and
I'm imagining this is like
a possibly tall statue
and the people can barely hear us
but then people are like
shush shush shush we need to hear the shit
we need to hear the shit noises
and then it's like
Bahudorus the song from
the Grinch and then they hear from the top of the statue
and we're all singing like group poop
group poop
I imagine this
and passersby just behold
this miraculous spectacle with tears in their eyes
as shit as just particles of shit
and splatters just like come down
just rain down upon them
I think that's far too romantic of a possibility
I think more of that he gets the chair
and it's all dramatic and some fucking
some sort of like a new metal song
is playing over it like
into the ground
and his heart stops
then fucking Max revive
he busts out
he gets out
because you know the law says
according to the law
if you survive
the fucking execution then you're off free
apparently that's what I've heard
you're not punished to be killed
you're punished to have this thing happen to you
that kills you so like if it doesn't kill you
then you're fucking free
fucked up
and on that
hygienic note
I think we should end the podcast
that's a good shit moment to end
possibly
that is fine by me
wasn't there one more question
maybe there was
but by the way about the shitting thing
I just want to let you know once you get someone
Ben in this case to shit publicly one time
once you force him to do it you won't be able to stop
you shit publicly
I'm just letting you know
a whole new world opens up
yeah exactly
he's not proud of it
he just can't stop
people are coming up to him
what are you fucking doing man
I don't know
I can't shit in that tiny bathroom anymore
it just feels wrong it doesn't feel right anymore
I have this new urge
these are horizons of Ben Broden
I have a punishment
for Ben Stain
every time that he
fucking gets a dollar on Patreon
his bones get stronger
he gets more calcium
why is that a punishment
he is
oh shit
I'm for it
I'll take that bullet
okay this one this is actually a question
okay well there's this thing
at Xylovitch has tweeted like a whole fuck
ton of questions all of them directed at
monkey but they're all based on the fact
that he is fucking dead
so the last
where does it go okay it's a monkey
why is my none the greatest pokemon ever
well you see
uh well you know
pretty uh not you know
yeah thank you for that
monkey just answered this question on an
AMA like the other day
he did yeah
well fuck I mean this guy it's just that
this guy has said like 10 questions like
how do you know you how do I know you really
love me if you willingly send me to my grave
I miss you monkey monkey better
be on this episode or else I wasted my
chance to just talk to him
well it's a good thing I am
on this podcast
I thought you said you picked out the good ones
yeah this was a good question god damn
it I'm invested in the monkey Jones
Nuzlocke right subscribe to
munchie jones
I haven't watched the last like 12 episodes
of monkeys nuzlocke so I have no idea
we should have ended on the on the poop
on the poop uh the poop
we should have quit while we were ahead
let's go everybody let's get out of here
okay we're done thanks for listening everybody
make sure to send us more questions at TP
cheers and we will see you next week
bye
hey
oh god
you need to go out with a strong kiss
yeah
I'm
supposed to be
working right now
I'm supposed
to be working
right now
but I'm not working
I'm doing
nothing
my dick I'm jerking
myself I'm
sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
don't want to do
it