This episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast was brought to you by our bonus episode.
Go to patreon.com slash The Pro Crastinators and pledge $5 or more to get access to all our bonus monthly episodes.
Last month's episode was Charlie Brown versus Inuyasha.
Charlie Brown is a popcorn nihilist. He's a loner with a heart of gold.
I'm gonna slap this book closed to show you how hefty it is.
Oh, shit! That's what you're up against!
I thought this show was about race realism. How can the Black Tetsaiga be the ultimate flaw?
Oh my god!
With the enhanced windscarability, let alone the Konogosha Diamond Tetsaiga with the adamant...
Charlie Brown has the nuclear bomb and that's a very powerful weapon that ravishes Japanese people.
But do you really think?
In my heart of hearts, I think that Inuyasha could have kicked that football.
That's patreon.com slash The Pro Crastinators, giving you a boner every single time.
I am the one who's in charge.
I am the one who says yes!
No!
Now!
Here!
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators podcast.
I'm the best guy ever.
Oh yes, and I almost forgot. The PCP is a podcast with a bunch of internet creators, mostly me.
These guys are also here for some reason.
But we all make stuff on the internet and here we are talking about our thoughts on stuff.
We've got Hippocrite here.
Oh gee, I sure hope I'm gonna do okay in this...
Oh boy.
Oh, come on, give.
Didn't you hear my confident opening there?
Oh no, I'm so sorry.
We've got Tom Oliver here.
I can confidently say that Nate is not as good as me because I'm the real best guy.
There you go, classic baking until you make it, everybody.
There it is.
Excellent.
Fuck you, buddy.
And we've got Lethal Aurora Mage here.
I'm gonna bend this podcast over a table and nail it in the ass.
Whoa!
Whoa, that is confident.
Now that's the kind of hardcore MiG-Tau sentiment you'd expect from Lethal Aurora Mage.
Well, guys, today's...
It's so funny how like...
MiG-Tau Mage going her own way.
Go on, give.
Oh, I'm so unconfident.
What I said sounded like something I would have said at the beginning of this podcast if you go back.
That's true.
That just is what I sounded like.
And now, it wasn't even a joke.
People would probably be confused.
I guess he's still unconfident as we expect.
If they listened to episode one and then skipped straight to episode 86 or whatever this is now,
they'd be like, oh, that gib still shaking in his boots, quaking in his quaker pants.
Well, we all know that once you become a racist and start saying racial slurs all the time,
you invariably get more confident.
I'm sure we'll talk about that point at some moment.
You kind of have to.
You kind of have to survive the onslaught, you know?
If you want to go out there and make race realism your thing,
you really got to have a strong personality to back that up these days.
And I suppose you probably always did.
But there it is.
There it is.
And that is our topic, everybody.
It is confidence, confidence, confidence, confidence, which I'm sure our audience has in spades.
I have no doubt about it.
Our wonderful teenage boy audience definitely is smash and puss on the reg.
Oh, wait a minute.
Has there been an incident?
Huh?
What?
Oh, sorry.
I heard it always and I thought I might have been cut off because I didn't hear you guys laughing uproariously
to my hilarious jokes.
And that was a big problem.
Okay.
I left in my head.
And joining us late.
Oh, who could it be but Digi.
Digi Bro is here.
Hey, I got tons of confidence.
That's what this is about, right?
He's got the confidence to join in whenever the fuck he wants to be casually late for the podcast.
What do you have?
Impressive.
Well, so here we are, everybody.
Confidence is our topic and confidence is our attitude.
So let's head over to Urban Dictionary and find out what the fuck we're dealing with here.
So the top definition of confidence is absolute could care fucking less what everybody thinks.
That is, that's okay.
That's it.
There's another way to say that is what confidence is but okay.
Yeah.
The second one here is confidence.
The thing girls say that they want in a guy when they themselves usually don't have the confidence to make the first move.
Amig Tao wrote this definition and I love it.
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
Third definition of confidence.
Yeah.
Which side of the fence is everyone on?
Who is a for and against confidence?
I'm against it.
I think it's a bad idea.
I think it's dangerous.
Oh.
I think it's really dangerous.
I'm confidently against confidence.
It's just a bad idea.
Wait, I just can't tell if you're fucking joking or not because I've never heard anyone state that they're against confidence.
I just wanted to say I'm confidently against it like as a fucking joke.
Confidence is like charisma, right?
They're basically the same thing.
Charismatic leaders have throughout history been responsible for some fucked up shit.
I think there's lots of people who have tons of confidence in no charisma.
Like that anime snob or something.
He's got charisma.
Well, could you define charisma as you mean it here?
You've only said the anime snob has charisma.
That's a dangerous thing to say.
He has a type of charisma for sure.
To be charismatic would basically mean that you have an attitude that makes people sort of want to follow you or to just take an interest in you as a charisma.
He has his legion of sycophants.
He has a charisma that's like cringy.
A cringe-ma, if you will.
Oh, that's good.
But I think there's lots of people who don't have any charisma but are so confident that they do.
And someone like him, yeah, he has enough charisma to have a follow.
He has a type of charisma.
The amount he thinks he has is vastly greater than that.
You know what it reminds me of?
It's like the mental equivalent of retard strength.
One who is mentally deficient can have maximum confidence that what they're doing is correct.
Like a baby crying.
But then they're caught and no one's going to give a shit or want to do shit for them.
So okay, okay.
I see a distinction here.
You know why that is, right?
It's because with normal people we only use 10% of our brains at a time.
But if you're not concentrating on which 10% you use, then you're just using your whole brain all the time.
So you can't think about any one thing, but you can do everything.
You know what I'm saying?
That sounds legit to me.
That sounds like science to me for sure.
I actually saw a video earlier about how the more confident you are,
like the people who are the most confident that they're good at their job are the ones who are the least effective at that job.
Like those people at the post office who give me shit every time I go in.
They're not that great and they also resent me for being there.
That's socialism at work, everybody.
That's socialism at work.
That's what it does.
That's my political point.
That stuff interests me like crazy.
And that's what is called the Dunning-Kruger effect.
Yeah, that's the one.
Believing that you are vastly superior than what you actually are.
Just because it's like the less you know about how much better you could be.
Right, right.
It's funny.
I was just recording a huge vlog explaining a bunch of shit about myself
and how I'm always accused of being super egotistical and stuff like that
because I think I'm better than most anime YouTubers, but I consider that a really low bar.
That's a good point.
There's tons of people I look up to who I consider to be way better than me
and I'm like, oh, there's tons of improvement.
Which is why I think I'm able to be successful and I see things that way.
But I've definitely seen people who are like, you know, I'm already amazing.
I don't need to improve anything and then they wallow in obscurity
and they don't understand why, you know?
Sure, yeah.
That sort of reminds me of how saying you're one of the better brony analysts
is like that doesn't mean much.
Yeah, no, it means nothing.
It kind of reminds me of like, so the world has changed, you know?
And guys like, oh, I don't know.
Guys like Dr. Wolf are now exposed to a worldwide audience
and they're able to garner some small following.
He has more subs than me so I'm not trying to say that he's a total shit or anything
so I respect the work that he's done.
But you can tell there's an internal limit within him
about what he's going to do, how high he's going to reach
and you can see the walls that he's put up for himself
just based on the kind of stuff he's doing and where he's going to go
and like the sort of people he's going to attract,
aka weirdo bronies, you know, who got no direction in life and whatnot
and yet like if he was out in the world,
like the real world equivalent that is like a cult leader.
You got like a cult leader and that's what Dr. Wolf is to me.
He's like a weirdo cult leader.
That's what he would be without the internet
and I think he's like Mormon so that might actually be relatively accurate anyway.
But the point is like...
We should probably name drop fewer people at this.
I feel like we started enough shit on this podcast lately.
No one's going to object to talking about Dr. Wolf.
I don't even hate Dr. Wolf the way like Ben does.
I just find him a curiosity.
So I'm just saying that like people form these very small communities
where they're like worshiped like gods, you know,
or that's exaggeration but like they're treated as like the king of their little pond
and people are often satisfied with that.
But with the internet now, you can compare yourself to the entire world.
So like where you're saying that people give you shit
for saying you're like the best anime analyst.
Oh, it's funny because they also accuse me of having that exact cult you're talking about
and like I'm not satisfied with that.
Like I don't think that's good that I have like a cult of people who worship me.
Of course.
And your commenters are formed from a lot of different people
and they each have the luxury to like choose the attack vehicle they want to go with
against, you know, any person they disagree with online.
So, you know, they've got the luxury of doing that
and not having to be logically consistent because they're an anonymous shit poster.
So, that's cool.
But anyway, that's not particularly relevant to...
I was going to say how I think of my own level of confidence
and I like to consider myself like low in confidence
because, you know, I do good things
and then when people, you know, see that I'm like, oh, it's not that good.
And then they say, but you're, you know, your work's so great, way better than mine.
And I'm just like, hey, it's exactly what I want to see.
Great, you know, like I don't know whether I actually think I have low confidence or not.
But it makes me feel good to make other people feel like they're comparing themselves to me
and it's bad for them and it's like, yes, sick, you know.
Do you like getting the feeling there of like, hey, if I really did it,
if I was like truly out there, I would like be so good.
You know what I'm getting at with that?
It's like if you like lower your, you know what I mean?
I don't know.
Like, I'm, I, you know, I, like, I like to think that I'm not very confident
because of that reason, but I think I am actually not very confident.
I don't know how to measure it.
Like, like, it's too like, you have to be very introspective to know.
You know, I think people who, I think everybody has like a lack,
like nobody's perfectly confident, but people who are like particularly
confident think that other people are like just confident about everything.
I think some people look at me and think I am confident about everything
and that is not even, I'm like everything I do, there's like an element of,
oh God, am I doing the right thing?
Like in the long term, you know, is this going to bite me in the ass,
whatever I'm doing, or like, or is this even good, you know?
And like, I just have enough confidence to do it anyways.
And I think that's what the real power of confidence is.
It's not about like thinking everything you do is definitely going to be great.
It's just about thinking that there's enough of a chance people will like it
that you should do it anyways, you know?
Well, there's like, there's a couple different kinds.
I think, I mean, I've learned in my experience
that there's a couple different ways that like confidence is segmented.
There is, there is such a thing as like pure confidence.
And it's things that guys who are like, I learned about this when I like,
looked into like pickup artistry stuff.
Like you can, you can develop a sense of just raw confidence in yourself,
which is kind of like Zen.
It's kind of just like accepting oblivion of the world
and like accepting that like consequences don't matter
and like just learning to accept like the fatality of existence.
Like, and that'll allow you to do things like approach a girl,
like be rejected and not care and then just continue on your quest
to, you know, keep doing that until you like smash puss or whatever.
So that's the kind of like raw, separate confidence.
But then there's the kind that in a way is much easier to obtain
but also is kind of much harder.
And so what I'm talking about is like confidence developed
through acquiring skill and through acquiring mastery like of a specific thing.
Like for example, and I think this is really the kind that I have obtained over the years
because I have just done so many vlogs, so many videos,
so many, I don't know, like songs and stuff.
I guess I haven't done as many of those.
So actually much less confident like my singing ability than other stuff.
But like you just by doing this, like if someone asked me like to be on a podcast,
I'm like, I'm ready. I got everything ready to go.
I'm prepared immediately. I will have no problem doing this.
And I know I can talk for a fucking hour if I need to.
I think a lot of that comes just from normalizing it for yourself.
Like, I don't even know if I'm better at podcasting.
I've just done so fucking much of it that like how could I not be better?
Or how can I not do it?
You know, like you just get to a point where it's not a matter of can I or can't I.
It's I know I will.
And that's like when a lot of people bring up confidence.
A lot of it is like, I mean, I always picture like a nerdy guy who's like,
I'm unconfident. What do I do?
And the question is like, what do you want to do?
What is your goal?
If the goal is to like get a girlfriend, then like immediately begin.
Like it's not hard.
You just like to start doing the things that will help you get your goal.
If you think you're unattractive, work on your appearance.
And I think a lot of people stop themselves when they hear what the things they have to do are.
They say, I can't do that.
It's like everybody can do that.
And the thing that really pisses me off.
How willing you are to just fucking go through with it, you know.
Absolutely.
And the worst argument you can ever make to yourself or hear when people say this thing is like,
No, I can't do that because that would be me being inauthentic to myself.
When they when like that kind of stuff comes up.
Now that pisses me off.
That reminds me of this this thing I heard at this like talk.
Where it was like talking about creativity and like stuff and like, you know, your projects and you know,
Are they going to go anywhere?
And she she said this thing which like stuck with me because of how like alternative it is to the usual like motivational speech.
It's like, not everybody deserves, you know, to be successful.
And, you know, maybe you don't maybe you don't deserve to be successful.
That's great.
I wasn't empowering thought though.
Yeah, because it's like, you don't deserve it until you have, you know,
Until you put the work in to be good enough to be a person who does deserve it.
People feel like they're entitled to a lot in the world.
And I think it really a lot of good comes from recognizing that the universe owes you nothing.
And it's completely does not give a shit about you completely indifferent to your existence.
And once you recognize that and you cast away all that foo foo bullshit about karma and whatnot.
And you just recognize I need to where I need to write this shit might write this ship myself.
I'm going to get where I want to go.
Then they can start to make steps towards it.
You know, you know, something you said earlier, Nate about people saying it would be untrue to themselves to do a thing.
My response to that would be like you are not you are nothing like there is no you.
It's what you do.
Yeah, that is you like you are just whatever you are performing at the time.
There's no like solid like like your personality or whatever is not like an object in your brain that informs all your actions.
It's like I feel like a lot of it comes from this idea of a soul, I think a lot of it steps from that.
Yeah, like, oh, I've got my soul is like this.
It's like, no, you are just whatever you are performing, you know, like whatever you're doing, that is who you are.
And if you do the same thing for long enough, you'll forget that you were ever anything different.
You know, like look at me.
I was born.
Yeah.
I'm just a meme now.
We were all born with Brony souls, but we chose to change them.
We chose to sculpt them for good.
I think some people really say it like that.
I think some do for sure.
People who left the Brony community and people view it as like you changed.
It's like, yeah, I was never a solid thing.
Like I was.
Everybody fucking changes.
Yeah.
Like that's just natural.
If you don't like endeavor to change, like if you if you think every moment that you have an opinion on everything like that is your opinion.
And if you, you know, nobody likes the idea of, I don't know, like making a review and then having a different idea about it later and making another review.
Like nobody likes that idea for some reason.
If you think putting things on the Internet is like, oh, that's the snapshot.
That is this person.
This person has talked about this thing.
And now that is what they think forever.
Right.
But you can change your mind.
You should be changing your mind constantly.
Guys, I want to say, I want to say I slightly disagree.
Like for what give has said, like I agree with that.
But with the whole not doing things like you thinking you can't do a thing because that's not the thing.
Like personally, I have changed over the years as a person's, you know, so I'm not the same person.
I was like 10 years ago or whatever.
So like progress happens, people change, people do become different.
However, I feel like a lot of people can sometimes like don't change at the core.
For instance, like there's still things I know that like 100% I'm never going to do in my life because that's not the kind of person I am.
And not the kind of person I would be able to become.
I'm just not capable of it.
Right.
There are limits, of course.
I'm never going to be the party girl that goes out every night and drinks a lot and the clubs.
Do you even want to be that though?
That's the question.
I would like to be more outgoing and not scared of people.
I mean, I think that I think there's a there's a big difference between like, you know, like you can change things about yourself.
But like if you don't want to be like if you don't even want to be that person, then no, you're never going to be that person.
But like if you were telling me like, I want to be a party girl who goes out every night, I'd be like, well, follow this 10 step program and you can be that person.
You know, but like,
Well, I think it's not something you can even envision yourself as.
The difficulty of stuff like that is like, oh, I don't really want to be an outgoing party person, but in order to meet people and get a girlfriend.
I think that's a misconception though.
Well, like that's the way people see a lot of problems like that.
They have to do something they don't want to do to get something that they do.
Yeah, that's right.
Like I actually have had this sort of experience back in high school in an attempt to sort of fit in with my fellow classmates and just like make some proper friends.
I did actually go out and whenever they would do meetups and like drink alcohol and party and stuff, I did actually go out my way and go out and try to mingle and see what it's about and just sort of blend in and it didn't work out.
I did it like several times and it's just it didn't happen.
Would you say that the problem was sort of realizing that fitting in wasn't something you really wanted if that's what it meant?
I think it's a matter of degrees.
Like that's the whole thing.
It's not like wanting something isn't like a binary thing.
It's not like I wanted or I don't want it.
There's tons of things that like I want it, but I don't want it enough to go through this like process.
I mean, that's sure.
Sure.
Like I want to be good at drawing, but like the amount of work I have to do to like really get super good at it.
I'd rather do 3d instead because I have more fun doing that.
I want both of them, but you only have so much time.
You have so much effort and I'd rather dedicate my time here.
That doesn't mean I don't want that.
It's just that I don't want it as much.
So we have to make decisions that way.
Like you could want to go out and party, but if you want that less than like hanging out at home and like reading a book or something, then you want things on those on different levels.
You know, the coolest example of all this is I was watching a David Bowie documentary and there was this part where he said, I don't really want to be famous or a rock star or anything, but I'm doing it right now so that I have the resources at my disposal when I need them to do what I actually want to do.
There you go.
Great attitude.
Like he became a superstar so that he could do whatever he wanted.
He became a superstar so that his Minecraft let's place would get so many views when they came out.
Totally the exact approach I have like at all.
Me too.
I fucking hate being famous and I hate it more every day, but like, you know, I can't make the kind of money I do without having some fame and like I like being able to eat out every day.
So like, yeah, I'm not interested in being a famous YouTuber.
I don't eat out every day, boy.
I'm not interested in being a famous YouTuber, but I am interested in eating out every day and like one facilitates eating out every day, boy.
Yeah.
There's number two.
But yeah, with regards to what Tom said, that was my approach to romance for like the last few years was like.
Romance?
Eating out every day, boy.
Yeah.
There it is.
I can confidently say I'm ashamed of all of you right now.
That was my approach to like after I had broke up with my ex-girlfriend like three fucking years ago, I think, over three and a half years ago.
Like for a long time it was like, well, I have discovered I like sex a lot and I'd like to do more of it, but what will that require?
Like what will I have to do to meet women and like be attractive and like flirt?
It's like probably gonna have to lose weight a little bit or like just change my appearance and stuff, which I don't even really need to do.
I just need to be more confident in myself, but like I definitely have to go out.
Like there's no way I can meet women without going out and like putting myself out there.
And I was like, man, I don't want to have to do that.
Like I want to sit around and make videos all day.
Like that's where my passion is.
And like until I've changed some things about my life, I don't want to rush into that.
And I think that's kind of what Tom was talking about.
Like that feeling of you will have to make sacrifices sometimes to get what you want.
But like maybe you don't want to make those particular sacrifices, right?
I mean, yeah.
And it's about working smart, not working hard when it comes to all things, including this.
And like just as you were saying before, like, yeah, like we approach these things in different ways.
Like my whole goal, the reason that I've started doing any shit was because I wanted to be a meme on 4chan.
That is my long-term end game goal to be a posted meme on 4chan.
That's what this has all been for.
Everything else is just filler until that happens.
I think it's working.
It's slowly getting there.
There's a couple threads.
I've seen the images of worst guy ever pop up and whatnot.
And it's good.
I like how that's your end goal.
And I did that without even wanting to or trying to.
How'd you do?
Oh, that's right.
Because you were like the...
I was Mexican Christian Bale.Jpeg.
That's right.
And wasn't your picture used for like some like fake thing?
What was that?
Yes.
It was like the brony dating profile or something?
Or like the nerd loser profile?
Something like that.
Oh, man.
Dude, something incredible.
That's really good.
It's good to know that I'm living your dream.
But I can tell you, someone on the other side, not all it's cracked up to be.
I understand.
But I don't know...
I don't know if dreams be memes.
I've also lived that dream.
It's not been great for me either.
But it's for like, I am one of them, you know?
And that attitude comes forth in my thing.
So like, I mean, the goal is to not be there as like a loser that everyone hates.
The goal would be as just like either a funny meme man or someone who's generally liked.
Like the way they post them.
I don't know.
Anywhere.
Like slash our guy if they actually let them post E-Celib stuff there.
Yeah, it's quite possible.
Yeah.
Honestly, like V is more open to discussing E-Celibs even though everyone says they hate it.
But you will get popular on V before A, even though you will talk about it.
I agree.
V is closet A anyway, as we all know.
That's true.
That is very true.
But what I wanted to say, just changing topics slightly, is that like this idea of like defining ourselves.
Like an adage comes to mind with this whole conversation that I don't know if it's an exact quote from someone,
but it's like you are what you do often, at least to other people and to a large part to yourself as well.
So like if you, and confidence has so much to do with self-identity and like who we think we are, what we think we're capable of.
So like if you, just like Digi and I, you know, and I was saying before, like because we do this thing all the time,
like make podcasts or whatever, it is basically an effortless thing to do.
And it could be enjoyable and whatnot.
It's so effortless and we're so confident that we drown out everyone else on the podcast.
Yeah, unfortunately.
Yeah, it's not effortless for me.
It's mostly because there isn't like a very clear format structure for this.
Like are we talking about our experiences with confidence?
We're just sort of saying things.
Whatever.
If anybody wants to break in with anything, you go right ahead.
Like do you realize that your earliest convenience, if you have an interesting thought on confidence,
just be very confident that your idea will be funnier than ours.
Well, it's interesting because my confidence level is basically zero.
I'm like the anti-confidence and I mean, I'm sure all of you guys are pretty well aware of that at this point.
I'm depressed and I want to kill myself.
Like that's me.
That's my confidence level, like negative seven.
But why, Tom?
Where does that stem from?
You know, I don't know.
I wish I knew.
I think about it constantly.
And the reason I wanted to be on this episode, because I wanted to get enlightened by your brilliant knowledge of how to not be me.
I mean, here's the interesting thing about that.
I always growing up thought I was a pretty uncharismatic person and a pretty, pretty shy guy.
And the time when I really mixed that up was after like I broke up with my college girlfriend,
as I've talked about it at great length before, and then I went to Japan and it was just a great time
and I had a lot of fun and like I forcefully broke myself out of my shell.
And during that time and afterward, like I did a lot of research about like the pickup community,
which is just how I like channeled my energy and like learned about, I don't know, I learned about a life.
I learned a lot about life, a lot about socialization, just a lot of things,
just through this vehicle that forced me to like go out and explore things,
because the only way to do this shit is to actually leave your house and fucking mix it up and see what happens.
And like, and that is like, when I stopped doing that, when I was just like home,
a couple years later after I finished my schooling, more or less,
and was just like at home, had no money, couldn't go out, couldn't like do anything,
that all diminished, that all diminished greatly.
But what it finally has taken the turn around the corner, and I'm seeing the light at the end of the tunnel here,
of this whole journey, is like becoming, I guess, an independent content creator at this point,
and just like finding something that I really enjoy doing that seems like it's going to work out long term probably.
And just the sense of joy that gives me every day, knowing that I'm on a path that will emancipate me
from my corporate slavehood and slavery, I guess is the correct noun there, for you grammar folks out there.
And yeah, like I...
Enough.
My confidence, I feel like the majority of my confidence comes from...
Wait, I'm finishing my point, I'm finishing my last point.
Okay, last sentence.
It was a funny...
Last sentence.
Okay, okay, make your funny joke, okay.
No, no, whatever.
I didn't realize you were cutting in for a goof.
I was cutting in to say my bit, but if you really have to finish then...
No, finish, go, please.
Do it.
Well, I was going to start a story.
I was going to start my little confidence story.
Your story is more interesting than Nate.
Just have the confidence to tell Nate to shut the fuck up and hit just a railroad.
One of us has to, let's be real.
Okay, fine.
Okay, yes, hippo.
Go ahead with yours, I don't feel anymore.
I have, like, confidence for me has always been like a problem.
Like, I was a little shy boy, I never really could talk to anyone.
But I've had, like, small victories here and there in kind of pointless things that
don't really match to everyone or anyone, but are, like, relatable.
And one of those was, like, I always used to look at my feet when I walked home from
school, and then I heard or realized that only losers do that.
You got to look up, because everyone else is always looking up when I look up from my,
looking at my shoes.
So I'm walking home and then I decide, okay, I don't want to look at people.
So I'm just going to do the opposite.
I'm going to look up at the clouds.
And I really like that.
It's very strange and, like, people like, why is that guy looking up?
But it's really nice and much nicer to look at than, you know, even looking to.
I fucking do that too, and it also gives me confidence.
And for me it was because, sorry.
I usually look at the ground when I walk and identify money.
So there we go.
Hey, there you go.
I actually do that because fucking the Megatocchio comic, the web comic Megatocchio, there was
a part, there was some real edgy dialogue at one point where there's this one, like,
goth girl character, and she was, like, walking on telephone wires.
And she was saying, like, someone was, like, aren't you afraid somebody's going to see
you?
And she was, like, oh, most people don't have the courage to look up or something like
that.
And, like, I was, like, whoa, deep.
So I started, like, always looking up, because I had always looked at the ground when I
walked.
So I started looking up and, like, somehow just, like, seeing more of the world.
And, like, it gives you more confidence specifically because the main reason I do look down is that
I'm always worried I'm going to fucking trip over myself and eat shit.
So I'm always kind of, like, watching where I walk.
But when you're, like, deliberately not watching where you're walking, you're, like, yeah,
I'm fucking incapable of walking, dude.
I'm a fucking badass, like.
Huge comment.
Yeah, that was, like, phase one of, like, my learning to walk cool.
And then later I decided, you know what, I am going to look forward like a normal person
and I'm not going to look away first.
So whenever anybody glances at me, they always look away.
And I was, like, I was doing that for a very long time.
I was, like, yeah, yeah, I own this sight line, this horizon.
This is mine.
Get out, you know.
You really figured out how to walk from the ground up, which inspired the legendary
Foo Fighters song, Walk, based on Hippocrates' legendary walk performance.
I like that song.
I like it, too.
Okay.
There we go.
How confident of you.
Yeah.
I just wanted to sort of quickly address what Tom said about, like, the confidence in
not figuring out, like, he lacks confidence.
Like, I feel like I lack confidence, too, most of the time, though.
Sometimes I feel like I have just enough of it just to function.
But, like, what I figured out, these are just my musings.
They're probably not the truths of the world.
That should be the tagline of this podcast, by the way.
Yeah, that's true.
And a lot of our comment wars that happened just clarified that at the start of each episode.
Yeah, it's just like, when you see other people be successful and do things, like, you only
see what, you know, they want you to see, because most of the people usually just share
what they're good at, what they're confident about, how they succeed in life.
But when you're with you, you spend most of the time with yourself.
You get to see all your flaws, all your struggles, all your down times, all your down moments.
Imagine spending exact amount of time with another person.
Wouldn't you start hating that person, just like seeing them in their worst as well as
their best?
They're always there.
I totally agree.
Are you saying something about the person you live with, Mage, here?
Is this a universal human constant?
No, no, no, I love him.
I'm with you, Mage.
I'm totally with you on this.
He's a great cash potato.
I love him.
This is why after Radcon, I hate all of you, because we spent too much time together.
I mean, kind of.
Distance makes the heart grow fond of my dude.
There's no doubt about it.
Yeah, and it's just like, you live with yourself and you end up, like, hating yourself as just
something you kind of need to get over or just acknowledge.
Well, I mean...
Also, just quickly, because you strive for success, a lot of people do strive for success,
and they feel like, you know, they're not doing enough, they're not getting enough, and
something I've decided to think about, like, just accepted, like, not everyone is meant
to have their name in the books, you know?
Like, a lot of thousands of hundreds, millions, billions of people die, and no one will ever
remember them.
Even the people who fought in the wars and stuff, they're just statistic at best.
And maybe I'm not meant to make the books, you know, and that's fine.
You know, I'm just going to make the most of what I can with my little life that I have,
and then when it's done, it's done.
You see, it's interesting that you bring that up, because I think about that all the time.
And this kind of back and forth I have mentally is that, is that, is that, because there's
people who vouch for either side, like some people say that you have to make these big
goals and never stop growing, that's the most important thing.
Then there are other people who say, like, carve out your niche that you're comfortable
with and, like, you know, do small things every time.
And I'm always like, which is correct?
Well, like, as our...
Okay, here's my objective utilitarian standard.
The one that's correct.
I'll be coming.
The one that's correct is the one that maximizes human development.
Like, we need to calculate that and find it out, which generally works.
We know that everything is, like, that's fine as your opinion, but it's not objectively
better because, as we all know, this universe is going to die one day and none of it matters.
Well, yeah.
So, like, from that perspective, like, human growth is nice.
We don't need myelism and utilitarianism in the same podcast.
Wait, but what...
I did want to make a point just about Tom's sentiment.
Like, I just wanted to...
The reason I was, like, telling my story was because, like, there was a time in my life
when I, like, really tried to gain that kind of, like, raw confidence that I described before.
And then, like, I kind of, like, gave up on that for a while due to circumstances, but whatever.
And, like, and the stuff that I have now is, like, the second type, just based on, like, skill
and just doing repetitive actions that, like, like, when I'm hanging out with Digi,
like, who's the one who calls the pizza man, because the other's too much of a coward,
to speak to another man on the phone?
Definitely, Nate.
It's me.
You know?
Like, this is the skill of the choir.
I am willing to call pizza guy, but if anyone else will do it, then they can do it.
Right.
And also, there's the internet.
Why aren't either of you picking up the phone when the internet is at this point?
What is the value of both of you?
We've had circumstances where we had to, but, like...
What a nightmare.
And then, like, talking to people on phones is, like, the worst.
I used to literally not be able to pick up my phone because it would just get me hard.
Tell that to your dad, who fucking stormed Normandy on D-Day, and fucking...
The funny thing about that is...
Oh, what a nightmare.
Calling someone for order in a fucking pizza.
You fucking millennials.
You make me goddamn sick to my stomach.
I gotta say, one of the things that's made me more confident over time is just, like,
growing older and more impatient, because, like...
Oh, yeah, that's a thing.
I hate talking on the phone a whole lot, but one day, I got so sick of me texting people
and having to wait for their response that I was like,
I'm just gonna call people every time, and now I do, and it just is so much fucking easier.
Like, I don't care.
Like, I kind of approach it with, like, an aggression.
I think that's another way to be confident, actually, is to approach things...
Like, if you don't...
If it's not something you feel confident in, just approach it like you're fighting.
Dude, that rule of aggression is exactly what George Costanza uses.
He's like, when he's at his desk in Seinfeld, he's like,
if you look annoyed, people assume you're busy.
It's exactly the same law being applied here.
I got used to talking to people on phone out of necessity,
because I had to make a lot of phone calls to the doctor and stuff, so...
See, that's the thing. Necessity.
Like, it's just an action you had to do, and it probably increased, you know?
Well, yeah, I mean, a lot of the time, things like talking to people on the phone isn't necessary,
and for things like pieces, it's kind of better to use the internet,
because there's less chance that they can hear something wrong.
It is a good skill to have.
We live in a world where...
It is definitely a good skill to have, and I can do it fine, you know?
I just...
When a bank card, like, fucking fails, or something where it's hard to get in touch with them
via their stupid internet crap, I will go and call the phone.
I was like, alright, you better be fucking...
You're fucking better at that than I am, then,
because I still haven't called the IRS, and I've owed them $1,000 for like four months now.
I don't know why, and I just need to call them, and there's too much of a pain,
but like, I have gotten a lot better at it just by taking the approach of like,
get as angry as possible that you have to do this,
and that will be what, like, just do it in rage.
You know?
Like, if I have to call my mom because she won't fucking answer my texts,
then I'm just gonna be like, motherfucker, I'm calling!
You know, like, I always take that approach, I'm calling!
It's funny you mentioned that, because I just finished watching the Netflix Punisher series,
and there's a line in there, he's just like...
This guy, he's with, is like, afraid to go do this, like, fucking mission with him,
and he says a line that pisses him off, then he gets all upset and marches out,
and then he just is like, huh, pissed off, beats fear every time.
Yeah, just like in Terminator 3, when I learned that.
But it was interesting what you said, Digi, about how like, old people,
like, get more of this like, angry confidence you're saying,
and I think it's because the older you get, the more time that you've spent alive on this planet,
I think the more entitled you get to being alive,
and you know, the more attached you get to this corporeal existence.
You know what I mean?
I kind of know what you mean, but I don't know if you're saying it the right way.
Like, they're more entitled to the amount of knowledge that they've amassed over their long lifespan.
It's like, think about a baby.
So people who need to learn things are just like more like, oh god, why didn't you know that already?
A baby is the ultimate popcorn nihilist, because it spends so little of its time alive,
as opposed to dead, you know what I'm talking about?
Mate, I am not talking, I blame this entirely on patients.
It's a matter of how many times in my life am I going to wait all day?
That's where it comes from for me.
It's like, how many times in my life am I going to wait on somebody to text me?
When that happens for the fifth time, I can't fucking take it anymore.
Like, that's where the aggression comes from for me.
It really sucks for me because I have really good patients.
That does suck for you, that's true.
My patients get slimmer and slimmer like every day.
And I mean, if I decide to be patient about something, I can be.
Like, if I know my girlfriend's like, she works till five, right?
And it's like, okay, she probably won't be home till six.
I can very patiently like not go to eat until she gets home.
Like, that's fine.
Because I know the schedule.
I know when I'm expecting the person to be there.
It's different if it's like, I can't get a hold.
Like, let's say you guys were trying to message me to come on the podcast today.
Like, you'll notice that, Nate, you've probably seen me do this.
Like, I'm always the first to say, just call that motherfucker.
Like, if Ben's late, I'll be like, call him.
Because it just resolves it so much faster.
Like, you can sit there and text him.
Absolutely, absolutely.
You can wait.
You can be like, oh, I don't want to bother him.
No, bother him.
Like, that'll get him on the fucking podcast, you know?
So, like, I just, at some point in my life, I have to go like,
how many times am I going to wait for the guy to show up, you know?
I couldn't agree more.
No more times than I have so far.
I am, I have a kind of tangential, it's not really,
it's just a different topic.
Emails.
I have learned to say fuck it when it comes to emails,
especially, like, important ones.
Because it's always like, for me, it was always like, oh,
they said hi, and then my name.
Should I say hi as well, or should I mix it up and say hey?
Or is that too informal?
You know, you think about, like, all the wrong things,
like, you might, like, offend them.
Because you don't really know people who you're emailing.
If they're on Skype, you know them a bit better,
if they're on Discord or whatever.
If they're email, it's just sort of like a little bit more like,
oh, it's still kind of like letters.
Like, I have to say all the best, or, you know,
best wishes at the end, like, I don't know what, fuck it.
Just put it, I don't care what I say.
Like, I don't have to look over it again, send.
And then it's fine, it's always fine if you just send it
before doing any adjustments.
That's true, that's true.
This podcast is really fascinating me because it's making me
realize the way I deal with so many different scenarios.
Because I get a sick, like, perverse joy out of sending,
like, really curt, informal e-mails.
Like, manic style?
Like, people send me, like, hi Conrad Collins or whatever,
then they, like, give, like, a three-paragraph thing
and, like, a signature at the end and it's, like, formatted.
And I'll respond with, like, yeah, that's cool.
Send me the paperwork.
Like, like, literally just one sentence,
like, no introduction or anything,
I'm just like, yeah, sure.
You know, I've literally responded to, like, ad offers
with, like, sure, sounds good.
You know, and it's the funniest thing.
Why not?
Because I don't fucking care.
Exactly.
They want you to advertise for them.
They don't care how you respond to your fucking e-mail.
Of course.
It's really fun.
I don't know.
I guess they're just making the...
I have no problem with, like, talking on the phone
or an e-mail or anything like that.
Mine's always in person.
Because in person, I'm like,
what do I do with this flesh pump that I'm in charge of?
I've realized I'm much better on the internet
than I am as a human being.
Most people are.
That's the stereotype.
True.
But, like, even in live things, like on podcasts
and stuff where I'm, like, basically am a real person,
it's... talking one-on-one is very difficult.
Yeah, like, I still have trouble making eye contact
when I'm talking to people.
I don't do that, like, ever.
It feels really weird.
I never make eye contact.
I think it's weirder to make eye contact.
Unless it's, like, a really intense conversation.
Eye contact is how you stare right into their eyes.
Exactly.
Eye contact is how you establish dominance
and you break their fucking will.
But it needs your powerful gaze.
I was always, like, a really shy boy,
and I was always, like,
I really got to learn how to do all this stuff,
but I was really bad.
I never really tried that hard.
But every sort of thing where it's, like,
you know, most people are like,
oh, yeah, why would you even try that?
Why would you look in someone's eye?
Like, this is just weird.
I think of that as, like, gaining XP
by the longer I look into the eyes of the other person,
it's like I'm gaining XP
and eventually I'll level up
and it won't be a big deal anymore,
even though it's kind of unnecessary.
But it's just like, yeah,
I see all those sort of things like that.
And it's because staring in someone's eyes
was a biological sign of challenge between males,
biologically speaking.
And it still retains
that instinct is biologically coded into us.
To look someone in the eye
indicates that you are, like,
saying that I am your equal.
I am, you know, it expresses confidence
in a sort of challenging way.
So to do that,
you have to, like, sort of face the fire
of contacting this person's personality directly
and saying I will not back down.
And so it's kind of like sparring, you know,
social sparring.
I was taught it's just rude to not make eye contact.
So I tried to make a little bit of eye contact
every now and then, like, to indicate,
yes, I am listening to you, person.
I am paying attention.
That's the way to do it.
Here's a little thing about me.
I'm not sure if you guys have it.
Does anyone has this?
Because I have this, and it's really annoying.
I look at people's mouths when they talk
because if I don't see them talking,
I have trouble hearing them sometimes.
That's really weird.
I think I've experienced that.
I hate, man, fucking watching, like,
videos I do where it's me and some other person,
watching myself as a fucking nightmare
because I never look at them.
I'm always, like, kind of half-glancing at them
and then looking away or looking into space.
You can see on my face that I'm, like,
just preparing to say my next thing
and not solely paying attention to what they're saying.
I fucking hate watching myself on those.
I hate listening to myself.
I've gotten so used to listening to myself
I could never hate that.
No doubt.
I wanted to talk about how I gained confidence,
which it's interesting because how I gained confidence
is something that also happened to Tom,
so it's interesting that I gained it and he didn't,
which was becoming brony famous.
And also, oh, I forgot how it was skipped over.
I actually think I can probably, you can tell, sorry,
but I think I already have an answer
of why it worked for you and not for me.
And I also skipped over this thing
I was going to respond to, something Hippo said,
about being easier to talk to people,
or harder to talk to people offline.
For me, it all depends on if I have an in.
It's very easy for me to talk to people
if there's any one thing that connects us
and if there's not, it's impossible.
If it's just someone in a store or someone around,
even if I really want to say something to them,
I cannot unless they give me an in.
That's why I'm really social at cons,
because I know those people know who I am.
So it's really easy for me to have in-depth conversations
with random people at conventions
as long as there's that in.
But BronyCon 2013 was a huge coming-out-of-the-shell moment
for me, because I'd been someone
who struggled with conversation my whole life
and never really had many friends throughout all the school.
I never really talked to anybody unless they talked to me first.
But going to that convention
and having literally 70 people come up to me
and ask for an autograph,
and then speaking in front of a room of people
totally unscripted, unplanned.
We were up all night.
We'd been kicked out of our hotel.
We were dying, and we get a fucking...
We get standing room only,
with those thunderous applause.
People telling us we did a great job,
and I'm just like, this is as raw as it gets.
If you enjoyed me in my purest unfiltered form,
then I know I can do it.
I know that I can be confident in myself
because I know that even at my lowest level
of being able to put on a panel,
people still had fun at it,
and people still enjoyed my presence.
For the sake of our viewers there
and people looking into the subject,
would you say that it was more of an intellectual understanding
that led you to that,
or was it the visceral experience of having that happen?
The visceral experience, for sure.
Intellectually, I've always known that confidence is...
I know about the pickup artist stuff,
where they just go up to women and talk to them,
and it's like, what the fuck are you talking about?
The cold approach is one of the most challenging things
for any human being to do.
I've never been someone who can walk into other people
and start a conversation,
but so many people walked up to me
and started a conversation at that convention,
and nobody seemed to come away upset.
Nobody talked to me and was like,
that guy's a piece of shit or something.
I definitely have had tons of awkward interactions
at conventions, especially at my first few,
where I was even more awkward,
and people would come up to me and say hi on day three,
and I'm dead tired,
and I have nothing to say,
and they're like, hey Digi, I really like your content,
and I'm like, thanks.
And then they kind of like linger,
and I'm like, okay, bye.
Now I've gotten into where I fucking stormed
through a convention,
all this was me at Crunchy Relaxed Boat,
drunk the whole time,
storming through the halls,
people come up, dude, you're Digi Bro,
and I'm like, yeah, bro,
give him a high five, and I just keep going.
You rock, thanks for subscribing.
You just gotta have that swagger about it.
That's pure confidence right there,
just feeling like people are enjoying my presence,
and I only know that because I'm at this convention,
people are confirming it.
When I'm out and about,
I feel like everyone is disgusted with me,
and I don't belong anywhere I am,
but through going to so many conventions,
I have learned to really get over that a lot.
It used to be a huge problem.
I'd go to Barnes & Noble
in my fucking pajama pants and my fucking robe,
and I would feel like everyone here
is looking at me, and they all hate me,
and they're all disgusted.
I used to always worry when I was on the Manga Isle
that if any anime fans saw me there,
they would think, oh, great,
of course I'd find this guy in the Manga Isle.
This is what represents us anime fans,
and now I go in there and I'm like,
yeah, this is what represents you anime fans.
You're a bunch of fucking losers,
just like me, you fucking assholes.
I belong here.
This is what you should all look like.
So I've had that kind of reversal,
and it's helped a lot, man.
That's why I go out so much.
That's why I go out to eat all the time now.
It's really helped me to get out
and enjoy life a lot more,
to not constantly feel like I'm fucking
don't belong anywhere I am,
which I used to constantly feel.
I think you...
It's weird, because I guess it was because
I wasn't hosting my own panel
at BronyCon when I went,
but every interaction I had was awkward,
and I felt less confident,
because I performed badly in the podcast.
I remember swearing accidentally,
and I was like, oh, shit.
Oh, that was funny.
We all like that.
I guess it was funny,
but I don't remember saying much of stuff.
And then afterwards, people came up to everyone.
I was like, a few people came up to me
and said, cool.
I would say it was very different
between those, because the BronyCon 2013 experience,
no one had known who I was before that.
I was brand new.
I had just taken off.
I had never thought that I would be big.
None of the other famous people knew who I was.
I was just hanging out with Tom,
and he knew a lot of Brony famous people,
so I was following him around
and meeting all these people.
None of them knew who I was.
For me, it was that very individual experience.
It wasn't...
Nobody was coming up to me
because they saw the horseshoe crew.
They were coming up to me because they saw me.
And I think for you, by the time it was BronyCon number three,
and you're just kind of in with the pack,
and there's less of that personal expedition
that would make it like that,
which is unfortunate in a way.
I think you could have had that
if you had been walking around on your own more.
Maybe more people would have come up to just you
and wanted to just be like, oh, you're my favorite guy.
It's just a numbers game.
I feel like if I had been at BronyCon by myself,
it would have forced me...
Because I didn't want to walk around by myself
because all of you were there,
and I was like, I don't know anything about anything,
and I'm going to die.
First time in America.
First time in America as well.
I wanted to stay tethered
to at least one person from the group.
But of course, if I'm with someone else,
there's a reason for me to not go out on my own,
and if I was on my own and somebody talked to me,
it might have been good.
I don't know. It's difficult.
That also contributed.
That was far from my first convention,
and all the cons I'd gone to before,
I went with my older cousin,
and usually hung out with him the whole time,
or hung out with Victor.
That was the first con where Victor and Shade were there,
but they were just kind of tag alongs to me,
and it was really my...
I was the guy leading the pack,
and it's definitely a different feeling
when you're the one making all the decisions.
You're the one saying, hey, let's go to this restaurant.
Hey, let's go here.
That builds the confidence as well,
and if you're always putting yourself...
It's basically alpha.
If you're putting yourself in an alpha position,
it gives you more confidence,
because you kind of see yourself doing it.
You see yourself having made a plan
and executed it, and you go, I can do that.
I don't need to follow my cousin,
who's older than me.
I can do it myself.
So much of this just comes from performing the actions.
Like you said, you perform it,
you recognize in yourself you identify
as someone who can do these things,
and then when a situation comes up in a similar way later on,
you just look back at your experience and say,
I have done this. Maybe you've done it many times.
It all builds up, and you just feel empowered.
There have been times when I've been able
to just walk around in a city by myself
and look at stuff.
That was the first time in college
we had a trip to Florence in Italy,
and it was like we were supposed to go around
and draw stuff in the fucking art galleries and shit.
And in between the sessions...
Please draw on the Mona Lisa.
That would be excellent. Please, thank you.
It's not even fucking there, you idiot.
Oh, no.
But in between, it was like the first time
where it's like a school trip,
but you don't have to stay with the pack
in between stuff like lunchtime.
You can just go, meet here, back here at this time.
I was like, oh, yeah, I can just go.
And I didn't really have any friends in that class
that I wanted to stick around with,
so I just ended up wandering the city streets
and looking at stuff, and I bought a vinyl record,
and it was cool.
And I went into a restaurant
and ordered pasta and sat by myself and ate it,
and I left, and I didn't leave a tip
because fuck that shit.
Hippo, I think you and I view this stuff
in a very similar way, like with the EXP meter kind of thing.
It very much is like, yeah, you're just working
until you level up, and it's less of a problem.
And I definitely try to put myself in situations
where I will have to be confident to succeed.
And the biggest one for me was this fucking year
taking a trip around the country,
and that was a huge leap,
because I was a guy who was afraid to drive.
I would never drive on the interstate for years.
I was so afraid of getting into accidents.
I had no confidence in myself as a driver.
I hated long-distance trips,
and it was only because I was literally forced
to take the drive to Atlanta when me and Ben and Davoo went,
because Victor was supposed to do it,
but he ended up having work.
And because I had to do it,
and I experienced it and realized it was not that bad.
It was a nine-hour drive, which sounds fucking insane,
but I did it, and it was fine.
And I was like, oh, this has totally changed my perspective
on road tripping, on traveling, and everything.
And so I was like, I could do this all the time.
And so I spent two months over the summer
just driving to people's houses and hanging out,
and it really broadened my perspective on the world.
I don't feel constrained to any place anymore.
I don't feel like a guy who lives in a town.
Yeah, because you've done it.
It's part of your world experience now.
I've been all over.
I want to share a story.
Okay, go for it, dude.
Yeah, it's just a quick story about me being a social weenie.
This was seven or so years ago,
so I hope I'm better than that.
But yeah, so back when I was still in college,
there used to be this shop that sell really cool game-related things,
like cards and stuff, and tabletop games and stuff,
and they also sold plushies of whatever was popular.
And it just so happened, they were selling Pokmon plushies,
like Snivy, Tepega, and Oshawa, the fuck Oshawa.
Hey!
Do you say Auschwitz?
Auschwitz is that?
Oshawa.
Well, that's much more disappointing than that.
Oshawa is not the Auschwitz Pokmon.
It can't be Auschwitz, because that's the water type.
It can be a fire type.
Or a poison type.
Anyhoo, anyhoo.
So they were selling those plushies,
and I really wanted to get them.
The problem was that the store was actually really, really small,
and there was a table in the very middle of the store,
and there were always people playing some sort of game there,
and me being the little scaredy-mage I was,
I didn't want to go in, because as soon as you go in,
everyone's immediately going to look up at you,
and I didn't want people looking at me just trying to browse games and stuff.
But I really wanted the plushies.
So I ended up circling that store like several days.
I think on Wednesday, they were always there playing the game,
and I was like, well, I need to go into the store,
but there's always people there playing those darn games.
So I decided, okay, tomorrow, tomorrow, no matter what,
I'm going to go in and get those damn plushies,
and never going to come back if I don't need to.
So I came back the next day, and just so you have it,
he had some sort of meeting or convention,
and the place was fucking packed.
There were so many people.
It's usually like three or four people.
That's kind of good, though.
You can get lost in the crowd that way.
Kind of.
I thought, okay, don't panic.
No one's going to notice you.
Just slip in, get the plushies, pay for them, and slip out.
Nate, you're forgetting the crucial part here, though.
Mage is a girl in a game store.
Oh, no!
No, there were actually a few girls.
I think they were like wise.
Oh, thank God.
Decoys, you're safe.
But yeah, so I walked into the store.
I got the plushies, and I go to the counter,
and lucky me, there's no one attending the counter.
So I had to wait.
I had to stand there and wait until someone goes up.
I don't know who the cashier was, so I had to wait for them.
And while I was waiting, someone noticed me,
and they were like, hey, are you waiting to buy something?
And I'm like, yeah.
And then they yelled loudly, hey, whatever your face is,
there's a customer.
And then everyone looked at me, every single one.
That's the worst possible.
That's right.
Come to sports, you can deal with these.
Right, right, okay.
Well, I got the plushies, though.
That story is so prescient to me,
because, and this is also a part of what I was saying before
about just getting impatient and fed up,
because that exact scenario, aside from the twist ending,
has happened to me so many times growing up,
where there's so many things I wanted to buy and didn't,
just because I felt uncomfortable in the place.
I didn't want to walk over to that side of the store,
because there were too many people over there,
oftentimes playing a game like you described,
or just the shop owner seemed like they wouldn't want me there,
or something like that.
All kinds of shit.
There's so many excuses I came up with like that.
And then at some point, I got so sick of never getting what I wanted.
I was like, I just have to,
I don't even care if they think I'm a fucking mongoloid.
I gotta get the shit I need to get,
because how many times am I going to go through going to,
because I go to stores all the time,
and I feel uncomfortable all the time.
I mean, just like, yeah, that's totally a thing.
When you hit the wall, honestly, this is kind of arbitrary,
because I don't believe in free will and all this stuff.
I don't really think any of us make...
We're slaves to the machinery of our brains.
Who cares about what you're saying?
Here's the point I'm trying to get at.
I'm going to talk about this really cool moment that's happened.
Actually, no, I had a thing about shops.
Fuck this idea that you have to be nice to the shop cashier.
It's impossible, and I've never been able to do it.
I can't say, hello, how are you doing?
I can't say...
Something about me, I guess, they frown.
They just frown at me like I'm supposed to.
They just hate their lives, dude.
I mean, it's not just that.
I've been a cashier, it's the worst.
The person who comes before me says, you know,
they don't say anything, but then the person smiles and says,
hello, how are you doing?
And they say, oh, it's great to see you.
I'm going to give you my life story.
Credit card beat.
And then I come up to them, and they just don't say anything.
I'm like, why don't you say hello to me?
Do I have to do you? Am I scary?
What am I doing wrong?
Fuck you, and I killed them.
The answer is yes.
The same thing happens to me, and the answer is yes, you're scary.
I think that's what it is for me anyway,
because I experienced that, and I'm like,
I just look like I don't want to be here,
and I look like I want to kill them.
It's funny you mention never talking to cashiers,
because one of the things I do sometimes
to try and build confidence is talk to cashiers,
because we have this whole ritual of like,
hey, how are you doing?
Fine, how are you? Good.
That's just how the beginning of the interaction goes.
Sometimes when I'm trying to do something more confident,
I'll deviate from the script and see what happens.
Because I remember I went to the cashier,
and I just bought some drinks or something,
and they're like, hey, how are you doing?
And I'm like, I'm kind of tired.
And they told me what to do, and it turned into a conversation.
We just had a conversation for like five minutes
as they checked me out, and I was like, alright, there you go.
I'm so glad you feel that way,
and I feel the opposite of how most people do,
because when a cashier asks me a follow-up question,
I get excited, because I'm like, oh, human interaction.
And like, most of the people I know complain.
Like, we'll leave the store, and they'll be like,
why the fuck did they ask me so many questions?
And I'm like, no, man, I just want to know someone cares about me.
They've literally been a substitute for a robot arm
that entire day, because they're just grabbing your stuff
and running it across a scanner.
They're just as desperate for an actual,
genuine interaction as you are at that point.
True.
When I went to England, like, I was startled
by how everyone was nice and polite.
Like, I walked into the store one.
This is like the very first times I was with my mom
when we were walking, and we walked into a store
and the cashier, like, we weren't even by the register yet.
We were just browsing around in the cashier.
I was like, hi, hello, welcome to the store.
And I'm like, internally, like, holy shit.
You know what I mean?
Meij, I'm just curious about this.
Was Lithuania part of the Eastern Bloc?
Was it part of the Soviet Union?
Yes, it was.
So was it a communist state under that government,
under that rule?
Do you know?
I'm just curious.
Because it seems to me that communism in general
seems to make it so that every person working
in a communist state isn't working for themselves.
So every customer becomes a burden and an annoyance
as opposed to capitalism when a customer,
that's where the customer's always right thing comes in,
and you have to be nice to them.
Or you want to, because they're the people
who help you make your money.
Lithuanians are rude.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know.
I'm just wondering if that had anything to do with that.
Yeah, they were part of the USSR and stuff,
but not anymore.
Perhaps that's relevant.
But I was going to say about the, oh god, I totally blanked.
God, what the fuck was I going to say?
This is slightly, this is less about confidence.
But do any of you guys sort of slowly start to view
like store clerks and stuff as like characters in your,
like people, or are you develop like some kind of weird connection,
like unspoken connection to them?
Oh, okay, hold on.
I'm quickly sorry to cut you off.
That reminds me quickly.
So like when I go shopping for food and stuff,
actually me and my boyfriend, we use the self-checkout thing.
However, it's like a female voice.
And like I named her Clara because like, you know,
you clear the items, Clara.
Okay, okay.
And like when she, when she's like...
This is the depressing version of what I was talking about.
Clara is great because she never judges me
when I buy Doritos and marshmallows and shit.
No, no, no, we have fun though.
Like me and my boyfriend, like when she says like,
please pick up items, me and my boyfriend go like,
no, shut up, Clara.
Everyone in this call, aside from Mage,
will have been to the Wawa by my house.
Yes.
I went there like every day, often several times a day.
So like I knew, like I don't know any of them,
but I know everyone who works there.
Like I know who, like I've seen them enough times.
Right.
And like because I would usually go at like four in the morning,
there's this one, this sweet little old black lady
who worked there every fucking morning.
Like she worked the graveyard.
She was like the night shift manager, I think.
And like, so when I went to check out, it was always her.
And like she obviously recognizes me, you know,
like we don't have many interactions,
but like if I suddenly trim my whole fucking beard off
after a year of growing it, she might be like,
oh, you lost the beard.
And I'll be like, yeah, you know, and I, I don't know.
Even though our interactions were that limited,
I felt like really connected to her to the point
that I was like really sad to leave that Wawa.
Like that was the one thing I felt like I was going to miss.
In Virginia Beach is like, man, all these Wawa guys
are not going to know why.
I thought about saying something.
I thought about saying one of them like, hey,
I'm going to be moving soon.
Like you won't see me anymore.
Just in case one of them wonders.
You should have done that.
That would have been like a total huge XP boost for that.
It would have been like a whole other level.
I didn't have the confidence to think that they would know
who I was enough to give a fuck.
That'd be so funny, dude.
Wouldn't that be hilarious if you went in there like,
I just want to let you know, like I'm moving.
I've always loved you.
And they're going to be like, who the fuck are you?
Dearest beloved Wawa.
Because the way my mind works is that if,
for instance, one of them had stopped showing up one day,
I would assume they were dead.
So I just don't want them to think I'm dead.
I don't blame you, dude.
I would probably like think the same things in your situation.
To me, I can't really understand that.
Because I don't think I've seen, like I think of cashiers
as like procedurally generated.
I don't think I've seen a cashier twice.
Like they just are.
I mean, really?
Because I don't go into the same stores at any time.
I went into that Wawa literally every day for like six years.
So like that's why it took that much before I started recognizing them like consistently.
So sometimes when the Clara's being a bitch, we have like...
Clara's being a bitch.
She doesn't say that we need extra help.
And like this one time, I think three or four days in a row,
she was being a bitch.
So we needed extra help.
And it was always the same lady.
And it was like in the dead of night.
Like, I don't know, 2 to 3 a.m.
And it was, it's kind of fun though, like seeing her like come up.
And it's like, oh, hey, it's you guys again.
And like, yeah, we're having troubles.
Clara's being a bitch.
Dude, there's this girl at my Kroger and my local Kroger
that we have kind of, me and my girlfriend have developed a kind of narrative about.
And it was fascinating.
Because one day, I've seen this girl a couple times.
We were there checking out, just buying some food or whatever.
And like, we needed her to come over and scan something.
And like, she did it for us.
And I was like, oh, thanks.
No response.
She like does her like scanning thing.
And I'm like, yeah, sorry for that.
You know, make you do this.
No response.
Not a word.
And like, she turns to face me.
She does not make eye contact, of course.
And like, the unbelievable, exaggerated, cartoonish like frown upon her face.
The biggest I've ever seen in my life.
Just making me imagine.
You know, like that Homestuck panel I linked to my Twitter earlier today?
Like the incredibly massive frowns.
It looked exactly like that.
I have never seen a frown of that magnitude.
And like, I was like, oh my God, what, what is her story?
What brought her to this lowly point in her life?
To be like, just so desperate and sad.
I mean, there's nothing wrong with her working at Kroger.
But like the sadness as she fucking performs her mundane tasks here at her job.
Just incredibly depressing.
But then, we happened to go back the other day and we saw her again.
And she helped us in that exact same way.
Only this time, she was like a thousand times more like Cheery.
And I'm like, did she maybe did her boyfriend break up with her on that day?
Like, what's the story here?
Did she get evicted on that day?
What is the narrative here?
I'm really dying to know.
She has binary emotions.
Yeah, happy and sad.
By the way though, I did want to share another little anecdote here.
And it's just that people think that I'm really confident.
But I really want to stick to this thing that people are confident at what they do a lot.
And like I argue and yell about stuff on the internet a lot.
So I'm pretty good at that.
But at my job, at my much discussed programming job, when I'm walking up to the coffee maker,
and I see people standing around there who I don't know specifically.
And even if I do know them, it is quite common to me do a 360 degree turn and walk the fuck away.
Just turn back right to face them again, you moron.
That's the joke, you fool.
I anticipated that and I've outsmarted you again.
Yeah, like I will literally do an about face and just like walk and pretend that I never wanted that coffee anyway.
And no thank you, sir.
I've got other things to do.
Oh, I've been there.
Just to avoid like having to make conversation with these people that I have no interest in.
And also, I'm always worried at my job that I'm like not doing good enough, that I'm not meeting the expectation.
Which is completely different from like my YouTube style work.
Where I know I'm on top of things, I care, I give a shit, I'm interested in doing it.
As opposed to that job where I don't give a fuck and want to get away ideally with as little work as possible.
And you know, make everybody happy and whatnot, but I just want to do my work and get the fuck out of there.
So I can come home and do this shit, you know?
I have a thing that I'm not sure whether people also feel this way.
So I'll be interested to know if you guys have felt this way.
I, especially like in school when it's like, you know, encouragement to get involved.
I hate it when I'm shy and I'm trying to think, okay, I've got to, I've got to psych myself up to do this thing.
Or maybe I should put my hand up or maybe I should do this thing.
And then somebody notices or assumes that I'm having trouble and they sort of slyly like create an opportunity for me.
And then I suddenly don't want to do it because they've just sort of like, you know, so what about you?
What do you think? And I'm like, I was, I was, I was thinking like that 10 minutes of how I should, like I want to do it.
I want to be the guy who does the, the confident thing. I don't need your help.
And now I don't, I don't know, sort of like a, like a nagging mother thing sort of like now that you've told me to do something.
I'm not going to know exactly how you feel.
Yep.
I appreciate it, especially like on this podcast when it used to happen.
But a lot of the time it's just sort of like, you know, it gets me flustered because I wasn't thinking, I wasn't expecting that.
And I was trying to think when to come in.
It's just like when they assume that you have something to say and you don't actually.
And then they, you know, pause and draw attention to you.
And I'm like, no.
That's when you can meme though. That's when your meme potential is at its peak.
You got to be ready to spring a choice meme that you've been cultivating.
You got to, you got to work on that.
That's what it's counting on you for.
Atom, were you making a point there?
Were you trying to say something?
I've been trying to like sneak in a point for some time.
So I guess I got, I got two things.
First, I wanted to go back and say like, why I think did you was able to cultivate his confidence?
Oh, yes.
I think, I think it goes back to what you were saying a little bit too Nate about how.
Was it the fact that in your ship, he was the top and you were the bottom?
Was that the issue for you?
I'm just wondering.
No, I think I was always the bottom.
He was bottom.
I think that's actually true.
He was always bottom for some reason.
Maybe it was a cognitive dissonance for you of not identifying as a top.
I guess so.
It shattered yourself perception.
Okay, I'm sorry, please.
No, I think the reason that that didn't give me the confidence that it gave Digi is because it goes back to what you were saying earlier about how you,
gain confidence by becoming financially and like critically successful at something you wanted to do.
And Digi did too.
I never wanted to do YouTube.
It's something I just fell into.
Oh, right.
That's right.
I was succeeding at a facade as opposed to something I actually wanted to do.
That's how I feel about my job, like my corporate job.
I don't care and it doesn't give me any confidence to do that.
That always felt like a job to me and the thing that I've wanted to do all my life, I've never been able to do or succeed at.
I hear where you're coming from, dude.
That's a good point.
It's interesting because I don't know how to segue into this nicely, but I'm just going to go for it is that being part of the PCP definitely hurts my confidence.
What?
How is that possible?
We've talked about that a lot.
It gives you a measurable structure, like a social structure and I'm at the bottom of that.
I make the least amount of money.
I have the least amount of fans at this point in terms of people who actually care about my contributions.
So it gives you a measuring stick and it gives you a very concrete surrounding of people.
I'm not making that much money.
But you do have a lot of subs though, so that's something.
That's nice.
You've got the views, Mage.
You've got the views.
That's a big channel too.
Mage technically is way less subs than Tom, right?
Tom has got like 56k or something.
Mage has like 55k or 56k or something.
It's those animation things.
Well, that's interesting.
That is definitely an interesting point.
I see where it comes from.
I think it's funny though.
That's why our stickers are linked.
We're both the bot.
You've got more...
Well, I was going to say you've got more money in subs than Munchy, but he's like 16, so it's probably not a huge confidence boost.
He's in a different category.
He's in the kiddie PCP pool at the moment.
Munchy's the weenie hut juniors of the kids.
Exactly.
He's got more subs than money than like DeVue and Hippo.
Well, maybe not more money than Hippo, but I don't know.
Well, I don't know.
We don't actually discuss like our finances really or anything.
I don't need to bring that out.
I think it's interesting that you focus on those things as opposed to...
I mean, you also are the...
I think the real problem is that you are the unhappiest in the PCP, more so than the actual stats.
But why is he the...
If Tom was making money and was able to do what he wanted, like he'd probably be happier.
If he was able to do what he wanted and make money, I think the problem...
Because it wasn't always the case that Tom was making the least money and had the least subs.
Like that was not the case when the horseshoe crew was a thing, certainly.
Right.
He was the second biggest of us, but it wasn't doing something he wanted to do, you know?
That's the issue.
Yeah, it's more...
I think it's more a problem of like...
Like if I had all these subs and all this money and I was like, man, I fucking hate YouTube,
then you probably wouldn't be as like, you know...
Like as readily going like, oh man, I wish I was like, had the confidence Digi has, like, you know...
Yeah.
I mean, you've got a guy, for example...
You've got a guy like Jesse, for example, who like has said many times his great frustrations with YouTube
and his hatred of the platform.
But like, he's a man who was already someone who would beat up like a 15-year-old in the movie theater.
So like, he's...
He already had his shit, you know, worked out on this front.
And also with Jesse, it's just that I feel like all of us are kind of so in awe of his talent.
Like regardless of whether he's successful, we would still kind of look up to him, you know?
In some ways, absolutely.
Like for me, despite the fact that I'm more successful than him,
like I will always view him as a better content creator than me, because I just think he's better, you know?
Like, so, you know, even if I'm the person who seems like, oh, obviously he's the enviable one,
he's got all the money and all the fans, like to me, I still like envy the talent that Jesse has.
Well, you know, like I...
In no way mean to like diminish your experience or your opinions on this at all, Tom.
But like, I very much felt like when I restarted Best Guy Ever,
I don't know if the PCP actually...
That happened like a little bit later, I think, that we made the PCP.
But like, doing that, obviously, was very difficult for me.
Like, I knew that I kind of needed to do it if I wanted to like go on and make content.
And like, I remember, I think about this sometimes, I was really keeping in mind Digi's phrase of like,
man, when you've got 2,000 subs, you're doing something very right.
That stuck with me over the years, for some reason, I don't know why.
But in any case, like, I...
Oh, just real quick.
If you want to cut in, yeah.
Yeah, to talk about like, why I got so much confidence so early doing this,
is because I was failing at this for seven fucking years.
Right, right.
You know, like, and that's the part I think a lot of people forget,
because like, I didn't start as a YouTuber, I started as an anime blogger,
and my anime blogger was, my anime blog was never popular.
Like, not even among the standards of anime blogs, at a time when that was the thing you could succeed at.
You know, like, and a big part of that is because I was fucking, you know,
I started it when I was 15, like, I was young as fuck doing a lot of this.
I have matured greatly as a writer, but like, all that time I was taking it just seriously,
like, I was still, like, the amount of failure that someone who's like 26 feels
when they've been doing it for two years and they haven't had any success,
I still felt that way when I was 17 and not having any success.
Obviously there's a magnitude of difference if you're older and you see younger people doing it,
that affects it as well, you know, that also can hurt your confidence even more.
But like, there was a seven-year period where I thought no one will ever read my shit
because it's too weird.
Like, I don't write mainstream enough stuff, I don't approach things in a mainstream enough way
that people will ever watch my content.
And so for me, and I've said this before, like, I literally got 200 views on my first Brony video
and that was enough to make me like, this is the future.
Like, 200 views was greater than I'd ever had on anything, you know?
Yeah, that's great.
So like, so me, 200 views was like this insane amount and now people look at that like it's literally nothing.
People are like, oh, if you got less, but people look at like 1,000 views like it's nothing
and I'm like, nah dude, like 2,000 views is better than the whole first seven years of my writing career, you know?
That's a fucking full gigantic auditorium or something, you know, if you think about it in those terms.
Yeah, exactly.
It's a fucking lot of people and like, so for me, when I saw 200, I went like, oh, this is the future.
Like, imagine if I could get 1,000, oh my god.
Like, and I didn't realize how hard it was to actually like make money through ad revenue.
Like, I think that a lot of smaller channels who I thought were making money off of it weren't like,
and then I later learned like, oh, you got to be a lot bigger than I thought to like for this to be profitable.
But luckily, I, you know, caught a windfall.
Like, right at the moment that it was a good idea to be on YouTube is when I got on YouTube.
So it's like very lucky, but, you know, for me, it was just such a huge confidence boost to have even a modicum of success after all the failure I'd had that also helped me.
That's an interesting point.
With regards to like comparing yourself to other members of the procrastinators, like, I understand, like, there's elements of every procrastinator that I envy, you know, like, I definitely...
Davoo's like mind brain, and then Munchy's like think brain.
He's like, well, two completely different types of like weird brain that I wish I had like the ability to replicate.
I know exactly what you mean.
I envy Munchy's radicalism.
Like, his ability to just fucking go for it.
Like, I can't do that.
I can't just scream in public, and I wish I could because I had hired that, you know?
Yeah.
So it's like, I know, it's weird because I have like struggled with like comparing myself to people who are better or younger and better or younger and the same in skill level and feeling like, oh, man, fuck.
But like, I think I've gotten over it at some point, and I don't know how, and I don't know why.
I mean, it's really important to be proportional and like keep perspective about these things because like, you know, it'd be considering we live in this world where we have contact with like literally every person on like Twitter.
Like, you can actually talk to like, I don't know, fucking Donald Trump, President of America, if you want to.
You can message the man.
Like, you can compare yourself in terms of like a 15 year old kid, a 15 year old like 90 pound soaking wet baby weakling could like say like, oh, man, what the fuck am I doing?
Arnold's up there at like a 300 pound golden god.
What the fuck am I doing down here when it's like, well, of course you're not that guy.
You haven't put in like 20 years.
There's only one of that guy in the fucking world, too.
Yeah.
I lately I've been I've been getting over that in a big way like because I used to bother me back when I was like 23 that like a lot of the rappers I liked were like my age or younger and I was like, how can they be so much more talented than me.
And then like right now, I've gotten really into post Malone because he's got a couple of really great songs and he's also on the H3 podcast all the time because he's good friends with Ethan and I'm fucking obsessed with that podcast right now.
But post Malone's 21.
He's got like three mega hits now.
He's 21 now.
Wow.
Currently 21.
Got three mega big hits.
He's a, you know, he's a mainstream success.
I hear him on the fucking radio every day.
So because I listened to the radio for some reason.
And I watch him on H3 podcast and I get really excited because he's like, he seems like a really interesting, smart dude.
And I can look at him and say, okay, the amount of shit he did by the time he was 21, like he just was doing better than me.
Like he was putting on, like he was part of a metal band that was doing shows back in, he was in high school.
He was putting together internet videos.
He had like people he worked with.
He just put more effort into his craft than I did by the time he was 21.
And like he's the kind of guy who like, yeah, there's obviously a huge element of luck.
Like he just happened to get like a song retweeted by the right people and he had the right connections and he blew up on SoundCloud.
And like there's a lot of luck involved, but that dude was better at what he was doing by the time he's 21 because he was smarter at 21 than I was.
Like I listened to this dude talk and I go, I couldn't have said that when I was fucking 21.
Like I'm just not as good as, like, and that's, that's normal.
Like of course in this insanely vast world, there's going to be a hell of a lot of people who were better at 21 than you were.
Just be proud of how much better you were than most of the other 21.
To make that like an obtainable or like a, like a useful maxim here.
It's like, I think it's important for anybody, once you start to reflect on how people are doing better than you, that's an important moment of self reflection.
And you can let that overwhelm you if you're a weak coward who's not willing to like face that reality down and accept it.
But the thing to realize is that even if you're like a fucking 55 year old man and you're just realizing this shit now,
you cannot change the past, but what you can do is take a real hard look at where you are in life right now
and start to make mature, rational decisions about how to get where you want to go using the tools at your disposal.
It's pointless to get upset at people who are younger than you and who have done better and been more successful, whatever.
All you can do is recognize that you have control over things happening right now.
And I know this is just an intellectual point that won't matter to a lot of people and it's useless.
I don't know whether it has to be like a rational decision.
You can just say, fuck it, I'll just try something and see what happens.
At that point...
Well, that's part of what I'm saying.
Either or. You can either like plan it out or you can go for it and at that age, you know...
Well, if your decision is just to try something instead of trying nothing, that's what I'm saying.
That's what I'm saying, it's a much better use.
Obviously, starting stuff later is harder to get good and stuff.
If you're a kid and you learn a skill, you'll be great at that skill by the age of 12 if you start at like 5.
Because that's when your baby muscles are growing and flexing and you're made of plasticine or whatever.
It's like how I learned English.
Yeah.
So it is harder to do it.
But it's either that or give up, you know?
Try or give up, that's all you can do.
I don't like motivational quotes because I feel like they...
Do or do not.
Just like that one.
Well, yeah.
I'm trying not to sound like a motivational speaker when I'm saying, just do it, haha, Nike.
You don't want to sound like a motivational speaker while you're speaking about motivation.
There's that phrase and then also like fake it.
It's mostly because like motivational speakers generally I feel like never actually say anything.
Like I made a video about this a while ago, a vlog, where it feels like it's like a temporary boost.
Where it makes people feel like they might be able to do something and then 10 minutes later they're like, I can't do it.
Because they didn't get any actual information on what to do.
And that's their responsibility.
Which is just like when you hit a boost in Mario Kart.
You get ahead for a little bit and you feel more confident, but then you get red-shelled and like there's no fucking point anymore.
Like you are dead.
Yeah, but you just got to keep driving.
You got to keep trying to find an explanation.
Try to hit every boost.
Sometimes some people just need that bit of a push to reach the goal, you know?
Sometimes, not always.
I personally don't like general speeches like on Twitter or whatever people post.
Hey, remember, whoever you are, you're beautiful today inside and out or something like that.
I hate that shit so much.
It devalues the times when you actually are, you know?
Yeah, also I know that I'm not pretty today.
Like maybe I just woke up, I haven't called in here and I'm still like, you know, groggy and like I have bags under my eyes.
Well, actually I have dark circles under my eyes rather than bags when I'm tired.
Yeah, I feel gross and there's this like Twitter post just like, hey, remember, you're beautiful.
And I'm just like very like cynical, I think that's the word.
I'm just like, no, I'm not.
Fuck off.
I don't need this shit in the morning.
I understand why like some people, some people might need that because they never feel good about themselves.
But like, if you're somebody who's capable of recognizing the difference, like, yeah, you shouldn't feel like, it makes it more powerful when you have put an effort to like shit on yourself when you have it.
Like there's a, I've known a lot of fat people who have like a really huge, Boogie is a good example of this.
He talked about this in the HD podcast and he's very against the healthy at any size thing.
Boogie the YouTuber.
He's about to get a gastric bypass so that he can finally like, yes, I believe he already did.
I think that podcast is pretty old.
So yeah, that's already happened.
I think if people talk to him, losing weight.
Well, in any case, he was talking about how like, you know, like if you are just confident in yourself while you're fat, then like how will you, you need to lose that weight.
You're literally not healthy at any size.
And like, once you have done it, like, you get to feel that confidence.
Like, if I look like shit when I wake up and I look at myself and I go, I'm beautiful, then like, I'm just going to look like shit all day, I guess.
This is why, you know, this is actually putting in the effort to make myself look good will give me the confidence.
This is why nobody can hate Boogie.
Boogie, everyone loves Boogie and it's for exactly these reasons.
But yes, please mage, go on.
Like, so I was having like a major health issues earlier in the year and a little bit before.
During that time, I lost quite a bit of weight due to the health issues.
And honestly, like after after I recovered and had the surgery and whatever, like, I felt like, like I haven't felt in such a long time.
I haven't depressed.
I felt more confident.
I felt like getting up and doing things like, holy shit, I got so super like,
I got, I got shit done.
Great.
That's fantastic.
Do you feel more confident?
Yeah.
Having done all that?
Yeah, I definitely like, like now it's coming back because I think it's seasonal depression.
But like during the summer and early autumn and stuff and right, right.
And like late spring after the surgery, like I haven't felt that good in such a long time.
And honestly, I don't want to attribute it all to like losing the weight.
Something definitely changed.
Like, like noticeably so.
And I, I, I love it.
It's worth taking note of.
It is not, it is not bullshit to say that like health matters to one state of mind, you know, and fitness in general.
Yeah, I thought I was like just like, I was so surprised how much of a difference it made.
Like I always, you know, I was always told that, you know, you know, it's healthier.
And I'm like, yeah, you know, it's healthier.
And like I would like to do something about it.
And I try and whatever.
Like I never, never realized how much of an impact it actually does.
Just remember everybody, remember everybody, fat shaming saves lives.
Keep it up everybody.
We've got a duty to go up there.
Not even just being fat, but like fucking just being healthy is a huge confidence boost because you feel like you can fucking do things.
Like I am a shit eater.
Like I, I don't eat very big proportions, which is why I don't really gain weight.
But the stuff I eat is not good for me.
And like, there's a lot, there's way too many days that I'm just sitting around bloated and I can't do anything.
Because I, I go out and I eat so, like I eat a pound of grease and then I just fucking, I sit on the couch and like I just like four hours of I don't really want to work my fucking stomach hurts.
Look at the fucking Ubermanch.
Casey Neistat is a, is a monster man of fitness and work.
Literally working fucking constantly cause all he drinks is fruit shakes and he runs four miles a day.
Yes, ma'am.
I was talking quickly about like confidence and feeling better and whatnot.
Like there's also like a, I noted a significant difference.
A lot of people have noted like if your surroundings are less cluttered and organized and clean.
Oh yeah.
It has an effect on your mood.
Also sunshine, sunshine helps, which is why.
You're right.
This is all real.
Currently, me and my girlfriend have been experiencing the same like manic depression.
Like, like even though we're both incredibly happy with each other, like because we kind of let our house get messy at the same rate and it's, there's no fucking daylight anymore because we live in the north and it's, you know, winter.
So like the sun goes down at fucking four.
And like, we've both just been kind of like, like very like low energy kind of rut and like just smoking pot all the time to deal with it.
Cause like, yeah, it's, it's hard to keep up with your environment.
It's hard when you don't have sun.
It's hard to like want to go do things when you don't have that fuck.
Don't live here.
Don't live in the north.
Don't live where there's no sun because you will never want to go out because it's dark by the time you have time.
Move somewhere sunny.
The sun is an okay substitution.
Like what I'm doing personally to deal with this.
Oh yeah, I don't sit in the car.
I never, I never fucking turn off the light bulb.
Even when it's daytime, it's always going to be like yellow in my room because of the light bulb.
I wish it was a brighter light bulb, honestly.
But yeah, like I never turn it off because I need the brightness otherwise I'm going to be sad.
I mean, the human beings need like, like why does one gain muscle?
It's a response to pressure.
Your body is coping with this issue.
The body needs challenges to like maintain itself.
And we live, we are lucky enough to live in a time when so much of our lives are made incredibly easy.
And as a result, like our bodies fucking degenerate and fall by the wayside.
And we ignore them.
We don't give a shit about them because like we're not, we haven't cut up to the lifestyle yet.
We're not fully adapted to deal with this shit yet.
So, you know, everybody, you got to take responsibility for your own shit.
Manage your body.
Manage your life.
You got to do this shit.
Wouldn't it be changing the name of this podcast to Bro Science the Podcast by the way?
That's all this podcast is these days.
I swear to God.
You're not wrong.
Incidentally team, we've been going for quite a while here.
And I got a bunch of questions lined up.
Oh, how good.
I trolled through the whole fucking discord fandom.
Incredible.
But if you want to fucking get your questions read on the show, become a patron of like anything.
You get access to the discord.
They ask questions.
We read mostly those occasionally a Twitter one.
What's the Twitter thing Nate?
What's the hashtag?
Oh, it is hashtag askpcp of course.
Yeah.
All right.
I got a couple of these are like burn throughs and a couple of them are real interesting.
So first let's go to burner.
Yeah, I want to know I feel like none of us might have something to say about this or maybe one will.
Me cool man asks how important is clothing slash fashion in your life?
Hmm.
Incredibly so.
Not at all.
Yeah.
Okay.
If somebody is like you got to understand is that I stay at home or I go work in an abandoned
building where no one's around.
So like I have no reason to even try.
Like I shower very rarely.
I don't comb my hair.
I don't do shit because no one's there.
No one's there to even know that I smell like a fucking like pile of shit.
So it's just like why if why even bother when I go.
If the climate allowed it, I would wear just shorts and nothing else.
Shorts are comfy and easy to wear.
But seriously, I love them.
They're great.
When I go outside of the house, I try to look presentable.
Like nothing people would stare at basically.
You know, I don't want to be scared at what I'm holding.
She had no thought, gentlemen.
But when I'm inside, I just I just I just wrap myself in my Cheeto scented robe and just sit around in whatever.
Well, it's good in winter because like you can wear a coat and it doesn't really matter
what you're wearing underneath.
Yeah.
Okay.
But in summer, you're like, oh, what t-shirt do I wear?
This is important.
Now people can see it.
They can see my body.
I like t-shirts because they're comfortable, but I also don't like going outside in just
a t-shirt because now people can see my arms.
Is that bad?
I don't like people.
It's it's just a it's just a weird thing.
Like once I once I, you know, do it like like I'm I used to never like not wearing socks
like people would go out in summer to the park and they would have sandals on or something.
And I, you know, I wore socks with sandals because I didn't.
I didn't like the idea of not wearing that.
I didn't like the idea of not wearing socks.
And oh, yeah, here's the thing.
For a long time, for a long time, I only had this one pair of brown shoes and brown shoes
do not look good with shorts.
I wore these to BronyCon and they looked terrible and I looked like a fucking silly boy wearing
my brown shoes with my shorts and get some get some trainers, please.
Everybody should get at least a pair of trainers so that they don't have brown shoes with shorts.
I wear socks with sandals all the time.
And I think it's anybody who says you shouldn't is just like full of shit.
It's like the whole pineapple thing.
It's just a meme.
It's a meme.
Kind of.
My metric for how successful what I'm dressed as is does my girlfriend think I'm hot because
that's the only thing that matters.
I don't have to impress anybody else.
I hate to tell you, but she'll think you're hot no matter what you look like.
That is absolutely true.
That's not a good standard to use.
That's why I just dressed in whatever I want.
Why else would I dress up?
Who am I trying to impress other than...
First society.
First society at large.
Who in society needs to be impressed with me?
There's a real thing where people like to look nice because it just makes them feel good.
They feel happy and confident.
That's a thing.
I feel better.
I like to exert my dominance on the world.
I enjoy the feeling that when we go to a fancy restaurant, like a really nice one,
when I'm in pajama pants, I feel like a god.
The reason everyone else in there is dressed nice is that they had to dress nice to get
that money.
You had to probably work with it.
I guess.
That's about simplification, I think.
The kind of job you would have to work to make a lot of money and be able to afford this
food would probably require you to dress nice.
Most jobs that pay well, you have to dress nice.
I'm making the kind of money that lets me eat in this restaurant and I show up in fucking
pajamas because I also made that money wearing fucking pajamas.
That makes me feel like a fucking god.
I get your point.
I like the idea of not caring about ... because I don't really care about what I wear when
I go out.
I've had history of caring a lot and I've just gotten rid of that slowly.
If I like the way I feel when I go outside, then that's all I need.
I see myself as a slightly understated version of a SoundCloud rapper.
When you see famous people, especially musicians, when they're out in public, they're always
fucking ... they got face tattoos and weird dreads and all kinds of shit.
It's just because they're like, yeah, they made their money looking that way.
That's the culture they're representing and that's what people resonate with.
That's what they're going to look like all the time.
I hear what you're saying.
You do, in your profession here, have the freedom to look like whatever you want.
You could dress and shoot and tie like our hero, Report of the Week, if you chose to.
I could, but I just wouldn't ... I don't think it would match my content, really.
If you say so.
I think the style I have is very much about embracing this personal self-image.
I'm a guy who wears pajamas and sunglasses and doors and an anime shirt.
That's what I'm comfortable with and I think I look okay in it and I think it matches the
style that I'm doing.
If I was in a suit, it would be fucking weird.
Well, that's what they said about Report of the Week and then he became the greatest
YouTuber of all time.
I don't know who that is.
Yeah, but he also has the slip-back hair and he's like ...
No, I've never heard of him.
He's the wholesome boy.
He's the wholesome suit man.
Yeah, he's the fast food reviewer who wears the suit and tie and you know ...
You really don't know this guy?
No.
I'm shocked.
He did a review of a store-bought water.
If H3 reviews him or has him on his show, then I'll know who he is.
Just look at this picture.
Let's just take a second here and look at this picture I'm looking at right now.
There.
Okay.
This guy doesn't look familiar at all to you?
He's weird looking.
Yes, he is.
Yes, he is, but he's a legend.
All right.
Well, whatever.
Okay, we don't need to dwell on this anymore.
All right.
Next question.
I like this one from Giffy.
He asks, do you think we should tell children that Santa is real or ripped the Band-Aid off
early and follow-up from anti-matter tape?
Do you think we should tell Christians that God is real or ripped off the Band-Aid early?
Oh, that's good.
Those are both very similar.
That's a very smart-
Red pill is both of them from Burris.
They're both bullshitting.
You think so?
I actually-
I don't think I can lie to my kids.
I feel differently.
Here's what I think.
I can definitely lie to my kids.
I think what I want to teach my kids is Santa's not real, but they should play along.
Yeah, that's definitely what you should do.
I want to teach them that they are smarter than all the other kids in their class and
they should pretend to be dumb so they can fit in and so they can manipulate people.
I just think this is just a cycle of just horrible mental damage we do in the world
as we treat kids with these special soft gloves.
We pull our punches.
We tell them the world's full of magic and great things and then you hit a certain age
and you're like, actually, no.
Everything sucks and now you're a part of it.
You're entirely right.
There are a couple of interesting facts, too.
The facts of the matter are children are not fully rational beings the way that adults are.
They cannot be expected to behave as logical operators the way that we at least expect adults to.
Of course not.
You need to teach the kids but you don't need to teach them the wrong things.
Keep in mind that kids consume a lot of media nowadays and when Christmas rolls around they're going to see a lot of Santa Clauses everywhere.
So I'm gonna like
Can I have a random side here for a second where they're not gonna believe you over the media?
So I mean how many kids how many kids like believe in like I feel like you would learn
It's not real really fucking young now with the internet, you know like maybe how many kids are out there who don't figure it out
Immediately well, I mean this is a question of like intent should you lie to your kids is like the real right here's that my problem with that
question, okay, is that I have no
idea why anyone cares because I don't see the ramifications of like oh, no my world is fucking falling up
No kid has ever done that. I that's I know kid has become depressed
Unless they're actually autistic in which case you should just keep telling them that I quite clearly remember a moment where like my mom
Accidentally dropped the bomb that the Easter Bunny wasn't real and then after that I extrapolate and realize like holy shit
None of this shit's fucking what the fuck like I remember that happening to me
But like looking back that happened in reverse for me because I remember my mom actually told me about this at one point when I was like
Oh, yeah about the story of how I found out Santa wasn't real
I asked her about it and I grilled her for a little bitch like you know what it's not real
And I was just like okay
And then the part that I remember that was funny is that she said she's like she distinctly remember
I walked away a couple steps and I turned around and looked her again
And I'm just like a bunny and she's like no, it's not really there
That's good
I I just can't like I don't see
To me it's like I want my kids to know as much shit as possible as fast as possible and like I don't see the point
Think that's important. I don't see the point. I do
Information for four years and then being like oh by the way, I was lying about that and they just like oh, okay
Why why'd you tell me it was real in the first place like I don't know
I I I'd want my kids to know a lot of stuff, but Santa is like I like Christmas. It's a joy
It's like it's like a it's it's a happy time and it's like it's cool
Like I remember this one memory of of coming down
To see the the presents under the tree and there was like fake snow and it wasn't there the day before and I was like
Oh my god, it snowed indoors. I had no idea what I couldn't tell I was just like oh
This this throws a wrench into my idea that maybe it's not real because this actual snow hit the thing about Santa that that
Erks me I on its face
I actually don't see a lot of problem with the idea of like telling kids about like a fake man who brings them presents
I think that's a cute story and I generally like it
But what I do not like is the way that it is a tool to control the behavior of children
By telling them that only if they're good then they'll get presents and then we'll get cola that I do not like I really
Dislike that just the idea of like I love Christmas, and I'm the biggest atheist you'll ever fucking meet
I'm an anti-theist. I hate God. I will kill that man when I meet him like it's I love the Christmas tree
I love the community spirit. I love being around my family
I love just the warm vibes and cinnamon floating through the air and an apple cider and an eggnog and family holy shit
It's I love my family a lot, but we're all very cynical about Christmas. Dude. We need to do a fucking Christmas PCP
Oh, that's a great idea. That's a great idea. I do. I do. I'm signing up right now live on the podcast
I don't mean on Christmas. I'm gonna do it next week. I'm gonna be at work on Christmas
So really just like I was I work every holiday for no extra pay no extra, but what do you?
Get away with no extra pay
If you saw the conditions of the building that I worked in you'd be like, how is it
I mean I thought you're supposed to get paid a half
I mean don't you work under the table or something isn't that no no
He just he'd the guy owns half the town
So if I tried to do anything he would just like crush me so there's nothing I can do about it well Merry Christmas everyone
I'm literally working for mr. Scrooge
You'll be tiny Tim
Wasting away
Okay, let me just say a huge
About the sand issue I have yet to fully grapple with the the moral implications of teaching my children about like
The control over them that Santa has but I think that it's a very cute story about a man bringing presents to children all over the world
And I love Christmas in general and the tree and all that shit
I felt like it is why Chiaro asks a question from age. What are your art ambitions? What are you doing with the draw pencil and stuff?
Like this is a really heavy question the question is what's what's your end-game page? What's your end game?
A pencil one day, and I do it. Oh, there's like I like this and I continue okay
That's that's great man. Why you because you can't fail. It's impossible to fail. Hmm. Whatever you do is just good
That's the opposite of me. I just want to be like have a cult following
I want to have tons of money and like be able to live by myself and not be fucked with all this like
Employment shit, so there's there's a high. There's a high skill ceiling for that first high skilled floor. I should say
Well, that's nice mage aren't you doing a comic at the moment
Oh wait guys, I have a great question
Are great a great pity question from our people on the on the on the Twitter here the ask PCP folks
All right
You're all gonna like this I think at XG upload asks would you kill someone if you could get away with it?
And I think I know the answer everyone's going to yes, the answer is yes
Without a doubt without a doubt. There are plenty of people
Like I am not generally in favor of killing I don't think it's anything I could do under normal circumstances
But there's like a couple of people who if I could kill them I didn't get away with it
I'd fucking I I feel like I wouldn't be able to forgive myself for murdering
So what about like a mass murder like if you got like a death note situation?
And you know about like some mass murderer from like the African, you know rape gang or whatever
I mean, it's a nice idea to think I wouldn't be affected by having killed
But but I
Likely would even if it was a mass murder, I'd be like, oh, I'm just as bad as him like it
I'll head of personal spite
I'm also imagining them doing it with a box cutter for some reason, okay, so that would be more traumatic. I
Think I mean, yeah, I wouldn't
Let them suffer through life like the rest
Well, maybe you could kill like your best friend, you know as an act of mercy that that's a thing to do
You know spare Tom from this cruel embrace of life, you know
If I was gonna kill anybody I finally have the confidence to kill myself
All right
Anti-matter tape this is actually kind of a difficult question because I want to take it as an absolute
Anti-matter tape asks what's the one thing you've always wanted to be able to do yet?
You've never pursued playing piano drawing making good videos, etc
And I want to emphasize never pursued like I can't say drawing because I've tried to draw
My answer is building stuff
Like I've always had like I always kind of look up to like people who are like
Like carpenters and stuff like that like people who could just are good with their hands because I'm not at all
And like in the rare instances where I have to like build a piece of furniture
I feel like oh man, I'm doing like what I'm supposed to do
It's like a man, you know like the hyper masculine idea that like we are here to build shit and like
I'm generally not handy and I wish I was but I've never really pursued it because it takes time to learn
I sort of feel this way about car stuff
Like I like people I respect people a lot who like know about car stuff because it's knowledge
That is very useful in our current modern lives like cars are like the biggest thing we depend on that are incredibly complicated
Machines and if you just at least understand the fundamentals of how they work like what a radiator is how the engine works the various belts and stuff
Then you can like not panic like I do when something goes wrong and you're like afraid to look into it
And so you would put it off for months
Yeah, that's me
Real quick to follow up on what I said like what makes me the most jealous is fucking when Casey Neistat
When he like wants to make some new prop or something and he just fucking builds it immediately
Like all those tools and he's got all this equipment and he just he just knows how to build things and like his one of his mottos
It's like there's two kinds of people
In this world people who make things with their hands of people who don't and I'm like
Does editing videos count probably not probably not
Okay, well anybody else. Well, I'm trying to think cuz like
Never pursued is like I pursued like in some small way everything I want to get good at
Like I've tried I've tried cooking before I've tried I've tried learning languages before I don't know
Like I don't think of one thing. I have an answer for this. Okay, I don't I don't know if did she's gonna say it doesn't count
But my my answer is getting good at math. I I love the idea of math
I think it's very like a useful skill, but I'm just so fucking retarded
Like like I can't math math is a fucking math is a foreign language from a country
I don't I've never heard the name of to me. It's you know, I just I would if I could I
Just I want to I want to so bad because it's like the coolest shit ever. Yeah, but I just I'm too dumb too dumb
Go to watch the number file. He's right. Okay, so like I'm not sure if it counts never pursuing
Um
But like singing like oh back in school when we were required to have like song lessons and stuff like that
I I
There was also like a little choir thingy that people could join
like usually the teacher would pick and like I
Asked if I could be on it and my teacher said my voice wasn't good enough and that's the end of that
Well, got him
Does that
You know, mage, I actually feel quite similarly
It's just the only difference. I think here is that like I mean I have done some saying but like I really want to like
Become maybe sort of professional level at singing like I'd really like to spend some serious time
Improving the way I say
Like I'm living in this torment because like I sometimes have these really wonderful awesome vivid dreams
Where I can actually sing and my son like and it's not just like I can't sing my voice is like so fucking beautiful that I
Belt out like a melody and like I literally stop wars with my voice
That's just me across
Exactly, yeah
What?
Macross or Macross. It's like that's the plot is that a girl like stops alien wars with her singing
Oh, yeah, I would a badass
It's great
Dude imagine if that was Gabe with his guitar instead in Macross that would be Macross 7 where it's a guy with the guitar
Listen to my song
21st century digital
Song second side and I just I just want to sing like sometimes when I was younger
I would just like sing to myself when no one knows that I'm doing a very quiet voice
So no one would hear me sing
I don't I don't have an ear for it. I'm not good at singing. It can be learned though. It can be learned with hard work generally
Yeah, I just I'm actually quite inspired
Recently my girlfriend was telling me that like Markiplier recently like spent some serious time
Improving his voice to become a good singer and for what I hear he has dramatically improved and this gives me great confidence
Well, you're already had a great he had a good he has a good speaking voice and his singing voice was good
But he has certainly he has worked on and honed it into a great voice
Like if you already have a great like speaking voice and you speak every day that you I mean Nate's getting good at singing is not gonna
Nate has all of those things. So that's what he's exactly so I can have confidence. I can't improve in a serious way
Like the name is already
The best one of the better singers I even like you're better than me and I consider myself a competent singer
I got a new song coming up here
But I you can you can look forward to that definitely
Because some people are like talented voice actors, but they can't sing for shit
Yeah, Tara strong for example, you know what I mean? What I mean is the a lot of a lot of the singing is just being able to say
Things really loud because that's what singing is and if you're not good at talking loud
It's gonna be more difficult to sing
I was more like thinking of like like I'm not even saying words
I'm just like making melody with my voice. So I'm just like, you know, one
One sound but I change it up to make a melody out of it
Like being able to do that that would be like the best thing
I it does anyone want to comment on this because there's actually someone posted a
Question on the Twitter. That's kind of a just an update to the other
I had I had one one of my
A question to this question. No, no, this was to a previous one. So yeah, please finish your point
And then I just want to add this. Well, I thought of what I wanted to do but never pursued is
Start a band. Yeah
Because playing guitar is fucking easy
But the baton family band is renowned across the land. I mean, I mean for their breakout album Hilary
Yeah, yeah, that was that was fun
but like like starting a band is is is so much more like
Social and you have to go out and play in clubs and what and you look at people and
My president a bit of that go up and talk to people and say, hey, I'm gonna
I'm you want to join my band like it's the sort of thing you can only really do in school
It's like I missed the boat and then I try I didn't even think about trying to do it outside
I was just like, I guess I'll just learn it's time. I I am so amazed that any band ever
Like that they do he's cuz like yeah, yeah
I you know
I was a I was friends with a ton of musicians in high school and like which they had a fucking band like there was this band called
The Friday ears and it was because they practiced on Friday
It was my friend Marcus on bass Brandon Tolentino on guitar
This guy named Arne on lead guitar and this dude named
I don't remember the fucking drummers name
I barely met him Herbert and like and they wanted me to sing for them
I sang for them at one show
But like even though they were all talented except for Marcus he couldn't play play bass for shit
But like both the guitarists were really good and the drummer was as good as he needed to be and I am a competent singer
And I had written like lyrics. I wrote songs for these guys
They just wouldn't fucking practice or get organized at all like there was the breaker no
Desire to organize themselves even though we like literally had songs that were good
Like just from like coming up with like riffs and me being like that's a good riff
Play that one for eight bars this riff for eight bars and I'll sing this over it and that'll be a song and they just wouldn't like
Do that and it's like this is impossible. I don't know how
Cannot it's tragic to me that you cannot inspire in people like a will to drive or create or like you just you got to have that
Taken like all the talent was there
There all it would have taken is people sitting down for like two hours
I I once met a man
I once met a man named Ben saint and as much as I tried to tell he could be cool
He could be cool if he just applied himself
He just wouldn't listen and and here we are everybody
Part of that is like I kind of want to to learn all the instruments myself, but recording is
Recording it's tough man. It's tough
Recording is the worst the the dump dump dump clack like what do you call the drums the percussion? Oh, oh, yeah
Yeah, metronome like like even with having that and you know doing all the things
I set it up like hundreds of times not hundreds of times
But like I try over and over again and it never I can never play in time with recordings of myself
And it always pisses me off and all I really need to do is just go to YouTube and type in drum beats
So I that I have that sure, but I just I just don't care. Yeah, that's a thing
I wanted I want drummers. I want a drummer to be there to do the thing
All right, Nate. What was that follow up cuz I got a great question. I want to get to oh, yeah
It's really just this is a follow-up to the would you kill someone if you could get away with it
Someone else right before that asked the question turbo cow 420
Smoking me for God, um, would you would you murder someone to get ahead in life? And the answer is?
Probably it depends on the person. Yeah, I mean if it's a again the same guy who I'd kill if there were no consequences
Yeah, also there were benefits the doubly watch out misty cronexia. He's coming for you
Here's a great fucking question
From Cyprus should we poison children to calm them down or poison ourselves to not give a fuck
But you mean like with drugs I assume things. Yeah, that's what I'm assuming which I thought this was okay
As a question as someone who recently started taking Adderall recreationally
I will say I will not give my kids Adderall unless they like need it like unless they are
Unfunctional without it because and why why is it because it has a really fucking strong effect on you
Like you really changes the way you think and act and in a way that kids can't like make that decision
Like they can't tell like if that's helpful for them or not like even for me like the amount of I don't know man
It really changes the way you think and like and act and like
If my kids just kind of being a brat like a little bit then I don't I think it's like way
Overbored to like give them drugs like my feta beans
You know, I hear what you're saying my buddy who I who I took some classes with I remember one time
Like he just busted out like a couple pills of Adderall
But like what he would do is he would just he would break them open and you see like the little tiny beads in the pills
He would just take like like three of those of like the tiny ones and there's like a hundred within the pill
I mean
There's a lot of ways that it could be beneficial and like if if my kids seemed like they needed it like I would yeah
Give it to him, but like I think that's a doctor's right
And I know like some of my friends like are horribly depressed as adults because they feel like like
Like Adderall like ruined their life like because they were like too good as kids
And now they're like made them into like a different person like my friend Mike was like a total spaz as a kid
So they put him on Adderall and like it made him extremely antisocial
He like he never he just never really knew how to communicate with people and he was so docile
And he felt like he wasn't true to himself and he feels like he wasted the last like ten years of his life
Yeah, that sucks man like being someone else who he's not and like that's just a lot to fucking do to a kid
Flippantly like the way that our society does it and I'm like and again if I can just poison myself tonight give a fuck
Then yeah, hell yeah, I'll take that route. I love poisoning myself
I want to be like I want to be the picture of Dorian Gray for my kid like like he stays perfect
I just get uglier, you know, like oh, I like that. That's cool. That's cool. What a cool thought
My solution is just not be around kids cuz fuck them. Yeah, we need to send them all to a concentration camp
Well, they can grow up to perfect automations
I'm just realizing this is a question that only me and Nate have probably thought about because we're the only ones with like
Plans to have kids in the oh, yeah
Fucking insane, you know, I mean, I don't know. I like the idea of having kids
You're all crazy. I'm so Vincent and Charlotte are going to transform the world everybody. What are they gonna?
They're going to be a twin president. It's gonna transform your world
I don't know if you're planning to have
Vincent and Charlotte with Michelle, but have you run those names by her and like gotten approval on I have got the contract
Signed in blood that these will be the names of our twins that are will be enforced
That's like brought up on an early date like by the way
I want to have kids anytime soon, but it will be a deal breaker if I can't name them
If you do not produce me twin god twins, it will be that'll be the end for you
They have to literally be like Daenerys Targaryen and and Jamie Lannister exactly
That's what we're going for and they better be blonde even though neither of us are blind Jamie Lannister even though I said
They are oh Daenerys. Okay. Okay. I'm thinking of Cersei and Jamie. That's what came to mind for me
That also works, but like I was thinking of Danny and her older brother, but like
They're like an insanely beautiful dragonborn children. Okay. I'm with you on that
We have we have discussed it briefly and I think we it was just a meme because it is a meme for the most part not entirely a meme
But I mean, she doesn't care then. Yeah, I mean if they don't care then why not why not, you know
I
Here's one that I don't even know if anybody I have an answer to but maybe someone magically does one spar asks
Are there any cool dead malls near any of you?
There's a couple of cool live malls around me. Yeah, if you go down if you look down the chute
There's a dead Darth Maul
Because it was
Are there any cool dead malls near you like places that used to have open stores and people going in and out eating dippin dots ice cream of
The future in the yeah, but now they're just empty sad graveyards of corporate history had to bring that up because a
Munchy was on a dippin dots tear like asking us a ton of questions about dippin dots and
And everybody joined in on that and that was where I cut off the questions
It's funny to mention that because at the creationist museum that is my favorite thing in the world
That is near where I live in Cincinnati. It's in Kentucky across the border
But there there were many like
Abandoned like the the creations museum is still alive and kicking but the dip and dot stands are abandoned and decrepit
Which is like I don't know is that like indicative like that's why the future
No, listen to this
Here's the metaphor the future has died at the creationist museum and only the ancient archaic past
Knowledge lives on it's interesting that you say that because I went to Six Flags
Like a couple months ago and all the dippin dots places today. We're all abandoned to oh my god
I mean open and thriving our future is over. There is no future for us
A few years ago, but like yeah, maybe me sister and her boyfriend at the time we were trying to go see a movie
But we were late at this one mall. So we quickly went to this other mall
That I haven't been to before and it was like partially dead because there's only like a few stores open
Most of them were already closed even though it wasn't closing time. They seem like permanently closed
No one else was around and we went to the like the movies and like oh shit
We're late is the movie still going and they're like we can run the movie for you if you want
Well, so you're like whoa weird. That's interesting though deep level dead
Well, I have one spar another chance because we didn't have that much of an answer to that
But this is our last question by the way, I think I've only got two more though
Okay, we'll do two more. We'll do one sparse the next question PCP
If any of you were given the opportunity to go back in time and prevent your real identities from being revealed to the internet
Essentially re-establishing your anonymity. Would you take it? That is fascinating?
Yes, that's a fascinating question because I actually did that when I like made best guy ever
Yeah, I'm in a sense. So I feel like yeah, but like now I'm like past it
And it doesn't matter to me like like just how people will like bring up like oh look at Digi Brony
MLP over here like no one can say like look at keg standard over here
It's like who are you talking about what they can't I don't understand
I'm lucky
But that's your but that's your your your your corporate identity mage
The lethal or mage brand is far-reaching and well-respected. I'm just saying like
Oh, I see what you mean. That's why I was laughing a little bit
May just be all of us. I mean, it's true
Tom you go I was gonna say I don't know if anyone I mean I guess some people know my identity
But I don't like throw it out there or anything. So I'm not too worried about it
Yeah, this is something I've been thinking about a lot lately because my identity is way too out there
You share a lot of information. You know, we all do but you have too much
it's gotten weird and
But like I can't imagine like I can't just imagine preventing my identity from being revealed because that would just mean like changing the whole nature
Like just yeah, who you are is to do this is to like reveal yourself
I have I have given a lot of consideration to
Disappearing and there are ways to do that and all you really got to do is ghost right or not
You know like just all you got to do is kill you
What was I mean?
I was just the idea for like the girl pony that he wanted to write for which is honestly like I have sheep over is that's like
Which yeah, I mean, I love sheep over new video today everybody fuck. Yeah, I was good
But it's it's it's not as hard as I think people would imagine and I've kind of done this before
I've made like blogs under different names and just like run it to a different audience and not told anybody it was me
Because I didn't want just because I didn't want my identity tied to it not even out of like any kind of fear
I just wanted people to interpret the text differently. Like I didn't want them to think of it as something I wrote
Yeah, remove the baggage. Yeah
I think anonymity is is a I really appreciate the theory behind 4chan like that's why I love 4chan still
Yeah, I'm fortunately like the theory doesn't like is in practice like not really that effective
It draws out the like people are gonna cluster who want to say things that they cannot say in public
So you get that too. I have come to realize in recent times that I don't really like being famous
I don't really like having my as much of myself out there as I do and I hope that in the future
When my YouTube thing kind of dwindles that I can just go straight for other people and and and get rich behind the scenes
That would be beautiful. I don't know how serious that's nice
I crave attention like a dying thirsty man craves water
And I will I think I'll continue to do this shit as long as I live now
But perhaps when I get you know bigger I might decide that I don't like it and I don't like all the attention
But for now I'm still going strong personally has has any but have any of you ever had like this weird thought of imagining like
30 years in our future where we're gonna have all these like 60 and 70 year old vloggers. Yeah, I thought of that
I think people are gonna change media will be the same at all. I agree
I don't think YouTube is gonna survive like five more years. We're gonna have some weird paradigm
I feel like that's gonna be a thing that still exists in some weird way like yeah, man. That's gonna be fucking odd
All right one last easy question squid Miku asks. What's your favorite strawberry thing minus strawberry milk?
I just had a delicious from P. F. Chang's. I got myself a
It was like a what was it called like a Vietnamese volcano cake
Which is just like a chocolate cake with some strawberries on top and other fruits and like came with vanilla ice cream
And like what I love about strawberries the most is eating like other things
Especially like a chocolate cake with a strawberry in it. Just like other fruit of the strawberry. It is
Divinely delectable like that meme where you see like the kaon meme of like the girl stealing the strawberry from Mio's cake
And she like breaks into tears. That's me if anyone takes my fucking strawberry. It is the most delicious part. It is fantastic
So that that's my vote. That's my vote
I like strawberry jam the most
I
Like in jam strawberry jam doughnuts and sometimes on toast. I don't know. I like strawberry
I don't have strawberry stuff that much
I want to clarify that like strawberry looks like the only strawberry thing I like because I always grape and blueberry if there's an option
Like but why does strawberry have to be just because it's not as delicious as a blueberry or grape?
It could still be your favorite strawberry thing like I love strawberry frosted doughnuts as opposed to like those bullshit chocolate frosted
Doughnuts strawberry every time. I love those. They're a niche product. If the blueberry is an option. I always blueberry
Well, all right, Tom and me cheesecake mochi
Hmm. Oh, that sounds good. Machi or mochi
Mochi mochi interesting
Mochi seems like American
Like something Americans would say but I feel like you the proper pronunciate wait, what what is this thing?
Please describe the characteristics of this delicious food. Wait mochi is a Japanese
Yeah, that's what I'm asking it. Is it the round squishy like Japanese food thing. Oh, okay. Okay. I see
It could also be like called a different word, which is like the sweeter version of it
It starts with a D
Dango dango. No, no, no not dango. I
Don't remember right now. It doesn't matter. But yeah, it's like for the westerners
It's usually just called mochi in restaurants and stuff. Okay
What about caramelized salted strawberries? That sounds delicious. I
Want to make that and eat Tom. What's your favorite strawberry thing? I just like strawberry milkshakes
Oh, we did we went to a sushi
The sushi was made of Pokemon
All right, oh my god. Yeah, we're done
That's for that extra important question. Did you really ran it on a positive strong note there?
Just I just want to talk about your strawberry milk
Okay, I'll have a one word answer. All right. Okay. Good point everybody
Please go on over to patreon.com slash the procrastinators new bonus episode is out right now
It is about Inuyasha versus Charlie Brown. We settle settle the debate
We settle the debate in long last there's that and eight other bonus PCPs
We can pledge $5 to the patreon immediately accessible to you and all your buddies
There we've also got merch we got red bubble merch
You got PCB logos and artwork and stuff you can get that on t-shirts and other types of things
Just go to the red bubble link in the description. Yeah, that shit yet. I am seeing almost every day people are buying more shit
Holy shit. Yeah, so you're getting good company people
Pictures of you wearing it. Oh, yeah
Great idea. I'd love to see like how people use the stickers send
Anything you have bought from the PCP. Take it. Yeah on Twitter quickly
Did you we need to eventually have a contest of some sort? Oh, yeah, so right PCP merch. Oh, that's a great idea
Mage yeah quickly
I just want to say this like keep like pay attention to the stickers
You'll see that some of them are facing in some directions and some of them are pointing to some directions
I had this idea of buying all the stickers. I'm arranging them and like
Making a line that like everyone's pointing or like facing at someone's and it's what are they pointing to?
Where does it all lead? What's the narrative? What's the meta narrative behind these? Wow fascinating?
Like like if oh if oh he placed a little Tom and Mage one to point to the power button on the on the PC
I thought that was how helpful how helpful
Yeah
Adorable, I love it. I want to I want to see people use the stickers. I know and yeah send us questions
Send us pictures. We will retweet them people. You'll be famous on the internet
also
Follow us on our Twitter for all the updates and whatnot at TP crass nators on the Twitter
And of course you're gonna want to be subbed to the channel in general for all the various content that comes out on the PCP
But you already know that fam. You're already a loyal subscriber. I am sure so I think that's ever
Listing this on Google player
Which you can do by searching for it
Procrastinators two words copyright and it's there all the episodes
I'm so glad you're here to remind us about that time because I legitimately just don't remember because I don't think about it
But it is I'm not trying to downplay I really have
These ads in the middle of the episode as well like you know your right podcast does that's we should do it like
We need some sponsorships
than any podcast that I listen to what are we gonna be sponsored by Casper mattresses that's what I'm
Literally have been using one for years. They need to sponsor us. I love
And are you serious as I've been listening to biggest problem and I do keep mentioning them
I literally
Before we go I know this is like totally like not something we should even ask on the pause
It's not but what was taking it out of the box as cool as they hyped it up on this problem
It's just that the box is so small and
Because you can't you literally could not get it back in there. It's like back right right so like it's uh
It's not something that you can read you just like solve the one of the mysteries of my life for the past like
Patrons I can send you that video
I need to know
I actually had a patreon goal of buying that I remember that
Right now I'm supposed to be working right now
I'm doing nothing
Myself I'm sucking
I've got a deadline don't want to
You