Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
First one back from Radcon, boys!
I am the best guy ever, and we're joined by Mr. Munchy.
Give me the chocolate.
Ben Saint is here.
Yes, Nate. Mr. Munchy is Munchy's father's name.
No, he has an unrelated name. Munchy is, you know, and Hippocrit is here as well.
I'm a nice guy to everyone, but myself.
And a special guest, Mr. Double Munchy, Munchy's father.
Hello everyone, it's me, Mr. Munchy. This is Double Munchy.
Munchy, I supplied the chocolate. That's why my son is so fast, because I have the bat chocolate right before me.
I am into forest feeding. That's my soul cake. No penetration, no any sex-only chocolate.
Well, there he is. Thanks for joining us, Double Munchy.
Let's give him a big round of applause.
Thanks for being here. Thanks for stopping by.
Alright, enough retardation. What's the topic here? Define it. What's going on? Tell us.
Alright, here you go, everybody. The topic today is why being nice sucks.
Why being nice is reprehensible behavior that you should not partake in.
But, Nate, what is the word nice mean? Like, does it mean something with army vets? Is it some sort of pension plan?
Is there something to do with these?
Let me tell you that that's right. That's a very nice thing.
Here we go. Nice. Adjective. Nice. An adjective used to describe someone with exceptional skill in a certain area.
The term is never used pejoratively or sarcastically.
And here's the example. My man is real nice on the microphone.
Stop. Stop. That is the worst possible joke.
Here's another one. Nice. This one has a bunch of definitions.
You're going to like this.
I doubt it very much.
I don't know where this, like, talented thing is coming from. I mean, I guess it's sort of...
Number one, talented.
Number two, an interjection similar to saying word when you are in agreement with what someone just said or you approve of what they said.
Wait.
Number three, high on marijuana.
These are the worst fucking jokes.
There's another one that says nice, something you say to the guy you don't want to fuck.
Like, hey, you're a real nice guy, dot, dot, dot, but pregnant pause in my non-pregnant vulva.
Mmm.
Well, this is a literal catastrophe.
This is terrible. There are literally no good definitions of the word nice.
I don't think any of these captured.
Here's my definition of the word nice.
Nice is nice, but it's not great. That's what I think.
You know what? Actually, there is one more. That is pretty accurate.
Here's like a longer definition. This one's like kind of okay.
Used by men to describe all women in an off-handed way when expressing their real opinions will cause them great troubles.
For example, they could be under threat of being slapped or dumped by their girlfriends or getting punched and kicked into a pile by their buddies.
Oh my God, this is terrible. These are all bad.
Punched or kicked into a pile by their buddies.
By their buddy? Like, what?
Hey man, what?
You don't fucking talk that way about a lady.
Roundhouse kick into the pile like the rest of the misogynist.
I've got a bag full of misogynists that I'm gonna stuff you into.
If one of my friends ever comes up to me and starts telling me that I'm not treating my GF enough like a queen, we're gonna have some problems.
He's gonna knock you into a pile.
Okay guys, we have to do it. We have to deviate from our God canon here.
I come up with our own definition.
We cannot do it.
We must. Like, below this is number six.
The plan is all we have.
Number one, skillful.
Number two, high.
Why is high? Why?
Why was high on there a few times?
Why is like weed related to the word nice in any way?
What?
I think we're behind the times guys.
I think we're obsolete.
Number seven, nice. Aesthetically pleasing.
That's like kind of...
That's sort of specific.
Nice is a very vague term.
According to Google search.
Nice is an adjective mean pleasant, agreeable, satisfactory.
Well, there you go.
Maybe we should use Google instead of...
Maybe we should Bing it guys.
Maybe we should Bing it.
We really should be Bing it.
That's the solution here.
What a fucking clusterfuck.
Defining nice has been the greatest clusterfuck in all PCB history.
You know what I'll bet?
I'll bet there's some like...
Child's play. Baby shit.
Trying to find out what the word nice means impossible.
Hey, what's that website that has like...
It's always like how to blank,
and then there'll be a bunch of steps with like really ugly drawings.
Rimezone.org?
No, no, no.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's go on wiki how and look up how to be nice.
Yeah, okay.
Let's see what we got.
I hate this.
This is not nice right now.
I'm gonna give an abbreviator.
Number one, smile.
Number two, acknowledge other people.
Number three, be a good listener.
Number four, be courteous, polite, and helpful.
You're welcome. Thank you.
Let me just amend that to include trustworthy, loyal,
helpful, friendly, courteous, kind,
obedient, cheerful, thrifty, brave, clean, and reverent.
To my scouts.
Number five, practice empathy.
Ooh, I don't know about that one.
I'm gonna have to crush that one.
Look at this picture of Nate,
best guy ever being empathetic.
I'm fucking blind.
I am blind in this situation.
He had to...
He's losing his sight.
He had to develop a new sense.
A new sense to help him navigate the world.
And that sense was empathetic.
What you're actually describing here is Mr. Clean
being nice to me post blindness
because it's the other guy asking for help
or asking if this blind man needs help.
You're not only blind, you're actually like hobbling.
That's not a walking stick.
That is a crutch you're holding.
My legs have been destroyed.
This evolves into monsters 2.0.
We could be not spending all our time on WikiHow.
We spent eight minutes trying to find out
what the word fucking nice means.
We have to get back on track here.
Pleasant.
Pleasant is really what it means.
Allow me to have the floor.
Allow me to have the micro pass.
Wait, wait, wait. First, I just want to say
that I don't think anything in the world bothers me
as much as the drawings on WikiHow.
They're very...
It's worse than that.
The kind of feeling I get
looking at WikiHow.
It's kind of like how when you see furry art
that's really furry and it's like,
it's got that furry feeling about it.
WikiHow is the same.
The dial of Mario's turned to maximum for way past
the legal amount.
The drawings on WikiHow is kind of similar
to my problems with being nice in general.
It's kind of just like basic.
It's kind of boring.
It's kind of uninteresting and surface level.
That leads into my...
I want to have the first word here.
This topic is
vile and embarrassing.
This topic literally
makes me feel like
sad that I live in a world
and I live in a group
where this topic can be seen as
okay to be. I can't believe it's real.
I cannot believe
that we are such a fucking
pretentious, sanctimonious, conceded
group that the topic
why being nice sucks
is treated with any sort of respect
whatsoever. It's embarrassing
and frankly, I think this is the worst topic.
Not like a mom...
Did you not suggest this topic?
This is the worst topic because it just shows
a look into our souls
and how dirty and broken we are.
In times, don't treat the PCP like their idols.
We are broken individuals
but that cannot be resonated
any higher than it is
right now with the topic
why being nice sucks. This proves
that none of us have love or
deserve love and we should be shot
immediately if you see us in the streets.
Any of us.
Was this not your suggestion?
Yeah.
Oh my god.
It was
but only because I hated it so much
that it was on the docket.
Fair enough. Listen
the reason why it is
perfectly reasonable to bring up this
topic is because just like Ben
everyone out there isn't using their brain
properly when they think about the world.
Tell me more.
Being nice is the most
shameful
course of action
that one can take in their life.
Listen, listen.
This is going to come down to the
topic of like nice guys for me.
That's what it boils down to.
Nice girls and anybody. Nice guys
finish last.
It is the most quoted
phrase in human history for a reason
and it's because it's so true.
Everyone understands this on an
instinctual biological level.
Being nice is a mistake
across the board.
Never apologize for who you are.
I have to take my wheelchair.
Never apologize for what you need.
I feel like I'm on
both sides of this because like
I understand that
yeah nice guys finish last
for a reason it's true but
I like being nice.
I like being wholesome and good
and doing good things for people.
Well, no.
The thing is
there's no pressure here.
This can be overdone and I think
that's what nice guys finish last
means because if a nice guy has nothing
but being nice they will not
get very far. They have to be cool as well.
Hold on. I'm sure this
realistically doesn't need to be said because
we can all imagine what Nate's position is.
We already know it in our mind but
obviously you're going to come down hard
on being nice because that's just the kind of guy you are.
So please explain your relationship
with being nice and having warmth
and loving. Let me blackpill everybody
as I do all the time on being nice.
Listen, being nice is a fucking
scheme to make you subservient
to the rest of the world. It is a literal
trick. Don't do it.
Don't fucking do it. Okay, here's the real deal.
Let's say you're a guy and you're
just like a 16-year-old guy
and you want a girlfriend. How do you
get the girlfriend? Yeah,
it makes out for life my brothers but
putting that aside, let's say this is your goal.
You don't get there by
just going around and being pleasant.
You get it by just doing the things
that you want to do in life and then people
gravitate to your animal
like sexuality and bags.
It's already like, the argument
here is not that niceness
is bad. It's just that it is not
a substitute for a real personality.
It is not a personality type in
itself. That's the thing though. It's just a set of
like, you know,
give people the benefit of the doubt.
Don't die on
every single hill of every argument
you have. It's just
like a code of
don't be a dick and it's not a personality
that you can astrive yourself
and if you try to, you will finish last
because that's not real.
I have a personal
history. I definitely have personal issues
when it comes to niceness because my
childhood, I
did the whole being a nice guy thing
and it did not work out and I deeply
resent the people who kind of
implied that that was the right way to go.
If I instead
be a nice boy, you'll get what you want.
Not true.
The idea that
the word nice has been boiled down to
just specifically being a nice guy
is very narrow
but that's fine.
In relation to nice guys
I completely agree that
you shouldn't just be like a nice guy
because that
just makes you a weirdo asshole
but I really don't
like why is being nice
bad exactly?
Why don't you want to be nice and just
live your life as a nice person
and be a good nice person?
On a conceptual level
there is nothing wrong with being nice.
If you've got two guys
let's say you've got like
when I think of nice guys, I think of this
I heard a long time ago
and it was like if you've got
a girl who's attracted to two guys
and one is like a normal guy
first of all let me say slut
but continue.
Exactly.
Who is a woman going to be attracted to?
A really attractive guy
who is also nice
but this guy is like
rich, he's really fun to be around
he's exciting but then he's also really nice
and he treats her well
obviously that's literally the dream guy
but as opposed to
some average looking guy
but he's not quote unquote a nice guy
he's a little more rebellious.
The girl is going to be interested
in the guy who's got everything going on
and is also nice
because niceness in itself is not actually
a bad thing but
what it comes down to for me
and I know this is a personal thing
it's that when you're nice as your identity
I know that's what you were talking about before
and I think we're all in agreement on this
but it's when you use niceness as your
attractive trait and it's like I'm nice
therefore I deserve good things to happen
and as I was told to believe
earlier in my life
so I have big negative implications with it
I feel like there's layers
of being nice
where it's like nice as like a vague
like you know say please and thank you
but then there's like niceness in terms of
like you are
unconfrontational
you don't take a stance on any issue
all I'm saying is
if you don't hit
if you don't hit your significant other
she'll never know how good it is
when you're not hitting her
that's what I'm saying
this is retardation
all these blanket statements
about like what will
a girl like just a girl
that you've whipped up in your mind
what will she pick
guys don't need to be nice to each other
niceness is useless between men
it doesn't matter
you know exactly what it means
it means that we care about what each other can offer
on like a
yeah that's you Nate
I want to be nice to people
it's just a basic human instinct
to be nice to the people that you care about
this is where it comes down to
you being Nate
this is a Nate being Nate thing
if you're talking about like
Nate we were being nice to each other in the chat yesterday
and it was nice
did you notice Ben
you may not have noticed
I did not comment
yesterday we were all
I was saying like guys
okay I won't talk about what it was
but I specifically did not comment
in a positive way
and I almost commented like yeah I'm not gonna be a pussy
and like join this conversation
you were in there being
all sad about some shit
and then the rest of us were like
yeah we are also kinda sad about the shit
and the rest of us were like oh no it's fine
we're all gonna be fine
thank god that Nate
I'm not stooped to the level of being like
yeah you guys are okay too
yeah I maintained my frame
and that's why I smash the puss
on the daily
the problem here is just
it's a different point of perspective
it's a different world view
you see like us
well I'll speak for myself
I value
being nice I value human connection
living my life to its fullest
I value
classical ideals
and I like when the world
is happy I like
when I am happy I like
good things and that's why I like being nice
because it is an unequivocal
good thing in almost
every context whatsoever
we can get to unconditional love I agree
that's not a Morley's town thing to do
but that's a 0.1%
there's not a whole lot
of real unconditional love
and most of it is just
people being nice to one of the people having
good emotional
connections with one another
and there's literally no reason to say that it's bad
there's literally no reason other
than to just sound sanctimonious
and be pretentious and put on air
and make yourself sound like you're
on your moille hygrim there's no reason
well that's what you're saying coming from your perspective
but that's not a full picture
like some people are emotionally manipulated by other people
and it is their nicest that allows them
to bend over to like
do what they're told and it's not always a good thing
you gotta watch out for that
the majority of people are just nice to one another
and they're not being manipulated or tricked
to do their unbelievable
stupidity of how the door
opened for such strangers
almost everyone is being manipulated
by someone in their life
in a deep way
that's what I would argue
you know someone? I didn't hear the first part of that
well I'm just yeah I think most
people are like everyone who's dating someone
is to some degree being manipulated by
that person it's just how it works
it doesn't mean it's negative or even a bad thing
but they are using
their emotions and the expectation
that the other person should be nice to them
these are like control mechanisms
we use over each other via society
and niceness is us
I'm not even saying it's insidious
I'm just saying that's just how people work
we're already seeing that this is sort of like
Nate wants to talk about Starfleet
we've got to stop this
we've got to crush it right now
I would like to talk about how empathy is good
and there's not enough of it
we've already done empathy
I totally agree that it's good though
what was our conclusion?
did we like empathy? did we not like it?
I'm still on the fence personally
let me just say that I actually think empathy is great
but I think that's totally different from niceness
I think they are too distinct
I think niceness is vague enough that it includes lots of things
and you are like
focusing on the sexual
the sexual courting aspect
of a nice guy
that is all you're thinking about
what can I say my dude
I always got pussy on the mind
yeah
we're sending you to jail now
the very first PC prisoner
right now
yes lock me up
it's gonna be dangerous for these ladies on the street
I am
the PC ratess
I think we can do an entire episode
on relationships but just related to
being nice real quick here
I am of the opinion that
you can just be a normal person
and like Nate said I completely agree
just live your life and eventually
people will come to you
that have similar interests
and are of similar mindsets
that just makes sense
this has nothing to do with that
well obviously
if you are a nice person
you will attract other nice people
or people are trying to manipulate you
I'm just saying
this whole courting
via measuring
does girls
do all girls want this nice person
or do all girls want someone
who is vaguely edgier
do all girls want someone who is rich and powerful
I just think it's unhelpful
it's better
I think if someone says that
they don't want that they're lying
you can probably draw some like
broad generalities
in what like certain demographics
want
I agree
I don't think it's very helpful
especially people who are listening to this podcast
who are like abnormal
no no no the people who listen to this podcast
are like teenage boys
and they need to hear this shit
we have adults
there are adults in the audience
I pray
I know they're there
I don't think that they should be listening to us
I don't think we're good influences
I disagree completely
I'm the best influence
I basically
when I come out here
I'm speaking to like young Nate
I'm trying to fix the mistakes
that young Nate made in anybody who's listening
and I want them to be aware of the lessons I've learned
well Nate if you didn't make those mistakes
you wouldn't have become Nate
but that's
not necessarily a good thing
like if I could be the same
did we agree on that
I mean I'm a deeply broken individual
and I'm totally aware of that
and if I could make someone have the same
guerrilla mindset that I have now
hang on hang on if you're a totally broken individual
how do we know what you're saying is a good advice
because it is intellectually
and logically sound
that's why
I don't know
this is a paradox
no it is not a paradox
just literally take my arguments and analyze them for flaws
if you don't find any then they're fine
if there are flaws then they are not fine
please do this to all my arguments all the time
and I will do it to everyone else's
I think most of the time
when you present an argument before the court here
most of the time
it's not exactly that there is
like a plot hole
it's just that
the point of view you're coming from
and your conclusions
most of the time I don't think
are anything that should be allowed
in society
well fuck you
it's your base assumptions
I think
that are a sticking point sometimes
not the actual logical argument
itself
the main difference that we're coming at here is
when I think about being nice
we focus in on like the relationship
aspects of niceness
whereas you guys are looking at it from a slightly broader context
we are looking at it from the cowards perspective
that's right
the blue-pilled cuck perspective
I think if we were being nice right now
we would be agreeing with you and be saying
exactly
I don't want you to be nice
maybe
obviously niceness
niceness 24-7 is not good
but any emotion
or any state of mind 100% 24-7
is not a good idea
over intelligence and anything is not a good idea
but for the basic
majority of all human interaction
niceness is the way to go
the one distinction I would make
there is that I would put niceness
below like being true to yourself
always
it's like always a lower priority
but I would give
what a grill name
it's examples of
when you can be nice and what you would do
and why
you're walking through a door
the person behind you
you know there's someone behind you
are you going to hold the door open
or are you going to hope that they push
forward and do it themselves
I'll tell you what I do
I analyze how far behind me the person is
and determine if it is worth my time
to hold the door open for them
but I'll tell you this
so you're being emotionally manipulated
to an insane stream of people behind you
to waste your time
I am emotionally manipulating them
by giving them a positive
conditioning view of me
by doing something nice for them
knowing that it could pay off in the future
I'm making an investment here
that's what I'm doing
I don't disagree that being nice to people
that you want them to like you
is like a thing that people do
the only thing is that I'm more blackpilled
that's why we do the things we do
I know that we're all just manipulating each other all the time
but you just call it being nice
I would say it's emotional manipulation
that's the only difference here
I don't disagree
I don't think about it as manipulation
in like a day to day
maybe I'll do a good thing
I'll do a nice thing to this person
maybe it'll be good for them
maybe it'll make somebody laugh today
maybe I'll increase
the happiness of the world
by like a certain amount
if we take the sort of vague
definition of manipulation
to just be like manipulation
the sense that you change things
to make certain outcomes appear
then literally every single action
that any human takes is manipulation
but I think there is an obvious social
what's the word
definition of the word manipulation
to be something
where you are intentionally tricking someone
to do something
that's kind of how I think about it
as I go about my life
so you think even in the situations
where you could just say
manipulation in the sense that
I'm changing words
I'm changing
ideas in my mind
to be words that people will like
a form of tricking and not just manipulation
since I'm changing
in a way, yes
the fact that you, Munchie, don't go out
and act as crazy as you do
when you're out in public
I would argue is like the same thing
as me like choosing to hold up
in doors for people who are nearby
because like you don't want the societal ramifications
the thing about it
all is that words are
terrible, I want to do a whole podcast
about language because
fuck language it sucks, it doesn't work
nobody uses it right
but like the fact that Nate is taking the word manipulation
and is applying it to all these
things and saying yes this is manipulation
when in my mind and the minds of most people
manipulation is a
by definition a negative
thing that you do not want to be doing
if you say I manipulate people
that gives like this connotation
of like oh here's a bad person
he thinks he's literally evil
and he likes it
that's the feeling the word manipulation gets
even if it technically doesn't mean that
it's just
language sucks and this is why
I like to be edgy, okay but listen
I have prepared a statement
of exactly how I am in real life
alright here's my statement
I'm on the PCP
my name is Nate Bestman
I'm 27 years old
I believe in taking care of myself
eat a balanced diet and a rigorous exercise routine
in the morning
I record the procrastinator's podcast
and if I have time
I record a bonus episode
I can do almost two now
after I finish recording the
podcast
blah blah blah blah I do all the stuff
I go to my workout I do a 3x3 blah blah blah
who cares okay here's the end
there is an idea of a best guy ever
some kind of abstraction
but there is no real Nate
only an entity something illusory
and though I can hide my cold gaze
and you can shake my hand and feel flesh gripping yours
and maybe you can even sense
our lifestyles are probably comparable
I simply am not
there
I fucking love that movie
I watched it again like two days ago
American Psycho is the greatest movie
I literally idolized Patrick Babin
he is my hero in every aspect
I don't know
I don't agree because I feel manipulated by you right now
well that is an emotional response
and I would urge you to crush those feelings
I feel really manipulated
by your speech there to laugh
you literally are
you literally have been manipulated
that's right that's exactly right
I'm being manipulated by everyone around me
that's how it is
look I'm sorry that
I phrase things differently than most people
but that is how it is
that is how it is in real life
okay okay
I can understand using the word manipulation
I can get behind just like you know
it being a word meaning change
but how is it deceit
how are you deceiving me
well I guess the only way
to argue that is deceit is to not do it
because like it was just
something that you wanted to do
but to do it specifically to achieve an intended outcome
I guess is the difference there
let me look up what the word deceit means
but even that's like not bad
there must be some lying here
I don't even think there's a distinction because like
why is it morally better to do stuff just because you want to
as opposed to achieve a certain outcome
there is no moral distinction there in my mind
I don't think so either
that's not what I'm saying
okay deceit
it's actually a practice of deceiving some
okay this uses the word deceiving hold on
well that's a fucked up definition
fucking
I continue talking while I find this
well you know what I honestly don't care about any of this
I wanted to get my American psycho joke in and I did it
so we can
I'm just saying that
doing things because you want to
in like and
doing something that you want to
that is not against laws
or against social convention
no reason to frame it as a trick
or like you are doing
something wrong
like like like deceiving people
okay yeah the implication
is that it's like
it's like abnormal and like not human
it's the thing humans would not do otherwise
I have a
I have a thought about this what if
you know
that like I don't know tell let's say telling
jokes like let's say you know
that like going out in public and telling jokes
gets a good reaction and people like it
you are not naturally
inclined to tell jokes
but you learn that like oh people
really like it when I tell jokes so I'm going to go out
to a party I'm going to tell jokes be the life of the party
everyone really likes it
is that is that deceitful
for you to go out and do that
because you know that it's
what people want even if it's not like what you were
quote unquote naturally inclined to do
an excellent question Ben
and it reminds me of the exact
same thing can be applied to like
I mean when people hear about like for example
pickup artists for just people
who go out and really try
to like meet women and like entertain them
and completely consensually like
get them to sleep with them by being fun
and entertaining yeah people have a reaction
to that like something bad is happening
there yeah but literally
what is the issue and it's exactly what you just said
like the whole that making people laugh to make people like
you it is the exact same thing
and I would argue that there is no
like I don't know why anyone would even say
that there's a problem with such a thing
I would argue that those people are better
than the people who are naturally inclined
I think it would be a little fucked up
I don't know
I mean this person who's
going out and telling jokes
I mean are they tricking you
like is by acting a certain way
that they have like made themselves act
because they know people like it is that a trick
because it's not like because they didn't use
to do that or because they didn't
because they're only doing it to get
a specific outcome
what is not a trick
is there anything in the world that is not a trick
the reason we got
onto this like line of thinking is that we were
trying to determine if being nice
is a bad thing or not and if
this all if all of this stuff that we're doing
is like manipulating and deceiving
but it's also totally normal and everyone
does it is not bad
what are we talking about
we're just kind of
why is nice is bad
nice is bad because it's what cucks do
that's why that's why just don't get cuck
look at this guy saying the cuck
well don't people
don't people like nice people
they like to use them
this is off topic
this is off topic but going slightly back to
pick up artists I completely agree with you Nate
like the way you've described pick up artists
it is indeed like who could fault that
just people being nice
and consensually having sex with women
or you know men whatever
like there's any such thing
I feel like
what's the
I feel like pick up artists go
have the same problem that I guess
this is kind of not related
but like feminists have where it's like
sure like the core ideal of like
I want women to be equal
sure who can agree with that but in
practice who can agree with that not
fuck yeah
that's true don't take that out
amplify that
do
but it's just like sure
these ideals if you want to define those groups of that
like who like that's just a good
thing people want that
but in practice a lot of people
that's not all people think about
when they hear the term pick up artists or
feminists they think of all of the pick up
artists or feminists that they've seen who are not nice
people even pick up artists
that I rather like like there's this one guy
who calls himself Tyler Durden
or Tyler RSD after the guy from
fucking Fight Club like even
he well you know what honestly
it might not have actually been him so take his name out of it maybe
he's in a relay but I have heard some pick up guys
who like promote the stuff or like teach
it say like that it's okay to like
lie about like who you are
and like I get the argument there because
like you're just like ooh it's all fun like crazy
night out and you're just giving like a fun experience
to people but that's always kind of rub me
the wrong way and I don't like
that stuff so again all that
stuff like you're absolutely right labels
are bad fuck the labels I'm just
I'm using it a shorthand which is unfortunate
because it will give these kind of you know connotations
I was having our say about this the other day
we're like like I
again it's all about labels and
when you say like you know
you just want to go out and have sex which is fine
not a bad thing that's fine
but there is obviously a pick up artist culture
and I don't I don't know that
culture like backhand I don't
really know what's going on I've seen
movies or pick up artists or like bad people and I know
Nate who you know who's a bad person
it was a nice person no it's a nice person
so yeah you know I don't
really know what the fuck's going on I'm just saying that like I don't
think it's unreasonable that people have a semi
bad interpretation of pick up artists
people can have based on the fact of
what I know about the culture which is limited
I mean I mean there's there's good ones
and bad ones and you know
your your opinion of the whole thing is
going to be like which you've had experience
with I don't even consider
myself really relate to the community I just
I was there and learn
some stuff and then you know like
moved on with my life because I hate labels
anyway um but anyway
let's get the fuck out of here let's
let's get back to why
why nice is tell me
why niceness is good what's there to like
there's nothing people like it like if
okay here's an argument if people
think that you are nice
then they will like you more and
and they will probably seek
out your company more yes
and that's pretty great
universal some people like think I
he's just nice I want to fucking
freak
freak some people
like the streets
that's kind of me that's kind of me
yeah yeah I feel that
but like like it can be kind of boring
but it is just nice if you know
if you know that someone is
is cool but like in person
say there's like an internet person
and they're like wacky and edgy and cool
and stuff well here's one but in
person they're like it then
nice to hang out with and they're not like abrasive
and shouting at you all the time
I mean I'm not I'm not really trying to show this
the obvious is more complicated this but like Joseph
Anderson making all his like millions of long
ass videos about video games
like they're all like just very similar like synopsis
and they go over shit and if he likes
or doesn't like it or whatever but then you got
Matthew Matosis who they you know they say that
like Joseph Anderson is like Matthew Matosis
2.0 but then he's like bargain
Matthew Matosis well that's what I'm saying
because he comes up with the Sonic Dreams
collection video that's like what the fuck
is this Jesus Christ yeah and like that's
like the coolest video ever that's got so
much more personality and it's like you know
who this guy is because he's playing this
kind of game I think about
I think about Joseph Anderson Matthew Matosis
all the time and how and how obsessed
and how obsessed maybe
yeah it's weird it's weird how much I think
about it like how I'll take
a Joseph Anderson video and I'll be like
okay well this kid this is slaked my lust
for the time being but but like
it doesn't it doesn't give me that deep
soul satisfaction that Matthew
Matosis stuff
you need your fix you just need your fix
really long video game analysis
they are good
where does where does Noah
Caldwell lie on this?
Noah Caldwell is like
God it's like
where was the angry Leo Game Nerd
Noah Caldwell he's like
is he worse?
it's like if you want a version of Matthew Matosis
or Joseph Anderson who doesn't
make any sense
okay
Noah will just he'll just go off about like
I don't know I actually listen to like his travel blogs
the other day I listened for like four hours
just him talking about like driving up the west coast
I was like uh yeah
is Noah Caldwell Gervais a nice guy?
is he a nice person? Absolutely
I mean I can tell he looks
he looks like he's uh on the
soylent diet
I got no hatred for the guy
he seems fine he's a big boy
he's a large man he could crush me
I'm thinking of like in terms of at a party
if someone you know you're just talking to people
and somebody is just sort of like
they're kind of boring but they're
polite I think when you think
of like the person who was not abrasive
but was also boring you think of them as
the nice person and you forget about them
but if somebody is like
they're really interesting and they're also polite
you think oh that guy's a great guy
it's just a different word people use
they say great instead of nice even though
the level of politeness the level of like
um what do you call it
manners or something like
there's the same amount of stuff it's really just
uh like
added on to what sort of person they are
and how cool they are if they're you know
a polite person who is cool
they're great and if they're a polite person
who is not cool they're nice
I have an anecdote that I would like to say
from my real life
where okay okay as I'm sure
even the audience knows I hang around
mostly freaks and geeks and assholes
I'm in the PCP
I hang around mostly
who are her sardonic or sarcastic
and who are you know vaguely edgy
and it's great that's the kind of
people who I want to be around I like
uh biting comedy
I like biting people I like
to consume flash
yeah exactly
yeah right
feed me chocolate yummy
um but there's this one person
who I know in real life who is the exact opposite
of this he's just a nice
wholesome kid
and I don't think
he's my best friend I don't think
like like we like
we uh we're just we're just sort of
uh good friends
and I'll go to him sometimes and
he'll be talking about how he likes like you know
the newest Marvel movie and you know
all that kind of shit
I'll be non-long like yeah sure
it's just a lot of saccharine stuff
but it's nice he is a nice person
and I need that refreshness in my life
so I can better you know
accustom with the word better appreciate
uh the biting uh
sarcasm and irony and
uh insincerity of uh
my time here on the internet
so it's nice to have people in your life
just genuine people you can just
rely on to uh you know
bring some life back in your life
are you talking about your Mewtwo?
yes I'm talking about my Mewtwo
thank you Hippo
my Mewtwo
from Pokemon Go, thank you
I would like
like I know that
we in the PCP are like
edgy and stuff but I feel like
we are nice in the in the sense that we know
each other well enough that we will not
cross lines we will be like
sarcastic but all of us can take that level
of sarcasm and we all know how much
you know everyone can take sure
so like we know each other we will be like
uh you know joking
around like insulting each other
and it's not like fake completely
but it's like at a level that you know
all of us can can understand
that it's not really like a
like a like a spiteful sort of like
actual attack and
and that's what I still feel
of that as being nice
because it's like it's just being friendly
and chummy and it's like technically
you put that the same words
in a different in a different
context it would be like horrible but like
because we're okay with it it's
nice and it's normal we talked about this a little bit
in the friendship episode the the the one we did
at Radcon and like
I think this comes up sometimes
and I again I do think we have a slightly
different perspective on it even
within our group whereas like I don't
really see I think
there's two things going on when you're like in a friendship
you want to be generally pleasant because like
you don't want to be you know overly
rough on like your friends and like make them
make like like their experience of hanging out with you
like just generally negative obviously
you don't want to do that but like at the same time
you don't want to like like
I feel like the people in your life
who can really like challenge you
that you will actually like listen to
and like respect their opinions of for
me it's mostly my friends
like I expect my friends to be the ones
to like because like the person you're dating
like again not to be rude or
anything it's just like when you're dating someone
they've got an incentive to like not piss you off
and like make sure everything's going smooth
and I don't really trust their opinion on
anything
I don't know if they're inherent qualities
and you seem to be like they are
they are just part of the relationship
I think they will
exist inherently to various degrees
I do think they are basically inherent
maybe some people can squash them and make them really really tiny
but there's always going to be
an incentive to just like be nice
to for example the person you're dating
but that's in any relationship right
yeah it's with friendships as well
like we have incentive to not like ruin
our friendships because
then we wouldn't have any friends
you're not wrong God knows I don't tell all the criticisms
to you guys that I could
like if we were like
super critical at each other all the time
we would all be econ and it would be
even more
I guess I would just argue that with friends
I feel I find it's like a little easier
to be more like roughly honest
with like with them as opposed to like
the person you're dating
I don't think that's necessarily a reflection of all relationships
well obviously it's not going to be
literally all I'm talking about a general trend here
but okay whatever doesn't matter
for me personally
I just want to say I don't know econ
I just hear things I don't hate him
shout out to econ
I still haven't gone on my hot sauce
which is fine
who? okay moving on
literally who
I don't know I pretty much said
all I wanted to say on this particular subject I think
I think people get where I'm coming from
like I come at this whole thing from the idea of like
I see like being nice
as like
a boring trait
that is like some it's
being nice is nice once you're already
like in a relationship and like you already
know people but like niceness
doesn't like grab attention it doesn't make you
stand out it doesn't really help
you achieve major steps
forward in your life but I don't think it's
sustaining but I don't think it hurts anything
it's not a large positive factor
but it is indeed a positive factor
you enjoy
well not you
you but like you know the general populist
would probably enjoy someone who is nice
to someone who is not nice
in most cases
the real thing is like getting a balance between
being nice and being real
if somebody is nice all the time
to the point where you can't tell when they're
actually being sincere about their niceness
well isn't that interesting
you can be critical and still be nice
and you are not nice
well it's true but like say somebody is like
saying oh my videos suck
and then somebody goes up to them saying
no they're not but in reality they actually
it's the interesting thing you're setting a dichotomy between
like honesty and niceness
which is kind of I mean I guess there's just
like raw realness
like here's my one like
black pill thing that I had
in my brain
is that um
I almost forgot it
oh I did forget it
dark dark souls
you went hollow
is this podcast the dark souls of the bcp
it is
it really is
I'll think of it
to record and I'm sure to listen to
yeah really
oh yeah yeah I got it
being nice sometimes is just
cowardly because
you want
if somebody is upset
or like they are like
potentially going to be upset if you get too real
with them and you are not nice to them
either by
not saying anything or being nice
to sort of like placate them
is cowardly because all you're doing
is preventing yourself
from being upset that they are upset
that's right totally true
I'm not proposing
that you have to be nice 100%
of the time I never have
and I even
there are a lot of cases where being nice is a completely terrible idea
again to like placate your friends
make them just feel that they are secure
and bad things you know
like if their videos suck you should probably tell them
but there are different ways
to go about that and I feel like this word nice just comes through
you can say hey your
views suck now lol
wins rayman 2
as I've heard
every day
your friend
disgasher but great to deal with that dude
you know munchie
or you just be like hey I noticed your videos are like this lately
can we please get some more
magenta filters
I think that really helped
you know what I'm happy to concede munchie
that I come into this thing
extremely biased just
against the word nice
it's like it's my daemon
it is my daemon that I grew up with
and now I just despise it across the board
but really the right way
my daemon
this is the same old english
like amber spyglass
yeah that's right
my british daemon daemon
that's what it is
no daemons are weird
only the
suck
your bus
I just want to talk about my favorite works
of young adult fiction guys
Percy Jackson
ok shut up
what I was going to say was
I am definitely wrong in that I am
way too black and white
take that clip right there
delete that from the podcast
I'm definitely way too
personally biased and the correct way to go
is exactly what you guys have been saying
with like your more nuanced interpretation
and like subjective and like
case by case basis usage of being nice
because it obviously makes sense a lot of the time
and I just kind of hate it
just in a biased emotional way
which is wrong
I'm definitely ready to give you some leeway here
because it was really eye opening
when we were talking about how like
with the french episode like about love
where definitions for
words have to be very exact
for you
which I don't think is really wrong
and a lot of words are really vague
and that is a problem
but I think that like you can usually
ascertain the general definition
of most things
I can't wait to do the language episode
because I utterly despise
that fuzziness that exists inherently
in the usage of these words
I hate it so much
I think it is probably the biggest problem
that we are of the modern age
but we'll talk about that later on
I would like to do the episode
that sounds nice
nice is nice
debunked, niceness debunked
God, removed from real life
never more shall be seen
if you want to be a nice guy
you can go pledge to our patreon
yeah you don't need to be a nice guy
you can be a cold calculating maniacal fiend
to get those bonus episodes
hear all the real black pill shit
it's too hot for TV
right now we're tricking you
into doing the DCP
that's what money is
money is lie
hashtag money is lie
correct
it's also the only objective good in this world
manipulate
that's my name
you found it
manipulate
where's the L
are we done?
closing statements here
we got a good question right
of course I just mean done
Ben what's your closing statement here
Ben I want to hear you
oh shit
well
amber spyglass was definitely the best of the three
you're not wrong
are you guys too old
remember percy jackson and lightning thief
yes I have heard the great gatsby
I saw the movie
shout out to all the twinks in the audience
who know shit about percy jackson
excellent okay done
moving on everybody it's time to go
to those beloved questions
that we all love so much
hey everybody
patreon.com slash the procrastinators
give us your money
get into the patron lounge
from twitter so we can get that out of the way
we can wipe that shit off our shoe
we can move on to the galaxy
that is the questions bar
here's a pretty good
I don't know if I've ever read this one before
there's a bunch of questions about radcon
things like will you do radcon again
radcon 4
radcon 2 electric boogaloo the fourth one
these cowards
how dare they appreciate radcon
who do they think they are
they're trying to trick us into thinking
that they like radcon
what the fuck
yeah how dare they
impede
impose their emotional
likes and dislikes
and let us know how they feel about the content
that we have generated for them
so as to guide our production
of future content that is
evil and that is core
I wonder why people think
this was the last one
did anyone I didn't see that
will there be another one
why is that even a question
maybe just because it took so long
for this one to happen
we did spend
man it was like a whole year
because radcon 1 happened and 3 or 4 months later
radcon 2 happens
it's weird to think about that now
it is weird
it's really just because we wanted to do it immediately
and we started it
the first one did not have a kickstarter
the second one did
put 2 kickstarters really close to each other
it's because did you and Jesse just were doing
their kickstarter and then that just got turned into
radcon 2 so it was like a big
we didn't plan that one it just kind of happened
on its face
but we are definitely going to work to make these happen
certainly more often than they have
I think the ideal
audience don't take this as fact
just the ideal thing that I think we all
would like to go for is like every 6 months or so
though that's probably unrealistic
I think that's a good middle ground
I'd sure like that if we could do that
and hey maybe if radcon hq happens
I mean pcphq happens
that certainly changed things
who knows how often we'd do it
I like it to be a special thing
it's radcon every day bro
yeah
hey but there's one other question
I wanted to read on here
this will be the actual real question
from the peeps on the twitter
at cultoftheyellow1 asks
Nate if you had a behelit
would you use that shit to sacrifice the other
pcp members to transcend your humanity
of course you would
here's the real answer it would be
morally bankrupt of me not to do it
I have to do it
because your lives are objectively less valuable
than the good I do
I don't blame you I would do the exact same thing
in a heartbeat
well thank you man
the one problem
it's a thing from berserk
basically a guy uses it
destroys his friends
and gains ultimate power
but see that's the problem right there
the behelit chooses the things that you care about most
in life and therefore the pcp is going to be
fine you guys won't be hurt at all
dab dab dab
fucking destroy
that's good for me
are you saying that the behelit just wouldn't
oh wait you don't even like it
that's what I'm saying
but Nate this means that the behelit
will stop
starfleet from ever happening
nooo
I don't know how
I think the behelit would like make starfleet
happen but kill like the problem is though
I'm so blackpilled I don't care about nothing man
I don't care about nothing who can even take
only a true cynic can wield the behelit
it would just take your sunglasses
nooo
you could never wear sunglasses you'd live forever
but you could never wear sunglasses again
that would be devastating and action giraffe would die
no fuck
the camino would be erased from existence
if I had
the ballet t.a
I would wish for all the chocolate
in the world
I'm so hungry
feed me yummy snacks
um excellent
I like this new character munchy
I'm so hungry
I only need the yummiest
of foods
good well let's go to the fucking patrons
now let's go to the real shit now
oh that out of the way
okay what do we got
read me feed me chocolate
questions from the patron lounge
from the patron lounge
Cicero do you guys think
competition like like cap like
proper noun competition is a good
or bad thing
lay does it help you improve faster
is it handling your improvement and creativity
competition is always good
competition is great
read bakuman
well yeah it's not always good
it's like very good
in the worst case scenario
competition that is like too steep
can make you discouraged because you're like well I'm never
gonna be as good as these guys
yeah uneven competition
is usually bad but like
if you're in an even playing field
well okay it depends on what he means
like does it mean like literal like trophies
like this is a professional sports competition
or does he just mean like
rivalrys between friends to see who can
I mean it sounds like in the case of us
he means like just for example like the
quote-unquote rival between
competition because like
like capitalism depends on you know
you know what kind of competition would really
improve my life as if patreon had some
fucking competition damn right what same with
YouTube same with okay I was just thinking about
this like Michelle has YouTube
read and like how
many millions of times is everyone said like
God I wish I could like close my phone
and still have YouTube play so I could like
save the battery life and stuff like that
function already exists and it's only
for YouTube red people
so like you so you have to pay money
for it but so like the reason competition
is good like we need a YouTube competitor so that
there's another app that does the exact same thing as
YouTube so that like they that other
company can give away that service for free
so that YouTube is pressured to make it
available to everyone that is how we get better
stuff through competition forcing
like the market to evolve and like
you know all these things get cheaper and more accessible
and they have to innovate and stuff
already yeah YouTube
I mean definitely that would help
YouTube get better quicker
I'm sure that they really
want to try and find ways to make
this everything they do
much cheaper to
to do because I have how expensive it is
to host video so like
I don't think I'm gonna stop until they're actually
making like big money and then they can just
rest on their laurels I mean
but if they had competition I mean
it would be good definitely
the specific kind of like feature stuff
like everyone wants this YouTube red feature
and I really think the reason why it's
not available to the public that it's like gated
behind stuff is because no one is
offering that service at like a lower
price or or even for free
and like the reason that like smart
phones are like now accessible is because
like everybody started making smart phones and it
has driven the price down so now it's like affordable
for the average person and stuff
otherwise you'd have like one if only one
company like owned like smart phone
technology like they could just
you know price that should up crazy high
however they wanted to and everyone would want it
but it's cuz you know we've got the competition
to one like fucking iPhones and the androids
and stuff you already kind of got that with
iPhones like well yeah
just live one like
if they're an iPhone they will never even
think about getting an Android
true true they will pay
all the money because like
yeah I mean it is a slightly different service
like iPhones just like work automatically
and they don't take the kind of like they kind of lock
shit down so you can't fuck it up which decreases
freedom for people who like want to mess with their
phones and stuff but I mean whatever you
get the idea but for competition like among
us as like creators I think it's generally
good cuz I mean all the time I'm always
thinking of like I kind of in my mind always
have like a milestone I'm trying to reach
and some of it is like people who had like
it should be nice to like pass that guy
hey I'm not just gonna say
I think I have just passed or I'm about
to pass a Digi brony after dark
that's like a milestone in my mind
you know you know so shout out to my boy
Digi
how many subscribers does Jeb Bush have?
cuz that's my goal is to always be under Jeb Bush
how many how many electoral
college votes are there that many
he got them all baby he got them all
my milestone right now is to get more than
10,000 views on a video that I post
you've done that though
I haven't thought about
I haven't thought about my YouTube in a
while but I am like creeping up to
10k I could probably hit 10k
without that much trouble if I like put my
mind to it
dude any with your fucking lecture coming
I think your fucking lecture coming
I think that's uh
oh you know what the lecture is gonna
yeah the lecture is gonna blow that shit out of the water
now Ben will be above me
but I have a couple of video things that I
have kind of been meaning to do at some point
and like I could
I could just do those
maybe after the lecture comes out and I could start getting
more hits I'll like put out
some more of that
yeah I bet I'll hit 10k when the lecture
comes out hell yeah
what are you at right now?
8 something? yeah okay
it's not unreasonable at all
it gets anywhere close to the views the other one got
uh no
am I subscribed to munchie?
I think I'm subscribed to in fact I know I am
subscribed to all y'all
I have 2k please
unsubscribe so I can go back to having no
k
alright another question
there are a lot of good questions in the questions
bar oh like this one uh chirpsky
is moving castle favorite anime
favorite anime oh my god
chirpsky no
stop it's got a bunch
of reaction emojis with just the word shit
reaction to that oh there you go
you see the people know the people know
but most of them I do not
have a good answer for
mozoelofinnikid
what is something you could never forgive someone for
making
asking that question in the patron lounge
that's a good question
no this is a good question a previous one
um
asking favorite anime
there's obvious things like killing my family
like yeah but I'm trying to
think of like the least that I would
I could forgive that
it was just bad
I could never forgive someone
for something like
something like um
probably like
telling people what I've done
like like
ruining my reputation or something
yeah yeah yeah
or showing someone my youtube channel
at all
that's pretty high
that's pretty high uh just like
me
I
that's a doing weed I could never forgive you
for doing weed anyone
I'm not too far off from that pal
I'm not too far off from that
in real life
I believe you man if you do weed
my perception of you will always be
colored that is not a joke
colored green and we know
much too fond of the colors so
you know um
I'm trying to think I mean you know like
I'd be very deeply upset
possibly forever if someone like
like fucked with
my relationship in some way you know
like fucked my girl like that would
definitely upset me in a massive way
um you know that'd be
bad that'd be real bad and that's where
my mind goes first because I'm a deeply insecure man
about my my my sex life
and that's why I'm obsessed with it and have
deep rooted fears related to it all the time
uh so yeah you know
things relate to that yeah
I mean I feel like
that would be I feel like it would be
something like that it's just I haven't had
like one of those things
happened to me yet like I've
gotten mad at people and I've been like oh
you know what I'll never forgive you but then
I'm like it doesn't actually matter that much
yeah that's really I think that's really what it is though
like if I was dating someone and they really
like cheated on me and like a deeply humiliating
and fucked up way that would
definitely be one of the worst things I think
outside of like fucking like mutilating
me locking me in a sex dungeon and like
torturing me for the rest of my life like that'd be pretty bad
well are you saying you don't want to be in a sex dungeon
well let's say a non-sex dungeon
I'm allowed to know sex
now that's a nightmare
it's like like
prepare to be locked in a dungeon for the rest of your life
and tortured a sex dungeon
no no
yeah great
I feel like in a perfect world
in a perfect world
I would be able to forgive
really anything
I wouldn't like to forgive you
because a lot of the time
when you have like rage in you about a person
all it does is like make your own life
kind of annoying
whenever you think about that person you go
you twitch and you like
and you squeeze your hand like Arthur
I would rather
just be able to just think about it
fuck
yeah I'm with you Gib
I have a Buddhist saying about that
it's like
you're a foreign language class bin
no anger like holding on to anger
and like hoping for revenge
is like holding on to a hot coal
hoping that you will throw it at your enemy
you know
yeah that is good
but it hurts you in the meantime
I've got another excellent quote
fear leads to anger
anger leads to hate
hate leads to suffering
get out of here Yoda from the prequels
um
I don't like the prequels
they'll never forgive them
well said
here's something
if you watch Star Wars
do not try to be my friend
it will only lead to you
being six feet under the fucking ground
I feel the same way
Star Wars is not something
that I want to invite into my life
yeah agreed
agreed
here's the question I want to read
I've been wanting to comment on this
in some public way for a while now
Jalen Harris asks
who started the sunglasses meme
Nate or Digi
I'd be happy to hear your guys' opinions on this
but we all know the little man named keg standard
started a particular sunglasses meme
long before any of this shit began
and since the start
since the start of best guy ever
sunglasses have been a defining characteristic
of the channel
and I think that was before Digi ever started doing sunglasses things
I wish Digi was here to comment
I'd like to hear his opinion
did you request that keg have the shutter shades
or did I give him them
I don't remember
I think that might have been my
I think I might have gone and been like hey what if he had some shutter shades
I'm happy to give you credit
for coming up with some shutter shades
and
things were never the same
I really think that I came up with those
I really think that I suggested those
I was really into Kanye at the time
and I specifically said like Kanye shades
I'm not sure
I could believe that maybe you suggested it
but in either case
especially in their modern
incarnation of the PCP
even if that's true though
how far back does the Digi sunglasses meme go
because best guy ever
is immediately defined
by the sunglasses of the guy
that was right out of the gate
and I would say that was significantly before Digi started his sunglasses thing
I give myself full credit
when did Digi start the sunglasses
I don't even know
you know what
maybe Jesse
because he wore sunglasses in Tony videos
that's not a fine characteristic of Jesse
okay
you know what I hate
you know what I hate the fact that so many of you guys
wear sunglasses is that
it means that I can never wear them
because then I would be like oh you too
you as well
just a bunch of sunglasses dudes
okay but I will say that currently
I am the most consistent sunglasses guy
it's like my thing
it's like my thing now
Digi's thing too he's always turned off the sunglasses
Digi fucking stole it from me
a race trader
I'm inclined to
don't you fucking say it
I think you did say it
I think you did do it first
damn right
yeah fuck it die
there you go
and it's over
okay next question what do we got
O2Miraseu
what is the biggest missed opportunity at Radcon
not recording the fucking
clusterpunk fashion runway
I spent 140 dollars
on that shit
you were talking about it before
and the whole time and it just didn't happen
is it a missed
opportunity or is it like a fucked
opportunity because we
what do you mean
we just had too much stuff booked
we would have done it if we had the time
it's not like we forgot about it
real talk if we had schedule
we got a ton done we deserve like no criticism
for the amount of stuff that was produced at Radcon
but if we had worked better
we could have produced more stuff
it was on the fucking schedule
it was on the schedule
we didn't fucking stick to the schedule for shit
we tried
I made it in the hopes we'd stick to it but we did not
and you know like
I mean I was there to make sure I got my shit done
and I did you know it was
same I got the stuff that I needed
to get done the clusterpunk fashion runway
was supposed to be like a PCP thing but I
it would have been cool
you know what
put a fucking feather in that one
and save it because we could do it again
someday and you know what tbh
like because digi didn't know about it
like digi would have been the only person that could
have rivaled me I mean that is true
so like
it was sort of a fledgling idea that needed
a little bit more expanding and like
being like we're doing it now everyone signed up
I gotta get svelte
I gotta get svelte for next Radcon
so I can not look like a fucking fat piece of shit
on the clusterpunk fashion run
oh Jackie just got me okay Nate
you know about um you know my pink chucks
that are like
fucking faded shit and falling apart
he got me some new ones they are there neon
they are vibrant day glow pink chucks
and they are they are coming
on the on the fashion runway
I want this I want everyone
to like for radcon for everyone to bring
their fucking a game and bring the most
we'll see if you see I don't even know
I had to prepare anything I guess I just didn't consider
myself part of it
you don't have to be yeah I know I know
the only problem with me is that
suitcase space
like I just managed
to get everything that I brought to radcon
well you could bring a second suitcase
and check it we could budget for it
like full of stuff one outfit
it's I don't know
well would one outfit really take up that much space
in your suitcase I mean I don't know
I feel like these are solvable issues but
we can worry about that later
I have one
this was one for their history books
I am sad the one the only thing
I am personally really sad didn't
get made at radcon was I really wanted to do
otaku workouts with digi
I really wanted to do another workout video
which we did not I didn't know that was on the
docket like did you came up to me as like
Nate I wanted to blah blah blah all this stuff that I don't care
about but then he was like but otaku workouts
I'm like yeah that sounds fun
but we just did that time
okay not a missed opportunity
per se but kind of
is that I do regret not
being on art apologies
which I am greatly looking
forward to listening to
I wanted to be on that well after I saw
like the behind the scenes footage
of digi and also
like that behind the scenes
like clip of him like filming you
and Tom
like drawing your respective comics
just silently was really cool
oh by the way I should have been there
here's a little message to all the backers we have already
amassed a ton
a huge amount of backer content
it's unreal it's fucking unbelievable
we're talking like 20
videos already exist and one of them
was like 45 minutes
gib and digi killed it with the amount of
shit they made and there's more
I won't go into it
but we're not going to release it until more content
is out because it's got spoilers
I swear to god like 75%
of the entire time at
radcon like not having sleeping
was recorded like there was a camera on
somewhere in the house thanks to gib
thanks to gib and digi for like fucking filming
a bunch of shit there are two
other ones one of me and digi
were writing a skit for project
awesomeness that was great
and we just didn't have time to
record it properly and
and also this is not
really a missed opportunity because it didn't
fact happen but I'm kind of anxious
of the result been
the referee's cop killers me maker
was great but the actual like we sports
resort was really bad
yeah um
uh oh
it's okay
overall I liked it like I'm not
well the game was bad but I don't think
the the recording was bad
I think the record
I have an idea of how I want to fix it which will
really fit in with referee's cop killers but I'll
let you after the show so you don't
okay okay word fucked up
oh should we should we make it like a statement
on whether the stuff will be available
to people at some
point oh yeah we don't
have a plan for it but we plan on making it available
some way to people afterward so we will
get back to you if you didn't back radcon
do not panic even though you should feel ashamed of yourself
yeah but they're
probably will be a way to get it so don't
forget it'll be jacked the fuck
up though it'll be twisted you will
you will regret your decisions
sphincter directly
indeed indeed uh
says what future technology you must excited for
auto automatic cars
bro self drive cars auto
self erotic asphyxiation
looking forward to that in a big way
um self
self
fucking sex dolls
so basically
what is wrong with all of you
with all the fucking freaks
right now
you know having a sex doll is great but it's such a
time commitment but now you have a doll that will
fuck itself so you don't have to
I want aeroplanes
to become like incredibly
fuel efficient so that they're super cheap
and I can fly all over the world
yeah
that's fairly likely to happen
that's my new answer
okay
I didn't really care about living abroad at all
until like I just thought about it for a second
about how being in the EU
I could just like live in
like London or something like maybe not anymore
but I could like live in
like Paris or something
and I could just like walk
well not walk but I could just like go to Germany
or I could just like go to Spain
and then it's not gonna be very nice
I would like to do that
maybe not a radcon but just specifically
a Gibbon Munchie Hangout
I want to go to Europe someday
that will happen I guarantee it
we could pokemon go all over the world
hey man radcon 4 London
I'm just saying it would be pretty good
yes it would be pretty good and also very expensive
radcon 5 Japan
and radcon 5 Japan I love this idea
of doing the next one in London and the fifth one
in Japan in Tokyo
radcon Japan is the worst fucking idea I've ever
no you don't know that
you don't know shit how fucking sick would it be
I don't think radcon Japan would work
as a radcon I think it would work as a
let's all go to Japan and be anime
it would be so hard
don't speak Japanese
I have lived in Japan for months
and it is a place that is designed
that you don't need to know Japanese to survive
I have been there I know the place
most big cities you can ask for help
and people will speak
the reason it's kind of a weird idea
is because radcon is about
making content together
rather than hanging out in a city
well not every radcon has to be exactly the same
as long as we pitch it with the honest
this is what it's going to be
we would probably call London and Japan
different things than radcon then
no because radcon implies
like we're getting together to make a bunch of content
and you'll see it soon
but something like that would be
we go to an expensive city and live in a hotel
and then we have like a fun time
and we could
literally just get an Airbnb
who cares it's fine
why can't it be both
well the reason it can't be both
is really just
there's no point going to such a place
if we're going to stay in one place and record
and not actually go out
literally go out and do stuff for a day or two
out of like the 10 days or whatever
how expensive is it to live like
just in Japan
and it is fair
do they have airbnbs in Japan
I don't know but we could look into it
alright there's no need to like fucking break
the fucking thing down I'm just saying it be cool
radcon 5 right now
agree it would be cool
do you agree alright
thank you
catch a farfetched
there you go
radcon 5 the quest for farfetched
that's what it is
that's the one
we don't have to get them
we have to transfer them
radcon exclusively
for pokemon go
exclusively no other content available
oh my god
two more questions
chip in the francs
similar question
what's a mundane everyday miracle
that you noticed and recognized
this is a really interesting one
yeah magnets
an everyday miracle
I mean just being alive
period
okay
what do you say is a miracle
is that just like for us to interpret in any way we want
I think so yeah
I get hung up on the word miracle
only because if people say that life is a miracle
we can exactly trace back why life exists
so what do we mean
think about like Dr. Manhattan
talking about how like
a spectacularly unlikely event
is a miracle
by that definition being alive
is definitely one
I mean to me when I think
miracle I think like
not necessarily something that doesn't happen
but something that I don't see a lot
and it's just like really like oh yeah
okay and for me
that would be like a sunrise
it's like Jesus walked
on water but in Kirby I can just run
across water so like there's an everyday miracle
like I was just playing Kirby so
there it is
it's just an everyday miracle
I think he's using the definition of miracle
which is not really a miracle
like the ICP version of miracle
something that you really like
when it happens
there's like oh thank god
the electricity works
what a fucking miracle
I think video games are an amazing
everyday miracle that I absolutely love
and I'm so thankful and the internet I guess
but I'm gonna go with video games
that's perfect because that's like
god we evolved in the way
that allows us humans to create
video games like what a miracle
I was gonna say
when somebody that I know
never followed me before
just leaves a nice comment and says I'm subscribing
that's a nice thing
that doesn't happen very often but when it does
it's like yeah I can do it
because of this
do you have an everyday miracle?
um
when someone goes to patreon.com
slash fantasy
I already said being alive
yeah
being dead
the two sides of the same coin
um
the oculus rift
the ability of the fact that I can enter cyberspace
at um at any time
yeah that's good
the fact that you were able to
successful kickstarter
that's an opportunity
the fact that the pcp exists
and is real and I'm a part of it
aww
and then it makes things possible
the fact that I could do this kickstarter
which by the way the vapers books just
arrived this morning
ohhh yeah
that's exciting
and the oculus rift is the stretch goal
and then I actually hit the stretch goal
and then the radcon can happen
and you know we get to do all this cool stuff
the fact that we got the t-bap stretch goal
in fucking radcon 3
is an everyday miracle
not even everyday
that's like a
shock
that was a perfect segue into my segue
you want to know what my everyday miracle is?
segues
here's a new question for you
do you guys have a childhood dream that you've successfully fulfilled
being in the pcp
well being in the horseshoe crew
really but
well that's great
you're still in your childhood
so you're fulfilling that dream right now
exactly
excuse me yummies I'm such a little baby boy
don't you want me to be big
and strong
I need my yummy chocolate
I don't want you getting any bigger or stronger
yeah that would be a danger to us all
I guess if I get any bigger
or any stronger
it would be a serious threat to not
it would be like
in the animatrix when that guy
literally became more physically strong
and fast at running
that was able to be handled by the matrix
and he shattered out of it
what the fuck
sounds like my life
that's literally it
with your resting heartbeat clipping the microphone of real life
every moment
pretty good
this was fine
oh by the way I just want to say
another missed opportunity at radcon 3
doing the oculus rift
yeah I brought it
and I brought my graphics card
and it didn't seem like
it didn't seem like it was going to work
we burned it out lighting at night too much
Tom said that it might have worked on his laptop
but we kind of ran out of time
and didn't get to like give it a shot
so that was a shame
oh well next time
actually in everyday miracles my computer didn't
break it radcon
it was really fucking
I mean well I'm jealous because my computer
did break it radcon
and now my laptop keyboard doesn't work
so it's all
it's a fucking brick now
shoutouts to my laptop who did basically everything
your laptop killed it dude
he's a strong boy I gave him a pat on the back
he's a good
guys there's a fucking
crowbat outside my door
like just a poker stuff
he's gotta go we gotta wrap this one up right here everybody
alright thanks for joining us everybody
yo listen everybody
patreon.com
slash the procrastinators go there
give us five dollars for bonus episodes
another one should be out now by the time you're hearing this
don't know what it is yet it'll be out
there's like a million already back there's like 12 or something already
they're all great
Gamergate fucking
Trump Trump etc
Insomnia incredible
give us money there one dollar gets you into the patreon launch
we take more questions give us that
it's a fun time we're all hanging out there
go to the twitter false and the twitter for updates
radcon 3 just happened
for the love of god check out the fucking playlist
to radcon 3 we should link it in the description
but if it's not there just go to the playlist on our channel
radcon 3 content is pouring out right now
yeah and all the
you've gotten two lectures this is
a minuscule amount of stuff that we
required we have so much
fucking content
all like we have like a bunch of little like vlogs
and stuff like that's all great and nice
but we also have huge fucking like
monstrous great like new
innovative types of content that
you know you're gonna
by the time of recording this we haven't even gotten out half
the lectures yet so they're all still coming
or you know have three of them are still
coming we got there's just so much
there's so much fucking shit still coming and as well
as the back rewards just a just treasure trove
of shit so look out for all this shit
at tbcrasnir's follow us for announcements
and you know all this kind of shit so and
thanks everybody who gave the kickstarter once again
radcon 3 huge success
gonna keep rolling out gonna keep on doing it
radcon 4 here we come
and we will see you on the next fucking
episode but bye everybody
bye
you