It's the same every day. Scrolling, always scrolling, looking for answers. But none ever
come. Who are you? It's been over a year since this search began and we're no closer
to finding out than when we started. I'm starting to think maybe he doesn't want to be found.
Well, we've done our best. I guess there are some things you just have to learn to let go.
After all, we're only human.
Sir, our calculation show at 99% matched.
Do them again, damn you. We have to be sure.
It's me, Austin. Oh, son of a bitch.
Hello, everyone, and welcome to another episode of the Procrastinator's Podcast.
I am the best guy ever, your host, The Best Man. Dude, did you just see the guy there
saying we know who he is? Okay, yes, we've got a huge announcement, people, a huge announcement.
But before we get to that, we have Hippocrates here. He's a guy that isn't real. We've got Munchy.
Oh, fucking press, wait, it's the fucking it's him. We've got Monkey Jones. I wish I was dead.
Big Manga anime fan here, and we've got Endless Jess.
Hi. Endless Jess. Hi, everybody. I'm in the game.
Is that Homestar Runner? Is that Homestuck, my favorite character? Is that Homo Jess?
Is that Skip and Take? It's me. It's me, Hobo Jess.
It's me, Homo Jess.
Everyone's favorite character from the Endless Jessiverse.
Okay, guys, we have a huge announcement today, and we've got a bombshell announcement,
not maybe like two hours ago. We finally had an answer to the question that's been
plaguing scientists for generations. All right, we have Virgin. The answer is yes.
The answer is yes. But unrelated, but similarly as important.
We have cracked the code. We have discovered the identity of the PCP guy, our mascot guy.
We have found out who the fuck he is. Okay, so let's just set this so if anyone doesn't know,
we've been asking people on Twitter and everywhere that this is not a joke. We really had no idea
who this mascot guy was. He was someone that I found one day when I was just on A, and you
know how I like to use a lot of fucking mango reaction faces and shit. I just used him because
he looked like a real procrastinator to me with that expression. So he became the mascot.
And we'd been, I had no idea what the fuck he was. I'd been trying to fight out for,
the show's been going for over a year, and I have been actively looking for that entire time
and as of people. And today is the day where we finally got our answer. So, okay, our buddy over
on Twitter at Stumble Reel, Akane 3, I don't know, at Stumble Reel. Apparently, actually,
it's months ago, actually, he had tweeted at Ben Saints. So, Stumble Reel here had tweeted at Ben
Saints like months ago. The act like the information about the guy, but Ben didn't get it because
he's an idiot. He doesn't, can't do anything right. But yeah, he's gone. He's dead. But today,
he linked in response to the recent conversation we've been having about who the fuck this guy is,
he provided a screenshot of the actual page. So we're talking about page 14, page 13 of
chapter five of the manga, Inari Konkon Koi Iroha. If you go to that fucking page,
there'll be a link in the description so you can see for yourself. They, he is the boy himself
by the name of Toka Fushimi, character from this manga. So we're talking about Toka.
Hiroshima.
What's even more disappointing is that this was one of Digi's top 10
animes of 2014 and he didn't even recognize the character.
Isn't that fascinating? And we, you should be able to see on the screen.
Yes, that's right.
That's how we found out.
Her though, he's gay.
And we look on this, on the screen, you'll see that what we have there is the anime version
of this exact pose from like chapter, chapter five of the manga.
He's a real anime.
He did it.
He really did it.
You know, I, I, I, it's, it's amazing.
We're so proud of him.
He's come so far.
I, I am immediately, I'm immediately fascinated by this character. And by the way guys, I looked
up his Wikipedia entry. I thought I'd read you a little snippet so you could know that what
we're dealing with here is the most red-pilled hardcore motherfucker who's ever existed. All right.
Okay. So here we go. Here we go. So here's Toka Fushimi's little bio from the Wikipedia page.
Toka, he is handsome, but a recluse who spends his time away from others and keeps to himself,
frequently studying to get into a good university and also has a strange poem blog post.
So we're talking about an internet creator here, a kindred spirit to us.
He is also short-tempered and childish, relatable, relatable.
Especially the childish part.
Yeah.
Frequently being referred to as having eighth grade syndrome or, you know, G-B-O.
He's an eighth grade syndrome.
Oh my God. I finally know what I am.
I don't know. Okay. I don't know if you guys are joking, but that's Chunebio. It's like a specific
thing in Japan where like kids think they have superpowers and like pretend that their evil
organizations are like following them. It's, it's a big, Google Chune's and you'll see like,
it's a real thing.
That's literally returning from NAROTO?
Yes.
Sounds like it's on NHK.
It's, it's some gay Japanimation shit.
So yeah, he's a Chune despite being in his last year of high school.
He also tends to get lost easily.
He's, so he's a millennial who doesn't understand directions.
Yeah.
He is protective of Inari and initially apprehensive of Uka, who's like the ghost
magic spirit from the series, believes that she has malicious intents,
but realizes she is a good person and befriends her.
Oh, befriending a woman, very blue pill, very blue pill.
Even letting her come over to play games.
Playing games with a woman there for procreation and nothing else, you fucking cock.
What else we got here?
Okay, that's it.
The rest is boring.
And he hates sex.
I forgot to read the last sentence there.
Oh yeah.
The last sentence.
Big, big hater of sex.
Big, big fan of the Listen Buddy podcast, funnily enough.
Can I, can I spoil you on the ending of this series guys?
All right, this is a spoiler for the end of this podcast.
No, no, no, no, I wanted to watch it.
I'm going to cover my ears.
Go ahead.
Okay, here we go.
So, okay, at the end, he confesses to like the ghost, the series is over.
In chapter 40 of 43, he confesses his love to Uka, the like spirit ghost lady.
And by the end of the series, he has literally become a god.
So, he could be with her and she has his child.
Oh my god.
So, our boy has started a family.
He's become, he's, he's gone full red pill.
Do you think his child is the PCP?
Oh my god!
Are the spoilers over yet?
I'm still covering my ears.
Does that make us old?
No, they're not done yet.
They're not, I was going to say, we, we, he became a god.
We are gods.
He has given birth to this organization.
Oh my god.
This very important organization.
This very us here.
Our mascot could have turned out to be any old buddy, but I'm not disappointed at all
in this revelation of who he turned out to be.
This is the best possible outcome.
Really, that ending.
We've all got the blood of the Messiah within us.
That's right.
I did not expect for us to be this gold-pilled, but here we are.
Here we are.
Man, this is, this is great.
No, we're fucking like black, we're like, we're like black-pilled or green-pilled.
We're black-pilled.
Yeah, guts is the black pill, right?
We're black.
Dude, we're pro-pilled.
We are pro-pilled.
We're mics or videos.
We're pro-pilled to get pro-fessional money.
So, go to our pro-patriot.com.
Fuck whatever it's called.
Ben Saint.
Yeah.
No, patreon.com.
Look at those.
The pro-patriot name.
We're award-winning.
So, you just want to, I press one for a munchie?
Well, so that's it, folks.
Tokafushimi from Inari Kon Kon Koi Iroha.
There you go, that's our guy.
That's a podcast over.
All right, guys.
Man, I've got Afterglow.
I've got the Afterglow going.
All right, so let's move on to our actual topic for the day.
Wait, I want to point out one thing real quick if I can, Nate.
Yeah, sure.
Today, this podcast right here is the first time that Munchie and I
have been seen together in public.
Yeah.
That's right.
It's a big deal for me.
I said all of our secret sescapades.
Right.
You know, you know.
Sescapades.
Yeah, we've had lots of, we've had lots of sescapades
when nobody was looking, but now we're together in a podcast
on the internet.
It's a big deal.
You're really coming out.
It's our first time, yeah, talking.
Now when people fuck up our names.
That's so bad, Nate, you fucking sewer rat.
You guys, if you guys didn't have literally the same name,
it wouldn't be a problem.
But, Nate, I'm going to fucking kill you.
You're dead.
So monumental occasion, and by that, I mean, doesn't,
doesn't matter.
Don't worry about it.
All right.
So let's move on to our fucking topic and let's see how
this Munchie-Mum-Key who has same guy dynamic plays out.
Even I'm going to fuck up the names and I don't even talk
about myself in the third person.
Okay.
So our topic today is irony and sincerity.
Yeah, that's that's what it's going to be.
So let me read the actual question that our buddy
over on the fucking thing asked.
So our question was from atmanslayer0, and he asks,
at TP Crastinators, you could talk about the ubiquity of
self-deprecating humor on the internet and the rise of
wholesome memes.
So, okay, so he's not actually asking a question,
he's just giving us a topic suggestion.
So he's talking about wholesome memes and self-depreciating
humor, but I think the broader scope of what he's asking
is about irony, sincerity, you know, that whole, that whole
whole gang, that whole gang.
It's Seinfeld and how it's the best show ever.
Yep, yep.
And the, when I saw this, my first thought was that video
that some, some fuckboy on YouTube had made recently
about David Foster Wallace and, you know, irony and shit.
Yeah, who searched the problem with irony?
Yeah, it'll tell.
The problem with irony, that's right.
Then I'll have that motherfucker smug face with like the
stupid, like, towel.
The bandam.
You know, I watched that, I watched that video because
you pointed it out right before this podcast, and I was,
I was none too pleased with it.
I have a, I have a, I have a point of contention
with that video.
Oh, let's hear it.
Well, like the whole, or we could do it later.
Ah, the fuck it, who cares?
I think the problem with David Foster Wallace is that
infinite jest is way too fucking long.
well, it is supposed to be infinite, so isn't it really
too short?
That's, that's true.
Never ending story was too short.
Yeah, that was, they both lies.
Yeah.
Never ending story is neither late nor early.
It arrives precisely what it needs to.
It's also not a story, it's a movie.
They really shit the bed on that one.
Let me, let me, all right, so let me break down what
this is about.
So in the, in that video, because that's really what
interests me to talk about, it talks about David Foster
Wallace was talking about how the rise of, of post
modernism is sort of, they're, they're within that,
or they're components of it that celebrate the
destruction of like the cultural norms of the day.
So, you know, things like irony are celebrated in the
post modernist, you know, kind of art style that we see
today.
So things like Seinfeld that are sitcoms that make fun
of the wholesomeness and the, the sugary way that
problems get resolved on older classical sitcoms.
It's taking that and making fun of the whole thing.
And so in that way it's being ironic and that's, that's
what post modernism is.
Whereas recently we're seeing things like, like the
show community, even Rick and Morty.
And I, Rick and Morty I think is a really interesting
example because Rick and Morty is a very irreverent
show with a lot of irony laced throughout it.
But there was, and I think Jesse and me especially
do this a lot, we, we relate to the way that it, it is
fully cloaked in irony, but then when you dig down
into it and you just give it time, there's always a
core of emotion and like good vibes that you just
need to crack that nut and the, the, the nut is
flaky and delicious when you get to the core.
That was my, that was my contention with the video.
It seemed to be using Rick and Morty as an example
of the opposite, like a cynical show.
And I don't think so.
And it, it seemed like the whole video was sort of
giving off this false narrative of like there were
wholesome shows and then there was an era of cynical
shows and now we're getting back to wholesome again
when the fact is like we've always had both at the
same time and both have always been great in their own
ways.
Yeah, I think he definitely oversimplified, but we
can talk about the topics, you know, like the two
irony and sincerity outside of like the temporal
frame, you know, we can just talk about them in
general because I think, um, they're, they're
always going to be applicable like, uh, you know,
South Park, very, and it could, okay, because that's
the thing that, and this is what really is
interesting to me.
David Wallace was talking about how like irony is a
purely destructive force and that's what it is.
It takes things and it makes fun of them.
It shows how they're not important.
It points out how silly and ridiculous they can
be, uh, like, like Seinfeld does with like everyday
life in, you know, New York City or whatever.
Average like, uh, uh, getting to be middle-aged
man, living in a city, not so charmed as we
thought from all those fucking sitcoms of the
nineties and eighties and shit.
Uh, but, and I think that is a valuable tool, but
I personally am a big advocate for their being,
or at least I really enjoy when a story has,
like, it doesn't just break things down, but it
also builds something up.
Like, it does talk about how, okay, like, yeah,
living in New York City or whatever, like being a
Jew, not all it's cracked up to me, but, uh, but,
you know, like, like what Rick and Morty does,
like Rick and Morty is really the great thing,
because like, uh, the way that, uh, Rick, like in
one of the best episodes where he has that
relationship with a hive mind lady, what's her name,
uh, Felicity, Clarissa explains it all.
Yeah, I believe that was her name.
Uh, she, he has this like romantic involvement
with this, with this person and in, in contrast
to his normal devil may care attitude,
that episode is a really good job of showing
at the end how he like, even though he looks
like he's just like this fun loving guy who
doesn't give a fuck about anything, he actually
does like have some dependency on the
relationships he has and he feels a sincere
deep pain when like, she finally realizes that
like, you know, this guy is a destructive
force in my life, I need to be elsewhere.
And so, and then he tries to fucking kill himself
and it's, it's an incredibly emotional scene
that everybody loves and is, you know, one of
the famous ones from the show.
But the way that he's, he's like, that's not a
joke, like it's not a joke that, that Rick
tried to kill himself.
That is like a holy shit, like it is horrible
to be a human being who has these things
happen to him and we all experience it.
And so it's just like the super relatable
scene that I think is, is kind of, is one of
those teachable human experience moments,
you know, and uh, and that, that's the kind
of thing that I like to have at the, at
sort of the end of my arc of like comedy,
comedy, irreverence, and then at the end
it's like, oh yeah, you know, we're all,
we had a bunch of laughs, but there's,
there's some things that we need to think
about and seriously at the end of the day.
I'm sorry the mysterious winner entered,
but not every cartoon needs to have a moral.
I'm not saying they all need to, I'm just
saying that I really like what it does.
It's something that I like.
It's like a trope I like, but I think
that it's a tool.
I don't, uh, I don't agree that irony is
like inherently cynical or inherently like
not sincere.
I think that irony can be sincere.
I don't think they're opposites, because
like, have an example.
Yeah, like, um, like, uh, the room,
by the Tommy Wiseau movie.
Everybody sees it the first time,
and they, they want to like it ironically,
because it's so bad or whatever,
and so they're ironically enjoying it at first,
but then they're showing it to their friends,
and every time they show it to their friends,
they get that sincere enjoyment of like
showing this funny thing to everybody,
and they start to like it more.
And the next thing you know, you're having
parties, and you're all watching their
room together.
And the next thing you know, you're going
to a movie theater, and you're watching
the room in a movie theater, and it's like
an event with your friends, and it's no
longer like an ironic thing.
You're sincerely a fan of this terrible,
goofy, amazing film, The Room.
You know, I'm with you, dude, and I am
a huge Room fan.
Absolutely love the film.
Possibly my favorite movie of all time.
Yeah.
Um, but the thing is, and uh, oh boy,
this is going down a dark path.
Uh, I have to bring up, uh,
authorial intent.
A little bit, a little bit into this, uh...
Done, done, done!
It's just that, it's just that,
I wonder how important we should consider
when we're talking about like, okay,
like the message of a show or whatever.
Tommy Wiseau did not intend for people
to have that experience.
That is something that came from like the,
you know, the community that formed
around this like new understanding
of the work.
And Tommy Wiseau, like, now he's saying
that it's like a dark comedy, but at 100%
was not intended to be a dark comedy.
So those things, that's totally true.
I have a sincere, I legitimately love
that film and love the characters
in a, in a very real way, but it is not
what was like supposed to happen, you know.
So I just feel like the rules apply
slightly differently in a situation like that.
You know what I'm saying?
Is that fair?
Uh, maybe you're still gay.
I want to understand you.
If I could provide a more nuanced perspective
into this, I think I could really educate
you people on the true, the true meaning
of irony, I guess.
I want to agree with what Nate was saying
at the beginning.
One of these fucking dictionary thumpers.
I want to take it a step further and go
ahead and say that irony is, is a disgusting
bottom dwelling form of comedy.
And really irony and sarcasm is what,
it's, it's how 14 year old girls
communicate with each other.
So how can we as professional comedian
adults even consider irony to be something
that we should use in our arts, in our comedy?
I think it's really pathetic that we're
even discussing this.
Dumb, you're dumb.
That's like saying, that's like saying,
that's like saying a fart joke is always
inappropriate because it's low breath.
No, what monkey has never used irony or
sarcasm in his fucking videos.
I would never use irony.
I'm sincere.
I'm nearly on like a fucking higher plane
than us.
No, Monty knows what he's talking about.
I've always been wholesome in all my videos
and I kind of look down on anybody who
uses irony and sarcasm as a crutch for
their comedy.
Exactly.
This is funny because just and Nate
were being totally sincere.
I know.
And Monty and Monty would be totally ironic
and sarcastic.
I understood.
After that.
Woo!
Press one if you love Munchie and Monkey
separately, not the same person.
The same, the same guy, right?
Press one if you love that one guy.
No, damn it.
You know, speaking of Monkey and why I
hate him, and this is actually pertinent
to this topic, because I was having a
conversation, a debate with Monkey earlier
because I was watching one of his
Countdown to Suicide videos and he was
talking about, oh when Monkey's anime
reviews is over, I might just start a
series called Jimmy's Reviews so that
people know it's a more serious
reviews.
And I said, Monkey, you make me goddamn
sick.
First of all, coddling these parasites
by trying to make your channel more
accessible.
And second of all, how dare you put a
fucking a line of separation and say
this is the funny wacky satire videos
and these are the serious videos that
makes me so it makes me just just burn
with unbridled rage that anyone
would imply that there should be a
separation between the two.
You gotta, the best part about your
videos is that when there's a sincere
video, like an Elliot Roger video or a
bobo bobo video, that it's mixed in,
it's hidden in this sea of wacky
insanity with nothing to discern it at
a surface glance.
That's what makes it all the more
valid, even more valid than it would be
anyways, because you gotta have it
together.
You can't, I'm vehemently, violently
against the idea of making anything
accessible for these fucking rodents,
these leeches who watch the videos
and demand, no, you gotta take off your
mouth, you gotta have a human face,
Momke, you gotta be Jimmy and make
use for Jimmy.
Well, Jesse, is that mostly the reason
why you don't like the audience having
an easy time, like you don't want it to
be accessible?
Is that the only reason or is it just
part of the reason why?
I just plain don't like the audience, I
want them to be sad.
Alright, I understand.
I want them to not enjoy anything ever.
You know, that's, I see your point there,
and there's definitely something to be
gained by creating a danker cloud of
illusion to keep you fully understanding.
Maybe I'm completely misrepresenting
Momke's intention anyways, which I think
I am, but going with that asinine
example, I...
Yeah, if I can respond, Jess, I'm kind of
hurt because I think you're misinterpreting
really the point of all my videos.
As I said a second ago, I'm not trying to be
wacky or anything.
I've been sincere in every single video
I've made, so that you think that there's
such a line of distinction.
Oh, you're being ironic again!
I take back my apology!
You do get apology from me!
Fuck you!
You're trying to fucking satire me,
and I won't have it!
I invented satire, buddy!
This proves that irony is a purely
destructive force.
It corrodes the human soul!
Like about Hippo as the character
making his own like terrible videos that
are stupid because he's...
I love that idea.
But I was thinking of making it on another
channel, but I don't know whether
that's a good idea.
No, put it on Hippocrite.
I guess I should, but it's just...
Vito that, Vito that.
I am the number one advocate for Hippo.
The thing is, the thing is, I understand
there's an advantage just in general,
just for, I mean, I like it when
certain types of content are split up,
so I don't get annoyed when it's like,
you know, there's a guy I follow,
and then he's doing all this stuff,
and I'm like, yeah, I like this stuff,
and then he starts uploading stuff
that I don't like on that channel.
I'm like, well, okay,
it's just a...
I like separating channels.
I mean, we all have like multiple channels for things.
Yeah, but Hippo, what segment of your audience
wouldn't love a Hippo review?
Well, yeah, I mean, that's why.
That's true.
I guess to clarify my asinine point
about what I was saying about Mumki or whatever,
I don't even fucking remember what I was saying.
I just think that irony and sincerity
are both equally valid,
and they're all the more valid
when they can work in tandem
and be together as a delicious little stew,
as opposed to seeing it as opposites.
Well, I still have to disagree.
I have to go with Nate and say,
it's only valid and entertaining
if it has sincerity,
and if this stupid dumb cartoon
makes me cry at the end.
Otherwise, why would I even watch it?
Right, I see that you're making fun of me,
but you're not gonna get the nuances
of my point here, Mumki.
What I'm trying to say is that
what we're talking about here are two different things.
We're talking about two...
They're not opposites.
It's not like you can only have one or the other.
I'm talking about these are two tools
that every creator has in their toolbox
that they can utilize to whatever extents they want.
So it's like...
You know, when you're making something like
fucking a My Little Pony review,
like you can have a sincere opinion
that you're presenting in whatever way you want,
but you can also make fun of the fact
that you're watching this fucking show.
Did somebody say My Little Pony reviews?
It's me drowning in horseshoes.
Oh my God!
The original shitty, endless, just character.
A horseshoe good boy.
I...
Oh my God.
You know, that's...
Brony's are dumb and I don't like him.
Pope Corona is a guy he lives in my house, I guess.
Fuck you.
Goodbye.
Wow, that's real.
Nate.
Wow, you don't have to say never meet your heroes
because they'll always disappoint you.
But let me tell you, he did not disappoint.
That cameo was truly top game.
But Nate, real quick in response to your example,
I wasn't around during the dark times,
so please correct me if I'm wrong.
But aren't you doing a little bit of revisionist history there
saying, oh, I was watching ponies ironically, guys, all along.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You're thinking, you're not, you're looking at
in too black and white of a picture
because there was nuance here all the time.
I legitimately loved that show for around four seasons.
I legitimately loved it.
At the same time, I was also aware
that there is this perception of people who watch the show
as artistic retards.
And I am able to both appreciate the show
and love every single aspect of the show itself
while also acknowledging and laughing at myself
for just being a part of this cultural phenomenon
where people think that it's just funny and stupid or whatever.
I have always maintained, even back during my pony days,
that the My Little Pony fandom, for all of its
faults and flaws of which there are many,
nevertheless, is more based more in sincerity
than it is in irony.
The fans absolutely.
And I maintain that to this day.
And then I myself, there's nothing ironic about it.
I still like My Little Pony.
I'm not as up to date with it as I once was.
I don't care as much as I once did.
But I still like it, sincerely.
I still to this day will watch some of the episodes
and ball my fucking eyes out at the sheer majesty.
Fucking, I don't need to go through every episode,
but I love the show.
It is a great show.
Some of the episodes are some of the best I've ever seen,
literally, some of the best I've ever seen.
And that's it.
And at the same time, I also find it amusing that I, you know,
let's just make this podcast a clip show
of like all of our favorite My Little Pony episodes.
Remember the time when the cutie markers sayers
finally got their cutie marks.
That's the best episode of the fucking show.
That is the best episode.
But, Nate, I'm still a little confused, Nate.
Are you fucking serious?
If you're giving a genuine review over it,
like just because you acknowledge that some bronies are bad,
how is that ironic that you're reviewing it
if you're being genuine with it?
Okay, you're obviously just trying to confuse,
I don't know.
I don't know why you're playing dumb at this point
because you obviously get it.
What's the irony in giving a sincere review of something?
Okay, here's the thing.
This could all be easily explained if you watched,
I don't know, Phantom Reviews or K-Reviews
or any of fucking Jesse's videos.
But he's not a real PCP members.
So he would never do that.
You should have known, monkey,
when we handed you the sealed golden envelope
containing your invitation to the PCP,
you should have known to do your research,
go back to the sacred texts and the ancient volumes
and go through the playlist of all of our separate sagas
together and separately and watch everything.
You, Rube, there is-
I can say sincerely that I didn't realize that,
I mean, I knew bronies were like lambasted for being like gay,
but I knew that it wasn't true because it was just a good show.
So when I started doing the reviews,
I was just doing it because it was a thing
that people in the community did.
I didn't really think of it too much as like,
you know, wow, this is really dumb
because it's like, I don't know.
People have been reviewing games and movies
and stuff from their childhood for a long time,
things that aren't necessarily for them.
I don't know.
It didn't seem as any any weirder than like that guy with the glasses.
In the video that I made,
Keg reviews putting your hoof down.
It opens, the video opens with a scene of Keg
talking about how he is a high schooler
and how just that day he had smashed innumerable puts.
All right.
That's what happens at the beginning of that episode.
And then he spends like 10 minutes
reviewing a fucking My Little Pony episode.
At the end of that video,
he then reveals that actually this entire thing was a lie.
He is actually a complete nerd,
or he was because this is a flashback.
He was a fucking nerd who everyone calls gay
because he doesn't have sex with women.
And then he spends that he then,
he then sincerely celebrates this show in the context of this review
for, you know, he met this character Iron Will.
It made him a real man.
Watching this episode of My Little Pony
made this character Keg a real man.
That is a both sincere and ironic way
to appreciate and interpret this episode.
And if you can't see that,
I don't know what to tell you, buddy,
because I can't feel any clearer than that.
I look down on irony so much
that I can't even recognize it anymore.
Fair enough.
We all have our disabilities.
Some of the motionability to others.
I wouldn't expect a fucking simian
to understand complex human emotions and concepts.
I think when it comes to comedy,
I'm standing way up here on a pillar
and all you people using irony for jokes
are like ants to me.
I can't even recognize what's happening down there.
I'm standing on a pillar, then I'm standing on the...
Oh, yes.
The bedside dresser on the duvet in the mattress.
I'm standing on the mattress.
I'm standing down inside of a manhole.
Monkey is the all-time greatest comedian.
We know that because the most impressive joke he ever did
was pointing out that he only has five jokes.
Yeah.
Very impressive.
There's nothing ironic about that.
It was a sincere joke.
As we've seen here on this podcast,
he is a master of the joke of pretending to be retarded.
He really knocks that one out of the...
Is he a master of it, though,
or is he just sincerely retarded?
The fact that we don't know proves his mastery.
That's, you know...
I hope you guys are being ironic
because this is sincerely hurting my feelings.
This is the worst conversation ever.
Everyone's just starting to fucking out irony each other
and nothing makes any goddamn sense.
I haven't said anything ironic
because I'm the only good boy.
That's true.
Hashtag good boy.
Okay, but see, that's interesting.
We didn't get into the nuance,
but I wanted to clarify how before when I said that
like irony is a destructive tool,
that's not me criticizing it.
That is just me pointing out that what irony is
is making fun of something.
Which is a purely destructive act.
There is nothing being built.
I think making fun of somebody to be constructed.
It's like, could you call Dynamite a construction tool?
No, it's a demolition tool.
You could.
Yeah, you need...
Oh, shut the fuck up.
If you need to build a railway through a mountain,
you use Dynamite.
But that's exactly my point.
It is a tool you use to get rid of something
so that then you can come in with other tools
to build something up there.
So if I'm going around and I'm saying like,
oh, you know, women are all retarded and gay.
I'm saying that.
And then someone says like,
look at me, women are retarded and gay.
Look at that guy, he's so gay.
This is me mocking him.
That's me, you know, making fun of that guy
to destroy his argument with my hilarious joke.
Which is what he just said in a retarded voice.
So that someone then can later on suppose like,
you know what, maybe women aren't all retarded and gay.
And then one's like, yeah, I'm with that guy.
That guy would be an idiot.
But like, okay, the fucking Dynamite analogy.
Is Dynamite not still then valuable
and should be cherished for doing its job
into help create a better future?
Of course, which is why, yeah, we are nebulous topic.
Can we just talk about like what animes we like
some time on this fucking show?
Didn't this used to be a show about like fun stuff?
Jesse, you hated anime.
No, we do.
You hate anime more than anyone I've ever met, Jesse.
What are you saying to me right now?
Now all we do is have these weird circular philosophical
discussions about the fucking nature of art and reality
and our place in the universe.
And I can't take it anymore.
It's making me too smart.
My brain's gonna explode.
You're wind too intelligent for the PCP.
I'm gonna ascend beyond my mortal human body
before I wanted to.
I'm not done cooking yet.
If it happens prematurely,
it'll be bad for the universe.
The PCP is like Aang
when he was opening his eight chakras
and we're about, we're right at the stage
before that cosmic chakra.
We're right there.
We need to, we can't, we can't.
We're fucking asleep to a high level of Christ consciousness.
That's right.
We can't leave Katara just yet.
I'm not ready.
I'm too goddamn strong in this podcast.
Oh my god.
If we go too far, we will lose all attachments
to both earthly desires.
Which just means my piss has been released from my body.
No.
I can't stop it.
My cock is turning into a lemon pie.
The lies.
Do you think it would be good if we discussed that?
Now you know the truth.
I'm actually a level eight Christ consciousness bee.
That's why I'm so powerful.
Oh my god.
Get in the fuck out of here.
Before this goes to a complete clusterfuck,
I was gonna ask,
since all five of us have created things before,
should we talk about the ways in which we have used irony
and sincerity within the things we've created
that all of our loving fans watch and enjoy?
Please.
I don't want to start.
I already gave an example.
Yeah.
I'll give an example of the irony in my art
that I haven't made yet.
No, god damn it.
Hippo was saying something.
I want to hear Hippo.
Well, I was just going to say I'm not smart
and I don't know what I do.
I don't know whether it's sincere or ironic.
I just, I like video games and I say this is a good one.
That's perfectly fine.
I like the way you do things.
And sometimes you can't tell if it's sincere or ironic.
That's great.
I really like that.
I don't know either.
I'm probably sincere the whole time, but I don't know.
Remember, you're opening to the Driver 2 video
where it just shows you rocking out to that fucking song.
That is both funny because it's silly
and also I'm sure that you just like that song
because I fucking like that song.
Yeah.
So it's that kind of middle ground.
Well, I think it's just that I make fun of myself
because I'm lame, but when I do silly things,
it's not because I'm ironically enjoying anything
or I'm just trying to say, yeah, this is silly.
I'm just trying to say that I'm silly
and this is how I react sincerely to things that I like.
Like what in your other video for the Fire Emblem,
we're at the end.
Oh, guys, this is my favorite.
When you're playing all the Florina voice clips
and then at the end, you just make that face at the very end.
You're like, ooh, and then it ends.
I've watched that like 20 times.
This is my favorite.
I have a question in reference to Hippo's comedy
because I think a lot of the times he'll do a joke
that is intentionally really bad,
but like it's still really funny.
So does that count as an ironic joke
because it's bad on purpose
or is it a sincere joke because it's sincerely funny too?
There's a, I think there's two ways those happen.
One is that I write a joke and it sucks,
but I don't realize it until I'm recording it
and then in editing, try to make it funny by timing it right.
Other times, I don't know.
I think I'm just not good at making some jokes.
I'm not sure.
No, but I think even in improv,
you just, you say really dumb things in a funny way
on purpose all the time.
And it's really funny to me.
Yeah, you say a lot of stupid shit.
Yeah, and I think what we're saying is
we're going to kick you out of the PCP.
Oh, I think I start with Travis.
We're on a roll lately.
They're dropping like flies these days.
So we're down to just this five now.
Everyone else is dead.
The five's best going to be the end of Taylor.
So, I mean, did anybody have any specific ironic jokes?
I want to hear Jess give me his spiel
because he's very passionate about this.
I am a man with many a spiel, that is true.
You know, I think that, I think all my content
is pretty much completely sincere all the time.
I mean, maybe more than people realize,
like maybe like 300% sincere.
That's a lot.
I think, you know, like my message is sincere.
My everything is sincere.
The only thing that's ironic occasionally
is like my delivery is ironic.
But even when my delivery is ironic,
all the other stuff behind it
and swirling around it is still sincere.
I value sincerity a lot, a lot.
Wait, how did, I guess I'm just dumb
because I don't know what it means
to have an ironic way to tell something sincerely.
I don't either.
This is a dumb topic and I don't like it.
I don't get it.
Well, whatever.
For example, I mean, the only time,
I mean, the times when I like my videos
are like the most ironic, I guess,
are like stuff with the kayfabe commander.
Because like...
Well, those aren't sincere.
What the fuck?
Oh no, the message behind the kayfabe commander
is very sincere.
He's really strong.
He'll beat you up.
He's like the evil.
All of his opinions are undoubtedly the worst.
Right.
But like the philosophy behind those skits
when I first started incorporating that character
was because I was just genuinely so like worn out
from like years of like trying to do YouTube good.
That like with the kayfabe commander,
it's just like I just want this to be blatantly obviously
not like not even trying.
So like whenever you see the kayfabe commander
in one of my videos,
nothing involving the kayfabe commander
is ever scripted or written.
I just let him come out and fucking ramble.
And then I ramble and I always,
I deliberately put on this like bad acting,
acting because I think that in the past,
I've shown myself to be a somewhat capable actor
when I actually try.
But whenever it's a dumb skit like that now,
for me, it's more funny to just like blatantly put
like no enthusiasm in it.
Like, oh God, the fucking kayfabe commander,
he's here again or some shit.
Just like leave like flubs in and just have him over there.
Like, I'm gonna suck a thousand dicks today
and then beat you up and then suck more dicks
and beat you up again.
It's just, I love it when you do that.
Those are great.
Jess, we were talking about this very thing
on My Spyro Let's Play.
And you said that you're sort of trying to go
for a parody of people like Movie Bob
who would throw in just retarded skits
into their review videos
and just kind of playing off of that.
Yeah, exactly.
So I can see how irony is being both
constructive and destructive.
It's a sincere satirical point,
but it has to be delivered ironically
because that is the point, I guess.
Yeah.
And if you're a fan of those,
and if you're a fan of those terrible skits,
oh boy, have I got an extra terrible one coming soon.
It might be out in a time you hear this.
I kind of want to make skits that are sincere,
like actually emotional, like because most of the time
they're playful laughs, whether they're ironic or not.
Yee.
I don't know.
Dude, frankly, it's way harder to make sincere ones
than ironic ones.
Oh, definitely.
This is like a thousand times harder.
That's why Monkey so puts so much work in his videos
because he has to make everything so sincere and passionate.
Yeah, I work really hard to make sure
it's not like ham-fisted or corny.
I have to make everything as sincere as I can.
I mean, the production value on Monkey's anti-reviews
is just so fucking out of this world.
I'm surprised he has any free time to record the PCP.
I really don't.
He's just fucking hammering out shit, dude.
Well, Monkey's young.
He still has that work ethic that I once had,
that many of us, I'm sure, once had.
But he'll be cured of that soon enough.
Thank God.
You know, I was thinking...
My favorite Monkey universe character is Grandma.
She's...
There's that bit of sincerity, you know?
Where'd you get the Grandma mask, by the way?
Where'd you get that whole Grandma from?
I find them in parts.
I can't put together a whole one yet.
I went on Craig's list and I said I'm looking for a Grandma
for these videos and she volunteered.
That's awesome.
Excellent.
That's beautiful.
Wait, is that actually true?
Yeah, yeah, that's not my real Grandma.
I just found her on Craig's list.
What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Is that actually real?
Are you telling me that that being did not spring forth
from your furnace room?
I'm not gonna show my real Grandma all that weird anime porn,
should I just found some actress online?
Oh my God, I had no...
Okay, okay.
Wow, that's a bombshell.
Stop the meming for just a second.
Is that actually...
Is that...
Is that real?
Of course.
Oh, he's fucking with us.
He's fucking with us.
He's being too ironic right now.
I don't know.
I really don't know.
I already fucking strained the PCP.
I told you it's a destructive force.
It's like...
It's like my power level is so...
You know, hey, what ironic thing I think, Jesse,
is that I think over the years you and I specifically
have tried to make really good videos
and ironically, those were really bad YouTube videos.
Yeah, yeah, that's a...
Yeah, that's a true thing.
Don't make that mistake, folks.
Be a shale.
Be a hack.
Make garbage like monkey.
Monkey's doing it all right.
Monkey's kind of straight from the get-go.
Wait, so, Ben, are you...
I mean, I'm Nate.
Sorry.
Are you all right?
Wait, just go, Ben.
I am not a worm.
I am not the scum of the earth.
I am not a little piece of shit, all right?
You will never do that again to me.
You're just both so suck and similar.
You're just like the same person, baby.
Shut up, monkey.
I don't even like you.
All right, what's your question, buddy boy?
Are you saying you're not a hack fraud in every way, Ben?
Oh, I'm saying that I'm doing my best to become a hack fraud.
You know, I've been releasing your comic on time.
Seriously.
Wait, what?
You're not even releasing your comic on a fucking insistent basis.
Shut up!
I don't do comics.
That's not me.
I'm not a comic guy.
The only guys who are gay do comics.
The only guy who's a comic guy is Piccolo.
I don't.
Are you talking about that comic?
No, wait, that's NAMIC.
I fucked it up.
What's comic from?
Comic is the, well, comic was the...
God damn it, I don't remember.
I don't remember either.
Dragon Ball Z is gay, because it's from Japan.
It's from Japan, so it's gay, it's bad.
All right, I don't know what the fucking Nate's point was,
which was a good point before it got fucking derailed.
Yeah.
But fucking Piccolo and whatever.
Um...
Yeah, I mean, I fucking...
Like, I don't ever want a video on my channel ever again
that's over 10 minutes long,
because it's just the wrong way to do it.
It's bad.
Well, hey, doing it just at 10 minutes is good,
because then you could put an ad at the end,
and you gotta do that.
Like, some of the stuff I've been doing more recently,
like some of the better fuck videos
are like the Not A Review series.
Like, those are great.
Almost no effort goes into those,
and there are a million times better YouTube videos
than stuff I used to work on day and night for 40 hours.
I just didn't know.
I didn't know how to play the game back then.
I still don't, but maybe I'll learn someday.
My Kingdom Hearts videos are my attempt to do that,
and it's so easy.
It's so...
I didn't realize it could be this easy.
It's insanity, and it's what people want.
You know, it's what YouTube wants, at least.
It's crazy.
So, I guess sincerity is strong.
I'm still struggling with being able to not do big things.
It's just, you know?
I think we're growing, you know?
I think we're learning the game a little bit.
We're becoming pros on this pro-crastinators podcast.
You're witnessing it, folks.
It's funny.
You're witnessing a chrysalis bursting
into a beautiful boober fly with big, saggy tits.
Really great point, Phantom Horn.
Anyway, to continue.
SHUT THEM!
It's funny, because my comic I'm working on now
is fairly big, but I've always had the philosophy
that just a ton of small things is good,
and I like that more than big things.
That's why web comics with more or less daily releases
are quickly home stuck.
It was popular with that.
Release in one panel.
Well, I don't mean like that.
I'm not directly like Steven Bombs in the release schedule.
But having small, contained stories that go on
for just as long as they need to,
and then have a definitive ending,
that you can wrap up in a neat little bow
that has a nice cover and you would pick them
in a bookstore, I like that.
I used to want to make every video like,
I'm going to review this thing.
So I'm going to make a huge, in-depth, sprawling,
30-minute review analysis,
and I'm going to touch on every little,
tiny aspect of it in the ultimate video.
And because that's the way I approached making videos,
well, what happened is,
either the video would never get around to being made
because it would become too massive in the writing phase,
or I would miraculously get the video made,
and nobody would watch it
because it was a giant 30-minute,
non-marketable piece of shit.
The correct way to do it, I now understand,
is instead of making a massive video touching on everything,
you just make little videos about the specific subjects,
and you can make as many of those as you want.
You can make them in a fucking day,
and you can have hundreds of them out every day forever,
and everyone wants to watch them,
and that's how you become a real boy.
Yeah, it seems to be that there is still like a market
for huge videos,
but they have to be spectacularly huge
in order to get a lot of views,
like Mathematosis doing like a 40-minute review
of Mario 64, and then a review of every other Mario.
Like they have to be huge, or they have to be tiny.
You can't really sort of make a 30-minute, 20-minute...
You know, I was looking at some old documents of mine,
and looking at stuff I never finished,
and I found this old massive, massive,
Mass Effect 3 analysis that I wrote when it came out.
This giant, this rage-fueled tirade of a review,
and it was like a million pages long,
and it touched on everything.
Like, oh, the ending is bad,
and Tally's face reveal is bad, and this is bad,
but I never got around to making the video,
because it became too much.
I wrote too much, but now I'm looking at it
in my old documents, and I'm going,
you know, I could still make a video
about why Tally's face reveal still makes me mad,
or a video about why the ending still makes me mad.
I could chop it up into these little segments,
and it would love that Tally's face one.
Like, I could easily do that, and instead of one Mass Effect video
that nobody watches, because it's an hour long,
I could have 10 Mass Effect 3 videos that everybody watches,
because they're easy and accessible,
and brilliant and nice and fun,
and works better with the YouTube algorithm.
It's better in literally every way.
You know, I think I've been trying to do that with the Rayman.
Once I've finished part three,
any other big video is going to be in parts,
and then later I'll stitch it together into one video,
so it will come out slowly, but not too slowly.
Ooh, I like that idea of stitching them together later
into one video for the people who want to see it.
That's a good idea.
I agree with everything you guys are saying,
but I think the one needle in the haystack,
just specifically for you guys, is that it's the Patreon.
It's that you charge people per video.
So, you want to make something that's big and grand
to justify charging them.
If you make 100 small videos, you might have some problems.
You know what I'm saying?
I can confirm that most people don't care.
Well, they definitely don't want Jesse.
People have proved they will pay Jesse for anything.
It doesn't matter.
The good thing about Patreon is that,
as you make more videos in the month,
the people who've capped increases.
So, you can make eight videos,
and by the eighth video, you're not really ripping anyone off
because the only people who aren't capped
are people who are like $1 pledgers at that point,
so no one really fucking cares.
Anything I make is worth $1, so...
The people who are pledging $5 or $10
are only getting charged once or twice.
I feel pretty strongly about this.
There's some discussion I hear about what you owe
your patrons and stuff, but I really, truly feel
the responsibility, if I post a garbage video
and I charge for it, I sincerely feel
it is the responsibility of the patrons to watch that
and determine if it is something
that is deserving of their money or not.
And don't get me wrong.
There is a level of trust that you have to maintain,
but I'm just saying, this shouldn't be thought of as like,
I am like an icon of virtue, and as a patron guy,
I always make great shit.
And then if I break that contract,
it's like I have committed a grievous sin.
I don't like to think about it that way.
I like to think about it in terms of market forces.
Am I supplying a product that people are willing to pay for?
If so, they will give me money.
If I betray the market expectations,
I will be penalized because people will stop patroning me.
I just really don't like this whole idea
of lionizing the Patreon creators,
as if they're so perfect all the time.
When they're really just people trying to survive
doing what they're doing.
That's the anxiety I've had.
I haven't had a lot of people leave,
but there's been occasionally just one person
like go from five dollars to one dollar,
and that's enough to make me go,
oh no, I've ruined everything.
My reputation's gone.
I'm homeless now.
We should definitely add to all this discussion,
the caveat or the disclaimer.
Don't anybody unpledged from us ever?
Don't anyone?
Never.
Don't do it.
Don't unpledge.
We need your money to stay alive,
especially me.
I sleep in garbage.
My life is hell.
Don't unpledge.
Don't edit your pledge lower.
Don't do it.
I'll die.
Jess is a sewer priest and ghetto spiritualist.
He needs your money more than anybody.
Yeah, it's just like real priests.
But by the way, all of us, excluding monkey,
use irony to some extent in our work,
but we all sincerely want your money.
So please go into the most sincere Patreon in the world.
Yeah.
If you want to support this podcast,
PAPES, go to, I think the URL is going to be
patreon.com slash theprocrastinators.
There'll be a link.
Look out the screen.
You're going to be up for this video?
What?
We'll be up for this video.
It's going to be out for the last video, actually,
but it's in this one too.
Oh, so we're not going to pay?
Can you haven't even pledged yet?
Yeah, man.
The payments will begin if you people pledge,
which I know you will.
You wouldn't betray me like that, fam, would you?
Would you, fam?
You wouldn't get on Ben's bad side like that, would you?
Shut up!
You're on my bad side, dad!
Fucking bitch!
Now, if you're thinking folks at home,
if you're thinking, I can't afford to pledge
the procrastinators Patreon,
all you have to do is unsub from BenSaint
and put that money into the PCP.
Yeah, that's the way to do it.
We have been championing patreon.com slash BenSaint
for too long.
It's time to take our cut.
It's had a rebar reward for propagating the stuff.
Pay what he owe.
That's exactly right.
Now, as we round the one hour mark on my record here,
let's just talk about how much Seinfeld is the best ever.
Seinfeld is really good, and it's the best ever.
There we go.
Am I wrong in thinking that...
Well, you should definitely watch it, dude.
It's great, even now.
Am I wrong in thinking...
Should I start at act five or not?
You don't even know, because there actually is people like that
for fucking like season four,
because that's when the show picks up.
Watch from the beginning.
Yeah, there is a tiny bit of continuity,
and it's all great.
So there's like no reason to skip it.
There is a lot of continuity.
Actually, I've been rewatching it on like fucking like kissanime.com.
I go to put locker.
I wasn't put locker.
Fuck yeah.
Am I wrong, guys, in thinking that Lethal Aurora Mage,
or Mage, as you might know her,
did she learn English from Seinfeld?
I can't remember who was that or something else.
No, she's from anime or cartoons.
Somebody else I know learned English from Seinfeld.
That's...
I can't remember me.
I'm gonna be best friends with that person.
Post in the comments if you learned English from Seinfeld.
A straw poll.
Did we learn English?
Press one.
At all, not from Seinfeld.
Yeah, press one.
Press one.
A straw poll.
Are Jesse's Donald Trump tweets funny,
because Nate doesn't get them.
No, no, no.
I stand with it involved in my hilarious...
My groundbreaking Trump tweets.
Nate just doesn't get it.
He's a little baby.
I would say that it is true.
My complaint with them is that I do not find them funny,
and I find them annoying.
Nate, do we have any Twitter questions today?
No, no, I have one more point about Seinfeld.
From the age I was like one until I was like 10 or 12,
that was literally the only TV show I watched.
That's not a joke.
You didn't watch Will and Grace?
I thought that, you know...
I actually watched a bit of The Golden Girls,
but other than that, just Seinfeld.
Wow, amazing.
Is that because your family is big Christ fags?
No, it's because they're really big Jew fags.
They only let you watch Jewish, right?
Jew fags, right, okay, okay.
I feel like we completely got off the topic,
and so shall we just go to questions now?
There's a shit topic, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, let's go to...
No, I thought the topic was good.
I liked it.
Me too.
I'm saying that with all sincerity.
Yeah, the final final opportunity.
Anybody got any last points to make on sincerity,
irony, any of that shit?
I think if you use it as a crutch,
you should just kill yourself.
Yeah, that makes sense to me.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Good.
Yeah.
Okay, all right, I got questions here.
Now remember, everybody, go to Twitter,
follow at TPCrastinators,
and send us fucking questions throughout the week.
And when we record these on Saturday,
I always fucking tweet to send us questions,
and then we're gonna answer them here.
Well, we're sorry that these past two episodes
have been really, really bad.
I think it's because I've been on both,
and I'm leaving the PCP.
It's basically like this.
Okay.
So it's been a send off episode.
Hey, while we're plugging stuff,
can we talk about the Wiki
that everybody should go check out?
We did mention it, but feel free to mention it again.
I don't know what the website's called,
but go check out the Wiki.
It's procrastopedia.mirahees.com,
I want to say.
There'll be a link in the description.
I added it to the description for the last one,
and it'll be there from now on.
But yeah, everybody, go add to the Procrastopedia,
the PCP Wiki.
We got fucking shit.
We need troops to go in and add meaningful lore
to the various pages I just made,
the Action Giraffe page today.
We need to add more to it.
I made the illustrious Undertale 5.8.7 page,
and it's beautiful.
Is the Wiki gonna have cliff notes
of episodes of the podcast?
Yeah.
You can link to all the information that you provide.
I don't think I've seen links of what specific episodes
are about, but that could be a section
somebody could add, certainly.
It could be whatever we want to add to it,
or whatever people want to add to it.
I think they should add links to the references,
otherwise it's too much of an in-joke.
Nobody's really going to get it coming from the outside.
I guess.
I like that feeling that you need to jump in and ride
for a while before you understand what's going on.
Yeah, but if we keep talking about a joke
and somebody wants to go see what the fuck that joke means,
and then the Wiki page for it is a bunch of more in-jokes,
they're not going to learn a damn thing.
If we have a list of the memes and in-jokes,
and then a link to whether it originated.
Right.
It should work like TV tropes, where there'll be a thing
and it'll be like, oh, Undertailer,
I don't know what the fuck that is.
Oh, I go to his page, and now I know all the lore.
There you go.
That makes sense to me.
And appearances, they can watch the episode
if they want to know where the fuck he came from,
any of that shit.
Yeah, that's a cool idea.
Well, my backstory is very long and complicated.
Let's try this in the Unteller 5H7 podcast.
I was a wee boy, and get the fuck out of here.
Get out, stop recording raps.
This is my house.
Get out.
OK, what are the questions, Nate?
OK, here we go.
We got some decent questions here.
So here's the first question by Atalexus.
There's a lot of A's and S's here.
But Atalexus says, should we feel bad
if we ask terrible questions?
Yes.
Yes, buddy boy.
And there's a second part in parentheses that says,
and if yes, what can we do to fix it?
So here's the person asking constructive questions.
I would say ask more specific ones
that let us answer with more,
like put a little thought into what you're going to hear
when you ask your question.
If you ask like, what do you guys think about
fucking Undertale?
But that's a whole.
Well, let me tell you what I think.
Let's shut up Undertale.
We made a whole podcast about Undertale.
It was the first one.
Yes, there's definitely enough Undertale-centric
media from us to ask for fucking lifetime.
There's not enough.
That would never be enough.
Are you aware, Jesse, that it's become a thing
where we're now just referring to video games
are Undertales?
Dude, I played the best Undertale today.
It was so fucking good.
It was like this fucking first, first shooter.
Well, that's the meme that everyone can be on board with.
That's right.
It's like how in the South they call all pop and soda,
they call it all Coke.
They call it exactly like that.
Go out there and play some Undertales today, guys.
Undertale Five Ground Zeroes.
Okay, and here's another question by at Joseph Ingman.
At T.B. Crasonators, what's the coolest fight
you've ever been in?
So I know we're all men of the streets.
We're getting a lot of brawls,
but this guy's asking for the coolest fight.
When I wrestled a penguin on top of an ice cream.
Oh boy, he took it that direction.
Of course I would.
Have you ever thrown down with anybody, monkey?
Yeah, the best fight I've ever had
was in the the procrastinator's discord
where I was fighting with Jess
about whether or not he has an ego.
That was pretty good.
Oh boy, that was a legendary brawl.
Yeah, I said that he didn't, and he asserted that he did.
That was just you being a dumb guy.
Is that what you call it?
When you punch him out in the street,
that's not a fight.
That's him being a dead guy.
Exactly.
Because he's dead, because you killed him.
I've never just been in a fight.
I've only been in, there's a dead guy next to me now.
That's great.
He just did dead at me.
I often beat up my friends as a sign of love,
and that's not a joke.
It's a mutual wrestling, like we do often.
You might have heard, it's called gay sex.
Is that what you do to establish dominance over the group?
Yes, that's what Ben and Diddy do.
Yeah.
Wait, wait, wait, Ben, you've had sex with Diddy?
Oh, you know, you should ask Ben when he comes on.
You know, he's not here this episode,
but maybe next time we'll be here to answer that.
Everybody, watch this animation about Ben and Diddy being gay.
The point is that I definitely don't have an ego.
Anyone who thinks that either is misunderstanding me,
or misunderstanding what is meant by ego,
and is a complete retard who should not exist
and should kill themselves, the end.
What's the name of that animation you made
of Diddy and Ben being gay?
I'm gay.
It's called I'm gay.
It's on the Give and Take channel.
Yeah.
Wait, what was this?
What video is it?
Oh, okay, I remember now.
The plot of gun.
Yeah, the best animation I've ever made.
It's the video I've ever made about you, retard.
I remember, I remember.
Okay, here's another question.
Okay, at Kinkuck, I think it's Kinkuck.
I don't know, it's all K's.
Is that Kinkrat's cousin, Kinkuck?
Basically, yeah.
Okay, I'm speaking of Kinkrat.
Go check out his PCP Wiki page.
It's really good.
That's true.
Made by, I don't know, Mysterious Forces.
Mysterious Forces came together to make that Wiki page,
and it's glorious, and all the information on there is true,
and has sources to prove what it says.
Yep, the mysterious Rhino editing
everyone's Wiki page in secret.
I learned something new about just every day.
God, who is he?
Who is that fucking Rhino?
No one will ever, that's the new mystery.
Now that we've solved the mystery of the PCP guy,
the next mystery is who the fuck is that Rhino?
We read farther in that manga,
there's actually a Rhino in there,
wearing a mask and a fedora.
Can we do a memes that need to die part two?
Oh my god, dude, what if there was a video where,
I mean, Colt Corona, I know he's real,
but what if he was wearing a horse mask,
and he took off the mask and underneath it
was the mysterious Rhinoster?
Oh my god, no!
It's my nightmare.
If that would be a nightmare.
And actually, the next question I was about to read,
Kink Cuck asked,
what will happen now that the origin of the PCP guy
has been rediscovered, or has been discovered,
now mysterious Rhino is their new mascot.
He's a new mystery guy, there you go.
The mysterious Rhino is our new mascot.
We put him in the corner of our thumbnails
and instantly all of our subscribers leave.
We have patrons in the negatives, we owe people money.
Oh, I wish you could pledge negative amounts to patrons.
Hey, but why do I want to know right now,
you fucking hacks?
Has he been on the side of the screen the whole time?
Yeah.
Oh my god, I don't know.
Oh, get out of here!
Get out of here, mysterious man!
I don't know what you're giving me out,
dude, get the fuck out of here.
Wait, wait, okay, so why do I want to know
from you fucking hacks?
Jess, tell Colt Corona my question.
When are you just going to invite the fucking Rhino on?
To the animal cast?
For an animal cast?
That's a good question.
Well, maybe on animal cast.
I just don't want him on like a people cast
among civilized folk.
He's uncontrollable.
He doesn't belong in society.
He tried to integrate into society once.
He had a whole thriving business.
He was a gynecologist.
They called him Rhino the gyno.
It was a whole big thing.
He got fucking disbarred.
He lost his license to practice medicine
because he kept molesting and raping with his horn.
And it was just a whole, whole big thing.
So that didn't pan out.
He was homeless for a long time.
You know, I found him on the streets.
I offered him a job.
I helped him out a little bit.
And he's been, he owes me a life debt now.
He won't leave me alone.
I just want him to go away.
But he thinks he owes me something,
even though I'm a white man
and he considers all of us evil satans
who deserve to die for some reason.
He's still, and he's fucking, you know,
and the last time I heard from him,
he, you know, he got a gun
and he went into like a town square
and he started shooting people.
And they never caught him.
So I don't know.
I don't know, man.
Maybe he's back home in Africa.
Ray belongs.
I long for the day he returns.
He never does.
Here's another question.
This is, this is more of a challenge than anything,
but I, I find it interesting.
So at Cephirzer asks,
Hey Tbc, can each one of you
say something good about your fans
other than giving you money?
That's a tough one, dude.
That is a tough one.
I can.
I like all my friends.
I mean fans, which I don't have.
But I was confused in sentence.
Fuck you.
I don't like them.
They're mine.
I don't like them anymore.
So you like them.
Okay.
You like them.
All right.
Well, I guess generally I feel like
the comments I get on my videos
are less terrible than comments
that any of you other people get.
So I guess they're good commenters in general.
If I could be sincere as I always am
and never anything else,
the best parts of probably my life,
the last few months have been when
somebody has read my book
and they'll send me like a really in-depth,
several paragraph long analysis of it
or just telling me how they liked it.
So that sort of thing like really gets to me
and I really enjoy that if that answers the question.
That I think does.
That's a nice thing.
Jesse, say something nice.
You know, I got one actually.
Maybe you'll, I guess what Mumki said is also true.
Occasionally, once in a blue moon,
I'll get like a really long thoughtful comment
on like a video of mine that says like,
oh, this touched me in a special way
and here's why you resonate with me
and I like you a lot and blah, blah, blah.
And those feel okay, I guess.
I don't know if they're worth it.
You know what it is?
If they're worth the rest of the fucking shit show.
But you know what the best thing is about any commenter
is when they're actually sincere in that comment.
That's, yeah, so it's sincerity.
Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey.
The fucking code, there we go.
Like how much do you enjoy when they're like,
lol, you such a fag, headless Jess, lol,
I speak your language, dude, get it?
You're a culture fag.
I don't enjoy that, Nate.
I don't, I don't think I enjoy that very much.
The irony is very destructive
and anything that's not sincere,
I just banned from the comment section
because I'm a big man.
Yes, exactly.
Monkey's trying to be ironic,
he's trying to have a goof on me,
but I'm completely sincere in that sentiment.
I am a big man and I will ban you
for being anything less than sincere.
Fuck you all, I take back anything nice I say
about any of my fans ever, you're bad and die.
Can Jess's new title be officially big man?
Hashtag big man.
And I just like to say that I think the only nice thing
I can say about any of my viewers
is if you're watching my content,
you obviously have great taste,
so there you go, there's your compliment.
Press 1 if you're a fan of Munchy.
One, fan of Munchy.
Press 2 if Jessie should shit himself.
Fuck!
Ah locals, fuck you, do this to me!
Fuck you, do this to me!
I'd like to point out that Munchy
has literally pissed on stream
And is number one and Jesse every time shits himself and is number two now. So there you go
We got number one number two. We uh, there's no other than the basic b-box
Is that is that vomit or is that I mean what is what is number three?
I think it should come because I want to make hippo come. I don't discriminate against women who can't come women should be
able to produce number three, right?
Any more questions nader, can I just
For you, buddies everybody press three for us all the twiddle or clits
Is that mage wait, did you just say that's mage? No, that's what you said. That's your clitoris talking to you right in the night
If an Asian girl is masturbating is that beans and rice? Yes. Yes, it is in our sideways vagina
So she has to reach over to the side
I am your clitoris I control your brain stemmed out to go have what protected sex with strangers
I didn't make taxpayers pay for your abortion
Wait, is that Bernie Sanders as everyone's clit?
Bernie Sanders is on Eric's clit
As Bernie Sanders as a clit at deceived eel asks, what do you think of these fans that worship everything that you do?
I hate them. I don't I don't get that myself. I don't really I know well
I guess it's better than it's better than not worshiping everything. I do I suppose but neither is preferable
Yeah, I think if you I mean people say they worship everything you do
But they're probably normal in that they enjoy
Stuff and sometimes they don't enjoy it, but they just want you to know that they are a fan
Yeah, you know what I take it back. It's good and everyone should do that. I forget what I said before
It's good. Everyone should like everything I do
I agree unless I don't like it because then it's objectively bad because I'm the author and I have the final say on it
Well, let me tell you I get a little peeved at these guys who say they love everything and then don't give me money on
Patreon gotta tell you
sincerity I doubt that patreon.com slash best guy ever there you go
I don't know fuck the rest of these questions. That's enough. We've answered enough fucking questions
Thanks everybody for sending them be sure to send us more at TP Krasnators fucking
Dude, fuck you. Everybody fuck you. There you go
All right, so anybody you have any closing points. No, you don't okay. That's great. Thanks for listening everybody
We will see you next time for the PCP. I've been munchie
That's yeah
Well, I've been munchie as well. I have I'm munky aka munchie the same guy. I'm the same
Man, I'll just
I couldn't hear you over Jesse shitting himself
It's like red con to all over again another quality episode of the PCP. Thanks for listening everybody
Bye
Yeah, it's quite the burden. It's a hard knock life being a genius