Hello, everyone, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm the best guy ever. What do we got going on here? We got Hippos here.
Hello, everybody.
We got Lethal Aurora Maid.
Oh, shoot. I'm second. Hi. Hello. I am here.
Indeed. I'm alive. We've got Ben Saint.
Tom Oliver.
Hey. Oh, let's go.
Oh, hey. And of course, Endless Jess.
Oh, fuck. Hello. It's also me.
Oh, man. Well.
What a cast of characters. What a motley crew.
This is a motley crew.
So, I posted a question, and I can't pronounce it because pronunciation is part of the question.
So, I want you guys to bidet it.
It's pronounced bidet.
It's pronounced by debt.
Anyone ever use a bidet?
I hope to one day. It's a dream of mine to own one.
Actually. Okay. Funny story about a bidet.
So, the house I live in, there used to be a guy who lived here,
who we called Little John, and Little John had bidets,
and he installed bidets on every toilet in the house.
Bidets for days.
Yeah. And so, we do have bidets, right?
Like, they are on every toilet.
But I tried it one time, and I hated it.
I thought it was, like, horrible.
It was like a powerful, concentrated stream of water that shot right at your anus,
and I don't like it. I do not like it.
I wonder about the cleanup. Do you have, like, a towel?
Like, how do you, I guess, toilet paper?
I assume you would just use toilet paper.
I mean, I never got good with it, right?
I never mastered the techniques.
Yeah.
So, we have them, and I don't like them.
Maybe I should give it another shot.
Another shot.
Suddenly, bidets.
They're in the general sphere of anything involving my asshole is gay.
Yeah. I was going to say, that's pretty homo-adjacent, if you ask me.
It's not, though.
It's not that it's gay.
It's just that it was like, oh, god, wow, what, no.
It feels bad.
This raises the old question of, is a man getting pegged by his wife, let's say, is that gay?
I mean, there's no man in the way.
It's not gay. It's just sad.
I actually wanted to mention this the last time this sort of thing came up,
because the whole, is it gay?
I know it's a meme, partially, but people do ask these questions.
And it's always stupid, because gay is a sexual preference.
It is not a physical action.
Like, any physical action can be anything, but your perception of it is your preference for the same sex.
That's what it means.
Touching a foot can be just as non-sexual as it can be sexual.
So, yeah, I can see what you're talking about.
Let me make an argument for why I kind of think it is gay, even though there's no man involved.
But the pegging is approximating or simulating an act that naturally could only be performed by another man.
Surely, we're not comparing the act of literally getting fucked in the butt
to just splashing water on it to keep it clean from poopies.
No, I don't think a bidet is gay.
I mean, it could be.
But I think getting pegged by your wife is kind of gay.
If the pegging thing isn't gay, we can surely say that the bidet is not gay.
So, you know, I'm using that as a starting point.
I think the getting pegged kind of is gay.
I think it's kind of gay.
I think getting pegged by your husband is definitely gay.
Well, of course.
Unless you're a woman, well, I guess that's not a good point.
I didn't think of it that way.
I think it's not gay unless you think it's a guy, unless you think it's the same sex.
I don't think so.
If you just concentrate really hard on it being something else, then it's not gay.
I think even if you're not into guys, I still think it's kind of gay to get pegged.
That's the thing, though.
Not if there's anything wrong with that.
Ah, Jerry, she had man hands.
This leads to another question.
Does that mean, like, food is gay?
It's also approximating dude parts?
I mean, I just said, like, gay is a sexual preference.
Preference for the same gender as you.
I'm glad that right off the bat, we're getting down to the real issues that matter in the world.
Man, these issues are too complex.
Why don't we all just, everyone in the world just say,
fuck it, we're all gay, and then we don't have to think about this anymore?
We're everyone's gay.
Hey, I think that's the big brain thing to do now in 2019.
We've concluded this.
Everyone's on the gay spectrum a little bit.
I don't think food is necessary.
It probably mostly is gay, but I don't think it's always gay.
Okay, so surely you'd say that, like, the whole man getting pegged by his wife.
Again, that's, like, partially gay.
Obviously not, like, full gay.
Well, we're all about a wife getting pegged by her wife.
Yeah, obviously.
It's not as gay as it's less gay than getting pegged by a guy, obviously.
But what about a wife getting pegged by her other wife?
I mean, that's still gay, but woman gay, which isn't real gay.
I think that would be straight.
That would be straight because, like, the phallus thing is like...
Oh, okay, well, then it's straighter.
It's straighter than not pegging each other, but it's less straight than getting pegged by a husband.
Can a woman be pegged?
We've got to draw up a graph here.
We've got to just, like, put all these in, like, quadrants.
Since we're talking about gay things...
When a woman gets pegged, isn't she just getting fucked in the ass?
Isn't that not pegging anymore?
Is there a distinction?
Is there a distinction there?
It's still gay if a woman's getting pegged.
Is there a distinction in the nomenclature?
The only pegs I care about are clothes pegs, to do the laundry and to put the clothes pegs.
Since we're talking about gay things, I want to mention a thing.
Double-decker, Doug and Carole, this anime, that's kind of a little bit gay, but not really.
Do you want to tell them our secret mage?
Yes, I want to share the secret.
I'm going to reveal the secret.
I showed Ben this anime, and although we haven't finished watching it,
he liked it, and I'm so happy.
We got, like, six episodes in.
Oh, no, Ben watched the anime.
And it was... I didn't...
Yeah, I actually was enjoying it.
It was actually pretty good.
Belie, I know, right?
I know, sad.
It was fun, though.
It is, it was.
Like, that's why...
What is the anime?
Give me the picture.
It's called Double-decker.
Double-decker, Doug and Carole.
Yeah, it's about cops in New York?
Question mark, question mark, question mark.
San Francisco?
I don't know, they're in some...
Oh, Maple?
I think it's like an American...
It's like a Japanese sort of...
It's sort of like...
If you took the character designs from Persona, and instead of a school murder mystery,
you put them in an American style...
Or the Japanese approximation of an American-style buddy cop sort of action drama.
And then you gave someone a big anime gun with a cool, like, 3D...
Like, oh, I'm charging up my gun, and I'm shooting my gun at the end of the episode.
Like, that kind of thing.
Now, is Digimon transformation happening?
Is gun a euphemism, or is it an actual gun?
No, it's...
He has a...
We were just talking about gay shit, so excuse my confusion.
He has a secret science gun that counteracts the effects of a drug
that turns people into monsters, not unlike Joy and Lisa.
He has a secret gun that counterfeits people turning gay.
So it's a magic gun.
Where did he purchase that?
I think he got it from the police department, so there you go.
Well, all right, so I guess it's a secret to the other people, but not to the police.
Just made to have answers.
It's similar to the police department.
It's called like...
Right, right, it's like a secret branch.
Yeah, it's like a sister branch of the police.
Okay.
That deals specifically with dealings with that drug, because that drug,
turns people into literal monsters.
So...
Yeah, dude.
It changes the human genome.
Sick, I love blood.
That's the way to do it, if ever there was one.
Hey, I've got a fear, a deep-seated fear and insecurity I want to discuss
based on the Miamath of an episode I just released of Green Screen Memes.
And basically...
Saw that on Twitter.
Yes, yep, it's out.
It's good.
Here's the thing, though.
When you are...
I consider myself a pretty funny guy.
I think I've got some japs and some jokes.
Oh, I'm laughing.
Yeah, indeed.
It is so...
Okay, with this video, more than others, but I feel this a lot.
It is truly terrifying to me.
The idea of releasing something that I'm trying to make funny,
but to have it not be received as funny.
This haunts me a lot of the time.
So where's that gonna happen?
Wait, what happened?
I stepped away for a bit.
What happened?
I'm sure you can relate to this, Jesse.
It's my deep-seated fear of trying to be funny and failing.
And it is just...
Oh, God, if that ever happens, I'll die.
I'll kill myself.
Thank God it hasn't happened yet, to my knowledge, indeed.
Everyone says this, right?
But, you know, they can't all be gems.
No one's gonna succeed 100% of the time.
So even if you're funny, even some of the time,
I think people will generally forgive you if sometimes you fail.
You know what I mean?
That's definitely, I think that's one of the most everything in life.
I think that depends on the age of your audience.
Young people expect to be laughing constantly, or else they'll kill themselves.
Well, you know, I mean, it's fair to consider your audience, I guess.
I've always heard, like, you listen to comedians talk about being a comedian,
and they always say, like, everybody bombs sometimes.
Once in a while, even the grits go out there and bomb.
But like, so here's the thing.
I've done stand-up two times, and neither time I bombed.
So like, if I never do it again, I'll be the only comedian I've ever bombed.
Yeah, yeah, perfect batting average.
Just leave now, you've done it.
I just retire, I'm done.
I'm the greatest comedian who's ever lived.
This is the issue, though.
I mean, okay, so like, when I'm normally making like a video or whatever,
so like, this is in the context of like, the green screen meme video I just released.
So like, haha, like, Filthy Frank did it.
You know, other people have done it.
I'm like, this would be funny.
Jeremy did it.
Jeremy did it, indeed.
So these people are like, you know, really funny.
And I'm like, I did this, I did some goofs and gaffes,
and I'm looking back at it, and I'm like, this is not as funny.
This is like, kind of funny, but like, but the thing is, I have to release a video,
because it's me and Mavva.
I have no choice.
And I don't want people to like, I'm not of a negative perception of the video.
It's like, I go into it and releases, and then someone says like, Nate,
you're no, you're no Filthy Frank.
And I'm like, um, okay, fair, fair, but I bet, I bet that in general,
this video will go around and some people will have some positive experiences of it.
And any potential, like, like, it's not as good as the best who've ever done it,
will be overshadowed by what good it does do in the larger, you know,
in the larger ecosphere of video creation.
And so I'm, I'm hinging my will on that.
And like, in general, when it comes to work being produced,
and this is kind of the spirit of me and Mavva, and I don't know,
and we ag want everything I do to force me to get stuff out.
So I don't obsess about it.
It's not worth just sitting around and being concerned about
and worrying that like you're going to bomb,
even if like this video turns out to be hated and despised or whatever.
Like it's just one video of many put out during me and Mavva.
I did that fucking Sopranos ASMR video who asked me a Mavva.
If there was every forgotten video in the best guy ever catalog, it was that video.
I certainly don't remember it.
Indeed, no one does.
And I can't blame it.
See, Nate, you have the perfect cover here because if this video does bomb,
you can just be like, well, I only did it in 24 hours.
You know?
I mean, that's true.
That's true.
You have the perfect cover.
But like, that defense, that defense is like, if someone,
like if you're arguing with someone as to like why you're not shit,
then like that's fine.
But that's a whole different thing from like
getting people to think you're funny in general,
because you can't debate them one-on-one and explain your situation.
You've just got to be funny and give them a positive pressure.
Humor like anything else is subjective.
So if some people don't find it funny, you're just like, well, that wasn't to your taste.
Like, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You got your bases covered here.
This was a prime time to experiment.
Look that another way.
You will always fail because someone will always not find it funny.
I mean, of course, of course, that's true.
And I don't know.
I'm not trying to say that I'm like overly concerned about it,
but it did get me thinking because like I do think about, you know,
I mean, I was thinking certainly about like the filthy Frank clock and like
but to think about it from another way, like that filthy Frank clock thing,
like sure, it's funny, but it was just some retarded shit.
He probably just had a broken clock around and he didn't like have some grand plan
to make it be like, you know, this thing that gets used all the time.
He was already a very successful guy, obviously.
So people would like it no matter what.
And here's another thing.
I don't know.
Here's another thing to consider, like all those green screen memes,
like their hilarity is reinforced by the context that you know them in.
So like, I think I think if we just saw the filthy Frank clock
of devoid of context now, we'd be like, huh, okay,
it's all the memes that it's used for that make it great.
That is absolutely true.
You know, it's all kind of just like the fact that it's filthy Frank doing it.
True. Very true.
I mean, what can you do about that?
You know, the filthy Frank is like famous man.
He's like the mainstream green screen guy that is everywhere that like broke into the
into the world.
But you know, who's the true connoisseur of the green screen,
the true champion of the green screen meme is Jerma.
Jerma put out a green screen video that was like he did it for like five hours.
And then like, yeah, it's a huge stream.
And he did like every possible like action and thing like reaction possible.
When I finished it, I felt so deeply and he made it for the purposes of like
having his followers make films with it.
Right. Right.
And it was so robust and great.
I one of the main things I felt as I was like editing and finishing was like,
oh, there's so many reactions like different types.
I wish I'd put really I skewed mostly towards the like negative reaction of various stripes
towards the thing on screen that I am referring to.
Like that's the vast majority of it.
And like that's fine.
But I wanted there to be more like positive ones that could be used in funny ways.
I don't know.
Yeah, I'd be like so scared that like I jump in front of the green screen and go,
this guy is a stupid piece of shit.
And then someone just put me behind me.
And it's like, oh, no, why would you do that?
I mean, I'm thinking about it now.
I mean, just I guess I was taken to the extreme.
Like you could take any of these kinds of things.
And like, I don't know, you could put it to like some horrible like terrorist footage
and have just be in me like, like, haha.
Epic joke, my dude.
I just had the perfect idea.
I mean, this is the thing I came up with like years ago when I was doing like the green screen
like stupid shit where I would you get this video from you, Nate, you take the same video
and you put in the background and you offset it by about 10 seconds.
Oh, yeah.
And so you're just reacting to the last thing you did.
Oh, that's good.
I will come out of that one looking rosy.
Let me tell you because I'm roasting guys in this in this clip show.
Well, that's it.
These are my thoughts on comedy and green screen memes.
Ladies and gentlemen, please enjoy.
I did.
Savory.
Well, speaking of Mia Maffova and speaking of having thoughts on things,
what about that final fantasy seven trailer that came there?
There's a topic.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, I haven't seen that yet.
I haven't.
Well, I mean, I haven't watched Nate's video yet because I was like, maybe I'll do a video.
So I didn't want to watch Nate's first and pepper it.
But since we're on the fucking podcast, what did you think?
Well, okay.
So first of all, there was the initial sinking in my stomach when I first saw it that,
oh no, it's still happening.
It hasn't been canceled.
Of course, though, that was the initial motion.
I had almost forgotten.
Beyond that, I mean, there were some things looked cool.
Like my second reaction beyond that was like, oh, it's cool to see final fantasy seven
like looking nice, which it does.
I actually thought it was pretty reassuring for the most part.
Right up until the end, where fucking Sephiroth shows up for no fucking reason in the reactor.
I made a big screed.
I said a big thing about like, no, no, no, no, you don't understand.
Sephiroth does not show up on final fantasy seven until so far later to like build him up
as an antagonist of like mystery and suspense and shit.
Like I get that like, because it's 20 years later, you can't really have Sephiroth be a
surprise anymore.
Yeah, yeah, but you can though, just like, because the eyes will be hungry.
Like it's like narratively and like interesting.
It would just feel better to like, even if you know, if you've seen a movie before
and you know what the monster that he comes out like, I don't know, like the thing or something,
you know what the thing is.
But watching the movie from the beginning, the suspense is still built because it's just
good film.
It's just good film.
Maybe, I mean, perhaps this is a more cynical calculation by Square Enix that like,
they just want to start putting Sephiroth in promotional art.
I mean, in every way, I think this is a mistake.
If they're doing it, I can't stop them, whatever.
They're doing this like episodic release as far as we know.
I think that was confirmed recently too.
The only way that it could be acceptable to me is if they're just doing like a thing
where they're expanding on clouds like mental episodes and he's hallucinating Sephiroth.
I mean, that's definitely what they're, okay, this is the thing.
Cause like FF7, to this day, I'm pretty confused as to exactly what the implications are of what's
going on inside clouds head when we get the like black screen, white text at various times.
And like we know Sephiroth is involved with like Genova connection and stuff going on.
But like, frankly, this is, this is kind of my other point I made in my video.
Like I love the ambiguity and I like not knowing what the fuck's going on because it makes the
game feel better.
And do I think that a bunch of like, I don't know, I don't think there's anyone in the world
who like really is served by trying to fill in every possible detail in a story.
I think that in general, you're better off leaving a bunch of stuff to the audience's imagination.
I think there's a difference between something being to this day confusing and something being
open to interpretation, like it could be this.
Well, like I said, I know what's going on.
Sephiroth is communicating with cloud like through Genova connection.
But like it's presented in such a mysterious way that like you won't know that.
But now you will in the remake because Sephiroth's right there.
I mean, like there are people who don't actually actually, there's probably a ton of people who
if they played following 57 for the first time right now, they'd remember the bombing mission.
But they'd forget that during the bombing mission at the very beginning of the game,
cloud has one of his psychotic breaks because we all kind of forget that like a lot of FF7
is just dealing with how mentally fucked up cloud really is.
We just think about, oh, the buster sword. Oh, we fight Sephiroth.
You forget about like the horror element and the body horror element of cloud,
literally losing control of himself and it's fucked up and it's scary and spooky.
And like, I mean, I really hope they preserve that element.
But I just think they'll lack kind of the delicate touch that's required.
I'm also really worried that they're gonna do like the fanwanky like arch nemesis thing with
Sephiroth that they've been doing. Of course they are. Of course they are.
Even in the trailer, he shows up at the fucking bombing mission and immediately refers to cloud
by name. And it's like, oh my God. It don't say that. Don't call him cloud. You don't care about him.
Cloud, it literally isn't important right now. He literally means nothing to Sephiroth.
Like in the game, like yeah, like cloud is kind of obsessed with him because he's scared of him.
I guess he did kill Sephiroth. I guess he is the one who stabbed Sephiroth before.
Yeah, but like to Sephiroth, cloud is just-
This isn't the 10th since I have no context for anything.
Well, like in the original game-
We'll be done. We'll write.
As far as Sephiroth-
No, it's okay. I legit mean it. This is funny to just listen to it.
Yeah. Well, like the whole thing was that like cloud thought of Sephiroth as like the worst thing
that ever happened to him. But to Sephiroth, cloud is just some dork in a blue suit who fucking
threw him over a cliff once by accident. Like I don't think he ever, in the original
game, is not until like halfway through at least, there's not a point where Sephiroth
goes, hey cloud, it's me. Fuck you. He's always like, who the fuck are you again? Oh yeah,
that little meat puppet that I fucking don't care about.
I think the moment when cloud starts to actually matter is when cloud turns out to be the most
successful of all the men cloaked in black, who's the one who actually delivered the black
materia to Sephiroth and Northern Crater. That's what made cloud like special in this situation,
basically. He was the successful one.
So what a good game. What a cool like, what a unique story that's never like been
done again. And you know what bothers me? I hate the fact that when this game inevitably
fucking craps itself out upon the world. Everything that is good about it, Square Enix is gonna get
all the credit as if they just now made all this good stuff. But everything that's good about it
will be the stuff that was good 20 years ago. And they don't deserve the credit. This game is
gonna get, this game is gonna get perfect scores that it didn't earn. It's gonna be standing on
the shoulders of what came before it. And that's my, I guess I'm, I don't really care. That's my
pretend. You know, my, the only other thing I want to say about it is that like with the episodic
release, I mean, God, I could see this game not doing as well as they think it's going to. I mean,
I don't know, it is like one of the biggest games of all time. It's getting this like beautiful
remaster. No, like people don't care that it doesn't play the way it used to, or that it's going to
be less subtle. Nobody gives a shit. They just want to play as Cloud again. So I was gonna say that
like, maybe with the weird episodic release, people will like get frustrated and if they make
weird design choices, but frankly, like considering how well like crisis course hold and like all
the spinoffs, like, I don't know, Advent Children, everybody loves it, it's probably inevitably
just gonna do amazingly well. So I'd let Square Enix really fuck something up. Can you imagine,
though, if they get like a game or two in and then like, wow, this is like not doing as well,
we have to drop this like this is we're investing too much in this and then they don't finish it.
Like, I'm just saying that would be a true nightmare for everybody forever. And then when
when this happens on that day, they'll come crawling back to me and they'll say, Nate,
you were so right. Oh, you we shouldn't have done it. We shouldn't have strayed from God's light,
but we did now take us back and I will whisper no, no, you die. You die in the muck with them.
As a me as a gamer who whose DNA is not like thoroughly interwoven with Final Fantasy seven,
like I played it a few years ago, not as a child and I like it and I kind of want to replay it.
But I'm not like me too. I'm not like it's on the switch. This whole like thing with the remake,
probably I would not completely ignore it. And that's fine. I don't really feel the need to get
another one. But I think we can all agree that the most interesting part of Final Fantasy seven
remake is what they will do with Tifa. Oh, boy, on the edge of our seats waiting to see if they're
going to have like maybe a virtue signaling, you know, like we made her like, what are they going
to do? It's just like that's going to give her no tits and like big muscles and make her look
masculine and be like, you know, let's just make her black. They're going to cover up her entire
body. They're going to put her in like a big coat, a big poofy like George Costanza, you racist,
bro. What are you racist, bro? It's time to make Tifa black. This was inevitable. I mean,
when you think about it, right, when you think about it, like the progress, like the progressive
thing to do, like all like all the things she does, all those stereotypically black things she
does, like obviously she was black all along. Like a data white man, for example. Yeah, exactly.
We got to change all the characters to be black and we got to change Barrett to be like Albino.
He's got to be the only white one, but he's got to talk exactly. Have you guys,
have you guys seen, there is an image, you know what, I'll find this for the show notes. There's
an image of like, actually, this actually looks really cool. It's the main cast, like they're
all black and like cloud has like cool, like I don't know what they're called, but like cool little
like sunglasses, spiky black hair guy, hair things, like Lil Yachty kind of, not Lil Yachty,
but whatever. Tifa's got like a big like poofy curly hair. She's a black lady, but then Barrett,
like is just a white dude, or he might even be Japanese with like this weird like shaved sides
of his head sort of thing going on. I don't know, I'm gonna find it because it's pretty cool.
But yeah, like that, the whole Tifa thing, they've made a point to not show Tifa at all.
And it's just, it's getting me on the edge of my seat. This is the suspense that they will not
have in the actual game is the meta. They've changed it all around. Tifa is Sephiroth now,
and Sephiroth is going to be with you in the party. That's the real hoodwink they're pulling
right now. They better give Sephiroth big boobies. What if you're, what if you're wrong? What if it,
what if they're gonna give Tifa big old titties and it's, and it's fine? Is that, will that be fine?
They're investing in millions. Will you be satisfied, you animals?
Millions of dollars right now, they're investing into our tip physics to make them be
fucking perfect. That's why they can't show her yet. They're not finished. My main issue
is simply that like, look, look, I played a game that you guys made a million years ago.
You're now, you're like, you're like, I get it, things have to change. All I'm saying is,
you can't expect me to not notice when things are different. Like, I will try to judge fairly and
decide if it's like a positive change, a negative change, a neutral change. But when things change,
my brain will notice. And like, what, am I supposed to apologize for that? I don't give a
shit. It's their problem, not mine. So, so yeah, that's, maybe, maybe like, if it was a company
had more goodwill towards, I suppose the nice thing to do would be like, you know, give them
some leeway, Nate, they, they're like, like, for example, cloud, cloud in the latest trailer
looked significantly more Japanese than he did in the first trailer to me. His eyes looked like
more. Yeah, I had the same thought. Like, it's, and frankly, call me a call me a KKK white nationalist
member of the Klan. But like, quote that, quote that, quote that, quote that, put that on the green
screen. It's just that like, okay, that that's taking some getting used to, because like, sure,
cloud's been in like Advent Children, he looks more Japanese, but like in the original game,
he's just like a Lego guy with like blond hair blue eyes, I don't know. In the original game,
he's from, he's from Nebelheim, which is clearly a European village.
That's true. And like, and there's already an Asian character in the game, Yuffie,
who comes from an actual Asian place. True, that is very true. Yeah.
Um, well, I don't know. I think you're probably right canonically about that. But probably the
audience, right, like the Japanese audience, because he was just a Lego man, probably looked at him
and saw someone like that. Oh, no, no, no, we saw someone like us. I'm sure that's true. And I don't,
I don't blame them at all. I'm just saying as a natural consequence of like having to make this
design more realistic, like now this thing, like I was saying before, like before, there was less
information as to like the specifics of exactly his facial structure and ethnicity, and we could
all project like whatever we wanted now as an as an inevitable consequence of upgrading it to HD.
They like, they basically have to choose a race. And I'm just saying like someone is going to be
like, that's not how I imagined it, no matter what. But I mean, it's just inevitable. I mean,
they didn't choose black, so they fucked up. I mean, when you have a game that was already
multicultural and clearly had people from different regions looking, there were different races from
specific different places already. And cloud clearly was from a tiny little European, like
German fucking, like leader hose in town. I mean, he's blonde. Yeah. And that goes a long way.
He's blonde. Yeah, blonde from the cradle. So do you think the cloud dies his hair? Do you think
he's the kind of guy to dye his hair? And he would have to have at like the age of like nine,
so probably not. Yeah. So I'm, oh, I don't know, gonna go out on a limb here. Yeah, I think Jesse's
probably right with the Nibbleheim connection. We got, we got to answer the NQ. Yay, I'm right.
Something's gonna be bad. Woo. I just want to say, though, that there was, there was a little bit
of controversy I saw online. This isn't a big deal or anything, but like some people were saying that
like Barrett sounds too stereotypical in the new trailer. They didn't like his kind of, have they
seen Barrett? In the original game, doesn't he literally say he pities the fool?
Okay. In the, he is, his design is 100% a Mr. T based design. This, I think this is confirmed
by the designers. So we all know this. So he's definitely just like a big black guy. Now,
I was actually doing a little research. There's some videos on YouTube and whatnot that are like
breaking down. This is actually specifically about like, if Barrett's like translation to English
was like an accurate representation of like the way he was. And it does seem like they played it
up a bit, not as much as like the video seemed to be implying at the beginning when I actually
watched further. But like he is like a big, you know, a fucking brutish kind of yell allowed
silly man. And he does seem a little more like wise in the, in the Japanese translation or whatever.
But I mean, in either case, I just want to go on record is saying like Barrett Wallace is like
one of the greatest characters of all time. I love him so much. He is so sick. And I said this
in my video, but when you do the first, the opening bombing mission, Barrett's like this piece of
shit asshole, like sure he fights with you. Okay, great. But he's yelling at you the whole time.
He's a big bully. But then you get home and you see Barrett run to Marlene and pick her up and
carry it around for like a train ride or whatever. And you're like, yes, kill Sheenra. They must all
burn, protect Marlene. It's like the greatest moment of all time. It's so good. And and like,
I'm sorry, but like Barrett yelling loud and like being I don't know what negatively stereotypically
black. Look, maybe you can make a case for that. I care so little about that compared to what a
great person Barrett is and how much I love him. So I mean, just what am I supposed to be mad about
to anybody who has that concern? I don't know. I don't know.
He's like the greatest. He's the opposite of the stereotypical black guy who bans his children
because this isn't his biological child. He adopted Marlene. He's a very, he's a very complex
character. Like he's morally very complicated. He's an eco terrorist. He kills innocent people
for the greater good. I mean, I mean, and he's also a single father. He has a heart. He's like
he's like a smart guy. Like really, it's shallow to see him as a black caricature when he's very
much I was just going to say it's so again, like I'll give people a chance to get but I did see
a little bit of this. It's so games journalism core to just read some of Barrett's like intro
dialogue and make a judgment on the character based just on that when like you got me and Jesse
out here like like nearly in tears just thinking about what a hero Barrett is and what a great
father he is and what a great person he is. It's so weird that like the the idea is that like black
people now aren't allowed to be stereotypically black. I mean like well people people who are
stereotypically black do exist. It's a you know and he's not just that he's also that and so much
more but people are going to look at it's the real racist those game journalism tier core
assholes they're going to look at it and go out he's just he's just a he's just a you know
he's a he's a buffer he's a fucking and so they're saying the racist thing you can't call Barrett
a buffer you fucking came through you're the racist. Is that wait I don't know what's a buffer
it's my it's a word that I use and I've never heard anyone else use and I don't know. Is that
that thing about like the people from the other half of Michigan? No I think I'm pretty sure that
buffer just means like poor people like dirty lazy poor people and that's how I've used it forever
but I mean what's what's the one I'm thinking of like there's two halves of Michigan and one oh
that's that you're talking you talk about Ubers what Ubers people from the UP yeah yeah Ubers yeah
that's the one that's that's what I was thinking okay okay well hey this this thing about okay like
on a certain level I can understand why people will immediately see Barrett's dialogue and at
least raise questions okay I like I get it but uh like beyond that it reminds me it's like the
same thing with Tifa basically that like okay so yes Tifa canonically Tifa has massive tits uh like
in the cutscenes they're even bigger those may or may not be like quote unquote canon I guess
but we know she has large tits this is established um so like let's just say that she had absolutely
massive tits that were kind of crazy uh like beyond the pale like the CG stuff in ff7 like I'm just
there are women in real life who have those so like it's it's a little bit odd to say
like we can't show those I think um or that we would change it that's like somewhat reasonable
it was like uh with her body type I those wouldn't be natural because that's just not how it goes I mean
that from from what I've heard absolutely women who have oh well okay but can't we can't we at least
agree that there's gotta be some women if you look at Tifa's okay I know I said like crazy tits size
but if we look at her more reasonable tits size like in uh in the original inter like combat model
they're they're big but they're not like crazy big but they definitely stand out and are noteworthy
there are absolutely women I mean millions I'm sure throughout the world who have tits that are
that are that size and look approximately I mean don't don't women who have big tits deserve to be
represented as well yeah I mean obviously they're the argument because they're the colonizing people
they're the ones they're the ones who oppress the other minorities on the body it wouldn't just
all go to the tits it just that's not how a body works are you saying that it's impossible that
there's a woman who's skinny with big tits could it never happen I mean I've seen in real life but
do you know if they're real are we are are we saying that Dolly Parton doesn't even matter if they're
really valid as a person the saint that is Dolly Parton listen I don't look at girls with boobs
since you often so I wouldn't know I'm just I'm playing devil's advocate here to major's point
too many just points let's let's think about this let's break this down reasonably I mean
it's probably I'm sure it's it's not impossible that a that a female could look like Tifa and and
well okay I was gonna say and perform like I mean they can't like fucking summon meteors
or whatever like she does with her fists or whatever yeah like summon dolphins get summon
dolphins with like a hand-to-hand combo or whatever but you know be a pugilist right all right but
I don't play devil's advocate here but why does she look like that why I mean it's not it's not
because I mean she looks like that there's an answer and I'll tell you people with I know the
answer see mm-hmm uh-huh so it's yeah in the game there's two central female characters
Aris and Tifa and I think the entire point of these two characters is that their personalities
are not how they outwardly appear Tifa looks like a bimbo with big titties and she's very shy
and very insecure whereas Aris looks like a demure like a nice girl next door and she's very outgoing
and kind of like hey let's you know touch my butt please sir so like they are the two characters
I think are meant to be a deliberate subversion of like not how they appear at first glance so I
think that is actually the real reason why she looks like that why she has big boobs that's
interesting and I can see that I can appreciate that so I think it's safe to say that there's not
zero reason that everyone looks like it everyone knows that Eryth it's all about that compensated
dating lifestyle yeah you know you guys know what I'm talking about I think I'm understanding you Ben
and I reject this meme because it's hurtful to my feelings about Aris she's selling a flower she's
selling a flower for one deal that's not a sustainable business model that's a dog whistle
that's a dog whistle I didn't read a dojin I read like an article explaining that this is like a thing
in in Asian cultures or something I don't know man whatever we meet Aris she's not a prostitute
this is how do you know how do you know I feel like it would come up at some point why would it
come up I don't I guess it might not well the flower thing is honestly the only thing but I mean
maybe you could say it's a strong case to be fair at one point in the game they are all prostitutes
even cloud that's true that's true but I mean I mean she lives she lives in like a fucking
she lives in like the poorest slum in the in midgard she is you know she lives in like a
fucking broken-ass church with a hole in the roof with like no no no she just visits that
wouldn't that mean though Ben that one gill would be would go pretty far in a broken economy like
well look it it's maybe it's sorry I mean doesn't a potion cost like 50 I don't know it's literally
never played you know that's I'm just saying that's the kind of neighborhood that's that's
definitely the kind of neighborhood where people would be I mean it's not even prostitution proper
it's like it's like prostitution adjacent yeah okay I will say this it is it's sort of implied
that because eris is etc and she has this connection to the earth that's why like flowers and life
tends to grow around her in places that she frequents yeah where it would normally it's not
flowers don't grow in this crappy city but at her house right she's got a huge garden of flowers
in the church there's a patch where flowers grow because she's there all the time so yeah it is
she is selling the flowers for cheap but she has a lot of flowers so I think it could be sustainable
because flowers just grow around her eris is I believe eris is 21 if I remember correctly 22
22 that's right because she's the one who's older and her cloud's mom says she's a fucking
christmas cake uh unfortunately she's not past the 25th Ben come on she's getting there she's
getting there she's only got three good years left we don't know what eris's mom does uh so maybe
she has a stable income you know as a sheen or employee maybe her mom is the prostitute yeah
she wouldn't live there she had a good gig
well you know a good gig at the honey be in as the milk the rest of the milk I mean I'm sure like
regardless they wouldn't have been able to even imply that in a video game
on the contrary they could only imply it well yeah I mean but like they didn't
well you know like not explicit there's no explicit implication that she could be a prostitute
look I don't think I don't think I'm not saying I'm not here to argue it's canon I'm just saying
you could probably read that into it if you felt like it and you wouldn't be wrong I suppose that's
fair Nate you did bring up the one thing uh the remake is bad and I want them to change absolutely
nothing and everything they change will upset me but you did bring up like if there's one thing
about final fantasy seven that I would update and change it would be to age up all of the characters
because in hindsight when I was a kid and I read in the instruction manual like clouds 21
that felt like to me oh he's an adult he's a grown-up now that I'm fucking almost 30 I look back and
I'm like 21 year olds are fucking children and I don't care what they're doing I don't care about
their problems because they're idiots they have no brains they have no uh they have no sentience
at all so like if I could change one thing I would just make the characters adults not like
mccloud at least 25 well hey just just for the record for the record yeah go on go on I I feel
that's so hard and I feel like it's like okay stop me if this is weird but I sort of feel like becoming
an old man has made me understand the arguments for like why aren't there more you know people of
color in media because I feel the same way about old people oh yeah absolutely like like the fact
that everyone's a fucking kid in all my Japanese anime is I'm like I can't relate to this shit
where's my relatable protagonist yeah I'm so sick of hearing about teenagers problems and like 20
year olds adventures they're none of them matter get that shit away from me it's it's media not for
us it's like sometimes I watch anime and you're like hello uh I am currently saving the world I'm
finding demons I'm killing people and I'm only 14 years old I'm like well this is why I mean
I mean if I'm if I'm watching if I'm like I can kind of like pretend that someone like I don't
know it sort of doesn't matter how old someone is in a certain sense because like as long as they're
an adult they it depends on the story they might act the same but at the same I like I see someone
doing something and they're like under 20 and I'm like I can't take it's hard for me to take you
seriously I mean there's certain context in which sorry sorry to all the zoomers in my audience
it probably like can you just I'd rather I'd rather the world end I would rather the world
end than be saved by a 20 year old that's understandable the thing is in most anime and
manga and video games uh unless the the graphics are super realistic you can't tell and the only
thing that will make you feel that is the number yeah yeah and so if you don't know the number you
will like the one piece characters are like like in the early 20s when I when I when I think age
is usually young just to attract you know the younger audience but uh it's still meant to be
relatable for the older audience unless you know I guess this has never personally bothered me I've
never really thought about ages is like accurate like they're just they're literally just because
like even if you have like a 16 year old protagonist they're still acting way above their their age
let's not let's not forget that in the old days folks uh like people used to mature a lot faster
than they do now like Alexander the Great was what like 18 when he conquered the world so you know
we've really infantilized ourselves what did you do with your life
when I when I when I read a character when there's a character that I like
conquered the world of warcraft and and then like I I look into it and I find out like oh my god
this person's like 21 I'm like ah shit just like that takes together Ben that's all I actually
what do you mean take something it takes something away from it for me I actually remember the first
time of the age anatomy bothered me I think I think I was like 16 or 17 and and I this is the
first time I came across Tokyo Mew Mew and I found out that the main main girl was like 12 years old
I think and I just sort of like what a minute yeah that's a little that's like surprisingly young
for like anyone to do anything I mean the Sailor Moon is like 13 isn't she and I'm just like wait
is she really yeah yeah yeah yeah look we're talking about the wrong side of this equation
right now because we're talking about how like anime is is has all these young people we need to
talk about how real life has all the young people now like there are people on youtube who are
multi-millionaires at like 18 or 19 that's that's the real problem my boy James Charles
killing the game right now 19 years old you can you you can fucking have and destroy a career
before you turn 20 you know likes to imitate your art at this point uh what's the I want to study
the life of like I'm gonna shout out uh acro acro station because like I never really think of them
as being young because I get along with them so well yeah and that 10 years younger than I am
they're like almost 16 whoa I had no idea isn't it crazy how the internet has like made it so
like people can like learn how to do things and gain an audience and get clout at like
I said in the old days I think it's really cool and I like the fact that I can like have
like a cool like like friends of all different ages and nobody thinks about it because it's
a crazy idea what if we didn't like shackle like development of a human being to like a rigid
societal structure that's like by this year you'll do this yes by this year you'll how about we
just don't do that that's exactly what the internet should be doing personalized learning
development I mean yeah exactly for sure I guess I mean I have to enjoy all the consequences
the peer the peer pressure of seeing people your age and like middle school accomplishing things
it lets you let you know it's real and it can happen for you and gives you more motivation
it should it should be a contest I mean when I was in like high school I didn't think I could do
anything exactly that was our problem that was our big downfall we didn't have a society that
reinforced that possibility like I dreamed about doing things at 16 but I didn't know it was possible
I think we also we were not necessarily that I wasn't one who grew up from like little childhood
with the internet which gave possibilities because back when I was younger the idea of being an artist
was still like you know easels and paintings the idea that I could be a digital artist like
was never something I could have even considered to become yeah that's that's exactly my point we
just we were all we all the possibility wasn't there so we never even considered it we just played
Final Fantasy 7 got really invested we sure did I think but not me I didn't play it at all I still
haven't yeah I haven't either Tom just sat there staring at the wall doing nothing I don't necessarily
feel like inadequate or like underachieved compared to like other people in my age bracket but like
I often like I genuinely wonder like am I less successful than other people my age or am I like
way more successful like I I think I might kind of like I think it depends on the metric like
think of all the people that you've reached with your with your content yeah I mean like
very well loved so yes I'm homeless and yes I'm a youtuber which are both knocks against me I suppose
of course but I mean like I have created a lot of art that is good and that people like a lot of
people like so doesn't that make me and like I do have some money not like a lot but like I have
a little bit of money in the bank and I have a car and yeah and I'm not like autistic so I'm
automatically like in the night in like 90% most successful top 1% yeah yeah exactly this is a real
1% or the non-autistic yeah we have to redistribute the autism it's only fair I can't I can't join
you there unfortunately I'm like uh I mean I'm I probably make uh I mean I make less money
than like all my friends but like like like all but I think there's a lot of people who would
you know like to do what I do yeah yeah I mean the thing I've always the thing I've always held
on to is that like me and like all of us because we're doing this like online thing where we might
be poor in money but we're rich in time and I think time's way more valuable you know I'm I'm I mean
I'm transitioning to a period where I mean I'm leaving my job in like a month and a half or
whatever and so I will be that's the whole point I'm selling my job I saved up money to get that
precious time to try to work on shit and yeah so it'll be interesting to see if I can manage it
you know that's kind of that's kind of what I did like I don't know I'm not not to the extent
like that you did but like there I did go through I went through a period of like I was I was tutoring
a lot and I and I and I worked a little job and I and I saved up some money so that I could you
know spend a whole bunch of time just working on like this is what this is when I was working on
Vapors one I think I was like now I've got like I've got enough money in the bank that I can make
it through rent for like a while and I did you know and I was like okay I'm gonna I'm gonna
invest this money that I've saved up in you know having the time to work on this thing and kind of
get my sort of art career off the ground with like my first big project and I think that worked out
pretty well not yeah not not it certainly is a appreciated word about that investment uh-huh
yeah I am pretty much hope to do the same but you know on the subject of like raising our kids
you know I think that our when our generation as kids when we have kids here I mean you know I
always wonder like how much does a generation learn like we all think that we're gonna do things
better and different from our parents I'm skeptical as to how much you actually like do in fact do
differently but like if there's one lesson I would like to take away it's that I think that like
the millennials I mean I'm not even making a judgment but they seem like relatively like the
coddled shelter generation in many ways not just you know not like whatever I'm just saying that
like I think with us I hope to and I'm seeing more I'm seeing these guys like um there's this one
guy who's really into like having free range kids and people like raise their free range kids well
well just let set him loose in a field and see what Jonathan height his name is Jonathan height
what does that mean though okay his whole idea is that like okay he's got like a daughter he
lives in New York City in like a very safe place and like his daughter is like I think like wait
did you say that New York City is a very safe place no he lives in a safe place in New York City like
not every neighborhood is bad or good he happens to live in a I mean this is what he says so I'm
taking him at his word sure um and so Jonathan height so like he'll do things like he'll give his
daughter like a $20 bill and say go to the store like it's like three blocks away and so like you
know in New York she'll like go down buy things and come back I mean it's the middle of the day
like statistically these things are very rare to happen and just like by getting your kid to do
this they you know if you do it regularly they get a bunch of life experience they learned like oh
here's life out here this is super important because I think we have this idea that like
children at certain ages are capable of only so much when really it's only because we're only letting
them do that much you know yeah like like back back in the day like 13 year olds were like killing
people and fighting in battles they'd be breeding like rabbits is what so I mean I knew how to use
an iPad by like h3 or 4 exactly they do that stuff yeah yeah I did navigate like youtube and
and find the videos you wanted to watch children are way more capable than we give them credit for
and if you just like let your kid like get life experiences early he will become a god among his
generation but I mean that's why I'm going to be the best father ever by siring dozens of children
all over the world and raising none of them letting them find their own fucking way to grow up in
whatever country or part of the planet for the number two headband so that they can challenge
you exactly you know just like my my hero the man I aspire to be like in all things uh Ujiro Hanma
from Baki the grappler I only want to be defeated by my son by my strongest son I want him to find
me and kill me yeah yeah yeah you sire the child you make the child you leave a treasure map with
the wife and then you go on your merry way and then like 20 years later um the the the sun's
learned about the map and they go on to to converge on a secret island in the middle of the pacific
where you will be you will be waiting on a throne I will be hosting a mortal combat tournament
to see which to see which of my children can finally kill me
that's so cool I hope that happens hey I distinctly remember like um
the talking about like raising kids just one what one more time uh that my parents or especially
my mother was like extremely scared of me going outside um because of I assume I I never really
looked into it but I assume it was just sort of like high-profile kidnappings murders uh that
were in the news that caused people to be like you know keep your kids inside there's dangerous
people around and that was just sort of like permeated through all the parents who were raising
kids at the time social media it's all up in our ears so we're thinking about all the time and yeah
like uh so it was like not a normal thing for me to leave the house on my own so I just never did
I would always go like uh to to the park or whatever when there was a family outing and
then I was like 16 and like I had I felt the need to like ask my parents if it was okay for me to
go for a walk and they they thought I was weird and I was like but but you've raised me like
yeah they raised you that way so I didn't know this was weird I was wait it was weird to go for a
walk or to ask to ask it was weird for me yeah to ask permission to go on a walk I was I was like
I was just like 16 like like I obviously I was a bit too old to be feeling like I'm not allowed
to go out the house it's not like they ever told me I can't go out but I just never felt the urge
to go out because of like um you know this implication that children do not go outside you
and do not go outside it's dangerous you'll die it instantly I mean it's it's like you could be
what if you're the one case in like a million where you get kidnapped and throw into a sex
dungeon gang banged for decades uh you know but like what could happen putting it like that sounds
pretty funny I mean I'm sort of sort of similar but not but not at all I guess I have yeah not at
all I have it of actually announcing when I'm coming in or leaving the house it was like if I'm
yeah you say uh it's very wait no no it was not before even anime was the thing I would always
like announce that I'm leaving or entering just weeb from the womb to die just just to let my parents
know but the thing is I never asked for permission I would just be like I'm going and right yeah like
I think from a very young age I never was really supervised when I went outside I was told to like
play in the neighborhood and the neighborhood's kind of big and sometimes I did disobey the rule
and go outside the neighborhood but they would never know because they weren't there to supervise
me so I'm somehow alive I mean that's the thing the vast majority of everyone you were almost
kidnapped oh yeah no big deal wait wait wait wait don't just fucking gloss over that yeah what
happened what happened I don't remember too well because I was quite young like six or so and I
was just like I was walking by it was near the neighborhood and I think that it was back when
it used to be like there was this um abandoned store well it was used to be this was before the
bomb it used to be it used to be like a pizza place and there were like two adult guys just
like eating pizza god pizza gate and I was walking by and I think I had a balloon in my hand and
they were like oh that's a cute balloon I was like yeah and I said hey thanks and it matches my t-shirt
and um not that I'm remembering it sounds really terrible what they said next but like my student
had didn't understand and they said like oh you know you're kind of cute yesterday we could never
girl just like you and I'm like okay wait I'm just I'm just curious is it possible this guy was like
was like in a way joking like just trying to like spook you for fun because that's a weird thing to
I don't know I'll never know is this is this when you took your spiked baseball bat and just beat
the shit out of this man until he was dead yeah how old how old are you like no more than seven I'd
say okay okay I'm gonna say I'm gonna go out on the limb and say that probably it was just a weird
joke yeah like like you know is that so so crazy from like when I came back home I told my mom about
it and and she just look I never saw my mom so scared yeah is it so weird from like an old person
that's like oh I'm gonna gobble you up I mean there it's a little more on the nose I mean I had to
translate and just like the way I'm remembering it seems ominous but at that time I didn't understand
yeah I get you you walk home with a balloon you say to your mother hey mom what's kidnapping
what does that mean yeah and she like puts down her fucking spat she's like what what happened
tell me everything I kidnapped these guys that they're coming to live in my house now
I'm remembering the source of incredible of my neighborhood boy how am I alive how
I don't know you well clearly you're you're very much an enigma I mean there are the
mage your your lifelong devotion of purple the patron saint of purple has protected you all this
time yeah the the life of your like mad max fucking road warrior apocalypse apocalypse wandering
like bombed out cityscape scavenging for goods and resources have I told you guys about like
that there were like a drug dealers living in my neighborhood apparently I mean I can imagine
not so strange this drug dealers right around the corner for me right now that's not so strange
I'm a drug dealer I dare you insult my people like that but like you know they do the shady
scary kind I'm not talking about we sure yeah like not wholesome friendly kinds like I mean I think
you'd probably wielding machetes and shotguns and then jumping out from behind the bushes and
going where drugs yeah and there was also not you're kind of cute I got a girl just like you
addicted to heroin yesterday in a neighborhood not too far from mine but I never went there
because I had no reason to there was a rumor that like there was a kid around my age I guess at least
you know I I don't believe this I necessarily because you know kids tend to lie but apparently
there was like this guy something similar to a Lithuanian mafia boss and he had a kid around our
age and yeah like you had to and like they were you know he had to pay a nice to this guy or else
you know you know he had in trouble or so or so they say but I really don't think the guy would
hurt like kids that are like seven or eight years old just because they were mean to his
friend no he just had you get kidnapped you know that was that was his plan one of the
quote unquote get kid one of the guys I live with works at like a deli and I mean I just
have his word for this but apparently it's run by someone who is like mafia adjacent like I think
that the deli is on the level like it's not like a crime deli or anything but supposedly the guy who
owns it is like a mob guy well it's not a front he just has a legitimate business I haven't heard
anything about it being a front just like the deli he just sells meats and cheese on the side
you know if things go south they gotta have a backup plan yeah exactly you know if the money
dries up in this whole crime thing all right there was there was something I wanted to kind of bring
up to kind of bring it back to what we were talking about with like uh like people having more options
for like being creative and doing it quicker I was wondering do you think that because our generation
was so coddled and we never had to worry about any of that kind of shit because it was all taken care
of for us that that's what allowed a lot of this technology to spring up and have it be possible
for like people 10 years younger than us to have all these opportunities like we weren't
worrying about oh you mean like the the digital arms race is was bolstered by the fact that
everybody needed these apps because they couldn't function normally um I mean I guess it's one
possibly the way I was kind of presenting it was just that because we never had to like
sweat the essentials or like figure out how to function because our parents were doing it for us
and like left us to be eternal dreamers and make all these like services that allowed us to kind of
pursue more creative things hard hard to say I definitely think there's something to that I
don't know like because I don't I don't like do you do I don't really see our parents like ever
even coming up with concepts like this even like an analog equivalent you know like that that was
never because like I don't know about you guys but like most of the like like my parents like
they they're always much more grounded and like get a real job get an employment that's more
more rational don't strike out on your own or anything like that uh but like because like
they're so they were so coddling when we growing up like it just left me with all this like time
to think and dream and want to do more than just like do nothing I don't know I feel like it's just
that the like the internet has made it so that like it's it's such a game changer because it's
difficult to have like an analog equivalent for an easy way for somebody to get published and
have everybody see it without going through a publisher like there's no real analog way to do
that on the internet it's completely different so it's it's tough to say man it's because it's
such a different paradigm you know I don't know like that whole that whole super prevalent notion
that like the millennials are a coddle generation like I don't get it I don't relate to it at all
I think it's totally bullshit I mean like how can millennials be like the coddle generation and at
the same time be the generation that's totally fucked all the time by everything well they're
fucked a particular way I I feel like maybe we were coddled a little bit like we you know we didn't
like go out and like run around in the neighborhood and so but then again we didn't grow up in like
in like a place where there was a lot of shit to do I mean it's a weird generalization to say
that a generation is is coddled or any certain way because I mean like there's poor people and
rich people in every generation I think yeah it's it's not like the people are coddled it's that
back in the day there were only so many things people did because there wasn't so much stuff to do
with the advent of video games and like taking up like like so great like video games are great
and they've been just like an incredible medium they're just sprang up and now we have those
and they're obviously very distracting and take up a lot of our time and cause us to not go outside
like I don't think it's like that we were coddled but we were distracted by so many
incredible things that we were being made I think I think coddle's not the right way maybe
shielded might be a better word for it well it's not like our parents were doing it because like
like the parents of the people like the older generations are the one who's who are saying
we're coddled because we can't like like you know very generally speaking uh like have less like
we don't use telephones that much we don't like talking on this on the phone but it's not it's
not because like napkins we don't go on luxury cruises it's not because we're like scared it's
not like on the whole we're scared of these things it's because we've like there have been
things invented that are better than they're not they're not we're not interested yeah it's because
we're smarter and we're more frugal because we fucking had to be can I just say that I think the
idea of a luxury cruise is like the most deplorable thing oh god I almost went on one I was so close
to going on a luxury cruise last year because fuck wait how because so the the wrestler Chris Jericho
put together his own rock and wrestling rager at sea where like he was gonna okay like okay this was
like a big thing they were gonna be like like famous wrestlers like wrestling matches on the
ship they were gonna be like rock bands like fucking fozzy which is his rock band and probably like
other ones it was just gonna be like a big like a three-day concert slash wrestling event on the
ocean and like tickets were like like 1200 for like a good cabin and like I was so fucking close to
getting it and I got talked out of it at the last minute like he's too much money and I'm so angry
that I was talked out of it but luckily he's he's doing another one there's gonna be a rocket ranger
at sea too and this time I'm fucking going no matter what nothing will stop me oh you gotta be there
dude well that sounds pretty neat there's an exception to every rule as they say it's just like
in general the idea is like spend a shit ton of money for like three days where you don't have to
like do your own laundry or whatever I don't yeah I guess it's like going to the beach but if you feel
like it the luxury cruise thing I've always felt like you know go like have a nice day at the beach
except you're in a prison ship you can't go home when you are in a fucking prison but there's lots
of activities to do you gotta look in the bright side I don't look in the bright side I don't want
to like this thing like I don't want to be tempted by this weird nonsense you gotta you gotta think
of the target demographic if you're like a boomer and like all you do is like worry about your lawn
and shit I'm sure that's a great respite from like spending the weekend like trimming the hedges
or whatever the fuck old people but then you come home and you've got a real long lawn you've got to
do double exactly exactly I guess the fact that you gotta weigh the way the pros and cons like
like you literally can't do anything like you can't leave you don't get phone reception probably most
of the time oh man if that's being a boomer sign me up hey man if this is being a boomer chain me to
a wall
god can you imagine if I went on a fucking on a wrestling rock and roll cruise and there was
like a titanic situation and that's how I died what a perfect death that's how I want to go out
I want people to say forever whatever happened to endless just oh he died on a rock and roll
wrestling pirate ship well dude remember at the end of titanic when the the the band's just like
gentlemen it's been an absolute honor and they're like just playing as
shit goes down as it's going around the rock and roll band well what I'm what I'm seeing what I'm
seeing happening is like snaps the ship in half you got you got lifeboats but there's not enough
so you gotta fucking fight for him you got a lot of people throwing each other over the top of the
last man standing it's the one lifeboat everyone's like is like I've been training my whole life
for this and then they flex so hard that they rip through their shirt and like
oh god if you don't think there's any such thing as a glorious death then you haven't fucking been
on the rock and wrestling rager at sea it's like that's that's the selling point it's like come to
the rock and wrestling cruise for a glorious death like we will cruise for three days and then we
will fucking blow our a hole in our hull and sink you know if my two options on going on a cruise
were to one either emerge a champion who had defeated all my rivals or to die a glorious death
those both sound like great outcomes there's only there's only one lifeboat and that's the prize
the prizes you get to live a champion yeah that's right it's the only prize worth fighting for
it's on international waters so no one can convict you of anything you you do in the process of
attaining it is is the whole international waters thing like the same as like uh if the teachers
50 minutes late who are legally allowed to leave is not like the same level of legitimacy or is
that actually true i don't know that yeah it's because i think um nobody can i think it's known
as international waters is is that um people can you know technically see what you're doing with
murder and stuff but uh you know different countries would argue different things over there so
everyone just agrees that that's we're not gonna bother because nobody has we start arguing over
patches of water it would be like a big a big mess i just i don't i don't buy the movie trope
that like if you sail out far enough and you're technically in international waters you can just
like kill someone i mean i love no one can convict me i believe that on the simpsons on the simpsons
they did that thing were like they couldn't like sell booze until they were in international waters
but selling booze is a far cry from like you know the other shit so that one seems that i totally
believe yeah well yeah jesse can answer the question for us when he sabotages the cruise ship
once they hit international waters we'll see what happens yeah because like of all the cruises
that have gone into international waters i don't know if any that broke into like mass murder
sprees because like law you're legally allowed to kill that guy yeah it's just a gong this is
like a gong and a cannon blast happens right now you can kill like everybody gets their daggers
that they've been concealing man i can't wait for this movie adaptation from hollywood to come out
it sounds like a great option just fucking death death ship that'd be great can't wait to watch it
i bet that exists gotta rise to be kaiji now that i think about it uh didn't that happen kaiji
well kind yeah kind of i mean they weren't competing to kill each other but the losers ended
up getting sold into basically like human slavery slash like they became like medical testing
guinea pigs or some some shit i don't know yikes yikes boy kaiji kaiji's good it's great
it's a good program recommended speaking of program speaking of kaiji speaking of anime speaking
of animation i was like i animated i animated um a gun girl doing a little jump down and shoot
thing dude yeah it's fucking sick yeah yeah yeah it's really good how long did that take
it's for the the thing the the crown prince map uh multi animator project there's so many things
that map stands for now we have to say i can think of a few that are not it's always it's always
misanthropony in my heart but yeah it's it was a little thing where half the screen is black
you can choose the left or the right and you just have to have a character do something to the middle
of the screen and then everyone's animations are going to be compiled and this is going to be
they're all going to be interacting with each other in some way it's like a tick tock kind of
thing isn't that what tick tock does you know what the kind of things are okay plot twist i'm
going to be part of it too are you ready or how long does it clip five seconds five i think it might
be closed oh like the deadline was yesterday yeah i already i already submitted mine nice
is it posted anywhere is it a c i haven't posted it yet i uh like no one's posting it so i get i
guess people are keeping it a secret for the most part i'll post mine on my channel as soon as the
actual map is up okay how about you give okay can we get a link to yours at some point it's on
twitter right um i i've posted around i can post it again i just thought we'd put in the show notes
so people can see that'd be cool yeah i i made a tweet where red uh where red man is having one
of his comic moments and dunge girl jumps down and shoots him in the head excellent uh but i i
just uh i've been animating a lot of things and that one i feel like is the result of me having
been animating for weeks because it's so good and it didn't even take that long it's fucking i mean
the there's like little things about animation that i'm too stupid to be able to quantify in
technical terms but i appreciate with them when i see them and just the way that everything's
weighted the way the move the movement feels like it has like some sense of gravity to it and like how
it moves naturally like the timing so there's a little bit of like weight in between each part
of the action so the next one has like the right sense of movement like it's all on point it's
fucking great i like i like animation but it's so difficult and like um yeah it's just like i've
been you know like i've been working on that like five seconds animation like i went through i think
three or four drafts before i settled on a very simple sort of idea which was basically
just a little blob dude bouncing around and bouncing against the side of the screen and
then attacking with with like a water gun not an actual gun you know pokemon water gun thing
sort of thing and i had a lot of fun with the you know bouncing and then bouncing off but like like
it bouncing off of the screen was very difficult to do uh ollie you know to give it like um
like a big believable weight to it dude that's the hardest part it's super fucking difficult
actually speaking of animation i'm putting out a call i tweeted about this earlier but i'm putting
out the call on the pcp i found out that if you have a connect for the xbox one whoa and if you
get a you get a pc adapter for it you can use it for motion capture in 3d software and i want
to try it so if anybody bought an xbox one on launch and their connect is just sitting in a
closet somewhere i will pay for the shipping if you want to send it to me for research purposes
so i can motion capture make zumi do cool fucking shit uh that's a cool idea yeah i want it to
happen it looks right you'll you'll do like a backflip and she'll do a backflip yeah exactly and
then i'll break my spine and uh and then she'll break her spine it'll be sick they'll be able to
simultaneously whip and nae nae and it'll all be captured help help commit to my suicide if i send
you oh yeah yeah yeah you should definitely do that just so you can do the dab and have her
dad oh yeah fun one armed dab it'll be a new a new thing you got to cut off one of your arms to be
able to do it i feel like a one-armed dab would look like something else yeah i don't know i guess
we'll find out when i do it and she'd lose her left arm or right arm uh right arm right okay okay
you dab to the left she's a forced lefty force that southpaw oh that sucks it would still work
as long as you the arm that you are dabbing with is the one that goes over your face and not the
other one because then you just that's true making like a dramatic side pose wouldn't have the same
but but you yeah yeah yeah you she can manage it i'm sure thank god i have to scrap the whole
character if she can you know what's the point your character can't you can't what's what's even the
point they're useless uh are there characters without arms out there who are just totally worthless
now who's a character without arms uh rin from that fucking from katawa shoujo uh oh shit i guess
that's true um shawnee he doesn't have arms or at least we don't know it's true he don't we have
never seen his arms he claims that he canonically has no arms okay and uh i think he's probably the
authority on the matter oh uh paradox crocs only he gets them sometimes as i understand he's got he's
got yeah when he wants he's got arms whenever he needs them so that doesn't count okay so he's
got the privilege yep well fuck him he doesn't he doesn't get that uh he doesn't get the like the
government benefits from being harmless well is it trackmaster snake or what's his name trackpad snake
yeah track snake i guess he's just a snake doesn't he doesn't have like does he have like tiny little
arms or i think i think that's in contention i think that's that's uh an ongoing investigation
i i'll wait to see the the official government report on the scandal uh after it breaks all right
people what else is happening what else do we got we got a burn some more time before we get to the
voice animation just to say that uh you know gun girls cool and uh the bail jpeh thing is in coloring
stages they've finished all the line art do you have an estimated time of completion for this or
is it kind of still out of the air i don't know how long the coloring is going to take obviously it's
taking less time than the line art so it won't be like another three four months how it'll be like
maybe a week the animation maybe two weeks because like you have the the the animation is like four
minutes oh fuck that's a lot dude yeah it's probably too much it's probably like a big like
i'm stoked as fuck now i mean it was like it's it's really cool i even had to like cut some of
the things i wanted to do um i know that feel but like um it's a it's a really big project
perhaps too big um it feels like a little bit of uh i worked hard not smart on this one
but the results are gonna be very good and i'm excited i'm gonna be sick i'm like legit excited
for this yeah it's fucking cool dude how long was your other uh like uh the spider boy and the
the fish at the door those are much shorter is i remember correctly right those uh were like uh
the fish at the door was first half of year two of like half a year so six months that was
the other one was another six months and then you took your six months to make them
it the the project was six months long yeah okay i think but but both the timelines of those
animations were both they were much shorter than four minutes right yeah it was like a one minute
and then a two minute film right and then third year it was a three minute film which took
just going up going up a minute each time right so like doing a four minute animation
obviously takes a while i'm not like but uh i have the luxury of not having to do any of the
preliminary uh you know stuff to like right get my idea present it to the class present it to the
people and then go back and like rework it like i i already had a web comic going i know exactly
what's gonna happen all i needed to do was like write down what scenes need to happen in this in
this thing and then i'm doing it sick it's fucking awesome coming soon ladies and gentlemen the
finale coming soon speaking of uh speaking of coming soon uh Vapors 3 only has like a couple
more pages to go oh damn i'm not sure how to how to handle releasing here's the i don't know here's
what i was thinking i was thinking that maybe because like i need some time to like prepare the
the the Vapors 2 Kickstarter right like that's been a thing i've been planning to do for a while
but there's like a lot of shit that needs to happen like i need to confront for it i need to
write some like the like side stories for it i need to like get people on board who are willing to
do them and work that whole thing out i don't know i was thinking that maybe when Vapors 3 is done
maybe i would do like because i have the the vaporettes from the previous one i was thinking
maybe like every friday like for like three weeks i would release like a new uh like vaporette
friday vaporette friday vaporette friday and then Vapors 3 comes out and may and that buys me like
a month to like you know build up to making this Kickstarter or whatever because i need yeah i need
i need time or i don't know i thought maybe that would be like a way to build some hype for it or
something i think that's a good idea yeah yeah yeah i certainly look forward to them i'm looking for
i haven't had much you know uh it's all so ugly is if that's still the overarching brand here maybe
it's not maybe it's just been st i think it's just been st yeah i've been i've been hungry for content
for for a while yeah i gotta i gotta you know i don't like i don't just want to drop it i feel
like it needs hype it needs it needs a good idea i want to make it an event like it's got to be
i want to build up to it so i'll probably do that so i don't know in the next like in the next little
while i'll probably be announcing like there will probably come a day where i'm like hey guys if
you're listening to this that means today there were there was new like vapors content on stcomics.com
or whatever patreon.com so it's been st um and then i'll i don't know that that that that i'm very
stressed about it honestly finishing a thing is very stressful i feel like now i'm stressed yeah yeah
yeah well what why what about it worried that you haven't done everything perfectly perhaps or uh
that i'm okay i uh i have i i you know i'm ashamed of everything i've ever made uh this this
especially i feel that way you know whatever whatever the latest thing is that's the thing
that i'm most like uh how why did i do this yeah i am i'm actually dying to get a new video out so
that i can push this green screen meme away forever and i can forget that i ever did it look
forward to that yeah yeah yeah so uh ben are you experiencing completion fatigue have you ever
do you even know what i'm talking about maybe what what does that mean exactly for me completion
fatigue is when you've worked on the long project for a long time and you're at the end oh and you're
just like uh i don't even know like i'm barely invest i just want it i just want it done i've
been staring at this for so long and like yeah your height to get it out is matched by your fatigue
of even looking at it at the same time yeah definitely like yeah definitely it's like
finishing the azumi demo was hardcore completion fatigue i just like i should be a more excited
because it's like oh this thing i've worked on so long like it's almost done it's almost time to
put it out there and you know reap all the sweet sweet accolades exactly it's it's time to do
the thing it's time for the moment that this is all been that i've been working in service of
this has all been leading up to but actually i'm just it's dread it's like oh god it's almost
it's almost done that means that means i'm gonna have to actually show it and and like oh god no
now that i'm staring down the barrel of that and i'm like oh maybe this was all a mistake
and this was definitely all a mistake i'm shut shut it all off shut it all down the the pressure
of the temptation talking about a project so that this is why it's so nice to have zero
hype for something and then to drop it so it can be pure pure positivity and anyone who
criticized like well i do you fuck you man i mean i it's free and i just released it to everybody
so what do you complain about you can you can fall back into that i guess but as soon as there's
stakes narrative stakes for one's own life and and hype builds and whatnot oh it's scary oh it's
spooky i don't like that one but when you pull it off the rewards are worth it because you deliver
on hype and it makes it even bigger that's rare but yes yes i don't know why i don't feel
completion fatigue for this because bail jpeg i said it would be finished like at the end of 2018
and it's been going on for for a long time but i don't feel like it was like my fault in terms of
like i'm not working hard enough i've been working like constantly all the time so it's like it's just
a matter of time until it's finished and it's not like i'm staring at anything or a blank canvas
and like i don't know what to do here because i planned it out i guess i think that's the benefit
of like doing a release cycle for bail jpeg like you're doing uh because you you do a page or whatever
and then you release it because like it's different when like if you were doing bail jpeg where all of
it was done up to this point but none of it was released and so you just been sitting on at this
entire time i feel like that's a different kind of psychological pressure where you have this
huge backlog and nobody knows about it's you've been toiling away without any context if it's good
this animation is kind of like yeah because it's a lot of stuff that people haven't been
seeing yeah so when you're in the last like 15 seconds of the animation maybe you'll have some
completion fatigue or maybe you won't maybe you'll be you'll be free of the curse in which
case i envy you deeply because i i i really don't know why i don't feel like that i i like i'm just
like curious like is there is there like an element of like you don't know what comes next in in the
work that you're doing and you're trying to think about it or is it just like you know exactly what
you're doing and it's just doing it that's difficult wait you're you're talking about well how long
have you been working on this thing uh months okay then then yeah you should be getting it i would
be getting it i i find like the like the longer i work on something the more like the more depressed
i get because about it and in and in general because it's like oh i've spent a now i've invested
all this time uh like okay it doesn't even matter how successful it is or how much people like it
because like it still would have been better to have done the same thing faster so the longer
you take doing it the more it's like well you know the end product will be what it's gonna be but i
i've wasted more time i feel i feel like i feel like that's a losing mindset oh absolutely yeah
no i i would not say completion fatigue is good in any way it's a big losing mindset
absolutely uh needs to be overcome so if you just naturally don't have it you've ascended
to a higher plane and uh i'm jealous yeah but it's but it's like okay with vapors um like a page of
vapors it'll vary but i would say that a page generally takes no less than four but no more
than 12 uh hours like 12 would be pretty rare like you should probably somewhere between like
six to eight would probably be the average um and that and that's long and that's long enough
that by the end of it i'm like uh and and and the longer it goes on and the longer it goes on the
less i want to keep working on it and and the harder it is to like make myself you know push
push to the end and uh so that's like i think with bescapades i didn't get that because a
panel of bescapades was done in you know five minutes sometimes maybe 10 or 15 maybe half an
hour like a gif might take a couple hours to work on but like uh like i feel like working on
something there's like a sweet spot where like the the best things and the the most satisfying
things and the best work generally happens when you have a project and you like however long it
takes it's it's it's under that threshold where past which you start to be like uh because like
as soon as it takes long enough that that fatigue starts to set in the temptation is like i don't
want to look at this anymore i don't want to look at it and that just makes it take longer if you if
you give into that i i suppose there's there's an element of like uh going a little beyond your
own skill level like nothing i draw anymore is attempting to be better than what i can draw
like i used to think ah it's got to be perfect and then i would never do it right and now i'm just
you know it's more loose and more you know just whatever um but it but it still works because
that that like positive vibes whatever is allowing me to work longer and harder without getting
sort of dissatisfied with what i'm doing i think i think you've figured out a method
a good method here and i we could all learn from it to just not i mean i don't know i don't know
what's so much pressure on any method is like subject to like a personal like you know differences
i don't know like whether anything i could say as advice would work with ben uh probably not it's
it's just it's just pathological for me yeah i'm just i'm just broken um okay yeah well
i still have hope that maybe one day i can overcome my innate stupidity but you know
it gets worse with every passing day i think that the the the less uh i care about the quality of
my drawings the better i feel about them well yeah yeah i know what you mean because what would you get
what would you get what's there to bum you out if you don't give a shit you know i'm not on that
it's not that i don't give a shit it's just that i care less about uh i give less overshad
like i i understand that i'm not the best artist in the world therefore i can draw
like once once i managed to draw a background it's a pretty crappy background but because
i included the background it gave my drawing the atmosphere and i just i still love that drawing
i showed it to you guys because i was just so proud of my my boy right just sitting there and
there's like a city behind him and that's like the the crappiest fucking city just like ms paint
sort of a quality city well like well like um but it works i just some some something something
that i definitely improved at in my craft is uh not putting in too much detail on backgrounds like
if something's in the background you can make it it can kind of look like crap like not like crap
but it can be very simple you don't have to really sweat the details and if and if you've
composed your panel right or your image right it fades into the background and you don't have to
think about it too much a trap i think i've mentioned this before but i used to fall into a trap of
like spending way too long on like way too many details of the background of like a tiny panel
that like you can't even see them and i still do that sometimes but uh it's something i've overcome
i do it a lot less smart yeah i'm a lot more efficient now didn't you post like an image of
you drawing like a really extravagant white picket fence like all the way across the background
like kind of recently yeah there were a couple vapors panels that had a lot of a lot of a lot of
my car and in the driveway yeah yeah trees and buildings and like houses and a car in the background
and a long white picket fence and clouds and stuff i mean it looks really good thank you but i can
imagine that took a long time i didn't like it the only thing i like drawing are uh people
faces uh and and like explosions and energy like beams um things things that are moving things that
are like emoting uh are the only thing that's interesting trees and buildings they're boring
i hate them i wouldn't draw them ever if i could get away with it but i gotta set the scene like
and yet i spent i spend so much of the time like wait like i can draw a face i can draw like a like
a like maybe like a chest up face making a making an expression and maybe a hand i can draw that in
like minutes but then like if i have if i have to like draw the room behind them the trees in the
sky and stuff that's like that's that's like the real labor both literally and emotionally
i just can't the backgrounds they're just like i hate how bad they look and so empty i'm just
miserable with those kind of comic pages it you can you can like minimalism is so powerful and
you can go it goes a long way and it's i yeah i mean i also don't like backgrounds but i feel like
i mean look at the gun girl thing i posted uh the reason there's just like a groovy background
is because i considered drawing like the floor and i drew a line i was like i don't want to do
that so i didn't even draw a floor i didn't draw anything it looks great the color palette of
this background reminds me of my favorite scene in any cartoon which is the part in cult cartoon
all stars to the rescue where the kid falls down into the sewers and is chastised by michael angelo
or rafael or whatever the fuck one of the the ninja turtles about how doing drugs is bad and
the sewer sludge is like vibrant like yellow and pink for some reason he's living in like neon like
cheese is like what the sewer looks like and uh it's my favorite it's just my favorite thing
and that's what this looks like you ever feel like when it comes to all this all this kind of
we're talking about compromising and and you know finding ways to get around stuff i always feel like
such a piece of shit uh just in general when i when i concede to like okay yes the reality is
i cannot spend all my life on this one panel making it perfect i'm always like if life was
perfect if i had the time i would make this one thing like as amazing as it possibly i i dedicate
you know 10 000 years to honing the craft of doing this one task that i'm now going to instead
spend like two seconds and kind of just bullshit because you know i need to get by i feel i feel
the opposite yeah honestly when i when i find a corner that i can cut that doesn't like negative
right like when i when i when i draw a background quickly right and i don't put in a ton of detail
but it still looks okay i feel like i have found a shortcut i feel like i found a corner that i can
safely cut and i'm like yes i've shaved a little more off like i should do more of that like i need
to cut yeah i need to cut as many corners as possible every time i find one it's like a victory
time savers that don't that don't hurt quality are great because like you have you have a purpose
for the work and if you can find ways to deliver the work faster that doesn't sacrifice the purpose
then like you're working better absolutely i want to be man so a new episode of monben got released
or got translated you guys know monben i've talked about this right yeah i kind of forget for the
for the viewers and for nate i guess yeah and me it's it's or mage it's so good mage you should
watch it it is a show where this oh god i god i always forget his name but there's this manga guy
he's like a pretty famous manga guy i've heard him compared to like the steven king of manga okay he's
very like you know he sort of he sort of makes manga for like the the the working the working
man's like he just writes you just fucking churns them out and they're just very kind of middle
of the road like yeah anyone can appreciate this kind of manga guy he's successful he he puts he'll
he'll contact some other manga man or women there's a couple episodes about women um and he'll put a
camera in their studio and just film their studio for a week and then they'll cut down the footage
and he will meet with the person and they will watch the footage of them working and just like
comment on it and just talk about their process and talk about their workflow and and their techniques
and all that stuff it is so good there's some some guy has uploaded like every episode that's been
translated to daily motion there is um i think there's like seven or eight that are translated
there's more like there's more than aren't translated and i'm so mad i hope that in the description he
says like if you want to help me translate this contact me here i hope that people contact him
and help him translate because i want this i want all this shit this is i'm here for it
but um wait what why did i even why did i start talking about that where how did they get on
to mount monben oh i was just gonna say watching that like i just i just want to be like one of
these guys i want to be like one of these guys who puts out like a fucking chapter a week that's
like a dream and like i know that they i know that i can do it right because i i could be like them
because i don't think that people are that different right like i i think that it's not
some inherent difference between them and me i could be doing what they're doing and i think
it comes down to like a combination of one they've got the discipline you know they work at it
like a real job they work like eight hours a day they show up to their office and they also the fact
that they have an office they have like a a specific space for working that they go to and while
they're there they work yeah yeah i don't have that that's a problem um there is and and and also
like their workflow pipeline like you know a bunch some of these guys have assistance and obviously
they can churn out more and pass it off their assistance to finish up obviously they're gonna
be more efficient at getting stuff out um but not all of them like some of them are are solo
yeah and and yet they still and and they just you know they have a they have efficient they
have made their workflow pipeline as efficient as possible and i want that i want to be a content
machine oh don't y'all i think yeah i very much agree and yeah you get just kind of find ways to
achieve that like like the office thing one of my main things is currently i have like um you know
in my in my apartment we've got like a bedroom and then i have a separate office this is one of the
main things i wanted moving from the last place where we lived i live in such a tiny place my my
office was the bedroom and i'd be working so often while like michelle was trying to sleep
and recording shit and we we worked out a system but now i have an office i go to and that one
change i mean it the promise it's also like i mean it's where everything is like my video games
my computer my work stuff it's all the same place i hope to divide that up but already i have a space
where like now i have rooms where i can set up a green screen and like record a bunch of bullshit
um and do all kinds of good stuff so yeah i mean i'm just saying that i totally agree having those
kinds of things to facilitate the the expediency of work as well as to shift into the mindset
is something i definitely aspire to and one day i straight up one i want an office that i drive to
every morning where i film things where i record things and then at like i don't know whenever
i feel like it's late at night then i come home and i i'm not doing it anymore and so it's like
switched off yeah this is the goal for me i i do you guys remember like uh kc nice that's 368
program yeah we just bought this really big place i was gonna do all this stuff i have no idea what this
is it's like a series of vlogs like he bought a huge place in new york um where any like he
documented the the construction and stuff he fitted it with a kitchen and like a studio space
downstairs where you could record things and um it sucked all the content that he made in that place
it's just like boring stupid shit and i feel like it's such a waste of kc nice that having that did
that project like fold is he still doing that i i don't know i've i've unsubscribed because
every vlog is exactly the same thing and you know i mean he's fine to a degree that's nice
that for you yeah uh it's like the there was like this news show that uh he he had like
with v-source three i didn't watch any of those i didn't watch any of the actual 368 content just
his vlog yeah because it was really really like um tone deaf like it didn't know it didn't know how
to get an audience for somehow it was just like really it was exactly what you would expect from
a like a vlogger in terms of aesthetic yeah doing a new show right but it was really boring and it
was still just a new show it's just like you know there's nothing interesting there and i feel like
that is exactly what i would like like a pcp hq is like yeah that idea of a space where you can
just go downstairs and there's like you know it's it's quiet you can record there's a big space to
put things up yep but they just did a really bad job of it it sounds to me like those guys they
led with like the they should just give it to us is what i'm saying yeah we can supply the soul
they can supply the tech and the money and the space we've got project 368 more like project pcp
indeed it's happening we're making the change
episode 368 of the pcp when we take over should i uh should i acknowledge what did
you just said in the chat here what did he say uh do you want to talk he said it might be possible
to do rad con at my house we definitely have enough space in a way more usable space than the last
oh well that's certainly interesting i mean that is yes he should give us the house log so we can
see have we yeah has he has he done like a tour of you know i think did you was saying that he
doesn't want to he wants to reveal it piecemeal to like the rest of the world uh but but i think
perhaps for us for for these kind of technical purposes he might be willing to uh to break it
down yeah uh rad con right um munchy and i munchy more than me because he's already going to
brony con tom you're also already going to brony con yes um and i've been like humming and and
humming and whoring about like the idea of doing a rad con either before or immediately after uh
brony con 2019 in august the very last brony con ever indeed where we can like like get the gang
back together and all like fuck around and be like stupid idiots and laugh at you know everyone
it's such a beauty it's such a beautiful idea it is it really is i love it so much i i i am not
committed but i'm very much like the idea it has to be real i'm hoping i i've i've basically 100
percent verbally committed i haven't like bought it i haven't like bought a ticket or anything
already i'm committed to make it so just what a shocker mage call me come i can't make it during
the summer that's like a known fact it's just just it's because you're with your grandma right like
90 percent of the year is gonna get a ticket for her but bring grandma no i can't that'll be a
stretch goal for the case we just need to do the house alone european vacation oh that's true
that's what we really need to see to find that guy that you you talked to when you were seven have
them kidnap you bring them i'm bringing you to bring that well we'll just we'll just put just put
her in a big hamster hole she'll be fine i mean that's fine yeah you guys come in and mean the
thingy when are we gonna do pcp hq walley world uh and then we go to las vegas and then we do the
european vacation yeah yeah europe you're a pc that's good that's good more like europe pc
shit anyway if i can the brony con radcon idea is really cool um but the reason i i've been
like not so sure about it before yeah was because not so many people were interested
it seemed like digi was completely hardline against it digi was hardline against it i'm
very enthusiastic that that he's maybe stone has warmed somewhat warm yeah because now now he lives
in virginia beach again which is is not so far away just to throw out the facts there i i bet it
would be possible now that he's thrown that out there perhaps the radcon could in fact be centered
at digi's place or uh or or you know we can all be upset well okay you know what never mind all
right fair enough fair enough so we could have the radcon digi's place right you know have a
good old time there and then go to brony con and then you know get brony drunk sing brony songs
and dance in the street uh do you know we'll do we'll do that all day and then you know uh it
will be drink incredibly epic drink some hard cider you know i mean definitely if we go to
brony con this time i'm going to get drunk because the last time i didn't i didn't get drunk it's
overrated it's not even fun i hate getting drunk it's shit i know but i felt i felt bad that i wasn't
drunk enough plus all the time i was i was drunk enough to feel like silly but i wasn't drunk enough
to do anything silly so i felt like you know when we went up on stage yep and and i was just sort of
like standing there i was like oh jeez i don't know what i'm doing and every and you made and
screaming i was screaming i heard my voice uh that was fun and digi of course uh i don't know
whether we're gonna be able to get any like panel stuff but it'll it'll be nice to see i think much
he said we already got shot down didn't we oh really we didn't get shot down we just didn't
get a response yeah they just they just stop disgusting yeah i mean it feels like time's
really moving along here towards brony con so i mean i don't know how we have we have a few months
left so we'll see i mean we'll see man if we're gonna kickstart radcon four we'd have to we'd have
to get on a ball with that pretty soon yeah yeah well these are all hypotheticals right now technically
i suppose i mean i don't really know what we have left to figure out press a hoof press press hoof
in chat if you like the idea if you want i mean i can't uh munchie and others will be there so no
matter what if you're i mean if you want to go or whatever like munchie at the very least will be
there a hundred percent and me i'm going all right i will be there as well there you go that's at
least three a hundred percent will be there so that'll be there forever there you go i'm gonna
say decide to go on that cruise instead and go sink into the ocean we couldn't blame you should
sail that you should take control of the ship and like sail it into the harbor and just crash it into
the surprise the surprise appearance by the pony cast yes the pony cast will arrive finally at
their destination all this time oh my god incredible incredible that's pretty good okay can i just i just
i want to see that the pirate does the ship have a name oh my god does it oh no it doesn't
oh no think think about it some some no wonder we've been crashing constantly we didn't we didn't
forget to name the damn thing some to some to think about i just i just want you to crash it into
the convention center just just like oh no it doesn't have a name remember it was it was the ss
friendship friendship of course of course thank god i remember okay i want to see the ss friendship
crash in a demonstrative fireball into the convention center hopefully it's doing
the last brony hopefully canonically it's been repaired after its uh its scuff on uh on the
on the waterfalls of canterlot as made famous in t-map resurrection it's like it yeah yeah yeah
easter egg that's an easter egg yep um it's like it tails gets trolled how they have the justin
beaver concert to get all the trolls together so they can blow it up and kill all the trolls
that's what we're doing with for the last brony con we're getting all the bronies together
so we can so we can round last turn so we yeah yeah you can round the ss friendship and then like
all the wrestlers who are on board charge out with the kayfabe commander at the at the to mop
up the timers the ultimate culmination of every arc from all these years pretty much it's all
leading to this singular moment all the plot threads the rich tapestry all combining to this
one singular event cool then we hopefully we can unlock true final boss of lauren faust who will
you know be there and fight us in hand-to-hand combat and bear my children can you imagine if
lauren faust did go that'd be fucking insane there's no way i mean yeah unlikely but would
be amazing they just like they're just keeping it totally under wraps everyone loses their
shit we fear i'll pray god has abandoned them yeah a relatable feeling well i mean i feel like
it's time to move on the last one should we uh there's actually like there's like there's like
one more thing i wanted to mention quickly yeah before before we wrap up um i just wanted to say
that uh i posted a zoomie game the demo on new grounds last week yeah i saw this the reception
was fucking way better than i was anticipating oh great uh it got front-paged and featured
whoa hey so that is so cool dude oh yeah oh yeah i remember seeing that tweet it was like oh holy
shit you did it yeah like it's the demo tom folk follows me on new grounds now i guess uh so that's
cool so yeah that would it went over really well people seem to be digging it so i will be making
a full game uh working on it right now and nice yeah so that's kind of why i want the uh i want
that fucking connect to do more cutscenes and stuff with like shit it'll be send him it's
shit people you're not using that connect that makes me wonder if um maybe i should go maybe i
should i never considered posting on new grounds but maybe i should go back and like post that
like champion i think you should i think it would do really well it's a good idea it's a good idea
like i posted i posted the game first on itch it has like seven reviews and i thought that was
seven ratings and a couple comments i thought that was pretty good i posted mine's the same it's on itch
it's got like a couple of i posted it on new grounds with no fanfare yeah it's currently has
seven hundred like seven seventy favorites like 450 ratings uh not bad i got like four thousand views
and like it's like front page and featured right now it's like on the games of the month page on the
game thing that is so i saw i saw you said like as someone who was on new grounds a lot as a kid
it was really meaningful and i'm like i guess so yeah i would kill the same way maybe i could
do you think uh snakes run away from snakes yes absolutely like some of the games on there are
like not great so like you guys are already way above the bar like because like people dump like
you know my first game and stuff on there which i guess is essentially what i did as well but
like speak speaking of like a weird experience i forgot that i totally forgot this i never
mentioned this on the show uh do you remember idealia uh he watched the show he did uh that name
is very familiar he he submitted a game him and his friends did like like last year um to us and
we were talking about it on one of the episodes oh was it was it that one that's basically um what's
that playing game yeah five lambir it's like some weird name but i i know but you're correct you're
thinking of the right person right yeah i keep talking i talk i keep in touch with him because
like i knew him back from the pony days and everything so we've gone back for a while now
and uh he's doing like programming stuff in school and he's also doing like tutoring for
kids on how to make games and he just messaged me out of the blue one time he's like oh um
your your game's on itch and i'm teaching a bunch of kids like how to make games and stuff
and uh during their breaks they just go on itch and find games and somebody one of these kids
found your game without me telling them it existed and they loved it and when i told them
you use the same software we're using it blew his mind he showed me a video of this kid playing
my game and was like the coolest name of all time whoa that's great what a great experience
so this is amazing so fucking sick yeah yeah yeah yeah um well
fuck awesome last last high note to go out on how can people send you that connect thing
if you if they want it how should they reach you uh just just DM me on twitter we can figure it out
was that at tom oliver uh tommy oliver says yeah tommy oliver says okay tommy oliver says
okay sick all right now they know well all right i sick i guess let's go to voicemails and gib do you
have those do you have those oh yes the voicemails uh i'll i'll do it man i don't i'll i'll go to sound
cloud i don't give a shit uh no it's just that i might be a little slow because i'm not used to it
oh yeah there's a there's a there's a rhythm to get into yeah if the if the voicemails are of
higher or lower quality today it's because gib went through them instead of nate so let us know in
the comments who's the better who's the better voicemail meister i'm fascinated to find out
all right uh so this first one is
is application for joining the tcp teen cp all right go dude i i want to fucking join the teen cp
the tcp i want to be i'm a teenager and i'm autistic and gay and also i'm the one who has been on the
bunch of voicemails but you don't know because i use like a fucking retarded name every time like
you know just like do the piano shit like that's good that's some good funk you could be there this
is the minstrel of the teen cp i think found the bard please let me be on the teen cp please
fucking god damn it they want new blood dog contact them this is this is like the platonic
ideal of a of a pcp voicemail yeah begging for attention and inclusion it's a little boy a
little boy begging for attention playing a piano actually that was been pretty good that was some
pretty good piano don't you just love how life imitates art like my little pony cutie marcusators
pcp teen cp it's clockwork it's like it's like it rhymes that's right i if this is the guy that
did all those other like funny piano things then they'd they'd have a pretty powerful member if
it's true teen cp i just i wish i knew how to contact the teen cp a munchie or munchie is not
here right now but uh i don't know i guess keep an eye out what an unfortunate name the teen cp
oh no you're right i just realized what yeah rock bro gulp okay uh next one i guess now i get it
that's really funny we better distance ourselves from that we better go off twitter for a while
okay this next one is uh bonus episodes what happens follow up question okay go okay i have
another follow up question till last week i was going to ask about what happens when you buy the
patreon like the bonus episodes and you told me those youtube links and that's very good i like that
but um can i just pay once because like you know i pay for it and it's five dollars and then i get
the links to all the videos presumably and then could i just immediately sign off like once i give
you five dollars i never have to pay you again or do i have to keep paying to keep you having the
episodes because uh i'd like to only spend five dollars and i'll give you a bunch of money
but now i don't know relax i feel like good money situation so could i do that right i feel like
this is like you don't boring question boring answer you just don't tell people you're doing
that what the fuck the the answer is you subs you you you pledge once and you will automatically
it'll automatically it's a subscription service you will have you will then have access to all of
the previous ones yep if you unsub then you will no longer be subbed and you won't get access to
the new ones the thing is i indeed i think what he's asking is like can you hold on to the links
i mean uh for later well this our big problem right now from what i understand is that we
have them in a playlist so if you have the playlist link you can just unsub and keep using the playlist
don't say the unspoken rules stop no here's here's here's the thing though i mean yeah absolutely
the the thing with it is like um every month uh it becomes a better deal because you're getting
more more stuff yeah absolutely five dollars absolutely and if you spend five dollars to
listen to a bunch of bonus episodes every month there will be a new one so if you unsub if you
aren't pledge you'll have to re pledge again if you want to listen to the new one i mean what we
should do is we just shouldn't we should put we shouldn't put the new episode in the playlist
until the next month well you can never get the new one you like the new one i i have long suspected
there's there's a few people that when the when the new episodes come out i see people come out
the word and say nay why won't you add it to the playlist and i'm like why do these guys
want in the playlist so bad hmm big think i'm pulling a big think right now well here's here's
a okay here's a thought then again the people saying that are in the bonus lounge which you
can only get into if you're currently pledging so maybe i'm just crazy could we maybe could we maybe
like refresh the url or something for the playlist every month hmm uh you know i don't know if it
works that way but make a new playlist every month you could you could make a new playlist
theoretically i suppose i mean yeah i know sure but yikes i mean yeah yeah that's uh i mean what
yeah there's really no way to do it because like i was i was gonna say we could use like a bitly
link and kill it and change it every month but like it the as long as you get the you can get the
link yeah yeah you would still refer to the the main the playlist really is the achilles heel of
this entire business model like we have to get kind of but you know it's so convenient for people
and i hate to take away that kind of convenience i i just hope that people i mean this is really
people are pledging for to support the show i i think so hopefully most people yeah i mean there
is a bit of an honor system involved but like yeah in addition to getting the bonus and you know
what and the reason i've never been too concerned is because i do just pay a general attention to
the total views of each bonus episode and frankly they're lower than like our number of patron of
of like bonus episode patrons so i'm like all right like this isn't getting out of control this
seems pretty pretty in hand if there was like thousands of views i'd be like well okay this is
it's nice that people are interested but this is spreading a bit beyond you know what i would
like it to be um i mean it might not be a terrible idea to once in a while you know maybe maybe
refresh the playlist or if you can't do that just sort of copy it and make a new one and have a new
link just so like maybe someone who paid five dollars like or if you just if you just have a
years ago isn't like you know still just co i mean i know people are gonna get the link if they're
dedicated and they want it and that's fine and i don't really blame him for it yeah i mean another
option is to have like a master post man patreon so the playlist is there if you're not a patron you
can't click it in that's not boring look if you have the opportunity if you have the opportunity to
steal something and get away with it do it take it i don't care anti business i don't care if i'm
shooting ourselves in the foot always steal always pirate always steal end of story i say i
understand closing my rules are different when it's my wallet being affected jesse yeah that's
the difference like i said i don't i don't blame anyone for uh for for doing that i really think
most people do it out of good will they want to support i i think so too but you know we shouldn't
make it like so we shouldn't make it like so easy right we wanted to be inviting it right all right
i i couldn't agree more i couldn't agree more and you know you know just of interest sam harris um
for his for his like membership program or whatever for like his podcast he does like extra stuff
beyond the scenes like it um uh oh no he has like an app or whatever that costs a little money the
interesting thing about him i might have talked about this before but it's just that like he
says straight up like yo here's the deal the app costs like five dollars like i think like forever
or something or like ten bucks forever or no i think it is monthly whatever but he says like
okay just so you know anyone who wants this app all you need to do email this email address and
just say hey i can't afford this right now we will give you like the month for we will just give you
whoever you are message us on this email you get it for free the thing is though you have to also
message us next month for it to say that i still can't afford please give it to me so there's a
little bit of work involved in doing this it's not a get out of jail completely free but if you're
if you're poor couldn't there's nothing easier than just sending an email so you that really seems
like a smart business model to me you're giving people what they need but that seems like a small
business model except for the work involved in like going through well the thing is he's got a team
so for him it makes sense but for us yeah yeah yeah we're a little bit too small of an operation
for that i'd say um well okay that was a that was a juicy one yeah let's go on right this next one
is i think uh by the the the grandmaster of the teen cp the first guy who who came up with the term
now this is a play he's getting more popular than the we have to destroy the cannibalizing our
audience uh it says apply to the teen cp or i'll have to fuck you in the ass uh go auditions are open
for the remaining slots of the teen cp and i wanted to get the message across the teen cp
it's better than any other shit so i thought that i'd say it in the only language on the
hands of thoughts can understand flames of fucking hell in a rap form oh my god i may be
former baby that's the more than all the good vids you may combine there's that shame lately i
haven't been laughing at any of this shit i blame all you boomers but munchy all the rest of you
fools are they punchy political discussion is rehashing oh shit y'all is basically like a
risk got on a scrunchie honey yeah i'm trying to line up try to zoom me because tom's the only one
that could speak just as much for me sorry tom that you've peaked now it's time for some more times
okay hey hippo you wanted a rap that's a bit hypocritical come with this movie boy crap sure
stop animating but why are you hating your hypocritical needs some more money simulating
this flaps chaps me and my fuck off nature debates are assless so an anime sort up your ass
and ass and not an abuser will come out for years you really fucking are retarded for no one could
hear she may be a major because i think i've been cursed all these stage curse words come
meaning this burst but i'm almost feeling bad going in on her but we're still my 90 seconds
and it's almost up oh well that's all the time i have here but you fuck boys try and come at me
and you better get ready for the squeakle apply to the tnc peter
i wish i could have understood what he said he didn't do me i think he didn't have time just
didn't have time he's gonna leave he's leaving me for the squeakle that was like a that was like
an early justin beaver video i think the idea of this track that was really cute i just i really
wish i could understand i yeah our boys need a little bit better mark i got a lot of it yeah i
got most of it i got most of it i think i just said hippo does this man have a name well i'm just
saying does this man know what his name is yeah he has his name i was ten cp your name is teen cp as
far as i'm concerned you're the embodiment that's you mr. teen cp that's you uh well sick uh i'm pretty
pretty happy uh can't can't wait for the squeakle i don't feel thoroughly devastated enough i need
more i say he's cannibalizing our audience and he's roasting us at the same time maybe this is the
true rivalry we've waited for all along what cheek what cheek i say all right all right as next one
is hater man oh go hello my name is hater man i just made up this persona because fuck you i hate
everyone and everything myself included the number one thing i hate about your podcast is that you
don't let nate and ben because who else would be having this stupid argument come to a conclusion
in their debates i understand the other members are discomforted by this but not letting the
argument have a conclusion is at best a waste of time between two episodes of this podcast there's
been no real conclusion or compromise on the pewdiepie debate the whole thing should have just been
cut if there was never going to be a conclusion it would be better to finish the debate at the end
of the podcast after the voicemails where the other members could leave if they so choose to
then to have a half finished debate where the other members are like ha ha that's stupid this guy's
stupid get him out of here no this guy this guy's exactly no okay okay here here you go dumbass
you can't you can't conclude such a debate you'll never end you guys will never yield to you
yeah yeah ben and nate will not yield there will be no conclusion ben and nate are batman
and the joker they are destined to do this forever yeah that's true that's true that is on point yeah
this is why we need you know we need two best brothers bitch about politics like that's the only
place we do we do i i want to do that's that's that's a very good i like i think that would
actually be successful maybe outside of us i'm pretty sure this is the same guy who commented
like the exact same thing on on the episode i agree i think i think it would actually be
successful i literally would be fine with going and like posting it on the old uh uh t now okay
i'm just converting it i'm i'm i am somewhat i don't know if i really want to do it but but uh uh uh
like the idea of sullying the the it's a it's a retired deceased channel the idea of taking
it into a politics channel makes me want to fucking puke it makes me want to make a new channel
branded as t bat politics fine we would okay we wouldn't have to put it on the old channel but why
the fuck not this is what we need to do you guys need to do just as a bonus episode you need we need
to do it as a bonus episode like a 15 hour debate where you guys just go until you're too exhausted
that's how every episode will be and if people like it make a channel yeah make a channel for it
have been draw like people instead of ponies this time and just like instead of doing it instead of
doing it weekly just do it whenever there's a big debate to have like in the news or something
literally literally would love would would love to would love every time every time a political
debate pops up in an episode we cut it and then you guys redo it on that show okay just keep going
forever i just agree with this notion that like yeah debates should or can just be like resolved
like sometimes it's not really a debate we're having a conversation just have it be natural and
it can get it can peter out and it can come back in the next episode i mean that's like the reason
we dropped the pewdiepie thing last week was because we weren't getting a lot yeah it was no
these are complex there was no agreement these are complex issues so if you just like pretend to
have reached a conclusion it's gonna be false and i mean i really think like okay either one
or two things will happen one we go like really research data and we're able to like disprove or
make a really strong case that the other person is wrong but barring that i really think basically
every political debate if it's not about the facts just boils down to the like the the core values
of the person because it will be attracted the the idea that debates need to be resolved or need
to have a winner is a cancer on all of society they're supposed to be an exchange of ideas not
necessarily a battle of wills the winner is the fact that it happened it would be nice if we could
come to agreements but like i don't know i mean do people really think that that's how it works
like i don't know that doesn't tend that doesn't tend to happen i don't i don't recall ever watching
a debate with a conclusion like that you know i mean don't they only say the debate is for jordan
peterson and sam harris like those discussions like never they never like come to yeah they all
they always end with people talking about things actually isn't it the point of uh a debate like
an official debate to just present your opinions to argue a little and then at the end let the
audience decide who was right yeah exactly i think most of the time yeah that's yeah like every
like no one's ever swayed in a debate like no one changes their mind at the every debate ends with
well you made some points and i made some points and we can agree to disagree because we're all sick
of arguing the end i mean that's how every debate in history is supposed to end maybe that's what
hater man is really craving he wants that moment of like we're like we've reached the end we cannot
go any further let's shake hands and say he's just another lost soul looking for an objective
truth in the universe that he will never find because it will never exist yeah maybe and i
sympathize as do i as do i i mean i got nothing else to say on this yeah we'll let you know if
we have any political little shows going or something um we i don't i don't know what we
would do it about specifically yeah but i want to do it maybe you know i mean we could we could
probably try it sometime we could you know we could argue about like where did where it should go
what to do i mean maybe hosting it just a separate video on the bcp that'd be the first debate like
where where will the shit go on the music what about this what about this com i mean what if we
put out like a promo on tbap for the new tbap the new the new bad tbap yeah okay i suppose perhaps
something like that i could concede on i suppose as long as it doesn't okay i just don't want to like
you know flood what i consider a nice old channel not everybody was on it but i like it to be
resting in peace yeah i feel you the well okay i just just just for intellectual curiosity
here's my case okay why i wouldn't mind i mean one the people like the people already subbed
to tbap they subbed you know because it was a show in which you and i talked about stuff about
ponies though so who knows how much is specifically that though yeah yeah that's there's that but like
you know there's both yeah okay i got you and two like the fact that the acronym is the same
would just it's funny like it's still tbap it's still tbap even though it's completely different
i hear you on that you know i argue it's purely sentimental it's purely you'd have to you'd have
to like trick people into getting invested you'd have to like phrase like frame the debate as like
something pony related like celestia versus luna politics and then slowly as the argument goes on
you drop the facade and then that's it wouldn't it wouldn't be worth doing if we had to do that
this is no i don't this is not i'm not saying that would be the whole thing just in the beginning
to get people to click on it but like 20 minutes into the video with hard pivots and then everyone's
trapped because they're invested no see see no i want to draw in this is for a new i don't want
i don't want the old the pony audience then why would you post on the old channel like you're
there's no benefit there's there's a there's a small but it's more than zero i suppose you know
so yeah anything under than a thousand doesn't matter in youtube numbers uh tbap's got like 15
thousand yeah at like 16 i don't i don't think you get even a thousand people interested in
political discussion off of a dead oh that's possible that's possible yeah okay well whatever
we'll get back to you people let's let's let's go to this is i'm yeah okay all right this next one
is a cluster punk kitchen oh hooray oh hell yeah everyone's favorite show oh munchie's gonna munch
he's missing it oh well that's what he gets and go pound of beef in the pan yes what's fed from the
ground stir it round stir it brown spaghetti sauce without the noodles liquid all the way
okay mix it in that's your din repeating jokes is a sin
saltine crackers in a bowl oh saltine crackers save your soul use the sauce as a dip
mm that's good chip
with whips brand parmesan crisps you could have a healthy keto alternative oh
how dare you show your face in my presence who is that you know the penalty for substituting
carbs at this my kingdom i'm sorry
oh my god oh my god take a bite change your life
wow wow the production values i ain't voice grail confirmed i think yeah we got it you're
welcome to the voice grail cluster punk kitchen you you've got i learned my lesson
yeah how dare you do my one week
it converts it converts ketones in your body to plasma and then they come exploding out of your
pores the heat of the surface of the sun yeah it's very effective you know you know i got a
couple of my clients on on on twitter a couple people were messaging me asking me uh like hey
nate um can you tell us like how to get like edited audio into speak pipe and like somebody
replied to it saying that there's like a setting that you can set on windows or something that
allows like your your general audio that's being played to like be received as input audio or
something so like if somebody could clarify that i guess in general i think some people are looking
for that information if we could like directly through soundcloud no no no it's like uh like
there's something you can do on your computer setting so that when you go to uh speak pipe
and you hit record like all audio like happening like if you're playing like something on youtube
and like your microphone it'll all get funneled like into the speak pipe like input well well like
okay i mean like for me to i look i would open up obs and i would just set it to like you know
register desktop audio and then i would just start recording and play the audio files that i
i mean for obs that's fine but speak pipe doesn't have that kind of like a setting on it so it's
like a more primitive sort of thing so you need to like change your desktop audio to a mic input
it's it's weird i don't know exactly how to do it but like it is doable clearly yeah so people have
been doing it for a while look at if we get i'd love to give people some information on that so
if anybody has that i don't know put it put it down below in the description if you've got like
steps or something so that people can see that we'll pin that or maybe maybe oblivion fall
knows maybe oblivion fall maybe oblivion fall knows all right what you need is a program called
voicemeter and vb audio cables what voicemeter does is it stands between your microphone and
all of the programs on your computer acting as a middleman and it lets you shift your audio inputs
and outputs around basically you can shuffle them however you like the version i use is the default
simple one and basically you have three main channels you use one for your microphone one for
your desktop audio and one for communications if you want to know how to set this up and how to do
it right check the show notes for this timestamp just look at where you're at i will be linking
download links to both voicemeter vb audio cables and a proper tutorial explaining how to install
how it works if you do this not only will you be able to pre-record your voicemails but you
can also basically have an infinite soundboard at your fingertips when using discord or skype
if you have a folder full of sound effects you just press a button boop they can hear your audio
boop but that's enough from me uh back to your regularly scheduled uh pppness time maybe oblivion
fall knows he probably does that guy knows everything haha we pay him enough to know all
the answers god damn it indeed we do by the way you know what i i've been feeling bad about this
i've been meaning to like do a tweet on the pcp like saying like hey guys just want to let everybody
know congratulations to our new editor oblivion like i didn't do it for the sake of the mystery but
now it's been like two weeks beyond that uh so i really got to do that i like i feel like he's
for all those people who follow the twitter but don't listen to the show uh i'm sure that yeah
for them you know what that's for some reason i feel like real like the twitter is like the
place where real announcements are made like big life changing but we get way more listeners on
the show than people on the twitter so so i don't know okay anyway anyway uh all right let's let's
move on what you got uh next one is critical mistake about hyenas sick go this is the most
embarrassing thing i've ever seen in my life i see the title the episode trans hyenas i know where it's
going we're going to talk about the best part of female hyena the coolest thing nature's ever invented
the pseudo penis but no we didn't get it we didn't get it so i just need to tell you you idiots you're
talking about like these big hulking female hyenas it gets crazier than that they have in large clitoris
that are so big that they literally are called pseudo penises by science this isn't a word i made
up unfortunately but they use that to literally subjugate the males as you would just i actually
knew that if that means why would you call it trans hyena is not mentioned the best part about
them actually being trans um fascinating we're bring it we brought it back to pegging we started
oh yeah we can just end the show right here it all so they literally fuck the males into submission
is this the gist of what's happened i think they do have the ability to sort of like make the
correctly oh yeah sure i mean a click can that be on ben sains tombstone it started with pegging
and it ended with pegging new shirt new shirt new shirt i don't know is it sure with a picture
of a tombstone on it with that inscription if it's ben sains tombstone with these words written on it
oh it's a great idea uh okay why not thanks for the info i want the words put this on a shirt on
my tombstone oh that's good yeah that's good and i want the words put this on a tombstone on a shirt
oh yeah what about what about a shirt that is a tombstone that says put this on a shirt um put
this on the ground it's okay all right what do we got next uh next we have riddle my ass oh
yeah here we go and we're getting down to it now we are what supplies did it bring robin i brought
everyone a whopper a fry and a medium mountain dew from burger king i didn't see him the chest
there though he must be the day off i don't work at burger king did you bring me anything robin
of course not with of course not riddler you're the bad guy
fuck you robin i knew i wanted that just for that you have to answer the riddler the riddle
and i won't make it easy on you well i got a 1550 shot riddler very well riddler i asked batman
i mean riddler i mean robin a wrestling fan is drowning in his cake fade was his original plan
loving him or hate him do not underestimate him yellow maybe he his videos will always fill
you with glee who is he riddler i mean robin this has got to be nate that sounds like the
burger king hall of famer in this just i told you i don't work at burger king robin he is correct
release him minions give me my food robin by the way well bam i was saying i worked at burger king
great now robin's knocked out well at least he brought the food you all take care of the last riddle
i take robin to the batman bill dinner is served by robin revisions is served by endless jess
while badman tends to robin's wounds will the pcp members be able to save the remaining pcp
to the next time i find out same pcb time same pcb channel holy shit uh another masterpiece
why am i a burger king guy you're just that's your that's your thing i guess that you don't work
that joke from family guy is my thing well it was you know as the joke as delivered by that
that's true is who's left is it just it's just did you so i mean will we be able to save him from
the riddlers conniving ways it's us now a batman has left the building he's tamed to robin's wounds
you know you know we're we're eight we're eight for nine maybe we should just quit while we're
was it not an episode did he oh me oh no no you were you were you were you were you asked you
asked this last week yeah yeah you were okay he couldn't guess you and you fell in but you
weren't hurt because you had no balls to be consumed by the oh right it was penis they're
penis eating that's right piranhas or whatever sorry i do i do have a very short term
well this weekly format isn't working for me again here's here's here's here's here's my question
if a if a female hyena were to fall into the bed would they eat a pseudo penis well they too don't
eat riddle my ass riddler how does that work they're not they're not gonna eat the no no no no my god
no this is specifically specifically no no they specifically eat the penis this is this is the
sort of thing that when the riddler asks us next week we need to be able to rebound with an even
more conniving and impossible to deduce riddle that will be what finally pushes him over the edge
and let's us save our last remaining i guess maybe like the pseudo penis is sort of like uh like uh
like those fake hamburgers or something like that what uh yeah i mean wait what could you explain
what you mean veggie burgers yeah yeah kind of like to the piranhas i suppose yeah to the piranhas
look like oh i see i see i see so i thought you were talking about yeah but yeah but would they
eat it that's what i want to know what we're going to find out i guess we got to ask the riddler we
got to find out we'll get asked the piranhas okay yeah there's one more voicemail it's also
by riddle my ass batman but it's an uh it's a shout out of a thing he's oh okay oh no shout out
for eight weeks of fantastic content i hope i've earned one minute of advertising
hello everyone we're at batman is making a fan fiction uh it's criminally underrated
about the pcp and i'm here batman to tell you about it it was star's flea cap star flea captain
nate bestman as an as the unfreezes the other members of the pcp from cryogenic stasis
freaks such as pirate jess lala digi and enter a more revised piece of slime ben
hello they are on a quest to save colt corona from the dashley hands of the evil monkey jones
and his evil monkey god join our heroes on their quest across the galaxy to to save their friend
you can find this story at wattpad.com under under pcp fan fiction the ultimate quest for colt
uh sorry pcp fan fiction the quest for colt corona please support this franchise as i
am criminally underrated in my pcp content thank you very much okay not here though not here you
are celebrated on this podcast um let me see let me see if i can find it what yeah okay well we'll
we'll put a link to that wait wait is he implying that the this podcast has an entire section on
wattpad i don't know if that's what he meant or see the only entry yeah there's just a baby
part of me hopes that he's not the only i you know i would be but i but i'm i don't
be terrified and curious at the same time i am already terrified he said quest for colt corona
right correct yeah wait a minute wait a minute uh uh uh now hang on just a second here again
because i think that you missed i now i call me crazy but i think i see one last voicemail
upload that appears to be my impression of a digibro impression and i i don't know what this is but
i've gotta hear it i'm playing it go yeah anime dude she's like an anime guy uh i don't
shower you know this is really informing our whole decision to save digi on the final riddle
my ass back i think we might just want to go a different direction with that um thank you thank
you sir i mean if we dropped him into a vat of piratas he would technically get a shower at that
point oh you know that's true that's true any luck there ben any luck no i am he said okay he said
go to wattpad and search pcp fan fiction oh dude just go to google and type in quest i found it
it's right here hey okay good fantastic huh that's okay i can't find it searching on wattpad i think
you know these onsite searches are pieces of shit fucking google's the way to go apparently it is yeah
fantastic all right there will be a link in the description people you've earned it you've earned
it my dude all right well i guess that's it right oh it's we good four chat there's four chapters
already what's the wait should i should i should i read an excerpt yeah oh let's do it good idea good
idea okay okay i don't this is we're going in all right best guy ever came to a few minutes after
being thrown across the room only to see with his own eyes a hazy image mumki jones walking through
the demolished laboratory door my god mumki walked over to best guy ever and took the tiny cubic box
containing the souls of the pcp members from best guy ever oh god mumki said to best guy ever
thank you but it is my weekend with the kids i think i'm gonna i think i'll end there that's
that's a high note right there what what does he mean find out the eternal rival mumki jones the
old the ultamite fanfic the quest for cult corona fantastic it sounds like a quest for the other
pcp members whose souls are been stolen but i mean i guess that gets wrapped up sooner i'm guessing
i want to find the where's where does slime ben come into it that's what that sounds fascinating
i hope you're like an actual star wars or like a star track i hope i'm like i'm like slime princess
yeah exactly small like i'm a small just a little globule with a little beanie on a little beanie on
yeah maybe unless i like dissolved it or something but i'll just i'll just keep you just you just have
your slime in the shape of a beanie oh yeah that would work yeah that's good yeah yeah i'll learn it
i'll learn the technique it's like you remember that time when uh in fairly odd parents when
timmy turner wished that everything in the world would be the same but miraculously his mom's bad
cooking was so bad that it turned like the weird food pink so everyone were only the same on the
outside not the inside and he shaped that pink cooking failure into a pink hatch so he would
stand out and be timmy turner again what an iconic moment in gaming history ladies and gentlemen
yes i totally remember that okay well with that ladies and gentlemen thank you for listening to
this episode of the pro crass natives podcast uh that's five dollars on patreon please patreon.com
slash the pro crass natives five dollars for i think the 25 bonus episodes i think we have now
and uh more to come more to come a deal if i dare say so myself a straight up deal uh and there
will be more fun things coming at tp crass natives follow us on twitter for updates and whatnot
and we'll see you here next week baby that's all there is to it all right thanks for being we'll
see you around ladies and gentlemen bye
an ass hole i am a stupid i've got a deadline don't want to do it
what the hell is wrong with me