Hello everyone and welcome back to another episode of the Productivity Podcast.
And we procrastinate so you don't have to. I'm a procrastinator and now you can too.
Was that from a comment? Or did you just come up with that right now?
That was on a comment that I stole. Shout out to PacifistBetaFish who sent that comment last episode.
I'm the best guy ever with the most original jokes ever. Munchy's here.
I'm livid about the comments last episode that they were all about politics and not like
they were like a handful about the other topics. I can't blame them too much for that.
I can. Politics are like a mind virus. I like people appreciated me.
People appreciated me in the comments last episode.
I have things to say. There's a reason I'm here and that episode is the reason.
Oh, I can't wait. I can't wait to obliterate you with an orbital fucking strike.
We'll see how it goes. We'll see how it goes. Ben and Tom, we just heard them.
Gibbs here, HippoCrit. Hello. There you go. And of course, Jesse.
Guys, I've got two great topics that we've never talked about on the show before. The first is
Kingdom Hearts and the second one is going to be debating the merits of capitalism versus
communism. Oh, I can't wait. What about Pokemon? I think that's a fresh one.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. We can do three topics this time. Three new topics that are totally fresh.
Actually, we can only do one topic per episode. Sorry. I guess you didn't hear.
We've got rules now. We made them. Topic today is telephones. What do you think about phones?
I'm against them. The end. Thanks for watching, everybody.
I'm saying, guys, new topic today, cups. I just don't really know if they're moral,
you know, they just sort of seem like their life is like as valid as a normal person.
And I feel like I could just take it. You know, cups are all right, but I prefer,
I prefer mobs and tankards. Oh, sorry. And, and, you know, the little, the solo cups,
those are bigger than I thought. The first time I saw a solo cup, I was like, that's big.
I'm used to like tiny little, tiny little plastic cups and with like one sip and you're done.
You got to refill it something. Yes. European portions. The last time I saw a solo cup,
I thought that that is Luke Skywalker's sister. I thought, what are you talking about?
I don't get it. I don't get it at all. I thought you were just going to say you
killed him because he was on his own. No, no, like it's Han Solo, guys, like Star Wars,
your favorite. Han Solo is not Luke's sister. What are you talking about?
No, no, he was copying, he was copying Princess Leia who he has sex with. Listen,
it's not rocket science. I didn't go to Harvard. I went to the fucking dump chair outside your house
to find this fucking joke. That's right. I'm turning it on you.
Hey, why don't we make this viewer appreciation day and talk about the, the PCP dating simulator
that just came out that I have not had a chance to play. I also have not had a chance to play it.
I was too busy. God damn it. Yeah. You guys were too busy bitching about gay politics shit.
Yeah, I know. It didn't stop after the episode. Hey, I had a busy week. No, no, I got, I got to say,
I was, because I was talking, I was talking to Hippo yesterday. The message, I'm like,
wait, stop everyone. More important, it's my birthday. Oh, that is important. It's my birthday.
Thomas mid-sentence, who cares? We'll get to that later, we'll see how it goes.
That's why I wanted to talk to you. I wanted to say, yeah, I wanted to say it in the middle of the break.
Yeah, I did it. I fucking got so much, I got so much out of head.
Happy birthday, because Maige really cares about her friend Ben and wanted me to know.
Whoa, amazing. Dude, I, dude, that was the ideal time. I got, I got, I got, I got so much out of that
announcement. It was crowbarring. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. This is it. Maige, take a lesson. Maige,
take a lesson. All right. That's all I got to say. All right, how you fucking do it?
I've never given you, if you don't start talking right fucking now. There's like a
giant chasm between the two sides of this podcast now, before and after this interjection, but
all I was going to say, all I was going to fucking say was that I was listening to last week's PCP,
because that's what I do. I listen to the ones I'm not on, because I want to know, I want to,
I want to know what the lore is about. I want to be on point. So the next time I do show up,
I'm not out of the loop. You know, I don't, I got to be on the Zemp, the them snakes cannon
and everything. That's why I'm almost always on them, because I can't bear the thought of listening
to one. So let me tell you, let me fucking tell you, I was having a great time. It was one of my
favorite episodes in a long time. It was all this like interesting talk about creativity.
And I was fucking hype. I was like, this is like a return to form. This is great.
And then, and then at the very end, my, I immediately go totally flaccid because it
turns into the same old political bullshit. Oh my God. Good solid discussion. And then it turned
into gay shit again. Well, people in the comments hadn't been fucking wrong. I wouldn't have had to
correct them. But you know what, literally, it just is our, like, like, okay, Tom, I'm completely
with you. I resonate with you. But look at the comments. No one gave a shit about the art goals.
No one cares about that. If the show is to entertain and to make the most down people
like interested, everyone like cared about the that the politics more than the art goals and
wanted to comment on that. It could just be the politics or like a hot button issue and people
are like more likely to like comment about them. But like, like what there is there's
productivity cast. There were some dude like saying that like, I don't know, like, like,
there was just a handful of comments, maybe majority of them were just about interrupting
mage and politics. So I don't know. Maybe we should focus on the things that people are more
interested in, in a way, like interrupting me, like, making mage feel bad. That's what got the
most comments. So we should, we should double down. We should lean in. I did see those with
the top comments. They were, they were. This is I guess this really is a viewer appreciation slash
response episode thus far. Oh, I see a f y sama on the top 37 minutes ago just says, would you guys
stop with the politics? That's so some of the politics commentary is to just say to shut up
about it. I do agree that politics is wrong and no one should ever speak of them. But then again,
Ben also raised a, Ben also raised a good point. He said the commenters were wrong.
So I have to side with Ben on this point. We can't have commenters going around being wrong.
What am I just gonna let them be wrong? Forget about it. Yeah, okay.
About that PCP dating symbol. I played it. I played got all the endings. There's well, I mean,
there's like, there's not really endings. You just do certain different branches. You go to speak
to like Digi, Munchie, or me, or Mage. Not everyone is in the thing yet. But I really,
really, really like all of the little references in the dialogue and the backgrounds. I love them
in the background. And you know, I've got like a like a weird like, like hip thrust, like sexy
pose going on. That's, that's funny. I'm laughing about it. You're like a main character. You're
like the childhood friend or something. I am a childhood friend character. I heard that I'm not
in the demo. Is that true? Yeah. But I mean, your influence is pervades. It's a progressive story.
They just haven't gotten everything yet. Well, I mean, hope, I mean, okay, by the time this episode
is out, I will have played it. But as of right now, I have not to my shame to my shame. We should
play on the nice man. That's part of the variety. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Munchie. We recorded. Okay,
but this won't be a spoiler by the time this is out. We recorded me playing trying to kill the
rowdy rat. Dude. And then since I failed to do so, immediately, we should do it. I should,
I should do it on the on the stream. I should do it live. Everyone got blue gets blue balled
in the in the video, but then they can see it live. That's a good idea. Yeah. Oh, I was so
tantalizingly close. Okay. All right. Was that surprise? What was that the surprise you're
going to tell me before the show? Oh, no. Okay, the surprises that I have a new energy drink
to best you. Really? Okay. Well, first of all, okay. Okay. The score so far, I have bang and I
have rain on my side. I have monster ultra. I have gridlock and now you have gridlock. Okay.
And now I have spike. Spike. Spike hardcore energy. I can tell just by looking at it that it's
shit because it's one of those cans that is like just one color. Yeah, I'm looking at it right now.
Yeah, this has no graphic design. This is the opposite. Have you had it yet? I'm opening my very
first can of spike blue razz right now. Okay. I was on my way home from birthday breakfast with
the parents and I was like, Hey, hey, dad, pull into the 7-Eleven because I was looking for bang.
I got to grab the wheel and steer it right in through the windows and I did not they did not
have bang. However, they did have a carnival candy rain. So they did. Oh, they had rain.
That's the most that is the most rowdy energy drink I've ever heard. Yeah. Yeah. It is. But I,
you know, I wanted to try it and it was really good. I really liked it. Oh, you liked it. I did.
Yeah. They also had a they had a ultra paradise monster, which I have not tried yet, but I've
got a can of it here. But anyway, let's let's get this let's get spike. Let's get spike. I'm
going to hear that pop. Oh, that there it is. That was highly carbonated. Oh,
flavor flavor. It's good. It's a very it's high. It's a high intensity blue raspberry kind of flavor.
Blue raspberry. Okay. Life. Let's taste. There's a flavor in Japan specifically called blue Hawaii
with just aware of this with just a hint with just a hint of just a hint of nasty
acrid like chemical water treatment plant underneath it. Yeah, that's that's how you
got the bargain basements. But I but I like but I actually like it. No, it's very it's it tastes
like blue raspberry. There's a seven eleven right down. It's no bullshit from where I am. I kind
of feel like I need to go on a quest. I need to start. I need to start getting caught up on the
energy drink wars. I mean, I don't drink energy drinks in my humble opinion, but I mean, you're
not wrong. What's wrong with them? You know, they're for the week. That's my main point. Are they
is coffee for the week? Do you feel that way about coffee? Yes, it is. And I drink it anyway. Wait,
wait, wait, pause for a second. Does do energy drinks actually give you energy? Because I've
caffeine in general, all it does is make me feel sick. I've never it's never made me feel energetic.
It energizes my heart and my heart beats really fast. And then I feel like I'm going to die.
But I've never been like maybe it's not for everybody. I don't know. I'm with you, dude.
Okay, it doesn't make me feel it has no adverse effect. But honestly, like it doesn't really
affect me. But yeah, that I'm hopped up so often that I don't feel it. I can't imagine. I mean,
you're already weren't functioning at an 11. I think I might have died. I think I might have
developed a tolerance to caffeine. Honestly, I don't feel like it wakes me up that well. Well,
that's like that's that's the RPG like stat positives and stat negatives of sugar in general.
Is that like it's, you know, short term energy, but in the long term, you're
fat, sad all the time. You can't move. Plus somebody like munchy as Tom was saying, when
you're blood is at a certain concentration of caffeine just naturally, when you introduce an
outside element that to a normal person raises their energy level, but to munchy it lowers it on
average, you know, wait, but have the opposite effect. Was any of that true? Does your body
create? I mean, he's saying that your veins are already pumping full of caffeine and specifically
bang energy drinks. There's something like mythical and exotic about hearing stories of like
American garbage core processed food. That's what it feels like because it's like, you know,
if you're in small town America and you just go down to the to the local whatever it is fast
food chain, 7 11 Walmart, I don't know what they have, all those things. And you get like some
like, like toxic brew or like, like, like dangerous will kill you product with bright packaging.
Yeah. And it's just, it just feels like another world. It feels like like Neo Los Angeles City,
aka Neo Milwaukee is America to me, because we have a lot of like regulations over here that
things like that just can't get on the shelves. And so it's cool just to hear like,
like bang stuff. It's a little bit of capitalism run wild.
You walk into the 7 11 and everything on the shelves has a skull and crossbones on the
body. Yeah, I mean, I don't it's literally like, you know, how like, like, like poisonous frogs
and like insects will have a bright packet of bright coloring on them. Yeah, it's like that.
Every single thing I don't know what you're talking about. I don't know if you heard,
but bang energy drink has been shown to to reverse retardation.
It has to be super cringy and fucking Britbong. Yeah.
Wait, it's that would that would just be called Tardation.
I mean, in America, we consume so much food that induces retardation that we have to
count it. We have no choice but to counterbalance it. I'm going to copyright my own energy drink,
Brandon. It's going to be called Tardation. Oh, no way. We can't call it what in Tardation.
That should be the full. And it's going to be and it's going to be like an off brand Yosemite
Sam on the label. It's like a legally distinct Yosemite Sam. Yeah, it's like a sasperilla.
It's like brood and barrels. Yeah, he's just he's just going to be called Simity Sam.
Everybody working on the PCP dating sim. Take notes. Fuck energy. This being the cafeteria
in the deal. Fuck it. The official drink of New Los Angeles. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. It's just it's just it's just it's just as fuck with a skull and crossbones.
It's like a skull and crossbones with their dollar signs in the skeleton's eyes.
But there's also like the nuclear like nuclear radioactivity. There's like like the chemical.
There's like the chemical warning, you know, like the four diamonds. Yeah.
It's super creative. There's ultra creatine two, 3D. Hold on. I'm going to post the chemical
warning diamond thing. Okay, good. I want to see that. It's it's like four quat. It's like it
literally looks like the the the the Steven Universe diamonds, diamonds, the diamond hierarchy,
whatever it's called. And it's like it's like four quadrants. And each one has like a number
or a letter in it that determines like in what in which specific ways is this environment hazardous
to you. Perhaps this is room for an epic New Los Angeles City Steven Universe crossover event
where the diamonds are the ones supplying this particular beverage, you know, involved in the
production. I've been looking for I've been looking for an excuse. I've been looking for an excuse.
Here we go. I'm posting it in gross disgusting audio. Okay, good, good, good. Yeah, here we go.
Oh, yeah, okay. Asbestos materials classification diamond. There you go. Damn, this is sick.
My hands on that. I died. Dude, dude, dude. No, no, no. It's that diamond. But in in in each of
the quadrants, it says N. L. A. C. Oh, that's good. That is pretty good. Yeah. Also, you could
just in the middle of each of them just have a middle finger just pointing to you will just or
or just like or just more dollar signs. God, yeah, that feels so good to be an energy drink warrior
where you can walk into your arsenal, aka your fridge and just pick from any of your many arm
armaments. It's like, okay, like a monster is like the basically everyone gets a monster to start out
with. It's like the skill floor. It's it's it's like the you know, everyone has that's the freedom
dividend. Exactly. Exactly. Everyone gets like a month's supply of monster energy at the beginning
of this war chest. It's like when it's like when Neo and Trinity are going to save Morpheus and Neo is
just like give me energy drinks. Lots of energy drinks. Have you ever seen that famous overlord
gift where there's like the skeleton man just casting like spell after spell like buffing
spells like greater dexterity. Yeah, and magic prow. And like it's a million those just like
chugs like a monster, you know, zero energy chugs of bang chugs, you know, rain, etc. etc.
just so many fucking just glowing brighter and brighter with like more like more and more particle
effects just like collect until you're just like a blob. You just like a light a luminous
like slightly shifting and has different hues. They're just rating out like you just you look
like a like like from a distance like from like miles away, you look through a telescope and you
see like a black hole with like a like an accretion disk like orbiting around you and you're like
spewing out like heated superheated particles from your axes. Mixing all these energy drinks
is like is like when Guy opens up the eight gates, the eight chakra gates. Yeah, that's the one.
Your fucking aura keeps changing colors because you're like seeping out. Tell me who just finished
Naruto at the end of the day. And then you're just fucked afterwards. Yeah, and then you fucking
die at the end. You fucking die at the end. Pretty much everyone agrees that that Guy moment was
like the highlight of like late game Naruto. Do you agree? Yeah, it was the fucking greatest
shit because like and when when Madara says you are the greatest Taijutsu user of all time. God,
that felt good. Everyone was hype as shit. By the way, by the way, Tom, I'm just curious.
While Naruto came up, I'll never talk about Naruto ever again, but I'm curious. My favorite moment
of of late game Naruto, it was truly the peak. It was it was a return to form. It was an escalation.
It was a it was a a fucking resurrection of a great old meme. It was that moment where Naruto
attempted to use sexy nojutsu on Kaguya. Did you love that? It was the best moment of like
arguably the whole series. Yes, it was so funny. Thank you. I watched a lot of Naruto in my late
teen years, but I never never made it that far into Shippuden. I got to I got to a filler arc and
something about that's why I watch I watched Naruto Kai. Everyone, if you want to get through
this, you got to watch Naruto Kai. It's a fan. I didn't know they made all the filler. They cut out
a ton of like the flashbacks that are pointless. Yeah. And it cuts it down to just
72. Yeah, it's it's all it's all. It's not even that bad. Each each episode is like 90 minutes
because it's like oh each each episode is a volume of the manga in anime. Damn. That's so that that
sounds really good. I might actually watch some of that. It's worth doing. It's worth doing. Is
that an official release or is this a fan thing? This is a fan thing. Okay. Okay. Yeah, so that's
like Dragon Ball Z Kai was a thing. Wait, wait, wait, Jesse, wait, rewind the tapes. Rewind the
tapes. Jesse, what did you just say? I said, I said, don't don't don't do it. Oh my Naruto. Shit.
That's what I thought. It feels weird having everyone jack off and suck off and just titillate
over a specific show that you've never seen before in your entire life. I feel like I
have not watched any of the same thing any of you have ever or played in the same thing. I don't
know. Sly Cooper could be a rat for all I care. No idea. No idea who a fucking Spyro is. Who's a
Spyro to me? It's a Spy Pyro. It's a Spy disguised as a Spyro. You don't know Spyro? That can't
be right. Do you really not know Spyro? I know. I know who Spyro is. I've never played a single
game of his. Oh my god. Okay. Okay. Okay. Complete understanding of Spyro. Spyro is a dragon and
there's a bear and he has money. Here's the here's the problem. Here's the problem. To Munchy,
the original PlayStation is a retro console. That's not even true though. Fucking kill this guy.
Well, okay. Well, okay. It's sort of true. Like for like, I think like my like my like eighth
birthday or something. I don't even remember. But I told my mom like, Hey, I want a PlayStation
because I saw my brother's PlayStation too. And she was like, I'm on it. And it was really nice
of her but she got me an original PlayStation. Listen, you fucking jackoff. Get the fuck on my
level and play fucking tennis for two on your fucking oscilloscope. You coward. I'm gonna play
fucking Sony All Stars battle racing. I've never played that before. You can't play that on an
oscilloscope. You can't play Smash Bros on an oscilloscope. Fuck you. Hey, if you try hard enough.
I just speaking of video games, I just want to share with you. I posted something in the
gross discussing audio links chat. So now that I say Kingdom Hearts 2, what final makes best
game ever? So right, it's still still true. But get this, someone just released a release a mod.
There's a link in the description or whatever, you'll see it. It's it's a it's basically a full
remake of Kingdom Hearts 2 final mix by a fan where you instead of playing a Sora, you play as
Vanitas, which is like evil Sora from birth by sleep, essentially. And he's got all new moves.
He's got like an all new setup. And it's like a totally new thing that a bunch of fans just made
because they love the game so much. And I'm probably going to stream it at some point.
And I was just, this is the greatest game ever, but it was tragically locked on a console. But
now that like emulators have like enabled people to, you know, fuck things up and make it free
and loosey goosey, you can make something like this. And it's just really, really sick. Really
sick. Actually, it's interesting you mentioned that because like I just found out recently that
there was a there's a mod for the PC release of Devil May Cry 3 that adds style switching. So
you can play, oh really, which is fucking sick. So I kind of want to try that roster of PlayStation
All Stars. Look at the roster of this. I've literally not played a single game that any of
these cages besides right besides right. The PlayStation All Stars lineup is like the worst
in history. No one likes any of these characters. I wouldn't know. I wouldn't even know. I wouldn't
even know. It has like two or three of games that like Ratchet and Clank, Jack and Dexter and
Sly and then maybe one other one. I mean, didn't they add Dante to this game, but it was Dante from
like DMC Devil May Cry? Oh, they might have. I'm pretty sure that's real. It is. I'm looking at it
right now. Oh yeah, there he is. I see Dante, D-O-N-T, Dante. Oh, I like, okay, I like Jack,
Jack and Dexter. Cool. Like, but like they're like main guys are like Sackboy, Sly Cooper,
I don't know, Toro, you know what the fuck is that?
We'll never stop being hilarious.
Yeah, Cole and Evil Cole. I mean, I guess there's a lot of links in Smash.
I'm just like, this is a shit lineup we all know that.
It's so lame. Like, it just feels so lame and forced and gay and shit.
It's because they, that princess.
Yeah, what? Like, I've always felt like PlayStation had its peak in PS2. I mean,
a lot of people would agree with that. And with the PS3, because it was like pushing
graphical capabilities as what everything was at the time, that was like the thing of the day.
Oh my god. They went to make like, look at how realistically we can render this human being,
and then everything they made was with human beings. And so they have no characters that are
different from each other. Nathan Drake's just got a gun. He's just a guy with a gun.
He's just a guy with a gun. You don't want to play a fighting game with a guy with a gun.
That's stupid. People would be like, what about Snake? I mean,
Well, Snake's not even in here. And Snake would be right in here.
Okay, so Riden isn't here. Riden's sick.
I gotta say, okay, so I have, I started to feel a little weird for a second there.
I looked it up. Turns out a spike hardcore energy. Okay, it, okay. So first warning sign.
Warning sign. On the back, it does not have nutrition facts. It has supplement facts.
Turns out it has like three times the caffeine of a monster. Oh, okay.
Okay, so I'm gonna slow down on that. Good idea. Chug it, chug it, chug it, chug it.
It's spike hardcore energy supplements. It's totally, all right, all right.
You know, I forget what it is, but it's primarily marketed to bodybuilders.
Michelle's mom is both like an alcoholic, seemingly, and like a weird energy drink,
like freak. So she will just drink, if I remember correctly. So she's a four loco gal.
Absolutely. Absolutely. And it's truly a fascinating creature in that human being.
Imagine stuffing your body full of a depressant and then full of a stimulant over and over and over
and over again. That's the only way to live. You gotta force balance. Force balance.
Yes. If you can't find it. Perfectly balances all things should be used to destroy your body.
Insert that meme. Dave Chappelle, modern problems require modern solutions.
That's relatively appropriate. By the way, shout out to Kat, the sexy gravity rush girl who's a DLC
character in PlayStation All Stars. Honestly, seeing that one character, it makes me want to go
look up gameplay because Kat is cool. Anyway, that's it. That's all I have to say about that.
Video games are sort of weird in a way where it's like everyone can more or less watch the same
movie, you know, they can just go to the movies, which everyone is like it's almost like a public
venue that anyone can go to. But video games, they're like super fucking locked behind like a
pretty big upfront commitment where it's like there's no way I really could have played some of
these games unless I was going to not play the other games I play because you know, you can't
really have that many multiple systems or at least I couldn't, you know.
Well, Munchy, it sounds like you, like so many of our brethren in the journalism field,
demand to be able to get through games without putting any time commitment in,
without putting any effort to learn the mechanics. I know you're not saying that, I'm just making fun
of that. Okay, there's been a thing recently with Sekiro being too hard for baby journalists.
Literally don't even know what Sekiro is. I have an opinion about that. Yeah, I don't like it.
I think a game, I think a game should be fucking hard if it wants to be fucking hard. And
well, yeah, I mean, most of us would be in agreement. Are we, are we, are we on agreement?
Yeah, I think we would all agree. I did, I did read a couple of the articles about that that I
saw. I wouldn't, I wouldn't be, I wouldn't say I wouldn't be against Sekiro having an easy mode,
but I'm not going to cry like it's not fair because people can't experience all the content
if they don't give it one. That's stupid. That's what they're doing, basically.
I don't know. There's like an article about, about like the accessibility written by a person who
has like a lot of physical ailments that cause their muscles to spaz out and seize up and it
hurts a lot. And it's like the, you know, the Sekiro is the big, the hot big game and it's,
he tries his best and he feels like, you know, it's possible, but it's really hurts and it sucks.
But he, he wasn't like advocating for making an easy mode. He was just explaining that accessibility
does not mean like, like literally making a baby version of the game as a mode. It's like things
I, I can't remember off the top of my head, but it was just very like,
What does he want is my, is my, I mean, I mean, what I'm, I thought people were being like,
this game should have an easy mode. Like that was the thing I came away with was that
you know, the people who write these articles, because I've read the article and it was like,
you know what, I can see your point and it was a good point. I can't remember exactly, but you
know, he wasn't an idiot and he was like giving, you know, I would agree with him on a lot of what
he said. And then everybody who saw that, you know, saw that thing tweeted in the, in the tweet
replies were replying to some nebulous idea of what the article was about and instead of actually
reading it, and it just really made me annoyed because of course, of course, nobody would
actually read the articles to understand what was being said. Nobody does that. And then I
realized that everything sucks. Yeah, so we have here, so we have here is, everything does suck.
So we have here is a spiral of fake news where someone, where someone makes like a moderate
take, someone, people misinterpret it and spread it around as like, this person thinks this
ridiculous thing and then it just becomes accepted in the zeitgeist that people are saying this
ridiculous thing. Fuck them. Like what are they stupid? Let's be slightly more charitable because
I think that that could definitely be the root of it. But like as the conversation swirls into a
more and more like toxic storm, I do think that like, at any one moment, like in that storm that
starts at that beginning of that conversation that may or may not be justified, within that storm,
there are like battles that are, you know, relatively reasonable. Like, I mean, I saw
a tweet from somebody before that was basically saying like, like, what is it that like, you're
really risking by like, basically they were, they were, this person was like, defending the idea that
like, why are you being so elitist about like, accomplishment in games? Like, what are you even
like, risking by, you know, having this high level of like failure that you might not get over. And
so they were kind of like attacking the idea of like accomplishment in video games versus loss.
And so, I mean, I think that's a reasonable argument to have. And obviously, I'd come down on
the, I'm into, I am the gatekeeper, call me the gatekeeper, I want to keep the gate and keep the
hacks out who can't hack it. I don't think that like, they're being an easy mode would like,
cheapen the hard mode, or something. I mean, it depends on how it's implemented, I'd say. And
I think it kind of, I would say it certainly can. Well, I don't think it necessarily would,
because like, I've been thinking about this a lot, because like, I, I've been trying to play
Sekiro, and I can't really get into it. Big surprise, I can't really get into any of the
Soulsborne games or any of, any of, any of FromSoft's work for the most part. And I'm trying
to like parse why, like why I'm just like, not a fan of these games. And I mean, and then this
discussion came up, and I was thinking about it, I'm like, yeah, I would enjoy Sekiro more if it
was easier. I think the hard, the difficulty, because like, my whole thing with games is that I
just don't want to spend the time getting that good, because I'd rather spend that time doing
other things and games. But there's the difference right there. Right. But like, here's the thing,
even with that perspective, I don't think it should have an easy mode, even if that excludes me from
having fun with it, because I respect the interest of the artist and what they're trying to create,
right. And like FromSoft clearly wants to make a title that is like, ball bustingly hard, like
that's the idea. And to change that. If you don't want the game to be hard, I mean, I can see your
perspective, because I kind of share it sometimes, because it's just us being old. Like when you're
kids, you have time to play a hard game, and you have time to master it. And when you're old,
you don't have time to give a shit so much. But like, if you're, if you work at like a
games journalism website, and your only job is to play games, that excuse goes out the fucking
window. I mean, I think there's a lot of overlap with like, well, I'm not even trying to like,
bait political stuff. But I just mean, I think there's a lot of like, literal advocacy that
come that they people perceive their job to be when you are a games journalist, they think like,
I need to make games for everyone. And you know, I don't know if that does, I don't know if that,
I mean, because if you're a games journalist, you got to play a lot of games. Like, yeah,
you think they'd be the best at games. I mean, you would think so. But yeah, but like, they can't
spend the week, they can't spend a whole week mastering their fucking counter attacks and
second row. They got to fucking play the next, they got to play the next fucking marble match,
fucking match three fucking, as far as I know, the greatest games journalist in the world,
in my humble opinion, is super bunny hop, because he does exactly that he has committed himself
on a deep level. It's like, you got those like roaming like war journalists who like go to like,
you know, the fucking conflict zone between like Palestine and Israel, and like talking to both
sides and like, could be killed in a moment's notice if they do something bad. But that like
super bunny hop is the equivalent of that with video games by 100% in Metal Gear Solid 5.
That is very cool that he did that. But that's not really equivalent, because that would be
like a war journalist reporting on, you know, news from like eight months ago, that there's no war
anymore. Like bunny hop takes his time, right? It's not like Metal Gear Solid 5 disappeared.
We got to put an endless war, Nate Bestman. No, I would never say that.
Journalists that like have to, you know, be timely with the thing, because the games out and people
want to know, is it good? Is it good? Somebody is going to fill that niche. Somebody is gonna have
to. And I'm not saying that the journalist has to be really good at the game, but I've read articles
by things like on IGN, where people are like going apeshit, there's the same thing as before,
they're going apeshit that, you know, they assume that the IGN guy doesn't play the game enough and
he's stupid. And he says, I don't play, didn't play this game for that long. And here's the problems
I found with it. But also, he understood, like, in the articles, they would, they would say that
they hadn't played the game for as long as they could have. Yeah, yeah. They put that in their
score and in their review. As long as they're transparent about it, like, what's the problem?
They're like, yeah, I played 10 hours of this game. Here's my impressions after 10 hours of it. You
know, I mean, what's what's the complaint about this? There's no problem with that inherently. I
would say just like the issue as it arrives is not with them, but it's that like, when people are
looking for information on a game, and maybe if you're someone who has put in like 80 hours,
100% of the game or whatever, and then you you you were just annoyed to see like, this is the review
of an incomplete, you know, playthrough of the game, like literally didn't even beat it, let alone
100% it. And yet this is the information people are taking away, which is why people like Super
Bunnyhop, those are the people you want to listen to. Not depending on who you are.
I would argue that Super Bunnyhop is made for people who have completed the game.
Yes, it depends. More so than for people who haven't even thought about buying the game,
because people who think about buying the game, they want information really quickly.
Yeah. You know, is it good? They just want to gauge like vague interest because they're
probably going to get it. They want to know whether it's like got a game breaking bug or
whether it sucks completely. Yeah. And if there's a review that says, yeah, it's pretty good, then
like, okay, good. I'll buy it. Yeah, it's the entire concept of reviews needing to have integrity
and needing to be helpful should just be done away with and thrown on the garbage because that's
bullshit. You don't watch a review to help you. You know what game you want. You know what you are
interested in playing. You watch your review because you want to hear a guy just talking
about a game and just sharing his thoughts. That's all should be this guy's talking about
games. It should be okay to be wrong. It should be okay to just fucking talk out of your ass.
You don't need to play the fucking game. I don't care. I also don't really understand. Like,
I also don't have the perspective of like, I go to a review to like get like be informed about
what kind of a product to make a decision about buying. I don't yeah, I don't do that. But my
understanding is that people do it. And you know, I just have to take people's word on this one.
Like, like these reviewers should be rising up and saying, no, we're not at fault for making
stupid reviews. You're at fault for being so stupid. You need reviews to tell you what fucking
game you want. You're at fault for basing your buying decisions on our stupid reviews. Yeah,
here's a real question. Here's a real question. What are the actual consequences of any of this?
Like, are people being led astray really? Is that even happening? Or is the issue that people like
me, elitist assholes, just see journalists with an opinion we don't like or like a not completely
informed one because they haven't like 100% of the game or whatever. Is that really the
consequence? Are the stakes are the stakes just you being annoyed or someone being annoyed by the
review itself? That's probably it. Yeah, probably. And so yeah, I mean, we should just do what Gib says
and either like, actually read the whole thing and have like the full context of okay, you know,
he says the only play 10 hours, whatever, or like, just don't get mad by it. The problem I think is
headlines. The problem when I see a headline that says, Sekiro needs to respect its players by
adding an easy mode. That was a literal headline. It just makes me mad. I think that article was
actually exactly what it looked like. Okay, well, that's another article afterwards that I read,
which was well, that's objection because the implication obviously is that Sekiro does not
respect its players, because it did not add an easy mode. And I mean, respect can mean a lot
of different things. And so that's where you have to get into the nuance of, well, what do you mean
by respect? I mean, obviously it means like cater to probably it's less capable fans. I don't
understand this idea that people have that any game is actually hard at all. Like they're not.
Well, they do dude. So I'm with you on that. And I've got two examples to show. One is a video of
a quadriplegic beating one of the harder bosses in Sekiro a quadriplegic. And in this case,
what that means is he just has very limited usage of his limbs. He can actually move his hands a bit,
but he is a technical quadriplegic with barely any function in his hands. And he shows he still
beats this boss in Sekiro. Like no game is hard compared to like the constant moral quandary
and crushing existential pain of life. So like if you think that any game is hard, you obviously
have no life and you haven't lived, you're a fucking stupid poopy baby. That's like, because
fucking people are all you hear about Dark Souls is like, Oh, Dark Souls is a hard game. Or, you
know, every year there's a new game that comes out. That's the hard game like Cuphead that all
anyone the only talking point about it is how hard it is. Like none of these games are hard. You're
all full of shit. Like, well, Jesse, you know what it is? You know what it is? The reason they say
this, when I hear they say like, I want an easy mode for this game, what I hear is this exactly
what here is, I do not want to have to devote the time required to complete these challenges.
Like, is Dark Souls even hard? I don't get it. What is hard about Dark Souls? It's like,
you fucking roll and you're invincible the whole time you're rolling. That's it. You have to learn
the system, dude. It's literally bullying to force them to have to learn the mechanics of the game
to get through it. It's such a disservice to these games in a way. We're like Cuphead or
Dark Souls. They're beautiful games in their own right. Oh, yeah. It's like, there's so much there
to talk about with Cuphead with Dark Souls, like just ranging from like themes to just like Cuphead,
like you could have an entire discussion about the art style or just the way it was made and the
interesting story there. But just for some reason, this one aspect of the game, which I don't even
know if it was intentional in Dark Souls case, maybe it was. But it's not the main point of the
game. So why is it the main talking point? I mean, I guess because it's the stopper that
keeps people from experiencing more of it. That was less the game. Ultimately, people want
everyone, somebody who likes Dark Souls wants as many people as possible to play it and enjoy it
because they like it so much. And so when there's this idea going around that Dark Souls is too hard,
in their brain, I think, you know, they probably wouldn't realize. But I think it's this, they get
angry about that because it implies that more people will not even give it a chance and not even try
and not even go through the pain to feel the euphoria that they felt when they finally beat
the hard boss. And they want, they want to share the enjoyment of the game. It comes out in this
vitriolic sort of back and forth with, you know, game journalists and, and get gooders and all this
stupid internet internet fighting. And it's like, you just want to you just like video games. There's
a lot. I mean, there's a lot. It's hard. Let me let me let me be good if you could calm down, everyone.
Let me quote this guy. He says, there's a lot of talk about quote respecting the player when it
comes to not including an easy mode, an idea that all players can and should play the game in this
particular punishing way. Yet I think the lack of an easy mode showcases the exact opposite.
It shows an almost stunning lack of respect for players with the idea that they cannot be trusted
with their own gameplay experience, that even those who want a challenging game would somehow
be lured by the siren song of lower difficulties and destroy their own experience because they're
too impatient or immature to know what they actually want. But I mean, that has happened to me. It has
affected me when playing games. I mean, yeah, my argument. Yeah, I remember now that I read this
one and my had my my fundamental disagreement was that I don't think gamers can be respected.
I think I think that there's an ED mode. It's an ED mode. They will go for it because they go to
video games to escape. If there's a difficult section and they had a bad day and they're playing
a hard game and there's a way that they can just make it easier, of course, they're going to take
it. This is this is dark souls race. Remember the Dark Souls race that we did? Yeah. So like the
the Dark Souls race was great. Obviously, everybody go watch it on the procrastiners channel that
you're viewing right now. And like I won and that was really great. But but the thing about that was
like what I wanted to do with that and with the Pokemon race that we did afterward,
I would it was you guys were there, you know, I was like, guys, we need to set the rules because
once the rules are set, I will exploit every ability I can find within the rule set so that I
have not broken the rules, but I can use every possible tool and gimmick and glitch that is
allowed under the rule set to win. So it's so important to set the rules so that you know what
you like are and are allowed to do. And I like I just think this is a pretty good way to do that if
that's what the developer wants to do, which from soft has said they do, which is just say this is
the baseline of everybody. These are the rules. You can't obviously like cheat the game unless you
use like a cheat engine or something. So was it level here? Was it? Did Matthew Matosis do a video
about fucking? What's the game where you're a guy in a pot and you go in the mountain getting over
it? Yeah, did Matthew Matosis do a video about that one? I don't think so. No, I did a video about
that one. True. Am I thinking of Joseph Anderson or probably probably. Yeah. Okay. Well, I don't
know, like, if it was Joseph Anderson than him, but if it was someone else, whatever, whoever I'm
thinking of said like, there's, you know, there's something kind of beautiful about the idea that
this mountain is a totally, there's no easy mode for this and there couldn't be. Because like the
mountain change the game, the mountain is what it is. It is a series of set obstacles that you
either can or cannot overcome. And everyone who climbs this mountain climbs the exact same mountain.
That's exactly what it is in this case. That's exactly what Sekiro is. It's a mountain. And I
think that's fine. And I think that's cool. And no, I don't think it's fucking disrespectful
to be like, this is the exact experience I designed. And, you know, I don't think I'm going to want to
let people change it and play it in a different way. I think that's, that's the thing. And forgive
me, I haven't been talking this whole time because some asshole is like mowing his lawn or some
shit. It's fucking loud. I want to get picked up on the microphone. But yeah, I mean, it's interesting,
Nate, that you said that like you've been tempted to go to lower difficulties because like,
I paradoxically want games to be easy because I don't want to like spend a ton of time with
them. I just want to like escape from my life and have fun and feel cool. But every time I can't
go to easy mode on any game because it infuriates me. It makes me feel like a pathetic bitch because
I rarely like there's some games that like if you fail enough, the game will offer to like lower
the difficulty or whatever. And it feels like a slap in the face. I mean, it does, but I have done
it on occasion when like the game is just, I'm against the wall. To me, when it does that, it's
just it like quadruples down my efforts. I'm like, I will, I will never take you up on this offer.
You disgusting mongoloid of a developer who put this line of code in here. How dare you insult me?
I personally, I personally, I can't even go ahead. Oh, well, a perfect example of that is like
whenever I'm in playing in Minecraft and I've got survival on because that's default and there's
monsters around. I'm doing stuff. And then, uh-oh, there's like, I'm trapped. There's things all
around me. Paul's turned it to peaceful. All the mobs go away and I could just continue building
what I was building. Yeah. I do that all the time. I was playing Super Smash Bros. Ultimate World of
Light and I had it on hard just because I thought I usually play games on hard. I like when things
are difficult, but I think it's almost a sign of like when a game isn't good, then you want it to
be easy just to get it over with in a way. It feels to me when you just want things to be easy. It's
just because you just want to have it be done as fast as possible, which is not how I usually want
to play a game. So like with Super Smash Bros, it was like, I played it on hard for a while and I
thought, well, this game sucks and I'm not really having that much fun and I don't really care about
continuing. So I always turn it to easy and try and crank through it. And even still, if you
effort was on easy, I was like, oh, this is just too much. I don't fucking care anymore. It's a lot.
Yeah. I haven't beaten it either. I personally can't stand when a game even gives me a choice in
difficulty. There should be one option and that should be how the game is meant to be played.
Because when I see like easy, medium, and hard, you know, it's like, well, what the fuck is the
real game? What is the actual game? Is it normal? So I usually just pick normal. But that's if there's
like three. Sometimes games get crazy and they have like six different difficulty modes. And
there's no middle option because there's like an even number. So you don't know like what the real
game even is. And I don't want to have to think about that shit. I don't want to sweat the petty
things. Just give me the game how it's meant to be fucking played. One fucking difficulty mode.
Don't give me a choice. Don't make me fucking think about it. I hate you. All game developers die.
That is ideal, which is why I like Securo and Dark Souls so much.
Yeah. And it's like another thing that annoys me about multiple difficulty modes at the beginning
is that I have a choice to make. And it's like if I choose easy, then the game might not be
challenging or interesting enough. So I usually don't choose easy. But if I choose normal,
and I'm like locked into it, or like hard, and I'm locked into it. I feel like I if I get stuck
at any point, I'm like, ah, I should have picked easy. Yeah, I got to restart the game because I
I'm not having an easy time. But there's a possibility that I could be having an easy time
if I had done the other thing. There's a handful of games that I've ever been like, I would prefer
to play this on easy. Have you guys seen that extra credits video on the true genius of Dark Souls
two? I don't wait. Yes. And I think I remember. So fucking dumb. Yeah, terrible. Okay, basically.
Okay, well, the idea of the video is that Dark Souls two lets you basically sort of soft set
your own difficulty. But like the key argument for it basically boils down to magic is way
overpowered in the game. So if you're having a hard time, just use magic and then the game
will be easier for you. And I disagree with that in the grounds of Have you seen the adventures
of Baba Duke spook? His life is suffering. He is a pure mage. He only does magic and his life is
constant agony. That's true. Well, a lot of that's of his own making. I don't know. They're fucking
wrong. That video is terrible. It's like, Hey, embarrassing. And this whole discussion of like
difficulty of Dark Souls, like everything makes sense so far. But but the thing is there's there's
games that are just fundamentally designed differently. And I think one of those like is
Devil May Cry. Because personally, I've never done this. Yeah, like I intend to with Devil May Cry
and maybe I'll go back. I've beaten all the games and basically a scrub. But like I understand that
the idea of those games is you basically get through them once. And then you go back and you do it on
like hard mode, and then Dante must die mode. And you try to like get, you know, triple s rank on
like every individual level or whatever. And so it's about like perfecting your gameplay and,
you know, upping your score. So that's kind of like a totally different approach to like how
difficulty should be handled, because that's a game designed to be played many times over and
over by the most committed. I really like rank systems, ranking systems, because is this is
exact same thing? Like, it's difficult to do an s rank, but you don't need to do an s rank to get
to the next part of the game. So you can beat the game with a low rank score, and you can see
everything there is to see. But if, you know, the challenge is always there. And, you know,
in Dark Souls, if you kill the thing, that's it. There is no how well you did it, how many
times you dodged or, or like how many estus you didn't need to drink. It's like, you just do it,
and it doesn't matter whether you're, you were terrible during the fight and got lucky, or that
you killed it in like five seconds. And you can do like self-imposed challenges, but those are just
those are an outside thing that you, but like having having the rank system as like a tantalizing
Ooh, I want the shiny one. I want the shiny one. It makes you, you know, it gives you,
you know, the whole game, you can play the whole game and beat the whole game. But if you want to,
and if you feel inclined to, you can, you can train yourself to get better at it so that you
can beat the highest scores. And often I don't do that, but I just like the fact that that is,
that is a thing rather than just, rather than just cutting my gameplay experience short and
making me rage quit. I think that's why I end up liking Devil May Cry more is because like,
it feels like to me that like actually like being good at Devil May Cry is, you know, S ranking
everything. You know, and so like you have this like kind of like skill floor difficulty where
it's like getting through the game, but like the real way like you've actually quote unquote beaten
the game shirt for in all intents and purposes by S ranking everything. Like that's, that's kind of
like, you know, what you should optimally do. Like that's where you kind of the games clearly kind
of like designed to influence you to try and do that. Whereas with something like, like Dark Souls,
the different, the difficulty is like, to S rank it is to just beat it, you know, just fuck your
way. So like, so like that's why it's harder is that like it the S the skill floor of Dark Souls
is S ranking everything. So it's fair to I get complaining about a skill floor being too high
such that it's too much for a lot of people to get over. But then it just comes back to like,
I mean, another another thing I was entitled like why are you entitled to an experience?
People feel entitled. People really feel like here's another video in the girls discussing
audio links. This is a video made it's on the Street Fighter channel on YouTube made like three
years ago, whatever. And it's of the number one ranked Chun Li player in the world. And I think
Street Fighter five or maybe Street Fighter four, whatever. And like, he's got a like a terrible
debilitating disability. His legs don't work. He like crawls around and his arms have limited
functionality. And if you skip through this, like the way he plays is like he has his face on the
game pad and puts his hands like claw like behind it. So this guy had to come up with a whole new
way to play the game. He can't use an arcade stick. And still he became the number one ranked
Chun Li and placed like fifth in a professional tournament. So this guy just like he adapted
and overcame. I don't know if we should base our expectations for people on like clear. It is.
Yeah, it is. This is a man who he's living out his fantasies of having legs by playing as Chun Li
and her beautiful, ultimate legs, big, meaty legs. Yeah, the most leg of all. I'm just saying
this is like the ideal of what I would want people to aim.
You know, of what this guy has done seems. I just think the world will be better if people
approach challenges in this way. The problem, the real problem in all this, of course, once again,
comes down to zoomers. It's all young people's fault that we have these issues. I'm not sure.
And I'm going to tell you why. And this is okay. I mean, the guy who wrote this article is not a
zoomer. Well, it's going to sound slightly influenced. I believe the guy who wrote this
article, even if he's not technically a zoomer, he is a zoomer at heart. He is a young person at
his core because there's an epidemic of people who are not classically educated in video games.
Because what my point of view with saying that Dark Souls isn't hard, like is Dark Souls hard
compared to Ghouls and Ghosts? I don't think so. Is Sekiro hard compared to the original
Ninja Gaiden? No, not even close. These people have played, they haven't played these games.
They don't know what a real hard game is like. They don't know Shinobi 3. They don't know the
fucking Lion King. That's why I went into a rant about the Lion King in my last video. Because
the Lion King was the first video game I ever played. The first video game I ever beat. I was
like, fucking five years old. So I never thought of it as a hard game my whole life. And then
when I grew up and I, you know, you look on the internet, it seems like every other week
to this day on Reddit, there's a big thread like, anyone remember the Lion King is the hardest game
ever made? No one on earth could ever get past the second level. And it's like, what is wrong
with you people? I don't believe you. I don't believe these people have played it. I think they're
just copying the notion that it's the hardest game ever. In my humble opinion, the world and the
people in it have all softened. Because there's just less need to try harder things. People used
to be a lot tougher, you know, back in the day when we were all Nephilim, you know.
But before the flood. No game made nowadays is as hard as Splatterhouse 2. It's never gonna happen.
They'll never make a game again as hard as Splatterhouse 2. The final boss of Splatterhouse 2
will reduce you to a quivering, weeping mess. Anyone out there, you try it. You try to beat
the last boss of Splatterhouse 2. You'll cry and you'll scream. You'll break your controller in
half with your hands. You'll get Hulk strength just for that one moment. I tried to play Contra 4
on my DS when it came out. And I was like, this is so, there was no chance. No chance. I will
ever beat this game without cheating. And so I just gave up. So yeah. I don't know. And I feel
like I have some ability to say this stuff. Because like right now, I'm at the end of Hollow Knight
facing down like some of the like the final challenges to get like the uber super secret
ending. It is so, it asks so much of you. And by that, I mean, it asks about as much as like
level one of Contra 1 asked, you know, to get like the ultimate, probably a bit more than that.
But like still, it's such a hurdle to get the final shit in Hollow Knight. And I have not earned
it. And I don't want to be just given a participation trophy. I want to work up to it over the next,
I don't know, months or years, and then earn it. And like satisfaction will be, will be there.
But if Hollow Knight had an easy mode, I mean, that wouldn't be like,
I mean, would you take that away from, I mean, I mean, you would have to opt into being given it.
You would have to be like, okay, I'm doing it. I'm macing that Faustian bargain. I'm hitting,
I'm hitting the button. I have decided on that. Easy mode. Does easy mode in this in this mean
like the main game is has an easy mode, but then all the extra challenges don't have easy modes,
or would they also? Yeah, it depends on how it's done. Because a game like Kingdom Hearts 2, for
example, it has a it has easy modes, basically, that just make basically the whole game easier
and then hard modes that make a lot harder, etc. But like the way that it punishes you is that the
like, the criteria to unlock like secret ending content is it scales up like exponentially based
on how easy you've made the game. So like, I think if you plan beginner, you straight up can't
unlock the secret ending. I think I might be off about that. If you're playing on like normal,
you have to like 100% Jiminy's journal. If you're playing on like hard, you have to like, you know,
like do some secret like collect all the answer reports or something. And then if you're playing
on like critical mode, all you got to do is like beat the final boss. And then you get it.
Oh, this reminds me back back in the day when I played on Sega Genesis, Golden Axe.
Yeah, Sega Genesis, my first console, I had I had Golden Axe. I love that game. And me and me,
I would play it on on easy mode mostly just because I liked how you gave you more life and
stuff. Because like when you play, when you play Golden Axe on easy, like doubles your life bar,
gives you more, more lives and shit like that. And so you play the game. And I beat it. And I
beat it on easy mode. I'm like, Oh, this is a fun game. I like I like this game. It's cool. I played
a bunch of times like that. And then I remember the first time I played it on normal mode. And
as a little kid, I couldn't do it. But like a year into having the game, I played it on normal.
And I got to the end of the game. And I realized, Oh, this wasn't the end of the game. This is the
end of baby mode. There's like a whole other game after this that I never knew about. It blew
my mind to shit. It was fucking cool. Yeah, that's that's the shit. And like, I didn't, I watched,
I look at Sekiro, I haven't played it yet. So full disclosure, I haven't played it, but I watched
people playing it. And it just looks to me like a modern 10 shoe, basically, stealth and the grappling.
And it's like, I haven't played it yet. But I promise you that the original 10 shoe was harder
than Sekiro. That's no doubt. And it's just, there's different kinds of difficulty. I mean,
like when you talk about difficulty in games, it sort of becomes like either games are easier,
they're difficult, but there's so many different kinds. Like I have, I have, I have an easier
time with certain kinds of difficulty now than I used to and a harder time. Like, like the kind
of difficulty that like wears on my patience, I can't do anymore. Like when I was a kid, I had
all the patience in the world for it. But like, the difficulty that's just like, it's just there
and it's hard and you're doing it and you got to do it better. That's easy for me. Like anyone can
just do it and do it better each time. But like, you were talking about Hollow Knight, I played
Hollow Knight for a little while, I didn't beat it. Hollow Knight was kind of hard for me, just
because like, it all looked the same and I didn't know where to go and I had no patience for it.
I had no patience to explore this, this world because I got lost like Teminis and I'm like,
this game sucks, I hate it. Yeah, that'll happen. Yeah. I mean like, and it's not, I don't know if
it's a flaw of the game, like it sounds, maybe it is. The game starts with a particularly kind of
steep getting into a curve at the first like 20 minutes to an hour. I don't know if it like,
becomes more varied later on, but the first part of it, like every background looked the same and
I'm like, what, all these rooms are the same. I have no idea. Like at least with like Super Metroid,
every area has different music and different backgrounds. Some of the areas are more interesting
than others, for sure. Yeah, for sure, for sure. But I agree with Hollow Knight. I felt the same
way when I first played it too, which is captured on-stream during me and Mafia 1, so people can
go see it. Boy, I really gotta get back, I really gotta beat Hollow Knight. It's on my list of
shit I gotta get around to. We can all agree that, you know, games are hard, but nothing. No game is
more difficult than Team Fortress 2, because you're fighting in a multiplayer game. You're hunting
the most dangerous game of all, man. Yeah, because in multiplayer games, the skill ceiling will never
stop from getting higher. It will just keep going as players play the game for millions of hours and
they become super duper squads that completely destroy you. Until every single one of them is
basically Mario like glitch jumping up the like backwards, glitching up the infinite staircase.
Your skill set in a multiplayer game is social engineering that is legitimately one of the
skills you need to develop in order to be a proficient video game player in the multiplayer
scenario. Like when I hit 100 Charisma, what I realized, I could just go up and yell at the
competitors on the other side of the room to intimidate them into just giving up and leaving.
That's what I knew. I'd unlocked maximum gameplay skill. When you're not playing as part of a
professional group or even just playing with your friends exclusively, when you are matchmaking
online with maybe just one of your friends or even just alone, you will have people on your team in
any video game that you play, multiplayer, you know, shooter or whatever, that are shit. And you
have to figure out how to make them effective if you want to win. You can make your people,
it will often be said that, you know, you're just kind of fucked, you know, oh, my team was
sucked so bad. It's so bad. But literally, you just got to carry or you got to be able to tell them
what to do in ways that they understand. You got to be able to make them better. That's part of
how you have to play the game or to accomplish. It's literally a skill. It's like I've had like
the most like angry, angry gamer moments of all time where I like gnashed my teeth.
I've been witness to them. It was weird. It's very weird that you weren't really,
HIPAA's not very an angry guy. But for some reasons, TF2 just unlocks something that's
primal. It just makes me go fucking primal. Because I know it's not just, oh, like video
game a little difficult. It's that a person beat me and they're probably happy about it.
They're looking at my corpse and they're like, hey. That's the moment where you switch from full
retro to full gamer and just the explosion that follows is, you know. Yeah. And it's,
especially when like someone duels me, like I've played TF2 with Munchie before and he's
dueled me and I'm like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Probably the worst experience of my life.
God damn it. God damn it. Fine, fine, fine. Probably the worst experience of my life was
playing brawl with you, Munchie. For the same reason, because I could tell you were having fun
and I wasn't, and that was unacceptable. Yeah. I was having fun for the first, okay. I was having
fun for the first couple of minutes because I didn't know how the way it would turn out. And
also the last couple of minutes because you were actually fighting me and it was fun at the end
because it was a real game at the end. Yeah. This is that like deleted video, right? That never
No, no, no. Oh, no, no, no, not the slime fest was saved. Unfortunately. Yeah. And all it's
fucking misery. Okay. Um, uh, I was going to say something. TF2? TF2? Oh, oh, oh, oh, it's not.
Because she's got ink. Just wondering about that. Yes. Also, inkling is awesome. Yeah.
That's true. These aren't captured any device, but I'm going to specifically call out Ethan
because I've dueled Ethan many times before late at night. And the way he gets when he's losing a
duel is simply indescribable. The most bitter that he could possibly get. Like that I've seen
a human become where it's like, like when you know that he sees you when he goes completely dead
silent, I would describe him as corpse silent to the point where he could not make a motion
even if you wanted to. I'll do that. And the amount of like expression that leaves his body
when he dies after after a heated encounter can only be described as like the creation of a sun
in a way where it's like on a cosmic scale, sounds leave his body. And when things are over,
when the rounds over and I win the duel by like a couple points, like you can like I physically
like saw like his soul leaving. I look up to the sky and I saw it leaving his body reaching towards
heaven. And let me just if you're not familiar. Wait, I always forget. Munchy, have you read Jojo?
I never remember the answer to this question. Yeah. Of course I have. Yeah. Okay. You know those
moments where like a character dies and you see like their ghosts like yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
like that's even spirit like floating away from his deceased gamer corpse. Did I fight
Ethan? Munchy, did I fight? Is Ethan one of the guys that we hung out with that one time?
Yes, he is. That time when I that time when I killed everyone. Yeah, that was crazy. That was
ridiculous. Yes. Wait, when did that happen? That was three before before everyone got before
you were like like you weren't there. Yeah, every at the law point. Everyone was laughing like oh,
look at the old look at the elder millennial with his princess P. And she doesn't know how to play
smash. And I fucking went in there with my fucking peach and my fucking you know, with my hip,
this isn't my fucking floating in the air and my fucking kick where you can see your panties if
you had pause it and ate the black hole. Wait, which version? Speaking of that, Jesse, the most
memorable moment of that was when you were about to get a kill and like I think when the tournament
before you did you did that up smash and then you just pause and saw our skirt. And that was the
last thing that happened before the other person died. That's what I want them to see before I
killed them. The last brawl. Is this brawl? No, no, melee, melee. Oh, okay. Okay. Yeah. I also want to
say you fucking zoomers. I was born in melee. I was molded by like never that was the first time
that I had ever seen like all those people that I had talked to like the like like for years.
And I was so tired from radcon three that I was sleeping in the cab. I got out. They all greeted
me. They were all so happy to see me. And I was like, yeah, yeah. Hey, is there like a bed?
Radcon three was was was an intense experience. So understandable.
Isn't that you know, it's an interesting conundrum. Yeah, seriously, radcon four. I was I realized
recently it's been like a year since radcon three. Yeah, I was wondering why my chakras were so low.
And then I agree. Of course, I haven't been recharged at radcon in so long. My Christ consciousness
has been fading. Radcons are honestly a really great thing just to do every once in a while.
They make you just feel good and alive. Yeah, you're with people who you like and we're competent.
Sometimes I have a flash and I realized that like there's for the vast majority of people,
they hang out with their friends daily. Yeah, we never do that. And I don't I don't understand
how that's even a thing like like it's a yearly event for me. It's bizarre. It really does. It
takes me back to those high school days when you actually could see your friends every weekend and
like hang out and eat pizza and stuff and have like sort of a pizza party, you know. If you had
a microphone back in those days, some manner of podcast. Oh my god. Where if only I could find
that feeling again if only I could find those glory days again. What? But I can't I can't seem to see
it. I can't find it. I'm having a I'm having a flash. Where is it? Where is it? It's on the tip of my
tongue. I can't I can't remember. Can't go back to that place. We sealed those memories away long ago.
Where's the podcast? Hey, we've got voice signals about that. I mean, I feel like we just been
we got endless stuff to talk about today. We've only been gone for an hour. That's true. I'm just
saying we've got we've got stuff about that. But yeah, we can keep going. I mean, I can I can shift
gears a little and talk about Homestuck a little bit a little bit of Homestuck. I got the the the
was a book for act five act one, which is a big heavy tone. And I've been reading it and it's
great. It's with where all the trolls are introduced. Do you have all the books?
No, I specifically have been, you know, because I really only want the troll ones act five and
act five act two. And I already have all guys I didn't realize they were they had continued
making the books. But I guess yeah, well, once once Hussie got bought out by a media conglomerate
or whatever, whatever happened. Yes. Well, he's underneath it now. So like Homestuck.com is
you know, I mean, that's like how it's not like Bioware got bought up by Activision. And now
they're slowly dying. Oh, no, he there's nothing like wrong with like the Homestuck books, they just
got to kind of shitty covers. But that's how they're gonna make like the final flash into a book,
you know. Well, the same way they've been making flashes into a book form the whole time is just
take screen grabs and then underneath Hussie gives his author notes. So he says God, if only this
was online, you'd be really good time right now in some format, it was possible to create like
moving images. But alas, we're trapped on this stone cold. Yeah, I just want to brag I just want
to brag that I have I have the entire the entirety of problem sleuth in book form. Oh, dude, same.
It's high five. It's great. High fucking hoof, brother. Yeah. But yeah, specifically about this
book, though, the the the author commentary, which is under every page of these books. I have
book three already, the old book three, and I was reading those and those sort of interesting,
sometimes silly, sometimes sort of a pointless but you know, it's Andrew Hussie's writing and I
love Andrew Hussie's writing. So it's generally good. But with with the trolls, he kind of went
like super deep analytical like arm retrieval tier sort of explanations of all of these troll
characters and their place in the story and the way he was thinking when he was writing them.
And it was really insightful, especially when he got to risk and explained why
risk is canonically and like in an outside universe, his wife in every facet in every
single possible way. And he had so many notes. He had so many notes about it that like the notes
went from one page to the other and he had the arrows going literally just made his waifu like
the most important character. No, it's not as dumb as that. Maybe it is. But like it was just
that the role she had in the story is like one little snippet of notes that I can try and remember
was that as she is like the bitch character, she's like the trolliest of trolls. She causes the
controversy and she like attacks and like tries to fuck up everyone's shit constantly. And she is
like sort of like a like a tier two surrogate author character, because the way he was talking
about it was as an author, you create your creations and then you give them problems to overcome.
And the more problems you give them and the harsher, you know, punishment you deal them,
you know, the more dramatic it becomes. And so Vriska being his favorite and like in universe
love interest, because his character is a character in the comic, like he loves Vriska,
is like part of the fact that she is kind of doing what he would otherwise be doing as an
author, you know, that is like putting problems in the way of the create the OCs he's made.
Is this like what he was thinking when he wrote her? Or is this him reflecting in the hindsight
and being like, you know, I could probably formulate an argument for this combination.
The way it comes across in the way he's writing, I mean, sometimes he does like say,
yeah, the reason I probably did this was because I was lazy, but I'd like to think it was some other
reason like he's quite about it. No, no, no, but he is being accurate, like some things he feels
are lazy. But it's usually just visual things. But things with like the trolls, he thought of
all the trolls before he started, he just didn't know what they look like. Or like, you know,
he came up with the zodiac signs, and the 12 of them, and then he came up with little things,
like he probably had a notepad with like, this is various things that can all these characters
can mean. And then he wrote them down. And then as he as he was going through, like,
Act five, Act one was like made really quickly, using all new assets and all new alien technology
and world building that he was kind of making up as he went. And it was, it's just, it's just
really brilliant to see. And I totally believe that the notes that he leaves behind, leaves under
the pages explaining his thought process, because it doesn't seem completely impossible. It just
seems like he had an idea, he went with it, and then he made it continue to work in the future.
And the ones, the trolls that weren't important became nothing.
Act one, I would be especially interested in reading his notes about.
They're all online. You can read them as the arm retrieval guy. It may sound weird that I'm
very, very quick to come to Hussie's defense here. Because Hussie is no idiot. He's not stupid.
Act six is not the work of someone who is just simply stupid. The thing is that he doesn't care
anymore. I have no doubt about Hussie's right ability. As he's shown, he like in the early
acts of homes like he is literally like probably my favorite writer ever. He just, I resonate with
his work more or so about than any other person in the world or earth that I've had. So it's not,
I don't think that Hussie just became stupid or that it's hard for me to believe that he had all
of these things planned out when he was originally writing the trolls. That's not unrealist to me
whatsoever. So I have no reason to doubt him that he can articulate the way that he felt before.
Well, some things are straight up retconned as they go along. So not every single thing was planned
from the beginning. Well, sure. But these major things that tie into the entirety of a character
who's probably playing. You know, I bet if we really dug into that, I could point out some
ways that it's not as brilliant as everybody seems to think it is. I mean, I don't know what
specifics we're talking about. If you understand the things that Hussie writes and the reasoning
he's giving for why he writes them that way, you come to understand that no, it's more likely that
he came up with the things and then he just got lazy later and didn't give a shit about making
the art very good. Like that's far more likely based on what I know about him and his writing.
Exactly. I think about the things that I know about him. What are the elements of this? There
is a pseudo self insert character. Very Hussie happens all the time. Aside from his literal
self insert, he describes very often in many old form springs about how many of the characters are
aspects of himself in very clear ways. Like he refers to Dave and Dirk as author inserts in
many ways. What are the other elements of this? You know, Riska being like a force, like just a
force for chaos and a force to drive the storm. Yeah, for the authorial wrath. Yeah, that is also
very Hussie and just his general attitude and way he's described things in his general humor style
is often just inflict pain upon others. And it's literally just something that he likes to do.
I don't think that's that's that's weird. I was I was saying I was saying on the I was saying on
the video before that just makes me so mad. It makes me so mad that people in this day and age
in 2019 year of our lord will roll their eyes at Homestuck and not and think of it as anything
other than just a brilliant work of genius. Hey man, I love Homestuck. Yeah, despite all its flaws,
like people that haven't read Homestuck, they just go like yeah. Yeah, Homestuck. Yeah, that's
dumb thing. Isn't it impossible to read more? Isn't it like impossible to read now though,
because the flash is down or whatever? No, no, it was the website. The website has changed and
the some of the flashes have been replaced with well all of the flashes exist, but you just have
to click on a little I was in which is the site from flash version to like non flash version. I
was in a comic book store and I saw like all of Homestuck in book form. And I was thinking like
how the hell does that work? I thought it was like a game or something. I would not want to read
it in book form. Not first, at least. No, not first. Yeah. It's definitely like a supplemental
item. And I like having it as an object. I like reading the author. It's like buying the soundtrack
to a sheet like or something. It has to lose so much. I flipped through it to try and like
understand like how you put this thing in a book. And it's like, yeah, all the things that
used to be like one sequential page of a like a website are now like all put together as panels
in a page. And it's like you are John Egbert and you're fucking over here and you're doing this
and it's like all on one page. And I'm like, how the fuck do you read this? Where do these words
go? Well, it's it was very confusing. It's not great. It's not great. I have I have book one and
two. And I regard them fondly. And I love to read the commentary. But it is. It's not fun to read.
I don't like it. Like it's not a great home stuck not so great. Just not good.
I've got the problem sleuth books. You know, I like them. I like reading them. But like the
animated segments lose like most of their impact much. Yeah, like they lose basically it's not
even an adaptation. It's just a straight copy paste like without any like you adapt a manga to an
anime like you do an a real adaptation you redraw you reformulate. But this is just you know,
basically like a flash zip file with the PNG is copied over to well, I mean, there's a little bit
like like the sepulchretude parts. There's like, you know, like the the it sort of flows out like
it like kind of covers the page and parts and like, I mean, there is some adaptation going on
there. But yeah, I mean, oh, by the way, the troll romance section was notes were really funny.
And I would recommend you at least try and find the notes. He was like making fun of
those wasn't he wasn't that like his main goal with that? Yeah, yeah. Well,
he was basically explaining how it's not actually as ridiculous as it looks. And it's
basically just human. It's just human romance. But with certain aspects of human romance given
silly names, and he made it look like ridiculous. And so people were freaking out and he was like,
that's the sort of thing he likes doing. Yeah, I mean, it's great. Definitely. I mean, there's
there's nothing like he brings when he brings the trauma romance back, he's like, oh, you don't
think I'm going to do it. And he has like all the text from all those pages, but like in tiny,
tiny, tiny typeface filling an entire page. And then like on the other page opposite is just him
doing that the laughing like haha. Got him. And it's like, wow. And then in the author notes
underneath both of those pages, he also put the exact same text. Oh, you know, it'd be really
funny if I put all of this troll romance stuff in the author notes as well. Oh, you don't think
I'll do it. And then he does like it's so hard to read funny. I can't believe Hussie never dabbed
a single time in the entire course of Homestuck. You might be able to find some some some dab like
positions there. I think I think just wasn't it wasn't a big did I mention okay, I think I might
have talked about this. Stop me if I've told this before. But I really like these videos by John
Boyce called like pretty good. And just he does like things about sports that are interesting.
And he and his he and one of his cohorts at SB nation discovered discovered the very first dab,
like the pro the proto dab. Was it Michael Jackson or something? No, it was just done by some player
on the on the the Troy State basketball college basketball team in the Troy State versus DeVry
University basketball game that holds the record for most baskets scored in a basketball game ever
in any in any league. But but how can you actually know that's really the first one though? I always
thought well it's the first one anyone's ever seen. The dab was like taken in inspiration at
least from Usain Bolt when he does the thing with pointing with two hands in the same direction.
You know that what I think I know what you're talking about. Yeah, who knows the same sort of
thing. I mean, okay, the guy in this the guy in this like record breaking basketball game,
he doesn't do like a full and he does sort of like a double mover like first he brings his arms to
the side and then he sort of bends over and like kind of moves them up in a in a it's sort of it's
like a proto dab. Yeah, okay, okay, it's not quite a dab as we understand it today. But it is, you
know, it has all the underpinning evolution. It has all the ideological underpinnings of a dab.
Uh, yes, okay. I think that's neat. Word. So what about the fastest dab of all time? Oh,
I can do that. Have you seen that video of the dude do moving at light speed? Have you guys seen
the video electrocuted myself to dab? No, there I was shown a fantastic YouTube channel highly
recommended. Michael Reeves, he is a like a baby, the smallest genius ever made, but he is perhaps
the funny it like the smartest person on earth. Okay, I'm sure it's really smart exclusively
exclusively for evil. I'm sure he's a technical creative genius. But he does things like programming
a robot to shoot him when he gets shot in fortnight or or electrocuting his muscles to force
him to dab. I'm gonna link it down right now. Okay, that's great. But please also review this
quickest dab ever caught on film. I love quickest dab. It's like it's like watching a frog catch a
fly with its tongue. It's so fast. It's so just you can't comprehend it in real time. Yeah, no,
the I can't catch it. I don't think the camera even caught the whole motion in like in he did it
like with between frames he hit the dab and then it's like there's just like the suggestion of the
motion indeed you understand but you understand what happens god damn impressive impressive. It's
like pornography you can't quantify it but you know there's something going on when you see you know
a dab when you see it. You can't you can't define a dab. Yeah, electrocuting my muscles to force me
to dab. He's screaming in pain. Did it work? Yeah. Oh, it worked. It worked perfectly. Damn,
but what was what was the trigger for the electrocution? These medical grade like electrodes
that he had strapped on to his entire body like like on his shoulders on his back that would
hide in the high frequency electricity signals to certain parts but parts of his body to cause
the spasm uncontrollable. Okay, I'm with you on that but the only issue with that is how do we
know that this is even true because we can't like prove he did it on an unsuspecting person who
didn't know what's happening but you could say he was lying but he does like I don't know I believe
him he does he does multiple like truth checks to like really okay yeah okay I'll have to check it
out more thoroughly um a robot shooting when I get shot in fortnight he um he like he like
does like a like a close-up of his muscles while they're spasming and like in a way that like I
don't think that you would be able to like fake if even if you wanted to and I see he's using the uh
the strand's cutaneous uh electrical nerves oh wait I thought it was a meme it the acronym is
shit but it just doesn't matter wait never mind wait you mean you meant like the the the place
where he put the electrodes makes the specific muscles that forces him to literally do the
dab yeah I thought it was like yeah whoa I thought it was like um if you don't dab you get electrocuted
or something no that's pretty that's that's way more sciencey and impressive yeah I like this
channel this channel confuses me there's there's a weird uh uh anomaly you scroll through his videos
there's like trigger me Elmo electrocuting my muscles to force me to dab I built the stupidest
gun in the world but if you scroll all the way down amongst all this stuff there's just like
two C sharp tutorials yeah I don't understand are they like tongue-in-cheek or no that's so odd
I'm trying to scroll through to see him like electrocuting his dab muscles I just want to see
it work it's towards the end yeah yeah it's there it's there
I mean he's the guy seems to be we got to watch this video like thoroughly to to analyze the
yeah yeah you know up front okay but anyway people enough on that uh uh uh I mean anybody else got
anything they want to talk about because I'm just letting you know we have like a bunch of voicemails
so we could spend a while on that a bunch we have like like 17 I'm not anything that isn't
home stuck because I have nothing to contribute fair enough Tom you got to read it you got to read
it dude it's the only way I had to get through Naruto Kai yeah Naruto Kai that should be your thing
Tom didn't you want to like didn't you want to like school me about like politics on the last episode
no I would but the point of me bringing it up was just that I thought it was gay that it ruined
the awesome art vibe I was having oh okay fair enough and then you told me I don't think I had that
I mean I remember Tom saying I think you tweeted the other day at the tweet I very much sympathized
with that was like something about like have lots of political things but the only thing I hate more
than political ideas I disagree with is tweeting about politics I know the thing about the tweet
the actual tweet was I have tons of strong political opinions but my strongest political
opinion is I hate talking about political right right okay um gay well fair enough fair enough
okay but regardless we got like a million fucking things we might as well get a million I'm not
something like there are 17 of these okay summer summer but um but uh okay the good news is uh we've
got uh some pizza party podcast updates here uh oh so let's just check in uh let me see this one is
okay this one's called where's the podcast okay let's let's see what this one has to say
eternal question I'm watching Michael Reeves just scream and pain as he's muscles forcibly
dab for him that's great great well while you're in agony listen to this uh as well
everyone was too busy asking where's the podcast that nobody bothered to ask
how's the podcast and I just think that's pretty sad I already know that it has to be
the most glorious podcast it has to be the thing that will finally fill that void in me
that I'm just I'm just every day all day I'm just scarfing content I'm just opening up my
brain hole and scooping as much content into it as I possibly can just to fill something to fill
that hole to fill some need in me that I can't even identify and I know that the pizza party
podcast would be it if only I could find it out there in the vast nothingness that is our modern
reality speaking of filling holes okay stick with me for a second uh has anyone ever read
that uh I forget his name ito I eat oh okay he knows exactly where I'm going uh there's this
there's this one the cracks in the rock or something I forget what it's called but it's
about a girl who I forget what happens she gets like grease on her and it creates a bunch of like
holes in her skin and it just happens more and more uh like her whole body gets covered in
these disgusting holes and she finds kind of joy in inserting things into them it gives her pleasure
so I'm just so just the the money shot is at the very end the final page is like her mom walks
out on her alone in a room that's her whole body is not only covered with holes but has
all been filled by objects that she's pleasuring herself with all these holes all over her body
as she says to her mom mom I need more I can't fill all the holes and that's now that's that's
how's the podcast by the way ever since you mentioned it uh I have been vigorously editing
this image and I have this to show for you I've created it is hussy dabbing that's uh you know
not a bent elbow there but it's better than nothing it's the best we could do it's the best
we could do again another prototype dab sort of thing is it done is it it's over yes we're done
describing gross things did you wait did you post a picture it's in the gross disgusting audio
links gross disgusting yeah oh oh I see I see now I was talking about the holes um not oh no no no
no images of that no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no all right all right alright I'll maybe I can find it but I'll I'll let people imagine it it's
Junji Ito you can google it whole girl or something uh but let's move on uh we've got another one about
the pizza party podcast, this is from uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh
millennium for all i know as my chakras were scrambled realign multiply divided hive and download the special event chakra events they were giving out and i've realized why should i just do all the work for you and tell you where it is no you want to experience this you put in the fucking effort and i've made it more difficult just despite you in my pizza party tenure i rose through the ranks tooth and nail in the arena undefeated until covered in blood and mozzarella ice
to death in my glory the pizza party president himself wanted audience with me and we did business saucy
cheesy business and i got it so that the sign outside looks just like any peter piper pizza by the way
that's canon now time honored pc p fan marin pan is affiliated with the peter piper pizza that's real
good luck finding it now you piece of shit and i thought you ever had a chance before marin pan you
piece of shit you pizza shit mother fucker where's the fucking podcast you gotta tell me i think this is my only in because he's obviously
like genetically related to pan pizza marin pan pan pizza that's no mistake that's obviously intentional
and it obviously has an unfair advance like oh yeah is it really a surprise when that's not
nepotism finds his father's fucking business yeah you know it's not it's not really that impressive dude
i can't this is a you know this is collusion this is collusion against me literally listen
uh what is it and i and i hear that's illegal yeah i heard it's bad i don't really know why but i know
i'm not supposed to like it okay the quest marches onward as always uh but uh so here's a little uh
voicemail called maximizing pcp enjoyment just as a preface to the voicemail so oh i almost forgot to
say um uh speakpipe.com slash whatever link below pcp voicemails uh but let's see what our friend here
maximizing has to say i've discovered the optimal way of listening to the pcp and viewers you too
can maximize your enjoyment by just doing one simple thing and that is leaving a message oh my god if
you leave a message you'll be listening to the whole episode standing on your fucking on your
fucking tippy toes sitting on the edge of your seat your balls full and your dick rock hard just
waiting to see if your message is gonna get played at the end oh my god the second that they say uh
time to move on to voicemails i fucking start coming over and oh my god one of my messages do get
played oh you can bet your ass that i'm just cooming yes i was gonna say imagine the contractions
taking place in him right now straight into my penis into my butthole and i love it leave a fucking
message and you can be a god like me there you go bro that man just experienced the greatest
pleasure of his or anyone else's life and you can too at at at speakpipe.com slash something
i'd never remember it i always forget link in the description it's there it's easier just to link on it
to the click to type it so you might as well um okay so now that's out of the way leave messages to
enhance your own enjoyment people um here is although i'm sure for most it's vast disappointment
because most of them do not get played uh but you'll still you're you're you're it's like it's like
why do people play the lottery they don't win every time why do they keep playing because yeah but
one glorious that one glorious win that one that one hit yeah they'll have you coming back for more
that's what you need the difference between the lottery and the pcp voicemail though is that this
is a test of skill so you can improve your odds by getting better much like the discussion that
opened the show it's all about skill the difference between uh gambling and sending a voicemail to the
pcp is that with the pcp even if you win you still lose with gambling you actually do win
there's the chance however remote okay next voicemail is from a free thinker but spelled with
like numerals instead of the vowels like fr three three you know thinker one three etc yeah let's see
what this maverick has to say you're paying the you're paying the picture for me indeed all right
let's go there it goes wait listen to me iphone warriors in worldwide poverty-stricken hermitages
believe the picture and see the truth two plus four equals six six equals seven seven equals eight
equals ending the eternal control of hyperfuckers sissy boy prostate gods and latino cream king
warriors forever look at the numbers flying into your eyeballs and adjust them through
intestines and outpiece the thinker of eternity into your brainwaves reverberating worldwide
into four billion people globe wide into pure strain gold poverty forever culminating in the
free market system equals eternal peace and liberty for all souls in the sensual chokehold
of steely dan's enormous man pussy clitoris all microblogged in the ever-watching eyesight
ear zones of tv iphone metacasts living surrounded by the lie of cigarette cash truth youth exo
criminals written on to the parchment of our mind souls bodies consciousness by the enron
international playboy vice lords committee of local boner lords computerized sex lords triumph
endlessly in the hills of your dreams death life free market and damnation running throughout your
veins into the deadly living world sight sound robot conspiracy of pyramid scheme ultimate hell
world death crime rip babies from the arms of mothers what's the direction of ultimate hell
world super king cock socks asshole feeding tubes even say deliver perfect poison intravenously
well-paid spokesmen say every timing sales oh my god oh i got cut i just learned whoa i think
going but it only gives you 90 seconds i got no no i gotta say i'm alex joe i'm truly humbled
that uh the guy who has taped the ceiling landing called into the show yeah yeah yeah thank god that
check the show notes people uh that guy taped to the ceiling while in a land party just called in
with that his his euphoric message well while taped to the ceiling as he is still as he is to
this very day thought it was convinced we're actually restraining his hour we had to win
to win to fucking seal him away god uh yeah accurate accurate um okay uh wait let me just
post this in the audio links thing okay there all right uh next one is we've got a voicemail from
i'd like a refund mr pcp oh okay uh i can already i definitely not i would like to ask
why uh do my fries have shit in them and why is their hair in the shade on my fries why why did
you do this mr procrastinator i'd like a refund on my fries uh thanks what's it with my people not
being able to take fucking spice oh yeah i just oh just take everything fucking plain you know you
can't have fries with shit in it you can't have shakes with piss in it oh yeah just my god just
don't add flavor to anything that you fucking entirely why these guys i personally contaminated
all of the pcp fries because they're not keto and i don't agree with you the customer eating them
although i do want you to continue to buy them and keep funneling us more of your pc pennies
that's fair thank you and god bless regardless just like like a fucking absolute version putting
salt and pepper on to season why not have the embodiment of all food the extra the extraction
of everything that was good about literal poop shit yes literal poop the culmination of what food
was meant to be washed it down with your piss shake my dude that's the only thing you got to do
shit is such a complex flavor it's not basic it's not fucking five guys version shit it's
fucking true so it's true catch me at the local cafe at the local pcp cafe sipping my piss shake
as you walk up and say like an idiot why are you drinking your own piss nate to which i brilliantly
reply um it's safe to drink your piss three times to which you restate nate why are you drinking
your piss to which i again reply um it's safe to drink your piss three times what more do i have
to explain about this regardless energy it saves the environment johnny walker third harvest
and regardless to your request of refund denied okay moving on we've got another voicemail the
fact will charge you again yeah double charge uh thanks for the credit card number idiot uh rodine
has a voicemail for us let's listen up you probably turned this off once you know who i am
i used to go by the name binary dude and was hailed by jesse as the worst commenter of all time
oh yes looking back i can simply see why it was everything that i said was my fault and i know
like probably jesse gets to do a lot but from that moment from like three days since that moment i
end on i just became really unsatisfied with how i was speaking the internet in general i did not know
it was completely because of my autistic fucking retardedness because i just didn't think about it
and just how that can look like like actually affect someone's day just a thought of ruining
someone's day because of some bullshit i said online is something that stayed with me and
actually altered my behavior on how i deal with this stuff online so even though i had no redemption
arc and of course i didn't act like a fucking jackass um at least i got that awareness and for
whatever for whatever that's worth i am completely sorry to jesse he's actually a guy i uh tried to
watch every video nowadays whenever they come up um so i probably there's nothing i can say that like
okay okay we got it disconnect is is too sad i thought i thought i thought it's over it's over
i thought there was a joke coming i thought there was gonna be a subversion of my expectations
that was worse than a bad comment all right that's fair i you're fucked up even harder this time
yeah i thought i thought i'd show him because just here's a guy who's who's who's who's who's
trying to redeem himself and i would just think it isn't that nice to see someone you know i do
remember the guy i don't remember what his comment was about i remember like an argument i think
like a long argument i remember writing paragraphs and paragraphs and like i remember like months
after that maybe a year after that he like he found like my defunct endless jest facebook page and like
messaged me like a private message to me like this even more massive like apology oh and that was
years ago that was years ago so this guy has been like stewing in this for years well you know what
maybe this will be his catharsis the fact that he was able to to be on here maybe he can rest in
peace at long last hopefully i mean i i don't even know what i don't remember what was bad about it
i'm sure your comment was horrible but i don't care you know this is the funny thing i i'm sure
that i've since seen many worse commenters in fact i i can guarantee it so don't please don't
beat yourself up about it anymore well yeah than you already have i think there's a lesson to be
learned here that that's something like well well it's possible he may have been a total pants on
head retarded commenter at one point like you don't need external validation necessarily like if
you've changed your ways or whatever and you're like you know what i'm not gonna do this anymore
don't feel like you you need like odds are the person you're wrong like they don't care anymore
you know maybe sometimes they might uh but certainly as like as if you're like a shitty
commenter odds are even if you were like a jerk or you made a bad impression on somebody odds are
they don't like specifically remember you or anything so if you just improve your overall
behavior going forward then you'll probably you know that that's really the best good you
can do for the world i'd say probably oh i don't want to shout out specific bad commenters right
now i don't want to cut out spider he makes these comments about how the piece of your
shit and you know keep it up dude and calls me out regularly and you know great job with that
however how much ironic this is cardinal sin which makes me so fucking mad spider just make one
long comment i hate that you make eight new fucking comments on the new episode video that's
your comments to find just put them one it must be so fucking mad when i scroll down
i see your name 500 times right the one i beg you no dude more comments is more engagement it
helps with the algorithm shut up well does youtube know that though i mean maybe does youtube know
about their algorithm i do you think i've heard about this has anyone told them about this algorithm
thing like it's really fucking us up uh maybe we just told them maybe if it knows it's the same
person commenting it doesn't get counted i don't know i don't know okay well in any case i'm begging
in any case in any case thank you for continuing to watch my videos i guess please don't hate yourself
anymore i think he'll he'll get over it he's he's pulling those big boy pants all is forgiven
my son okay moving on uh speaking of forgiveness we're gonna need some after this because it's the
lost tape archive number two digi bro uh let's see what we've got awaiting us
i was making sandcastles with billy the bitch boy today there was something glistening in the
sand nice so i pummeled his castle with my almighty fist he cried i rejoiced another day
from digi bro
digi bro whispered in my ear just how much he loves the taste of my semen on his lips
i was it's my why is he all you were saying this i sure hope nobody finds his taste
i've gotta go digi you never told me about such intimate secrets i'll tell you what digi
mr bro i've got something else to tell you there are no castles left for i've consumed the
deserts of the earth
fuck damn that was we waited for a while for that what was this guy's name uh this is the the
fuck what is it it's the the lost tapes archive number two digi bro that's the
miss the first one holy shit it was there i mean i forget what it was about but it was uh it was
something go listen that that was a really good iago i mean that was a yeah that was a yeah it
wasn't a gilbert godfrey it was iago specifically yeah that would make for a really good uh like
fan art of digi bro sucking iago's birdcock is that what you're talking about of like of like a
lip-sync animation of iago like a get a disney anime like james baxter in here yeah to draw that
like actually being like to say to see him like in disney style say digi bro sucked my fat car
you know an Aladdin when the when the sultan uh tries to give iago a cracker and iago doesn't
want it uh it's short it's shoved down his fore uh his throat and then jafar says you certainly
have a way with the dumb animals that that scene should have gone like uh sultan like shoved down
his throat and then he goes like actually eating food makes me sort of anxious now yeah i haven't
eaten in like three days because i'm just too high just makes me anxious to eat now
yeah i i it should have gone that way uh miscast mis mis mis written is cast okay let's move on uh
next may i'm just yeah go on then i'm just pleased as punch i'm just pleased as punch good we got
we got quality things here on the on the on the i don't know part two the real whatever on whatever
show this is yeah i don't remember uh okay zoomer joe is calling in once again uh let's give him a
floor challenge he looks like sniper joe but he just has like a bernie 2020 hat on him that's him
okay go hey guys it's me zoomer joe again this time i'm calling in from my vr headset actually i'm
doing a new challenge a new zoomer challenge that all the kids are doing it's called calling to the
procrastinator's show while in vr but the vr room that you're in is actually a room with your
mother staring intently at you looking disappointed that's what i'm doing i'm calling you right now
i'm speaking these words while staring into the disapproving soulless eyes of my very own mother
well i gotta go now zoom i like the zoom i like the action he did it he he beat the challenge
what was the challenge wow call into the channel oh i like how it's not a challenge for anyone else
it's just a challenge for him and he's already completed it by the time he calls well you just
gotta get your mom to fucking to fucking you know understand what you're doing so she'll look at
you disappointedly oh and then and then the challenge begins incidentally zoomer joe after
listening to last episode he left a separate message and said do not play the one i just played
he said play the other one the thing is though this one was funnier than the other one so i just
didn't want to you made the executive decision indeed i did and it paid off in spades yep all
all right i think so cool okay moving on uh we've got another call from correct correct okay go
okay spell differently hey you fucking nuts i'm curious given someone who disagrees with you
do you tend to believe more frequently that they have been misled by a set of incorrect information
or do you tend to believe that they just value different things to you i that's a real question
i assume i will assume that they are misinformed first and only only only after like only after
like serious probing of the subject we like disappointedly conclude that their their core
values are just fucked because they're different from mine right uh you know i've uh i've noticed
that i've i think for a long time i've been possibly a way too charitable arguer and that
like i'm it seems like when i argue i'm looking for ways generally with someone i would like
respect and don't think it's like a total idiot i'll i'll look for ways to like you know make them
seem like to really straw a steel man their argument i guess like i guess that's what i'm
just describing a really steel man arguments and i want to touch on like wait what what is a steel
man well it's it's the opposite of a straw man or what you're well sort of an opposite it's what
what you're trying to do is give the strongest best possible interpretation of your like quote
unquote opponents did you make this up no no it's it's making the rounds i i didn't make it up um
it's it's pretty good though it's uh i mean i pretty much believe in it i think it's like the
best way to get to like good faith arguments though to to abide by it so i guess just answer
his question i think i think that i generally go to like my default now is that people have
different values that's that's seems to be where i start whether that's smart or not i don't know
i i i start arguing text because if i am to take this in the way it's probably obviously
meant and like the stuff we've been talking about recently about politics and stuff like that yeah
i think most likely my my first reaction is why do you think that like like what like why are you
thinking that and that could be your misled but i don't know if i know i don't know if i make a
judgment on whether what people do i just kind of want to find out why and then i'll make my
decision based upon it but if i had to like guess like it like what do i think the people at large
like are they irrational or are they rational i would say i think like they are like just they
had different values than me in general i i think that it they might not just be like
led astray yeah i don't know that's a particularly healthy way i think i've come to a conclusion
about this that might seem radical to some yeah i i have come to find that opinions in general
having opinions is just wrong and it's bad and i so i i don't have any i strive to have evolved
beyond the need for any opinion so that i can just fucking float and just like be like water you know
that's kind of what the monks do right they try to just dissociate from reality because like you
know because humans are not rational humans are highly irrational highly stupid morally
bankrupt evil sacks of shit every single one of them and like every opinion that you see
if you talk to these people even a good opinion that you think is good even an opinion that you
might agree with if you talk to these people and if you scratch the surface you will find
the insanity behind everyone's reasoning everyone has their own fucked up just their
brains are just shit everyone's brain is just shit and piss and cum and it's just that's all
there is even even even something that you think sounds smart if you really scratch the surface
and talk to the person long enough you'll realize they only think that because of something fucking
wrong with their brain everyone is fucked no opinions allowed i don't like them just everyone
just be like water man just fill the glass you're in okay fuck it there there's go with it i mean
it kind of makes sense i mean when you get like to like a large enough scale like if you're like a
president or like a a dictator whatever like you don't treat like your subjects even if you're like
the smartest rule it doesn't really make sense to like treat your rule like your subject like they're
all like perfect philosophers who you know are able to like totally like you appeal to like
their interests like if you got like a farming population you're like okay let's like lower
taxes on like seeds and i don't know if you there's somebody else you don't like let's raise taxes on
something else it's like boom i just boosted my popularity and you can even may argue that like
that was like a good thing because there's like more farmers in the country than there are i don't
know like lawyers or something and so was this an objective good uh i don't know maybe uh may i feel
like i just got whiplash right now how is this really what was just saying what just being said
well i'm just like i'm i'm trying to make a comparison of like the the how there's no like
there's no inherent like correctness in any kind of like political idea that a lot of it is just
coming down to like a person's personal values like that you could call you can call that just
like their own personal madness just like that's not that's not the that's not the question well i
know i'm just responding to jesse's point though and i'm aware i'm you know wondering a little bit
i don't think it's totally irrelevant like all these people commenting on on my videos like oh
your opinion is bad you have the wrong opinion and it's like you don't get it it's not my opinion
it's all made up i made it up because it's funny fuck you i can't be right or wrong i don't fucking
give a shit what you think i'm wrong about resident evil too because i said i hate it i lied
it's great you fucking morons you clods you dumbasses you're just playing right into my hands
um i don't know correct i have no fucking opinion i can't be wrong i have no opinion so i'm always
right that's the perfect flawless position unassailable from any side uh well moving on
let's move on to comments our sin by our next commenter comments our sin uh go
in regard to the point that ben made last podcast about not wanting to have comments associated
with your work because inherently when there's comments under like a youtube video you associated
with it when i was reading through hunter hunter on the most unsavory of online sites i found this
one motherfucking commenter who at the end of every chapter would just post the most
uninsightful vapid trying to be funny he had a fucking he had the fucking um guts icon
the guts face where he's like smiling really big and it just made me hate him even more
to know that he ride berserk as well but it was just like he developed a cult of personality
in this comment section people would comment and say just hate him just attack him and he
would just keep doing it and he got stronger from it and all i can think of is just like why
is this part of my hunter hunter experience why is it tied to this now but also why am i so interested
fair question you got sucked into the cult man we got a deep platform guts guy
he's like uh he can't he can't keep getting away with it who's that one famous commenter
kevin why or something is that him you know i'm talking about uh you talking about retro
gamer kevin no no there's this guy who comments on like every does the y stand for yellow i don't
know god damn all right let's move on i guess um wait who is kevin why there there is like a famous
youtube commenter with like he's got several hundred thousand subs but no videos and his thing
is that he just comments on like every video uh it just goes around and like is a notable
commenter on youtube are are they good comments i don't think they're that good i'm not really
sure i haven't studied them how did this happen they can't possibly be that good how could this
how could this have happened yeah this is a mistake we need to detach his platform i don't know i don't
know i i mean he's he's not benefiting from it because he doesn't make videos it's just no what
if he had his own patreon like just to support his comment does he have a silver play button
sorry oh maybe he should get the silver play button as like a creator on youtube right maybe
you have to have one video the only one who never made a video to get the silver play button
he might he gets like a silver like a comment submit button instead oh yeah yeah it just says submit
he's a hero um anyway well that's fascinating yeah he's a fascinating guy and this this this
comment this this voicemail uh was interesting as well and it's just yeah like i don't know like
with somebody like me who reads one piece weekly and stuff i go to like 4chan on a and like talk
about it in a group but that's like me seeking that out specifically like on on manga stream or
gymonies box or whatever like there's no comment section like directly under it so i i'm totally
free of that and it's great and i'm super happy that that's the case uh so yeah i don't know i it's
i definitely will impact like the delivery of the content if there's like you know
visible comments around it or on it or whatever so uh yeah you know it's always felt really weird
to me um and i also keep looking at them even though i hey i don't like them at all is uh
comments under like hentai and porn yeah we talked about that and and comments on porn are so weird
like i remember like uh that on the site site frequent there was always this one guy who would
have something funny to say on every page of every dojin and hentai i was like
like what what are you doing and then like he it can be cool but then he's sort of it's the same
sort of thing the cult of personality people started to recognize this guy and then people
started to imitate this guy and and like there was a whole there was a whole like subculture on
this porn site people were jacking off and then laughing or like hating got any examples of like
what he might say in general uh i mean it was never like unfunny it was just sort of like
i'm trying to jack off this is a porn time sure what does he get out of it what does he get out
of posting a little bit of community a little community in this particular you know forum or
whatever well but there was no form like back and forth it was just like he was throwing his thing
out in there and then people would keep seeing it well i mean it's i think that the what you get
out is just yeah it's exactly that it's like you like you're here obviously people do come here
to some degree if you comment they might see your thoughts and it might you know feel kind of nice
if people like or see your comments especially if as this guy has it becomes kind of a thing that you
do so i'm not saying it's a lot but i'm saying there's there's something of value same with you
too i want to like go off i'm like how this is so weird how people spend their time and build
community but i spent like three years talking about my little pony so i have no i've no ground
not too different from that equally sexual i'd say
okay let's move on hey season nine just premiered like yesterday uh no it did is this the last season
yeah oh god oh no what are we gonna do guys what are we gonna do our revenue stream is gonna dry out
yeah this is our cash cow i watched the latest episodes of my own did i ever talk about this
no i don't think so no i watched a handful of them you mentioned it once or twice how they how they
hold up i um how do they hold up yeah uh on how the age paralleled okay so i watched this
probably the worst possible way that i could go about doing it and that's um i watched season eight
and sevens uh start and end in reverse order okay so i watched four two parts in reverse order
so i watched the end of season eight the beginning of season eight the end of season seven and the
beginning of season seven and uh it was sort of like being on drugs in a way that like you can't
really trust what your body is perceiving sure uh the first thing being thrown back into the arena
after uh you know being away from from hashtag enter the arena hashtag right before exactly uh
was okay the end of season eight was unbelievable how much change from really what i just dude i've
seen the like collections of new characters and i'm like who are these people what is this okay
it's uh it's pretty insane it's bizarre there's like a weird like red not not knowing what happened
between net then isn't like tirak back as like a good guy or something now i think i saw that
he was back in a new episode he was in the most latest uh latest episode all right the last thing
i remember happy to my little pony is twilight and the main sick go to like a parody of new
york and rarity is there and she makes dresses and she works herself too hard yeah i remember that
now twilight is the headmaster of a school what there's a literal weird white nationalist pony
who wants to wipe out the other sub races dude yes this school is meant to be for ponies only
these beasts are not fit these not fab to the equestria school unified school district guidelines
is is there a pony is there a pony trump is this pony um it might as well be this guy it might as
well be this guy imagine if imagine if like ponyville got a new mayor like they elected a new and he's
like orange and he has like a big like swooshy blonde mane and he's all like wrinkly and stuff he's
like a mean boy gotta build a wall like is is is is the headmaster they wouldn't do it too they would
fucking do you know honestly he got elected because he was colluding with the dragons they don't forget
my little pony came down hard against communism so i don't think they're like that uh i don't know
anti trump e i mean maybe i'm just talking to everyone knows communism's bad but uh that's that's
like uh like a big jump to take all right all right you know what you know what that's a huge
jump that i sound dumb okay fair point i i i i will give them credit i think they're a little bit
most of the world agrees communism isn't great but i gotta get into the world i think we know
what's going on okay anyway much but i'm sorry okay so so twilight is the headmaster of a school
and the main six are like teachers at this giant college is erected in ponyville is what is your
high on is fluttershy a teacher too yeah i think it makes sense that doesn't make sense she wouldn't
be a team why do they make what fluttershy in fact has won teacher of the month for like two years in
a row because she fucks her students because she won't say no that's why she has low self-esteem
she makes up for it like all sexy young women do by becoming ethos uh and this is the closest you
can get um wait i don't nate i don't see your logic here that fluttershy wouldn't be fit to be a teacher
isn't she i don't know she doesn't seem like she's like she's the element of kindness she's
she's the she's the perfect teacher okay isn't she like what about pinkie pinkie she would like
to be a teacher pinkie can't be a teacher can she like not talk to people doesn't have a whole
point you gotta get in front of like a bunch of like lecture to people fluttershy is so far beyond
that she's grown she has grown i guess she has grown she made she made so many baby steps that
they added up to one adult she made so many babies too many i'm trying to say fuck that
fucking horse what what fluttershy in her i like fluttershy but uh it was 1 000 baby steps for a
pony one giant baby one giant baby for mankind all right okay so fair enough they're all teachers
okay they're all teachers twilight has like a weird like surely temple pony who is uncomfortable
and is like for like assistant in some weird bizarre way you see you open the door a crack and
you let in a star set sunshine glimmer or whatever and then the floodgates burst open all these
fucking weirdos there's a bunch of eclectic cafe-esque misfits and fucking morons there's like
there's yaks there's griffins there's dragons there's changelings all the races are intermittently
and the and the donald trump pony hates it that's hates it uh okay oh my god cozy cozy glows evil
cozy cozy is evil she uh wants power and she tries to summon t-rex uh and she traps twilight
in the co in hell and she traps them well the the the beast myth fits eclectic cafe members
have to uh try and like at least you know make it the people known that she is an evil imposter
and a dictator she imprisons she turns the masses against starlight glimmer who is a good personnel
she uses like kindness to manipulate people into liking her literally now gore toxic femininity
nice nice yeah yeah yeah i'm definitely not reading too much in this is definitely a pro jump
anti uh sjw episode hey i'm just saying uh looking at i'm on the villains i'm on the
villains wiki uh and i'm on cozy glows page and and and right above her image is a big red banner
labeling her in the category of evil doer so don't get confused hey i see is your kid mark a
unlike all the other villains on this on this week she is an evil doer rook in chess is that what
that is no no it looks like it looks like it might be it's kind of a spirit by her wing
type of villain tyrannical brat i mean that's a classification i just want to say that i i actually
like uh that idea for a story and i like her design and i think she's a cool character and i like her
ponies are good guys let's review the show let's like as in as in like watch oh maybe we should
maybe we should that was tame that was tame because that's just like like a massive departure
from the job then you go back to season seven yeah and it's fucking insane okay okay so twilight
sparkle likes star swirled the beard so she like plays god and brings stars swirled the beard no
back to life are you kidding me other mythical friends to just these historic people from the
olden days twilight brings them back to life what i guess typically she unseals them that's
literally fucking what's his face that's literally like what twilight did in remember what's that
fucking apple she ate too many apples and she had a psychedelic trip and there was an episode
for each of the other ponies too you know what i'm talking about max dot mauve dot mauve yeah
that's the one dot mauve whatever it's fucking twilight dot mauve magic dot mauve whatever
that's exactly what literally happened uh what the fuck they're all they're all labeled evil
doer every single one is labeled evil doer why have it um they're all they're all because if they
don't do evil they're good but this is the evil person wiki right like by default well that it
probably be like evil doer and redeemed doer i guess they're being thorough okay anyway so they're
bringing them back to life but but because they bring them back to life the pony of shadows the
villain the pony of shadows he is a pony who just is black and somewhat wispy that's his fucking name
is the pony of shadows no stop that's the guy he was the one that they said was in the castle in
that one where they're running around the castle castle mania oh that was real that finally means
materialized or something was real that was confirmed as a joke but i guess they turned it
into a oh isn't that great when you turn jokes into like actual plot points great i love that and
and yeah it's good it's actually better no it's not it was like it's like what it's like
these like to do with the party god and it sucked in adventure time no i mean you guys are bullshit
you're all bullshit you're all just going off hearsay from munchie all right i am caught up
with the show oh i haven't seen the season nine premiere but i've seen all the seasons seven and
guess what everyone in the world you fucking idiots yeah show's fucking fantastic it's still
fucking great okay one of the greatest cartoons ever made and it's it's it's amazing that it's
still great but it is still great and no one will ever know because all anyone will ever know about
the show is bronies and how stupid they are and this is this incredible gem of a creation this
wonderful artistic little masterpiece of a cartoon will never will never get its respect will never
get its proper due it's fucking great hey man teabab resurrection gave it its props it was good
it's a good show it was finally acknowledged it sounds like the way the analysis was the
comic section of my i don't know if i was making like a value judgment on it i just think it's crazy
that so much has changed and there's so many weird different storylines i never would have expected
and that it was so i was caught off guard it is crazy yeah okay that's what is that's what i still
love about it is that like the show is so different from what it was when it started and like for
for like a cartoon that is for like things technically for stupid technically for stupid
baby toddlers uh but like for it to have like so much ongoing depth and narrative and continuity
and like it's a totally different show now it's a good show hey hey i'm with everyone i mean i
mean i believe you on all that i'm just curious what's the cmc up to what's what's their arc right
now are they doing anything they had like they started their own camp to like help other ponies
get their cutie marks sure sure which i which i which i did think was stupid and it is actually a bad
show okay right that i said uh yeah that's what they did okay all right fair enough that seems
i feel like like a like a concentration camp yeah that's what kind of camp it was concentrate
really hard on the concentrate all these fucking blank flanks they're just want to eliminate them
from the populace uh they they grab their trowels and their bricks and their mortars and they're
building dude imagine all the ponies they're like they're they're all blank flanks they bring them in
but when they enter the camp they all get like the you know like the badges that the concentration
kit like the star the star for the jews like the pink heart whatever uh oh yeah we got it we got it
we got it we got to get rid of all these blank all these blank flanks are just coming over the
border and taking our jobs and taking the lack of jobs because they have no talents exactly yeah
yeah we can't uh i guess it comes back to the nurture versus nature uh facet of of the synopsis
for season nine the first the two-parter and it's pretty insane okay all right let's let's check it
out people we'll have an educated opinion one of these days i feel like the i may be the reason
the reason that um my little pony can get so crazy is is literally because
of it being like a show kind of for babies that is not supposed to be really serious
because they can it for like from a writing perspective you've got all these silly ponies
and they do all these ridiculous things and um anything you want you can you can just throw in
there but because generally from the beginning since lauren faust is it faust or forced i can't
remember faust um haven't said in so long uh lauren faust's like has a vision and she got like
certain writers who she she felt like you know that could could make it like an actually good
show that sort of has been carried on uh through all the seasons where it's like they can have fun
but you know they don't need to they don't need to be too serious but because they don't need to
be they can you know they can choose to be serious when they want to and that's why things get so
crazy but the quality of the show doesn't get stupid because it's not like it's not like a game
of thrones where people are like it has to be really good in a very specific way and if it goes
silly or like has a bad episode or something people people wouldn't go apeshit if my little pony
has a bad episode here or there they're just sort of you know what i mean like it's like under the
radar and that's why it can do all these crazy things and it's fine it's like even to this day
like in the hasbro offices when they're all making the show you know even though lauren faust
hasn't been there in all these different years there's there's there's probably like a big
like words written on the wall like big words that everyone can see that's like a quote from
lauren faust that says don't forget don't be shit and so everyone knows when they're making the show
they know not to make it shit and if every show had a guiding principle like that then every show
would be great god the whole uh i've only ever had the wisdom to say don't be shit the whole
contents of the show bible just contains one sentence a full blank page and then the one
sentence don't forget don't be shit it's real you need to know collect the link in the description
to see some nightmare fuel uh there you go please do uh okay but let's move on to our
couple of last voicemails we got here people um we've got another one here oh i forgot to
record in the show for a second there i understand what wait what possibly could have been the last
voicemail what yeah possibly why did we start talking about it was okay the last one was comments
our sin uh and and forget it just yeah yeah it's a mystery wait i'm curious because i i have
forgotten you have to listen to the episode no wait a minute a fate worse than death is listening
to my own podcast agreed um okay but here's uh here's one from art director 69 uh okay go
hey guys i have a question um so like i was at home and listening to the podcast and then my friend
was fucking his girlfriend too loudly so i came out here to record this uh so i'm a zoomer right
like i'm on like i'm a zoomer uh i'm 19 and for a couple days like look at me i'm a zoomer uh
what point in time does someone become a zoomer or not like i have a game team for people who are
like old fucks or like 20 somethings but i'm a zoomer because i'm 19 right right right that's it
20 fucking 24 no 25 just the cutoff if you're if you're currently 25 or over you're not a zoomer
damn that's a pretty harsh uh cutoff i think that's i think it's a little high i think 25 barely not a
zoomer then i think 20 so i think this guy's got it right i don't know i i think 20 20 year old
are insufferable have you ever seen a 20 year old i don't want to zoomers i don't care to look upon them
i feel like 25 is about right okay i i i think that's too old i know the real answer i know the
real answer if you if you remember what you were doing on september 11th you are a millennial i
don't you're a zoomer okay that's fine yeah that works so i mean september 11th is the is the
is the cutoff point for all human history it's where it's before and after you would have had to
have been like maybe five or so on like september 11 so how old would you be now uh that was well
i don't remember it was like 23 23 or 24 something yeah yeah yeah all right i'll take that okay there
there you go there you go good old september 11th it's safe the day again our favorite character
came by to fix it did you guys see that in the pcb dating simulator 9 11 is a character with uh
yeah yeah oh god and i got it i got to fucking play it i will have played it by the time you the
listener here me too and and you should go play it people link in the description to it it's out
right now go play also uh uh endless war is a girl and i want to date her i want to when it comes
out boy wait am i wrong is she is endless war in the dating sound yeah yeah uh you will you will
know her as endless lewd it's Gabe's rendition of endless war as a girl that's fine that's fine with
me Gabe i know that's controversial but i'm i'm game i'm down okay well great uh okay moving on
we've got another call here from uh tio tio t y o okay uh go oh he is a programmer on the
oh that's right good fucking recording but then i found out that there's a 90 second
fucking limit to the fucking voicemail yeah all right we got it damn it whatever let's go uh so uh
to make it quick my name is tayo uh i'm the fucking programmer for the pcb dating sim the
april first one you know welcome uh and i'm just gonna cut to the chase uh we got a lot of
fucking uh support for it people want to contribute but the thing is like zero of the people
who have expressed interest in showing like you know it's contributing to the project
our programmers and that's fucking mental because we need we need those guys we need
code boys we need people like me who are on the front lines and like developing shit because
rempy isn't going to cut it we uh we were looking to expand operations i'm not gonna say too much
about it but we're looking to expand operations with this injection of new talent and we can't
do that if we're working with like shit fucking software and no programmers yeah i could also
use rempy programmers if uh we don't get enough code boys just so like you know like make it easier
on everyone involved but we need more fucking programmers and welcome to you viewer uh fuck
this podcast fuck the people on there all means to an end we need more programmers to program the
shit and that's it uh that that's all okay bye oh wait didgy uh i saw the video you did with may
it was really cute and adorable thanks for doing that okay that's all see you oh yeah they did a
playthrough um all right so viewer you know i mean i guess they're looking for programming talent
on the pcp dating sim is their twitter people i would probably the best way to get in touch would
be to message them on twi on the twitter probably i imagine so it's the only way i know how to contact
them so yeah um have they tried asking like the the many programmers involved in endless war
probably not because that's a that that's a large enough we need we need them maybe we need all their
energy uh but also probably maybe i don't i mean oh please just shut the hell up bro i
am games discord and there's a whole uh channel the i'm game discord specifically for game devin
programming and i haven't seen him fish for people there i mean this is an open source project
regardless so yeah i am games whatever uh endless war who gives a shit point is the call has gone
out people at pcp dating sim needs programmers if you are a programmer think about it see if
you want to get involved go message them see what they're looking for there you go
that's all there is to it and go play the demo that's out and get inspired to
contribute and help because these guys are doing God's work and it's fucking
sick good good good call Tio Nate yelling voice Nate is forceful this is how I get
things done by escalating my volume okay anyway let's move on to the next call
thank you Joe thank you whole team on the dating sim next one is from Gator
inflator this message goes out to Tom Oliver in regards to the vertical slice
that he just released for a zoomie game quite enjoy it but suggestion the sword
the hitbox for the sword is way too fucking dinky it's you have to get in
way too close and it just doesn't go play strider and you'll see what I mean
that that man can fucking swing a sword out like 30 feet and it's just like you
got it's just the right amount of room I'm not saying exactly I get that she's
small but her sword doesn't need to fucking me like a little fish a little
floppy little fish give me incentive to use it over just spamming shirkins all
the time maybe put a limit on them or maybe make them a little slower or because
just I hang back I just use that instead it just feels so much better
lastly knockback it's a fucking it's it's it's too ninja-guidant for my taste
you fly back and just out but you don't have the invincibility frames Tom tighten
it up a little and it could be great the little raccoon which you could go far but
as it is thank you okay way this guy sounds like he wants an easy mode I
don't know if I can do that I suppose I think you I think you gotta tighten up
the graphics on level three oh fuck you're right yeah yeah that's some solid
feedback it sounds like you went to school for that dude like damn I'll uh you
know I await my check in the right I mean I'll say I mean I thought this was
relatively insightful and decent feedback I remember when I was playing
specifically I I suppose while the game still in development it's fair to
make you know critiques or whatever I agree that it feels like you do have to
get very close to enemies in order to hit them and considering like the
relatively large size of a zoomie I mean again maybe this is literally what
you're going for but I basically of like it feels like you're you got to get
real close to do a hit and it could theoretically be more satisfying to have
like a slightly larger hitbox which yeah I'm aware would require changing like
you know a bunch of stuff including the animation itself but I don't know just
saying that seems like reasonable suggestions would actually be
relatively simple to fix yeah okay you just gotta edit a couple frames and
then change the actual hitbox size do you use physical hitboxes for the damage
calculations yeah okay cool cool oh I'm curious because I don't know well you
know okay what I what I mean is a fitbox as opposed to like I mean some people
use like ray tracing or stuff and that's a that's another method of calculating
damage hits and whatnot but like I was curious if like because there's there's
images that get posted like game dev threads on V and stuff of like the
different games with like the different styles of hitboxes do you have one
hitbox do you have stacked hitboxes to like because if they're rectangles you
got to stack them to emulate like a circle shape or Smash Bros actually uses
circles themselves so I'm curious what would you use for the vertical slice
they're all just a single square and they approximate the size pretty pretty
well I mean the the sword swings in the game that you use the area is can be
covered with a square pretty effectively I didn't see a need to stack squares yeah
that's um I figured like if it extended a little bit beyond the animation itself
like I'd rather have people like wow I can't believe that hit they're like oh
that's bullshit that sort of hit yeah kind of like overcompensate instead of
undercompensated probably good yeah but yeah I mean the the shuriken thing is
probably the thing that I want to address like that's something that is
planned to to be changed yeah right now the reason not to use them is they do
like so little damage compared to the sword but you can just kind of sit back
and just spam them if you want to it just kind of gets boring but you know I
mean that's a that could potentially be like a criticism of the game that's like
even though like the game might feel boring to play that way to more cautious
players like especially on like the first playthrough if you're just trying to
get through the game like if the game incentivizes you to do a most boring
option because it's super safe then you might want to funnel into that there
actually is a bunch of logic right now turned off that controls inventory like
one of the conditions for throwing the shurikens you should have ammo I just
didn't get around to adding in the ammo yeah at some point there are supposed to
be kind of like in a shinobi for the Genesis like I mean the Sekiro is the
same way kind of Sekiro like the shurikens are kind of OP in some
situations but you only have like 17 at a time so right when when did this
vertical slice release like yesterday oh shit well why don't we put that in the
fucking show notes god damn it wait yeah yeah yeah where can they find it it's on
itch itch.io so it's Tom Oliver itch.io slash Izumi and it's the pinned tweet on
my Twitter so there you go there you go all right I'm gonna I'm gonna check that
out fucking neat. It does have controller support now which everyone was very
adamant on adding so if you plug in your Xbox controller if you can play with a
controller not a keyboard if you're that so inclined. Controller babies. Ben's of a
higher grade. We need to respect players by adding controller support wrong okay
oh god damn it I posted a keyboard mouse and keyboard please. I've posted the
fucking audio link in the wrong okay whatever I just posted the link to the
thing in the show notes so people have it okay but anyway moving on next voice
mail we're wrong I think we got like three or four left Izumi and the vertical
slice that's really funny oh okay solid snake one solid snake is calling in oh
my god it's exciting let's let's get to it go.
Colonel I've managed to sneak in to PCPHQ which was tough as it doesn't exist
and likely never will but regardless I'm in and wait what's that on the floor is
that my god it's the body of Andrew Yang oh no he's been force-fed heavy cream
oh man how could you he's covered in snake bites I was my god I was I was
middle gear solid them twin snakes
oh no I forgot to tell you about the fucking poison gas room sorry I know
that's kind of important but I forgot you're now just dying a poisonous gas
right now that my experience he was he was like he was dying of poison and he
asked me he asked me to suck the poison out of his wounds but I thought that
sounded a little gay so I just said no here drink this heavy cream instead
it's good for what else you know the electrical floor room yeah sorry the
room where people just shoot you automatically just entering I forgot I've
got a guillotine if we decapitate you it'll be really easy to drain the poison
out of you and then we can reattach the head afterward this is the only way to
go there you go that's that's there you go yeah solid okay moving on thanks
solid snake appreciate that okay here we go this is a this is a bit of a spooky
one the biological clock on Nate's branding I saw this in the evening I
was curious about what this let's let's hear what they have to say Ben is
losing all his hair and Nate is Ben's brother yeah you know lead related but
unlike Ben Nate's hair is a part of his brand it's on his avatar so Nate what
are you gonna do if and when you lose your hair gonna wear a wig maybe implants
or some shit you know your shit's in danger you're you're you have a
biological clock on your avatar I'm what's your contingency plan here man all
right I well hey regardless no wait hold on hold on listen I listen guys listen I
am you know what I'm fucking argue I'm not argue this I my I just have a huge
forehead I just always have a huge forehead is it's the same what is a huge
but the absence of hair to cover it listen yeah my hair my hair is seated
when I was a baby my hairline my hairline just went way back up there and
gave me a giant forehead and you know it's fine and I'm gonna have this you know
and my hair my hair my forehead will be just as giant the day I fucking die
your claim then at 80 at 89 years old of a fucking of a fucking eyeball popping
out because I sneeze too relevant to me but but if you if your claim is simply
that your hairline has not receded anytime recently then fair enough I'm
sure you know people could probably I don't know the data could be compiled
you know I I have I okay now I could be crazy I could be imagining it but I look
at pictures of myself in like high school and I've got like a fucking giant
forehead and like the same like it's it's like kind of yeah I've got the sort of
it's not a widow's peak but like I know what you mean like it goes kind of like
up on the sides like it sort of sticks out front yeah but it's I mean it's
pretty much the same so I'm okay I'm going I'm going I'm going great really
fast like at a rapidly accelerating pace but you know that's fine that's
different it's all the heavy cream you know I thought about this a little bit
because I mean my hair is tied to my brand a lot more than Nate's is to his
I'm known as the long hair even if I just got a short haircut that would be
like what's going on but you know like I'm I'm a man I'm probably gonna lose
my hair and I think that the solution is to just rebrand and just be an old
person because if red letter media has taught me anything is that it doesn't
matter what you look like as long as you're funny and I am funny so I'll be
you know you know I that is totally fair but you know what there there's a
reality to be addressed of just just for example if you've got a really hot
chick and she's like a host on a show or whatever if she begins to become not
hot even if the other hosts are like straight-up ugly that will be very
noticeable to the audience let's say she starts to get fat or just stops wearing
makeup or anything like that people notice similarly I think I have kind of
look earned or not I think I have something of a reputation of like of like
the hot one and again I'm not saying that I deserve that I think that frankly
workout it's it works you're the you're like the fit yes deservedly or not I'm
working on it guys I swear I really am right now but don't look at me in real
life but so yeah I mean like in the PCB demo like I'm huge and muscly and stuff
which okay I do work out whatever I'm not gonna get to that the point is on like
if I I'm somewhat associated with like looking relatively handsome and I think
that like if my hair does start to go away I that will impact it so I thought
about that one thing to do is to rebrand I don't really want to do that I
could like I if I had no other option I could definitely do that and I've
actually been thinking about this about how my avatar is tied to hair and some
people have been roasting me on it whether it's appropriate or not how is
your avatar what do you mean how is your habits are tied well it just has hair
it's all like if I went bald it would be weird to keep using an avatar that just
had hair don't you think I I mean isn't it isn't it kind of lame to use the same
avatar forever and ever and ever anyway I mean probably you'd want to switch it
up eventually yeah you'd be like a wrestler going through I mean I mean
that's fair I'm mad because my hair is falling out fuck the world here's a
video game you know that's true and as a YouTube you know you'll you know you know
I'm this is a business opportunity for me because when you go bald that means
you'll have to get me to draw you a new avid so that's fair that's just money in
my pocket but you know what the thing is and maybe I made it do that but I've
thought about this there have been stories I haven't verified this of how
Elon Musk like seemed to be going bald when he was younger but right now he
has a beautiful full head of hair I think the technology has advanced you
got implants I mean implants or whatever it is I'm telling you right now I don't
mind about everyone talks about baldness like they've never fucking even heard
that implants exist like they exist they've existed people start to go bald
and then they just get their fucking hair back it's not even complicated you go
you pay like a thousand two thousand whatever dollars or whatever I mean I
just put your hair back in I think it's pretty fucking expensive I'm probably
expensive but I mean it exists it's weird that people act surprised like if
you're gonna save up to buy a new car you know that's one that you do you'd save
up you know buy hair implants if it's important I mean women do it with like
you know breast implants I just as an example you know similar sort of thing
and I think it's relatively similar to that and so I'll tell you people I I've
considered it and I don't think like obviously I'm whatever I'm doing fine
right now but like it's just there's such a weird thing of like it's it's like
shameful to do it you know like it's like embarrassing like unfortunate but I
don't know well women where we that has to be destroyed we have to fuck that I
think we should have an option when you're going bald it's it's like you're
game overing on life and then the implants is like do you want to go to
easy mode if I go bald before I'm 40 I'm starting a fucking go fund me for
hair implants fuck I will not have you guys I don't have you guys seen you guys
seen community you know Jeff from community main guy yeah Joel Mikhail
the handsome one he's a you ever you ever seen him before his hair implants
that guy had a that guy had a mess so that actor got implants when he was like
younger or something definitely because there's there's there's like much oh
there's much he looks like fucking Sheldon but like look up like look up
like pre hair implant like Joel Mikhail sometime and like you know like that guy
would not get leading right it's just a deciding factor on oh my god I see the
images right now they are yeah right you oh my Jesus like and he's like us he's
like a leading man now he's like one of the he is like known for being handsome
now you got a post I'm posting it in the links for right now look at this here's
one yeah or like how about this one over here there's another one and like his
hair's still back that's that's actually that's less dramatic than I that's less
dramatic than I remember look at this next I mean I don't know he's he's still
got a giant fucking for you know this guy this guy went from tool to cool in one
simple step and the step was being rich so I mean that's fair you know what so
I'm just gonna tell people right now I'm gonna I'm gonna make it man I'm gonna do
whatever it takes and frankly I got aspirations to do things and be more
widely known and if hair is gonna get in the way I will get implants in a
fucking heartbeat if I know all packed right now we're all fucking
sign it never go bald okay the only reason I won't sign that right now is
cuz when I if I if I reach this moment I might want to go the Joe Rogan like
ripped bald guy route and like see how that goes that's the only thing that I
think I kind of like that's nothing wrong no I love two minds on the subject
like cuz like I always like I always thought George Carlin looked cool when
he was like sort of balding and like like Jerome Flynn the guy who plays
brawn on Game of Thrones yeah yeah he looks cool he so like I always thought
that like if I'm in my 40s and it starts to go I'll just be cool like whatever
exactly but like if I'm if I feel like it's happening too soon fuck that I'm
getting it fixed yeah yeah I feel yeah I feel so we could at least make the pack
of the no shame the no shame well here's the thing the moment I like go like
start to be like embarrassing bold I will shave my head and then I will grow
my beard oh yeah yeah good plan I know I can do that that's true okay if I
decided to to make that demonic packed take that fousty bargain and switched
and switch on easy mode because the hair loss was just too too much to handle I
might be tempted to over correct and bring it down like bring my hair line
down like further than it ever was to begin with like like all the way down
shows up looking like the old-timey wolf man like hoping no one notices
anything's different like hey guys well we'll think about we'll think about this
remember okay remember Harry Potter right any anyone anyone else remember
Harry I don't know which time like remember when Hermione got her like
teeth knocked out or something and then no no she got shrunk she got them shrunk
she got her teeth cursed and her teeth became right and she went to like
Madame Hootcher whatever the nurse's name was and she had them shrink her
teeth and she just let me sort of like make them a little make make them a
little smaller than they started where I'm gonna go I'm gonna be like hey bring
my hair line down here and then just keep just keep going and then it'll just
come all the way down to my it'll just blend right into my way you know what
though Ben this is why the reasons like this are exactly why I want to have money
like a bunch of money so I can make these kind of fixes in my life if and
when necessary that's freedom baby sure freedom yeah that's what money's for
yeah to fix the things that go wrong yeah that's what I think sure I think yeah
totally now I agree okay so I guess let's move on are we done got another
I don't have to think about this for at least you got ten years for sure unless
something happens some people are unlucky but that I don't know man okay
anyway anyway let's check in again ladies and gentlemen it's time for riddle my
ass Batman everybody's okay and go episode redeemed holy bolly parasite
Batman I got your message I'm on my way now what about man who what my winter was
near once called his computer my ticket out of here you don't mention him by
name for he does not see fame call him a loon for he's a roller coaster tycoon
he was not elected by his part of the collective your windows are too easy
Batman it's the new collective
yeah well done Batman release and minions thanks Batman and maybe the first to
welcome you to the Voo Collective resistance to die I would never resist a
Voo Collective to Voo you've been waiting for this all my life and then I
remember the PCP saved and now I remember the PCP of the Voo Collective
same PCP time same PCP channel
exciting adventure called the riddler Batman on accident I like the fuck-ups
and the just stuttering and whatnot I like how fussy as he just doesn't just
know down at all to catch his own no also the beginning about like I'll be
right there I think we're introducing Robin into the arc I think that's what
that was that was definitely Robin I think we're setting up for a big change
in the paradigm and I don't know I'm I'm ready for a narrative it's not like
the riddler has Batman and Batman has to answer nine riddles and then he's
released every single time he's released again and then assuming he is just
captured again releasing the PCP he's releasing the members of the PCP
there of his own free will indeed he's free he's free he's trying to save us
okay right okay I understand nice job he's a good man good it flew over my head
it was too smart for me most things are okay we've got I think that wait wait
what's this guys I'm getting I'm getting a secret message there's one final
addition to our voicemail section this is from chilling chocolate this was
passed me on the deep web personal it was on a sealed floppy disk I had to
hack though the enigma code in order to decode for your enjoyment here today let's
to solve the anti-life exactly let's let's see what he has to say go here deep
in the ruins of Momo Khan I'm moments away from finding the remnants of Eldorado
aka PCPHQ aka the love battleship aka the pizza party podcast oh my god what's
that is it a weird monkey or a deformed squid and what's that sound I'm gonna
click down the track down the track where they all coming from
down the track down the track down the track down the track
thank they got me
no couldn't get there in time you have to find Jim he knows where the podcast is
and most importantly don't forget to go to patreon.com slash Ben wait who's
screening these voicemails this guy ever yeah there you go this is our last
message from the signal on our agent in the field chilling chocolate no we we've
got our contact the signal went blank you heard though we have to we have to
contact Jim aka mr. Maddaker we got a podcast is he's the only man who can
get us the information we need we're getting closer I like the trails hot the
trails hot and I'm excited my blood's boy my blood's boiling my god it's people
or our beast were like the sitting upon him who could who could that have been
there's no way to know I thought that was like like like a lot of trains I just
hope I just hope I never meet them I just hope to avoid them I don't think we
stand any chance against a force like that hey by the way I'm really guys it's
like normal to cry and masturbate at the same time yeah I mean it's not for
crying so anyone's fall for a mask pencil you at the same time like that's not
that's not weird let's make another pack that will never shame each other for
crying and masturbating at the same time that's yeah I can't cry unless I
masturbate I can't masturbate unless I cry all right well that's it everybody
thanks for calling in speak by we there it is man what twists and turns I know
twists and turns place I think these voicemails were like I don't know like
over an hour I think a lot of that like we just like forgot that we were doing
the voicemail section I think you know we had to talk had to talk about ponies
and some other things yeah okay fair but that's how it should be in you know
someone called in and said basically guys what a rook but somebody called in
for the message that just guys just scrap the episodes and just do voicemails
like just do voicemail just trash them all dude and just um and I was like we
should have like a voicemails only episode we should do that you know what
that wouldn't be a bad idea to try and we just you know we we but then again like
I do cater these for the best ones we would get some less good ones but you
know maybe some that's don't seem great to me would actually lead to better
conversation than I think yeah I don't know could be definitely could be
episode like a special thing I don't think that's a bad idea at all just like a
little like a fun we did that we should all like go through and pick some of our
favorite voicemails that's true that's true but bonus episode this month bonus
episode this month you know not a bad idea not a bad idea although we'd have to
like I don't know we have to have like tag it yeah and like a separate way or
something I don't know we whatever we can figure it out anyway well we'll look
let you know people what's going on anyway thanks for leaving the voicemails
speak pipe link down below send yours as well and maximize your enjoyment of the
podcast by leaving your own and hearing if you get chosen patreon.com
slash the procrastinators five dollars for all the bonus episodes last bonus
episode sunshine and rainbows art and idea concept by lethal or a mage with the
ride hey guys I'm having a little I know I shouldn't have done it but I
finished that spike hardcore energy and my eyes aren't looking in the same
direction and I think I someone you got call 911 if you please looking in two
different directions but both see the face of God I'm having I'm having this
I'm having my left arms going right and my right I'm like electrically
energize your body from within to automatically dab against your own
physically it's twisted it's twisting me up in my arms is sticking up and I'm
damn guys this is how this is how the ancients first discovered the dab and the
killer archives long long ago but I gotta slam a fuck I gotta slam a
lot of brands I love you know I take I take you know I stimulate myself with
spike and then I relax and then I downer myself with fucking and it comes out
downer or just a relative downer to spike well is that when I drink a fuck
my credit card just gets to just starts getting declined so much star wars
so much Game of Thrones merch let me let me crack this fucking up fuck and
buy some Funko pops sending a hundred cans of fuck to get your free Funko pop
everybody all right all right all right all right I'll follow us on Twitter at
TB Crass Nators and also go check out the the dating simulator link in the
description and also at PCP dating don't be like me guys don't be like me don't
put off playing the PCP dating sim for another day and embarrass yourself as I
have done here please now hey everybody it's bestie boy here with a final update
about the PCP editor contest no we have not forgotten about it at the time of
recording this we are just about done reviewing all the entries and we are
consolidating our votes we are gonna get in contact with the folks who are
making it to the end of that thing so I just want to let everybody know we have
not forgotten about you we will be getting to you soon and you will hear
from us and you will see a winner in the near future with a new editor for the
fucking PCP peace and and we will see you ladies and gentlemen next week with
another fun episode have beautiful day see you later
right now I'm supposed to be working right now
but I'm not working I'm doing nothing
my dick I'm jerking myself I'm sucking
I am an asshole I am a stupid I've got a deadline don't want to do it
you