Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Yeah, I'm the best guy ever, and today we're joined by Digibro.
If you can't tell the meme, you should.
But a welcome one, that's the one.
Hippocrit, there you go.
I'm alright, I'm pretty good.
I'm a pretty good character on the Pro Crastinators.
I agree.
And then the opposite of that would be Tom Oliver's here.
I have nothing to say, but I'm very upset.
How dare you.
Oh, okay, okay.
I go on your stream and everything and give you hours of free entertainment out of my time.
And you betray me the very next day.
That's true, that's true.
Disgusted.
Join us on the best guy ever live stream yesterday.
We're streaming Super Smash Bros. Ultimate, and it was a great time.
Munchy and FitMC were there too.
You should check it out on twitch.tv.
God damn it, we're not even two minutes in, and ads.
Oh, that's what the people really come for.
No.
Let me get paid for this shilling.
I know, but I do.
At least to Squarespace.
How often have you guys started like a YouTube video now and the fucking, like as soon as you hear the ad, you just start going,
No.
I usually like, I go on recommended and I'm like, I mean, that sounds kind of interesting.
Clicking is like, is this video sponsored by Squarespace gone?
Like, I would rather just not.
It's the only videos that I get stuck with that on are things that YouTube recommends to me.
VPNs are the big hot thing.
When are we going to get a VPN ad deal?
This episode of the Procrastinators podcast is brought to you by Private Internet Access.
Private Internet Access is the most secure VPN for making sure you can get past all the geoblocks on your internet connection.
Watch lolliporn without being spied on by the government.
Private Internet Access slash the Procrastinators.
I mean, that would, that would be on brand, I think.
It would absolutely be on brand.
Man, I don't know.
Have you seen a lot of this?
I see what people seem to be doing.
I've thought about maybe this makes sense to incorporate, and I don't know.
We Aguas or something, but it's like, they start with like a summary of the issue.
You see like, today's episode of whatever, we're talking about how the libtards got blown the fuck out once again by strong African Americans or whatever.
But first, your VPN security or whatever, and then they go into it.
Ben Shapiro is the worst at that.
It's like a meme now.
Every time I listen to a show, it'll be, he'll be like, but first, and I'll immediately alt tab back to it.
And then like, he'll always have like a little like, cut in of it, and then I'll just scroll to when that like,
image disappears.
I can just skip all his ads.
It's great.
You know, it makes sense.
The good news is, since this is a YouTube video, do you guys spam ever since that hero, that unsung hero who I'll never forget that he taught me this,
grade A under A, with like his first big video teaching me that space bar is bullshit,
K is the instant pause or play video button on your keyboard,
and J and L are the skip forward and back 10 seconds buttons.
I'll never forget what a hero he is for teaching me that.
For some reason, that is stuck with me.
It's like the grade A under a tutorial that the only thing I actually care about him for.
Wait, why is that helpful?
Why is that better than using the space bar there?
For some reason, when pressing the space bar, just sometimes it just doesn't work and like it does some other function, but cable always forces it.
It's specifically, for whatever reason.
You have to have the window selected in order for it to work.
Well, the window selection, I think, all that allows you to use it.
No, the video selected rather.
Like you have to have clicked on the video last as opposed to have somewhere else on the page.
But if you're just on the page, the J, K, and L, those work just as long as the window is selected.
Interesting.
So interesting.
It's better.
It's dope.
It's real good.
Rest in peace.
I wonder what that guy's up to.
Him and Leafy.
Just in retirement.
I don't know.
You think, do you think, here's the thing.
Do you think we're just going to see continuous cycles of internet content creators forever?
Absolutely.
As you rise to prominence.
I think, yeah.
That's just top culture in general.
I was looking curiously at Game Grumps.
I had stopped watching for a long time and they have had this new show called 10-Minute Power Hour,
which is like Aaron and Dan doing live action stuff.
And that is the most popular thing because it's actually funny.
Yeah.
But the Game Grumps episodes are getting like 100 something to 500 something K views,
which is still a lot, but they have like 5 million subscribers.
And back in the day, they were getting basically the same, if not more, views than they were subscribers.
And it's just like less people give a shit, but more people subscribe.
And I don't, like Game Grumps, I feel like if they keep going down this road of just being
not that interesting, they're going to die.
And it's going to be really sad when it happens.
That's true.
But it's good to see them mixing up the formula, I guess, with new stuff.
I haven't really been keeping tabs on that.
I mean, I feel like they're going to, you know, survive like Aaron and all that.
But like the Game Grumps Let's Play show might actually end at some point.
And it won't even be like I'm sad that it's gone.
Because I wasn't watching it.
But like it just, it just makes me feel like everything is temporary.
Yep.
I have been really fascinated looking back through my own history of all my videos,
like all the different people I collaborated with,
and how many of them have just simply evaporated from the internet entirely.
Like people who were really good, and then they just like closed shop and disappeared.
And you've never heard from them again.
And it's just like, well, I guess what's what happens when YouTube doesn't really
pan out after a couple of years, you know, you're just gone.
It's true.
I mean, even like, I don't know, things like the My Little Pony thing,
obviously that's tied to like a specific show.
But like, I don't know.
An interesting example I think of is a guy like who is still somewhat active.
And I quite like the guy, but it's Holden Reviews, the anime reviewer guy.
And that guy, like what happened to him is, as I understand it,
he kind of stopped doing YouTube as much because he just actually is a real animator
in the industry now.
So like, okay, so he's he's doing just fine.
But like his, I mean, it makes me wonder, like, for how many people is YouTube,
like a place to like, you know, rest and like, actually build a future on kind of,
where as opposed to it being like a step, I don't know how much involved it was for him.
I think for him, it was just fun.
But like, because he was he's like an animator at heart, as I understand it.
But and he did like anime reviews and stuff.
But now he's back to actually animating.
So but you can tell in his videos, like there was so much extra work put into them
that probably didn't give a return on investment.
Like I very much know that feeling.
But yeah, I mean, I wonder for how many people you can actually carve out a long standing space
that you can, I mean, I guess it depends if you're trying to make a living on it or not.
That makes a big difference.
I mean, yeah, the living on it, that it was always annoying to see that like animators like left.
I mean, this has been said a million times, like the way that the algorithm rewards
frequency of content and longer videos.
It just it just ends up like ruining people in terms of like they get all of their content out
that they could ever possibly make really fast.
And then for the rest of their life, they have nothing to do except do sponsorship deals
and sort of fuck around.
Yeah, because it's all about the frequency.
If it wasn't about the frequency, they could spend time to make, you know,
movies or short films or whatever it is, like like larger projects that stand on their own
and people return to algorithms are ruining our straight up.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's I mean, and I would argue that it's also kind of the the impetus for frequency of
content because I don't know yet.
We've said it a bunch before, but it's like, how much interesting stuff do you really have to say?
Probably not that much.
Everything's been said a million times.
So like you either need to be like a fucking Logan Paul style daily vlogger and like get into
shenanigans or just like talk about everything you think about and get people into that.
Or you can like take your time, cultivate something actually interesting to say and like
do some real work like an animator would or I don't know, like a documentary maker, for example.
And then, you know, it comes out and it's like a big like, oh, wow, this is impressive.
It's like the two options you have.
Here's something that ties into this.
I was thinking like advertising is the end of like the Internet.
If we keep relying on advertising, we will all die.
And the thing happened recently is that Tumblr cracked down on pornography because
they weren't able to get like the iOS app store app, you know, they couldn't have their app on
because it had too much, you know, risque stuff.
I think it was some somebody found child porn and that got reported and it was like, oh shit.
And then Tumblr responded in by banning all and any sexual content at all
because they want the ad revenue because they're a YouTuber and they're struggling.
They got to water down their content.
And now everybody is basically like, OK, well, goodbye.
Everybody's leaving and Tumblr will have nothing.
Like I get this idea.
I just heard about that today that like the reason was because they were trying to launch an app
and it got rejected and shit.
Like Twitter is on fucking Apple.
Twitter has porn.
Like to ban all porn is way over the top.
No, but it's because, you know, if people were aware,
like if the companies were aware of the stuff that was on all the platforms,
none of the platforms would be allowed.
Yeah, it's just because like some incident caused
caused iOS to be a web browser.
You know, there's a lot of really nasty stuff on the Internet.
Yeah, it's it's just like that there was an event that
clued iOS or Apple into Tumblr being a porn thing.
Like some executive gets a note saying Tumblr is bad.
He's like, oh, I guess we get rid of it.
Well, like it's gone gone.
I've been here.
No escaping the fact that we have all literally all of us.
I mean, I'm sure there's some saints out there who I guess haven't,
but any adult, I would argue, has done something in their life.
If the entire information of your life was laid out before like a judge in a fucking jury,
none of us would be innocent and we would all be shut down or taken off whatever
because you can just cherry pick.
And that's that's it.
You can characterize people based on their worst actions once or twice.
And I mean, and that's why like that's actually a great argument.
Literally, why have we not banned every Internet browser?
Because they all facilitate your exposure to hate speech.
I can go to altright.com or whatever.
Communism dot like whatever's evil.
I can just go there.
Nate, don't tell me.
Dot com.
Well, like the reason has to be right that they are a like they're a what's
the distinction that's being made?
They're not a curator of content.
They are a a platform.
That's the platform of a publisher.
That's got to be the defense that allows the shit to work, right?
Because like how does any browser defend itself while allowing you to get to literally hateful
places unless that's the argument that they're not choosing what to show you.
It's on the consumer to choose what they are and aren't exposed to.
The weird thing, though, is that like legally all these social media sites are platforms
and not publishers, even though they're making editorial decisions as tumblers clearly exemplifying
right now, they're currently getting away with having their cake and eating it too.
And that's at some point, I would hope that that gets addressed or like like a lawsuit
against a company like this, like by people being ideologically repressed or whatever.
Like I get, you know, they're a free company, but like that you can't curate the shit that
you choose to ban and also say you're free and open platform because you are making
decisions on an editorial basis about what it is and that you're lying what you're not.
There's more to the tumbler thing because I started looking into it because like
my friend Matt, who I do market how do it, like his blog got pulled and like he lost all his shit.
Shit, what was it for what?
He did like NSFW commissions and like lived off of it for like a year and like made a lot of
money off it and they just got deleted and because they deleted accounts, all of his safer work
stuff got deleted as well because they were tied to the same account. And like he got them back
after like bitching about it, but like the next day they're like, Oh, we're just deleting all this
on the 17th. Anyway, so this was his tumbler page. This was on tumbler. Yeah. But the interesting
thing with tumbler is that like apparently tumbler was already planning on doing an NSFW
ban because tumbler, it started back in like 2011. It was an independent company. Then in 2013,
it was purchased by Yahoo. Yahoo did nothing with it. So in last year, 2017, tumbler was bought
from Yahoo or I think Yahoo entirely was bought by Verizon. So tumbler is owned by Verizon now and
they wanted to use that network of like tumbler and like Yahoo stuff to sell ads. So the reason,
like they're not making any money off tumbler right now because of all that the porn shit,
they can't sell ad space against it. So it all comes back to Gibbs point about how ads are ruining
the internet. Well, that's that's why I thought that's why you brought it up, I think, right?
The yeah, the future I feel is like people funding the stuff they like. I'm glad we have Patreon.
I'm just I'm just like wary of like Patreon also succumbing to this bullshit.
And they just banned a bunch of they banned Milo Yiannopoulos. Yeah, and a few other guys.
Did you guys? Sargon got banned as well in this recent thing. And the the reason why they banned
Sargon is very interesting. And it was because I have I saw his video about it before this,
it was that on someone else's live stream. He used the word white hard R n word, right, and to
describe the alt right as like they're acting like the black people they claim to like think
or lesser and like bad and shit. So he used that term to describe them. And so that's that's
so on someone else's why it was not on his channel. I mean, he didn't do you a couple for that,
right? Because I mean, you should know did you because the man's got an edgy soul,
and which I can certainly relate to. I can too. But like, even I would make sure
that if I was going to use a phrase like that, it was in a context that was that I could easily
defend myself on, you know, well, like the context is fairly good hearted. Like he's making an
anti identitarian argument in the like in his actual say, saying like, guys, guys, all right,
people who are currently trolling me, you're acting like the people that you claim to hate and are
bigoted against by doing that, he's like implying that the type of people that they hate exist
and are worthy of that hatred. I mean, he would absolutely argue and was his point that like
he doesn't agree with that, but by their argument, they're behaving like in this way.
So I can't be confused. Not worth it. Not worth the joke. Okay, that's fair.
That's fair. Not worth getting yourself in trouble for.
Well, what's interesting about it is that Jack Conte in his in his interview with Dave Rubin
specifically, this is like a year ago or something, a couple months, he specifically states
about how they police the content that people host on Patreon, as well as their, I think it's
manifest observable actions, like the shit you do in real life. Like, like Lauren Southern,
when she got banned, that's because she got her boat to like interfere with migrants trying to get
to Europe or whatever. So like, okay, that's something she did. Sargon, like, I, this is not
a manifest observable. He didn't do anything. He used a word that, you know, they, they don't care
for, which is okay, fair enough. But it was on someone else's stream, whereas the trust and
safety people were the ones who actually banned Sargon because he had used this thing on someone
else's stream. But Jack Conte made it super clear. They only police as long as it's not
manifest observable behavior, anything you say is your business elsewhere. They are only going
to ban you on Patreon. If it's content supported by Patreon, and this is somebody else's stream,
this was unrelated. He didn't post this shit to Patreon. So I mean, basically, there's a
lies going on here. It's not lies. It's just, it's just general incompetence. They say that
they're going to do that. But if they get like, you know, they're, you know, they probably would
be like, I fucking hate Sargon, but we got nothing on him. Like, like, there's some people who just,
you know, they have some general idea of what a certain type of person is on my platform.
And they get a small opportunity to get rid of him. They're like, oh, good. And even if it's not
like malicious, it could just be somebody got informed. And it is, you know, the same thing
with like, the executive getting a note, saying Tumblr is bad, the executive of Patreon getting
a note. This guy said a bad word. This is a bad thing. This guy's a bad guy. It's like, oh, he's
a bad guy, click the bad guy button, ban that bad guy, the word lie. I should not have done that
because I hate, I feel like saying the word lie implies direct malicious intent, all that stuff,
which I don't think was had. I think these are people in their bubbles, not communicating outside
clearly and then like having different views of the world. I mean, in this case, this does seem like
an actual miscommunication between like the trust and safety people and Jack, because Jack said,
like, you won't be judged this way unless you physically do something in the real world. I
don't know. Maybe they have an issue with like Sargon literally being a political
entity now. I don't know. I don't know. I mean, I don't trust anybody to say anything that is
what they will do. Yeah. Because it's never, ever happened. I would be willing to say that they
probably legitimately think that Sargon performed some kind of illegal hate speech with what he said.
Like, they probably just think that like what he did in real life was in fact like, like, if they
don't have necessarily even the full context into what he said, or if they do, and they just think
that even with context, it comes across as hate speech, they might just see it as like, oh, like,
this guy crossed the line that we don't allow creators to cross. I don't know if they have,
if they're supposed to have a line like that, though. Well, here's the fucked up thing.
This put, this means that we all can be banned from Patreon at any time. Yeah, the groundwork
has been set because like we've all done basically the same thing that Sargon did. We've all hard
arred on this podcast. Well, I don't know if it's just the fact that he hard arred or like the
implication behind his words. I would say that what we do probably is worse than that. If he's
trying to like insult, like take down like a hateful ideology by giving an example of their
own backwards thought. That's like, I think, a better moral ground than just saying the word
just for fun. That's true. Well, I mean, yeah, like, okay, like, because actually there was some
clarification on this, that it was like, the issue is you can't use the word, I think we said, in an
insulting way. So like, so okay, so like, if you simply state it in an academic way, like blah,
blah, blah, the, you know, the N word is used to insult people, blah, blah, racial hatred, whatever.
But like, if you, if you call someone that, like, you call a black person that like, okay,
now you're insulting people. But he's calling white people that. So it's like, you know,
I don't know, I feel, I feel like they just didn't look at it very hard. I don't imagine people
looking at it very hard and thinking about anything. They just, oh, they heard the heart are
this is the bubble effect, because like, you get exposed to one tiny bit of information, like,
okay, he said the word, we've got an audio, you can hear it, like, boom, case closed, that's all we
need. Ship him down the line, it's over. It's really annoying how like, you know, robots and
algorithms are terrible, but also real humans are just as bad. We're all broken, we're all fucked up.
For the record, I don't even think the most malicious use of the word in the world should
be grounds for like, taking someone off the internet or banning them or whatever. I mean,
I've been thinking about this, like, I mean, this is stuff we probably already agree on.
And it's not like mind blowing. But like, I was just thinking like,
a much, much more racist thing to say is like, we don't serve your kind here. And that doesn't
have the heart are anywhere. That's true. It's just like, we've literally just, I mean, we've
talked about this, but like, we give words so much fucking power, guys. It's really just like,
the people who are actually racist know that they're going to get in trouble. So they just
imply it heavily and they can't get in trouble because they use the right words.
This is the thing that gets me about this. Okay, it's like, okay, like, like guys like PewDiePie,
guys like Sargon, they've, they've dropped that heart are my dude. Okay, got it. Literally,
what was the intent exactly what Tom just said? What was the intent here? Like, I mean, okay,
PewDiePie slips up and says it, you know why? Look, I feel an empathy with PewDiePie on this.
It's a word that makes people mad. And it's the worst word you can think of that I'm sure
that is why he said it. Because if you asked PewDiePie, why did you say that word? That's
what he would say. He wouldn't say, you know, let's get back to Sargon. Like, why did you say
this word? He's like, well, because I'm trying to create a point that like the alt right is wrong
about their, you know, whatever racist stance. And so that's why I use the word like if you
and okay, you ask, okay, how do you feel about black people? And he's going to be like, yeah,
it's fine, you know, right? It's cool. Nothing to worry about their races are different or, you
know, there are different races. It's fine. There's I don't discriminate. Like, okay, you ask them
the question, you get the answer. But no, we need to deduce the true nature of people because
they're all going to lie to us. They're going to attempt to pull the wool over our eyes, right?
We can't take people at their word. But if you just talk to them, they would tell you how they
feel about this shit. But we got to be the fucking Gestapo here. We got to be the fucking moral
police. You know, what it really comes down to is not that like people are excessively moral,
but like if Patreon was just, you know, inclusive, and people who were racist could get a platform,
it just depends on them finding racists to be paying them. Like if there was no moral,
you know, jumping in, it was just like a neutral platform, then they would lose money over like
PR disasters of like, Patreon accepts Nazism. And then a competitor would come up and say,
we're lovely on, we love people and we're against hate speech. Patreon's not against hate speech.
So come to us instead. And then that site would get all of the money and then Patreon would have to
be like, oh, shit. It's always a fucking money thing. And I don't like that.
I think that it's it's a money thing. But I also think that it has to do with the fact
that Patreon and like all these companies that are doing all these rules are from like Silicon
Valley, like the same kind of area in California. And they're largely informed by the moral values
of what is like normal there. And like when you're in a place where there's just like an
overwhelming amount of not just like liberal people, but like talking heads like media pundits
who are everywhere because every celebrity wants to have that as part of their image that they're
taken seriously. And everyone in Hollywood wants to have an agenda for for personal clout reasons
to have a narrative about who they are, you know, and like all these companies are surrounded by that
and following in that moral footstep. And it's really funny because Dick Masterson will talk
about this on his show and like complain about Silicon Valley types and their moral codes.
But he has he struggles to use the word retarded, like he'll stop himself, he'll avoid using it
because where he's from, it's like seen as a big deal to use that word because they're just like
it had like major policing on it in the late 2000s. So it's like a whole campaign against it
where I'm from people say retarded constantly. Yeah, it's totally not offensive to me. No,
not in the slightest. So like, it's really fucking funny when I hear him like stop himself from
saying retarded, he'll say it anyways, but like he'll he'll whinge about doing it. And I'm like,
it's really fucking hilarious to see the guy who writes men are better than women whinging about
using the word retarded on his fucking show. But that's how deeply it affects you when you live
in a place where everyone feels that way, where they really will give you shit for using the word
and like make you feel bad and give you their sob story. See, like, you know, like in in this
discussion today, I'm censoring myself saying the n word because I'm here giving it power.
But nigga, it goes out. There you go. Nigger. See, it's fine. We're talking about in an academic
way. What Sargon said, white nigger, everyone. That's what he said. Now, you know, you've heard
it from my mouth. Like retarded roles like butter, baby, like butter. Oh, it feels good. I love it.
And like, I mean, the word okay, just I this is silly, whatever we're talking about this, but
like the word idiot and moron literally defined clinical states of being for people of like
mental disability or low IQ. It's just that nobody gives a shit anymore. That's the only difference
that culturally we don't care. And guess what? I grew up in a culture where nobody fucking cared
about saying the word retarded. So what are you going to oppress my culture with your culture
out on the fucking west coast or whatever? Why do you get the right to do that? You don't. Fuck you.
And I'm not just going to say that people the most offended just win in every situation. Like
no, and those those people who are in California and they're looking at it in that that mindset,
again, to them it's normal, but it's not just that it's normal for them. It's that the people
around them are yelling at the rest of the country because of their perception of how those people
are that they perceive it as like, oh, everyone's everyone's being mean to retarded people and
offending them. And it's like, no one even connects this phrase to like an actual like nobody
recognizes a retarded person when they see them per se. We call things retarded when you like
just a regular person does something stupid, you know? Yeah, it's culture shock. It's global
culture shock. I just it doesn't mean anything. It's and I'm going to keep saying new fag moral
fag. It's interesting with with gay because like, yeah, gay is become a little bit more like fag is
more acceptable than gay to me. It's probably true since like, um, like, I don't know just where I
was when gayness was like becoming it was it was a thing in school people would say, oh, you're gay.
And then I was growing up and on the internet people were gay and I was like, oh, is it okay to
be gay? And then I realized it was but it was just like and like now I can't say that because that's
not very nice. But then, you know, fag, I'd never heard of fag. We don't say fag in the UK. So I can
say fag it all the time every day. Do you still say fagged for cigarettes or is that just an old
school thing? It's it's a bit of an old school thing. All the older gentlemen in the old cockney
London town would probably say fags. That's for that. You know, this this whole thing reminds me
of Majid Nawaz, the the Islamic guy, anti and basically anti like extremist activist and
shit. And he he made the point that like when he was getting sued by sorry, he sued the Southern
Poverty Law Center, which is based in Alabama, a bunch of white dudes, these guys decide what is
acceptable and like what's hate speech. And then they let everybody know they put you on a fucking
list as they did with him, basically putting a target on his back for extremists to come to.
And like, these people are dictating what this Muslim man these Christian guys are dictating
what this Muslim man is allowed to criticize about his religion and his culture. And they deem
the fact that he has identified this is not me making a judgment. This is his words that like
there's an extremist problem in Islam, like and he wants to work on that and address it within
like respectfully as a Muslim himself within the culture. And they call that hate speech. Well,
there's a reason why he sued them for that and fucking one and that they had to take it back
and apologize. That's the stupidest thing I've ever heard. Yeah. And there's a bunch of fucking
white Christian dudes policing with this fucking guy who was deep in the shit man deep in the
shit went to fucking jail for like 10 years for being an extremist. Yeah, that's right.
I might might might have been a little bit less than that, but it was a long fucking
time. Well, I'm glad he fucking sued him. Yeah, damn right. And he fucking won. And I don't think
they've learned anything, but I don't know. Hopefully the money will make him regret it.
I think he won like three million or something. Oh, God, man. Well, you know what people, we get
it, right? We're all on the same page here. You know what? You don't have to fucking agree with me
exactly, but at least represent like if you're going to debate me, just all I ask is that you
actually address the points that I'm saying or anybody else is saying, right? When we talk past
each other, it's a complete fucking waste of time. Yeah, please. Nothing gets done. I always want to
remind anybody who listens to this show. I can't speak for you guys, but I don't listen to any
fucking political shit on the internet. There's nobody who I follow who's like my political guiding
light. And like a lot of these fucking kids, when you start going on like a political tirade,
they start trying to figure out who you're quoting or like who they can find a video essay that their
side has made that they can link to you to show you the other side of the argument. And it's just
like, look, I'm not coming at this because I have like an agenda. I don't vote, you know? I don't give
a fuck. I'm just looking at the world and trying to parse it in a logical manner to be consistent
with its own rules, you know? I respect that. I must admit, I'm getting, well, listen to a bit more,
you know, a couple of years ago, listen to the Young Turks a lot these days, listen to more
like Sargon and Tim Pool and guys. I wish I could just, I want to just not do any of it. Are those
like political opposites from each other? Yeah, they are. Yes, they are. Yes, they are. That's
because like things have gotten a lot more extreme. And it's funny that you mentioned that because like
I have only starting like three days ago, I made an active decision to unsubscribe from all the
political shit and just not a bad stop. Every time they pop up on YouTube, just click not interested
because I feel bad because I think there is like some sort of, I think there is something valuable
in being like educated on what's going on in the world. And that's kind of why I got into it in
the first place because I wanted to like just be informed. Yeah, but it's such a fucking downer
sometimes. And I'm just like, that's, that's the reason that like, I really only listen to the dick
show that even comments on that kind of stuff. And to me, it's enough to just hear that that
something's happening. I don't want to hear anybody's like opinion about it. Like I don't want to hear
Sargon give his spin on a story because they all tell the stories in the way that benefits their
side. And even if they tell it well, like I love Razor Fist because he does a lot of research and
he will present a lot of evidence for a point, but he will always be more forgiving towards the
people on his side and like extra come down with people on the opposite side. And even if it's a
little tongue in cheek and like jokie and irreverent, it still is like, I have to take this with a grain
of salt because I know that you have an affiliation, you know, whereas with, with at least the dick
show, he is so politically neutral and somebody who normally wouldn't vote that like I can, he
doesn't usually really share his opinion on it. He just kind of riffs on the fact that a thing is
happening, you know, and that's easier for me to consume because it's not like a guy trying to
tell me how to feel about an event. It's just a guy reacting to it in a funny way. And then I hear
about it. I find out something's going on without having to listen to the hot takes and the immediate
press coverage that all wants to be as inflammatory as possible because that's what gets attention.
You know, I was just going to say where our brains are just being captured, at least, you know,
me, for example, like Tim Pool is a smart guy. I like him, but I do feel he is going for the
clickbait titles and like they, I'm sure a part of it's like a joke and self-aware, but I can just
feel the aura of like, let's get these views, let's like represent the story, at least with the title,
you can like read further for clarification, like, oh my god, battlefield five, you know, hates all
men or something, and not that he necessarily did that, but like they do it on both sides, right?
They skew things a little bit, they tweak it just based on maybe their own perceptions or something,
but like, you don't get the full truth when you listen to either people embedded and whatever,
Tim Pool's in the middle or whatever, but it's just, the whole thing is, it's unproductive
and probably specifically counterproductive to just making your life better, working hard on
shit you care about. It's a good thing that we did something unproductive for the last half an hour
then talking about this and wasting everybody's time. I just think that like it's, it's not cool
or like a good idea to be ignorant willingly, but I feel like it is very respectable to admit
when you are ignorant on something rather than taking any old thought that you hear.
You know what the thing about that is though, Gib, I feel, the reason that I'm, I feel almost
paralyzed politically a lot of the time, it's because I legitimately feel everybody,
basically everybody who's not a complete idiot. By the way, offensive word, why are you okay with
that word and not retarded people, think about it. God, I'm so fucking smart, my brain is absolutely
check, I can't, Jesus Christ. I checkmated all of them. I forgot my point now because I was just
talking about how smart I was. Okay, you know what, it doesn't matter.
All right guys, I had to, oh, Kippo, you go ahead. Oh, no, no, if you got something.
I had a great idea for a good Pokemon anime. Okay. It would be like a mixture of like Code
Geass and Yu-Gi-Oh and Pokemon and the idea is that the main character is like, like a guy with
like a big smile on his face, scheming, kind of like Sora from No Game, No Life and he's like,
I'm gonna become the champion through fucking tactics. And so through the show, you'll see
him like watch other, he'll watch like a gym leader fight somebody else and they'll pull out like,
you know, you'll see their spread and like what tactics they're using and why they're so hard to
beat and then he'll come in and he'll have like really obscure counter picks. So like every time
he reveals his Pokemon, it's always like, oh yeah, like muck happens to have an immunity to this
thing. I was inspired for this because of a false swipe gaming, the YouTube channel who
of all of you heard of him, if not for anyone in the audience who doesn't know,
he does videos that are about how viable each Pokemon was throughout the generations in competitive
play. And because of the fact that Pokemon's competitive play is split into categories
where there's like the Ubers, the underused, the overused, like Pokemon can have, you know,
matchups that like even if it's not the best Pokemon, it could have a place in one of those
categories of fighting. So because of that, there's lots of really unique matchups that
can happen in Pokemon where like specific guys can be used for specific tactics. And if you wrote
an anime around that, it would make Pokemon seem really cool and deep and smart. And it would be
really fun to watch and the main character would be a badass. And you could get away with making it
like it would feel kind of edgy without having to actually be edgy. Like it would be completely
family friendly, but older. If you made it look cool enough, older kids would also be into it,
you know, that just kind of just sounds like the earlier generations and the nerds were kind of
afraid of like being a little bit edgy with like Mewtwo's origin and shit, as opposed to now where
it's kitty baby fuck time. I don't think it's kitty baby fuck time now. But like, like the movies
later had like a fucking war in one of them. Did you know there was a Pokemon war in one of the
movies? Did they shoot guns? Oh, was it was that the one with them? Well, there was a war in Gen
one with Lieutenant Surridge having come back from the war with his electric boys. That's true,
but they show a war in one of the movies where like people are writing on mammoth swines and
thrusting spears into each other, like writing on mammoth swines and Charizard's. It's in like
the Diamond and Pearl movies, I think, or the black and white movies. Dude, I'd love to write a
Charizard and then kill everyone with a spear. That would be great. Where's that Pokemon game?
You know, that reminds me of, did anybody ever watch a living flamethrower using a spear? Make
sense to me. Well, whatever. Did anybody ever actually watch? I always wanted to. There was
like an OVA that was I think it's six episodes long that like actually covers like red, like
actually charging the elite foreign shit. They're good. It's pretty sick. Like that that sound
like so there's the show the show in general is kitty baby fuck time. But this this OVA is like
technically more true to the games in that the character is actually making progress and like
defeating gyms left right and center and being a badass. I think the final episode is the final
champion fight against blue and all that. And dope. It's like actually hardcore legit. There's
like an infamous scene in that when he fights like something for the first time and I think he
had Charmander. His Charmander just gets like bitten and it just screams in pain for like 30
seconds and you're just like, oh, this is what we've been playing for years. That's a little
too real. That's a little different. Oh, wait, animal abuse is a thing. Like they went the root
of making it like, whoa, it's like a little like spooky because it's like violent. Do you like
they actually in pain? But like I want to go more the root of like the main character is like really
deeply strategic because yeah, like we'd frame it like Yu-Gi-Oh where you're just going to explain
what the thing does anyway. So it's it's going to be like they they fucking but like if you if you
know the game well enough, then you can see the things coming. You can see everything falling
into place and you'd be excited and we wouldn't reveal who the Pokemon that he has on his team
are until they like come out, you know. So it might be that like he watches a gym leader fight
and then it'll be like he goes, huh, guess I've got some Pokemon to go catch. And then like in
the next episode of he's fighting the gym leader and like maybe he'll like pick out a Pokeball
and he'll be like, huh, I thought you were going to use that. And then it'll cut to a flashback
of him like in a location where this Pokemon to be found. So if you know what it's going to be,
if you know what a good counter pick is, you'll be like, oh, shit, he's in the fucking power plant,
he's going to get fucking Zapdos, you know, and then we get like a clip of him catching Zapdos.
And like it'll be interspersed with footage of him summoning it for the battle. So then it's like
showing both the hard challenge he had of catching it as well as the challenge of using it to overcome
the boss, you know, and then like you can match cut like the ball
against like the final attack, fucking draining the last hit points off of the fucking boss,
you know. So that makes sense. Oh, so it's like Hiroyuki Sawano music, like Kill La Kill,
fucking attack on Titan, like epic fucking trick or Pokemon anime would be great.
Oh, yeah. Well, so would these okay, now I think I have the idea, but I gotta ask anyway,
are we talking about like actual game strats that would be implemented, or is it going to be like,
like you said inspired by Yu-Gi-Oh. So does that mean we're going to pull out like some weird
bullshit like the fact that was immune to electricity. There's already enough in the
actual meta of the game that if they did it based on the real meta, the fucking Pokemon
nerds would be like just eating it the fuck up like the guys who think the anime sucks because
it's baby shit because they like the deep tactics of the games like if you gave them an anime that
like played up, you know, the kind of shit that like Nuzlockers or competitive players are into
then like they'll fucking lose their minds. How long is it going to take? How long is it going to
take until like the Pokemon company, the game freak, like understands that there are a lot of
older big nerds that will love Pokemon if they made Pokemon. I think they will never care because
that's a much smaller group than just the world. Could they have like a branch of a game dev team
to make a little version of something? I mean, I think with Mario and Luigi RPG, those don't sell
as well as like the fucking, you know, big Mario platformer, but like people love them and they'll
buy them, so do it. I think that with the with Pokemon though, it's just that like the easier
way to reach the Pokemon is too big. Like it's bigger than its hardcore audience. Like yeah,
they could make games that were just for the hardcore people, but there's lots of adults who
will be interested in Pokemon in a much more basic way who just will play the kiddie games
and like the normie games and not even think about it. And like, I think that like let's go
Evie and Pikachu. Like a lot of people have made it to do about it being like a baby game, but I
think it's way more for like the people who were into Pokemon in the 90s and then got out of it and
then came back with Pokemon Go. And like it's trying to appeal to those people and be like, hey,
we remade that game from your childhood, but with the mechanics of the thing that you like to play
now and you know, reimagine with modern graphics. On today's episode, there's three people who like
Pokemon Go and then only me on the opposite side who has not even played the game. I
can't defend myself. I mean, let's go. I mean, let's go. I haven't played let's go either because
it's a video game and you got to buy it and I don't have money to put to like like Pokemon
Let's Go in a perfect world. If it was a free thing, I would definitely have it and I would love
it because it looks great and it gets rid of a lot of annoying tedious bullshit that didn't
like out of the Pokemon games because they are JRPGs and I don't really like that. They just take
so much time. Well, so like Pokemon Let's Go is great for me, but like I forgot the point I was
saying. Speaking of JRPGs, everybody go watch my Tales of Fantasia analysis on the I Am Games
channel. That was good. Thank you. I haven't watched it yet. It's like 50 minutes though, ain't it?
Yeah, it's as long as fuck. It sounds deep as shit. By the way, by the way, just I was just
imagining. Okay, imagine that the the Pokemon OVA that you're thinking of there, Digi, is a nine
episode long OVA, maybe 10 if you want to one for each gym and then two for each gym and then but
imagine it. It basically it's like Katana Gatory or Katana Gatory, whatever it is. You got episode
one through eight where it's like insane strats, like talking about optimizing and observing gym
behavior and like what the leader does and then you beat them with tactically and you whatever.
But then the final episode, like he's prepped his team because I just experienced this with
my Nuzlocke. You prep your team. They're like God mode could prepare to defeat all of them in a row
and it's just like that final scene in the last episode of Katana Gatory where he just mows down
all of them for the final battle against the actually difficult one at the end who isn't
elementally themed. I fucking hated that Katana Gatory though. It was like I don't know why people
don't like it. It's so cool. Well, I didn't like the show at all. So well, okay, that's
understandable part of it. You know, Ben said the same thing though that like he thought I think it's
just that he hated the show and that the last episode. Okay, the thing is that like for me
watching that show like the writing style of Nisi always seen is that he likes to be extremely meta
and to like have all these twists for the sake of themselves. And to me, it felt very forced in
that show. It felt like he was like showing off how much he could undercut what he had set up.
You know, I mean, I just didn't even fucking I basically blanked out for the first like nine
episodes or whatever and just like let it wash you like well, there was like half an hour. Well,
there were like an hour long episodes. I think there was 12 the moment 13 or whatever. No,
because there's 12 stories. Yeah, okay, whatever point is like basically talked forever. And I
never cared about anything they were saying outside of like, just tell me how you're gonna
beat the next guy. Just tell me how you're gonna fucking fight this guy and not destroy the sword.
That's all I care about. Your personalities are boring and you're a blank slate, whatever. It's
fine. They're actually kind of interesting. There was that whole ninja thing going on. I didn't
care about that at all. I didn't know what the point of any of those characters was.
Do you know about how that story came about? No, I have no idea. It's a stunt novel where
Nisi Oesin decided to write a book every month for a year. So he wrote 12 books, one for each
sword and each one is just like about a different, you know, them trying to track down a different
sword held by a different person. And but that's also why it's like that's what I think sucks about
it. It clearly was just written like in a very speed, like efficient way and not really having
much thought put into it in the end. I bet that works way better as a book where I can like use
my imagination and like think because it just does not work as a fucking anime. And the show was
also adapted the same way. They did one episode a month for a year. That's why they were like 45
minutes long. And then fucking the last episode I felt was fucking dope. There were some weird
things, weird characters. I don't know. I don't know. This has been your PCP anime review for
get out of here plebe and the weave. All right. I have an artist's tale. A little story. A couple
days ago, I woke up at 7am with like a severe headache. And it was like the like a like a red
hot poker. The tip of a red hot poker was like in the center of my skull and I couldn't get at it.
And it really hurt. And it incapacitated me for the whole day. And I was just like drinking water
and trying to get better and feeling like shit and dying. And I couldn't work on any of the things
that I was working on up to that point. And because of that, like the day after I was still
recovering and I just I was trying so hard to work on the things and I was going all depressed
about like I'll just and I couldn't I couldn't I couldn't do anything. And it was just really
upsetting that like physical like pain could like interrupt my flow. And then I couldn't get it back
until just like five minutes before this podcast, where I was like, oh, you know, I should I should
do some stuff. And I was doing some stuff. And there was this one moment where I in order to
like cool off, I guess, I went outside at night out into the garden. And I was just looking at like
the silhouette of the trees, swaying in the breeze, the completely pitch black against like
the orange glow of the city street light street lamps off in the distance. And I was just I was
just like, God, like this, this, this is so beautiful and so calming and so perfect. And I
could only feel this particular way in this particular moment in having all this pain and
like slightly getting over it with this cold breeze and looking at this really nice like
this calming image. And I was just really, really wanted to to be able to like replicate that in
art in some way and show people how cool that this feeling I'm having is and I was so annoyed
because I suck at drawing and writing and everything. And I was like, I can't make this.
I can't paint a picture. I can't make a video game that feels like this.
Should have made a song.
God damn. I mean, I could but like I'm not I'm not even good at songwriting. I'm just
it was just really in that one moment.
It sucked.
I know what you mean. I know what you mean. I've felt that before.
The melancholy of not being able like knowing you can't replicate a feeling for,
you know, for yourself or for others.
I feel that I understand that because there's lots of like, there's lots of songs that I've
written in my head that are to express those kinds of feelings. But my pain is more from
not being able to replicate the sound in my head into reality that like, yeah, like I feel a certain
way. And then I go, oh, man, I could communicate how that felt this way. But I have no means by
wish to produce this thing in a way and like to enough of a degree that anybody would get it.
Because if I tried to just describe it to you, you won't get it. Like it needs to be done in
the form of like a song. But like, I just can't make that song. I don't know what I would need to
be able to. I don't even know what I don't know. Like I don't know what things I need to learn in
order to be able to produce this song. Yeah, that's what got me on the whole. Like, you know, I was
thinking I should I should figure out how to draw this and then make it real. And then people will
be like, Oh, dude, I know that sort of feeling. But it didn't work. And that was why I was getting
more depressed upon, you know, realizing that my skill level sucks. And I would need to work. But
it's so hard to work when I'm in so much pain. And I can't do anything. And I just ended up playing
Dark Souls 3, which is pretty good. At least that this story is a happy ending. Yeah. By the way,
unrelated, but kind of cool is Dark Souls 3. I usually spend like video game time, especially
Dark Souls, just listening to podcasts. But since I cut out so many podcasts, except Hello Internet,
I didn't really have anything to listen to while I was playing. And so I just had the
game audio and I had blasted it out the speakers. It was really loud. But it was like,
really immersive. Because, I mean, obviously, but like, imagine having the game audio be playing
when the game's playing. And it feels like it's a totally different experience. And I really
like it. And I would recommend people listen to that Foley. That Foley's really good. And it's
really scary when it's at max volume when you stab a guy and it's like, I can see it now. Give
just playing Dark Souls 3 having a grand old time, all the pain leaving him. And then he gets like a
calm point as he's like traversing through the land, he looks over and like the sun setting,
where these silhouettes of trees perfectly captured, he's like, God damn it, they can do it, but I
can't do it. That's that. Dude, it's exactly this sort of feeling. I was thinking like, oh, if I could
make a Miyazaki movie, there would definitely be a moment where it would see the silhouettes of the
trees and the city and this exact feeling would happen to me as a viewer. But dang it, I can't
do that. That's a lot of work. Yeah, it sure is. Fucking Miyazaki's. What the fuck? Yeah, why is the
world gay? You know, I heard he's coming out of retirement. Anybody else hear about this? He's
doing a CG movie. A CG movie. Yeah, his first ever. Completely gay. First ever that stands for.
Well, I guess we'll have to see how that goes. There was a new Ghost in the Shell standalone
complex announced as well, also directed by the guy who did the, yeah, and all. Is that going to come
out before Best Anime Ever, Ghost in the Shell? Probably. Probably. Maybe, maybe not. That was
the joke all along. That announcement was for this new version of Ghost in the Shell. And that's
why it hasn't out yet. You were just waiting for it actually to be released. Actually, it's a
collaboration between me and Mr. Ghost in the Shell himself. You know, to the Lord of Ghosts.
It is Best Anime Ever. Is Ghost in the Shell next season of standalone complex. It's been a long
time coming and please enjoy and pay my rent. Hey, Digi. Yes. You said a while ago, or not that
long ago, really, that you were talking about, like, Endless War, the Rowdy Focus Cop Killers
Discord video game as an ARG. Yeah. And although Munchie and Ben are not here, I would like to
know what you meant by that. Well, the game takes, it kind of takes place in an alternate version
of reality because everybody's playing like a character version of themselves. It's almost
like a role-playing game. Like, it's kind of an MMORPG, but like, because it's set literally in,
like, an alternate reality. Like, because it goes outside of the game board. Like, they hold
conventions for it and shit where, like, you know, the characters are still alive in as much as in
everyone's heads. So it's kind of like they're in a shared alternate reality to an extent. And like,
definitely, what got me thinking about it was that I was just on the IM Games Twitch channel and we
host everybody else, so there was a, there just happened to be a slime fest going on or something.
And they were like listening to what I assume was a Slime Times, like, audio recording. Like,
the in-game newspaper made by a fan has graduated to the level of being a radio program that they
play during live streams. And I was like, this is an alternate reality at this point.
Yeah, I wasn't sure when you said ARG initially, but like, yeah, that is very much, it is very much
a role-playing, like, character server. Because even though people are, like, normal, they generally
keep up some sort of appearance of, like, being completely insane. Because, like, Munchie used
to be big into, like, role-play threads on, like, slash MLP and shit. Like, he used to do a lot of
those character games, so I think that's probably, like, part of the inspiration behind it.
Yeah. I like it. I recently made some characters. The, the, the image of my, my discord icon is
Redman, one of the, the new rowdies. And, and his character is, his character is that he is a very
philosophical guy, but he's also like a big hulking blood beast that drinks blood and needs
always looking for blood. But he's just kind of a nice guy and he's kind of chill.
Yeah. And he thinks, he thinks a lot about video game analysis. He has a video game analysis channel
and he made a video about Pokemon Let's Go. Can I watch this? Is there a link to this?
Yeah, I can link it to you. Oh, shit. That reminds me of us. Put it in the show notes, people.
In the, in the story that I was working on a couple months ago that I was going to make on a
DAT browser, there was one guy who is basically inside of this universe I created. There's a
guy who's an AR programmer and he, he's like, if you wear AR glasses and walk around this town,
you can see like an overlay that he's created across the entire city. So like everywhere you
go, there's like holographic shit that you can see if you've got like glasses on. However,
he's a huge fan of Knuckles the Echidna. So everything in town is themed around Knuckles
the Echidna. And I made a Knuckles fan site that I just, I built myself out of HTML on a DAT site.
So I would link to it, but like I'd have to have it open for it to exist,
which is why that we haven't been talking about DAT as much lately.
Okay, okay. Hey, by the way, listen to the description of this YouTube channel for Red
Man. It reads, hi, I'm a rowdy fucker. I will get blood. Game reviews are my passion. That's the
full description. Yeah, I went, I went to extra lengths and I subscribed to like as many blood
related YouTube channels as I could. Jesus Christ. That's fucking hilarious. I will get blood.
Oh my God, featured channels. NHS Give Blood is a featured channel.
God damn. Well, what about Gun Girl? Where's her, you know,
Gun Girl is on the killer side and she is a, she's a Fortnite school shooter. She played
Fortnite and killed her parents because she loved Fortnite so much and she thought guns were cool.
And so she has a gun and she just goes around killing. And that is, that is, that is Gun Girl.
That sounds good. I kind of want to like make more of these characters, but I kind of just
like that they exist and they're in the server and they do, they can talk to people. Yeah, yeah.
God, Red Man. Please click on the link in the show notes, people. Check this shit out. I will get
blood. Game reviews are my passion. Yeah, he's all, he's all. It's really good.
Yes, it's great. I got to click on this fucking video and it's 18 minutes long.
Oh my God. It's just his face is huge and slowly is getting wider as the video goes on.
Is there any actual game analysis? There is like five minutes. He just,
he's just singing for like five minutes and then he starts talking about Pokemon Let's Go.
Oh no, it's, it's recorded like, it's got like, like a munchy level of effects on his voice.
Yeah, it does. Okay, this is good shit. This is where we need to be headed in the future.
This is where things are going. Yeah, so like, like role playing as strange characters is very
much the core of Endless War and, and it's more fun to do stuff like that than it is really to
play the game. Haha. That is literally true in my humble opinion. I thought that was like the
point was like the game is just a framework for this bizarre story. Well, there are some people,
I mean, for a while at the beginning of season two, I was pretty dedicated and was leading the,
the boards. Not, I wasn't first place or anything, but I was doing quite well actually playing the
game, but I've just, you know, I thought you were first place at some point was like the most
slimy. I might have been. I might have been. I can't remember offhand, but there's just people,
man who've not to insult them, but they got a lot more time than I do to play ratty fuckers,
cop killers, and you got God bless them for their dedication, but I just can't keep up. I can't do
it. It's cool though. It's cool shit. Hey, so Smash Bros is out. Smash Bros is out. That's exciting.
That's pretty cool. Check out the streams. They're all they've all got. They've all got them. But
all right, I'm so annoyed. Well, I'm not that annoyed. It's, it's fine. It's, it's understandable,
but like I go into a number of discords and then there are people, groups of friends, and there's
always a call going on and it's like, okay, I'll jump in the call. See what people are talking
about. They're all just in voice chat, playing Smash with each other. And I'm like, well, I
can't really listen to this because they're not talking. They're just going, oh, fuck you. Like
every single discord call I could possibly be in is a Smash call. I'm just like, well, I've been
playing Smash the entire time. Ooh, ah, getting the kill. Got him. There you go. That's what it
sounds like. Is that what your streams sound like? That was exactly. Getting the kill.
Plus 100. Here's what I wanted to talk about. I was, I was curious. I talked about this a little bit
when I was streaming yesterday, but, but I was curious what you guys think. So not every character
was unlocked in Smash Bros, right? In Smash 4, they were all unlocked. In this game, they are
not. And you have to play to unlock them. I like it a lot, but it took a long time. And I feel
that's going to annoy some, you know what? I don't even know why I'm, I actually, I literally like
that you have to do that. But you seem like the sort of person who would like that. I do. Other
people who are angry about it. I love it when other people are angry about things that I did
better than them at. That's literally true. But, but what I was annoyed at was that like, after I
had unlocked all the characters, and I know Tom said something about this yesterday, that he got
like a notification, but after like, I fought Chrom and I lost, right? After I like did the whatever
to unlock Chrom, like tucked off in a secret menu. Okay, I kept trying to like do the running thing
and then like do the 1v1 stock match, whatever to unlock Chrom and like Ridley. I've both lost it.
This is like 10 characters that's happened with because I'm shit at the game. But uh, uh, like
I kept doing it for like two extra hours. I was watching Star Trek or something and I'm like,
well, that's weird. Why am I not getting any of the characters popping up again? Turns out you
have to go to the fucking settings menu and in that menu, there's like a little thing that's like,
do a rematch against the characters. And so I fight Chrom. Guess what? I lose again. All right,
because I'm shit at the game, but fuck it. It doesn't matter. And then I had to like wait
like half an hour in real time. I tried restarting it. You don't get to fight him again. You have to
wait real time for him to reappear in this sub menu to fight him again. And I'm just saying,
I don't think the game did a good enough job of showing me what I had to do to unlock this character
and it pissed me off. And that's why I'm mad. That's such a weird Nintendo smash thing to do,
to take the conceit that was kind of cool and just run so far with it that it goes around to
being weird and baffling. And like, I like the idea of having to unlock all the characters,
because when I was younger, that used to be what I saw as like your goal in a fighting game. It's
like, yeah, there's a bunch of open slots. I want to fill those. That's the, that's the, if you're
somebody who only plays a fighting game for like a week after it comes out, you know, like a regular
video game, then that's pretty much what you do. And with smash on melee, like I had the strategy
guide, there were a lot of guys that took a lot of effort to get because it was either you had to
do something really difficult or you had to play a certain number of hours or a certain number of
matches. And like to get everybody, you'd have to play like 1000 rounds in order to get the hardest
to get character. So, you know, hearing that you had to unlock everybody in the new game was really
cool, although I also heard it was like really easy. But then in order to mitigate it being too
easy, they put in like a weird mechanic that makes it like, oh, well, now I'm just waiting around,
and I can't do anything to expedite making this happen. I can't just get better and beat the
challenge that I was stuck on. I just have to wait, you know? Yeah, I mean, you can play through
World of Light to get them, but like that, that's like a 40 hour gauntlet, basically, from what I
understand to get everybody there. Maybe it's a little faster than that, if you know what you're
doing, but I certainly didn't. I don't know. You know what? I'm not that upset about it, frankly.
I just thought it was weird that it was like tucked off in this side menu to unlock them,
and it was very strange. But you know, I literally like and am glad that some people are getting
fucked and they don't know how to unlock, and they're confused and scared. I like this. I like
this, that people are traumatized. Because like, remember Mortal Kombat back in the day or whatever,
where like, you get you got fucking, I don't know, Sub-Zero and what's the fire guy, you know,
the fire Sub-Zero? Scorpion. Bowser. Scorpion, yes, thank you. The fire guy. I'm sorry. But like,
then you got like, I think, I think just Scorpion was unlocked to begin with. Like, you have to like
figure out how to unlock Sub-Zero. And then it's like, oh my god, I think there's like a green one
two, what the fuck? And then you unlock fucking Reptile. And then there's like a gray one two,
who I can't remember, like Fog or something. Smoke. Smoke. Fog? Really? Fog, whatever. Okay,
I'm sorry. It's like, Jesus Christ, there's a gray one. I can unlock this guy. What the fuck do I
need to do? I guess I just missed the mystery, you know, of the olden days. Before I was an old
jaded fuck, who knew too much about video games. I remember unlocking all the characters in Soul
Calibur and like, fucking... Fucking Yoda. Fucking, what's the other, what's another good game?
Tekken. Yeah, King, I don't know, Dead or Alive. I never fucking played Dead or Alive. That's
another one I was thinking. That one wasn't about secret characters, but getting extra costumes
for all the characters. You got to unlock the booby sliders. You can just pump them all up to
max. That's the way. Oh, you know what? I was thinking like, I don't, I can't relate to this
because I've never played a fighting game enough to unlock characters, but I do remember
in Rayman M, Rayman Arena, you can, you can unlock skins for like Rayman and Glowbox and stuff
by playing loads of levels and completing different challenges. And I did enjoy... That's fun.
That's cool. Completing all of those. Kind of like that in the city too, but you know what,
actually now I think about, in Dead or Alive, I distinctly remember, I think we were playing
Dead or Alive 3, me and my boys on his like Xbox or something, we had heard that like there were
tricks to get nude cheat codes in Dead or Alive. So I remember playing that game extensively and like
doing deep dark web internet, you know, searching, trying to, trying to get big old Kazumi titties
out or, you know, you know where that came from, right? Do you remember? No, where? That was from
the pages of Electronic Gaming Monthly, that was their April Fool's joke for that year. Oh,
fuck! Yeah, the screenshots in there were photoshopped. Oh my god, that's literally
not acceptable. The year before that, they photoshopped Sonic and Tails being unlockable
characters in Melee and the whole world went insane for a while.
Literal fake news. Shut them down. They have to... That was the thing because like GamePro had like a
fake insert of like joke articles, but EGM just slid something in there that was just plausible
enough to piss everybody else off, and that was their expert troll. So yeah. You know, I like
that a lot, I like that a lot, but that is cruel to do to children who just want to see big anime
titties, goddammit. I just want to see big anime titties with Sonic the Hedgehog. Well, the internet
has some places for you, my friend. That's true. That's true. Okay, I'll go to tumblr.com. Oh, no.
Oh, no. Where am I going to get my Sonic anime titties now? That's a good question. I wonder what
the future has in store for Tumblr. Hey, have you guys heard about the... Okay, this is actually
fascinating and hilarious. With the shutting down of Tumblr's NSFW shit, the refugees from
Tumblr are flooding like Twitter and other places, and have you heard that as a consequence of like
a light being shown and all the cockroaches scattering from inside Tumblr, things like the map,
the minor attracted persons or whatever, are making little communities outside of Tumblr?
This is hilarious. The degeneracy is being exposed, and it's like becoming a minor attracted person.
Wasn't that what fucking Clegg called himself? I think so, yeah. I think so. It would give this
like a minor attracted person, aka literally just a pedophile, like who advocates. I mean, they say,
you know, like, yeah. They're trying to rebrand? I mean, that's for a while. That seems to be the
option when shit goes south of PR. That's true. It's kind of funny that we're even playing along
with that. I mean, we call it, because if they call themselves the map community, then it's like,
well, I guess that's what they're called, but I mean, yeah, it literally is just a word that
means the same thing as pedophiles. It's just for pedophiles. There's a thing for no contact maps,
you know? I'm like, okay, good. That's good. But man, this is just... The fact that this was just
going on... I wouldn't trust somebody who says, oh, yeah, I'm no contact rapist. Okay, I believe you.
Yeah, good. You can stay at my house. I don't know, man. This is like, there's these little pockets
where like, I mean, for example, there's like, when 4chaners like leave 4chan and go act the
same way they do on 4chan elsewhere, you know, there's slapback. There's like, well, you can't
behave that way here, sir. We don't do things that way. And it's like, okay, fair enough. But it's
just so funny to me that all this degeneracy going on there, when it's brought other places,
suddenly there's a spotlight on it. Yeah. It was just going wrong. Are these people confused and
surprised that they're getting backlash because of the they've stayed on Tumblr for so long? This is
the fascinating thing. Shu on head made a video about it and I've seen, I've heard about it for a
while. But like, there's a legit attempt being made by these individuals to hitch their wagon to the
LGBTQ plus like wagon because like, it is true. I guess it's fair to say, and I do feel for people,
they didn't choose to be born a map, I guess. So okay, that's fair, I guess. But there remains
a distinction here, I think, between, you know, the ability to consent and not the ability to consent.
Like, if you're a necrophile, for example, like, I frankly think that's not such a terrible thing
to be. It's obviously not really a great lifestyle. But like, in no way are you really a threat to
anyone. In terms of, I think, I think there's, I mean, yeah, at some point, you've just got to
realize that like, sex is not actually that important to one's lifestyle. Like you, if maps,
like, whatever, pedophiles, they can't help being attracted to younger people. I can imagine that
that is true. But like, you just have to go without. There's no way around it, you just can't do it.
You know what, this is the thing, like, okay, I kind of get the argument that like, hey, like, stop,
like, I don't know, what, bullying us, being mean to us, because like, we didn't choose this. So like,
I get the connection there, and I'm not trying to conflate this with any, you know, like, sexuality,
whatever, like, being gay or whatever. That's obviously a different thing. But it's like,
I legitimately feel bad for people like this, and they don't get to choose it. And it kind of makes
sense that there could be people saying like, hey, man, we didn't choose to be this way. We don't
deserve to be hurt. We haven't hurt anybody. Like, I get it. But I'm not advocating for them to be
bullied. I just feel like you've got to realize that you can't, you can't be protected with having
this thing. There is no way to be a good. No, we have to imagine the other way. We have to imagine,
let's say, that we give total acceptance to the pedophiles. And in fact, the government's like,
we feel for you guys, you can't help who you're attracted to. And it's not fair that you have
to go your whole lives penalized and not able to have sex with anybody. So we're going to cover you
guys. We got you government mandated lollies. So you just round up, no, you just round up a bunch
of like orphan girls who've got, you know, what the fuck. And these girls are going to die in the
streets anyways. So we're just giving them the pedophiles as a prize. This is justice, ladies
and gentlemen. No, dude. I got it. I got it. 3D printed silicone lollies. That way nobody gets
hurt. And it's very funny. That's good. They can't hear about that. You're just fucking a doll. But
I mean, good. I guess, I mean, you could already do that. You could already just go and get a real
doll that looks like a little girl. They have those. You know, like, some people... Where did
you? Where can I find them? Just Google real doll. I hear that they're like being banned in places.
I don't know. Like, I get the idea. That's dumb. That's really dumb to ban them. I was looking at
real doll websites before because I wanted to know what all the different types are and shit and
like what even because they're fucking fascinating. And the ones that are like smaller, they refer
to them as travel size. Okay. Well, like on the plane, you just get them out. No, they're like,
oh, this one like can be taken with you because it's only like three and a half feet tall. So it's
just, you know, just, you know, it's a three and a half foot tall facsimile of a human girl.
Air gun. It looks like a little, like it looks like a child, you know? You know what would be
interesting? An interesting experiment, though. If someone could do a study of this, it's like,
okay, you just take like the same like document or style or like doll thing or whatever, like the
design is the same and you have one that's like, I don't know, five foot five and one that's like,
like, I don't know, like four feet or whatever, like child size, like the design is the same. There
are no differences. It is simply the size and like one's labeled travel size and one's just labeled
normal. Like would people have an issue with that? I assume they would. I assume they would
when in actuality, there's no, nothing is really being implied or anything with that, you know?
It's just a difference of size. It's just like getting to own a physical version of when you
imagine your girlfriend what she looked like when she was like 14 while you're having sex with her,
you know? Well, I mean, I could understand people having an objection to that, I suppose, but yeah,
I mean, I've thought about, I've talked about this before. It's like, I remember when I was 12,
and I was way into Nina Mori from Fooley Cooley. And like, what am I going to pretend that I
like don't have a memory for that? I'm thinking about this. Like, I'm thinking that if you made
a doll of like, like that looked just like a real little girl, it would probably be seen as like
hyper illegal and not okay. But if you made a doll that looked like a younger version of a woman
who is of age now, would that be illegal or questionable to people? I mean, their parents
would probably be fucking weirded out. Everybody would be weirded out. Everybody on earth would
be weirded out by this. By the way, the question is where is the line? I'm very, I'm just, I'm just
no. I mean, the line is and always should be at real people. Right? Well, it doesn't matter.
This is a person who was real at some point. I mean, and now they're dead. Like, I mean, I get
the through line that like, okay, this person's attracted to like the facsimile of an actual
child doesn't matter that they're older now, they used to be. And like that's like, I get the connection
there. I mean, I'm not even asking if it's right or wrong. I'm just asking like, would yeah, like
if you made a doll of a real little girl, it would definitely be not okay, like legally, you know,
well, sure. But if it was like of a girl who is of age, and you were doing a doll like what she
looked like at a younger age, I don't think that makes a difference. I think people would still
be upset. I think that they're equitable. It all depends on like people finding out. If they find
out that you have a sex doll that raised eyebrows already true. And then the fact that it's young
is like, Oh, well, it's okay. So it's of his wife as a girl, like that nobody's gonna say that.
But like, okay, what about this other thing though, that's like, in Australia or wherever,
I always, whatever. So somewhere this is true, that like, if you have like women who have a
petite build, they are not allowed to do porn, even if they're fucking 35. Yeah, because they
just like so. So now we've got that thrown in. So that's pretty weird. So now it's,
I guess it's just about the appearance and nothing else.
Weird guys, I don't know. Let's go. Yeah, you got it. There you go.
Shall we move on to voicemails, please? God save me. Okay, let's do it. Let's do it.
Let me let me pull it up. Everybody. Let me wait. No, I'm going to do it right this time.
Speakpipe.com slash PCP voicemails, right, Tom? Yes, you did it. Is it doesn't have an s at the
end? Is it voicemails voicemail voicemail? Okay, so I'm still wrong. Oh, you got it wrong. Fail.
You said voicemails. I did. Well, you were close. I'll take back those claps, but I don't know what
the sound is. I'm clapping right now. It doesn't make any noise, but okay, I feel the pain though.
Okay, first one. Here we go. This is from definitely not one spar. Let's see what he's got today.
Shot it. Now I was thinking back on my voicemail from last week and I realized I definitely didn't
have as good a time listening to it as I remember having recording it. Now you guys know good old
one spar. If there's one thing I could certainly use more of, it's male genitalia. And if there's
another thing, it's constructive criticism. But before I go anywhere with that, I just want to
say shame on you, PCP, for making fun of my accent. I know my audio quality was significantly worse
than usual. That wasn't him, right? We're being beamed. Just awful. But that one was a bit of a dirty
shot. Anyways, back to my personal shortcomings. First of all, I should have known better than
to ask a specific question like how can I be more gay without even knowing whether or not Digi or
Hippo would even be on. I mean, that's just a beginner's mistake. I did also realize that I
spent most of my question rehashing the same joke, which I guess was just referencing my sexual
preferences. I don't know. It doesn't seem like my strongest entry to date. But let me know what
you guys think. And if you see any more one spars running around, please feel free to destroy them
because like my stalemate Hans and Jerome from the Glory Hole convention told me, no one likes a
biter. See you next week, guys. Oh, that was a great ending gag. Yeah. One spar is he's really
evolving the medium here. He's really moving us forward. I am confused. But what wait, was there
a question? Okay, last week, we got a question from someone who I think was I forget what they're
saying their names, but their name was like definitely one spar, I think was it. And they just
went on about how they can be more gay. And they like had an accent that we thought was weird.
So I think we're so it's someone who who knows one spar and was trying to be funny. That's probably
true. That's probably true. Or maybe he just was Asian for a day, or whatever that accent was.
Maybe he was gay for a day. Oh, shit. What do I do? People will get that eventually someday.
This mystery rag. No, never, never. No, I was promised much. He promised it's coming. I'm
waiting for it. I made a vow or a bet or whatever. So we'll see. You did. Okay. Anyway, next one's
from Centerpoint. Let's see what Centerpoint's got for us. Tell us your favorite Christmas story.
Whimsical, delightful, filled with blood and violence. Epic. Yeah, favorite. It's getting
close to the Christmas season, people. I want to put this in to get us in the mood. It's time
to deck the halls and you know, I don't really have a good like Christmas story that's like
unique to a specific year. But there was one time when it snowed a lot and I think I may have
talked about this before on the PCP, but a long time ago, where it snowed a lot and me and my
brothers went down to the park and there was snow in the park and we rolled a snowball together,
all three of us, around the park and it was it was just got really big. It just went downhill.
It just got really, really big. It was like three meters tall by the end and we couldn't move it
anymore. And then people went up to it and like, well, dude, look, check this out. And they took
selfies with it. Dude, that was the coolest snow time in the snow that was really big.
Hippopotamus, the snow that was really big. Hippopotamus, the snow that was really big.
Yeah. You know, one time a little Nate woke up on Christmas morning and ran downstairs to find
a beautiful, shiny new pair of Jordans of sweet kicks. They were red and black and white and
they were pristine and I put them on and just felt like so happy and content with the world. I
was running around jumping and feeling great, filled with a Christmas spirit. Nate, why do I
feel like I never see you wearing those shoes anymore if you loved me so much? Well, because
you see, then something happened. A dark shadow began looming over me from the distance who
pushed me down and ripped the shoes off my feet and he pulled them on himself and then he said,
haha, Nate, I, Ben Saint, I'm stealing your shoes. I have no justification to be doing this. I have no
moral right to do this, but I'm doing it anyway like I will steal your dollars at patreon.com
slash Ben Saint for the shittiest quality of content. And that's the story of literally how
I lost my shoes in real life to Ben on Christmas. He is a monster. Don't support him. Give it all
to me instead. That's my Christmas story. Oh, it gets me in the Christmas spirit every time
I think about that cruel, vicious blows that Ben reigned upon me. We're stealing my chopping off
my feet with your own sneakers. Okay, that's all I got. I don't have any good Christmas stories,
but I did start making up my own Christmases at some point. So my family was just like,
eh, Christmas, whatever. So one year I was like, hey, let's do Festivus, which is a thing in
Seinfeld, the Christmas for the rest of us. And it's, it's just you do a bunch of silly
shit. You have like a pole instead of a Christmas tree. You eat lasagna and you have an airing of
grievances and yet the rest of the head of the family. It's a fun time. And then like the next
year I started making up my own holidays. So then we did a, we did one called agarwood day where I
themed it around the lyrics of agalodge songs. That's pretty fucking nerdy. And then it was the
hearth's warming eve where I did the My Little Pony holiday with a bunch of just basically a bunch
of events themed around the stuff that happens in the episode of the show. And there's a video about
Oh yeah, we would do, we would do like different things throughout the day. Like there might be
like a scavenger hunt or a fucking big luncheon of some sort. You know, that's pretty cool. I mean,
that's a lot more work and thought than most people put into it. Um, yeah, it's good. It's
cause like generally I've always been like unable to sleep before any kind of major holiday. So I
would just stay up all night and set shit up until morning. That's all right. Hey, that's,
that's constructive. You know, I've been dreaming about apple cider that one time my cousin, I
think cousin Maddie came over and I was like, Hey, let's make some apple cider. And so we did.
And that it's like, it's just apple cider with fireball whiskey. And I think like with like,
we made like cinnamon, um, sugar like crust for like, you know how you make that like the top of
your glass with like the sugar crystals or whatever you like dip it in. Oh my God. It was
like the most delicious drink I've ever had in my life. I've been dreaming about it for years and
I never made it again. Uh, I'd highly recommend it to everybody out there to drink on Christmas day.
Make this drink. It is so good. I'm just going to go over it again because you should do this
because it's so good. Just get some apple cider, fireball whiskey, and then look up a recipe for
like cinnamon and like sugar topping on like the rim of your glass. You will love it. Oh,
and you got to cook it in like a crock pot thing. You just like, you just warm up the drinks in a
crock pot, uh, the fireball and the apple cider. It's so good. It's my favorite. Nothing's better.
And it's so please play another fucking voicemail. Okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Anyway, let's move
on. Next one's from, uh, Cluster Punk Kitchen. Hey, go. English muffin in the toaster.
Butter that shit up. Yeah. Arrange six cheesy Doritos in the center. Press it down. Hear the
crunch. That's your lunch. Take a bite. Change your life. You just learned how to make an English
Doritos sandwich on today's episode of Cluster Punk Kitchen. Hell yeah. Now you're cooking with
what the fuck? That was amazing. Thank you. Cluster Punk Kitchen. Damn. Uh, I'm going to try
that next week's episode. Speaking of cooking recipes and shit. Um, damn. Finally, finally,
some quality programming to replace poor boy eats. I've been waiting forever. Oh yeah.
Poor boy eats was legendary, though. I want another episode. One of these days,
Radcon 4, maybe? This voicemail gives me ideas of having, you know, how like in
just stealing that idea and making that a show we do live action. Well, no, no. Like having people
do ad breaks, but for the PCP, like how you did and how they marketed. Yeah, that'd be great.
Okay. Next one's from Mr. Upload. Uh, let's hear what he's got.
I got a question from Nate. What is your favorite Stanley Kubrick movie? Because I know
you mentioned and other episodes, 2001 Space Odyssey and The Shining. And I'm pretty curious.
Yep. This is just my chance to gush about Kubrick because I love him so much.
Okay, that's fine. He's normal question. I'm like kind of confused. I know it's weird, right? Uh,
my favorite Kubrick movie is probably The Shining, but I absolutely love Doctor Strange Love is a
masterpiece. Everyone should watch it. Uh, Eyes Wide Shut is a masterpiece. Everyone should watch it
as The Shining. Um, oh, fucking, what's the other one? Um, uh, the first half, I was just watching
a ton of Full Metal Jacket. The second half is good, but the first half is better. Um, and there's
other stuff, but I forget, but he's just the best. Everything he's made is gold. Highly recommended
across the board. Um, okay, that's it. I'm looking at, I'm looking at the list. Yeah. And I think
the only one I've actually watched all the way through is Full Metal Jacket. The other ones were
just on TV and I was like, oh, what's this? My dude, do yourself a favor and watch The Shining.
It is the best movie. It is the spookiest movie. God, it's so good. Everything. Kubrick is just,
he is that guy. He is that bitch. He went there. He's not afraid to go there. Um, okay, let's go
on to the next one here. This is from Moon Jew. From Moon Jew. Big, big, big friend of the show.
Let's see where he has to stay. Big. All right, Nate, bud, this one's for you. All right. I'm
recording this the day after Smash came out at midnight and I am so fucking hyped and I cannot
explain to you just how badly your ass is going to get beaten. Your next stream, I swear to God,
my camera will fucking demolish you. No matter what character you play, I fucking destroy you.
So get your lube ready because I'm ready to fuck you in the ass.
Um, is that, is that another Smash, Smash, uh, stream, uh, ad for, for Nate?
Maybe a little bit. Maybe a little bit. Uh, I just put that in there to, to, in case I didn't
say it before, to, I don't think I did. I feel public service announcement. Uh, I made a bunch
of Smash videos. I'm a huge fan. The, the thing is though, um, actually shit. Uh, so I feel like
I've misled people a little bit into thinking that fighting me would like be interesting or
challenging or fun. I mean, I put up a good fight against Nate. Tom beat me every time except once.
Yeah. Um, and it was on a gimmicky bullshit stage. Yeah, that's true.
I, I, it's, it's, it's strange cause like I don't feel that hype about Smash because of,
of how bad I am at it. Okay. I'm divorced from that. Interesting. I was talking about this on
the stream. Is that like, I don't like Smash at all. I find the mechanics, the mechanics are good.
I don't like the controls. I don't like the lack of flow, but then I played little Mac who's all
about just heavy single hits and I'm like, this character makes sense for the control. So I almost,
I almost, almost kind of like Smash now just because of little Mac. Well, all right. Almost.
Yeah. I mean, we were talking about this on the stream that like with fighting games, it's really
about like whether or not you like the game is going to depend on if you find a character that
you can play. Yeah. You know, um, like that's the reason I never have gotten too into street
fighter is like the only character I'm okay with is Kami. And all I really do is like spam the same
couple of attacks. I don't know how to like play her on like a technical level. So like in a fighting
game like Smash, where you can use such a huge variety of different techniques and how you want
to play the game, depending on who you're using, like just because I found a way to play Samus,
that works for me. That's why I will go back to Smash. But like as soon as I have to venture
outside of Samus, the game is significantly less interesting and less depending on the game. Like
in Smash four, I really liked playing as Ganondorf. So it made the game fun again. But like I wasn't
good enough at it or playing him to like, you know, consistently beat my friends. So it's like
ultimately I, if I'm having a good time, it's because I'm playing Samus and winning a lot.
And then people get sick of losing to you. And then the game is not fun anymore. And that's a
Smash session. Yeah, more or less. Luckily, you've got a new Echo fighter to mess around with,
being a Dark Samus, just like a variant of Samus. Incidentally, you said you played
Kami? Camille Toe? Okay, moving on to the next voice. Thank you. Here we go. You're welcome.
Terrible. So hello there, procrastinators. This is your old ass boy who said that you were my role
models. You all sucked. And I have no friends. Well, two things, you know, actually suck. And I
got new friends. They were fun for like two weeks, because I told them that Pokemon Go was great.
And it was fun. But then they got bored and said it was gay or some shit. After that, I realized
just how unintellectual those people actually are. I was arguing with them all day, every day,
just to understand where they're coming from. Still still don't understand. They got mad at me
for some reason. So I don't have any friends once again. But the point is, the best guy from the
group messaged me after the incident and told me that he has completed Homestuck and he's now gay.
My question is, what the fuck? What? Homestuck? How did Homestuck turn him gay? Is this real?
Well, what the fuck? To be fair, you have to have a pretty high IQ to understand Pokemon Go.
Yeah, that's true. To be fair, you have to be a pretty high gay gene. To be turned gay by Homestuck.
I mean, this is the guy who the other day, if people remember, which is like, guys, I'm literally
too intellectual to talk to these people and make quote unquote friends with them. It sounds like
he gave in, finally did make friends with them and then fucked it up immediately somehow.
That's what it sounds like. I mean, I mean, he said there was an incident. So yeah, what was the
incident? Unless you beat the shit out of somebody. And even then, I don't think it's like completely
a lost cause. Did you ever have friends growing up who were on paper? You'd think you'd get along
with them, right? Because they like the same shit as you, but they just were annoying and not fun to
hang around for one of many reasons. Maybe they're just like, they're really nitpicky. Maybe they,
you know, try to correct you a lot and it's just kind of wears on your patience.
I knew a kid who was exactly like that in elementary school and in high school,
he tried to shoot up the school and is now in prison. Maybe that's our voicemail caller here
today. This is his future as well. I would say, dude, look a little more inward. I would guess
the problem is you. I'm just saying pragmatically, even if you're like the greatest person in the
world, this is not an objective like good versus bad thing, right? If other people are forming
friendships and they're getting along, but you're not able to, I would say that there's something
you got to change. I mean, that was a joke though of his call, right? Like he was trying to imply
that it was him because he's being like an elitist. Was he? I mean, I don't know because he made a
similar call before and I just assume that he's relatively serious about this. The fact that
he's shitting on them for being like so unintelligent comes off kind of cartoon-y. That's gotta be,
that's a joke for sure. I'm curious about the homestuck thing. Does he, when he said, his friend
called him and said, I finished homestuck and now I'm gay. Now I'm gay. I think he's messing with
that. Obviously, that's not like homosexuality. I'm just thinking like does he dislike homestuck?
Or is this good for him? Is this one of the guys from his friend? I took it at face value and assumed
that his friend had been like gay and didn't recognize it in himself until he read homestuck
and like related to Dirk super hard and was like, oh my god, I'm fucking gay. Yeah, maybe that's what
it is. I can see that happening. Okay, next call. This is from Steve Help Me Saint. Okay, go.
Upon hearing Munchie's clarification last podcast that Ben St is in fact a real boy,
I felt like I had to be pragmatic about this and test it. So I took Nate's advice. I stared into my
I stared into my bathroom mirror, my eyes milky and bloodshot as I chugged three pints of heavy
cream and went into a keto induced coma and didn't wake up for three days. But when I did
woke up, I was sprawled out on the ground like a sweaty beast. But you know who was there? Ben,
haven't showered in three months fucking saint. He was staring at me, sipping my fucking heavy
cream again that he stole from my fridge. A devilish grin etched into his sunken face. He
stole my heavy cream just like he stole Nate's shoes. He's just a thief. He snapped the fingers
on his right hand. Boom. All the food in my house that wasn't keto friendly. Gone. He snapped the
fingers on his left on his other hand. I put my bank account. Gone. Why are you the page on
dot com slash ben saint? That's page on dot com slash ben saint. I can't live like this when I
he's haunting me when I try to fall asleep. All I can hear in the background is in the distance
is a can of monster zero popping open. Every time I try to fall asleep, I don't know what to do. I
really like Ben St, but I can't live with him haunting me Munchie anyone. Can you give me a
keto exorcism? Can someone help me? Also, I really like that just has been on the podcast
again recently because I really like him and he's like best boy. Thanks. Yeah, that's that's great.
That's great. I think I look I've been trying to rid myself of the Ben St demon for for 28
years. All you have to do is all you have to do is bread all the meat in your house.
Yeah. Yeah, just bread that means read that much ketoing power. So you just keep keep hitting him
with the non keto shit. He will overload. Here's my here's my tried and true method.
Schedule everything and he will always schedule everything in your life and do it on time because
he won't be there on time. And then you're in the clear and then you're in the clear.
He'll always be 10. I mean, if you think about it, he showed up late because you were in a coma
for days and woke up and that's when he was there. So that's true. That's true. I think we found
is one weakness, the way to cut through. Okay, next one. Okay, this is an important call everybody.
This is from this is called Reclamato Reclamato. We talked about Clemato juice.
Clemato is disgusting. Let's let's hear what he's got. Okay, so the guy who is asking about
Clemato juice as an clamato, not clamato. It's it's it's tomato juice. It's not there's no clam in it.
Oh, my white person. What are you doing? What it is is like a margarita. You add fucking tomato
and shitty beer. It's like you're drinking healthy shit, but you get to get drunk on shitty Mexican
beer. He's wrong. Clemato is clam and tomato. Don't ever say clamato again. It makes me it
fucking it hurts my client Mexican. It's not just a beer. It's like a it's like a thing that's consumed
as a regular drink. Is that okay? Maybe there's like different varieties or something.
I thought it was like a clam tornado. Okay. Clemato is a commercial drink made of reconstituted
tomato juice concentrate and sugar, which is flavored with spices and clam broth. Okay, so it's
called Clemato because it has clam in it. This guy has no idea what he's fucking talking about.
This guy is a little off base. Sounds like the facts are on it. So I don't listen to a white
people about a Mexican drink. Obviously, this guy is Mexican now. So I guess he's
all right. I'm confused as to why this is being advertised as a drink and not a soup.
It is a drink. It comes in a can. Soup can come in a can. It's fucking disgusting. It's really
gross. It tastes like drinking tomato juice mixed with clam. I like the idea of like a clam and
tomato soup, but like that sounds good. A drink. Yeah, like a refreshing drink like I wouldn't
call it refreshing. It's odd. So it's like he was doing a little he was putting a little
panache on that. We put a little spice on it called the Clemato. Clemato juice, right? So that's
I mean, it is they do make beers that are like Clemato beers. I had one on on a fucking
the beer alcohol on Sundays show I did. It was the fucking disgusting. I had to like spit it out.
I couldn't drink it. All right, we'll shit alcohol on Sundays as well as some other ones of
the of that of the series are just great names. I really like like unironically enjoy alcohol
on Sundays as a name. I got that from a skit that's in AMV hell three where Shinji is on the phone.
It's like the clip of Shinji on the phone and episode one of Eva on the payphone and like
this guy's running through all these like options of what he can click on on like the button. So
it's like if you're out of alcohol on Sundays, press five. If you need a hoe for the evening,
press six. If you woke up with a hangover and a pair of sweaty balls on your forehead, press seven.
And deep lore show. So alcohol on Sundays comes from that. I because in a lot of places you can't
buy alcohol on Sundays. Since why? Yeah, yeah. All right, well, let's go to our next call here
from the worst guy ever or possibly H four hot boy. I guess that's also his name. Do it.
Nate, it is me from the deepest darkest pits of the deepest blackest hell. Your tithesis,
the worst guy ever. Can't be. I've come here to tell your general audience. No, a success is bad.
Don't pursue success ever. You be gay and be that your dreams are dumb and that you
shouldn't try to do any of them ever because they're all going to fail.
Now that I blew built your audience, there's nothing you can do to stop me.
Oh, yeah, munchies gay,
which I assume is a resounding endorsement from the worst guy ever to say something's gay.
Nate, have you listened to the latest Andrew WK album?
No, I don't think so. You should check it out because it's basically it's the most like life
affirming motivational music imaginable. And all of it is basically after hearing
Fantana's review, I would describe it as music about finding inner greatness through sheer force
of believing that you will find inner greatness. Okay, just believing in yourself so hard that you
just do everything because you just believe that you can do anything. What's the name of that album?
I don't remember the singles called music is worth living for.
What fascinated me about that was I listened to Fantana's review of it and I haven't listened
to much of WK's music in the past. I know you and Jesse are fans, but the way he described it was
that there was an evolution of the concept. Originally, Andrew WK was the party guy,
like the party never stops, party every day, etc. But now he's adapting this party every day formula
to a lifestyle of like the party is light. That's what his thing is because it was that
from the beginning really that was the idea of the party was that he approaches it as
not literal, but that at all times he's having a party. There's a lot of reference to the idea of
partying primarily by yourself. Most of what his parties are is him by himself finding the inner
strength to have fun and consider all moments a party. He used to tweet constantly about what is
a party. He would say things like just pissed on my hand, life is beautiful, hashtag party.
Goddamn. That's dope, that's dope. It's like, yeah man, wake up, go to your nine to five,
that's a fucking party. Come home, change the baby's dirty diaper, make it a fucking party,
dude. I concluded that it is the ultimate bloomer music and it really sounds like one
rung away from being Christian Rock. That album in particular, it's so sappy and over the top and
cathartic and almost religious sounding that it's Christian Rock for people who are too edgy to be
into Christian Rock, basically. That sounds good, I'll have to check it out. Okay, last call here
from, this is from, this is called Racist Forest Gump Finale, so this sounds like a big one, let's
brace ourselves. Johnny, it's finally time to put an end to all of this. Not far as what are you
gonna do? I'm gonna say the end word. No, stop, there's still time. Neon Genesis is about to get it.
Oh my god, he did it.
Nice. Boris, Boris, that's three words. Shut the fuck up.
Johnny, blow the fuck out. God damn. Oh shit. Thank you very much for joining me on Racist Forest Gump.
I'd like to thank the podcast players for hosting this. I got to thank God, Netflix for sponsoring
this episode and God bless the world, thank you to the economy, thank you to God, thank you to Jesus,
thank you to the idiot piano and thank you to all of you, you've been a wonderful audience.
It's been an honor.
Congratulations. Congratulations, you did it Gump. Wow, he really leveled up there, he did it.
That was good. God, I like this, I like the voicemails of like, there's like,
now I'm musical, you can follow along with it. Yeah, there was effort put in there,
there was a complete character arc of Racist Forest Gump evolving, you know. What a joy,
what a joy. I would like the audio for all the Racist Forest Gumps to be put into like,
animated as a thing. That would be incredible. It would be the coolest looking thing I'd ever seen.
I'm sure they're all available on the SoundCloud, you know, under Racist Forest Gump,
because I put the names in all of them, so they're all there. It's probably like four or five or
something, including if you want to include the intro to last episode where someone did the voice
of Racist Forest Gump. Anyway, that was dope. Thanks Gump, appreciate that, love you, see you
soon in that dusty trail. But that's it for the episode I guess, that's our last voicemail,
that's our last problem. Do we still do questions? We don't, we stopped doing questions,
we've evolved. When the fuck did this happen? A month ago? A month or two ago? That's impossible,
I was on like four episodes ago and we were still doing them. Yeah, pretty sure we stopped at that
point. I think the last time was, the podcast went on for a really long time and then we did
voicemails and it felt like there couldn't possibly be anything else to do anyway. But we already
had stopped doing questions by that point and that's the end of the show. I just didn't even
fucking notice. Well the voicemails are fucking way better than the questions, so I'm happy.
Agreed, we all agree, I think. I don't think anybody misses them too much. Anyway, patreon.com
slash the procrastinators people, one dollar and you're in the cool kids club, five dollars,
and you get the bonus episodes. There's 20 of them now, last one was incredible,
probably the best one ever, Baron Munchausen bullshit, Ben put some crazy editing in there.
Go check it out, it's literally Kino, go get involved, it's good, it's good. And we retweeted
on the, on at TP Crastinators where you should follow us on Twitter, Ben's little like demo
preview reel. I know, I think it was actually posted on the procrastinators fucking Twitter.
Okay, there you go, it's good, check it out, it's all great, 20 episodes people, it's worth five
dollars, give us more. That's it, thanks for joining us, we'll see you again next week,
have a beautiful week, and have a wonderful life. Bye!
What the hell is wrong with me?