Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am the best guy ever, send all your money to patreon.com slash best guy ever.
There's also these other people, but don't send them money, here's The Davoo.
Hi.
There's Endless Jess, Ohio fuck, Mumkey Jones.
Hey guys, don't tell Nate but I'm hiding under the table.
That's an original meme, and Digibro is here.
Hey, what's up buddy?
Hey, thanks for being here.
Alright, hey guys.
It deserves mention that we were going to have Ben on this episode, but Ben spontaneously
re-grew his virginity and couldn't be here.
This is mature men only, there's no room for it.
I think we decided to rule, what was it, if you go for, I think we said six months without
having sex, you re-grow your virginity, it just comes back, right?
That time frame is completely, first of all, it was, I think it was like two years or something.
It was one year.
One year.
I don't know.
It's second of all, I'm thinking more like five minutes.
I can't be on this episode if we keep this rule in place.
That means that if you space it out strategically, you can lose your virginity every six months
for the rest of your life.
That's right.
Oh shit, that's the goal.
That's the perfect life.
Time out Nate, what's all this virginity talk, what is this episode even about?
This episode is about virginity.
That's what the episode is about.
It's a weird topic.
The lack thereof.
The lack thereof, that's true, that's true, because every man in this call has in fact
lost his virginity, though he may have grown it back at some later point.
That's what this is about, losing your virginity?
Yeah.
Well shit, okay, sorry guys, I didn't mean to waste your time.
He actually dropped out of the call.
Okay.
Hey, I'm back.
Did you lose your virginity just now?
I ran off to fuck junkie and now I'm back.
Okay, great.
That's fantastic.
So we're thinking about doing this just round Robin style, telling stories.
I mean, I'd like to talk about virginity itself at some point, but it's more fun to
just talk about the fucking story.
We're all such funny guys, you know, it's no wonder we've all had sex.
Yeah.
We're so charming.
You should see me on my A game, dude, with my van outside the back of the club, you
know, a woman comes out for a cigarette, I entice her with magic tricks and sleight
of hand, and then I clock her on the head with a bowling ball, get her in the fucking
van and bam, that's how you lose your virginity.
Wasn't she already enticed?
Why did you have to clock her out?
It's a complex dance.
You wouldn't understand.
Believe me.
It's a back and forth.
They want to be clocked.
They want the caveman thing.
This seems like a very dentist's method of using it.
He has to use bowling balls because he only goes after gutter sluts.
I actually meant to say bowling pins because you actually can juggle those, but no, bowling
balls.
Yeah, you hit him with bowling balls.
What size bowling ball do you use?
Because I need to practice this method.
The bowling balls I keep in my jeans, dog.
There you go.
So weirdly small, and it takes several slabs to get the job done.
That would just hurt you.
So we're recording this episode in celebration of the fact that Davoo lost his virginity.
That's right.
Congratulations.
That's why I propose we do this episode now because it's a toast, if you will.
Davoo lost his virginity to someone in this room, but who is it?
Find out the procrastinators.
Find out what this quote-unquote room that we are recording in, of course.
It was Digi Bro in the kitchen with the candlestick.
Who is the candlestick?
You're tearing me apart, Davoo.
Okay, now to Voo.
I don't want to be accused of coercing someone to kiss and tell, but perhaps you could give
us some tasteful information about...
That's the whole point of this episode.
I was definitely coerced into this episode.
That's right.
We forced him to.
Just like he did with the girl that he lost his virginity to.
There was some forcing going on there.
We forced him by providing him with a list of topics and him writing his name down on
the list of topics for this episode.
That's how we forced him to be on here.
Okay, Davoo.
Tell us the tale.
Tell us this hot, fresh tale because we're all very curious.
We don't know anything about this.
Hold on.
I've got to get my lotion and tissues, one sec.
Okay, I'm ready.
Let's do it.
You are now listening to erotic stories from real men.
I had sex.
What the fuck?
Hold on.
I want to hear someone else tell the story first, so I get an idea about...
Yeah, I think it'd be better if someone who's...the rest of us have had years to take these stories
in turn.
To come up with a convincingly cool sounding story of it.
Yeah, exactly.
But to figure out what the heart of the story is, what's the real meat...the fact that we
got laid is the cool part that makes us look cool.
You could just say I had sex.
I don't know about you guys, but...
Now I just look at it more as how can I make the story as hilarious and wrong as possible
is now what I want to focus on.
Yeah, there's that.
And everyone knows, every real boy knows that sex is the culmination of a lifelong struggle
and battle to obtain ultimate victory for one brief moment which continues for the rest
of your life, you know?
At first, Nate, I thought you were going to read the Urban Dictionary definition.
Maybe I should, dude.
Let's go check that out.
Well, Nate, do you want to be the first to tell your story?
Sure.
I'd be happy to.
Let me just see if there's an interesting description here.
I ask because I feel like Nate's story might be comparably normal compared to the rest of
us, so I want to have it established.
I like that you have no idea what my story is and you just automatically assume Mumkey's
virginity story is going to be embarrassing.
Well, tell me that it's not.
Tell me that it's not.
I can't say that my story is going to be normal in any sense of the word.
Well, I'm assuming that like it involves time travel and like a net and like a beam saber,
some kind of helmet that makes that makes monkeys smarter, something like that.
Okay.
So here we go.
Here's like a little girl from Ape Escape.
Is that what you're saying?
You fuck someone from Ape Escape.
I don't know that it's the little girl or a human from that game.
You got fucked by the net.
So, so listen to this fucking description of sex on Urban Dictionary.
Here's the description.
Sex.
What kind of moron are you that you look up sex in the Urban Dictionary?
That's it.
I'm getting tired.
They got me.
They got us.
Oh, man.
These fucking smug cunts.
All right.
Anyway.
It's an epic joke, XD.
Okay.
So let me, I'll tell you my tale.
So I lost my virginity when I was 21.
So late, late bloomer for sure.
I was in college.
I was a senior.
So I had a girlfriend.
And you know, the thing about sex is that no guy wants to admit it, but it's like a,
maybe this is just me, but I'm like kind of obsessed with sex and that I think about it
all the time and how to get it and whether or not no guy has ever admitted that.
It's a secret to everybody.
I don't know how important it is to every guy out there in terms of their self-identity,
which is what I'm trying to say.
Literally all that matters.
I would say.
Okay.
Good.
All right.
It's probably high on the list of the only thing that matters.
A list consisting exactly of sex.
I would, I would describe myself as nihilist except for sex.
That's the one thing that matters in this life.
Yeah.
So when you're talking about, I don't typically care about other people's feelings.
But as a long time researcher of virginity, I think it'd be best if we avoided saying
things like, Oh, 21, I was a late bloomer.
Like I'm guessing a lot of people listening are older than that and also virgins.
So maybe avoid that kind of phrase.
I mean, I, okay, I will, I will.
But, uh, sensitivity training with Munky Jones.
Yes.
We have to be, did Munky just give us a trigger warning on this video?
We have to make sure this podcast is inclusive for fucking, for incels.
Because specifically, I know that people who are virgins over the, a certain age are going
to go shoot people and I don't want Nate to be the next victim.
Yeah.
You know what?
Before, before I get into that, I have friends who are still virgins who are much older than
and it pains them.
And I have such deep sympathy for anyone, for any incels out there.
And I don't use that term.
I just, just to shorten to say people who haven't had sex, but they want to.
They, they know.
Empathize guys.
Empathize.
Yeah, they know.
There's no fucking, you can say 21 is a late bloomer.
We all know half of our stories are going to be over that age, just so you know.
So like.
It's just that the average age for having sex in America is like 15 for losing your virginity
or something.
So it's, it's, it boggles my mind.
The average up baby.
Yes, we are dragging it out.
Okay.
Partly because, partly because we're millennials and this is a social thing that, that our
generation has a harder time communicating and getting laid.
Yeah.
So, you know, it's, it's, it's partly a generational thing.
That's my excuse.
That was like the most insecure sounding sentence I've ever heard you say.
I wanted to make it sound that way.
Generational thing.
That was, that was a joke.
The problem isn't me.
It's my generation.
So go ahead and talk shit.
Talk shit about me.
I got my millennials backing me up.
We don't, don't give a fuck.
Yeah.
We won't ever give a fuck.
Oh, tell you, you give a fuck about me.
All right.
Let me get my generation.
I got a chainsaw.
I skin your ass raw.
That's a different song.
I don't care.
It's all the same song.
It's just one continuous.
It's all a concept album.
I was just so excited that someone made a reference to limp biscuit
that I had to follow up on it.
Well, I'll tell you, these biscuits ain't limp because we're talking sex here
on the Pro-Presonator podcast.
That's right.
That's beautiful.
Okay.
So, so just, just, there's a, there's a fun bit.
So I went to Japan when I was, so I had a girlfriend in college.
And never.
Who did that?
Who's the funniest guy in the world?
Well, well, well done.
Well done.
That was, that was my, my jingle for the imagery we all had in our head
of the plane flying across the map like in Kill Bill.
That's what I was imagining as I said that.
That's Nate flying to Japan.
You know, yeah.
Oh, okay.
Great.
Perfect.
Moving on.
Did she love you a long time?
Well, no, no.
Actually, I'm sorry.
I'm just, I know I'm a guy who tells way more context that is necessary.
I was just going to say in college, I had a girlfriend, got a couple handys here and
there, but never lost my virginity, which really bummed me out.
And then I went to, I hope this story is just a plot of Beverly Hills Ninja.
Who made it first.
Yes.
That's exactly what you can forget.
If you want the short version, just go watch Beverly Hills Ninja.
But it additional detail.
So I went to Japan like immediately after I had broken up with this girl.
And there was a great awakening that took place in me while I was there.
And I was the most outgoing I'd ever been in my life.
I went out with my buddy Garif, another guy.
I was at this big school where everybody learns Japanese.
And me and him hooked up.
We met a couple of friends there and we went out to the red light district.
We hooked up in terms of heterosexual brotherhood and partnership to get laid.
We were both virgins at the time actually.
Not with each other.
But it became our quest to get laid because he had the worst case of yellow fever I've
ever seen.
And we both just wanted sex in general.
He succeeded while we were there for like three months or whatever.
I did not.
But I got so much practice.
Guys, go to Tokyo.
Go to, I forget the name of the district, but go to the red light district.
It's the most fun place in the world.
I need to.
Do whatever you want.
Nate, you were telling me that the methodology these guys were using was to go into bar
bars and then just grab women and pull them aside.
That's what we did.
Because there was a language barrier.
So you guys would just go in and just grab women.
And if they didn't run, then they were interested.
That means they were down.
That meant they were into it.
Yeah.
That's how it worked.
We actually met a bunch of like, I mean, I'm not going to call them professionals,
but like guys who-
It's nice to know that some things are the same all over the world.
That's right.
We met guys there who like their life was they had come to Japan.
There was a bunch of like American dudes from like New York and shit.
And there was this one guy, I forget his name, but he-
Were they wearing Naruto headbands and stuff?
No.
These guys were just like professional yellow fever like curers of themselves, if you know
what I'm saying?
Like it was their goal in life to have sex with as many Asian women as possible.
And they allowed us to observe their techniques.
And it was fascinating.
Nash, no, Nash was my other friend from there.
Okay, whatever.
I got a massive amount of experience in a very short amount of time as to how to meet
and manhandle women.
And it was great.
But I did not get laid in Japan.
However, got back to college, came back to school, and with my newfound, highly honed
Ninja Asian skills as in my movie, Beverly Hills Cop.
I mean, Beverly Hills Ninja.
Beverly Hills Ninja.
I was then able to utilize those Ninjutsu arts to like Halloween came and we just went
to a party or something.
And I mean, just the story was actually pretty cool.
Like there was a bunch of, there was a party at this Halloween place.
There was this one girl, I was trying to hook up with her.
It didn't work out.
And I was really bummed that that didn't happen.
But then another truckload of new freshmen pulled up to the house in front.
They all got dumped out.
And on my second major pull of the night, I just grabbed this girl, literally took her
out back of the house in the dirt and we just fucked like animals for a while.
And it was fucking amazing.
There was dirt everywhere.
What were you dressed as?
I was dressed as nothing.
Yeah, I had no costume.
What?
I was just a dude.
I had no costume.
You got laid at a Halloween party without even wearing a fucking costume.
I can't remember.
I honestly can't remember.
The only thing I remember was that I lost my Virginia at this party and that was really
cool because when I came home to all my friends, I was like, guys, I did it.
I had sex.
I have laid with a woman and formed the man.
He went to the party as a virgin.
And I came home a champion.
When you had sex, the party was over.
She was dressed as...
You know what?
Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe it wasn't actually Halloween.
It might have been a little bit later because I'm thinking and I don't remember anyone actually
being dressed up as anything.
It was like Ash Wednesday.
Exactly.
And he excused the party.
Yeah.
Anyway, that was it.
It was just fun.
It was just this experience of going out, learning a bunch of shit about how to deal with women
that I came home, applied it to these weak white women.
And they fell to me like dominoes before my eyes.
My two questions are...
I'm just amazed you lost it in the dirt.
Like just fucking outside like an animal.
It's awesome.
It was actually nuts.
So I met this girl on the dance floor.
And I had been bumped out because this other girl it didn't work out with.
We had tried to fuck, but we got interrupted.
And then I went back downstairs to the basement where everybody was dancing, saw a girl.
And God, it was a magical moment.
I was so amped up.
I saw this girl, said, hey, that was the only word I spoke to her, grabbed her, pulled her
to me, started dancing with her.
And not 10 minutes later, I had just pulled her upstairs.
We were in back of the house and we were just fucking in the dirt like animals.
It was nuts.
No words were spoken.
Wait, upstairs?
Well, we went from the basement upstairs around the back of the house where nobody was.
And then we fucked.
Wait, is this like an MC Escher house?
They were in the basement dancing, so they went upstairs to the first floor.
Wait.
Do you remember her name and did you ever talk to her again?
I never got her name.
And I saw her again at another party and pretended I didn't know who she was.
Yep.
What the fuck?
Well, she doesn't remember me either.
So who gives a shit?
Does not remove social awkwardness at all.
Well, it was about social awkwardness.
I just didn't want to have to then deal with the baggage of having fucked her.
I'd rather just move on.
He just didn't want to suddenly be married.
Well, no, monkey, if you talk to her after you become married and that's where it all
goes downhill.
That's the law.
Yeah, I didn't want to talk to her and get her pregnant.
That would have been a big mistake.
Yeah.
That's Bundy's law.
That's how it works.
That's how it happens in Clonad.
That's right.
Exactly.
Okay.
There you go.
There's my very sloppy story.
All right.
Yeah.
Who wants to go next?
Monkey?
Jesse?
I think it's Davoo's turn now.
If he wants.
I don't know.
Maybe we should save Davoo for last.
You can just listen to everybody.
I think Davoo wants to hear everybody else's stories to gauge his own.
I don't know.
Where are you going?
Nobody's going.
Nobody's offering.
Fine.
You're a bunch of fucking bullies.
Good.
Go.
You're a personal story.
And I never should have come here.
I'm only here for the money.
I have to say things about my life for money now.
This Patreon has ruined everything.
Oh yeah.
Patreon's on kind of Patreon now.
The procrastinators.
Yeah.
Everybody go.
Bonus episode every month.
If you pledge $500, Digi will take your virginity.
Yeah.
What the fuck was that?
I don't know what that was in response to.
Go ahead.
I assume a spider fell on him.
So.
No, that was a combination.
The mental pot of Digi naked.
It was a combination of thinking about Digi naked and taking my virginity and also, and
also grabbing my pants.
There it is.
There's that world famous Endless Jess meme.
Pants man.
Yeah.
World famous Endless Jess wit.
So all right.
My story begins as so many of my stories do on the internet, on the pub crawl.
The show that I do every week.
I still do it.
Show where I get drunk with my Australian friend Sider and we talk about whatever the
fuck.
And it used to be that this show was a live radio show that had a live chat.
So people would, you know, like interact with us while we were doing the show.
I say radio as an internet radio.
Very few viewers.
But it was like shortly after my 23rd birthday, 23rd, something like that.
It was 2013, maybe 22nd birthday, whatever.
I was complaining about how I just turned 20 something and still had never had a girlfriend
or gotten laid.
And I'm just like whining about it.
And then someone in the chat is like, Hey, I like you.
I'll have sex with you.
And I, this is always my reaction.
I don't believe you.
That always how I feel.
My reaction is always like, I don't believe you unless you can prove it.
But some a certain, a certain persona non grata was in the chat and was kind of trying to
convince them to give more information.
Are you talking about Dr. Wolf?
Was it Dr. Wolf?
Dr. Wolf, Dr. Lee.
Hell yeah, hell yeah.
So she kept nothing.
She started expanding on the information.
It was like, I'm completely serious.
I want to fuck you.
I'm a big fan.
I am a woman.
Here's some pictures of me, you know.
And she'd taken pictures of like, like no face, just body, you know.
She knows what to do.
She knows.
Yeah, but she had a, she had a nice body, you know, a nice enough body.
Did you request a shoe on head picture?
You should have.
A shoe on head?
What is, I don't.
By the way, I hate that the shoe on head meme has been co-opted by that girl shoe on head.
Does anyone else present that?
I don't know this meme at all.
All right, don't worry about it, never mind.
So she, so I tell her like, you know, since she seems serious, I'm like, here's my Skype name.
So we get on to Skype and we're talking for a few, a few more hours after the show, you know.
I'm sourced.
I'm open.
And we quickly start talking about it stuff and kind of kind of hitting it off because
the only requirement I have to find someone attractive is that they find me attractive.
That's, that's all it takes.
You just have to be into me and be at least physically attractive enough that I can be into you back and I'm sold.
So by day two of me talking to this girl, we already have decided that we're going to be boyfriend and girlfriend now.
Might as well.
After I've, after, after through like one conversation, I've already made her cry because I just was like asking.
And they cry a lot.
So I was asking about her personal life, which was shit.
So she,
Oh, what's your dad like?
That's,
Yeah, exactly.
That's how you raised me.
I asked what's your dad like and that might as well be exactly what it was.
Oh, Lord.
So I asked her what's your dad like and then we, she was totally into me.
So it took obviously though, here's the problem.
She lives in Montana.
I live in Virginia opposite ends of the country.
So we're already at the, we need to fuck now stage, but we're living too far apart, right?
So instead it's just lots of sexually suggestive texting and Skype calling and, you know, and, and, and, and flirting that way.
Lots of very sexual Skype calls, but I'm like, all right, I got to get over there.
So I within like, I would say within a month of our, of our relationship starting, I bought a ticket to, to go to Montana.
So I fly out there and she's waiting for me at the airport and like this super skimpy outfit, which is hilarious because it's the, it's like October.
It's like the start of October.
In Montana.
It's freezing cold.
And she's waiting for me in the car, like freezing her ass off in this skimpy little outfit because she was trying to look sexy for me.
You know, she'd been taking, she'd been taking birth control pills, which I guess like completely fucked with her and like made her have like all these horrible migraines and stuff.
She just wanted to be sexy.
Right.
I respect that effort.
So sorry for her.
Yeah.
But, but at the same time made her extremely horny.
So, so we go to her place, you know, we, we walk in and immediately we're like, we start making out and stuff, you know, I'm like, oh, I've never had never been kissed before.
This is happening.
You know, that's some sick makeups going on.
Start taking clothes off.
Start moving towards the bedroom.
Now here's where shit gets weird.
Uh-oh.
So, so, all right.
How comes that BBC?
I know it's going to hit that table any second now.
BBC.
What is that?
She has a big black cock.
Oh, okay.
No.
So what happens is, now mind you, she'd been listening to me on the pub crawl, right?
Now this, this girl has listened to me like nonstop continually for months.
Like she would go to her favorite video of mine is my vlogs about BronyCon 2013, which is like three hours of me just describing what happened at this convention.
Because she just likes listening to my voice and so would listen to it on repeat like all day.
And she had listened to me and Cider talking about like video game discussions on the pub crawl.
And we've been talking about the concept of ludonarrative dissonance a lot.
So this is important.
Now I know what that is, but for the audience at home, please explain.
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
You're bringing back the trauma.
So ludonarrative dissonance is when the narrative and gameplay elements of a story seem to be in contrast.
Watch Dogs 2.
Well, the classic example that Aaron's signal made a whole video about was Grand Theft Auto 5, where in that game, it's got a very serious story.
Four.
Or four.
Yeah.
Grand Theft Auto 4 has a very serious storyline.
And then in between that story, you're just like murdering people haplessly on the street for no reason.
Like just the gameplay and story we're in conflict with one another.
It's a very debated phrase, especially in the academic world of gaming.
Killed a lot of people, and they were.
It was a very romantic thing as I run over these seven fucking people walking on the sidewalk.
So, now my ex, she loved listening to me talk.
Didn't comprehend a lot of it.
Not exactly an analytically minded person or someone who studies music.
Is she watching this, did she?
No.
She's dead.
I killed her.
She's in the ground.
That's how the story ends.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to that.
And she would, I don't think she would, she herself would always say like, I don't really,
she doesn't care about what I was talking about.
She just liked that I sounded smart and had a cool voice.
Like that's what she likes about my content.
I thought we had to tell real stories here.
So, she, I'm sorry, a woman being dumb is the most realistic story I've ever heard in my life.
That's right ladies, I hate all of you.
There you go.
So, she, so I'm in her room, in her apartment in Montana, very sparse room on a mattress on the floor, right?
Whoa.
And we've gotten to the point where, you know, I'm naked, she's on top of me, she's naked.
Ooh.
She, you know, she, she's always about being on top, right?
Likes to control the situation.
I think out of, out of like embarrassment sort of, like she wants to think, like, yeah,
like she wants to be in control because she's shy about it, essentially.
Yeah, I get that.
So, so she gets, you know, she inserts my dick inside of her.
All right.
And she's struggling on top of me.
We get what's going on here.
Yeah.
Well, it's all important.
More detail, more detail.
I'm almost there.
Then she, she, oh yeah.
Now, keep in mind, mental image here.
I am five foot eight and a half.
My girlfriend was six foot two.
Holy shit.
She's way taller than me, right?
She does not deserve a dick.
So she has, because she can easily tower over my whole form and she's at this time, I'm
probably a hundred and seventy five pounds, you know, she's like proportional to her height.
She's only a little less heavy than me, you know, so like, I'm not, she wasn't like fat,
but she had a little chub shabbiness and she's way taller than me.
So she was physically much, much more imposing than I am.
So she grabs onto my wrists and is holding them above my head, right?
Cause she's, she's sort of locked me down.
Okay.
Like I can't, I can't move.
And I keep wanting to just like, I just want to touch.
I just want to, you know, grab things.
I just want to, I'm seeing all this for the first time.
I want to, I want to fucking figure out what it all does.
You know, I'm like, whoa, what's this thing?
Oh, I haven't seen that one.
I'm like trying to reach and grab for everything.
I just want to touch everything.
I want to shove my fingers into her eyeballs.
You know, I just want to like touch all the parts, figure out what they all do.
But she, every time I start touching her, because again, I think she's just like shy about it.
She keeps grabbing my wrists and pinning me down.
And then she would just sit there and she was like, I'm not like, like, I'm not going to move until
you explain to me the concept of ludonarrative dissonance.
What, what?
A phrase, a phrase which she cannot pronounce.
She keeps saying ludum and the dissonance like that.
She can't pronounce the phrase ludonarrative dissonance.
This is next level shit, dude.
How did I never know about this?
God damn.
So she keeps telling me like, explain ludonarrative dissonance.
And then I'll start explaining it and she'll start moving because she's like getting off to hearing me talk.
But then once she starts moving, my mind completely goes blank and I can't do it.
So this is like probably 15 minutes of struggle between she won't do anything unless I start describing ludonarrative dissonance
and I am just so far out of my element that I cannot possibly describe ludonarrative dissonance in this situation.
But part of what I'm grappling with also is that this is my first time having sex.
But I jack off more than anyone else in the world.
So I'm realizing the difference in feeling here.
Yeah.
That, that, uh, that it's big.
I think, I think, I don't want to, I don't want to like this.
I don't want to make this gross.
But I think she, gross, gross, gross.
I think it's been gross the whole time.
Yeah.
I'm already, I'm already gay.
Wait, no, the opposite of that.
Whatever.
My theory at the time, she was masturbating a lot.
Like she, I know this because I would watch sometimes on Skype.
She had, she used all these like dildos and stuff.
I think she was just a little too wide for me at the time.
Oh shit.
Okay, okay.
And that's how he became dildo, bro.
The world.
My point is I'm just not quite getting the level of grip that I'm used to.
Yep.
You know, I'm used to my hand, which I can manage the tightness of exactly.
They call the Death Grip Digi Bro.
So yeah.
Exactly.
Death Grip Digi Bro.
Um, so I'm used to, you know.
Is that where Death Grips get their name by the way?
Is that?
Probably.
Yeah.
From Digi Bro.
From Death Grip Digi Bro.
That's what.
They heard this story and they were like, that's it man.
Right there.
Okay.
Anyway.
So yeah, I'm used to the Death Grip, but she's, she's, you know, I mean, aside from
not being the tightest, she's also extremely wet because she comes nonstop.
So like, um, so there's just liquid everywhere and I'm sliding in and out and around.
And I'm like, I'm trying to figure out.
It's like a slip and slide on the floor.
Yeah.
I'm just trying to figure out like, is this, like, am I doing something wrong or is she
doing something wrong?
Yeah.
I can't get off like this, you know.
Um, so after all this ludonarrative dissonance and shit, like finally we start getting into
the meat of it and we have sex for, I want to say literally an hour and a half and I
never can come.
And like, she starts to become kind of distressed about it where she's like, you know, she's
like, am I fucking up?
And I'm like, but I think I'm like, at this point I'm having fun, like after the whole
all the ludonarrative shits over, I'm like, all right, now I'm starting to get the point
of this.
I'm starting to be fun.
I can, there's boobs here.
That's cool.
You know, I can put those in my mouth.
Oh my God.
So I'm, I'm fucking up for like an hour and a half.
So if we're counting losing your virginity as you have to come, then it took, it took
like,
Wait, hold on.
You have to come in a vagina?
No, you don't have to come in a vagina.
You have to insert your dick is what I would say.
Well, anyway, so I just, my point is that it took a really long time because it took,
we probably had sex like two or three times before I, before we got the rhythm down and
then it all made sense and it clicked and it was like, okay, now this all makes sense.
I know what's going on here.
I know where my dick is meant to go in this, you know, it's not just a matter of sticking
it in.
It's a matter of, you know, fitting it, you know, no matter who you're, no matter who
you're getting with, there's always going to be some period of adjusting to each other
to figure out, you know, what works.
So this makes sense.
I can't help but notice that Ben St. has suddenly joined the call.
I don't know if he's recording audio or if he, if he's,
Hey, hey, hello, hello, I'm here.
Are you recording?
I am recording.
You lost your virginity just in time.
Wait, this is, this the ladies, is this the ladies cast?
It was the virginity cast.
It's the stories of how we lost our virginity.
You know, oh, oh, well, should I tell mine?
Well, if you want to, that's what the point of this show is, Ben.
Digi, Digi, that story of yours, you were literally describing like my worst nightmare
in life of like, like, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll get with a person and we'll be having
like a real human intimate moment and she'll be like, yeah, now do like YouTuber stuff.
Be a YouTuber.
Yeah.
Explain to me things.
Do an analysis video.
Tell me why Applejack is a real character, Jesse.
Tell me about it.
Exactly.
God fucking dammit.
Exactly what it was.
I wish, I wish.
When you come in here, I want you to go, endless jack.
We're not, we're not, we're not.
I want you to say it.
I'm a demon.
And I want, and I want, and I want Gibbon on guitar in the corner to strum, to strum
the beat.
Yeah.
Um, I'm so sad, I'm so sad that I missed everybody's.
Um, I'm sure I missed.
Well, you only missed two.
You've only missed me and mine.
You've only missed me?
Yeah.
Me and Digi.
Oh, okay.
Um, um, well, mine, mine's not really that interesting.
Um, I went to college and I, and I met a girl and there was like some drama about would
she leave her boyfriend from high school for me and eventually she, she was like, okay,
I broke up with my fucking high school boyfriend and I was like, oh, sweet.
And I don't know.
We fucking, oh, we like kind of, okay.
Well, specifically we were on like the couch in like our dorm basement and we were like
making out and we, and we kind of like started, yeah, my first time I kind of like started
fucking or like on the couch in like, sounds like he's making the pump as he goes, in the
basement.
No, no, we were in like the public, we were in like a fucking public basement like next
to like the fucking laundry machines and like, I think, I think someone like, we heard someone
coming down the stairs like to do their laundry while we were trying to do it and we were
like, oh fuck.
So I think we had to give it up at that point and then we just like, I don't know, went
back to my room and like did it and it was like, okay.
And that's it basically.
You had to follow indigy step and tell us about like how she inserted the penis and
all like really close details.
We were like laying on the couch and I don't know, fucking inserted the penis.
It's just, it's just normie sex is what it was.
It's pretty, pretty, the only thing not completely normal about it was that we were in like a
fucking public room and then someone was coming by and we were like, oh shit, let's go to
my room and then we did and then it was just like whatever.
Yeah.
Well, I'm glad my story is so much better than that.
Oh, so glad Ben could make it for this episode.
Yeah, really great contribution, Ben, get the fuck out of it.
Wait, wait, I also want to say that I'm pretty sure I didn't come my first time because I
have the endurance of a fucking, of a fucking athlete.
Of a Kenyan gazelle.
Yeah, I mean, I, I'm a guy, I'm a guy who didn't my first time for like an hour and
a half.
Yeah, I'm all about, I'm a slow and steady, I'm all about that endurance.
That's me with sex.
I actually felt, I actually felt more accomplished once I was able to come in like three minutes.
Yeah.
Like that's what I was like, don't you mean?
We've got this down, like we figured this out because now I can do it as quickly as
I should be able to.
Yeah, the story is about people who like guys who like come too fast their first times,
like I don't fucking get it.
I don't get how that happens.
I wonder if that's a bit of a meme.
Because they probably don't jack off that much.
It's probably guys who don't, who don't touch their own dicks that much.
That doesn't, that doesn't like, like going a while without jerking off doesn't really
make, well, I guess if I go a really long time without it, then yeah, like it's, it's,
I'm fucking a little bit of a hair trigger.
I guess, I guess that could be part of it.
What's the thing about guys who jerk off a lot, or I mean, isn't like the meme that
if you jerk off a lot, like you're conditioning yourself to come as quickly as possible, as
opposed to like if you edge or whatever, that's like training yourself to endure longer, right?
Right?
I don't know if that even makes sense.
Well, the thing is, since I was like 14, I've trained myself sort of inadvertently
to make it last longer so I can get my money's worth.
That's good.
Yeah.
So I basically expect myself the wrong way.
I can control the exact length of how long I want to jack off.
It's all about like, am I doing this because I'm bored and I want it to last all day?
Yeah.
Or am I doing this because I need to get a quick nut before, like, you know, I just
like, I'm anxious or something.
I use jacking off like drinking a coffee.
It's a great pick me up and then I can continue other stuff that I need to do.
Somehow it both puts me to sleep at night and wakes me up in the morning.
I know.
It's incredible.
I don't know how that's possible, but it's amazing.
Wait, is that not the case with anyone?
No, that's not the case for me.
I fucking, I focus, I focus so much better before I jack off.
Once I jack off in a day, I'm kind of like, my focus is usually just like fried for the
rest of the day.
You know, I guess I just wish that there was an old born out there that interested me
because I'm always interested like, oh, hey, how can this narrative bend itself to be even
more hot in the next page?
I don't even understand that.
Like women, just look at a woman.
That's it.
And then, you know, it's attractive or it's not.
The other day, as I was starting to get sick because I was so lethargic and didn't want
to do anything else, I just jacked off like probably seven or eight times that day.
What the fuck?
It was a great time.
It doesn't take anything from me.
I can jack off to literally nothing.
It's just like...
Okay, we're talking about jacking off and shit.
The mere thought.
We're talking about losing Virginia.
Well, Ben's virginity story was too short.
Yeah, that's true.
Nate, Nate, I want to say, maybe, I mean, maybe you're normal and I'm crazy, but it's
for me.
It's not enough just to look at an attractive woman.
I'm turned on by fucking concepts as gay as that is.
Yeah, absolutely.
Well, I know what you mean.
There are certainly things that are more attractive than others.
Can't you just come up with them in your head, though?
I could come up with them.
I can come up with them in my head, but...
I have so many.
I have scenarios that I've imagined for jacking off that I continually come back to.
I have a sort of library of pornographic stories that I have written in my own mind,
and I can remember all of them going back like 10 years.
You know what?
Some of them are just like random, you know, like, some of them are original characters
do not steal, and some of them are, you know, like anime characters who I've imagined into
these certain sexual relationships that I've just held onto, that exact imagination for
so long.
It's like a spank bank of a creative one.
You know?
Yeah, I know what you mean.
I used to do that when I was younger.
I don't know.
I don't maybe, yeah, I don't really imagine it for myself.
Now I like, I don't know what it is.
It's just so easy to Google porn.
If I'm imagining it for myself, then it's not as real as if someone else has created
it.
If someone else has created it, I don't know.
Maybe there's some kind of...
I could definitely get off faster to someone else's creation because they're probably better
at it than I am.
At least the drawing.
I don't know.
I don't know what it is.
I don't know why it's hotter if someone else has fucking created it and prepared it for
me than if I'm just thinking of it myself.
Just think about it this way.
Like, I don't think our brains are wired for us to like imagine, like when you're talking
about being aroused or like sexual attraction, it's not like our brains were programmed
to like for us to imagine things that make us, you know, aroused and then do that.
It makes sense to me that we're built to like visually observe a phenomenon that immediately
is a more efficient way of like triggering our responses.
It's more like it's a real thing that's happening.
Right.
When I...
Incidentally, I don't know about you guys, but if I decide like I'm bored, let's jack
off, I need to, you know, like I have to accomplish a boner first.
My method is just to go to A on 4chan because guaranteed something on the catalog page is
going to give me a boner.
I know what you mean.
That's my pro tip to the audience.
If you're, if you need, if you, if you were like, like always trying to find something
to like start, like, you know, get the, because you can't just go right to porn because it
looks gross.
When you don't have a porn, when you don't have a boner, porn looks gross.
You know, I don't find myself with that issue much.
I usually don't jack off unless I'm already aroused and that happens like all the time.
So I don't really have much of a need to do it because I consider it a waste of time
to jack off.
I'd rather be doing work except I need to deal with this problem before I can, you know,
go do a show.
But sometimes, sometimes the, the, the crushing reality that your life is the same thing day
in and day out really seeps into your bones and creates a lethargy where, where you think,
man, I should really do work today.
I mean, I've already produced literally 12 vlogs and a whole video, but I should really
do more work today.
Never mind.
I have to, something has to make me go to bed because this is too much, you know.
It happens.
It happens and it makes me sad every time.
Okay.
Let's move on to our next story.
It's enough about jacking off for now.
How about Jesse?
Why don't you tell us your tale?
Okay.
It was a dark and stormy night.
A boy was walking in the snow with his loyal growl from home.
On the outskirts.
He was walking far from home.
On the outskirts of Ponyville, a dark shadow was cast.
Nate, don't try to appropriate my memes.
Oh, I forgive you.
It's my meme now, baby.
I'm the puppy dog boy.
You stole my career, so I stole your meme.
We can co-opt it.
Okay.
My story is a, is a story of, of, of, of perseverance through hardship, onwards to glory, onwards
ascending to manhood, to godhood, fighting all obstacles, going through them.
Having sex.
No matter how many policemen tried to stop me, I got what I came for.
Yeah.
This sounds like it's going to be a good story for Victor's book, the, how to find, how to,
how to get a relationship in just six easy years.
Right.
It sounds like it would fall into this category.
How to escape the friend zone in six easy years.
Right.
That's what it is.
Yeah.
Okay.
It sounds like a great piece of fiction.
The friend zones for life, baby.
Believe it.
Okay.
Sheld that away in the fucking fantasy section.
You know what they say, real niggas stay friend zoned for life.
That's right.
Hashtag babies.
Okay.
Let's go on, Jess.
What else?
What else happened?
Okay.
So this is a, you know, it was way back in, in high school.
And my, my, my best friend at the time was a girl whose, whose identity I will protect,
whose name I won't, I'll give her a fake name.
Her name was Angela Lena.
Angela's mom.
Angela Lena.
Yeah.
So Angelina Jolie.
Right.
Yeah.
Exactly.
So she was like my best friend.
I had a super huge crush on her.
I was totally in love with her, but I was very shy.
I didn't know about how to make a girl like me.
I was nervous.
I thought that she would hate me if I, you know, encroached upon our friendship more
romantically, which is always true because women are psychotic.
True.
Right.
So, so I didn't know how to, you know, make it go that next step.
And you know, every, we would go to like, like high school dances and they would always
be so horrible and I hate them cause I'd sit and I wouldn't, you know, have the courage
to ask her to dance or anything.
And it was just lame and I hated it all.
And then I fucking, eventually it was at, it was, it was at senior prom.
And she was there.
That's a make or break.
Yeah.
It was make or break.
It's like, this was my last chance.
If I don't have the courage to dance with her at the senior prom, then that's it.
It's my last chance that she's gone forever.
I'll never do it.
And I didn't do it.
So I was just what I thought.
This was like the idyllic high school romance 80s film story.
Oh, just, oh, just wait.
So it was at senior prom and I felt like I was, I was blowing my one, my one chance,
my last opportunity.
I was sitting there sad.
I was watching her, you know, on the dance floor having fun.
I was off and at my fucking table with my friends and I just, I was feeling so low and
so down in the dumps.
So I just had to get up and I had to walk out through the door out into like the patio
because we were at some fancy fucking prom place with like a, you know, patio or whatever.
Right.
So I just, I walked out the door out to the patio and I just, to just stand by myself
and just mope around and gaze for Lauren at the stars.
And I was out there on the patio and this other girl comes up to me who was two grades
below me.
So it wasn't supposed to be at the prom, but I guess she had just snuck in there anyways
to hang out because she was fucking, I don't know.
Some other guys date maybe?
I can hear, I can hear a rumbling in the distance.
I hear a chant coming over the horizon as the story continues.
Sex with the young, sex with the young, sex with the young, sex with the young, sex with
the young, sex with the young, sex with the young, sex with the young.
So, so I was feeling sad and rejected and lonely and I felt like, you know, I lost my
chance.
I'll be a virgin forever, whatever, you know, and I was, and I was sitting there.
I was standing out there on the patio and this girl from two grades below me comes up
whose name, whose identity I will also protect, um, Adriana.
She comes up to me and I remember exactly what she was wearing.
She was wearing this like beautiful, like, like shiny emerald green gown.
Her hair was like down to her ass.
She has super long hair.
She was magnificently pretty.
She was a perfect specimen.
Everything, body, young, hot, sex with the young kind of girl.
Jesse, how long was your hair at this time?
My hair was about as long as it is now, back then.
I see.
So I was a long hair boy back then, too.
And so she comes up and she's pretty and she's, it turns out, like I found out years
later that like every girl in high school had a crush on me, but I didn't notice any
of them because I had such a crush on my friend.
Oh, fuck.
So she came up to me.
That's the Victor story, isn't it?
Yeah.
This really is the six easy years story, except that you got it much quicker.
Well, there was no friend zone here.
Well, OK, go on, go on.
So, um, yeah, I just remember she came up and she approached me and she talked to
me and we just danced.
Like she danced with me alone out on the patio.
It was like there was no one else there.
And it was like this weird, like a romantic, like a, like a height, like a teen
movie, like a John Hughes moment of me, like, wow, that's a cool thing.
But then, um, anyways, later in the night, I got arrested.
So I ended up.
Jesus Christ.
I ended up, I ended up not following up on that with her right away.
Yeah, there was a whole big thing with with guns and swords and, you know, the cops,
they took my sword and I never fucking, I never got it back either, because they
put it in their fucking police station that we were, we were fucking on.
And they really took your sword.
That wasn't a cautionary tales of swords.
No, that was it.
No, we all are.
Why did you have a story from his real life?
Because I went to, because I went to prom as a pirate.
I had a sword.
This is a whole new dimension.
The cops took my sword.
Is that what the girl came up to?
Yeah, me and all my friends, we were on our knees in the side of the road.
We were laying on our bellies that I had like fucking like 12 fucking guns
pointed at my head at one point.
It was really scary and really traumatic.
And they took my sword and I lost my sword forever.
And also, you know, and so I didn't, and I didn't see Adriana for a fucking
year after that.
And also, so it was like, so it was, it was a year later.
And by now I was however old you are after high school, a year after
I was like 39 or something.
So that was still a Virgo.
All these long months after high school.
So after that, so it was a year later and we ended up getting kicked out of
our house because of rent stuff, which is why we always get kicked out of the
house.
My life is just a, my life is just like an intermittent, intermittent
homelessness, peppered by like occasional sex with the young.
Right.
So like we were getting kicked out of our house.
I know Ben can relate.
That's so true.
Yeah.
He's a worthless human being.
What else is going on?
Yeah, yeah, totally agreed on all counts.
Yeah.
So we had to move.
We had to get out of there.
So my mom, you know, we fucked around.
My mom picked a house.
She fucking in a little bit of ways.
Turns out out of, out of complete happenstance, this house that we were
now moving into was neighbors with the girl who danced with me at the senior
prom.
So she, she messages.
Counts is John Hughes level.
I don't think we've lost it yet.
Yeah, yeah, it's got some extra plot twists, but it's, it's going in the
right direction, the action, the action scene with the sword fight and the,
and the guns was a nice little, a nice little interim.
Yeah.
The, the fucking, maybe this is a little bit more Joss Whedon.
My, my, my, my, does she die at the end?
My, my Scott pilgrim sword fight at senior prom that ended in bloodshed
and carnage and tears.
Um, yeah.
So she messaged me on my space because that's what that was in.
That was the fashion at the time.
I had an onion on my belt and we were all using my space and she
messaged me on my, okay.
What does that mean?
I know all about the onion on the belt.
Us, us old, us old timers.
Us old timers.
Yeah.
Okay, great.
That was the fashion at the time.
Yeah.
You know, you, you, you could get the yellow onions, but if you really,
the choice white onion, if you were a high class bloke.
What about red onions?
Foreigners only.
Okay.
All right.
That's how you knew they weren't from around here.
So fucking.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
So fucking Audrey Lena fucking messages me on, on, on my space.
He goes, Hey, uh, I guess you're moving in next door to me.
Whoa.
And I'm like, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
Oh my gosh.
I'm like, Oh yeah.
Totally.
Babe, I was real cool on my space.
Um, yo, so he was calm.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
I was like spaghetti all over me.
Yeah, there it is.
That's the one.
Yeah, there we go.
That name.
I really blended that one.
All right.
So yeah, we moved into this house.
It was a really cool fucking farmhouse with like a huge, like a yard.
There was like, there was cattle.
There was like big old fluffy cows in the backyard and stuff.
It was a cool house and, and it was a big old farm.
Like, and then like there was a fence at the top of the hill and you just hopped
the fence and then you were at her house.
So we started talking when I moved in and like, yeah, let's fucking hang out and
fucking, and fucking hang out.
So I fucking, so, so she, she messages me one night while I'm there.
She's like, Hey, I had a, I had a big fight with my dad.
I, my, my dad's a jerk.
I hate my dad.
I'm like, Oh no, what's your dad like?
So she starts telling me about her dad.
So, you know, so I go over there.
I climb, I climb the hill.
I hop the fence.
I go over to her yard.
We sit on her, on her back porch.
We have to be quiet cause her parents are sleeping.
And, and, and so I'm just sitting there on her porch.
I put my arm around her.
She's, she's like crying about her dad.
We, we look at the stars together.
We talk, we bond.
At night, we, we, we gave a little kiss.
Got a little kiss that night.
Nice.
And I, and I.
On the dick.
Hey, hey, hey, don't make my story.
This is a, this is still an innocent.
You don't sully it with your porn fantasies.
You're still, you're still on the, you're still playing the, the Marvin Gaye.
You haven't yet switched over to the DMX.
I'm still.
That's right.
I'm, I'm still, I'm still dabbing the, the lube on the butthole.
I'm not pushing on it yet.
So I went back to my house and I went to bed that night feeling so fucking groovy.
So like, yes, I have a girly friend.
I'm going to get more kisses.
Maybe I'll even see a bub.
I was so excited.
So the next day she comes over to my house and we start kissing more because
now it's a thing that we do now.
And now we kiss and we were fucking making out.
We started making out, I started touching boobs, started touching her fucking body.
Pulling her, I gotta start off, got her fucking pants off, started touching that,
that, that, oh, that little, little hairy 17 year old puss.
And that's, and that's why I'll turn B.
That went through the air.
You just heard that one, that one song coming out of the ether.
I go hard in the motherfucking paint, nigga.
I leave you stank, nigga.
What the fuck you thinking, nigga?
Yeah, that was the one.
No, no, this is the, this is the song I heard off in the distance.
Bork, Orph, Bork, Bork.
I got a tiny little puppy dog erection stick it inside your Johnny with a protection.
So, so I was touching on the vagina.
I was holding her, her, her, her smaller, her thin little frail, perfect little
teenage body in my hands, you know, holding, holding a young woman's
body in your hands, feeling her, her skin in your palms.
You know, you just realize at that moment, I realize that this is the only
thing that's real in life.
Everything else is the fucking matrix.
This is all that there is.
This is all that, this is all that will ever matter to me.
This is, this is my fucking, this is my desert of the real.
And I am fucking Morpheus.
I am Morpheus and Neo combined.
I am the one.
I am all the ones.
I'm Jet Lee combining all the ones into one one.
Everyone wants a munchie.
In that moment, my Christ consciousness levels skyrocketed to a plateau
never seen before or since by anyone in history.
Just fucking holding that small, young, sexy, sex with the young woman in my hands.
Yeah, I can still fucking picture it in my mind's eye.
It gives me power in that moment.
In California, a being was created by the name of Munchie, who had all the powers
of this Christ consciousness.
That's the origin of the munchie.
Yeah, that's where it comes from.
So we were getting real hot and heavy, me and this girl.
And I was, I was, I was touching that little vagina.
I was touching those bubies.
And then I got, I got the blow job.
I got the bludge people.
Nice.
The blow.
I got it.
I got a nice.
I got just, just, oh, that, that, that, that, that perfect inexperienced,
toothy, 17 year old, bloge.
The best thing that you can experience in life.
Tray magnifique.
Yes.
Oh, it was so cool.
So cool.
Yeah, so cool.
So when do you actually get played?
I'm not there yet.
I'm not.
This story has layers.
It has chapters.
It's a saga.
It's an onion, like Shrek.
Right.
My, my, my, this story is like a section of half.
This story is almost as good as Shrek.
Yeah.
So we were doing the stuff.
Somebody once told me.
Hey, depending on what year this was, that could very well have been playing.
I know Jesse was a big Smash Mouth fan.
Shrek is just the story of Jesse's life in the ogre form.
Taking girls back to my astral lounge and, and sexing with the young.
And they're fucking swamped, don't you?
No, no, no.
Back then in my old house, I lived in the upstairs.
Yeah.
I had like a patio on the roof that I could walk out and do with a door.
It was awesome.
It was tops blueby.
But anyways, you know, I was, we were, first we were at my house and I was
touching on the vagina there.
And then we, we went and we hopped the fence over to her house and that's
where I got the bloge.
So I got the bloge at her house.
But, um, but she goes, Oh boy, my dad's going to be home any minute.
You got it.
You got to get on out of here.
So I, I fucking left and I walked home feeling good.
Oh my God, I got a bloge.
I got a fucking toothy 17 year old bloge.
Oh my God.
And I fucking, I went to my fucking house and I went to bed that night feeling
like any day now, any day now I'm going to have the sex, the real sex.
The next day she sends me a long message on my space.
Oh, we went too far, too fast.
I'm not ready for this.
Sex with the young sex with the young sex with the young.
The mistake.
Don't do it.
Sex with the young.
It was tragically ripped away from me.
80 years later, Jesse still crawls the land to this day looking for bloge.
She's crawling through the desert, malnourished, dust on my breath.
Sex with the young.
Wandering the streets of the city of fallen angels.
Wandering with my little cup full of spare change.
Sex with the young, sir.
Can anyone spare some sex with the young?
Jesus.
The fucking the sheriff of Nottingham combs and pushes me in the mud and says,
Get a job.
He takes all my fucking spare sex with the young out of my cup.
You almost have a whole one.
There's that that clockwork orange scene where your two old high school buddies
who were your droogs, they find you out of the street.
They drag you to the fucking bathtub and just drown you for fun.
Just to watch you suffer.
We've got sex with the young.
Where's your sex with the young?
My droogs.
My loyal droogs.
Every time Jesse comes close to having sex with the young,
it triggers the memories of the program he went through.
And he has to be like, he becomes paralyzed and his dick falls off
and he just can't even do anything.
I hear the fucking Beethoven.
No, they play fucking Macklemore.
No, stop it, stop it, please.
No, no.
Yeah, I hear the fuck they gave me the fucking Ludovico technique
where they fucking played that Macklemore song telling me
I have too much white privilege and I can play it straight to it.
Now whenever I try to have sex with the young, I have to read an article.
Little did they know that would create the greatest white privilege warrior
the world had ever seen.
So, Jesse, I gotta tell you.
Yeah, what the fuck else happened?
She didn't act three.
So she broke, so she broke up with me and I was fucking devastated.
Not just because I liked this girl and my heart was broken,
but also because I was fucking close to losing my virginity.
And it was ripped away from me tragically.
So, so as a young man would do as like a however the fuck I was
19, 20, 39, whatever the fuck I said, I raped her.
Yeah, of course.
She owes you.
She owes you at this point.
It's time to take what you owe.
You know, I just I flipped out, I was not mature enough to handle it.
I was blown away that I had gotten so close.
So, of course, I begged and I pleaded and I did all the, you know,
the beta cut shit.
I was very pathetic.
I didn't beg for sex.
I begged for her to like to get back with me.
Oh, OK, of course.
That was Jay Bauman back in my school.
I wouldn't blame you, though.
I beg for sex every day.
Yeah, so my favorite thing to do.
So the breakup got really ugly and really weird.
It got really horrible.
She ended up like telling like all of her friends at school that I was like a
like a bad guy or like a creeper or pervert or something.
Oh, God, what the fuck?
It was fucking terrible.
Fuck, I remember.
Buyers remorse.
Yeah, this one guy who was like a friend of both of ours.
I'll say his name, Chris Peters, because he's a fucking piece of shit.
Fuck you, Chris Peters.
Yeah, I hate him to this day.
You know, he was like he was like a friend of both of ours.
And he like sent me he sent me this message one day like out of the blue
like calling me like a sick pig.
You sick motherfucker.
You're fucking down.
All these like made up rumors of the stuff that I supposedly did typical
orbiter behavior.
Yeah, exactly.
He's the one who sucked your dick.
She's the pervert.
You know, he's coerced her, though.
He was too sexual of a man.
It's his fault.
Yeah, exactly.
Doctor.
Yeah, I was too irresistible.
You know, I, you know, I made her abandon her scruples and she she couldn't take it.
She had to she had to lash out at me.
So I was like I was like persona non grata.
I was like fucking ostracized.
My personal and professional reputation was ruined in my hometown.
Everyone, everyone hated me.
You know, I was banned from the theater.
I was banned from I was banned from the high school, even though I had graduated a year earlier.
I they had to keep me away from all the young.
I'm sure they were they revoked your key to the city at this point.
Yeah, they tore down my statue.
So, so at this point, I'm just I'm just like a shell of a man.
I'm just a I'm just a fucking broken boy.
I'm walking around.
I'm just a fucking I'm just I'm just as fucking sad.
I'm a lost puppy dog boy howling at the fucking moon.
Bark off, bark off.
I'm fucking lost in this world.
I have no one and I'm feeling I'm like this is it.
I'm never going to lose my virginity.
I'm going to be I'm going to be like this alone.
It's never going to happen for me.
You know, I had gone through high school watching all my buddies, you know, one by one, high five each other.
One by one, they all had that morning, walking in and high fiving each other at the fucking lunch table.
And every fucking time there were more high fives that I wasn't a part of.
I had to fucking you know, it does something to a boy, you know, watching everyone lose it.
But you and then you fucking and then you get so close and you fucking I was just hopeless at this point.
And I was I was on my fucking rock bottom and I was like that for a whole another year of like when's when's it going to happen.
And so then, you know, and during that time I kept trying.
I just kept fucking, you know, when I fucking saw her on Facebook, I'd messenger.
I'd try so hard to make conversation with girls.
Oh, God, Facebook came around by this point.
That's how long it took.
Yeah, yep.
I think I think the the the dear John letter I got from Adriana was was the end of my space for me as I had to go to Facebook at that point.
You know, and so the year went by and there was all kinds of, you know, more awkward, terrible fucking things.
There was a fucking thing with a girl that I fucking spooned with one night and it got weird.
There was and she got mad at me and that made me they ruined my reputation even more.
There was like five girls that I that I tried to rape, but they all beat me up because they all knew karate one time.
It was fucking all these karate girls got off a bus and I thought they were regular girls and I could rape them.
But it turns out they were karate girls.
If it would any other bus, it would have worked like a charm.
Fate just it wasn't in the cards in this day.
And who's just going to try the next bus?
Like at this point, you know, you're all battered and beaten up.
And you just like the wily coyote trying to get sex and boulders keep falling on your.
Sometimes you just got to know when to call it quits and cut your losses.
All these damn acme broads, they always backfire on you.
What is the road runner cartoon but an allegory for male sexuality?
That's really what it is at the end of the day.
I mean, we all know that a girl's version of karate is to kick you in the balls.
So he probably had like his balls were probably just in pieces at this point.
That's right. That's right.
So the story is reminiscent of how I met your mother where like eight seasons of the story have nothing to do with what happened.
And the people are still clamoring for more at the end of it.
They don't want it to ever end.
That's so far the weakest last three seasons I've ever seen.
They said they say, God damn it, Jason Siegel, tell a new story, please.
Don't abandon us.
That wasn't Jason Siegel, it was Bob Saget telling the story.
I never watched that shitty fucking show, I don't know.
Learn your how I met your mother, Laura, you stupid.
I would rather fucking die than watch that shit.
That fucking country.
It has that Patrick O'Neill of what's his name?
Yeah, it's not even a real anime here.
He makes funny meme jokes, dude.
All right, I need to know the rest of the story.
Yeah.
Neil Patrick Harris.
It was Neil Patrick Harris.
That's the guy.
So surely we're near the climax.
Neil Patrick Harris.
So I fucking, I desperately tried, I tried for a year still to try and make hours ago.
I finally got a girl to be like responsive to me and it was another girl who had apparently
had a huge crush on me in high school and never said anything about it because I guess
girls just think, you know, they don't have to say anything about it.
It is my fault somehow.
Fuck you.
You know, there's another girl who finally is like, okay, I got her to come over, I got
her to come over to my house.
There's another girl whose name, whose identity that I will protect.
I'll give her fake name, fucking secretariat.
So this beautiful, this beautiful gorgeous young horsewoman comes to me.
Over to my house to hang out and we just started kissing and we just started making out and
I remember my bed was a futon and it was currently in couch mode.
So we were laying in the couch on the couch in my room with the lights off.
We were just making out and touching each other more and more for hours and hours.
And we, I just, you know, got her clothes off by the way.
I have a perfect, I have a basically a flawless record except for that first time.
She's always sex on the first date and ever since then, no one will ever stop it.
We were fucking touching, we were making out and I got it in her.
I got it.
You got it.
Monkey.
Monkey, you were absolutely right.
The story had nothing to do with the ending.
The whole thing was just a big fucking shaggy dog.
We'll see.
That's what I was saying at the start.
Well, when you're talking about a man, you're describing the story of a man's entire life.
That's right.
You philistines.
You needed the emotional arc to find out.
Without the emotional arc, you just get a Ben story.
It's like, oh, yeah.
That's right.
And that's what people want.
No one wants a Ben story.
That's what people want.
They want clear, concise, sterile Ben stories.
Your story was awful.
My story has a fucking human element that people can relate to.
That's why people fucking love me.
That's why I get the patron dollars more than Ben does and always will.
That's why.
When you began telling your story, I went out to like get some tea and it took two minutes
and I missed the whole story.
I understand people.
I know how to connect with people on an emotional level.
And so, you know, as I was saying, Ben wasn't here for Nate's story, which had the entire
story of him going to Japan and coming back.
That is super relevant.
I want to say about this story too.
I could have gone on about my life story leading up to like when I went to college and met a
girl and all that shit, but like it's not relevant to the actual act of how I lost my
virginity.
You have to know the fucking emotional arc.
You got to know about the fucking John Hughes prom.
You got to know about the fucking police cops who took my sword away.
You got to know about the thought of the fence that I had the hop of fence.
You got to know everything.
I think Ben might have elaborate more if he had heard the story.
This is a story that I think I would have.
And now I'm kind of fucking lamenting that I didn't fucking know what I was working
on.
Maybe you should be on time to the fucking PCP.
The story that spans from my space to Facebook.
The greatest expanse in human history.
I'm just, look, I could have, god damn it, I could have spun a yarn.
I could have spun y'all a yarn, but now it's too late.
Fuck y'all.
You don't deserve it.
I don't care.
Shut up.
I'm not even done.
We were making love.
Me and this fine, this fine young mama's seat, we were making sweet love on that couch
in the dark.
We made love for like fucking eight hours, you know, my mom came home and she's like
blah, blah, blah.
I'm like shut up.
I'm making love to a beautiful young woman in here and ma, get out of here.
Get out.
And I'm fucking making love and it was, you know, it was, it was, it was that very special
kind of, kind of like awkward and terrible, but also passionate and awesome first time
sex that can only happen that one special night in your life with that, with that one
special girl.
And so we did it.
And so then after I took her home, I came home and I was so amped that I just started
eating everything in the house.
I ate all the food in the whole house.
I fucking opened up a can of beans, like fucking skull monkeys, cold beans, a whole, a cold
can of beans.
I just fucking devoured it like an animal.
I was a man possessed.
I was fully in touch with the primal, manimal beast, the ancient thing deep in my lizard
brain had awoken.
And so then the next day she came over and we, we watched Rambo too.
We watched Rambo first blood part two and then we, we did it a million more times and
then we dated for like a couple of years and it was a good time and that was, it was the
most important story ever, better than Ben's.
And that's all that matters.
Yeah.
I think everybody's is better than Ben's.
You fucking, you fucking faggots.
All right.
Hey, hey, hey.
Ben was a cliff notes of, of, uh, absolutely gets, uh, hey, but before we move on, I just
want, I thought it'd be interesting just to point out how, uh, cause you know, everyone
was saying Jesse went on for a long time before the actual act.
But I think that that's really what's interesting about it because to everybody out there who's
a virgin right now, it's not like you just miraculously have sex one day.
It is about a real, a real life struggle.
You have to go through like Jesse, both you and I had innumerable, innumerable failures
on our past.
That's what I'm saying.
Everyone has to go through that because like you were saying at the beginning, we all have
friends who are virgins, who are late bloomers as we were and who are, who are losing hope.
They're going to, they're going to lose hope as I once almost did, but you can't lose
hope because it's going to happen.
It's going to happen if you keep trying.
That's the moral of the story.
That's why I had to tell you about all the failures, all the struggles, all the trials
and tribulations you had to get real, getting a lady is exactly like working out in that
it is an ability that you can start training at any time and get really fit and get really
swole or get really good at getting girls at any time you can start.
So if you're 80 fucking years old, just start now and in a couple months you'll have one.
I guarantee it if you work at it.
Incidentally, I might as well, for the members of our audience who don't also listen to the
dick show, I'll give you dicks, two most important tips for picking up chicks which have worked
for tons of people.
Number one, your opening line, comment about their shoes.
That's a good tangible word.
It works on all women, no matter what, if you just say, hey, I like your shoes, it will
be an opener.
Just talk about their shoes.
Because they're also shallow and stupid.
You just take care about their shoes.
No, let me fucking fix all of your wagon right now and tell you why that line works.
It's not because women are stupid or because they're shallow, it's because literally anything
can work.
It doesn't matter what you say.
It doesn't matter what your opening line is or stupid thing about their shoes.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The thing about the shoes specifically is that all women wear shoes and, well, for the
most part, is that no matter what they're going to be wearing it, but it jungles lots
I'm fucking do.
I don't know what you're talking about.
If you compliment a girl's shirt, it looks like you're looking at her tits.
If you compliment this or that, there's some things that girls don't want to be complimented
on or that it'll mean the wrong thing to them.
But if it's just the shoes.
No, no, no.
Here's why.
It's because men don't think about shoes.
I drew a character design last night and my girlfriend was like, where's the shoes?
And I was like, oh, yeah, I didn't think about shoes.
I am male.
So girls are not accustomed to men commenting on shoes.
So what you're telling me is that what women want out of men actually being considerate.
So what women want out of men is a woman is what you're telling me.
All right.
Step one is that a woman is nothing more than a bigger six year old girl.
And instead of dressing her dolls, she's now dressing herself.
Of course.
Always with the red pills, Mom.
Thank you for keeping us safe.
So aside from that, the shoes are the opening line and it's you can find there's other opening
lines you can use.
I should have the other day when I recorded my my what was it, neurotic stories from real
man where I had my failed story of where if I had just asked the girl about the beer,
it would have been the perfect opener.
But I failed miserably.
If you haven't heard that story, it's on my Reddit.
But so but but shoes are a universal.
All girls are wearing shoes, compliment the shoes.
You don't even have to look at the shoes.
So what's good about it is that it's when you can use any time.
It's because it's something that women put a lot of thought into is what fucking pair
of shoes they're going to wear.
And nobody mentions it.
All they hear all day is you've got a nice rack, you've got a pretty face, but you should
smile more and your hair is pretty.
Everybody says the same thing.
Smile more.
Yeah.
And so and then the second important line because you've got yourself in the door with
the shoes.
But now you're lost because you don't know what to talk about because you don't know this
girl actually.
You're just you just started to write a conversation.
So if things seem to be going well, you bust out what's your dad like?
Ask them about their dad.
It doesn't matter if they have a good or bad relationship with their dad, either way, they're
going to open up and become more intimate in the conversation.
And that's what you want.
So yeah.
No, no, no.
This is all.
Follow up with that.
What you're laying here is all a bunch of like secondhand stuff that he's heard.
Yeah.
Another man say.
From the.
Aren't you going to.
From many colors.
I'll give you.
I'll give people a real tip.
I'll give people a just tip and this was is tried and tested.
The true way to get women is not with some some magical pickup line that you're going
to go up to some stranger and talk to someone like that's going to happen.
It's just a template.
It's not something that's always going to work or that you just guaranteed.
I think that people know.
I think people really need to quit being bitches and be less afraid to fucking talk to each
other in real life and go and fucking hit on a girl in public because who fucking cares.
You're absolutely wrong, Ben.
And I'll tell you why.
Because anyone who fucking approaches any other human being for any reason in public
is a piece of shit and I want them to die.
Hey, actually, I.
Anyone fucking came up and started talking to me whether it was a man woman or child
that would snap their head backwards and let them fucking twitch on the floor until
their life escaped from their eyes.
Hey, it's.
No one should.
I'm giving a fucking just tip.
God damn it.
This is the only real fucking tip is to just fucking evolve into into a man.
You have to have that women want to come to you.
That's the only fucking tip.
You fucking because.
Well, yeah, sure.
I have zero respect that's hard for anyone who fucking approaches a stranger and tries
to fucking hit on them.
They just look pathetic to me.
They look like pathetic little weak fuck.
No.
Fuck you, dude.
Searching for women.
Like a fucking caveman.
I'm a hunter gatherer.
What are you talking about?
Picking berries in the fucking jungle.
Like desperately like standing out there like a bullfrog shooting your fucking neck
sack out saying, please, some woman in here, please like me.
Do you like me?
If you have the balls to go out and try to make a human connection, put yourself out
there.
You're a fucking hero.
It's not as cool as celebrating.
Talking to girls.
Talking to girls is scary and it's scary and it takes fucking.
It takes fucking courage.
It takes balls.
I'll tell you what takes courage being a great man takes courage working day in and day out
to be better at your fucking chosen profession than anyone else to where you're so fucking
good to where you're so talented and so inspirational that women everywhere flock to you that you
don't have to go up to them.
That's what makes a real man.
That takes courage.
That's what we should tell.
That's what we should tell every fucking lonely guy out there.
Don't approach them.
Yes, it is what we should tell them.
Don't talk to women.
Be a better man.
Just whoever you are, no matter what, just stay home and practice your shit or whatever
and eventually you'll be so fucking good that every fucking girl will come and hit on
you.
How does this work for people in non-creative positions?
It does.
Fuck them!
Fuck people in non-creative positions.
That's what I thought.
They're less than human.
They don't deserve to live on my planet anyways.
So you know, guys, you know, everyone knows, oh, you just got to get good at talking to
people, but it's like, do you want to go through the whole pressure of failing at that over
and over again?
You're going to have to, but I have a life hack for how to train up those skills in some
regard without as much of the shame.
Omega.
You know, whether or not the person that you're talking to is actually female or is actually
90 years old, the fact is they're a human and you can use that as sort of like a punching
bag to train your strength of talking, breaking the ice, figuring out what question to follow
up another question.
Just go on Omega for like hours into the night and just practice because when it goes wrong,
you just pull the plug and you don't feel that much shame because they don't know anything
about you.
That's what you've got to do in real life.
I honestly feel like that was how I leveled up my ability to fucking like talk to people
and like give off the air of being natural and fluid in the conversation.
I knew how to like progress the discussion without it seeming forced, but still being
interesting.
That was how I trained.
What happened to just being like a normal, like a cool person and you know, you hang
out and you talk to people, you get to know people slowly in your circles who grow to
like you because you're just cool.
And it happens.
Let me tell you, I'll tell you what happened for these cowards, these chicken ship pushy
men who walk up to strangers.
It makes me sick to think that if you're not meeting strangers, then you're never going
to fucking expand your fucking circle.
All right.
That's exactly what what happened, Jesse, is that the real world has changed and people
spend their days alone.
They need resources that they can use to God.
Meeple, we don't just work on fucking farms now and you're, you're co-mingly with people
all the time.
I mean, people fucking work IT jobs, they sit behind a computer all day.
There needs to be things they can do if they're going to meet people because their day-to-day
life doesn't introduce them to people in a regular way.
It's fucking psychotic.
They have to, it's not like, no, what is psychotic is the lifestyle that we've all been living
as humans in the 21st century where we live isolated, alone lives.
We need to strategize to make our society function so that people have opportunities to have
the real human interactions that you're talking about because they don't arise naturally anymore.
Primitive?
Like, this fucking primitive, like standing around like a peacock, going around fucking
coming up to women like a fucking monkey and fucking approaching strangers.
You know, maybe some people don't want to be approached and talked to by a stranger.
Maybe some people, maybe- SHUT UP, MUNCHY!
Maybe some people- FUCK OFF, HOLY SHIT!
Maybe some people have social anxiety.
Maybe some people don't want to be fucking talked at by a fucking stranger.
Maybe people shouldn't fucking think it's normal to walk up to someone like a fucking
psycho and start trying to hit on a fucking stranger who might not fucking want it.
It's retarded and psychotic and creepy and it's fucking- it's like a- you're like a fucking
animal.
Why is everyone a fucking goddamn primitive idiot but me?
So you advocate for never introducing yourself to people and not-
Never talk to anyone.
I just want to thank Munchy for coming in and peeing while Jess was screaming.
Yeah, I heard that.
I heard that.
It was not eco-hered.
Holy crap, I advocate being a regular fucking guy and like talking-
No, you advocate being a YouTube star who women approach.
That's what you said the first time.
Yeah.
How's that regular?
Yeah, it works for you.
What about- what about the rest of the world?
Hey!
What about me and my blue collar?
Yeah.
I fucking- I was able to get girls before YouTube by being a normal fucking person who
was just cool and funny and you know when I- when I'd go around in my social circles
and- and I would fucking hang out with people.
Where do you get these social circles?
Where are you developing-
Jesse, Jesse-
Because fucking friends have friends of friends!
That's how human beings meet!
Wait, look, the first friend!
Where does the-
No, I-
The age of zero-
What?
No, you know what?
Look, I think if you've got a fucking healthy social circle then yeah, you probably are
gonna be meeting new people in the course of fucking, you know, your circles- your circles
connecting to other circles and stuff.
Yeah, I think that's legit, but like, I'm talking about what if you don't have that?
What if you're just fucked?
Yeah, what if you have no-
Then fuck you!
What-
What matters, what matters is thinking about this question in the context of the audience
who's hearing it right now.
And these people don't need the kind of advice like, go be a YouTube star.
They need tangible things-
I'm giving them advice!
Go be a regular person!
Go outside and be like a normal, nice guy!
Look, I'm just saying-
Okay.
What if you've got- what if you're- what if you're like a bunch of- what if all your
friends are like a bunch of nerds who just hang out and fucking, I don't know, play Magic
the Gathering all the time and you never go out and you never meet anyone?
Well, you know, there's the-
Then you're fucked.
Okay, well, there has been this invention called the World Wide Web and there are like
trillions of dating sites that- that are free that people go on and they-
Yeah, just in your own system.
I'm not against that.
They came up to you at prom and gave you a fucking blowjob a year later.
If she didn't approach you as a stranger, you never would've got that blowjob.
There we fucking go.
There we go.
I wasn't a stranger.
I knew her.
We went to fucking school together.
But she's-
Look, I'm sure she- she approached me because she knew me and lied to me and saw me hanging
out.
Nobody fucking should approach strangers randomly.
Jesse, Jesse, okay.
I- I agree that it'd be great.
What's wrong with striking up a fucking conversation in public?
Because I don't want a stranger to fucking talk to me.
Well, listen, you don't want to strike up a conversation.
You don't want to-
Jesse, Jesse, I'm just a great line once.
No, no, no, listen, listen, I want to say this.
Okay.
All right.
People need to fucking- I think people should approach people in public and I also think
that people shouldn't be afraid to tell others to fuck off.
And like, I think-
I agree.
I think that girls, I don't understand this sometimes.
I feel like girls can get approached by guys and feel scared that, like, they can't
tell them to just fuck off.
And I- I- I don't know, like, if it's like alone in like a dark alley or something-
Of course they feel fucking scared!
Guys are stronger and might rape them!
But if you're fucking in public, if you're fucking in a public place, you can just be
like, leave me alone.
I don't know.
I feel like a lot of girls are scared to just be like, I don't want you to talk to me,
okay?
But maybe some guys don't take that well, and maybe it doesn't always work.
I don't know.
Am I fucking crazy?
I think that the way the world should be is everyone should be feel free to like, go
up and strike up a conversation with anyone else, and everyone should be free to just
be like, fuck off, don't talk to me, and then we should all just respect that.
That would be my ideal fucking world.
My vision for the world is that nobody should ever have to say fuck off because everyone
should mind their own goddamn business and be normal.
Jesse, I heard a great line-
I've heard a great line every week.
I heard a great line once, and I'm going to say it to you now because I think it's really
important for guys to think like this, and for women too, and it's that no woman ever
walks out of the house in the morning not wanting to meet the guy of her dreams.
And if you just think about that, it's the fucking retarded pick-up artist, bullshit
is that.
Who gives a shit?
It's-
What do you mean who gives a shit?
It's making a point that it's never a bad idea to try to introduce yourself to people
because you never know if your interaction is going to be mutually beneficial.
I disagree vehemently.
It's very bad to introduce yourself to strangers, it's the worst thing a human being can do.
Can I tell my story?
This argument's retarded.
Yes, my peep.
It is retarded.
Everyone is wrong but me.
Okay.
So, unlike some of our predecessors, I'm not going to give any extraneous details that
aren't important to the story.
So when I was growing up, I lived in a pretty poor neighborhood.
Oh, okay.
That was the joke.
The joke-
The joke is that I said I wasn't-
Okay, never mind.
But it really was.
I got it.
But that actually is part of the story.
I was just fucking with you.
Yeah.
So you're growing up-
So fucking tell the fucking story, Bob.
I'm confused.
They're wasting my goddamn time.
Where did his truth end and the lies begin?
When I was eight, I lived in a pretty poor neighborhood and I was actually like the kid
who got bullied by everybody.
First of all, I've always been really short.
So I automatically had the nickname Little and everybody fucking called me Little.
And I remember one time, the leader of the bully pack was named Terrell and these fuckers
would just chase me around the neighborhood, like calling me a faggot and stuff and I would
have to find-
Jesus.
I'd have to like find places to like hide like inside like abandoned buildings and shit.
Got that.
But it was motivation.
Because as I was aging, I wanted to not only one, get taller, which never happened, but
two, prove to them that I am not a faggot and that I can have sex, god damn it.
So I assumed that one day when they were chasing you, they caught you and that's how you lost
your virginity.
That's what happened.
Yeah, right?
No.
You're days of the kind of flyer.
Anyway, so yeah, at that time when I was a kid, the only friend I had was named Kevin.
And he stood up for me sometimes, but he was mostly, he ended up getting peer pressured
by the other guys to also bully me.
But Kevin, he was like halfway there for me, like when it was just me and him.
And then in public, he'd like, yeah, fuck this little monkey bitch, but it's all part
of the story.
Okay.
I'm 15 and Terrell, this guy I was talking about, he really got me.
He just fucked with me at lunch one day and I was like, you know, I'd fuck this.
So I left school early and my school was kind of near a lake.
So there's like a little beach that I would always go to.
And I was sitting just in the sand, just like, you know, maybe today's the day I kill myself.
Fuck this.
Oh, shit.
But Kevin, he followed me.
That's really sad that you didn't.
Yeah, no, you made the wrong decision that day, monkey.
What happened?
He said, it's really sad you didn't kill yourself.
Oh, yeah, well, definitely.
I still believe that.
Right.
Okay.
But Kevin saw what happened at lunch and he followed me and he was sitting down next
to me and we're just like talking.
And then he, um, he like just reached over into my pants and started giving me a hand
joke.
What the fuck?
So like that's the first time anybody had ever touched my dick and Kevin just jerked
me off.
That's the first time anybody had ever had sex.
Is this real?
Is this a true story?
Yeah.
This is a meme.
We're getting memed.
I'm not meming on you.
So what happened?
I was taking a piss.
Did you?
Did you jerk off a guy?
He's doing a fucking fake story because he's insecure because he's still a virgin.
So after getting my dick jerked off by Kevin, I got the motivation to get revenge on Terrell.
So I went into class and I picked up my fucking chair and I smashed it against the back of
his head.
Instantly expelled.
I got arrested.
Fast forward.
Ten years later, I'm a 24 year old gangbanger.
What story is this?
He's quoting some story.
What fucking story is this from?
I get a phone call from Kevin.
Is this a plot of moonlight?
Is that what's happening here?
This guy must have seen moonlight.
It's funny.
So Kevin calls me and he's like, you're little.
And he's still going anyway.
He's still going.
The fucking jig is up.
I was like, you know what?
I'll go see what's going on with Kevin.
You know, maybe he'll be arrested.
I'm now a big, muscly black man.
So I got arrested.
From the beginning, I almost said at the start of the story, when you said Tyrell, I was
going to joke.
That doesn't sound like a white person's name.
And then I was like, well, I didn't want to bring race into it or anything.
Well, no, I thought it would be funny.
But then I remembered that monkey told me that he didn't really grow up with any black
people.
So I thought, and that he definitely would have mentioned if the guy had been black.
So then I was like, well, maybe it's a white guy.
Everyone's going to think I'm racist.
Please don't interrupt the story.
He's still telling the story.
What else would happen, monkey?
So yeah, I go to Kevin's restaurant.
He cooks me dinner and he has a wife and kids now and stuff.
Kevin's restaurant called Kevin's dog house by chance.
Oh my God.
But he was my dog.
That's what we called it.
That's anyway, how my story ends is he takes me back to his house and we have like this
really weird, awkward like moment and then it just cuts to black and we don't know what
happened.
Man, that story was worth the best picture.
I would have given it to La La Land, I think.
See, that's my story.
Thank you.
If not for the fact and none of it would have happened if Ben St hadn't approached the stranger
monkey in the sand, we never would have figured out what that was if not for the fact that
I've listened to monkeys podcast about moonlight.
That's the only reason I was able to pick up on it.
Well, this has been a great waste of time.
I don't suppose we're ever going to get the monkey loses his virginity.
No, that's what happened.
That's what happened.
Davoo, do you want to tell your story?
Who do we have left?
We've got Davoo and just Davoo.
That's it.
That's just Davoo.
Oh man, this is fucking fresh.
This is fucking fresh.
First of all, I'm going to be coughing during this so I'm going to have to keep muting my
microphone.
I have some tea coming up in like a couple of minutes.
I'm going to get that tea.
It'll suppress the coughing some.
But yeah, this is going to be a bit disjointed, okay?
In fact, I'm going to do a small cough right now.
Okay, I'm back.
Okay, cool.
You know that'll still be on the recording.
No, no, no.
I didn't mute it on Discord.
It's way funnier than it was cut out.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm a professional.
Holy shit, that was hilarious.
Okay, all right.
So I should begin this by saying that I've never been like particularly outstandingly
interested in sex specifically.
I'm not exactly sure why, but I've been much more of a fetish person, I guess.
I kind of grew up on Deviantart kind of thing, right?
Like, I mean, I started jacking off when I was like 11 or 12, I think, but it was like
when I was 19 when I had this moment of, man, you know what would be really good to fuck
a girl?
Yeah, man, I should really like do that.
So I mean, I guess maybe part of the reason why I was like that is I was raised all Christian
and stuff.
So I was just sort of like in a Christian environment where like all the girls around me, you're
not going to have sex with.
I'm sure like the really cool ones are all like, you know, getting it like in some sort
of sub zones away from the eyes of all parents and all pastors and shit.
I didn't know, I wasn't nearly on that level of cool.
So, you know, this isn't, this isn't a criticism on you at all, but it's interesting that like
the Christianity kind of suppression of sexuality seems to have the result of kind of pushing
you to the fringes to be into more, you know, outsider.
Absolutely.
Yes.
Without question.
Well, I mean, I assume that's why I'm like that.
I don't know.
It's kind of strange.
It's like growing up, not having anything close to sex, like I hugged a girl once, that
was the extent of it when I was 15.
Yeah.
But it was never like me feeling bad about myself because there wasn't this sense that
anyone else.
It's like not feeling like you're poor because you live in some shitty third world nation.
You weren't watching the high fives like Jesse was.
That's the stuff, man.
I have sex with girls to get to the hugging.
That's what I value.
That's what I look for.
Yeah.
Me too.
It's like fucking good.
That's what they called me.
You know, back in my college days, good old desperate for an emotional connection.
Jess.
Yeah.
Desperate.
I need a hug.
Yeah.
That's the one.
Holy fuck.
Yeah.
Like, you know, I've always, I've always wanted a girlfriend for emotional connection so
I can hug something and also so I can do all the kinky stuff with it.
I've bought a lot of pillows to help with that.
You know.
I recommend it.
Yeah.
So, you know, but again, it's just like the idea of getting a girlfriend in the environment
I was in would be a huge pain.
Like, you know, my parents have a pretty like free form approach to parenting in a way where
it's like, if you can make your own lifestyle happen, then you can do it.
So basically, if I was willing to like completely upend my like shut in lifestyle and like obtain
social gatherings outside of the purview of my parents over the course of years, I probably
could have gotten laid like when I was like, you know, 17 or something.
I mean, I am pretty forward with girls, but probably in more of a holding up a sign saying
have sex with me sort of way.
So maybe not in a successful way, but I don't know Christian method, but I mean, I got like
a couple of girls who are like, I like you and I got a girl to hug me and who was going
to like go mini golfing with me.
But like, this is the hottest story, this is the hottest one yet.
Yeah.
But like the girl who was going to go mini golfing with me who I hugged, she was like
too nervous, right?
This is the league that I'm dealing with.
Like she was too nervous to do something as steamy as go mini golfing with me.
You know, like that this was just the kind of girls I was surrounded with or at least
the kind that are attracted to me.
So yeah, you know, so it was just and then after that, you know, after I'm out of high
school and stuff or rather high home school, you know, the first job I get and the only
close to regular job I've ever gotten was just working in my family business.
So once again, my dad and my brother are around all the time and the only people we interact
with are our customers who hire window cleaners and they're all in their 60s.
So you know, that's not going to work.
So I doubt many millennials are hiring window cleaners.
Indeed.
Yeah.
So yeah, we just have an app for windows now.
So what we so yeah, so I go through sort of like the end of my adolescence also just
in this like environment of not having anyone around.
I do have I did have two friends who I hang out with like once a week, every week, both
were female.
Neither were like interested in me and I wasn't particularly interested in them.
But I was around estrogen all the time.
So it kind of like kept me kept it in my mind.
I was like, yeah, you know, I really need to get out there.
But like how I don't have a huffing you were huffing the fumes of estrogen in the air.
Hold on.
Let me let me go get my tea.
Getting from the bleeding pus of all the surrounding dude, I fucking vape estrogen.
I'm way.
I get my tea.
Okay.
We'll do.
You know, let's talk about this phenomenon.
Let's talk about this phenomenon of being around girls because I find it not at all satisfying
and mostly infuriating that I'm not having sex with them.
If you're if you're not having sex, then being around girls is infuriating and frustrating.
I wouldn't know.
I've never done it.
Speaking of which, I'm I'm recording this from my girlfriend's house right now.
And when this podcast is done, when this podcast is done, I'm going to go lose even more of
my virginity.
Oh, that's not okay, dude.
That's not okay.
That's been in the corner.
That's been in the spotlight.
Losing his virginity.
Trying to keep a few.
It's it's been five minutes.
So it's not a sudden it's not a sudden one year and it's back.
It's a slow tick up to 100% virginity over the course of a year.
Yeah, like Bob Psycho, but it's but it's an exponential growth.
So like halfway through the year, you're 25% back to being a virgin like that, like that.
You know, it's funny.
We had that argument earlier about approaching girls.
Yeah, I remember I have approached girls and had sex with them who were strangers.
They're completely a hypocrite.
It's good.
It's good shit when it works out, right?
And I think as long as everyone's cool about it and the guy and like, like you, I think
you can approach a girl and not be weird or pushy.
And I think that I had a highly condone that I'm still against it morally.
But Jess, if they weren't YouTube stars, how did you know to ask him out?
I'm back by the way.
I don't understand the question.
Okay, let's continue to your argument with a single rhetorical question.
Go ahead, Davoo.
Yeah, you know, it was it was tricky.
It's like how exactly I'm going to have sex.
Like I have a lot of space in my room, but it's not like quiet.
Like there's not that much like audio suppression.
So like people could hear what's going on.
So it's like, who would I bring home?
Like I don't have any like public social life.
So it's like, who am I going to show up to my house?
Who I've been like, it's just like tricky, right?
I was trying here and there, but like tricky, tricky, tricky, tricky.
I don't know about you, dude, I want them to hear.
I want them to hear my grunts and my slap sounds and my the dripping of my
leavings as I as I abandoned this corpse on my bed.
In the middle of sex, is that what's happening?
That's not all fluids are being released.
Let's not gloss over this corpse angle that emerged.
No, no, the thing I look for in a girls, the more people I have living
in my house, the louder I want her to be.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
And well, so, you know, you know, when I then in September of last year
moved into this house, it's like, hey, my parents do not know what I'm doing at all.
I could like go to the airport.
Did you could drive me to the airport and I could go anywhere now.
My parents don't got to know shit about fuck.
So now now there's no limitations, really, as long as I can show out the money.
So I just, you know, I was going to dating websites again.
And I discovered one for a very specific fetish of mine, and it's like sweet.
And I looked at the profiles here and it's like the number of incredibly
attractive girls who are who describe themselves in a way that is so perfect
to me in regards to their kinks.
I was like, where where are these people been all my life?
They're just all here.
And this website is particularly scammy with its paid membership thing, right?
Where without a membership, you can't message anyone, right?
You can't even read the messages from other people, right?
For a like $15 a month membership, you can send messages to other people.
Don't worry, this is very important, right?
You can send messages to other people, but they can't read them
unless they are also a $15.
Yeah, so like the silver membership, right?
But there's like a $80 for three months membership, which is the gold fine.
But if you get a gold
membership, which is expensive as hell, you can message people and they can read
it even if they aren't a member at all, even if they don't have a membership at all.
And I was like, aha.
And I was like, you know, there's just so many good profiles on this website.
I'm going to go with the forest.
So I sank 80 bucks, right?
And I'm like, well, I got three months.
I better message everybody.
No woman is worth that.
I get the impression this whole story is going to be very expensive.
Hey, man, you got to do what you got to do in today's fucking economy.
All right, I mean, I spent 400 something for that round trip to Montana.
That's the road with that.
Mine was an expensive story already.
Fucking and it had exactly the effect I thought it would have, which is that
when there's that huge of a paywall, the number of people actually writing
messages is pretty small, right?
Sure, which meant like an actual, like perceptible percentage of girls
replied to me like one out of every five.
And I was like, holy shit, this is exactly what I paid for.
Right? Because the girls on this website are not being bombarded with emails.
Like they are everywhere else, right?
The system works.
Right. So like I was like, yeah, this this is scammy as hell, but it works.
Right. So eventually I got a girl that way.
And like very forward, very fast paced, like the like a few hours
into our first conversation on a Facebook audio chat.
She's like, yeah, great, we're great matches.
What do you want to do about it?
You know, I'm like, oh, yeah.
Yeah, you're feeling lucky punk.
I kind of took a while, but eventually, you know, I flew over to her at this point.
She's just like a wreck waiting for me.
And incidentally, like she was like a car wreck afterward.
She doesn't have a home situation.
Her house is really tiny and packed.
So we're like, oh, we can't be there.
So in addition to a plane ticket to Oregon, by the way, the actual opposite
end of the country, well, OK, the actual opposite would be Alaska or I guess Indonesia.
But anyway, fucking in addition to that, I also paid for a hotel.
So like a lot of my money.
Well, OK, most of my money.
But hey, it's it's it's to a good cause, right?
So lose your virginity.
No price to high.
It's got to be done.
Yeah, the first time the first time special.
Every time after that, you start to come.
Your nose grows longer and longer.
And your care gets curlier and curlier.
What? I don't know what you're getting at.
David's symbol starts emblazoning itself on your chest.
Oh, God. Yeah, you become more of a juice, what I'm saying.
Well, I thought it was funny, did you?
Thank you. Thank you.
So, yeah, that's that's I flew over to her.
But yeah, it's in a little hotel, you know, it's it's smaller than it looks.
This is how I learned that all those like travel websites use
like wide angle lenses for the interiors.
So it was a really small room and we go in there and she's just immediate
because we've been like, you know, just hugging and like smooching each other's
cheeks for like, you know, for like a whole hour now, like in preparation to get there.
So at this point, she's like, let's fuck, come on, let's do it.
Just go, just go.
I'm like, no, I was like, no, babe, we're going to.
No, babe, no, babe.
Come on, we're going to do hand stuff and eventually we're going to go.
And she's like, no, come on, just come on, just fuck me.
Come on. And she's just like, she's just pushing me towards the bed.
I'm like, oh, fine, whatever, you know,
she was like, I was like, it was like fucking pulling teeth in there.
You know, you know, that's pretty fucking alpha.
Davoo be like, oh, whatever, I guess, I guess I'll fuck you.
If you I guess I'll lose my virginity if I must.
That's hardcore. I like that. I like that.
I mean, later, like a couple of days ago, she called me and was like,
I wish we'd taken it slower.
And I said, oh, you wish you.
Oh, fuck off.
And she's like, yeah, and I'm like, yep, I'm always right.
Well, Davoo, how does she feel about having been absorbed?
And then being right, she's more satisfying than the sex.
Nate, what did you say?
I said, how does she feel about having been absorbed into the Davoo collective
to be, you know, to combine her essence?
So, you know, I mean, like she had sex before, but only like once.
So, you know, fucking she's a member of a few collectives at this point.
She is like four years younger than me.
It's like she's like, she's going to turn 19 tomorrow.
So it's like, you know, sex with the young hashtag, of course.
But like she wasn't like really experienced at all.
But like I was just like, I don't I don't fucking know.
And I had the same issue that did you described, which is
it just wasn't enough pressure to like, like really like get much of a thing going on.
And I should probably bring up at this.
Ladies, do your kegels, steer kegels, ladies out there.
Yeah, she was also on her period, too.
What an issue. Yeah.
That's that's an or flight timing or planning.
Because, well, what can you do?
You can't regulate. You can't schedule your life around that shit.
You could. You could.
I absolutely could have. I absolutely would have.
She had told me that it was an irregular schedule, right?
And it is. But she said, yeah, but it is toward the end of the month.
And I was aware that when you'd scheduled it at the end of the month,
it was probably likely, but I was just so desperate to get you here as soon as possible.
Why do women choose to make life so difficult for everyone else?
By having periods.
And as the days went on, she had already been going for like three days
by the time I got there, but for whatever reason,
she had like this extra long one that lasted the entire time I was there.
That was God trying to stop you, but you've defeated him.
You didn't let it. He killed God.
You killed God with your mighty God.
It pretty much didn't allow sex to happen for the most part.
We only liked it like a few times.
Hey, you got it once, dude. That's enough.
I made her go a couple of times.
She didn't make me make me go a couple of times
because it was just so hard for me to get into the mood to do it
because I was too squeamish about it.
You know, I didn't want to make me stay in a couple of things.
The funny thing about that, like the second time I went to visit
my my ex at the time, like she she was on her period.
And like I didn't like she didn't like just say that outright
that that's why she wouldn't because like it took like two days
before I could convince her to have sex with me.
It was driving me fucking insane.
Like I was like flipping the I was like flipping.
So that's why it's happening.
Why isn't she was just like, but I'm on my period.
And I'm like, I don't care.
Why would I care?
She was like, it's gross.
I was like, I don't I don't fucking care.
You can run your blood all over my body.
I don't give a fuck.
I feel I just want to put my dick in my body.
It's just, you know, there's sheets everywhere, which, you know,
it was doable because related to the kings we were participating in.
We had those bed pads you have for a bedwetting purposes.
So you just put some of those down there on the bed on the mattress.
That makes it pretty fine.
But still there was just one time you fucking you don't.
You don't have to explain what your fetishes are,
but did you at least get to indulge them in this trip?
Yes, but not a whole lot.
Like it was OK.
It was it's funny.
You got to confirm whether or not you were like like
because I feel like with with weird fetishes and stuff,
you always like you you you expect that you're going to be into it.
But then it's not until it actually happens that you're completely sure.
You're like, yes, I've confirmed now I was as into this as I thought.
It's really difficult because your period
and interferes with the fetishes.
It just interferes with everything.
And like it was just, you know, it was just a different sort of situation
where it's like I felt weirdly less horny than usual there
because it's like I'm meeting a new person.
Well, I mean, not physically new to me.
I'm in a new environment and I was really more just interested
in hugging her constantly because I hadn't had someone to hug before.
And it was just nice.
It was just nice and fun, you know.
Yeah, I by the way, I think a lot of a lot of fetishes are
exists a lot more in the people's minds than actually performing them.
You know, like a lot of them are the fantasy of it.
I'm not saying that's necessarily you.
I'm just saying that in general, I'm sure there's a lot of people
who aren't actually into scat as much as like the porn they like to look at.
Right. Right. Yeah.
I don't know. I mean, for example, for example.
Right. For example.
Right. Yeah. That's not mine.
But like, well, not exactly.
But like, yeah, as I said before, I'm more into like a concept type of thing.
So it's more it's not as much about the physicality.
It's more about the idea of what's happening.
Like, like, by far, the best, the best, the best day that we had was toward the end.
When we went out and we ubered around town and she had a sippy cup
and she acted like she was like low functioning autistic.
And I was like talking to her all condescendingly.
That was like the best day.
An ice cream when we get to her ice cream.
I was like, here you go.
And I was like, fucking yes.
Great time. What the fuck?
See, it's not so much about coming.
It's about having it's about having fun experiences of life
where you fuck with the definitions of society in ways that no one knows about.
I get it. I do get it.
Yeah. So I mean, yeah.
So like.
So yeah, we didn't we didn't do a whole lot of I mean,
like she was never once able to make me come in any way, like directly.
Like she couldn't even jack me off.
She doesn't she doesn't have she doesn't have the fucking endurance.
Like her arm just isn't capable of doing it.
Like, you know, I had a as I will say, I mean, I've only been with one woman,
but she was completely incompetent at the act of jacking my dick.
I literally like, you know, they don't have the kind of she like wanted to.
And she kept trying.
And I was just like, stop it.
You don't know what the fuck you're doing.
I mean, for what it's worth like there was a time
where I was trying to check her off with a little thing of a jig.
And like my fingers were like we're like we're like splitting out
because they weren't leveled up in the regards of the finger pushing.
But I was able to do finger basically.
She was way more horny than me the whole time, you know, that that's understandable.
OK, but yeah, I had a great time, just not a whole lot of sex.
So I didn't once come in her at all.
But, you know, we have plenty of we're going to we're going to see each other
again somehow sometime, preferably soon.
So yeah, the most important thing is we had a great time even if it's a complete cluster fuck.
Like it doesn't matter if this is a skill to be learned anyway.
So nothing is totally reasonable.
I had a terrible time.
I guess that's it. Yeah, nightmare.
Yeah, well, that's all about fetishes yet,
because I want to hear about this low functioning autism shit.
No, but we should talk about that.
So we had a porn episode and Davoo wouldn't come on
because he didn't want to talk about these ones.
That's right. Well, I just felt like it would it's not that I didn't want to talk about it.
It's just that I felt like it would be too far along for anyone to be able to like deal with.
Like you would be like, yeah, you're not like on a level where like I can care anymore.
But I don't know. I as time has gone on,
I've I've witnessed the extent to which Pete the other PCP people and the viewers are
are like surprisingly similar to me.
So I might change my mind. I don't know.
Yeah, that's fair. That's fair.
Yeah, I'd fuck a retard.
I think it is a it is legitimately offensive to me that people think that retards wouldn't also enjoy sex.
That body in a minute.
How are we allowed are we talking?
We're talking full retarded.
Just just just pick your Nate. Just pick your Nate.
As a retarded man, Nate is offended on behalf of his people.
It's a well-known thing that that that like the first thing babies do and you know people with low IQs are like babies.
They'll dintle themselves. They'll play with themselves. They fuck with their junk.
So why don't they why doesn't society allow me to play with retarded people's junk?
I thought you were gonna say to play. I thought you were gonna say that.
I thought you were gonna say to play with direction. I thought you were gonna say to play with babies junk.
I don't I totally change directions in the middle of that, but hey, whatever.
Yes, I want to have sex with retarded people. That's what I'm trying to say.
All right, let's move on to the questions.
Okay, let's do it.
I just want to say did she when you were telling your story and when you were trying to do the impression of how your girlfriend couldn't pronounce that phrase.
I thought she was retarded.
No, she I think she I mean she just was stumbling.
I think she was like playing up the fact that she could pronounce it.
She was holding me down.
Yeah, she while she's playing it up weird like the fact that she couldn't pronounce the word because she like like I
Think she's like she's pretending to be dumb so that you'll explain it to you know
It's like exactly like the old saying goes
I would never want to sleep with a woman retarded enough to sleep with me
Very she was something very like redneck mentality about like intelligence, which is like I'm a simple kind of person
I don't want to know these more advanced things. Okay, but then what's attractive about me is that I sound smart and cool
I don't know. It's it's an odd combination
So sure you're kind of like a fetish the intelligence is like a fetish. She's a savioresexual. Yeah
Yeah, there you go. I don't think she's like exclusively into smart guys or anything
It's just particularly appealing about me is that I use big words and have a good voice, you know, so
Mm-hmm
Okay, all right look for the love of God, let's move on
Our first question here comes from our good friend at the hypocrite
Will I ever get a girlfriend sad face? Yes. Yes, you will
This is the public service announcement everyone get out there and date
I'm not
If you happen to live in England or France
Then and you and you think hippos adorable go suck his dick
Yeah
Circle don't talk to him. We already found totally we already found PCP guys. So now our next bouncy is
If you want if you want a prize a PCP prize just like in last yeah, you'll get a shout out on the show probably from
I
Should be a
Patreon that should be a patreon reward. Yeah, no cuz that's gonna make it harder for it to happen
But we want it should be given away for free on every street corner. We should be throwing it is his innocence
You know that there's just yeah, there's there's some I think there's a real psychological incentive
If you have to pay for something you you want it more so maybe we could set up some reward system
All right, whatever give us a great guy. I love him more than anyone especially Ben
I
Just say his girlfriend hippo's hippo's short, but he's got big hands and big feet. So that's true big dick
You know, you know what they say about guys with big hands you can trust them
That's right. They're capable men at physical labor. Okay. What else we got going on. Is that a joke from Trump?
It's a joke from Marco Rubio. Yeah. Yeah, Marco Rubio
Yeah, you know what they say about guys with little hands you can't trust them
Yeah, and if there's any
If there's any young girls in it, there's any sex with the young kind of girls in the audience, you know
Is that still on this out there? I have a really comfortable new bed and I'm not fucking someone on it by the end of this podcast
I'm gonna shoot up a hospital
Do you want that on your conscience ladies?
You had the power to stop this. I need that sex with the younger people will die. I'm a man of my word
I'm a man of my word
Okay, here we go. And if you're 12 my buddy King Critic is looking. Oh, yeah
There's a guy we should get on here for the sex with the young episode
There's like a there's like a hierarchy of what everyone's looking for like 12 15 King Critic 15 to 18 endless Jess
18 to to the London hippo
If you if you like look like you're like
14 but you're actually like 90 then that's where I come in
Yeah, I want I want footage of this event happening to the two anarchy in the UK playing in the background
All right, okay
All right, here we go at Cybershell asks this is a question. I think it's cool
I don't know if you guys have seen this but what do you think about lasagna cats?
And why is it the greatest web series of all time top kek?
It's the greatest. It's fucking it's it's taking you know
It's taking it's taking the shit that is Garfield and just and just out
It's like that scene. It's like that scene in the holy mountain where where Christ shits into the into the bucket
And the guy alchemizes it into gold. That's what they've done with Garfield into lasagna cat. That's right
None of the rest of us have seen the holy mountain. Well, what the fuck?
To the glory that is Garfield
Comic of all time and how dare they mock it in such a fashion
I haven't seen the new ones, but I won't out of principle. Let me let me just say
Garfield for anybody who isn't familiar there was this series that came out like ten years ago and stopped nine years ago called
You know lasagna cat which just takes like comic strips of the of old Garfield
It's it takes like the worst and most banal
Garfield strips that there are and then enacts them with guys in like in like fucking
What do you call them like fur suits basically first suits basically? Yeah, and and then they enact the strip with like this overblown
Laugh track to it, and then they take what they've just done and they fucking cut it into like this fucking spicy ass music video
And like they fucking just
jam out to this shit
And and sometimes it just dissolves into absolute mania. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I feel like I'm having a fever
Suicide is painless
It brings on many changes, and I can take
Oh
I was just gonna say and the series came back
Miraculously nine years later out of nowhere. I'm just dumped like I'm when he episodes
I'm stunned, and I have to go watch it soon. You watch them
Oh god the the things they've done with this phone bank like the newest episode fucking insane anyway
Go check it out everybody watch this on the episode where
Odie is wearing a bag on his head. That's my favorite one. I can't remember which one that is but they're all watch them
All guys and he goes to heaven and then he gets get sent to hell
My my personal favorite is the bilamos which is just like a Garfield dancing to spicy
Fucky Ricky by legato by legato. No, no, no, sir
All right, this is this is a fascinating question. Okay, this is a bad question that ruined the whole party
Yes, okay, but this one's great, and this one's really got okay. Just think about this. Okay at out sin asks
Okay, what's this fucking question? What's the worst case scenario for each of the PCP?
And that's it. What's the worst case like what I'm just thinking about
That is the ability skin ripped off one chunk at a time that I die that I die in any fashion ever is the worst case
Scenario best part about that. It's 100% guaranteed to happen
Finally getting my consciousness put into a computer and becoming immortal except it turns out that it's just torture for all time
I have no mouth, and I must scream that that story. That's the worst case scenario for any of us. That's pretty good
That's a pretty good answer. My worst scenario is just normal immortality in my normal body
Yeah, cuz you love for death. You love for that. Yeah, okay. I'm with you
My worst case scenario is all the all the innocent children at the hospital who are gonna die if I'm not having sex with the young
By the end of this podcast. It's still a thing. That's really gonna happen. I've got my gun
We're on a timer now. I've got like five minutes. I've got my fucking my my ninja daggers
I've got sure kids. I'll kill children with shurikens
I've borrowed. I borrowed some ninja stuff from Shinobi. You know, it's you know, it's really sad
You know, what's really sad is this podcast isn't gonna go up for a while
So by the time it goes up, it's gonna be too late. Those kids are done. Those kids are gone already
It's a shame
My worst case scenario is if I have cavities right now because it might just be weird standing on my teeth
Which is what I thought it was but now I'm like, oh, it might be cavities. I've never had cavities before
It's been a it's been an issue. It's been a matter of pride for me
And my cousin once told me many years ago. Don't get cocky with your perfect teeth
I first got a cavity when I was 22
Well, I'm 22 and I might have cavities and that I I just don't like being wrong
So that's the worst case scenario for me
Fucking I might have another cavity and it might be taking my tally up to literally 30
Well, you know the best way to not get cavities is to never go out of the dentist
Yep, yep, I think you should read the question by monkey Jones. I think now's the time is that was that from the very start of this thing
Let me scroll back up
Okay, here we go. Oh, that that is a good one. Okay at monkey Jones asks opinion on kicking Ben out of the PCP
Well, I think we just made our case pretty eloquently just I vote for I vote pro
Pro, let's do it. All right
I believe we were once talking about the idea of making the PCP more like zoom where it's a rotating cast of young people
We're like once you turn 30 you're out and it's only 20. Oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, and then and then you know, I'll I'll have to go inform my own PCP with blackjack and hookers
And then Tom and Jess will will come along shortly. I hope if they'll have me
Okay, let's do one more because this is a topical question
I'm just I'm curious what you guys would say so at spacko 306 who's actually making a bunch of cool PCP gifts
Keep making those dude. They're they amuse me any thoughts on the Nintendo switch and or the new Zelda you're gonna buy one or not
No, I don't I hate video games. Okay, gotcha
Okay, I have a very very thorough thought which is that I was watching Vic play breath of the wild on the
Broke college students edition the Wii U version and he was like in a little shack
It was like a worn-down check was only a couple of beams of wood here in there
You know and there was just like one like like wall of wooden planks
That was like, you know a few inches higher than links head
And he walked up to that wall and pushed some button and jumped over the wall
And I didn't think he was gonna be able to jump over the wall and I was like, oh, I'm convinced this is a 10 out of 10
Well, I'm not convinced but I do want to play it. Well, I did buy breath of the wild
But I bought the Wii U version for poor people. Mm-hmm. I haven't played it yet
But it's yeah, I mean poor people have a fucking Wii U
about I
Think monkeys say he's too poor to even have a Wii U. Oh, shut up, mom. You've got all that fucking book money you little bitch
One home month a rent, baby
I am going to actually buy a switch just because it looks cool
And I want the games that are coming and I don't have a Wii U
So if I want to play Zelda I got no fucking choice, so I'm gonna get one
They got you by the balls on this one. They do by the balls
All right, and there was another question about why all the questions doing it guys
So they're doing it. I'm having sex with the young here in the past. All those children saved. Yes, it's a miracle
It's a miracle. Asian wife. Yeah
You all saved the children you saved the children's hospital
Thank God for that girl. I'm so proud of us
Yeah, we really did it. We really this was a this was a wonderful arc that we've journeyed on throughout this
Podcast
Yeah, we're done. All right. Thank God everybody. Whoo. That was an exhaust everybody say goodbye