10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1
EVERYONE CAN BE SO D meal
EVERYONE CAN BE SO D
GASP
MEMBER SEMUM
MEMBERS
GASP
Hello, my honey, hello, my ragtime girl.
Are you the WB frog?
Because that's what I picked.
No, that's not his name.
His name is, oh no, he's got a name.
Let me quickly Google Hat Frogs to find out what's his name.
Homestuck, Munchie.
Oh no, it's Pepe, it's a Naga Hat.
Michigan J Frog.
Yeah.
What?
Hmm, okay.
Is that real?
Yeah, it's real.
It sounds ridiculous.
Michigan as a name, huh?
I wonder if the J stands for anything.
I'm going to guess that it's Jones because he was created
by Chuck Jones, but that's pure speculation.
Wow, what a character.
What a powerhouse.
He made that up.
Well.
Oh god.
I'm just overcome with love for Michigan J Frog in this machine.
He's a maverick, you know?
He's out there living his dream every single day,
and who in their right mind would stand in his way?
Michigan, Michigan.
Cursed with that forbidden name, unfortunately,
but other than that.
It's all gravy for him.
Anyway, it's 2018, guys.
What?
This is important, shut up, the topic of his podcast.
This is the Michigan J Frog podcast.
In a clip from a DVD special, Jones
stated that he had come up with the name Michigan Frog
during the 1970s and was inspired to add the J
as a middle initial while being interviewed
by a writer named Jay Cox.
Jay Cox.
He was thinking Cox would be a weird one.
So now I'm in question.
Now, does the J stand for Jay as in Jay Cox?
I mean, probably.
Like J-A-Y?
Just like Homer Simpson.
Homer Simpson's middle name is J-A-Y.
Oh, dude, they're related somehow.
They're related just like Monkey D. Luffy and Goldy Roger.
Well, pretty much.
The J. The J is the destiny.
Imagine if the D, it was just D-E-E for all that time.
Dude, Michigan J Frog is a special person.
He's got the will of J.
What if a straw hat land takes place in the same world
as Kirby in the distant future where
King Dedede's descendants have all propagated and spread
throughout the land to overthrow the kingdom of heaven
started by the corrupt.
Wait a minute.
Original founder is Kirby.
That's the last you'll freak.
But wait.
King Dedede is an earth elemental lord of the dancing.
He will see his empire toppled.
And Dedede, in order to make offspring,
effect the year 2018.
So back on topic.
Now that it's legal.
King Dedede.
In Ohio, where I live, 16 is legal.
So just saying.
But in the UK, 16 is legal.
Now I know why you guys live there.
I didn't think of that joke in 2016, but you know.
Did you ever see that meme that's like the Shaq euphoria meme?
Something like, I don't know, Massachusetts,
Age of Consent 18, Midwest, Age of Consent 16, Japan,
Age of Consent 14 or 12.
And then I think it was like Saudi Arabia,
Age of Consent, none.
And it's just like exploding eyes.
It was one of those Middle Eastern states.
I don't mean to insult the good people of Saudi Arabia,
if I'm incorrect.
But anyway, here we are talking Middle Eastern politics.
On today's episode of the Procrastination Podcast.
Wait, I'm going to say I'm going to fucking be racist.
I got beef to pick with Saudi Arabia.
I strongly object to its people and culture.
And our oil prices, they're surging.
Please stop.
No.
Let me tell you why.
It's because I've met a couple of Saudi Arabians in my life.
And they've all been rich assholes
because they have government grants to go abroad
and be rich in another country.
So I'm sure not everyone is like that, but just the ones
that I've been like that.
Yeah, they have a literal aristocracy,
as I understand it, in Saudi Arabia.
Yeah, I'm sure the ones you run into in America
are mostly the rich ones that are like government connected
or whatever.
Indeed.
They're like Dubai, though.
I mean, that's the United Arab Emirates separate.
That's like a literal future.
OK, anyway, it is 2018, guys.
And we're here to talk about our plans for 2018.
Starting the year off with some good old fashioned racism.
It wouldn't be a PCP if we didn't have a little bit of that
mixed in.
Oh, don't say that word.
Don't say mixed here.
Oh, no.
We'll have none of that.
All right, our first goal of 2018
is to help our bro, Richard Spencer,
start the ethno state clearly.
It's time.
The time is upon us.
But really, our first goal is to define what even is 2018.
What could this creature be?
So just for perspective, I went ahead
and we've got our friends at Urban Dictionary
have a definition of 2017 for us.
Oh, you're going to like this one, fellow Redditors.
2017, the struggle for humanity.
Embarrassing, embarrassing.
OK, so that's what we've left behind.
Wait, all right, here's one thing.
I just got to say this.
I don't remember 2017 being bad at all.
I can't remember what happened.
But Donald Trump was president.
He was president at the end of 2016, wasn't he?
Only for a little.
Only for a little bit.
He was elected in 2016.
He was inaugurated in January.
This has been his year.
2017 has such highlights as the release
of our favorite video game, Undertale.
And many other excellent animes.
I just am not understanding the, like, oh my god, 2017.
Will you survive?
Like, what?
Nothing happened.
All to do with the Trump stuff, I'm pretty sure.
It was no 2016.
Like, 2016 was a real shit.
Everybody died that was cool.
That was a bad year.
I fucking died.
That sucked.
Wait, this year?
No, that was 2016.
Yeah.
He died.
God, I can't believe it.
It feels like it was 2016, like, a week ago.
Yeah, exactly.
2017 is exactly not a half-wall.
Because we're closing it on 30.
So our perception of time is beginning to speed up.
Soon it's going to be, I feel that,
decades are going to be a week ago.
Oh, boy.
And we're just going to, like, jeez, Christ.
I better start some, like, Buddhist meditation or something.
That's a good idea.
So here's our definition of 2018 that we'll
be working off of for the rest of this.
I'm sure we will.
Something I hope won't be shit.
Thank you, fellow Redditors.
God.
Tipping my cap to you on my way.
In this trooper's opinion, 2018 is gay.
Let's just go on and define 2018.
Oh, I thought I saw a comic by our good friend Shen Comics.
And if I know anything, 2018 is a very buff naked man
who has a JoJo's-inspired outfit on,
ready to beat the shit out of you.
Is that the Shen Comics?
Is that Bike Cuck?
No, that's Altered.
Altered, the worst comedy game of all time.
No, they're the same thing.
Altered is Shen Comics.
Yeah, yeah, that's OK.
His handle.
OK, there you go.
So, yeah.
Oh, Bike Cuck.
Dude, he totally redeemed himself, though.
He's definitely making some strides.
Every now and then, I see one.
He memed, did you see how he memed on himself
when that new trial they got repealed?
It was fucking brilliant.
I think so, but I can't remember.
What was it again?
He did the exact same comic, but it was like,
net neutrality got repealed.
I'm pretty sad about it.
But then again, maybe the people who repealed him
were having, then he just pops out of a port.
He's like, no, fuck you.
And just beats this shit out of himself.
Like, yeah.
OK.
That was a good way to meme on yourself.
Yeah, I remember appreciating that.
I appreciated that.
You know, I've been seeing these comics on Twitter lately.
They have some generic name.
And they're just drawn as blobs.
And it's like the most generic sentiment.
God, I think it's called webcomicname.
Yeah, it's webcomicname.com.
OK, I get it.
Oh, is it like a parody of all those people who do nothing?
Yeah.
Oh, that's great.
But at the same time, it still manages
to get like the same message across.
It's like, this latest one is, my life has no meaning.
Maybe the meaning of my life is to make an offspring
with a meaningful life.
And then the baby is like, my life has no meaning.
And the parent is like, oh, no.
Yep.
I really hate that sentiment about, I don't know,
does anybody else feel similar?
This is sort of relevant.
Try like goals for a new year, whatever.
I, whenever I see a parent who like defines their life
by like raising their kid right, it makes me real mad.
Yeah, it's like, if everyone does that, nothing new happens.
It's just the same shit forever.
And I'm, I don't know.
Well, don't you find it weird that like parents would be like,
I'm going to raise my child, right?
But then they raise them with the exact same like values
and goals that they had, which led them nowhere.
So it's just like, you're just pigeonholing your child
into being as MD and vapid as you are.
I've given up on the, on the hope that like,
I'll be a miraculously way better parent than like my parents.
We're like, what are the odds that I'm going to crack
the fucking code and be like a magically perfect parent
who makes the perfect kid?
Highly unlikely.
No, if anyone could do it, it's me.
I'm a gambling man.
I, if I make a kid, I'm going to, I'm going to just go into it
with the, with the idea of like making them into somebody
I can have a conversation with that is not like,
uh, God, this fucking piece of shit.
I'm not going to, you know, this isn't the parents.
Impossible.
Yeah.
There's a generational divide.
So from like, you know, like 13 to like 25,
they're going to hate you.
What I mean, what I mean by that is,
is giving them like the, the tools of like
figuring things out on their own.
So that they can be an interesting person
without doing what I do or like knowing what I know.
I don't know how to explain this,
but I don't want to talk about it.
I don't want to get into it.
Because that's, I'm not going to do it in 2018.
That's for sure.
The best, the best way to, the best thing you can do for a kid.
Give a man a fish, feed him for a day,
teach a man to fish, feed him for a lifetime,
teach a man to catfish, get him economically secure
for the remainder of his existence.
That's relevant somehow, I think.
So what do you guys got for goals?
You got any new year's resolutions,
any hot off the press kind of stuff?
People have been doing that a lot.
People have been doing that a lot around here.
I don't know, I don't really trust them.
I don't really trust them.
Like, I mean, of course I'm a gym guy.
So like every January, the January joiners flood the gym
and it's a nightmare.
Every, every workout guy goes, that's like the worst time.
The January joiners and it's bullshit.
Cause they, cause they flake out.
They flake out.
Cause if you're just, if you're just there, cause like,
yeah, like you're not, you're not gonna stick to it
based on like, oh, I can't let down my new year's resolution.
That principle is what, is what kind of turns me off
of new year's resolutions in general.
Don't get me wrong, any excuse to try to work on something
is an opportunity that maybe this will be the time
that you really stick to it.
And I'm all for that.
But like if your primary motivation is just to stick
to your own desire to stick to your new year's resolution,
to me, sounds like a, a rocky foundation,
but maybe you can build on it.
You know what they should do?
They should, they should have all the gyms in the world
have like a, like a four mile radius all around them.
And with like spikes on the roads that you can't drive
over them, over the border.
And you have to run all the way to the gym
cause there's lines and shit.
So if you manage, if you have like the, the, the tenacity
to run all the way to the gym to do your workout,
then you've proven yourself worthy to be in the gym.
It's like a Pokemon gym because you got to go through
the gym leaders minions before you fight the gym leader.
You got, you got to show that you can beat that diglet
before you can fight against Brock and his mighty Onyx.
That sounds like a dick metaphor if I ever heard one.
I don't know.
A dig, you know, diglet, Onyx, whatever.
Point is, I have no resolutions though.
I have been thinking about like fixing my diet forever.
That's, that's one thing I'd really like to do this year.
And like, here's the thing about me.
Everything that I should be doing, I'm already doing
in terms of finances economically because I recognize
there's no point in waiting.
You just got to do it and don't be a pussy.
But one thing that I am not really doing perfectly
is, is eating exactly as I would like to
for maximizing gains and maximizing health.
Not, not quite enough kidney beans these days
and not enough salads and too many carbs, far too many carbs
as everyone does in America.
Yeah, I want to, I want to knock that shit off.
So that's, that's something I'm kind of keeping.
Carbs, I hate carbs.
I, I've came to a revelation recently.
Yeah, for the last, well, here's the thing.
This is, this is the catch 22 or horrible situation
I'm in with carbohydrates because like you,
I've been trying to improve my diet.
So for the last like couple months from like,
I want to say August to probably the end of October,
I was having migraines all the time.
Like I have, I've had chronic migraines
since I was five years old, but like they were really bad.
Like so bad.
Like I was like, I don't know if this is migraine.
Like it's so much worse.
I went to the hospital like three times.
I was like, there's nothing wrong with you.
Like, you know, like you're fucked up.
And I eventually figured out the reason,
the reason that I was getting all these migraines
was because I wasn't eating enough carbs.
I was trying to lower my carb intake.
And because I wasn't having as many carbs
that like made my headaches worse.
And then I looked it up and like, yeah,
this thing kind of happens.
People have like chronic migraines.
Like you have to like carb load
to keep your headaches away.
I'm like, whoa, I'm totally fucked.
Is that because you're eating far less
than the average person does?
Or because there's something about you
where you need more carbs than the average person?
I'm not sure.
It's interesting because I wasn't,
I wasn't having like no carbs.
I was just like cutting down on it.
And that was enough to like make like something that was like,
I'd get like three or four times a month
to be like three or four times a week.
And like made it impossible to function.
So my own body is deciding to fuck over my resolution
to eat better.
So thanks, thanks biology.
Where's genetic engineering?
Or even better, where's the robot bodies?
We need the cyber brains now, all right.
That indeed, indeed.
Okay, well, does that translate
any kind of resolution for this year?
Any plans for that?
Well, I want to try and find a better balance for that.
And I also want to start exercising a little bit.
I feel like if I go into,
if I turn 30 as a flabby fuck,
I'm just probably just going to kill myself on my birthday.
Just like, can't let it happen.
Can't let it happen.
It's been too long, like I can't.
Okay, the best way to do that is set the date
that you know is the day that you're going to kill yourself
and break up all the time from now to then
into small achievable goals.
And so you can track your progress.
And even if you don't achieve all the way,
you'll have come a long way by then.
And if I don't get all the way,
I'll just like cut off an arm instead of just straight.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Your death will be proportional.
Yeah, consequences.
I'll just like poison myself,
so I'll die in like a few years, you know.
Okay, okay, if I hit it bit,
if I make a million dollars by the time I'm 30,
if I don't make a million dollars by the time I'm 30,
I'm going to kill myself.
But if I make say 500,000,
I'll just start smoking instead.
Yeah, cut off a proportional amount of your life
by engaging in bad activities.
Gabe, were you saying something?
No.
I don't know what this thing is.
I don't know what we're doing.
Are we just saying resolutions?
We're saying things we've got goals for 2018.
I mean, right now we're talking
about New Year's resolutions, basically.
Yeah, cause let me talk about anything here.
Because those are slightly different
in that they feel, even the word,
like it just feels like,
yeah, I'm not actually going to do that,
but I'm saying it.
Do you want to know why?
This is why New Year's resolutions are stupid
and why goals are good.
Because of resolution, you're just like,
oh, I resolved to do something.
This is something I'd like to do.
It's not committal enough.
A goal is when you're just like, okay,
I not only do I have something I've resolved to do,
but I assumedly have some sort of plan in place
to get there.
And so I can make these smaller steps to accomplish it.
That's the difference.
That's why goals are good and resolutions are bullshit.
Because so many people are just like,
they have, you have your resolution,
like the day of like, you know, like December 31st,
like I'm going to go to the gym tomorrow.
And then like that's as far as you planned out.
That's not going to work, dude.
You got to have a system in place
or you're fucking yourself over.
I just, I can't respect someone who says,
I mean, I don't know if theoretically perhaps I could,
but it seems like a big bad mistake to be like,
yeah, on January 1st, I start going to the gym
and it's like, it's like the middle of December.
Like if you really are committed,
you'll start today or maybe tomorrow,
like, I don't know, whatever,
but you'll start now.
You won't wait until then.
That's, you know, it's the way to fucking do it.
That's the way to fucking do it.
I mean, my resolution or rather goal was,
I mentioned it in the last PCP of the questions
when we mentioned like plans and stuff,
but we're going to go more into it here.
I mentioned that I was going to make videos every week
and stuff.
And the reason I was going to start on January the first
was because I had work that I couldn't,
like I had to get done
and that I was stopping me from starting immediately.
So basically my goal was to finish what I had to finish
by the 31st of December,
which I actually on the last day of the year finished.
And I was like, oh, ooh.
And now I can just celebrate for a bit.
And then I actually, January 1st, I did work
and I was working.
And I was working the second day and the third day.
And this whole first week, my plan was,
well, my goals, my, yeah, my plan for 2018
was to make a video every week.
And as of the first week, I have done two videos
and I'm starting the third after I've finished recording this.
So it's going well.
And at the rate I am going, I can imagine,
like one week I can do two videos
and I have four videos per month, basically.
So by June, I should have the whole fucking year,
fucking dumb.
Sick dog.
Yeah, I mean, that's great.
Yeah, I mean, of course, if you are just like,
if you're busy accomplishing other goals
that prevent you from starting until January 1st,
you know, of course.
Yeah, immediately means as soon as it's feasibly possible.
Not like. Indeed, indeed.
You're drowning.
It's time to start working on that video.
You know, if you're not starting right now,
trying to present yourself from drowning,
like I'm pretty sure you're a terrible person.
Drowning in footwear, though.
Oh, well, you know.
Got him.
That's a realm I'm not familiar with, let me say.
That's a level of existence I can't fathom.
Ben, you got any resolutions for 2018?
Tell me them.
I guess, well, on a personal note,
I guess my overall, the thing that I'm aiming
to start doing that I wasn't doing previously in 2018
is start paying my student loans off.
They've been deferred.
Hey, glad to hear it, dude.
Yeah, they've been deferred forever, and that's bad.
I made a big payment on them a couple years ago,
and I'm pretty sure that a bunch of what I paid back then
has grown back to interest, which is very,
not all of it, but yeah, it's very frustrating.
And like, I don't know.
I have been roasting you, Ben, behind your back
for years about these student loans,
just so you know, roasting you like a Christmas goose
you were, and succulent, succulent,
the word I'd use to describe it.
Well, yeah, so I'm gonna do, and like,
I'm not hemorrhaging money anymore, like I once was,
so yeah, I can start doing that,
and I'm sure that will be a smart and I won't regret it.
Our dear departed papa would have been so pleased
to hear this news.
Good, yes.
I'm glad that he'll be happy, and I'm glad that he's dead.
Yeah.
Yeah, sick.
Is he actually dead?
Ben, make the same joke in the drug cast.
No, you ding dong.
That was his ghost.
He drew a picture of his ghost.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't hear from your dad that much.
Is that true?
So, therefore, he must be dead.
A munchie, however, is in close communication
with everyone's dad, and is keeping tabs on all of them.
He's got the big map with all the red strings,
triangulating locations at any given time.
Right, anyway, is that everyone?
Has everyone said, I don't know,
we did resolutions, I do wanna talk about larger goals.
Goals are far more interesting.
Yeah, yeah, I don't know, I guess let's get into it.
Ben just basically said one of his,
but what's your big plan for 2018?
What are you gonna be producing
over the course of this year?
What'll be on the other side?
I have a few things.
My stupid fun little comics that I do
over on APSadventures.workpress.com.
What does that stand for again?
Adobe Photoshop Adventures.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Yeah, I did one during a stream,
like I drew a whole comic, and it was like,
ah, that's fun, I'll do it again.
I did another one, it's not finished yet,
but I wanna do more of that,
but that's obviously time consuming,
and it's fun, but it's not really a product
that I can be like, yeah, I could turn this into a real thing.
So I kinda just, well, I mean, it doesn't look very good,
and I'm not that good at drawing yet.
Just fucking print it as a zine.
Oh, what's that?
It's a zine, dude.
What's a zine?
It's like a cheap fan magazine.
It's like a one man show, sort of thing.
Yeah, you know, that 80s style Xerox grunge kind of aesthetic.
I mean, last year I had this idea
that I would make an album, a book, and something,
maybe a comic.
And a baby this year.
No, no, no, disgraceful.
I'm a baby, baby, it's you, it's you.
I mean, that is something, you know.
Not like making the baby,
but like getting the v-cards punched, that's something.
Yeah, oh, I'll give you a punch, all right.
Just come over to my crib someday.
You'll get that v-card abused heavily.
Yes, but like what I want is I want to continue doing
those comics to the point where I have so much of them
that I can actually release a big old book of them,
like just like Homestuck.
Just like Homestuck is in a funny book,
but it's not as good as like it's looking at it online
because there's so many flash pages and GIFs.
But I bought the Homestuck book and I'm reading it.
I'm like, this will be good to have one of these.
Hey, I've been wondering just about that book.
Ben has the first two Homestuck books,
but I read them, but I can't remember.
No, I don't think I have any Homestuck books,
but I have all the Problem Sleuth books.
Oh, shit. Yeah, those are good.
So like with the GIFs,
with like the high super fast GIFs of Homestuck,
I'm imagining that what Hussie does is on one page,
he puts the first frame, on the next page,
he puts the second, instructions are flip
at extreme speed back and forth between these.
Not actually.
I mean, it's a lot of the layout is kind of like terrible
because you can't accurately show,
because like a lot of the stuff in Homestuck
is like it moves across the screen real fast,
but what is moving across the screen
doesn't look like it's like drawn to be moving.
It's just a thing being dragged like really fast.
So it's like, it's great in motion.
It looks terrible like in what do you call them?
Thumbnails.
It's like with those animation super sleuths,
do you have a frame capture on like one blurred
motion animation or like exposed.
This is a terrible anime, et cetera, et cetera.
Yeah, but yeah, I want to draw a bunch of comics
because those are more fun than trying to write a book.
I might do music as well, I don't know.
Basically what I want to do is I want to get
all hypocrite stuff done.
Hillary was the breakout hit of 2017.
Hillary was a pretty funny one,
but it's not that good to listen to.
And it was made in a day, that whole album.
If I make like, if I do like a month of like
doing a song in a day, that might be actually pretty great.
Yeah, yeah.
So, you know, I just, yeah, I just want to do
creative stuff that I like.
And in order to facilitate that,
I need to get hypocrite stuff done earlier
so that I have months and months where I can just like,
hmm, think about stuff and things.
Yeah, you gotta stick with this school.
My plan is to be creative and facilitate
the ability to be creative.
Respect.
The noblest of goals.
Yeah, that's just a good overarching life goal
to have that informs everything else that you do.
That's basically my life pattern for myself, more or less.
I'm sure you guys as well.
Like everything that I do,
every individual thing that I do
is done with the understanding that like,
this is a good idea, if and only if,
it in some way contributes to like,
that more of my future life will be spent
pursuing my own artistic endeavors.
Yeah, yeah.
And I mean, artistic endeavors, sure,
but I am always very conscious of.
Or just my own endeavors, like doing what I want to do.
Yeah, sure, sure.
I'm just very conscious personally
of I have a baseline economic reality I need to meet.
I need to achieve that.
And once I'm over that,
then I have a lot more flexibility to do whatever I want.
Yeah.
That's how I approach it.
There's really no more like detailed,
I mean, I guess I could go into some details
of like some videos I plan to make.
If you want to.
But I don't know how long I could talk about that for,
because it's just.
You maybe take one that you want to share,
if you do want to share any of them.
Well, I don't mind sharing the ones.
It's basically I want to go over all the hypocrite videos
that were like the first in a series,
like Ratchet and Clank and Jack and Daxter
and Kingdom Hearts and stuff.
And I do the sequels to those.
So I would do GRPJ on Kingdom Hearts 2.
I would do a review of Rayman 2 and Ape Escape 2
and Ratchet and Clank 2 and Jack and Daxter 2.
And it'd just be like, I'm better at videos now.
And here's these popular games that everyone likes
clicking on.
And they'll all be good.
You need to release all those on a Tuesday.
Oh, whoa, that's a good idea.
That's a fun gimmick.
I might do that.
Excellent.
Yeah, all right.
That's cool.
I don't know.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's gonna be a good year.
It's gonna be a good year, I think, for all of us.
Ben's Kickstarter is wrapping up.
My Kickstarter. It's not done yet.
Oh, God, I want today.
Since you bring it up, I just want to say that today,
this very day, is the last day of my Kickstarter.
Oh, yeah?
When you, the listener, are listening to this.
So go to my fucking Twitter, link in the description.
We're fucking going for the final stretch goal,
which is that I buy a fucking Oculus Rift
and turn memes into reality.
Make the dream real.
Yes, make the dream real.
Send me surfing down the VR superhighway.
Ben, you know, if you want to sell that
as something actually meaningful,
you know there's a VR program for Oculus Rift
where you can draw in VR and 3D,
so you can walk around the drawing
as you're drawing it and stuff.
I have seen it.
Yeah, I mean, if I get a,
I don't even know what I do with an Oculus Rift,
but I would, you can probably, you finally live.
You have just post photos on Twitter with it
and then mention, map every time.
I mean, I owe it all to him, man.
I owe it all to him.
He sparks the creative drive in you to get to the point
where you could buy an Oculus Rift.
That's true.
And they say capitalism doesn't work.
Yeah, excellent, excellent.
So Ben's going to get an Oculus Rift.
That's his goal for 2018.
Yeah, what I'm saying is that's my goal for 2018.
I can't wait for the Rowdy Funkers Cop Killers episode
all in VR. Oh my God.
Oh, the Oculus Rift theme.
Rowdy Funkers episode.
A five hour free video.
How could I not have thought of that?
Of course, of course.
Oh, that's the capstone of the saga.
Oh my God.
We got to get Munchy one too.
There's another special, dude.
We can fucking have VR adventures.
Guys, please get Ben this Oculus Rift.
So this can be real.
Please.
Yes.
I mean, this was just a fucking joke,
but now that we're talking about it,
the actual real world possibilities are just staggering.
Oh shit.
All this corruption will have been true all along.
This is all part of Ben's long game.
He's been playing the long con here.
I'm always playing the long con.
He's joking.
We all act like this is just spur of the moment,
but no, inside there's a calculated psychopath.
We just made those statements,
and then we didn't see, because we're on a podcast,
Ben, like it was a freeze frame,
but it turned red like death though.
And he's like, it's all according to plan.
I didn't have to say anything about the benefits
of the Oculus Rift.
They said it for me.
So I'm totally in the clear.
I don't look like the bad guy.
Dude, when Ben touches the Oculus Rift,
just like it does in all his memories,
he's come flooding back with his own plan.
But he's suppressed with his fucking mind,
and he's like, just as good as new.
Oh my God.
He's gonna be the god of the VR world.
Yeah, the god of the VR world.
Oh my God.
And Munchie's re-euk, right?
Oh yes, oh it's perfect with his fat little body
with his little wings floating around.
Only instead of eating apples,
he eats a disgusting fast food food.
And it's, oh, it's whole pizzas.
Whole pizzas, oh, incredible.
You know, that just gets me thinking.
The wheels spinning in my head of like,
what we could do with that at a Radcon,
at a Radcon, at a place with the procrastinators.
That's sort of a goal
that is not like individual to any one of us,
but that's something that could like begin to,
I mean, I don't know.
We don't have like big plans.
That's the 2018 goal for all of you, the listeners,
to go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators,
give generously and make it happen.
It's true, man.
I want to meet up with my good boy, baby friends,
and suck everyone's dick.
That's what I want to do.
Indeed.
I think we're pretty firmly out of any Kickstarter jail
that we may have been in up to this point.
And I think that, yeah, man, the door's wide open.
And of course, not to mention,
like Digi's got plans to be moving sometime this year.
Things for me are looking way up in general
in terms of just like my YouTube success
and just like my economic stability.
Just getting closer.
I'm already above like technically a livable wage,
but it's lower than I'm comfortable doing at the moment.
So I gotta keep working, gotta keep grinding,
earn a little bit more,
and then once I'm at that point,
my student loans, they're getting way down there, dude.
They're way down there.
And they will, these will 100% be paid off in this year,
in this year without a question.
So that is very exciting for me.
I will no longer be a negative financial boy.
I will finally be positive.
And that's-
You'll finally be in the black.
Wait, what was the pause thing you just said?
Is that like that?
Is that that thing about like people who like to get aides?
Yes.
And it's like sexy for me?
Yeah, you're right.
That means you're, you know.
That's what I was saying.
You've got the gift to give.
I've got the gift, the gift, that's the one.
The gift, yes.
Well, the gift is the bug.
The two are one and the same.
Right?
God damn.
Degeneracy is really in a spiral right now in 2018.
It's the in thing to do.
The fact that it is the in thing to,
well, okay, I'm exaggerating a little bit,
but yeah, what the fuck, guys?
It's definitely you.
Please stop.
Let me see, what else am I doing?
Hey, I got plans.
I got some plans.
Weagua is proving to be a pretty strong success so far.
It's the content that I think I was more or less destined
to do, just some sort of regular content
to force me to make stuff.
Just, it's just like back in the T-Bap days.
I was forced to make an episode every week
and it forced me to get a little creative.
It's been really good for me.
So I'm gonna keep doing that for forever, for the next while.
And in the meantime.
Which ever comes first.
Indeed, indeed.
And just do it.
I don't know, for me, I'm pretty much staying the course
and just like trying to like grow
and everything's going very well for me.
So I'm just doing what I'm doing.
No surprises.
Though there will be surprises in terms of content
that people see for me in 2018.
Especially if I am able to go full time
and I'm finally set free to spend all my time
working on content.
Oh man, you guys don't even know.
I've been saying this forever.
The content that I work on every day
that is coming sometime soon.
When, when it goes to the show.
That is a good question.
Who knows man?
When it's one piece Nate, we filmed it like 60 years ago.
Oh shit, Ben was that, didn't even know that.
Ben helped Ben.
Dude, I got incredible footage that day.
You, we certainly did.
The footage was ridiculous. I did.
Yeah, Ben held the camera, Ben held the camera.
It was me.
Someday soon, someday soon everybody.
2018, 2018, that's something you can mark
on your fucking calendar this year.
A promise.
The whole year, mark the whole year on your calendar.
At some point.
Yeah, block out this whole space of time
from January 1st to December 31st.
You're gonna wanna have that time booked for me.
Cause I'm gonna be filling it.
Every orifice.
Just like your hero, Shadman.
Every hole is a goal.
You know, I respect Shadman as a businessman
and as a rebel and as an entrepreneur.
But his art is, I am growing a little bit out of favor
with the art itself.
Well, that's what he, you were just telling me
how he's your hero and your favorite person
you aspire just to be like him.
Because he has the audacity of hope
to quote my hero, Barack Obama.
Or was that Hillary Clinton?
I can't remember.
No, that was.
You know, he is a literal internationally wanted criminal
as I understand it.
Wait, what?
And he just doesn't give a fuck
and he just keeps drawing lolliporn.
Why is he an internationally wanted criminal?
Because he draws lolliporn.
I thought it was because he had a fucking scary skull.
They're cracking down on skulls in Europe
in a big way right now.
But yeah, he's just like,
if his identity was revealed, he'd be real fucked.
And I just, I don't know, he just has a passion
and he's uncompromising in his devotion to it.
And I really respect that.
That's all.
That's pretty neat, honestly.
Yeah, super neat.
And he carved out his own space.
Yeah, he's kind of a hero, kind of a hero.
But anyway.
All right, that's what I'm doing.
That's what I'm doing.
What about you, Tom?
I have a lot of stuff going on in 2018, hopefully.
I think the big thing for this year, like macro goal,
is just like focus.
Cause last year I did a bunch of things
and it was a clusterfuck and I hated it and it sucked.
So I just, I killed off one of my YouTube channels.
I was running two of them.
So last week, I put the kebab
wash on Rebel Pixels cause I, it'd been like months
and no one had sent me anything.
No one responded to my emails.
And it was just a distraction at this point anyway.
Cause the Patreon never got any money.
It was just like, it was a lot of time to make those videos
and as informative and as helpful they were
to thousands of people, they didn't pay me anything.
So fuck it.
So.
Rest in peace, Rebel Pixels.
So that, that went away.
And I'm just focusing on 3D this year.
So my old channel, which is not my new channel again,
it's all about 3D.
So I'm going to do analysis videos on 3D.
Yeah.
Your Berserk series is going along swimmingly as I saw.
I'm going to work on today on a, a, a interlude
on land of the lustrous cause no one will fucking shut up
in the comments about who built land of the lustrous.
It proves everything you're saying.
Oh, that's who's so sick, you know, Coney, right?
That's, that's what that is.
Yeah, right.
So of course, like.
I also just downloaded that today.
It's, it's fucking amazing.
I watched it.
It's great.
The month after I start the series, you know,
Joseki Nocuni drops and like everyone's like,
Oh, well now anime, 3D anime has always been amazing
because this one show is great.
And we never shit on it ever.
Berserk just happened guys.
Berserk just happened.
Let's not forget.
Well, the thing is like, I have like clips from like
dozens of 3D shows that all have like the same like
kind of weirdness to them.
And then like the next part is going to talk about 3D anime
and video games and how that's kind of looks weird sometimes.
But this one show, of course.
So I got to, I got to put the whole series proper on hold
and be like, all right, you peasants.
You know, I watched some of Joseki Nocuni just in clips.
I didn't think it was like perfectly.
It's still a little bit uncanny valley, but, but anyway,
I'm sorry, I don't mean to.
It's much, it's much, it's much better for sure.
And I got some real laughs.
There's, there's some good stuff in there for sure.
It's, it's fucking great.
So I'm working on that series.
And then I'm also doing more animation,
just like making 3D.
So the whole channel is going to be on making 3D
and talking about it and just enjoying 3D as an art form.
There's one problem with your whole, a business model here.
And it's that 3D pig disgusting Tom, 2D waifu for life.
You need to re-configure your whole life.
You know, I'm just like, like your hero, Shadman,
I'm a disgusting degenerate with a mission
and I'm just sticking to it.
So respect my vision as you respect his.
I'll try.
Do your best.
I'll have to get some lollies in there.
And that's how I'll gain your.
That would help.
Yeah. So I'm doing at least,
I think I'm going to try and shoot for three more animations,
short animations this year,
kind of like her that I did the end of last year.
I'm sure you've learned a lot
in the process of making that first one, right?
Hopefully faster.
Yeah, there was, yeah.
The next one I'm doing is a lot simpler.
So I want to get the first one for this year
done by the end of February.
Then the next one will be much more complicated.
And I want to try and end the year
with like a full like music video,
which will be like three minutes long.
And lots of crazy fucking choreography.
So I'm probably going to take an actual
like online course on 3D animation.
Watch out, Monty Ohm.
There's another man looking to fill that grave.
The only way I can live up to him
is to clearly just kill myself,
which might be the plan.
If I don't, if I don't get swole by 30,
I'll just have to like pick out a plot right next to him,
just be like, buddy's in the grave.
But yeah, that's also I'm going to be making
just like more just models in general.
I'll be, I just did my first live stream of the year
yesterday.
I'm going to do one every Friday this year.
That's the plan unless like something really stupid happens.
And just do 3D on stream.
So I'll probably, I'm going to actually make a 3D model
of Foss, the main character of second okay,
that's going to be my next model,
to get them clicks, get them Patreon bucks.
That's the way to do it, that's the way to do it.
But really though, why not?
Why not do the thing that's popular
if you're just going to practice anyway?
It's certainly, yeah.
I mean, that's kind of the idea behind it.
So I'm going to do that.
And then in the background,
I'm just going to keep writing the script for Sorceloss,
which is not dead, it's just,
it went through a huge rewrite all last year
and I finally figured out what to do with it.
Tom, Tom, I gotta say, when I saw that update video,
I forget what it was titled,
but the one that was saying Rebel Pixels is dead.
I thought that it was going to be,
Sorceress lost is dead.
Like that's what I thought you were announcing,
but I'm glad that it wasn't.
Never, it's going to survive for all time.
No, actually the story,
I just had like a huge change of heart
with how I wanted to do it
and it took all year to figure it out.
And I talked to like a couple of my comic friends
going like, what should I do for this?
And then it finally clicked in like November.
I'm like, oh.
Now that's an up and coming female politician
who was going to lose to the evil race realist,
male supremacist.
Now she's going to shatter that glass ceiling.
It has nothing to do with real life events.
Excellent, yeah, I look forward to it.
I was really inspired by what happened.
It let me figure out what's going to happen
in my story.
Like what if someone didn't pay any attention
to US politics, but still read what happened?
Is there anyone who's like done that?
That'd be incredible.
Yeah, me.
Right.
Me and you.
That's true.
So I think that's pretty much it is just.
It's pretty full schedule.
Well, also the whole like moving out thing
I have to move out this year.
So I don't know really what's going to go on to that.
I'm either going to try and get like a small studio apartment
or live in a car.
That'll be fun.
Hey man.
Whichever feels right at the time.
Yeah.
Cincinnati, you get a decent apartment,
you know, okay for 500 bucks a month.
So it's pretty all right.
So that's your horrible.
But then again, if we're going to Boston,
I'm already like right outside of Boston.
So why would I go all the way somewhere else?
Yeah, that's true.
I'm kind of waiting on you and Digi,
what you guys are doing.
And I'll kind of plan appropriately.
He's holding out for a hero, ladies and gentlemen.
We'll see how that goes.
Well, yeah.
Hey man, run your own shit though.
Don't wait too long.
I don't want to fuck over your plans and whatnot.
If there's nothing in place by like April,
that's when I'm really going to start pulling a trigger.
Because I got like $18,000 right now in savings.
Hey, not bad.
I'm just going to try and hit 20.
And then I'm probably just going to like leave my job.
And then because like I'm last.
Yeah, it's fucking awful.
I haven't, I worked six hours this week out of 40
because like there's no heat
and it's been like negative degrees every night.
So I'm just like, well, I don't want to die.
So I'm just not going to go into work, I guess.
So my paycheck is going to be abysmal.
But yeah, once that's done, like my student loans,
I can pay with PCP money and then some.
So that's not a big deal.
I'm glad to hear it.
And if the PCP keeps growing, then I won't need a job.
And then I can just live in a car with.
Oh, good.
The ideal living situation.
It's going to be great.
Dude, there's a.
Vlogs while driving.
I mean, that's a thing people do.
Didn't that guy, who was that guy who announced
that he was going to be homeless and vlog homeless
for like a full year?
It was like one of the big reactor guys on YouTube
who's dead now or something.
Joey salads or something.
I don't know.
It was something like that.
That sounds right to me.
That sounds like that sounds like the name of a person
who would do that.
Good old Joey salads.
That's a real name.
That's a real.
I know it's a real guy.
I don't know God.
I'm taking pot shots at him anyway.
No, Joey salads is a real dude.
He's actually pretty successful.
He's a real person.
Guys, please don't laugh at his.
I can't I can't I can't it's not it's not acceptable.
I agree.
That name is not acceptable.
No, it's pretty pretty bad.
It's pretty bad.
I scoff, frankly.
Well, that's that's going to be fun.
We'll see how that goes.
Hopefully it won't go too bad.
Hopefully, man, hopefully.
Patreon.com slash save me.
Give me money so I can make this stuff happen faster.
Yeah, so I'm going to I'll add a lot of a lot of gold
to give me an Oculus Rift, you know, I'll get an HTC Vive
and then we can have a battle.
Let's start a rivalry going on.
Yeah, I'll have a mansion in VR.
Let me tell you.
Well, just like with D&D, just like me and Tom
will just make opposing YouTube videos.
I'll say why the Oculus Rift is great
and Tom will say why it's shit.
That would legitimately be hilarious.
And I would totally do that.
Looking forward to more of that.
All right, well, Ben, did you want to talk more
about your goals or did you I don't know, you said some stuff
before, but I have I have I have a couple art goals in mind.
I want to.
OK, so I'm working on Vapors 3 right now.
I'm hoping that gets done in not too, too long.
Maybe like, well, I don't want to put a number on it.
But like, yeah, not I'm not like six months or anything.
Yeah, OK, significantly less than that.
After that, I'm not quite sure.
I think I think I'm going to probably do
Champion Chapter 2 after Vapors 3.
Unless maybe I have a great idea for Vapors 4
and I just want to bang out another one real quick.
But I'm also going to do another game.
Like I'm going to I'm going to start Champion Chapter 2
with another like game section.
And I want to do that.
I also want to I want to make a video.
This is not like a big project.
It's just a side thing.
I want to make a video that's just me going through all my code
in Game Maker and just explaining how the first game that I made
works kind of as a kind of just as a little like blog thing.
Like that sounds cool.
I'd like to watch that.
Yeah, yeah, just take a couple hours and like go through it
and be like, this how did I do this?
I forget. Let me.
Oh, yeah, Ben, Ben, Ben, Ben, Ben, a couple hours.
That game takes me like a couple minutes to beat.
That doesn't make sense.
What are you saying?
That's ridiculous.
Yeah. Code is effortless, Ben.
I know, I know, but, you know, I struggle.
I struggle with even the meagerest of tasks.
So, so, so, yeah, I want to make that.
And I'm going to so.
And I don't know what I'm going to work on past Vapors 3
and Champion Chapter 2 and the game, but while I'm doing all that,
I'm probably going to do more kick starters.
Like I'm going to I'm going to kick start Vapors 2
after at some point, maybe I'll wait a little bit and then do that.
I guess if Vapors 3 is done by then,
maybe I'll kick start Vapors 3.
Oh, and I know we joked about it a while ago,
but I'm like, I'm actually unironically
considering making DVDs of the Nuzlocs.
Like I got some DVD software and I'm like,
I've been putting together menus just because I think it's neat.
And because I just I would just want to own one,
even if nobody bought one, I think it's cool.
So, yeah, maybe I want one.
Nobody, none of us have like set anything.
I know the the Pleeve and the Weave plans on being set to disk,
but no one's actually pulled the trigger on that yet.
Yeah, I would like to see that happen.
The thing about that is that looking into it, I am like,
it was really difficult to find like how to like make
like a professionally set up DVD.
And I kind of wonder if anyone else even gave it any thought.
I don't know.
With regards to Pleeve and the Weave.
Like, we all know the level of planning
that went into the Pleeve and the Weave, of course.
So, you know, I'm sure they've got to figure it out.
Like my like my DVDs, they're going to be an experience.
They're going to have menus.
They're they're going to it's going to be like
have like a chapter selection.
It's going to be it's going to be the full work.
You're going to have like a full DVD like experience.
Ben, is it like a like a like a special like Adobe
something or other Adobe fucking show time
when that helps you build DVD menus and things?
I don't know.
I found a DVD architect that I got a free trial of.
Yeah, because because for for my like for my animation stuff,
since it's like, you know, you can submit it online
and most people do or on USB, but they want you as part of the course
to figure out how to make a professional looking DVD
of your animation to hand in.
And if you don't have that, you don't get full marks.
And it's not that difficult.
I don't think I didn't do like special menus.
Help me.
I guess talk details after the show.
No, tell me right now.
Well, it's it's really I mean, I didn't do like a very elaborate menu or anything.
But it's basically you just that there's a software that there are softwares out
and you just you have to render your video files in like a DVD format.
Like HD stuff doesn't work.
It has to be like a deep because like DVDs have a certain amount,
like eight gigabytes of space.
You have to make it the right sort of format so that it could all fit on.
Well, well, you and you and Davoo both said the thing.
You both said there's software out there.
I've been looking for software.
I'm trying to remember that there's an Adobe thing.
There's an it's like it's a blue Adobe.
It's a blue Adobe thing called something something.
Adobe Blu-ray.
Let me let me crack on my keyboard and find it.
All right, Ben, do you know what a light scribe DVD is?
No, you should get a light scribe DVD.
OK, because this is how you make them super cool.
So you get a light scribe DVD burner and what that is, it burns a DVD is normal.
But then the the top of the disc is like, I don't know how it works.
It's like heat sensitive so that you can burn directly a black and white image
to the top of the disc.
You don't put a sticker on there.
It's like burned on top of the discs so you can make them look super professional.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
So I can just burn the image right onto it.
Yeah, you just take you take an image
and it burns a black and white version of the picture right onto the disc.
It doesn't like peel off or anything.
That is the greatest.
So that's what you need.
That is exactly right there.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's it's called Adobe Encore.
Adobe Encore. OK.
Yeah, I don't think they have it on the CC like a creative cloud thing.
But I think that the last one was CS6.
But you know, you can you can acquire that program.
Yeah, I have the means.
I can seize the means of how ominous.
How ominous, yes.
By use license on eBay.
What are you guys talking about?
Yeah, so have we all gone through our plans now?
I feel like we pretty much wound through them.
I was about now.
Yeah, I mean, I sort of yeah.
Yeah, I sort of like skimmed over like specifics
and how I'm going to make videos.
But it's really just it's not much for me to say
other than I'm going to try to do them faster and still be good.
And that's, you know.
Yeah, sure.
I just I mean, since this is the PCP,
I mean, I was I wanted to say that this I think is definitely going to be the year.
Assuming things go as they've been going, where I personally am emancipated at last.
I thought it was going to be the last couple of years.
But now now there is a clear, trackable path of progress
where things are really going well and I could really see how
within the first half of this year, things get to a place where it's,
you know, it'll make sense.
Like I'll be able to finally break out and then consider doing YouTube full time,
which will free me up to explore YouTube possibilities with the PCP.
And then and then we'll just see where that goes.
Well, speaking of that.
Do we have anything to say on the idea of PCP HQ as a plan for 2018?
That's that's what I'm talking about.
Really, when we didn't really talk about PCP goals,
do we have anything we plan on doing with the PCP this year?
Yeah, about the show itself.
I don't know about you guys.
I would like to bring in more guests where possible.
I've got a couple of people kicking around.
We talked about a couple of before the show.
Sure, be nice.
Oh, no.
Oh, yes.
No.
Let's just say we're going to take a trip to the dark side.
Everybody.
You know, you don't understand how bad you don't understand how great
an idea I think that is.
It's it's a yeah.
Yeah, I know.
Like why would we not want that?
Well, OK, but we're just I mean, that is one thing I've been thinking about.
And also, like the the PCP episode that came out before this was like a
totally different format, the interviews and stuff.
I want to keep mixing up content like that.
I enjoyed that thought that was fun.
I don't know.
I want to mix things up this year.
And we did it.
We did pretty much the exact same thing the entire year last year.
And there's been some new stuff.
The PCP animated that's like pretty much started this year more or less.
Those are great.
I want to keep doing this in mind.
People keep making them.
You know, that's I think I want to to finally get off my my A.S.
and and and get some PCP races organized and happening.
I did I did write up like a like a guide for how it should be done
so I can refer to it and show people what they have to do.
But the the the PCP races are going to be a little different
if the the the next one we do at least.
Yeah, yeah, where it's it's more about from the beginning.
But like we I'll run through the the basic idea.
People gather to record and then we spin a wheel of what game
they have to get and play and it will be like a free game they can find
or you know something hopefully that they all have or can easily acquire.
And then they from that point have to go and play and speed run the game
on get to whatever point it is and then get the footage back to me
after like a set amount of time from the very beginning of the recording.
And the it's going to be more of like a frantic like oh my God.
I'm downloading the game.
It's taken too long.
And then you got a speed runner and it's going to be very funny.
And yeah, I like it.
And yeah, and then we're going to go when I watch the footage
and it's going to be it's going to be more of a structure that encourages
people to to, you know, try to go really fast
and to be really frantic and unprepared.
And it also means that people don't have any sort of idea of,
you know, getting their time perfect by spent like you, Nate,
playing the thing a hundred times every night to get it.
It's bad. Yeah.
But that's the fun of it.
Well, they just won't get done if they take so much time.
Like the reason the races have never been like it's just hard to get people
to say, OK, I have time to practice this for 20 hours a day.
Like nobody has that time, but they want to have that time.
And it's just never going to happen unless it's more of a speed thing.
We can always choose to do certain races like that if we so choose in the future.
But yeah, if we want to pump them out regularly, something like this,
well, I don't know about regularly, maybe one or two months or something.
But like, yeah, whatever.
Yeah, more than I want that to be a thing that happens.
Because those races were great.
Like the first Dark Souls race was one of the best.
Oh, it's legendary. It's legendary.
Everyone, if you haven't watched it, go watch the PCP Dark Souls race.
It's incredible. I'd say the Pokemon race is equally legendary.
I don't know about that.
So there were some some highlights of that for sure.
Yeah, certainly my favorite.
The draw cast have been going strong.
I've been happy to see that.
Great. And I feel like they're underappreciated.
I feel like they're some of the best content that comes out on this channel.
And I feel like they're underviewed.
No, no, no.
But they're they're way fun.
And they get people and they get people like, you know, drawn along with us
and, you know, people tweet us, you know, like, oh, here's how I did a challenge.
And I love that shit.
You know what we could do?
We could we could combine the idea of having guests and having draw casts.
We could we could maybe get like an art guest to be on a draw cast.
That would be an interesting new thing. Sure. Sure. Yeah.
And you must be, for example.
No, he's banned from the PCP.
There will be no mention of his name, his cursed name.
Picasso, give him an art tab.
We need we need to get Chris Chan in on a draw cast.
Oh, oh, yeah. Imagine.
It's time. Yeah. Yeah.
But the possibilities are end full, but there's a lot of them.
Yeah, man. Yeah.
I don't know. Mix and stuff up.
Try new things.
I'm excited to do more of that in the coming year.
And if you guys have any suggestions, you know, feel free to leave them in the comments.
You know, I'll take them out. I'll check them out.
Yeah, there you go. I don't know.
All right. I feel like we're good.
I feel like we've exhausted everything.
We're fucking done.
Agreed? OK.
I guess. I mean, the only thing left that we didn't really talk about is
PCP HQ and or a new Radcon, but we don't know anything about it.
Yeah, we just want it to happen.
We all still want it still waiting.
I don't know. Like I remember I had said a while ago that we should just set
a date and figure it out, guys.
Just make yourself available for that day tomorrow at one p.m.
I can take off a week from work and like be at a Radcon sometime.
And I just need to know while in advance and I can do it.
Same. I need to know quite a while in advance for plain ticket reasons.
Sure. Sure.
But we got a week that that's on us.
We got to figure that out.
We got to commit to that and make it happen.
Though also the location was always an issue, but.
Right.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, you did like a like a mini
Radcon with within the Boston thing.
I don't know whether that's like public knowledge, like secret classified documents.
No, not at all. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, and Ben and Digi and Munchie and stuff.
You guys were there in person in real life.
It wasn't really a Radcon.
We were just hanging out in the same place.
Well, that's what a Radcon should be.
I just want to hang out for a bit.
I don't. I have no interest in that.
Well, I mean, I do, but I will not go if there's like just hanging out going on.
Just letting you know. Just letting you know.
Well, I know, but like, I understand.
Well, we have to put in some work to like make it happen to arrange where
and how it's going to be. So that's really on us.
I think the biggest, the biggest problem with it so far has just been
that we don't have a place to do it anymore.
That really is.
That was that. Digi's gigantic house was great.
And Victor, as the cameraman, was incredible.
And I'm so sad that we won't have him unless we can convince him there.
Like if we do do a Kickstarter, I'm happy to try to give him some money.
You know, yeah, if we could.
I mean, just just ideas, just ideas.
So now, hey, here's an update, folks.
Now that so much of the plebe and the weave has come out,
would you have any problem with a PCP Kickstarter for, you know,
Radcon Awakening or perhaps we'd probably give it a new name.
So it's no longer at Radcon anymore.
I don't know.
Feel free to leave comments.
I'll read them. I'll check them out.
I'm going to bet.
I mean, I'm imagining that the people who are interested in making that happen
would have been fine with it all along.
Generally speaking.
Probably right.
Well, that's that, Aaron, our dirty laundry in a way.
2018's over.
Go over 2018.
Let's let's indeed let's let's go to those questions, guys.
By the way, before we read a question, I want to read a comment.
So as you know, everybody, hashtag ask PCP on the Twitter is the tag.
We every Saturday we record, we put out a little thing.
Yeah, OK, we got we got a friend here to address our right.
So, you know, I always tweet or we somebody tweets Saturday, you know,
to remind everybody to send in questions.
And so as you've seen, we've taken less questions from there
and more from the patron discord, which, I mean, is just where we want to
incentivize people to be patrons seems reasonable to me.
But a friend of ours here, the one true Henry had a comment about this
that let's just take a moment to address.
Here's here's a response to us asking for questions on Twitter.
Why do you even ask Twitter when you only take one question?
If you just restrict it to Patreon, that will encourage more people to sign up.
You are just giving people a false sense of hope
that their question will be read on the pod case.
Henry, my dude, what the great Henry Yoshi.
Yeah, dog, he's back.
He's back. Listen, dumbass.
You are a silly, silly boy.
Look, look, you just you're just not what is this that we like owe people
to be on the like if we tweet that we will only take, like, you know,
if you watch the show that we take like a pity question.
It's a joke. We address this at the time.
We take like one or two and you're like, oh, you're giving people a false
sense of hope their question will be read.
Well, maybe make it a good question and it'll be the one that we read.
So what exactly is your fucking grievance here?
I don't like this point might be that
people who would want to ask a question instead of just giving us a dollar
or whatever and getting in on it, they're instead just rolling the dice
every week and hoping I think he's just mad that his question has never been asked.
Except for this one, except for this one.
That could be a possibility, which just encourages people to be annoying
and title ourselves because that now we are reading his question.
I am so sorry that we read one question from the Twitter as opposed to zero.
Like you suggest that we do.
I am so sorry that we continue to take questions without putting it behind
any kind of paywall. What a mistake.
What a fuck up on our end. Really got to fix that shit.
I don't know, Nate, you don't seem sorry.
What? How dare you question my integrity?
Henry, I humbly disagree with your point there.
That's all I'm saying.
All right. Real question.
Yes, real questions.
There's this one here.
From the Patreon Discord.
Yeah, yeah, from the Patreon Discord.
Real question time. Yeah, we're away from that bullshit now.
Please, yes, go.
From Great, because we talked about this earlier,
Grace Yu says, how can a plebe, how does can a plebe stay motivated
to go to the gym regularly?
I'm attempting it and want wise words to keep me inspired.
So I'm assuming he had a new use resolution.
Now he's going to the gym.
But how do you do it, Nate?
The problem there is a fundamental question of motivation.
There's a lot of things people do wrong when they're trying to keep themselves
motivated to work out and stuff.
But like it sounds like your core, like your impetus to go
is your fact that you made a resolution.
Well, he didn't say that. I'm just assuming I'm inferring.
I'm inferring here. So I admit, I don't I can't read your mind.
I can't tell everything.
But you're you're you're going because you made a resolution.
And like you definitely want it on some level,
but you don't want it that bad, do you?
You're not willing to sacrifice, you know, the the effort that it takes to go.
Are you? It's really this resolution that's the binding contract,
keeping you going and like just no insult, but that's no basis
to like keep you going long term and stay, you know, exercising and stuff.
You have to the only way to make this work is you have to, I would say,
a, like actually enjoy the process itself of working out.
Like when I work out, it hurts, you know, it's tiring, it's exhausting.
But afterward, just think about that glow you get afterward, how great you feel.
I feel that every time.
That's that that is the specific motivating factor that keeps me going.
And then, of course, in my mind, I have the like long term thoughts
and I guess this will guide me on the physical path, you know,
that I want to get to long term.
So you got to have a short term.
Humans are dumb and we think with our stupid, stupid brains about like the here
and now, and we prioritize that so often over the long term,
you have to know that about yourself and trick your own brain into doing what
you intellectually wanted to do by making yourself focus on the short term benefits
like that, like that pleasurable feeling right after you've worked out
and how good you'll feel knowing you worked out as opposed to how shitty you'll feel
knowing that you were supposed to work out today and you flaked or shit like that.
That's I think that's the long term, more sustainable way.
Also set yourself like reasonable, actionable goals.
But that's that's a whole other story.
Yeah, that's my thoughts.
My thoughts is don't go to the gym.
Just run around, just run around and pick up rocks.
It's the same thing. Yeah, pretty much the same thing.
A good question, everybody.
This is actually from the Twitter from at Lobo.
Oh, no, no, no, no, that guy has deleted the Twitter.
You know what, you're right.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Henry has said that we're not allowed to take questions from the Twitter.
So, you know, I don't want to give anybody a false hope.
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
But Henry has forbidden it.
All right, please go on, get what else you got.
You're such a wrathful God.
I know, I know.
I'll go look at some of these.
Here's one.
Tom Sieg asks, which PCP member has the best fan base?
And I got to say, Monkey Jones, obviously.
Yeah, for sure.
For sure. No argument here.
But aside from him, best fan base.
I mean, I would literally argue that it is mine.
I would argue that it is mine.
Because just because they suck your dick.
No, but they it's well, OK, they really do suck my dick.
And I don't actually like necessarily respect them for that.
Because, you know, like they will suck anyone's dick who they like,
you know, like the Jake Paul people suck, you know, whatever.
But it's they seem quite open to the kind of intellectual discussion
that I'm usually talking about.
And I find them to be very reasonable.
And I don't know, maybe this is a projection of my own reasonableness.
Like when people come at me with bullshit on like my Twitter,
I respond just like, I'm like, hey, dude, what's the problem?
I like how you're just saying like, I like how they're they approach me
and they're reasonable and all this shit right after I just shit on a random
Twitter guy for daring to question our decisions.
Well, that's like a PCP guy as opposed to a best guy, I guess.
I don't know. I don't know.
But I mean, he deserves it because he was talking.
Well, you were just saying that like, I like how they kind of like embody
my ideals of like being reasonable and open to discussion.
Don't mind me as I just shit on Henry.
Well, if you'll notice, if you'll notice at the end of my shitting on him,
I ended it with a with my actual point of like, I humbly disagree,
which is honestly how I really feel about it.
So I'm meming, I'm meming a dream and the people understand that, I hope.
I don't know.
Me, I have like an I think because like it's it's it's weird to say
that it's not my own fan base.
I think it's the best fan base, but I obviously do love my fans.
They're cute and they're great and cute and I love them.
I want to give them a big old hug.
But I think Munchies fans, like the people who understand and appreciate
Munchie are probably my favorite people like those people a lot.
Yeah, because they get they get it.
You know, they they're cool. You're right.
I mean, I'm a pretty big fan of my people.
They're all just a bunch of real nice boys.
I've taken notice of the the Ben and Jackie wholesome fan base.
There's just a bunch of just a bunch of swell guys that hang out in our
discord and just are like great, fast friends with each other.
And like, sometimes I get emotional about it.
Lol, I think it's too it's too wholesome for me.
It it it's it's it's making my brain turn it to to to get there's a certain
number of of what is it NPM.
You have to reach a certain ratio of NPM for give to be happy in a community,
which is nine elevens per minute.
There has to be a certain ratio in order for him to feel not even that untrue
because I like I like my edgy boys.
I like people being a raucous and edgy and then also being like real and nice.
All I'm all I'm saying is just yesterday, Alex S.
And paradigm and Phil draw Phil draw just put just they just made a song.
He's made a song about how much they love the discord and how much they
love our streams and I got a little a little choked up.
That's nice.
Yeah, I have a discord as well.
My patron discord and I've had some great talks in there,
specifically with this one guy Denali about like fitness.
He's like he's like he was like a competitive weightlifter or something.
And he was just such a sweetheart who gave me some real great advice
and gave me the info to start the routine that I'm on right now.
So shout out to that guy and just everybody and there's a real nice guy,
especially shout out to me, me, Tian or Midian Mishin in the like a ten dollar
patron in the ten dollar chat where we just talk about one piece all the time.
This person read all of one piece on my suggestion and is now caught up.
And now we're talking about it and it's extremely wholesome and I love it.
Hot shit.
Yeah, I'm a buzzer.
People have like read all of one piece now because yeah, of course,
he's watched every episode of the podcast.
Except crazy, right?
Crazy. It's good stuff.
Oh, yeah, podcast.
Got a patron out of fucking.
I don't want to plug too many extra things.
The podcast pirates, I think that the description is like like bloated
with so many links, nobody's going to click on any of them.
Yeah, it's true.
Except for my Kickstarter.
Give me that Oculus Rift.
It's the last day guys.
It's the last fucking day.
Ten p.m. EST tonight is when it all comes crashing down.
Wow.
That'll be about nine hours from when you hear this or is it ten?
Whatever, something like eight hours.
If you get it right when it comes out, if you're really on top of your shit.
Oh, I was I was including that hour difference if they listen to it
right when it comes out, because it's been an hour.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, right.
Yes, because we're an hour.
That's that's thinking ahead.
That's the best guy ever for you.
He's always 10 steps ahead.
All right, I got one.
We've got one more question here.
Nice, nice light question to end the show.
Hey, he asks, what would you do if your son turned out with heavy autism?
Oh, no, I get my gun.
No. Oh, God, I think this question haunts me literally every day.
I like, am I going to say that I'm going to be like thrilled with the situation?
Well, no one will be not.
Oh, that would.
But it's like also the kind of the most evil thing you can do.
Say like that you don't hear you're not happy with your kid.
Oh, it's fucked up.
Well, I think it's not.
I don't think it's like a bad showing of like a bad person
that you don't like having to deal with a child that is going to be like,
you know, for sure, will be a whole life.
Their whole life. Yeah.
I mean, you know, it's not like autistic people can't work.
They do get jobs and stuff.
But like it's it's more difficult.
It is more difficult as a parent to do that.
I think we just go go grab his son in his arms,
look him straight in the eyes, take him up to the cliff of Sparta
and just cast him off and be like, we're utilitarianism compels me.
I'm trying again with another one.
Oh, it's fucked up.
Yeah, I don't ever worry about this because I'm never going to have a son
or a daughter because it's ridiculous.
Yeah. OK. All right.
Fair understood, understood.
But here's what I would really do is I would really try to analyze
what my kid like check for diseases.
You know, I don't know how much you can predict autism like in the womb.
But seriously, I would if I have a kid that's that's that's brewing in a belly,
I will try to find out every disease so that I can abort it
if things are going wrong and just try again,
because I don't consider it a human being worthy of moral consideration,
not even a little bit until it's like one year old.
So, yeah, that's what I would do.
I mean, I'm not against abortion, but that the idea that you would like,
you know, you would think about that a lot before.
I mean, yeah, of course, what's wrong with that?
I guess. I don't think that's because like you're you're making
a commitment of time and effort when having a child and to be thrown
a curveball like that and expect that like your initial time and investment
and like your commitment that you made is still valid when they're throwing
that huge thing in there. I don't think that's necessarily true.
And I'm taking the steps so that I don't have so that I just like it.
So there is no problem.
I'm addressing it before it becomes a moral question
because an embryo is not a human being.
So there's nothing I don't really see the problem.
Well, it's like, I mean, all right, all right.
Here's my thoughts on the matter.
Like, OK, of course, this is a this is a there's a spectrum here.
The autism spectrum specifically.
Of course, this is a shade of gray.
But like you get you get far enough down on the spectrum.
Like you get to the point where they're like don't even really
like like interact on like a human level anymore.
And like I kind of feel like the closer you get to that spectrum.
But yeah, like like they they they're they become less and less like
worthy of consideration on like a human level.
It's it's just I think that the thing that none of us know for sure
is whether you can tell in the womb quite how autistic a child is going to be.
That's fair. That is fair.
I don't think I don't know if there's any way to test.
Yeah, I don't think you can. Yeah, it's like magically know we could do something.
But I think practically speaking, you're probably I think I think this is why
we need genetic engineering. All right, we can fix.
I agree. I literally have the genome.
We fix all that. Just fix all that in post, you know, just fucking.
Exactly. Yeah.
We need IRL editing tools for human beings.
So that we need we need to invent a robot to do it.
Dude, imagine how sick that's going to be when you just fucking
you do the deed and then you go to the hospital and you just do get the
creator wrestler UI and you can just map it out exactly how you want.
Hell, yeah. Hell, yeah.
I want him to have shoulders that are 10 feet tall.
Just like my World of Warcraft characters. Yeah.
Hey, OK, I've got one last question here that is the most important.
And then we can wrap up.
It's chirps case moving castle asks, how does the rest of the PCP work with
the best guy ever without being super jealous for not being the best?
I still have that one question.
That's a very good reason because the best is subjective.
The best is a subjective term and there's nothing that Nate.
There's no work Nate does that I actually want to do to give a serious answer.
Well, hey, that's probably why you don't do it.
You know, we're all free agents out here in the world.
You're doing our own thing.
I'm going to say I'm going to say how does the rest of the PCP work with the best
guy ever? The truth is we don't we don't work.
Oh, which is actually which is actually a compliment to you, Mr.
Nate, best man that you keep the ship running very nicely.
And I'm glad you do.
How nice of you to say you get all you get all the all the stuff in order
so that I don't have to think about anything.
That's exactly. Yeah, I think a lot about how I want to make
everything easy for all you guys and for like my patrons.
So I always want to do things that I can do so that people will continue
to want to work with me at their own volition.
See, that's that's that's that actually kind of answers the other question
to because, Nate, you found a way to weaponize your autism to make all this
stuff work. And so you can pass that on to your son.
Yeah, you're not wrong.
Vincent will inherit the world that I give him and Charlottes will get the scraps.
The way my way, God intended, indeed.
All right. Well, I guess we're done.
Yeah, thanks for the questions, everybody.
Thanks for all those wonderful questions using hashtag ask PCP on the Twitter.
Oh, that was a good time.
Thanks for pledging, everybody in the patron discord.
We read most of those were from there.
If you just pledge one dollar, you get access to the patron lounge
and you get all that stuff, pledge five dollars to the patron
and you get all 10 of our bonus episodes that are out right now.
All 10. Unbelievable.
Absolutely decadent.
And that's that.
We got some merch.
You want to buy some PCB merch, red bubble links down below.
I think that's.
Oh, and of course, Tom's the links.
We got the podcast on iTunes and Google Play.
And of course, Ben's Kickstarter.
Last day, Oculus Rift.
Let's go guys.
Maybe maybe the even higher pledge could or a goal could be to get
Munchie, a Oculus Rift for the.
You know what? Yeah.
OK, if we if we if we make if I make a.
Yeah, if we make it pass that the next one will be to get Munchie and Oculus Rift.
So if if we're past six thousand by then,
then that's what then that's what we're going for.
Corruption loves company, as you can see.
All right.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
And we'll see you next week with another dank old meme.
Bye. Bye.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, I'm supposed to be working right now.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
Why did come?