Hey, it's a new day. It's a brand new dawn. It's a new episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast
here on theprocrastinatorspodcast.com, not on YouTube. Because YouTube just keeps lying.
They just keep lying to us. They hate us. We're being oppressed. We are being cancelled. We've
been cancelled. This is cancel culture. We've been cancelled culture right now by YouTube.
They don't want us on their platform. We've been de-platformed. And for what? For being
based all the time. We are constantly punished on all sides for doing our job too well. We
are called The Pro Crastinators. We are professional Crastinators. And yet, we're constantly getting
shit from our audience for procrastinating. We're constantly getting shit from YouTube
for, I don't know, being on YouTube, which is again, our job. Just trying to do our fucking
job. We're just getting shit on all the time. Everyone says, oh, Ben, where's slime and punishment?
Ben, where's the finale? Where's the new Endless War update? When's the new season starting?
Where's Vapors 2? Where's the- Where's my parts for the rap? Where's the Kuzo Mega
Kickstarter? Where's the Radcon Light Novel? Where's the- Yeah, Radcon Road to Radcon for
part five. Where's the OVA? Where's the dojin? Where's the- Where's the- Where's the- Where'd
my $34,000 go? They cry and weep and gnash their teeth. You know, the problem with the
theory of the $34,000 is that it doesn't feel real yet, because none of us have gotten
any of the money. No. Presumably, Nate is just like holding it in like an offshore Swiss
bank account. It is like earmarked to be spent on stuff, to be spent on like- There were
too many- And none of us are getting any of it until we've done all the- There's too
much post-production cost and some of us haven't even- Some of us are so lazy, we haven't
even submitted our receipts from Radcon yet. Or maybe only one of us is that lazy.
That was the first thing I did. Mine was mostly for food and stuff.
I'm really bad about that kind of shit. I mean, but I'm good at like- The way I've been
filing taxes- I don't remember if I've been reimbursed. I'm not sure if I've been reimbursed
for like food. I hope so. Have you even had to file taxes in the last few years?
Yeah. Yeah, of course, everybody does. No, I've done my taxes every year. And in fact,
I was doing my taxes like two days ago, and I realized that you can just apply for an
extension and get it extended to like October. And I did. And they gave me the extension
in like immediately. And so now I don't have to do them until October. It's pretty sweet.
Do you end up owing the government money? Oh, yes. Yes. Because as a self-employed
person, if you work for an employer, a lot of times they withhold your taxes anyway.
And then sometimes you get a rebate. But for me, nothing gets withheld. So yeah, I always
don't- But do you get anything back from being low income?
There is a- There are certain- Self-employment is rough for taxes. There are- Yeah, there
are like low- There are limits. Like there is a certain allowance of a few thousand dollars.
I think it's up to like maybe like two or three or four thousand dollars where basically
that much of your income is like- I think it's two thousand something is not counted.
So like the first amount, it's like you don't get tax on that. But after that, there is
like a certain amount and I am above that. So I do get taxed normally on everything
beyond that amount. And actually, if we're talking about taxes and I don't mind, I mean,
I don't know what the audience thinks about tax talk. Personally, I don't find it boring.
But I was doing it- I'm always interested because I have tax problems.
Last year, you know, I did the Vapors 2 Kickstarter and I got the money from it. But I didn't-
I didn't have the book ready. Incidentally, I have the book ready now and I'm going to
be getting it printed like this week. Like the time has come. It's a miracle. But so
I didn't- I didn't spend it last year. So theoretically, I would have had to pay taxes
on the entire amount even though, you know, a lot of it has to go towards production.
And I was sweating that. I'm going to get overtaxed on this shit. But it turns out there
is something called the accrual method of accounting, which long story short, is basically
just you checking a box that says, I want to count my later expenses for earlier, please.
And if you just say you're using the accrual method, you are allowed to consider future
expenses incurred by a previous thing, a transaction, as though they occurred at the
moment they were incurred- though they occurred when they were incurred rather than when you
actually paid them. So I can do that. And I- so I'm glad I was able to delay paying
my taxes because now I don't have to do it until October. So by then I will have, you
know, printed the books, gotten all the rewards and stuff paid for the shipping and all, which
is probably going to be another thousand dollars or so. So I'll be able to mark all
that as expenses off of that Kickstarter money.
The money behind all this stuff is the way it moves is so much more complex than people
think about because it's like, you see, like, okay, well, they just got this money and then
they used it for this thing. And it's like, yeah, but you spend it incrementally over
the course of the entire creation of the thing. So it's like, you have this money, yes, but
this money is for this thing. And it continues to be for this thing.
And it's not, it's not your money. I mean, it's not, yeah, this is true for Vapors,
it's true for the PCP, Radcon, it's probably true for everything. It's not your money,
or it shouldn't be your money until you have fully done everything you were going to do
with it. And then you can be like, okay, okay, I can keep whatever's left over.
That's the problem.
You know, fixing your leg, but you also cannot complete the project until the leg is fixed,
that it's like, in that sense, the money, it would be going towards the project if it
was used to fix your leg, you know?
Yeah, sure. Well, that's kind of like, that's sort of like borrowing against yourself. Do
you know what I mean? Sure, you might find yourself in an emergency situation needing
that money for something other than what, you know, a new expense, right? That wasn't
accounted for. And then it's like, well, I need to spend the money on that. I will then
have less money for the things that I expected to pay for. But what else can I do? Sure.
I mean, it kind of, it puts you in a no-win situation where either you can say, okay,
well, this money is exclusively for this project. I will not use any of, I will not
dip into this funding to fix my leg. However, in order, if that is the case, then in order
to fix my leg, I will have to either incur a separate debt or I will have to like, you
know, have somehow work hard enough to have the money to just pay for it, you know, without
having to incur debt. Either way, you're saddling yourself with more work than the thing that
you're supposed to do, which in itself will postpone the thing that you're supposed to do.
So either you're postponing it because you're not using the money to fix yourself or you use
the money to fix yourself, the project, assumably can get, you know, further along. However, it
also now requires more funding as some of the funding was diverted to emergency relief, you
know. When you're like indie crowdfunded, going over budget just means that you're paying for
it. So if something happens and you end up over budget, that's just out of your pocket.
Right. And the onus always falls on you as a business person to have made a good decision
about knowing how much money you needed. And the fact of the matter is that indeed,
people have no fucking concept of how much money will be needed in most situations. Like,
and there's like, you'll go over budget every time. Well, there's an amount. There's an amount
that you know to account for. And then there's things that you just will not know to account for
until the time comes, either in terms of time, invest like for us on like Radcon four, it wasn't
we didn't fuck up on the money end of things. We fucked up on the time end of things, like
just overloading an amount of things that we thought we could do, get done in a shorter
amount of time than we could, you know, a little bit, a little bit. And even so, like, I mean,
some of the things are things that, you know, I don't think anybody expected to be done quickly,
like the OVA, like, obviously, the reason that's in the works is that there's a fucking animation
being made for it. Like, it's not because of us. It's because it's a big project that's in other
people's hands, you know. Well, it's, yeah, on the one hand, it's a big project that's in other
people's hands. On the other hand, we have never done a thing like that before. So we kind of had
to like discuss like, how are we going to go about doing this? And then like try and figure out
what's the best way people know we have not made it hit a patient before, you know, but like,
in terms of other things where it's like, okay, like the diss track, like the exact nature of how
we were going to do it, like, we didn't have a proper microphone set up to get like the song
done right at Radcon. We got a demo version done that we could record the music video against.
But like, there was not enough time to, you know, come back and record a proper studio version on
top of everything else that was going on. And so in the aftermath of that, it's like, okay, well,
now everybody has to go and find time on their own to, you know, record for this thing. And the
work wasn't over at that point. Exactly. The work was not all done within the time that was allotted
for the work to be done. And then like you and Tom also had to do, you know, like shipping and
product fulfillment, right? Making shirts and posters. Well, Tom did. I mean, all I had to do
was mail him the posters, which I did a week ago. Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, sure. But yeah,
so I mean, for Tom especially. But I mean, you know, we had a portion of the budget earmark to
like cover the estimate, the estimate, like I got paid for drawing the poster and, you know,
he's getting paid for like the the the chipping and the and the printing the stuff. Yeah. Yes.
It's very involved. And it has been like, like Radcon for the event lasted, you know, was it 10
days? Yeah. But like, in a very real sense, it's still it's still going on, like it's still in
the process of happening and unfolding. Well, that's how it was for all of them. I mean, like
with Radcon 2, it took so long. Yeah, Radcon 3 took a year. All of them. Radcon 3 took a year for
all the content to come out. I was still working on 10 paces and draw a year later. I think
Pleven the Weave took like a whole year for the whole season to come out. What the hell are you
stirring around? I'm glad you asked, did you? Oh, God. This is this is this is coffee. And this
is a half a pint, half a pint of mint chocolate chip keto ice cream mixed into it. Yes. I'm
glad you noticed that I was loudly stirring this cup so that you would ask me what was in it.
No, I'm I'm stirring it because I want to drink its contents because they're delicious. But I'm
very excited by this by this new recipe that I've started describe it. That's it. It's just
it's a it's a mason jar full of coffee that I dumped half a pint of low carb mint chocolate
chip ice cream into and mixed it up and I'm drinking it. Good. Oh, I put some stevia in there
too. I guess I was thinking what's the word there's a word for when you put ice cream in coffee. It
might be macchiato, but I'm not sure. So I think this is a keto, a keto macchiato.
A keto macchiato auto. Yes. Patent pending. How does it feel to me the most like you're like
you're like a budget version of an insufferable hipster.
Thanks, man. It's like I appreciate that. That's like what makes it it's it's like,
like you would just be like a douchebag. But the fact that you're doing it all on your own
gumption, like you made it entirely by yourself is so respectable that it's like, wow, he's really
putting effort into this fucking like. Yeah, I, I mean, sure, like, I started, I started ordering
out food like like two weeks ago, I went on a kick where I would order food all the time. Yeah.
And like, but then I realized like, oh my god, like with delivery fucking food,
like with delivery fees and like you got to tip your fucking delivery guy now, your door dash or
whatever. And it's like, it's like, it's like 25 fucking dollars to get a burger. I actually just
pay for the grub hub plus and door dash premium because of the fact that I have been ordering
so much that it is legitimately benefits me, especially because with grub hub plus,
every time you spend like 100 bucks or so, they give you like a $10 rebate or whatever. So
it's like, it's definitely a system that entraps you. It's like, if you could, if you can afford
to be in the system, then it is more affordable than trying to like just order from it regularly,
you know, but like, yeah, but you'd have to order enough for it to pay off. And then at that point,
you're spending a lot on eating out and you shouldn't be, but that's right. Yeah, that's what I did.
That's what I did with Instacart, which is like the grocery delivery service. They would normally
charge a fee per delivery. But if you do their, their like premium program, you know, deliveries
free for like a one time yearly fee, and I calculated it out. And it was like way cheaper
to just pay the yearly fee or it would have been, except that then I stopped using it because the
pandemic hit. Although I might go back to using it at some point. It's funny that you stopped with
the pandemic hit because I feel like a lot of them started with it. Well, they stopped delivering
for a while. So with, and that was bad, but then they pay for that. They should fucking rebate
you that period of time. Like, it was, it was actually a pretty brief. It was actually a pretty
brief period of time. I'm not that upset about it. But even on top of that, they don't, they don't
take a, they don't take EBT, which seems like a big oversight. Even Amazon, Amazon started taking
EBT recently, which is like a real game changer. So like since, since Instacart stop doesn't take
EBT. And since, you know, I don't want to fucking take public transit to like, Wegmans or something
which is cheaper. I've just been shopping for food at Whole Foods. And like, yes, I know that it is
more expensive to buy food from Whole Foods, but they take, it's close to me. So I don't have to
put myself in contact with people and they take EBT so I can spend my fucking government monopoly
money on it. Suckers. It's great. It's, it's, it is amazing. It's amazing. But ordering out, ordering
out. Groceries, you know, gotta do it. You know, it's a necessary expense. One must, one must.
Ordering out, I, I was like, I have to stop this. I don't care how good boneless,
buffalo wings from wings over are. I cannot, I cannot maintain this lifestyle. It's, it's,
it's especially if I were to like, I could technically afford it. But if I keep doing this,
I'm going to find myself at the end of next year, getting hit with that fucking tax and I'll be like,
oh shit, I forgot. Oh shit, I forgot. I'm a self-employed peon and I owe like fucking half
my fucking money that I made to the government and now I don't have it because I spend it on five
guys. Then how much variety is there in the stuff that you order? Because that's a big part of why
I order so much is that like, I just like to eat tons of different kinds of food. So it's like, you
know, um, in the stuff that I order, uh, well, I don't do it very often. I ordered, I ordered Indian
food. No, no, it was Greek food like a month ago and I didn't like it that much and I didn't think
it was worth the money. So I didn't order for a while and then someone in my house ordered
buffalo wings and I was like, yeah, I'll get in on that. And they were so good that I had like,
had to get some more. So I ordered a bunch more over the next week. So I guess there's not that
much, I guess there's not that much variety. I'll order food if like I get like a particular thing
that I'm like, I want some of this. I must have this.
Hearing you describe the way that you ate Greek food made me realize something because
I think that most, most Americans, they like, they just eat American food
like almost exclusively and then like once a month or so are like, oh, I'll mix it up. I'll like,
have some Mexican or like some Chinese or like some Thai food if I'm fucking really feeling
freaky. And like, this is very strange to me because like, I mean, when I was growing up,
I ate like nothing but TV dinners and bullshit and like, my mom became a vegetarian in like 2001
and her cooking just degraded over time because she doesn't eat what she's cooking. So she doesn't
give a fuck, you know, so like, and nobody else in the house could cook.
Imagine being a vegetarian mom and cooking for your non vegetarian family.
I don't blame her at all because, you know, I mean, it's just a hassle and, you know,
nobody really appreciates it or helps out. I respect it. I respect it that you would be like
principled enough to be like, I want to make the world a better place. I think being a vegetarian
is a good way to do that. But I don't believe in imposing my values on others. So I'm still
going to cook. I'm so I'm still going to cook me that I don't believe in. Right. Yeah. Yeah. You
know, if you're not eating the food, it's really hard to make it good, you know, and like, yeah.
So my mom has become a better chef, apparently now that she and my dad are both vegan, and she
could just make vegan dishes because obviously it's to their palate. I don't like almost any vegan
food. So I have a roommate who is a loose vegetarian. And I don't know. I don't think I don't think
I don't like the things he makes. And I but I don't think it's because it's vegetarian.
I think he just under salts everything. I think that's his problem. Yeah. If he just
fixed that, he'd be fine. I mean, it's always just a matter. I mean, I used to not even eat like
any kind of dish that did not have meat in it. It's like I did not even see the value of a dish
without meat until like May started cooking dishes that are like actually good, you know,
like not to say that she often makes up with no meat in it necessarily or that that's my favorite
shit, but it can be good, obviously. And like, sure, you don't we don't need to eat anywhere
close to as much meat as we do. You know, I think meat is good for you for the human experience,
but you don't have to eat it even every day, you know, no, to get to get the benefits necessary
from it. But like, but nonetheless, I'm a big time meat person. I like to eat a lot of fucking
meat if I can. But like same. And I tend to favor like just getting a sandwich, which is like no
fucking lettuce on it or anything like that. But like, I in terms of flavor palette, I'm interested
in a huge variety of styles of preparing meat, or you know, of putting it with other things. And
like, so much of American food is just meat plus lettuce, tomato, onion. And like, sure, not that
I'm not fine with those things, but I do not find that to be a very interesting flavor combination.
I don't like lettuce very much. I'm not a big fan of tomato. I put, I put love onion curry. I put
curry powder on my colleague on my steamed more sauteed. It's gonna half steamed half sauteed
cauliflower. I put curry powder on it the other day. I sprinkled some mozzarella on top. I don't
use curry powder very often, but this was like, Oh, it's perfect. Oh, it's beautiful. I tend to crave
like, I want to eat fucking onions and mushrooms and fucking peppers. And like, you know,
shit that would be in a curry, or shit that would be in a soup or something like that.
But also stuff that would be on a sandwich sometimes it's just like, I want to mix it up. I
want to be eating different stuff every day so that I know I'm getting like all the different
types of fucking nutrients, all the different types of immunities, you know, I want to be
fucking ready for any situation with through my body's fucking makeup. I want my body to have
evolved to deal with all kinds of different things, you know what I mean? And so, so I try to mix it
up. But like, you know, it's just funny because most of what you actually can get in America is
not like authentic cuisine from places. Like, like if you get Chinese food, almost all of them are
the same unionized Chinese American food, American idea of Chinese food. It's like Tex-Mex. Yeah,
like it's like Chinese. It's like, it's funny because it's funny because it's like Tex-Mex,
except that the Mexican restaurants are also like that in America. We're like, they're also like,
what we think of as like real Mexican food, i.e. not Taco Bell, like Mexican family restaurants are
also like generally the same unionized like template idea, like American idea of the Mexican
place where they're serving quesadillas, which are not even a Mexican invention, you know, like,
yeah. So I definitely add like a, I've definitely been to like one or two like pretty authentic
little like hole in the wall, like like Mexican place, like in California, I went to one or two.
There was a place near our house in Boston that was like, it was like an expensive sort of like
higher end place, but it was like much more like it was clearly Mexican food, like like someone
from Mexico making Mexican food, but like at a higher, you know, kind of class Mexican food.
So not necessarily like street Mexican food, but like it was not the same menu as what would be
at like a standard family restaurant, you know, and like there's a Chinese restaurant in my town
called Jade Villa that I highly recommend anybody who happens to be in Virginia Beach.
It's like right by town center and they actually have two menus. They have one that's like the
standard American Chinese menu and then they have the Chinese menu where it's like frog legs,
jellyfish, fucking, uh, you know, all kinds of crazy shit that is awesome and is stinky tofu.
They do not have stinky tofu, but we did go to that place that had it. Well,
actually they might, maybe I just didn't, I've never looked for it. Were you there, were you there
when econ got the stinky tofu at the place in China town? The story was told to me many times.
It's so bad, so disgusting. I can't believe it. You can't insist it's good though, so whatever.
I'm not like, no guys are free. Well, yeah, I'm at the end. I mean, I'm at the end.
He's a chocolate chips as well, you know, a cup, a cup. Yeah. Well, like literally. Well, did you,
okay, uh, he was on. Oh no, do we want to get into that? I mean, go ahead. I don't care. This is public.
He was on, okay. He came on Glinkstream. Do you know who Glink is?
Ah, fuck that guy. Yeah, I know. Yeah, you don't like that guy? Well, he was.
Not even a little bit. He was doing a live stream and econ went on there. Econ is pals with him.
And he, he was asked by somebody about his love of NTR porn. You know what NTR is, right?
Netsur, Netsurari. Yes. Yeah. Is that's like, that's getting cucked, right? Well, it's,
there's three perspectives on it. And as econ put it, he said that he is 30, he is spends
30% of the time in all three of the perspectives. So he gets off on being any of the three people
in the scenario, which is to say. Oh, sure. Yeah. The cuck, the cuck, the wife or the bull.
All three of them, he's into being all three. So. Oh no. Oh no, I can't, I can't hear anything.
Eleazar, Eleazar, cut this part. Okay. I'm back. You can, you can, you can roll another blunt if you
want. I don't care. Okay. Okay. But I'm back. So, so you mean, right, 30% bull, 30% cuck, 30% wife,
right? That's exactly. Sure. I totally get it. I totally get it. Yeah. So, you know,
as far as I'm concerned, if you're 30% cuck, you're a cuck. 30% cuck. Sure. Yeah, sure. Any
percent cuck is a cuck. It's like, it's like, it's like being white, you know, if any part, if
you're at all not white, if you have even a drop of non white, you're not white anymore, right?
If you have even a drop of cuck, you're no longer a bull. It's funny you say that because I think
that goes both ways with race. I think that if you're mixed at all, you're just mixed and like
nobody will have you, you know? Oh boy. I mean, it's like, there's a sect of people who do not
want to say, there's a sect of people who do not want to say that Obama was the first black
president because he is right because he's half white, half white. So, well, yeah, I mean, that,
I mean, it's a big, big topic. We won't get into all, we can't possibly cover it all. But like,
neither of us is really in a position to have a strong opinion about it. I guess that's what
we're trying to say. I mean, most people say that Obama was a black president, even though he is
demonstrably half white. But yeah, it's kind of a fringe position to say he's not black because
like, he's black because he looks black. And like, at the end of the day, when you get right down to
it, that's what race is. It's like, you can make like, you can claim some kind of genetic lineage
and like, yeah, maybe, but at the end of the day, what you really mean by white is just that you
look white and that's basically it. Then are you familiar with the rapper Logic? No. Okay, Logic
presents one of the most interesting scenarios in my mind because so Logic is is is is half black,
half white, I think. Yeah. And he raps a lot about being but being half and like not really
fitting in with either crowd, right? And there's a lot of people who talk about how they they
they're sick of hearing him talk about or they're sick of him sort of like talking about that
experience because of the fact that he doesn't really look black at all. And so it's like hard
to believe that he would have faced the same prejudice that they do. And when I think about
that, I'm like, well, aren't you exhibiting right now the prejudice that he is speaking about
in the songs by saying so. But at the same time, so before I ever saw what Logic looked like,
he does look, I mean, I can, I can kind of see it, right? Okay, I can kind of see it. He looked
like though, but he looks, he looks, he looks pretty white. Look up what he looks like in
Rick and Morty, though. This is really funny to me because I saw his appearance at Rick and Morty
before I knew what he looked like and assumed that he looked like this. And that made me think
like, oh, yeah, he looks like he's like mixed. He looks like he would be like considered a black guy.
But it's just funny because they present him as looking like especially mixed, but he doesn't.
He kind of looks way whiter than that in real life. They got his chin wrong. It's funny to me,
like the thing that looks the most black about him is like his hair. He's his like kind of like
curly hair. I mean, to me, they gave him like these big lips and like, he just kind of has like,
it kind of has like normal. I mean, I'm being, I'm being Eurocentric when I say normal white guy
lips, you know what I mean? I absolutely believe that like Logic has experienced what he talks about
because like, from my perspective as a white guy, I look at him and I think, well, he doesn't really
look white enough to fit in with white guys. Like I know that, you know, I don't know if black guys
know that, but I know that. But him the way he looks in real life. I think that a lot of black
people think that he wouldn't be singled out because he looks too white because, okay, black
people are very fixated on skin tone. Like in my experience in going to black school,
black kids talk about each other as like, oh, that light skinned guy, that dark skinned guy,
that mid-tone person, you know, they pay a lot of attention because they think that
there's like a sliding scale of privilege based on literally how dark you are. And the funny thing
is that in those communities, that is even more true because of the fact that people
perpetuate the stereotypes. Particularly African kids get bullied a lot in African American
communities. For being the darkest. Right. For being the darkest and for being just culturally
different, you know, because they're from Africa. Like I'm talking about literal like, you know,
kids who are from Africa who come over and trying to adapt. But like, you know, and I saw all of
this as myself an outsider at the school, but, you know, I was literally like a white kid from
the suburbs who just somehow ended up here, you know, so like, I didn't feel like I was,
I didn't feel like I was being singled out so much as just like, what the fuck is this person
doing here? They have nothing to do with the infrastructure of what's going on here, you know.
Infrastructure.
Yeah. But like, I look at logic and I think like, if this kid went to an all black school,
then they're going to treat him like a white kid. And if he went to an all white school,
they're going to treat him like a mixed kid. I know that would be the case because I went to
both and I've known kids who were mixed and I know how they're treated. It's kind of hard to
tell in some of these pictures, he looks completely white. And then in others, it's like, okay, I
can kind of see it. So I don't know. Maybe. Yeah.
It's just the white people. I guess what I think that like, people who have like, I think when
you have a racial, like when you are, when you are a minority race, you feel particularly like
there's nothing I could do about this. And I'm just being shamed for for who I am. But it's like,
when you don't have that, they still find a way, like whatever is, whatever there is about you
that is different or or weird, you will be bullied for, you know, and it's like the severity of the
bullying or like where it happens, where you can get away with what is different depending on who
you are. But that's always the case. It's like, you can always get away with being certain people
in certain places and not in other places. And, you know, maybe being white, there's the
like gives you far more places that you can feel secure. But that is also under the circumstance
that you are white and like normal, you know, you're like, yeah. And you'll definitely be
bullied. You're definitely liable to be bullied for any any difference that you have from what's
perceived as the normal status quo. That's definitely true. I will say that for me, like
I as a, you know, as somebody who as a child, you know, I was a signed male at birth, told people
said I looked like a girl. I didn't like the people said that about me. But I did not attempt to
change myself. I could have though. And in my mind, that was always like a choice I was making.
It's like, I could choose to fit into society. I just would be really depressed and I wouldn't
want to. So if I can get away with living being like, you know, weird looking, then I'll just
I'll just do it. And like, I'll put up with whatever the consequences are, even if that means
getting bullied or looked down on. And like, you know, I understand that that's not viable for
everybody. And I never I never put myself in dangerous situations or had to be put in dangerous
situations because of my parents taking good care of me, both being around, having a house,
I didn't have to leave, you know, not having to involve myself in anything dangerous in order
to survive, which is something that both of my parents had to do. Like, they both had to commit
crimes to survive when they were teenagers, you know, so like, I understand, like, I understand
both why people would do that. And also, like, like, I would never because I've been I've been in
a situation where I didn't have to. And I understand that life is just better when you don't have to
commit crimes, you know, that's true. Definitely. So like, you know, when when the when the only
when you just commit crimes for fun, it's like way better than when you when you got to do it.
Yeah, it's better when it's when it's an unforced error. So yeah, when you can choose the crimes
that you want to commit because you feel secure and committing them were morally righteous and
in doing so, not because like, if I don't commit this crime, I won't be able to eat tonight. And
I'm not sure how many nights I can live if I don't eat, you know, right? Yeah, which is what poor
people experience, especially teenagers, you know, yeah. And like, in in their minds, they will
convince themselves that it's like normal, because it's just like, that's all they know. It's like,
yeah, crimes. Yeah, well, well, that level of life, that level of like, because that's what
society is expecting them to just continue on. Like society's expectation is, okay, well, your
life may be shit. But if you work really hard and get good grades, because you are smart, then
you'll make it through. And it's like, okay, well, like, like, make it through to do what, you know,
like, what am I, what am I aiming for exactly here, you know, and that these people just kind of
fall by the wayside and society doesn't make it through to make it through to, you know,
take out a bunch of loans and go to college and do it again, and then take out a bunch more loans
and go to, you know, grad school and do it again or whatever, and take out a bunch more loans and
like, you know, get a mortgage on a house or whatever. So they're just constantly trying to
meme you. It's the whole, this world is run by ad agents and intelligence agents. And most of them,
most of the ones with the power are just doing it. They're just in it for the boy pussy.
Like, okay, that's not where I was expecting you to go with that. But okay, I've, okay,
through the realization that almost every billionaire has been implicated as a pedophile,
I've come to start to wonder when you say when you say implicated as a pedophile, what do you
mean by that? Like associated with Jeffrey Epstein having gone to his island,
implicated in child sex trafficking, or child pornography having, or just being, you know,
being basically FBI case files or people who are protected by the CIA. I have no doubt that
like lots of them are, you know, billionaire pedophiles. I mean, I don't know, like, like,
having been being associated with Epstein isn't, isn't like a strong enough link for me because
like Epstein was a well connected billionaire himself. He probably knew all kinds of guys.
And part of, part of what him and, and, and just laying Maxwell, we're trying to do is to make
themselves constantly photobombing everybody so that everybody's implicated with them, you know.
And I definitely think there's different levels. That's why, like, and I know this.
Did you see the thing about Gislein's Reddit account? Oh my god, that shit is fucking incredible.
That is the revolution of the century. Karma account on Reddit. And she was like,
The first account to ever reach a million karma. She was like,
she was like a moderator of view of world news, I think, like a big subreddit.
People are speculating that she may have actually owned Reddit for a brief period
that like she had actually bought it and like, and that she's like literally one of the most
influential Reddit users of all time. And I completely believe it. But okay, you have to
think about it this way, because this is, this is all plays into why I was thinking about this,
because like, why would you feel the need to become a billionaire? Like, for me personally,
that's a great question. I love this question. Like, let's see where it leads us.
I mean, Ben, you, you are probably the person I know who is the most satisfied with the lowest
quality of life. And I mean that as a compliment, because I honestly do admire that about you,
because I'm so I, I'm somebody who like, when I picture like, what is the ideal way to live?
I think of like being just like a mountain man in a cabin, like growing my own shit off the land,
letting the insects have my crops and shit, you know, like not using no pesticides, nothing
in natural Henry David Thoreau thing with the rats eating your potato or the moles eating
your potatoes. I don't know that reference, but it's probably the same thing as the Arjuna episode
that I am referencing. So like, you know, who just joined this call? Gibbo just jumped in.
Hey, are you recording? Yes. Okay, we're fucking going to town. So I was just explaining to Ben
that like, what I consider to be the like, that my picture of like an ideal way of life,
like morally is like being, you know, like a mountain morally like, like, like morally and
also like, I think this would be, I think this would be like the most peaceful way to live your
life to like live in tune with nature out in the mountains, like growing enough crops to just take
care of however many people there are around, you know, fostering a healthy relationship with the
planet as you just live your life casually without really concerning yourself too much with like
advancing, you know, things like culturally or whatever. That's really hard though. It is,
it is difficult and you have to basically decide that that's going to be your whole life, you know,
is like, is homesteading. And I think that the purpose of society is that we don't need everybody
to do that. A few people can do it enough to provide for everybody. But I think that we have,
I think that we are, we build our societies too big that like ideally there would be more people
doing the agriculture for the benefit of, you know, making each community like more
agriculturally stable, less reliant on factory farming and all the other bullshit and factory,
everything factory education, more locally sourced. Yeah, like I decentralized, decentralized.
Yes, more decentralized because like when we think about like the ideals of like communism and like
what it should implement in the population is that like more people want to work for the government
because of the fact that there is no higher station really. Like the greatest purpose you can
have is towards the betterment of the community. But like communism only really, in my mind,
like makes sense on a community scale, like within one isolated community that has its own rules.
And like the, I think that there's a good reason to have like, I have a counterpoint to that.
Counterpoint. Part of the reason that and econ will, you know, make fun of me because
I'm so predictable for saying this demonstrably true thing. The part of the reason why communism
has never succeeded, has never really been implemented is because you can't really have it
in on a local level or even on a national level. You can't really have real communism,
a classless moneyless, stateless society in a world where you have to engage in trade
with other nations who do have class and money. So basically, I mean,
communism can only really work in like a completely isolated society or on an entirely
global scale. Okay, so by that definition, is there any meaningful difference between
communism and anarchy? Um, well, because it sounds like you're describing my ideal anarchy
by that. I mean, I guess, I guess the ideal anarchist society is also a classless moneyless,
stateless society. So I guess they are similar. I guess I don't know exactly what the distinction
would be. I mean, I think to me, the main reason that I run away from the idea of communism and
prefer the idea of anarchy is just that like, with communism, it's always going to come down to
someone's making the rules and about like, what is ideal? And like,
I don't know who, I don't know how people would become a part of the decision making process
of what are those ideals without like, democratic process of some kind, you know?
Yeah, well, yes. I mean, part of like, part of the idea, and I don't know exactly,
I'm not sure if this is like a Marx thing, or if this is like a later thing. But like,
part of the idea is that you, you move towards a society in which you abolish, well,
basically, you democratize everything. And the idea is that like, the more you democratize
everything, not just government, but like, you know, the workplace and stuff like that and like
community life. And the more you democratize everything, like the details kind of take
care of themselves. I was reading, I think it was in capital, but I was reading somewhere,
where no, it might have been a video, I don't remember. But the idea is like, if the more
things become democratized, like we don't have to speculate on, well, what does civilization
look like under communism? How do we handle this or that or the other thing? The answer is, we don't
know. We will find out when we get to a point where things are fully democratized and people can
decide things for themselves communally. And then they decide, and it might vary from place to place,
right? Like one community might run things one way and another another way, right? I don't know.
I guess lately I've been on this vein of thinking that like, the point is not, okay,
how do we structure society? How do we just, how exactly do we redistribute everything?
The point is the democratization wherein we just make those decisions as we need to.
Ideally, society should be in a flow state where we can make decisions as quickly as possible.
And like, I think the biggest problem with the government is too much bureaucracy and like,
which is ultimately like the, you know, what makes me fall, I guess, libertarian,
because I want the government to be smaller. But it's not about, it's not even for me about the
power of the government's being smaller. It's about the government's power to be reactive,
to like change its mind, to, you know, like, think about like how hard it is for somebody to be
let out of prison who, who did not commit the crime, where like, we've reassessed the case,
we know that like, there's not proper evidence, but like, it takes 15 years for this person to
get released, you know, that's a product of like, over bloated bureaucracy. And there's,
there's a lot of things that get caught up in that. And it's like, we need both, we, it's like
both going in and out, I guess it's like, the government needs to be able to react quicker,
and then also to take it back quicker, you know, the, the, yeah, the idea of the bureaucracy,
there cuts both ways, because on the one hand, the situation you describe is bad. But on the
other hand, that situation also means that there are all these procedures that we have to go through
before someone gets the death penalty, right? Like that's the reason why giving someone the
death penalty is more expensive than just giving them life in prison. Because there's all this red
tape to go through. And it's because we don't want to do this by accident. We want to have these
procedures to make absolutely sure that we're not just doing this willy-nilly.
I personally think it's weird that we even have the death penalty. Like, I don't, I don't really
get the point of it, you know. Yeah, the, there is a great video, I think it's his newest video
by Sean, where he talks about the death penalty. And yeah, like the point of the death penalty
is basically just to make people, like, feel better? Like, not the victim. It's to make, like,
it's because people in society are mad. Like, the argument is that it's a deterrent. The evidence
isn't really there to suggest that it actually is a deterrent. The purpose is because, like, people
who are mad about crimes want punishment. And that's the point. So, like, yeah, I mean, at some
point I will finish Foucault's crime and punishment and form a full... Foucault. Wait, that's Dostoyevsky.
No, what's the name of the book I'm thinking of then? Not crime and punishment.
It's a similar title, though. The Foucault book. Slime and Punishment. About, about, um,
Uh, that's F-O-U-C-A-U-L-T-Y-O-U-R-F-C-R-F-C-K, uh, Foucault. Foucault.
It's the one about fucking the death penalty and why it's a good, and I haven't read it yet.
It's scary. I don't, I don't know. Well, actually, it's more about why... I haven't read any Foucault.
It's not even, actually, it's not about why the death penalty is good. It's about why public
execution is good and why the death penalty is bad, actually, because it's not as good as public
execution. Because it's not public enough? Discipline and punish, that is the name. It's not televised.
Hmm, I see. World's deadliest executions. Uh, that's a Simpsons, Simpsons reference.
Hey, you know what's real fucked up just thinking about this? Is that everything I own and have ever
owned was made by somebody I will never meet and have never met, like, everything, except for the
like, the small, like, little bits of, you know, things that people physically may and give to me.
Brownish shit that you have. That's a little thing, that's a little thing we like to call
alienation from the means of production, my friends. That's, you better, you're talking
straight marks right now. You're gonna get, you're gonna fucking radical.
No, I feel that too. Like, my ideal, my present ideal is like, I want to have basically just like
a town of people I think are cool, where everybody makes their own shit, and it's just a self-sustaining
economy of people making cool shit and supporting one another on the basis of making cool shit.
I was, I was watching this. I like that idea, but it reminds me of something. Like,
yesterday I found this channel called Tasting History, where a guy cooks recipes from like,
cookbooks from like, Victorian times or like medieval times or even like ancient Greek stuff.
Like, he made this fish sauce called Garum out of like, fermented fish paste. It's like, it's like,
he does like, historically accurate reenactments of food that people in the ancient world used
to eat. It's pretty interesting, but he, he, there's one video, I think he's making some like,
some old bread. I forget what the name of the bread is, but he is talking, he talks about
Chaucer's The Canterbury Tales, which I read in high school, but I don't remember it all.
And I guess in Chaucer, Chaucer I guess really hates millers. Like, he basically thinks that all
millers are like, greedy businessmen and like thieves and like, rapscallions and rogues and
like, thinks they should be put to death because like, repeat offenders, right? For like, people
that are like, like cutting their, cutting their flour with stuff that's not flour. He's good.
I guess, I guess like, in medieval times, in a time when you would have lived in a little village
where like, one person makes the bread and another person like, you know, forges your plow or whatever,
the millers, there was an idea that these people, you know, owned the means of production in the
sense that like, everyone's got to eat and they're the ones that are feeding everyone,
but they're greedy and like, they'll overcharge you for the bread. Like, they'll fill it full
of air. So you have to pay more. They'll put their thumb on the scale. So like, so they,
you think you're buying more than you really are. A golden thumb. The phrase was, he has a golden
thumb, which both implies wealth, but also it was like, the thumb is, the thumb is heavy. The thumb
is heavy on the scale. So it's, he's charging you for more than you're actually getting. Millers,
dude, fuck millers. I hate them. Maybe this is arrogant. Everything wrong with society.
Maybe this is arrogant of me to think, but I feel like throughout history, like the problem has
always just been that like, people can't really like, communicate well. Like, I think that like,
communication has never been very good. And that like, in the past, I think we really like,
underestimate how fucking confused everybody was about one another's intentions and like,
how difficult it probably was for people who were not, who didn't know each other and like,
literally everything that was going on with one another all the fucking time, because that's
how people like were. It's like, people in your community, you literally know everything about
them. You see them constantly. There is no lapse in your understanding. But like, people were so,
because of that, people are super tribal and like, people from other communities, like, even if it's
just the next neighborhood over, it's just like, I have no idea who this person is. And then like,
this guy's from Shelbyville. I don't trust him. Yeah. I don't know. And I think that's the street
who are they are. Well, that's the thing. I think that the creation of the nuclear family
created it so that every household became its own community, because we started just like,
the idea of the, the, the fifties idea of the family is like, you personally have to write
everything. You don't rely on anybody. You own everything in your house. You have your own copy
of everything that you could possibly need. And therefore, you're self-reliant. But like,
people think that they need to be self-reliant to be successful. And it's like, you don't,
you could literally share these things with other people and live. The nuclear family is like,
a more recent idea. Like, like, obviously, people have like, lived like, just them and their partner
and their kids. Like that obviously always happened. But that wasn't always seen as like, the ideal
or the modern standards. You know, people lived in like, big, like, like extended family dwellings
or whatever. Like that was, that's normal for a lot of human history. I think it's a result of
having a culture of excess and proposing that excess as necessity because of the fact by way
of sociopathy. Because it's like, in America, we're told to fear our neighbor. Do not associate with
other people. Other people are scary. You should stay away from them and have all your own things,
you know? And so you convince yourself that you need to own, like say, a microwave, right? Like,
how often in the day does one person use a microwave? And imagine if there was like, a
microwave somehow in like the middle of the street in your, in like a cul-de-sac, right? And
everybody shared the same microwave. Probably wouldn't really be that much competition over the
microwave. Like, you know, point being, you know, and think about how much money is spent on all
eight people in that cul-de-sac owning their own microwave. It's like, this is what the government
wants to be because that level of consumption causes you to spend all this money that literally,
you could just go to your neighbor, if you knew your neighbor, you could just go to their house
and use their microwave, you know? And this is something that kids understand because kids are
in a position where they, you know, they have no power and so parents will let them sort of,
you know, rely on them a little bit more or adults in general might do that, especially in
suburban places. But like, you know, that doesn't mean that those like that, like nothing changes
about that when they grow up other than that they become more afraid of other people and more, you
know, uh, insistent on self-reliance. I'm just realizing that that was like the cause of so much
social distance, like not to use that term. Like the idea that I could like live in a rented flat
with a bunch of other people and share like a bathroom is like, oh, gross. I don't want to
have to like talk to people. I don't want to say anything to people down the hall. I just
want to have my own house. I want to buy my own house so I don't even have to talk to people.
That's what I'm doing. That's what my big dream is to live alone completely. And it's much more
expensive. I don't know. It's just like, why? Because, uh, what's the, you're not saying this is
a good thing. I'm saying this is like how society is meant to be. You're saying that it's not a
good thing, but then like, okay, so like, so you don't want it, right? Because it sounds like it
sucks. I think it's, I think it's a difference of faith and it's a strange one. It's interesting.
I think that, uh, for me, at least it's like, I have very little faith that I'm going to share a
house with somebody and it won't suck. But there are certain people who like sharing a house with
you was not a problem for me because you are pretty much completely on your own anyways.
Like you don't have a lot of space. Yeah. Uh, and, and you pretty much keep to yourself anyways.
You, you're not very like demanding of attention or anything. You, you, you don't cost much money.
You don't like, you don't use a lot of, you don't use very much electricity. You don't use very
much water. You don't use very much food, you know? Uh, so, and you eat my leftovers. So like,
if anything, you're helpful. Uh, that's like, that's, that's such a win with a real symbiotic
relationship. Everybody fucking gets what they need. Beautiful. You are very, let's me eat their
leftovers now when throws their leftovers away. I hate it. And Tom is very similar to you. You
know, having him as a house guest, never really a problem. The only concern could be like privacy,
just not being able to like walk around my house naked comfortably, you know? Right. Right. Which
never stopped you anyways. Well, but it doesn't to this day. Yeah. But like, I, I, so, you know,
to me, it's like, there's, there are certain people who I'm willing to share a house with.
Uh, I don't imagine there being that many people who I could, but I think it's the fact that I even
have faith that I could have a super comfortable home environment where it's like just me and the
closest people and we could be as open as we want is like a romantic idea to me. And I think that
you, Ben, are just somebody who like on some level just doesn't really believe that that's
necessarily true or even need it. Or maybe you just feel so comfortable that you just don't even
care. And like, sorry, it's easy for you that I don't believe what's true that you could have
a situation where you would be 100% comfortable at all times with another person.
Um, no, no, no, no, like the lack of beer. You're correct. It's kind of like in a strange way.
The, the, the idea that your thought in your head of like, okay, well, I will never have a 100%
uh, like comfort zone. So I might as well just have whatever comfort zone, like I don't,
I'm I'm actually really confused what you're saying. Okay, what the point you're making about me or about society or
What I'm trying to say is that
for me, it's like
If I were to live in a house, let's say like okay, I lived with you in DeVoo, right?
And living with you in DeVoo was fine and and shade and shade shade and amber
Yeah, they were forget they were around because we saw so little they were never there. Yeah
That situation was fine because like you're all people who I am comfortable around
I'm comfortable sharing a house with you, right?
But like obviously I wouldn't do everything that I would do in my own room in the middle of the house, right?
Like how many times yeah, how many times that I come to your room and you're like wait a minute
I'm naked. I have to put on clothes, you know usually right so like there's a certain level of you have a comfort zone of your room
But like you step out of that to go into the house and like for me
It's like I like having a house where the whole house is all my comfort zone and
The only way that can be possible is if the only people sharing the house with me are people
I'm completely comfortable with you know, but if if I didn't feel that there was anybody
I could be completely comfortable with then I would probably just be like, okay
Well, I'm fine with just having people I'm somewhat comfortable with and having my own room as a comfort zone
It's not like a terrible way to live and I think it's how most people live
I don't think there's many people who can find somebody who's like it's just gonna do like literally be down for absolutely every
Tendency they ever I don't you know, like I've had I've had like obnoxious living situations before
Right, I didn't like the people that I lived with and I wanted to avoid them and I felt anxious about seeing them
I don't feel that way here like sometimes there will be times when like I don't really feel like socializing
But like I'll have to go and like to the kitchen to get something and I'll have to walk through the living room
People are in there and oh god. Oh, they're gonna say hi to me and like whatever. That's fine. That's like not a problem
It doesn't it doesn't bug me. So I don't have any problems. That bugs me
That I definitely had that big time in the past. There was like particularly family members. There was a moment
Multiple I never feel like anything is demanded. Let's give it finish first. Okay multiple moments
When I was at uni when I was like in a shared house with six other people in their own rooms and stuff
We're like I needed I was hungry. I was at the computer in my room safe safe
No one can get me in here safe. Oh, no, I can hear people in the kitchen. I am hungry. I need to eat but
You know what? I think I'll just starve
I'd rather just like be hungry wait until they're gone to bed and then I'll eat and I happened a couple times
And I was like I know I mean I know but I did it. I know the feeling. No, I know the feeling
I used to I used to I'm a little less like that now
I did sometimes I still feel like there's people around like I don't just I'll just wait
I mean back. I guess that's true. I'm back in my hikikomori phase in particular. I'm I'm really stealthy
I'm very good at not being detected and like it was especially
Under the like waist-high walls
Yeah, I mean like particularly in in big houses
It's it's fun because there's a lot of different ways around and you could just quietly sneak up on people and like
You know, I'm big on both like surprising people by just like when they turn around. I'm suddenly there and also like
You know, just just but also just concealing my presence when it's like, okay
Like you said if like I want to get something
Downstairs, but like I hear somebody's down there
I will not go down until like I hear the sound has cleared and like, you know
I might still suspect that they might be awake and if they hear me they might say oh
You're still awake and I'll go
Don't think about the fact that I'm awake
run away
So the fucking people around feel very much pressure here with the people I live with now
I don't I'm not worried that they're gonna say anything. I don't I don't care what they think
I'm just like yeah, whatever and if I don't want to hang out. I'll just be like okay. Bye. I
Fucking hate the moments when when somebody is like, oh, you scared me. I didn't hear you
I didn't I didn't sense your presence. It was like I don't make I don't make a lot of noise
I guess I don't breathe heavily or stomp heavily and then they turn around
I'm trying to be stealthy and I feel like
Like a fucking serial killer. It makes me feel everybody says that I'm I'm very stomp
I'm like stomp apparently I'm very heavy footfalls
But like also I'm very easily snuck up on and like sometimes it happens all the time that I'll be cooking many times
Yeah, it's happened with a bunch of people here
Like I'll be cooking or something and I'll just turn around and someone will be in the kitchen
They came in when I went and I'm like, oh god. You are so easily frightened that I
I got to a point where I started expecting it
Like I tried to I would try like my approach you in a way that would like minimize the level of stress that it was going to
Yeah, like like people now like like my friend
Doob will like he'll he'll like kind of like step stomp a little loudly out the kitchen just to make sure he'll like knock on
The wall or something before he rounds the corners, so I'm not like
Yeah, I mean I might call out ahead of time just like hey Ben before I even into the room just so you know
These coming it's just I was just I would I was thinking of stuff like that
Like sometimes I try to make sure that my steps are pronounced, but not to pronounce
I don't want them to think I'm trying to get their attention because then they'll be saying huh, and then I'll be like
Why are you stomping bro? I hate I hate it when people are like why are you still walking?
Why are you doing anything and I and I'm literally just like hey, I'm a I'm walking here and like that's it
That's the answer
Can't fucking don't fucking question people hate hate hate being questioned. I hate when my methods are questioned
That's it. Yeah, well, this is this is this is fucking generalized anxiety disorder the podcast
Yes, wait you guys talk I have to pee I'll be back in two seconds
30 seconds 30 seconds
This is a story about a guy named Al who lives in a sewer with this hamster
Pal and I don't know any of the other words of the song because I never memorized it. It's really hard
Now you should have said long as I rhymed
Yeah, I thought about it, but I was like that doesn't make any sense so that I swerved
Crash maybe maybe maybe making sense was overrated in that context
Maybe rhyming would have been more aesthetically pleasing. You know, I was thinking about anxiety. I feel
like I used to
Like dismiss the idea that I had anxiety even though I was like socially awkward and a bit shy
The idea of like people who had anxiety they always talked about panic attacks and and like serious like
Immobilization things that they just could not do stuff and I was like, well, I guess if I push myself
I can do most things so I don't have that
Then I sort of internalize that as like every time I do feel a bit scared. There's no there's no excuse
I have I don't have anxiety. I have to do it. There's no way you know that I could be like
Some like mental blockage that here. I'm just like stupid or bad or something
I I think this is what we what you what you're describing is what you and I and and I think a lot of our audience
Have in common with with our anxiety is that like
It's it's like well, I'm I am sane and like I am smart enough to keep a handle on this
Like I don't have I don't have panic attacks all the fucking time because I understand that I am like what's wrong with me
so like
You know to some degree. It's like I understand that I'm panicking like I know that's what's happening and like I mean
I have had panic attacks
I am prone to them, but I I don't know they're not too scary for me because it's kind of like I understand
What's going on? I know why I'm panicking, you know
If anything the fact that I'm having a panic attack is kind of a relief and that it's like, okay
I get it. I get I get what's happening. This is just anxiety buildup, you know, and I think that that's I think that's something that a lot of us
Struggle with is literally like being like well, I feel the exact same way as a crazy person
However, I'm not crazy. So what do I do with that? You know like
Like I'm not demonstrably crazy
It's sort of a case of like, you know, the what's what's the phrase that basically mean like, you know
The the bigger wound gets the band-aid like what am I is there a idiom that means that agree the gray the squeaky wheel
Yes, thank you. Holy shit
Create a new idiom to try to remember that
The bigger
Squeaky wheel gets the grease so it's like, you know, yes, the people who are having uncontrollable panic attacks are the ones who are going to
You know, I mean who are gonna feel like they need to seek
help from somebody and
And get that dealt with and then the people of us who are like, okay
Well, I don't quite have uncontrollable panic attacks
But I feel everything just short of that and I still could use help
But I don't like need help so badly that I am a squeaky wheel, you know
So it's like I'm just a fucking half flat like I'm a halfway deflated wheel
I am I have poor traction on the road and I am a hazard, but I am not
Obvious enough for you to fucking get my air pumped up, you know, which is which is what I drive on basically is four of those
I mean a lot of
Like
Therapy or whatever is about or I don't know. I'm a fucking idiot and I don't know I'm talking about sorry if this is stupid
I'll go say it anyway. I think a lot like a lot of therapy and and psycho shit
Is about
Like just it's just about managing symptoms. Yes, like it's just and it like if your symptoms are managed
And if you feel that you are living more or less successfully without like great interruption from your issue
Whether you reckon whether you have issues or not if they're not fucking you up then that's okay
That is something that okay
I think this is a problem in basically advertising for psychology is that like
They they want to give everything a diagnosis so that everything is like clearly like we know what we're working towards
We have names for things and we can help these people out, but like by viewing everything that way
It's like like psychology is almost like an advertisement of like hey is your life really fucked
then you should come seek help here and it's like
Psychology and and therapy shouldn't be just for people whose life is uncontrollably fucked
It should be for anybody who's dissatisfied at all like you can iron out the dissatisfaction
You know like therapy and therapy doesn't have to be literally paying a
Psychologist to do it for you can just be talking to people because that's all it is you talk to a person who has more perspective than you
Do about how the mind works you you have plenty of friends who can probably give you
Something akin to a therapy session, you know if you have friends and if not make friends
It's it's it's good therapy, you know to talk to people who who could understand you but like
That's essentially all therapy is and if you understand
Psychology yourself you don't really need to talk to a therapist. You could just talk to other people who understand psychology
You know I have been
Because yeah, I've been thinking about that like for years like I don't really need to pay for things when I could have like people to talk
to but
It is a bad idea
Generally, I found to go to the public and to say on Twitter or in a YouTube video
Yeah, it's helpful somewhat because it's like a it's a different medium
But like I've got counseling like recently for the first time ever I've paid for a fucking bunch of stuff and
yeah, and I've had a few sessions now and
The the appeal is not that they know more than the people
Who could reply on Twitter or anything? I mean they do know more, but it's not that's not like the thing
I'm paying all this money for it's
the the the knowledge and
The the security that I can say all of this stuff and they are not ever
Going to cause they're not ever gonna cause Twitter drama. They're not ever gonna cancel me with this information
This information stays here
They are not like I am not at risk of making like ruining their day because it's their job to listen to me
I don't have to worry about like
Bringing the moods down or like doing anything to like a friend that would you know like make their day bad or you know
Whatever the the anxiety is like it's all just just speak and it's it's better than speaking to a brick wall or to a microphone
And then deleting the recording because it's a person and they can respond
Yeah, so it's like that is the value. I think the trust element is definitely is definitely when I when I see someone
Go on Twitter with like a problem, right and be like guys
I'm having a problem. This is really bothering me. Let me bear my soul. I'm
My reaction is not good. My reaction is is like, oh
if you're
This is not the place for that you're doing that you're doing it wrong
You're doing it wrong. I get I get why no no I get why they would do it
But I don't think they should and I think they should know better and I'm like
Don't please don't do this. I think it's it's sort of
It's sort of a matter of like these people don't know who
They can talk to and sure I would I would highly I totally sympathize for why I totally sympathize why they're doing
I just don't think it's going to do what they want it to do. I guess I guess I would say because like
those people
I completely agree with you like don't post in that kind of shit like on twitter is usually not
Very helpful, but it can attract people to your dms who might be able to help you
But maybe more effective than that is just going to people's dms like because people come
I opened up my dms after coming out. I have become a literal fucking guidance counselor for the entire
Trans anime community. So like you know, I I talk to people all the time about their issues and stuff
but
like
You know
It's easier if you're like coming to me
like
Hey, do you have a comment on this situation? And it's like, okay, like I know
I I know why you are coming to me
You know and like if I have a response, I'll give it to you if I don't I won't um
That's just it's as simple as that I give responses when I have thoughts
I read when I have time, you know, uh, if I'm interested if I'm bored
So it's not like I respond to absolutely everybody or anything like that. Um, just you know the level of engagement
I feel appropriate, but like, uh, you know, I do think that for a lot of those people
It's like they can't afford therapy
They don't they don't a lot of them just haven't yet accepted that they have a problem or like don't really they
Again, they think oh, I'm not that extreme like oh, I don't have panic attacks or oh
I don't have like extreme body dysmorphia and it's like, okay
Well, do you find that you live most of your life in a in a sort of dissociated haze or you're not really paying attention
Anything going on around you and it's like, oh, yeah, that's how I live every moment of my life
And it's like, okay seek therapy, you know, like that's not it's not supposed to be that way
It's like, yeah, uh, you know, you definitely
But it's all I've ever known
Say I'm so comfortable here
um
It's nice and gray
Imagine imagine living in an associative haze cringe
Associative haze boys
This hashtag
Um, Ben, you you're you're a lincoln park fan. Yeah
Yes
Yes, yes, that's right. So I've been thinking a lot about lincoln park and about chester bennington lately because of him killing himself and
Right, I don't know if you know much about his past
But like no, it's nothing nothing at all. Uh, well, uh, it's horrible. So I'll say it in a funny way, uh, but he uh was
Sexually abused for like, uh years by
By like an older friend and he was afraid to say anything about it
You hate to see it. Yeah, he was afraid to say anything because he thought that they would think he was gay
and uh
Like it's it's it's really interesting because like that would really suck to imagine being gay
She's exactly
Uh, so he uh
he uh
You know, when you when you listen to lincoln park's music knowing this and knowing like
He was also he basically became an alcoholic
Uh
And like in early lincoln park
He was an alcoholic and a lot of the song like crawling is about alcoholism that like he said so as much as like
It's about my an inability to escape my alcoholism
And when you look into the lyrics knowing why he was an alcoholic and he's talking about these wounds that will not heal
Uh and how fear is how I fall. It's like, okay. Well, this is what the song's about, you know, I see it to be fair
You can read almost anything you want into the lyrics of lincoln park song
Uh, but that's that's it's it was fascinating to me to because I've always felt that way
It's like oh anybody can project onto this
But once I actually knew what he is like what it's actually like what he actually went through personally
And I mean particularly with some of the later songs because
He you know, aside from the fact that he went through alcoholism
He later on uh, he because he became a recovered alcoholic
And there's a bunch of songs that are about like alcoholic recovery about
Recovering from your past traumas. They have one song on one of the songs. It's called like victimized. That's just like, you know
You've been victimized or whatever and uh, so like, you know
I think that he was he was dealing with these demons trying to move through them
And like holding himself to a really high standard
And it seems as though basically what happened is that when chris cornell the singer of uh, um
Soundgarden killed himself who was like one of chesters like best friends and personal idols
He like couldn't take it and not too long later
He lapsed
Drank some alcohol couldn't take the idea that he would become an alcoholic again and killed himself. So
Wait, who was it that died that made him relapse the the soundgarden lead singer, you know black hole sun
chris cornell, I don't know is okay
Cool. Um, so he had committed suicide not too long beforehand and then chester seemingly like fell as well
But anyways, it's it's fascinating to me because of the fact that
Um before he was in linkin park. I had not known this. He was a part of a band called gray days
just
Gray and then days da ze
Um, and I they they they like reproduced their first album
Before chester died. So like this was going to come out
Then he killed himself and it now is out like they finally released it the songs have been on the radio
And it was really funny because I saw that the when I first heard the song
I saw it said gray days and I thought oh, there's a band
That's called gray days. That's funny because mine. I've called myself gray
In reference to the fact that I spend my time in a gray days. This is perfect, right?
And I'm listening to it and I'm listening to the music and I'm like this sounds just like linkin park
Which is really funny because I grew up listening to linkin park and thinking, you know
Like connecting to those emotions not even realizing it was chester and his old band until I looked it up
And then I'm like, okay, this all makes sense
Um, but like the songs
The album is like I won't say it's great. You might enjoy it. Um
It's pretty all right like radio rock type music pretty much very like washed out and daisy
But like the lyrics from the perspective of knowing that he killed himself the lyrics are too fucking depressing like
The the second track the second track is like
Maybe maybe things will get better
Maybe things will get brighter
Maybe maybe
And it's like oh no
And they did it they clearly did it. No, I guess I guess not. Well, maybe next time
But it's just funny because like that music
Again, like linkin park like you said the emotions are painted with such a broad brush
They don't seem to be about anything in particular and like listening to gray days, which is
They're even earlier, you know writings in linkin park like this is must be how he felt when he was a teenager
Maybe resurfacing these emotions gray days was from before linkin park. Yeah, that was the band
He was in for like six years before
Linkin park and they were like they broke up because they just like it wasn't going anywhere and then he joined
Linkin park and became huge so like
You know, I think he was basically trying to like readdress
these past emotions
And so he was thinking about them a lot
And then, you know, chris cornell killed himself and he's like well if chris couldn't make it
I can't fucking make it, you know
Because he tweeted something like after chris cornell died like I can't imagine like living in this world without you or something like that
um
Yeah
I mean if you ask me he might have been gay for chris cornell
And that was what was you know, what was no he was gay after all
I mean
That's just my personal theory, but like
uh, okay
You know, but like it's just like man the fucking the lyrics their lyrics that like again
If you heard this on the radio, you would just be like, oh, this is like cheesy fucking radio music
It's just so general it could be anything but it's like this motherfucker actually killed himself
And we know what he went through. We know he was an out of recovered alcoholic
We know he killed himself because he relapsed
We know that he was an alcoholic because he was trying to deal with these childhood demons
And he wouldn't talk about it
Like his wife became like a big advocate all the stuff surrounding him after his death that like all the money
Surrounding him is going towards uh, like basically boosting mental health
Normalization of like talking about it because like obviously he was somebody who the reason that the lyrics of lincoln park are so reserved
Is he didn't want to talk about it?
You know like he didn't want to be specific because it was too fucking hard to deal with so
Uh, you know which ironically makes it connect to the most possible people
But it means that he was the most guarded person
You know like the person least capable of actually confronting the reality of what had happened to him
Uh, so like and you know in his attempt
Ultimately fell. It's just depressing
Sorry to bring down the room
But I thought you'd appreciate that as a lincoln park fame
I do that's neat. No, I didn't know I knew chester killed himself. I didn't know shit about him other than that
Yeah, I hadn't been told recently either, but
Um
Well, hey we're at
We're at an hour and 20 and we've got like a million voicemails to get through but let's like try and rapid fire them
Yeah, but you still are you still here? I'm still here
You we're on we're on speak pipe if you want to oh the first one we're gonna do is
Yes, yes, I know. Yeah, there's like 30 fucking voicemails in here
I'm gonna try and just like we're gonna go fucking bup bup bup bup bup through all this shit because I'm
You know
Nate was like, uh, hey, I'll fucking curate these for a fee
Um, and I'm like no man anarchy
curation it's for the birds
Everybody everybody gets a platform here on the pro krastinators podcast
All right, call it and say some nazi shit. I don't give a fuck
Uh, okay, I'm there
Okay, here we go with ben playing d&d
three two one
go
Yeah, cool. All right. Good. Good stuff. They
True, it's like
You know that meme that's like what's your sign? I'm a leo. Fuck you. I don't believe in that made-up horseshit
And then he's like so true to the periodic table. I was excited by how short that one was but
Unfortunately, it's a rare breed amongst these in that regard
We don't have to listen to all of them if they're boring. Let's see how cognate cognate cognate potus potus potus is
Christ, okay. Here we go. Three two, but no, but I'm saying that's me. That's me going so true looking at this song
Ribbit ribbit ribbit. I'm a goddamn frog. Haven't played d&d in like two weeks now. Kind of kind of disappointed, but okay, whatever
Uh cognate potus three two one go
yo
cognate
I think this is gonna be boring running for president
Everyone is saying that it's like a trick by trump to get people uh to vote cognate. So then that like the everyone that is
All right, let's go to the next one
My my thoughts on this ever everyone says like oh no if people vote cognate
Then it'll split the vote and trump will win like I think a lot of people who would have voted for trump would vote for cognate
I don't see I don't see this as like a thing that's gonna exclusively like cut into the democrats at all
Uh, I I mean, I just straight up wouldn't have voted if not for cognate. I mean, I'm only going to vote if I can vote for cognate
Yeah, oh god, jesus. Oh, whatever fine. Yeah vote cognate. Yeah vote cognate. Fuck it
Fuck it. I'll do it live right you ready for super smash brothers pedo and g-note. I absolutely. I'm ready. Okay three two one go
It seems as if the super smash brothers plays are all pedophiles
They're all groping at children and kissing miners and then the dog is crazy
That's a narrow and zero and the catara are these super smash brothers. I don't know if we need 57 seconds of this
It's it's a terrible
Yeah, that's it. Okay, cool. Yeah for a second
Uh, yeah, it's it's another one. There's another super smash post ultimate pedo ultimate g-note
It's the same. It's almost the same length. Should we just listen to it? Let's do it. I guess so
Three two one go
Well, it's happened all of the fupus smash brothers play as a pedophiles
They have been confirmed as such
Fucking zero
This is a different voice. I guess he thought the first voice is still annoying. I don't I don't know if this is no better
If it's like a redo, I don't know if that's a remake or a sequel
Um
It seemed like he started off saying pretty much the same shit though
Oh, it was almost the second one. It's like well now it's all of them. So the oh the situation has progressed
Maybe not. Um, I was seeing people
I was seeing people on twitter saying like oh no
I saw someone say like god if my family finds out about this shit. It's all over
I won't be able to go to smash tournaments anymore. And at the time I didn't know the context but in hindsight i'm like
kind of hope
They don't have any smash tournaments for a while after this
Kind of hope they don't do it. They probably shouldn't be having smash tournaments in the middle of the uh, you know
COVID and all that yeah
I think it was vosh tweeted something about how like
Sky williams house is like the the epstein island of the smash community. Do you know about this?
Yeah, I I know nothing about any of this. I guess a lot of these smash tournaments were held at the home of this guy named
Sky williams and it's not it doesn't there's no explicit accusations that sky william who I think is a guy
I don't even know that sky is a is a pedophile himself
But like I guess it was like at this house that like a lot of this fucking
I don't know fucking diddling it happened
So it's like I don't know big deal
The dillyard. Yeah, the dillyard's room. Uh, let's let's watch the best reality tv show of all time. Absolutely
in three two one go
I've recently discovered this uh, absolutely crazy fucking reality show and you might be thinking
Oh, well the reality shows they're all they're all staged man reality
It's fake
No, this is like the kind of reality show that gets canceled after the first season and it gets sued like a shit ton
times afterwards and years to come and then uh, the studio tried to hide its existence
But it still exists. It's on youtube and there's like a bunch of people talking about it
Get to the point. Yeah, what is it?
Mainly just john trun. He made some videos about it. I don't care about fucking john trun hilarious, man
And I uh, all of you should watch it. It's all what's it called youtube. It's called kid nation
It's fucking brilliant, man. They they take uh 40 kids
And they go to a literal ghost town and they just have them like to live there for 40 days
They just like lord of the flies like a class system
And uh, okay, okay, I'm interested. This is all just the first episode man, and they split them into like factions
I've only watched one episode so far, but it's fucking amazing
And so I've never heard of this
You gotta watch it man. You gotta I want to hear kid nation on the procrastinators podcast
Because it's it sounds like ben is in so I think I'm in I'm in like
I don't know I
It sounds like it could be
insane
But but because this is like on tv. This is on cbs
So like how crazy can it really get you know?
You know
Uh, I don't know I put hydrochloric acid in the water pistols
Just just to see like what would a child? What would an innocent child do?
You know who hasn't learned racism yet
I have to say I don't know if I could possibly care about anything in the universe less than a minute and a half
Of my true persona 5 opinion forget. I sent the other voicemails
Um, let's let's give it just we gotta give a shot. This is we got to democratize
I can democratize the the voicemails. Okay, three two one go
Like a few weeks ago. I sent some gay ass voicemails about persona 5 where I was like, oh, this part's too hard
And then another one was like, oh, I did it. Okay, but fuck that. Um, that I shouldn't have sent those
I uh pretend I didn't this is the real opinion
Of persona 5 that everyone should wait wait. They don't they just unabashedly praise the fucking game
Um, what's the opinion they think it's the best game of all time. It's not give me a number out of 10
Really good. So give me a number out of 10 thumbs up or thumbs down and it's really fun. You know, you're like
Oh, should we please not the end not over one thing one thing I ask of everybody's speed doing your doing your calls
thesis statement
Start with a thesis statement that catches our attention make me interested immediately
I will listen to you stammer and stutter and fucking try to make a point
But just please start off by just laying out why I should care like right away
Yeah, uh, it's it's you know, it's just that's just good writing. Yeah, you know in general
Uh, next up PCP secret cabal operation green turtle thing
So that's mysterious. Let's find out what that's all about in three two one go
Blah
Blah, what what what is it the alarm's a sounding? What's going on sir? We have to evacuate
We're dropping it never before seen records. What is it?
What's dropping our viewership the number of pcp members per podcast my newborn baby all three sir
It's all dropping the ship is sinking and it's turtles all the way down. No impossible. I gotta believe we just gotta believe
Oh, yeah, baby little girls
Donatello
Security no wait, sir. This might be our final chance. What donatello's appearance in pcp episodes
Actually correlates perfectly with our ratings. We might be able to save the pcp if we send them back in time
Fire up the time machine then listen area slimy green demented shell trash. We have to go back
You have to save the pcp. Oh, baby. I love
I
Oh
Come along with me
On a trip through pcp
We can journey back to rad con and save it all from brad con
I'm donatello and I like
Ah
So wow so long way of saying that we should get donatello on the pcp
That was fantastic. I like I think that can be arranged. It had a music. It had a musical number. It had stakes
It had rising action. Yeah
I would call this this a masterpiece great acting great acting. Yeah
Um
You know, you really you really believe that this is a guy who's trying to yell into the microphone
But has to keep his voice down so he so he doesn't bother his parents. You really buy it
Oh good good stuff good stuff
Uh, cool next one only 20 seconds. Thank god a dank wizard is a pussy wussy
Uh, I'm ready for this one three two one. I have written this add in k wizard
Uh, I know who this is, but I will I will comment afterwards three two one go
Oh, my my name is a dank wizard. Um, I'm such a pussy
Ben isn't t for what what a bad boy. He he his ideas scare me
This radical far left ideas. They're so scary
Wow, I love you too a dank wizard
Um, do you know who that is? I have no idea
It's it's that funny video. I did you see the funny video of the guy saying don't support digi bro or the pcp
Because digi is a degenerate and ben is antifa. I did not but that is I I posted it on twitter
I guess I'll I don't know if I want to link it in the description or anything. I kind of think
I like the guy's been flooded with like youtube comments and I kind of don't know if we need to do any more of
Of that. No, but um, I will I will post it for you here in the fucking chat so you can see but yeah
It's basically I mean, it's exactly what it sounds like
degeneracy
Antifa
These this podcast hates america
Uh
Defund them abolish them
Um, uh, it's good stuff. It's it's great. You know, it's classic anyway
Let's see if we can find something even better at this guy who's just got a youtube link as their name of their voice
Okay, I'm gonna play it link is to please stop supporting digi bro the procrastinators by a dank wizard. Okay
Oh, lol, okay, which is like a four almost 420
length, so I don't know if it's a meme
But uh, I don't I don't think so
It is almost exactly for pretty
I'm gonna play this this voicemail though just to see what it is three two one go
Hey guys, have you seen this video? I'm linking as the title of this voicemail by a dank wizard
It's fucking funny. We've seen it and it is pretty funny. All right. Good school
So, okay, so that that previous voicemail was somebody making fun of a dank wizard for being a uh
A dank pussy basically about a pussy a pussy wassy
You think that was the real dank wizard
No, I thought they were making fun of a dank wizard. I thought that was no
No, I think that's I think that's what his real voice sounds like
That's just how I think it's a controllable smooching
It feels like what he would be
I don't you know, it's funny. I'm not I'm not mad
I just think it's funny that someone made a video like that
And I have to share it on twitter because I just want to spread the love and good times around
I want everyone to enjoy it as much as I do
Uh, all right next one
Thirteen seconds. Thank you merciful shower speed run chads three two one go
Any fellow shower speed run shads still hanging around? I just got a
149 that's pretty damn fast. I'm not sure I can get it any lower
We'll see though. We we should have leaderboards
149 doesn't seem that fast for a shower. I mean, what are the requirements? Like what all do you have to do?
That yeah, like do I like if you have to use conditioner that it necessarily takes more than two minutes
If it doesn't require a conditioner if it's just shampoo and body soap if you just use like an all-in-one
It would take like what 30 seconds like
I feel like I could do a really bad job washing myself off in like 30 seconds. Yeah
Like just like jump in grab the soap rub it around rinse off jump out. You know like that's all it takes
It's technically a shower
Well, we need categories. We need categories, right? We need speed run categories
It's like, you know the category for like you with conditioner without conditioner shampoo. No shampoo, you know
Yeah, how rich is your lather? All right hippo. What were you trying to say?
I'm sorry. By the way, sorry. I still call you hippo because I realized everybody's calling you gib again
Since you don't really have an active hippocrite channel. I just got so used to saying you hippo
It has a good cadence to it. Uh
I don't mind. I feel like there's still no consensus
My my my preferred my preferred pronoun is gib. Is it okay? I was told that so I was like, okay
But like it it you know, it doesn't matter. It's like it's it's just like I prefer the word give
I've never actually been sure
Well, uh now, you know, I'm just saying
I've been getting into the long play shower game
Where I I I use the shower as my my chance to meditate and I I sit like crouch at the at the bottom of the shower
And I close my eyes and I go into a deep trance and I wake up
Um, and uh, it takes a very long time. So I made a new category long play
Uh, you we need it's it's it's good. Okay. We we can have a leaderboard
But the thing is we're gonna need like it needs to be verified
So you're gonna have to film yourself showering and send it to us
Uh, and we're gonna have to manually review each submission in order to verify that no, uh, you know that there were no cuts in the footage
Yes, and that you were playing all the pictures that you and that you were playing on approved hardware
Approved hardware only in that you must have tits
end of vagina
That's the hardware i'm talking about
Okay, okay
One piece more like one piss
I am ready as a matter of fact
three two one go
PCP more like ppc
In other words, yeah
It's like it's like the regular ocean this guy's like on crystal math
It's the ppc
Like this guy
Crastinators
Hey
Ocean
I think this guy's actually on i think he's actually on drugs guys. I would very much believe that
Voice grail voice grail
No voice we got up. I'm sorry. We have we're hard. We're hard on crime hard on drugs
The drug war rages. We got to put him in jail and get his put him in voice. No voice grail
We didn't abolish it the funniest voicemail i've ever heard
Hmm
The line is like the year in ocean the line between greatness and and idiocy is so is so paper thin in a case like this
Genius or insanity. I am ready for an emotional journey because the next two are called margarh and margarh's apology
Margarh has been margarh has been sending voicemails like the last several weeks
So they've clearly got a lot to say so let's well, they're they're saying something and then apologizing. So that's what i'm the most curious about
Let's let's let's jump in there with them three two one go
Hello pcp
Yeah, I do always send the voicemails late on saturdays
And I guess that means that I usually end up being the final voicemail
Uh having been the final voicemail two weeks in a row
I'd like to issue a challenge to the community to uh beat me and be the final voicemail
Um, I haven't even been trying so
He succeeded massively on I mean a lot of people want this challenge because there's like 10 more of these
Things after this you're yeah, he's he's already won because like yeah
He normally sends he was the last one because he would always send it on like the day of or the day before
but this time we got like
We got like 10 voicemails in the last like 12 hour or in the last like 24 hours
So I don't know what's up with that
So next margar's apology. Let's find out what he's so sad about
three two one go
Hey margar here. I'd like to issue a formal apology to mr. Tom oliver
Uh recently one of my voicemails. I asked why there were so few members coming onto the podcast
And tom clarified that it's literally because of the fucking unemployment shit
That uh, it's just better for him to not show up as much. So
Uh pretty cringe, uh bad
Bad take on taxes from the government. Uh
No hate towards tom though. You got to do what you got to do. Uh, so sorry. I complained about that
But the complaint stands for all the others unless you justify it. So fuck you
I don't know what an apology was necessary for
I'm I'm fucking on unemployment too and I all and I just show up anyway. So, uh, you know, whatever
No, no, fuck tom. No fuck tom and fuck you too margar voice jail voice jail. Huh, huh?
I thought we abolished the voice no
We did not the the stream only raised enough to free
I think it was three out of the eight people in voice jail. So we did not fully abolish it
We did defund it though, which is something. Um, but we're still we have voice voice chair
Hmm
Voice chair, you know for the ones we really don't like oh like with a single bare light bulb hanging above them. Yeah
Yeah, see
This'll be easier if they tell us their voicemail secrets
Uh, next one
11 seconds message to ben part two
Mysterious three two one go
What did I tell you ben?
Get off twitter
Bad ben bad ben shoo shoo shoo go to your room. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Fuck
I hate the yes. I know twitter bad twitter bad, but we all do it. We're all guilty. I love trying so
I have no bad relationships with twitter
I you know, I just I was thinking about it
All like all you see all you see are the worst takes on twitter
But I don't know i'm with two minds about this because on the one hand
Yes, what I get on twitter is a concentrated stream of the worst things that happen and the worst things that people think and it makes me upset
So is that reality because on the one hand I genuinely believe that these are real things that people think
On the other hand, they're probably not as common as they seem
When you when you're getting them. Well, it's both that they're not as common and also that these people are not as likely like
Acting on these beliefs like like I think I think most people have like it's easier to talk shit on twitter
Yeah, well not just talk shit
But I think that people live in ways that are contrary to their beliefs without realizing it because it's easy to like
To to intellectually
Internalize a set of beliefs but to actually like perform in a way that would best
Cause like your like to best further your cause
Is really difficult for people on on any side like most of your life is dedicated to just trying to live your life
Not trying to further anything and like in many cases living your life is actively furthering causes that are against you
And you really can't help it. I mean like you've you've said many times
There's no ethical consumption under capitalism, you know like sure
So it's just and I am and I did invent that phrase as well
To make you to make people understand
Yes
Sorry twitter is
Yeah, go ahead
I was just gonna say twitter is like reductionist goggles
Like you put them on and you see the most reduced form of a person due to the character limit
And then through that you form opinions that are not necessarily correct in any way
All in the people that are speaking and then you get a sense that things are terrible
And I don't know whether it's it's actually that as as bad as it is
Uh, I mean there are genuinely there are genuinely terrible people
Let's let's acknowledge twitter amplifies it. Yeah. No, it's true. I mean I definitely I
Ben I think in many ways that you you are right in your approach to twitter because like people take it too seriously
Well, it's not like okay like
The way that you go about it is I was I was I was catching some flags
I was catching some flak the other day about my approach on twitter
Yeah, I would say the way you go about it is alienating and like there are definitely people who it's gonna make mad
But do I think it's necessarily ineffective?
Like I do think that you if you if you really have a problem with the things that people are saying
Aggressively letting them know that will cause them to reflect
They might just double down on hating you, but they will have to think about their beliefs that much is true
And I do like I I do not endorse bullying
But do I think bullying doesn't work or that it can't be a viable tactic? No
And so like ultimately I don't I don't see anything that I do is bullying. I am am I caustic sometimes?
Yes, do I say mean things? Yeah, but like would you say it's but it's bully
It's bullying if there's like an unfair an unfair power dynamic
I mean if I say bullying I feel like it's a cuter way of saying being abusive
Or or abrasive like what do you want me to say?
Those are not the same thing. Those are not those are two different things. They could be close
Am I abrasive? Yes. Am I abusive?
I don't think so unless like insulting someone is automatically abusive. I wouldn't say so
I think you're I don't think that you are uh
I I I wouldn't call you abusive. I do insult people like I definitely do that
Yeah, I saw some of the flak you were getting and some of the the responses would just sort of like
Uh, you're not gonna further any causes by the way you act right and you were getting really mad like do you think it's
Do you think it's like annoying that people expect you to be fighting for a cause with everything you say a little a little
Yeah, a little because I I always feel a little like like
if if I like
There's like a watch on your back like
If you're gonna be progressive you better be progressive in exactly the right way
Otherwise, we're gonna shit on you as well. It was it was I was getting a little annoyed because yeah the feeling I was getting was like
Ben
We we you you know we share these like we share these ideas. We share goals politically culturally whatever
And what I want is to see you pursuing those things optimally and the way you are comporting yourself
Is not optimized and I'm like you might be right. Well, I mean it's kind of also like no I'm not going to like
Who I'm not going to behave off literally who you know that can be optimal
Who can behave optimally all the time is in in any given situation
Would I maybe get better results from being like hey?
I see that you said this weird thing you said something about the jews that I don't agree with and I have some historical like
References that you might want to read that might disprove some of your hypotheses like let me go through them one by one and point
Maybe that would be more effective than saying like like like fuck off
Nazi right maybe that's more effective, but I'm not going to do that
I can't do that
What do I get the most bang for my buck from and you know this is in terms of both
Impact on the water broader world at large and also like how does it affect me?
How taxing and painful is it for me to go through exactly that's that's the part it's like being
Being polite is like it takes effort. It takes like if you are not I think there are people out there who just naturally are
Frankly, I have a low capacity for it. I really do
I mean there are people out there who have who really are good at being polite and understanding and
Like it's just the way they were raised
You know it's just they they came up with that and like for me
It's it's not that I don't want to be polite and understanding. It's just really hard, you know, and it's like
I I think
As long as I mean in my mind
It's like as long as I'm trying my best to not be like
Deliberately an asshole
Then I feel like I like I'm not going to overextend myself
To the to the like furthest extent I can to be the nicest I possibly can especially to people who are being mean to me
It's like if you are being mean to me
I am going to feel you know, like hey, you you really need to know
Like I guess it's it's kind of like if somebody was
Bumping into you constantly and you kept saying stop or like could you move away and they weren't doing anything
At some point you just have to fucking jam your elbow into them and just be like get the fuck away from me
You know, so it's like
If you if you want to live in this world you have to be somebody who can eventually just say like hey
Your existence threatens me and I'm going to do something about it, you know
My yeah my last argument on the way about the way I can port myself on twitter is there are now
I might be I will admit that maybe I am
inclined to
Take this approach maybe slightly more often than it is strictly necessary, right? I'll grant that but there are some
Things there are some ideas. There are some opinions. There are some things that people can say
That I believe are so
Are so despicable and so wrong that to that to try and like
Like
Respond to them thoughtfully and to to try and like answer them and rebut them
Is like doing them too much credit
I mean it's it's sort of like and and and a more way let me fit and a more appropriate response
And in some of those cases, I think a more appropriate response is not to even do so at all
But just to say like I have nothing but contempt for that. I will not answer this
I I will simply express my disgust and that's all that is required at the root because it's like
You could attack what they're saying, but like what they're saying
Like in order to express how wrong it is you would have to peel back so many layers of the wrongness
It's like this is this is not even from a perspective capable of expressing
Something correct because it is so wrong and so like at that level. It's like
My inclination would be more likely to just ignore it like even if I thought even if I did have like a visceral
Reaction of hatred towards something I read my reaction is like I don't want to get involved
I don't want drama. I don't want to I don't want to get to I don't want to get into an argument
But I do understand why like if you have that reaction and you say something like again
Even if in the short term it doesn't seem to have quote-unquote an effect
Like when you let people know that you have a problem with them
Then they are going to have to think about the fact that they're going to think about that fact and granted
I think that when you are super aggressive
It is more likely that the conclusion they'll come to is well. Fuck you even harder than sure like I don't think that
I don't think it's a bad thing to put it in people's head that people have a problem with them
You know like yeah, that's that is step one towards changing your behavior. You know to to us too
I think I think that just like putting up any
Yeah, I feel like the word resistance kind of aggrandizes just being a should be like being shitty being me and insulting someone online
But like putting up any kind of resistance at all to something that you think is bad and needs to change is like well
It's not it's not is it optimal who knows but I do think it's right to do that
And I don't ever feel but I almost never feel bad about it unless I decide like oh
I read this wrong or like I misinterpreted
Well, I mean worst-case scenario you change it back like I think I think one of the biggest problems facing our like generation
And the the one of the things caused by the anxiety we all feel is like we're so afraid of doing it wrong
Of like hurting somebody's feelings and then not knowing how to deal with it afterwards
And it's like the best way to deal with it is like if you were wrong admit it as fast as possible
And make things right, you know, just be like oh, I'm sorry. I was wrong like I've changed my mind
I understand that I that you that you were not saying what I thought you were saying
We're cool now, you know, like
It's just like adaptability is the way to navigate conversation, you know
Yeah
Although I'm usually not that interested in a conversation. I'm usually just interested in expressing an idea or a feeling and then like leaving
I mean, I think that you're I guess what I'm saying is that from the perspective of other people
Analyzing your actions. It's kind of like they look at it as oh, well
I wouldn't do this because I wouldn't want to face the social ramifications of this
um, so
like so ben you need to stop because like
They assume you wouldn't either. Yeah, I don't want to I don't want to face the social ramifications of this
So I should become the social ram right exactly
That is literally exactly a little dude people people fucking like that though and and we do it to ourselves too
We're like I don't want to be too mean to these guys because I know that like in a way
They have their hearts in the right place, but I whatever I do think it was dumb the whole the whole discussion was stupid
It's like I think that uh, that you know, we can get into a
Shit, I forgot what I was going to say. I heard a weird noise and it distracted me. Let's play the next fucking speak pipe
Yeah, yeah, we're ready. Uh, next one is pancakes
Confederate lost cause movement
Three two one go
Hi pancakes here. Listen, you don't have to play this voicemail. I'm just here to tell you something that you might be interested in
You know with all the tearing down statutes and stuff. I feel like you might
Look at the lost cause of the Confederacy
It's uh, it's holy fuck. This is weird. I don't care. Interesting
and fucking no, it's not it's not interesting like what are some of the long lasting impacts
They're the ones that uh
Just did the issue that
Civil war is not based on slavery but based on states rights
Check it out. Oh, he's
Is that it? Do you ever hear a video game? What the fuck? What the fuck was the point of this like?
Yes, I know
I know that they's
Okay, did you ever heard of reddit.com? Did you I know you were talking over a little bit?
So maybe I missed something, but I don't think I did was the point of this just to say that the south
Claimed that it was about states rights
Yes, I know and yes
I know that the conf that the confederate flag was known for for a while as a symbol of lost causes because that's what it is
And it was you know now it's racist or whatever
Um
Did you know that it's and I also happened to know that what is considered today to be the confederate flag was
Is not the flag of the confederacy. It was a battle flag of a regiment in virginia. I mean it just seemed like he was saying
Just look into this thing. It's interesting
Which is fuck you pancakes. Uh, well, he's got the fuck out of here. It's food for oh god
All right, this better be good if you want to redeem yourself. Okay, three two one go
Hi pancakes here. Listen, you know how most people are vegetarians because of the moral implication of killing a certain being for its flesh
Bombs if we reach into the future
Where we no longer grow animals, but like use their dna to just grow the meat itself without
Ascention being being involved
Then for people like tom or something would you be more inclined to tom's not a vegetarian anymore?
Is he no, he's not but I mean obviously his answer that question would be yes, like
Absolutely, obviously anyone who does it for ethical reasons would be like, oh, there's no ethical problem with this food
I guess I'll eat it unless there and problem wasn't like environmental concerns and then it's like oh
Well, what's the impact of this genetic farmer? Are they creating more fossil fuel? Okay easy easy question easy answer pancakes never fucking dark
in my doorstep again
That food for thought had like zero calories
Burn owned
All right. Well, next is john youtube
John youtube love you man. Can't thanks for all the shit you've been doing for our channel
Recently really appreciate all the work you put in helping us out three two one go
Hello pcp
My name is john youtube
On the one who deleted your videos
I can store them above three demands that must be met
One
He must vow to never have mother's basement
And podcasts ever again. I can't make any promises. I can't I can't number two
Ben saint must endorse
joseph robin hat biden jr
repressed in the united states
Is that really his real name?
It is
Best man must complete and post
best man may ever
ghost in the shell
If these demands aren't met in the next 13 days
I'll terminate all your channels
Damn, that's mean though john youtube. Uh, we just make a twitch. Fuck you. Don't do it. Don't do it
Don't do it youtube
I just I want I want the animorphs lecture back with all the views and comments
That's what I want. It had like a hundred had like 200,000 views. I just want those fucking views back all the funny fucking
Give me the give me it. What was that one with the one all the streams back dude the the gif
Thing the gif button that was cool
Remember that the gif button the gif button discussion that I filmed
Where tom tom was champion. Yeah, yeah, that's lost. Yeah the cringe trial cringe trial, right? Yeah
Ah, that was good times, man
If only we could revisit them on some sort of platform for for hosting video media
Uh, but unfortunately no such platform exists because the only things I know about are fucking demons
Who just fucking kill channels and destroy content and ruin lives for no reason? Yeah, it's a real bummer
And I don't know why it has to be like this, but uh, it is
Let's let's let's just not never give it give it any more thought
Uh, next one is give me the buster cast
Three two one go
Ben tom, I just watched gun buster and die buster for the first time and I need your buster cast
Please release it again. Who cares about the pcp?
Give me that fucking podcast
Thank you
I wait what happened to the buster cast it was destroyed. I wasn't it. What was it?
Was it? I'm not sure. Was it not caught in a blast radius?
um
I I don't know
Was the wait that was post no that was post radcon, right? So yeah, it would have been destroyed
um
Yeah, so
It'll be back
When youtube
Do have I complained about how youtube just keeps telling us they're gonna fix it and not doing it?
Have I said that yet this episode?
Because it really bears repeating explicitly it's just now, but I'm glad they just keep
Like nate nate keeps it like for the last like week or two nate keeps emailing them and they keep saying like hi
Hi, nate. This is greg filling in for my colleague, george
Thank you for your patience on this matter due to the situation around surrounding covet 19 our staff is limited
And so our backlog is blah blah blah. We appreciate your patience and we will be letting you know when there are developments on your case
Thank you for reaching out appreciate your patience. Love you. I like how I like how the
Disease that causes everybody to have to be in their houses is somehow causing this internet-based company to do less work
Like what the fuck?
I can't work from there. Literally. I guess there's literally no work involved
One person just needs to fucking hit some buttons. Yeah to say undelete the content
Like just fucking undelete maybe the employees have gone from one to zero and it's all robots now
Like it's really frustrating
I feel I feel like they wouldn't lie like it's not that I think they're honest, but I don't see what they gain
by telling us
Be patient. They're just disorganized as fuck if they're not gonna do it
So I feel like at some level they do intend to do it
But will they ever that's the question is a totally different question three months at least I'm thinking
And then they're gonna bring back like half of the videos and we have to do it again
Three months of winter coveted and awesome quarantine. Let's cheer ourselves up with this. Thank you message
Hey, love it three two one go
PCP
I just want to thank y'all
Today, it's july 12th
2020 and
one year ago episode
167 spiritual bathroom dimensions
My first voicemail ever
Just wanted to say thanks. That's all
Okay, you've you've had a long and storied career here celebrating the one-year anniversary of his own first voicemail
I guess he is
Uh, uh, uh, you're welcome
You're welcome and uh, have we've really been doing voicemails for a year jesus
Where does the time go? Ah
My life is gone. It's unraveling. It appears to have been activated
Uh may printing something. I guess I don't it's just it's printing. It's coming out of it. It's just making sounds. It's horrifying
That's okay. You know what that's gonna
This one is a this one's gonna listen to the video again. Is this just gonna be the same one? Let's listen to it
Wait, is it the same one? No, this one links to no, no, please stop supporting best guy ever in the procrastinators
From sly for shon
Way
Sly for shon
Uh, let's listen to the voicemail and maybe react to the slide. This is this is a parody. This is a this is a parody of
Uh, uh, that's cool of the dank wizard. Okay. Um
Yeah, let's listen to the voicemail three two one go. Hey, listen
Disregard the past voicemails about a dank wizard and from me and just play this one instead
It's a link to the video. I just uploaded. Ha ha. We will
Ha, okay, so he made it. This is like four and a half minutes long though
I
Yes, I I'm not gonna we're not gonna watch this right now. Are we now we could just put it in the show notes
We will put it in the show notes to check out please guys. We highly recommend
Please stop supporting best guy ever and the procrastinators. I like quality content like this first frame
I could put that in the show notes. Uh, if you fast forward you see that there's a lot more of it
Ha ha ha. Oh god
He's too close. Okay
Uh, shit dudes, uh, we made it to the end. I think that's the last one, right?
Amazing. I'm hungry. We I'm fucking delirious
I gotta go mix up another another mint. Uh knife a makido yado
Actually, I'm gonna go hang out with kazzie and munchie. I think after this is done
Sick. Um, so anything any last
Last last note for me. I mentioned it earlier. Uh vapers too
Is like basically done. I've been procrastinating on uh, this is my name. That's our name on like actually like like
Finalizing it and like sending off to the printer, but I have everything. I have all the chapters. Oh, you go have all the content of a prints
Yeah, yeah, they're all in it's ready. It's like basically ready
I'm gonna fucking send it off and get it printed like probably like today or tomorrow
I'm gonna get a gift in the mail
You are will receive you will receive one envelope containing content
Now it's gonna be my turn. I have to do my physical media preparation
Physical media, baby
That's the wave of the future
Did we mention the the merch?
Uh, peter the red corn floor merch is basically out. Everyone seems to be getting their packages now
Um, major scott his uh, so
there
Everybody's got it
Um, I I'm I'm I'm opening up the internet to find okay, so become a patron
At patreon.com slash is up procrastinators for all our fucking bonus content
Shit tons of it. Keep you occupied for a year. Put it on just put it out
You you're you're a hard-working single dad and you need some time to yourself to decompress
Just drink just have a have a sip have a sip of old timey brandy
In front in your in your office chair smoking your cigar any evidence that anyone in our audience has children
And if you want the ultimate you want to you know, how can I get these fucking kids off my back for a goddamn minute?
Just put on the procrastinators podcast bonus episode playlist and just put it on repeat
And you will never and you will never hear from them again. You're welcome
They will run away. Never. You will never have to work another day in your life
Um, send us a voicemail at uh, uh fuck the voicemail link
speakpipe.com
Slash no speak like dot com slash pcp voicemail
Is the uh, is the link there?
Uh, if you want to fucking have us read your stupid boring
No thesis statements message on our on our show. Uh, thanks for that
Um, anything else anything else you want to say before we we leave off for today?
Subscribe
Subscribe like comment subscribe smash the button because
Don't support the channel and his antifa
The channel we've been actually releasing this on actually are we still just on itunes and and we have been releasing them on like itunes
And on our web and on and on the procrastinators podcast.com the website and on spotify
Share the fucking share the podcast people
Yes, share the podcast on these alternate platforms. I guess like I don't know
Maybe there's an untapped market of people who might be listening if they knew that you could get it on fucking spotify
Uh, uh, yeah, but uh pretty cool. Hey guys, thanks for listening two hours pretty good. That's content, right?
That's that's you getting your money. Uh, we'll we'll keep we'll catch you next time
Uh, peace out. Bye
Good night