Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast, your favorite
and most lucrative friendship simulator. I am the best guy ever and today we're joined
by Lethal Roarumage. Hello. How deadly of you. And Tom Oliver. I am here, I am, games
are pumping through my blood and my veins and my brain and my synapses are firing up,
up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A select start. Let's do this. Why is it
never just hello with you people? Why can't you just say hello? Because you got, you have,
you have the domination, the sole proprietor license to use hello. The rest of us have
to come up with something clever every time because you, I think there's a, I feel a spirit
of one upsmanship that I want to be the best and to trounce everyone else with my magic
comedy skills. I don't usually succeed or anywhere close to it. Right, right, no, no,
me neither. It's, it's, Mages just takes the, the safe effective route every time it works
and she keeps going with it and we just keep botching it, trying to be entertaining clowns.
I gotta queue up that sound bite. She's such a normie. No, no, no. One day I'll have that
sound board actually working. I should take Bitterthorn's advice and get that stuff set
up. Yeah. How have we gone 131 episodes and not have a sound board? It just seems some
people don't like the idea of a sound board. I don't like the sound of some people like those
people and the words they're making about sound boards. Did you just hear that noise? No, I did
not. Why? What was it? It was my alarm for the podcast. It was supposed to be an hour before
or like half an hour before, but I'm guessing, I'm guessing the time. No, no, no, no, I'm guessing,
I'm guessing what happened is Daylight Savings. Oh, did that, why is it Daylight Savings like
switches like every fucking week of the year is what it feels like? Can we talk about time zones
and how they're bullshit and how people know? I don't get it. I don't understand. Just watch that
video. How is this so complicated? There's a great video by, what was it? Some fuck who was it?
It's like, it's like, why time zones suck or something about like, why making a clock sucks
or something like that. Why making a clock sucks. I was, it was, it was, it was something about why
programming like a digital like timekeeper is like such a pain because the rules of time zones
are so crazy. It is. And actually, I remember like, I think that like the most, so there, first of all,
like there's, there's just straight up time zones, then there's Daylight Savings time, which does not
stay like consistent between places. Then there's like, like London has its own kind of system where
it like switches actual time zones or something. Then there's, and I think the worst example of all
was like, I think it's, it's actually the Gaza Strip. Actually between Palestine and Israel,
I think they actually are in different time zones. And it's like, now you have to get political with
what time you decided is in like this region of the world. And it's like, well, shit, man, I didn't
sign up for this. It's interesting. Whatever video that is, it's great. Like, I remember, like, I
remember even like weirder is that like back in the day, I was big into conspiracy theory videos,
and I watched them all the time. And I watched this one conspiracy documentary called Chimatica.
And in it, there was this guy who was talking about how clocks and time itself is a conspiracy
about how like, what way I don't remember exactly has been forever, but I just remember him,
like, he's like, we're all slaves to the watch. And that time is an unnatural way of like humans
to like track things. And like, it was developed specifically to keep us like tethered to like
a false reality. And that like humans are supposed to be more organic in their experiences. And we're
all like fucking ourselves over and like getting loose in touch with our chakras by being a slave
to the watch. The thing about that is the thing about that is there is a nugget of logic to that.
They're like, there is a core that sort of makes sense. Because it's true, the 24 hour day cycle
that we all do everything to it is reasonably artificial. But it's like, we've got to organize
society some way. And this seems like a pretty reasonable way to do it. Apparently not if you
want to keep those chakras blitzed. That's what I learned from that. That was also that was also
the documentary that talked about Admiralty Merit or maritime admiralty law. That was some
fucked up. Do you ever hear about that that conspiracy? Okay, as conspiracy know, what's
the deal? Okay, so the idea between maritime admiralty law is that everybody technically has
two names. You have you have your personal name, then you have your corporation name. And they're
the exact same thing, except your corporation name is all in capital letters. And like, like on your
birth certificate and stuff, it's in all capital letters. And the theory behind this is that every
the reason you need a birth certificate in the first place is because every human being who's
ever been born is technically not just a human, but also a piece of collateral that the government
takes out against its loans. And so whenever they're referring to you in all capital letters,
they're referring to the technical corporation of your personhood. So I guess the corporation is
people after all, exactly. But like the thing is, is that like, these people also believe that if you
go into court, when you're summoned to court, they're summoning you the corporation and not
you the human being so you can just not go or just show up and be like, I'm not the person,
like you're trying to talk to the corporation and they're not here is just me the person and I'm
going to ignore these things that's like, like jury nullification that like, you're not supposed
to know about it. But I think I think that's the idea. But I think it's also bullshit, you know,
it doesn't sound like that's going to hold up. No, no, no, no, when the cops come, I say,
no, no, no, no, no, I just didn't show up to my, you know, murder court appearance because
I'm the person you're looking for the corporation exact Nate best man that that guy's elsewhere.
Yeah, okay. That guy's based out of like, I don't know, Dublin or something. If you want to have
some good sillies, go go search climatic. It's like a 2009 documentary. And it's it's some crazy
shit, dude. You know, this just reminds me of I think I've said it before, but there's it's a
if it's a separate thing, but it just reminds me of like, in Japan, there's a law that's
effectively like you're not allowed to drive like something about like in rain, you're not allowed
to drive too close to the edge of the road or something. And but like the wording of the law
is something that is like, drive not near the edge of death in the rain for there the skid demon
lies. Oh, God, imagine how much cooler history class would be if our laws were written like that.
Holy shit. It was something like that, at least. Yeah, look it up. It's one of the it was in like
one of those like, like sounds fake, but is real laws that's like of antiquity or something.
The best shit. The best pretty good stuff. Hey, guys, I want to yeah, I just want to close the saga.
I bought candy corn. Oh, have you eaten it? Yes. Yes, I have. What's the conclusion?
It's okay. It's like, it's quite different from what I expected it to be. But it's not as bad as a
lot of people made it out to be. To those who are listening, it sort of reminds me of the candy
called irises in the opinion. It's not exactly the same. At least the ones I bought, they have a
very strong honey taste to it. Honey taste, okay. Yeah, so it might be because of that.
Made, you know, you have to do now, you have to get the companion candy to the candy corn,
which is the candy pumpkins. They always come together. So now you're going to go on another
epic quest to get the candy pumpkins. Yeah, which tastes more ubiquitous. It is more ubiquitous,
but those are everywhere. They taste almost exactly the same. So it'll be a probably made of the same
material. A largely useless quest, but I'm sending you on it anyway. I have the option to refuse.
You could, but you'll disappoint me. I appreciate the seasonal timeliness of this whole quest,
which I guess is why it came up, because it's a Halloween candy thing. Yeah. But it gets me in
the spirit. Although this episode will be airing after Halloween. So hope you're enjoying your
post-Halloween lull, everybody. Yeah, go to your candy bin and grab some candy corn.
Everyone's on that Christmas hype now, Christmas. Oh, you're right. I forgot after Halloween,
it's Christmas season has begun, basically. You know what the best Christmas present is?
Donating $5 or more to the procrastinators on Patreon, we have a new bonus episode out
and edited by Mage. Oh, that's right. Over all, people. A hot coals of After Effects rendering,
taking their CPU to a hot sizzle. There's a lot of work there. Go do it. I didn't use,
in the end, I didn't end up using After Effects because it was just not agreeing. Yeah, it's just
me and Bentley. So were you able to get the animation stuff working?
Some of it, but not the mouth flaps, sadly. It was just too much trouble. I'm sorry,
I'm sorry. There's no mouth flaps. Hey, it's okay. It's okay. That's cool.
I was going to say, speaking of skid demons with that law, I have a thing to bring up relevant
to that exact thing. I think I was visited by a skid demon actually multiple times.
And this is about my skateboarding exploits on my wife's skateboard, effectively.
People were roasting me in my stream yesterday about that. Anyway, yeah, so I've been out
e-skateboarding and it's pretty great doing Pokemon Go and loving it. But there's been two
times now that I've wiped out hardcore and it's been pretty brutal. The first time was definitely
the work of a skid demon. I was going up this hill I've gone up many times before, this little
ramp into this big parking lot that I love to just go nuts and go max speed. And on the way up,
there's always these grass clippings across the blacktop leading in. And on this particular day
it was pretty wet outside. It had rained and I go up and I just wipe the fuck out and I scraped my
elbow. My right elbow got a little fucked up. That wasn't that bad. That was okay. I got up
and I hobble away and I'm okay. But then there was a couple days ago, like three days ago,
when I'm just skateboarding on the sidewalk and I'm coming up and there's a group of kids in
front of me and I'm like, actually, I had passed these kids, I had passed these kids on my way down
and they were like, whoa, dude, that's so cool. And I was like, yeah, nothing personal kid as I
max speed away from them. And I look totally sick and cool. And then as I'm coming up, actually
they ran alongside me like trying to keep up. But I just room I just knew where they say
they're like, I don't know, like maybe late elementary school to early middle school kids.
So like 12 or so probably 12. Yeah. So that was cool. And and then on the way back,
I see the same group of kids and I'm like, well, they're kind of taking up the sidewalk. I don't
want to cut through them. So what I do is I just skate off the edge of the
sidewalk onto the street as I'm coming towards my place. And so normally this can be a fine thing
to do. But there's lots of times when the difference between the sidewalk and the road is can be like
over two inches. And this is one of those times. And if you if you if you're if you're going straight
and then you just kind of veer to the right a little bit, you get like one wheel basically off
the thing. And you I mean, the imbalance going at fairly high speed is just quite high. So
I did this literally just to look cool to these kids that were thinking I was I was dope, because
I could have just stopped and gotten off. But no, no, no, no, you got to do in one motion. As I do
this, the whole thing buckles, it goes like a 45 degree angle. And I just go flying into the middle
of the road. Just just fucking up my body bad in I mean, I scraped my hand terribly. I have many
wounds on it. Did you not wear gloves? I was not wearing gloves. I told you to wear gloves. You
did specifically suggest wearing gloves. And that would have been a very good idea. I was wearing a
long sleeve shirt and jeans. Thank God, because I tore up my jeans, still got multiple wounds.
And my elbows got a little fucked up too. But the worst by far was my hand that was not covered
in any clothes. And so I got a big gash. I've got a picture. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's not
of the wound. It's of my bandages. That's all it is. So there's nothing graphic there, just to give
people an idea of is it like my favorite animes were just wrapped up in gauze. That is what I
used actually. I did use gauze. Of course, of course. The shonen healing device. 100% effective
every time. And it's pretty cool. So you can see that in the links below people. And I just uploaded
it. So yeah, pretty fucked up, hurt a lot, still hurts. Definitely looks like an anime.
So basically what I was going to say is I think this is there was one time I was playing on the
black top as a kid where I got pushed. I was playing four squares something and I fell back
and hit my head and like blacked out for a second, which technically counts as a concussion.
But the thing is, that was probably the worst I've ever been hurt in my life, which is to say I really
haven't been hurt a lot. I've never broken a bone. Like this scrape like stands out as one of the worst
things I've ever done. And it really wasn't that bad. Just kind of, you know, got a couple of cuts
and stuff. And so I was just wondering if you guys have had like worse injuries than this.
Like have you ever, I know Tom has had some issues where his like heart literally stopped
for a bit. I don't know if that's an injury per se. My body is even more suicidal than I am.
Have you guys ever like broken a bone while like shredding hardcore or anything like that?
I haven't had any broken bones, but I recall three instances where the injury was pretty
not fun. What happened? Okay, so the earliest I remember was back in the Violet Violins days.
Indeed. Yes. As one would expect. Yeah, we were in a place where we weren't supposed to be and there
was a lot of lumber and the lumber had a lot of nails. Rival gang territory. No, no, it was in our
territory. And there were like a lot of lumber, a lot of nails and I stepped on one and it went
straight through my foot. Oh, went through your foot. Ah, yeah. Oh Christ. Okay. I didn't even
realize what was happening until I couldn't lift my foot. Okay, that's pretty serious. That's pretty
serious. Yeah. And another one was I was there was a recently they cut down a giant tree and it was
like scaling up the logs because of course I would and I slipped, I tripped and what happened
somehow a piece of what's the outer layer of the bark. Yeah, the bark, a piece of bark got under
my toenails. Oh, fuck. Fuck. Anything involving toenails just like freaks me out. Yeah, it was
agree. It was it was terrible. I'm surprised it didn't fall off. At least I don't remember it doing
so. But yeah, were you wearing shoes? Like did it cut through your shoe or something? I was wearing
like, I think it's called sandals. Yeah, you were wearing goddamn woman. What are you doing climbing
trees wearing flip flops or something? It was it was it was summer. And the last one was quite
recent. I think it was last year. I think I was back in La Peña and my mother put a new carpet
in the room I was staying. And like the carpets was very slippery and a few times I was I sort
of slipped but I regained my balance and my mom was like, Oh, we shouldn't nail and we should nail
it down or something like that because I feel like one of us is going to trip. And I was like,
Yeah, we should totally do that. Do that. But same same day a bit later, we haven't done that.
And I was going into my room and I slipped really, really bad. I couldn't get my balance up and I
fell and I hit my hold on right side, the rib cage onto a table. And not only that, I skidded a bit
and some of my skin went off of my foot and I think I still have a scar. Hold on, let me check.
This carpet is evil. So the fact that the carpet was so loose, it just moved on the floor and it
Yeah, okay, okay. I'm pretty sure don't have the scar anymore. But that's good. Oh, no, no,
wait, wait, wait, there's still a little bit of it. There's still a hint of it, but it's fading away.
So Jesus, I'm definitely going to have scars from this from these fucking skateboarding wounds.
But you know what, you know, I was going to say about this, I kind of feel like a badass. So I'm
kind of just happy that it happened. You know, like it wasn't that bad. Everyone needs a little bit
of wear and tear to be a cool guy. So you know, maybe I've been a little too pampered. I feel
cool. I'm happy that I do it. Speaking of scars, a weird scar I have that still hasn't healed and
it baffles me to this day. I was playing with my cat and this is totally earned. He bit me. And
he doesn't bite me hard, but sometimes just enough to break the skin. And it still hasn't healed and
I swear it's been like just as long as like even longer than a year now. And like the skin on my
foot that had completely come off, it's almost almost completely gone. There's barely anything
there. But these tooth scars are just still there. Are they vampire mics? Mark's on your neck. Is it
a vampire cat? No, no, no. It's on my arm. On your arm. Yeah, like the two little streaks on my arm.
I know I have no idea why they're still there. Those platelets need to get to work. Yeah, healing
that shit. Shit, dude. Well, how about you, Tom? Anything like this? Well, I did break my leg in
elementary school. How'd that happen? I constantly had this bad habit and I still do it to this day
of like fucking running up and down stairs with reckless abandon because I just, I got places
to be. I don't have time to casually go down the stairs. Fuck that shit. And so my mom was always
like, you know, you keep doing that, you're going to fall down the stairs. I'm like, ah, dumb bitch,
you don't know what the fuck you're talking about. One time in sixth grade, it did happen. I did fall
down the stairs. I did break my leg and it did suck balls. So were you heading up the stairs
and then just like, oh no, I was going down. Gravity was totally out to get me that day. So you like
tumbled forward or something? Yeah, I slipped and it hurt. It was bad. And then I had to have a cast
for a while. And one of the things that I remember distinctly about this, I had crutches, all that
fucking bullshit, is that during the school I was at, the last period of the day, some days of the
week would be chorus. And I'd have to walk from once, you'd have to walk from one side of the
building to the other to get to the chorus class. And now I had to hobble on crutches and it was
very slow. And most of the time, it would take the entire period for me to crutch walk. Nobody
helped. Nobody waited. I would just show up at chorus and then it would be over and then have
to go all the way back to the other side to get my backpack. Are you kidding me? No, no, no. This
happened multiple times. I just like missed chorus because I just was hobbling my way from one
side of the building to the other, trying to get there. Well, fucking fumdus, Tom hobbling his
way across. Nobody helping him. Chorus sucked though. So I was totally okay with it and never
spoke up about it. So I'm like, yeah, if anyone ever gives me shit, I'll be like, I'm crippled.
Fuck you. Damn. So that was breaking my bone. What else happened?
Oh shit. Oh, when I was a little kid, I got attacked by my cat because I was a retard.
So Mike, I loved, my first cat was cool. He was a cool guy. He was this big fucking massive
death cat and I was a little wee lad of like eight years old and I loved this cat. He was
a cool cat. But one time we were out just hanging out with the neighbors and then their dog
tried to kill our cat. Oh shit, okay. And I had the dumb idea of running over to save
him because I was like, fuck you dog. Don't hurt my cat. He's the best. And my cat was
freaked out. So when I touched it, it attacked me because it thought it was being attacked
by another animal or something. Right. And it ripped my face open and shit. Oh fuck.
I had to get stitches on my eyebrow and let me tell you, that hurts like a bitch. I did
once get an eyebrow piercing so I can kind of relate. This is like getting your eyebrow
pierced like 16 times in a row. Yeah, that's way worse. It's not fun. I still have a little
scar there every time I squint. There's a little like fold there that shouldn't be there from
like a scar. It's very weird. Yeah. But I described getting my eyebrow pierced as like the worst
pain I've ever felt and feeling like a lightning bolt going through my face. Yeah, what it
felt like. Speaking about broken bones, this didn't happen to me, but I feel like I can
share the story. Sure. I was one time in camp and they had like the concentration camp. No,
no, it was regular camp. Just the buildings were like concrete or brick laid like two
story buildings with and what happened was like some boys decided to climb from the second
floor window to the second floor. What is with Eastern European people and climbing shit
where they shouldn't be doing and risking their lives. But okay, all right. From the
window to the balcony and we were like the girls were on the balcony were ready to sort
of like help them over and I was one of them and it's just it's so stupid. We should have
told them no, but I don't think they would have listened. Anywho, so they did doing that
and one boy sort of reached out and we tried to grab his hand, but we didn't manage to
grab his hand and he slipped and he fell. Oh God, from a second story. Yeah. And he broke
both his arms. What happened? He broke both his arms. Shit. He broke both his arms. Oh my God.
And so like you're there reaching out your hand and like he missed your hand. All right,
all right, mage, mage, be honest, be honest, mage. You did this on purpose, didn't you? You wanted
him to suffer the violent violence. No, no, no, no, no, no, I had a crush on this boy.
And you crushed him. So you had to see him crush below you.
Oh God. No, no, it was it was. It was a weird affection thing. That's the custom I just don't
understand. That is seriously though, you see those videos of like Russian boys like climbing
on these weird like just like freakishly tall like oil rigs and shit and like hanging off with
one arm dangling over nothing and like giving a thumbs up with like the other hand. You see that
shit? I mean, that's what it reminds me of. Jesus Christ. There's a yearning for death in the Eastern
European population, I think. I can relate since I'm half Polish, you know, I get it. Fascinating.
Yeah, they called the ambulance and he, you know, wasn't in camp for the rest of the time.
I would hope so. Did his arms heal okay? I mean, did he? I think so. Like by the time it got out,
I went to actually visit him because I was I lived near the hospital. Well, not near the
hospital, but it was a walk away. And I went to visit him and he was already out. So. Oh, that's
good. Okay. Well, still. God damn. That's pretty fucking funny. It wasn't. He's the important
question that made you guys ever hook up after that? You ever go anywhere with that crush?
The thing is that we might have, maybe, but his mother was a psycho. So. Oh,
cockblock by mom. The worst fate. I was going to say, having both arms paralyzed can put a man
in a compromising position at a formative young years and will need assistance with various activities.
Well, I mean, okay, I guess that that's pretty much it. Any other traumatic stories? I mean,
there was the time that I just kicked Ben for no reason. That was pretty funny, but it wasn't
really a serious injury or anything. Was there anything else? I mean, I had crazy fevers when
I was young, but that's not the same kind of. Yeah, and axe fell on me and almost cut my head off,
but only to cut my finger instead. Oh, I mean, how bad did it hurt the finger? Not bad at all.
Like I still have like a scar on my finger from where it like sliced a bit of flesh open and
had to get stitches and everything. But like if I had not moved when I did, it would have like
hit the back of my neck and probably killed me. So that was cool. God was just like, no,
you still got another couple of decades of suffering, boy. I mean, there wasn't at one time.
I know I've told this before where I was just what I was on a bunk bed. I like flipped up.
I was like on the bottom bunk, but there were bars above. I grabbed those bars. I flipped upside
down as I like to do on those to like do flips. And one time I was just hanging upside down head
down. And I was like, this will be fun. And I just let go and dropped onto my head and nearly
snapped my fucking neck like for fun. I don't know what I was thinking, but it seemed fun at the time.
But that's how it goes. That's how it goes. Yeah, yeah, that's just really all there is to it.
Really stupid retarded ideas, I suppose. Yeah, well, I guess that's it. I guess that's it.
Yeah. Don't die, kids. Yeah, try not to do this. Don't do dangerous things. A little bit. If you're
going to do dangerous things, you know, prepare your will ahead of time and I don't know, make sure
it's worth it. Like I've done skydiving and could have died, but it's actually pretty safe. Safety
precautions. Yeah. And I did it in tandem. One thing I remember. It wasn't an injury or anything,
but it was very scary. So, you know, like those thermometers that have like, what's it called?
Mercury in them, I think, right? Yeah. And mercury is poisonous when it's like gas, right?
Yep, sure is. It's liquid, too. But yeah. Yeah, so I broke a thermometer and I was really scared
of telling my parents, so I hid it. But then, thankfully, I came clean because where I hid it
was the bedroom. And well, if I hadn't told them, I dread to think what would have happened.
You know, on that specific thing, my mom told me, you know, my mom like grew up in like the 50s
and 60s and stuff. Well, most of the 60s, but whatever. A point is like, when she was a kid,
she told me the other day, or this was years ago, she's like, yeah, well, like when we were kids,
we used to intentionally crack open like mercury thermometers and just like fuck around with the
mercury and just like, you know, play with it and like roll it around. And she's like,
this may have been a bad idea. Fucking terrible idea. I mean, yeah, but how the fuck this was
like before they knew, I guess. Yeah, it's just like, oh, because like mercury is kind of cool.
It's really cool. It's liquid metal. It's dope. It's pretty sick, too bad. Everything that's cool
is also bad for you. Unfortunately. Yeah, like dropping onto your neck from a bunk bed. It's
cool as hell. But damn it. It's a forbidden snack. The worst thing for you. It's a forbidden fun.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, God. Yeah. You should title this segment forbidden fun, aka traumatic injury. Yeah,
exactly. I mean, those those girls who cut themselves because their emo seem like they're
having a good time. Yeah. Well, if it's good enough for emo girls, good enough for me, you know,
that's my that's my bar. Shit. So so anyone. Alright, well, what else we got on the table?
I got another thing to talk about. But you got you guys you guys got a I'm done. I'm done with
injuries. So if you want to move on to something else, please please save me from my floundering.
I did have a funny thing happen to me right before this episode began. And this is I got to start
today's episode of the PGP the Pokemon Go podcast, which is just to say that my mom calls me
so my mom visited me in Cincinnati recently at the legendary encounter legendary cat of being on
the Shekels for heckles episode and whatnot. And while she was here, I got her introduced to Pokemon
Go and got her playing a little bit. And she seems pretty into it. And the way I can definitely
tell is that she just called me asking for like help. And she she was walking the dog beanie.
And she was just like, Nate, how do I or I just got a thing I'm going to polka stops to get polka
balls. But I'm it's telling me max I've got max capacity for items. What do I do? So I explained
to where you got to throw away items you don't need you can upgrade if you pay money or you have
due gym battles, which I'm sure she has not done yet. Or but mostly just throw away items to get
more polka balls and stuff. So yeah, I guess what I'm saying is that was funny. And parents will
never get it. It's interesting, like because like Pokemon Go is one of those games that's
definitely like got like normie potential. Yeah, Pokemon like the Pokemon spin off game seem to
be good with that. Like my parents hate video games, think they're gay, think I've wasted my
entire life and they're not wrong. But they are both huge fans of Pokemon snap and we would play
that together all the time. And my mom like beat that game and played it multiple times. Wow. And
like, interesting doesn't play video games hates them a lot. But Pokemon snap for the n64 was her
jam. And she was obsessed with it just as much as we were back in the day. Wow. And I don't was a
little bit like that with racing games. He never really played much, but he always like showed an
interest whenever it came up, which was interesting. My dad is like into video games, but doesn't play
them and is in denial about it. Like my dad is just like a nerd in denial. Like at some point,
he got like bullied in schools who became jacked and like learned how to fight and like became one
of those guys. But but he was before that he was a nerd. He's left that identity behind.
But it's still there. He just ignores it to the best of his abilities. I think my dad
generally likes video games, but he doesn't play them at the moment. I remember in my childhood,
he would play. I don't remember the name of the game, but I think it was on a Nintendo console
because I remember we also had like the original Mario's that my sister and me played and he played
like this other one where you had to build like a maze sort of for tanks to battle like and and
then yeah, you built the battlefield basically and then you maneuvered around it with one little
tank while five other tanks went after you. So you had to yeah, it was quite fun. And the other
two games I remember him playing would be like Doom and Doom 2. So yeah, yeah, that's some good
I guess on Doom 3. Yeah. So, you know, the Doom series. Sadly, his computer is not strong enough
to handle the newest doom. So we cannot probably play that on your fucking phone these days or
something. I tried. I tried. It didn't run. Oh, yeah. Get a new graphics card. Just go out buy GTX
1060 slap it in your nest machine and yeah. Yes, my dad had bad might and magic for the PC.
Him and my uncle would would hang out together and play might and magic for the PC back in the day.
And that was a cool game. I played that a little bit later in life because I was a little child.
I ruined one of their might and magic games when I was when I was like a very young kid like
younger than five because I've come a long way with computers in my life. Now I can like build
computers. I can put them together. I can do all this cool shit with them. I'm basically that
IT guy right now at for I am games. It's like my job. But back in the day, they were playing
might and magic like three, I think, for like DOS and I came downstairs and I thought the computer
was hungry. So I shoved a cookie into the floppy drive and crashed the whole thing. Are you kidding
me? Are you fucking serious? No. Okay. Why did you think it was hungry? What a fascinating
I can relate, though. I had the same experience. What? Are you kidding me? Like, I think it was
like a what's it called? VCR thing? VCR. No, no, the tapes. Yeah, the tapes, those big tapes,
big bulky tapes. Yeah, VCR. Yeah, I thought it was hungry. So because I put like metal bits inside
of it instead of like a cookie because it's a metal thing. It eats metal of things.
Mage went to the next level. And what about like a TV being thirsty? Oh, no. Oh, God. You didn't pour
shit on a TV, did you? I pour liquid into the TV. You got to water the TV. Why? Why? It was thirsty.
Okay, wait, stop, stop. What made you think specifically that they were hungry and or thirsty?
I don't know. What was it? This is like 25 years ago. I was I'm not going to recall my thought process.
I was like a literal baby. Yeah, I was five or less years old. I can tell you that much. Five or less.
Because like, I could see think like, okay, you see like a floppy disk drive, and it kind of looks
like an open mouth, right? I sort of get the connection there. But like, was there something
on the screen that said like, feed me? I mean, I don't know. I think me and Mage both just have
like, like had stupid amounts of empathy as children. Yeah, I still have stupid amounts of
empathy. Yeah, I try and crush that feeling every day.
Well, for the yeah, that's good. But for the TV being thirsty, like, where did you pour the liquid
into? Remember back when TVs used to be like super bulky and not like flat screens. So on the back,
there would be like, slits to get like the hot air out. So I did that. Oh, God.
Surprisingly, right onto the CRT, like, like, yeah, surprisingly, dear God, it did not ruin the TV
because I turned it off right afterward. And I think it had time to dry. Oh, and just did anybody
know? Did you ever confess your crime? No one? No one knew. Oh, man, the perfect crime.
Watering the TV. So did did your shoving food or metal bits into the VCR?
Oh, that's right. Oh, that's fucked it up.
What metal bits did you shove in there? Like, where did actually this metal shavings hanging
around? It was it was from, um, uh, I guess when you live in the desolate wasteland of the violent
violence, there's metal bits all over the place. A brush, a hairbrush. There we go. A hairbrush.
A metal hairbrush? Yeah, the metal is spiky bits. Oh, yes. Oh, okay, okay, okay. Yeah, so
oh, but this is funny because this is kind of the origin story of how I learned English because
once the VCR was fucked up, my parents got me cable, which had Cartoon Network in it and me
being four to five years old, I didn't care what language they spoke. So I, you know, it's just
pretty cartoons. So I watched TV a lot and that's how I learned English. So this was like a formative
moment of your life. If you hadn't fed the VCR, you might not even be able to talk to us at this
point. At least with very broken English. My God, who would have known that at this point,
reality is forked and there's another fork of reality where mage decided, you know what,
I guess the VCR is not hungry and then none of her life is the way it is now.
What a fascinating situation. The butterfly effect for sure. Holy shit. What about you,
Tom? So shoving the cookie into the floppy disk drive, how much did that fuck it up?
I guess that fucked up their game and they couldn't finish. So was the disk in there currently
or something? It must have been. It must have been because there's no way, because even,
I think about it now, there's no way that shoving something into a floppy drive would kill the
entire computer because all the actual components are way far away, but they must have been running
off of floppy disk and that just broke the game. The computer itself probably still worked.
Yeah, probably. Yeah, it's pretty stupid. Definitely. I've come a long way.
Guys, remember floppy disks? I do. I used floppy disks back in the day.
I used to use floppy disks. It's just so amazing now how much stuff we can cram onto disks and
stuff. I think a floppy disk, if I remember correctly, I think they had a limit of about
two megabytes if I remember correctly. It was 1.44 megabytes. Yeah, there you go. I have no idea
why it was that number, but that's what it was. Do you guys remember before those floppy disks,
like the bigger floppy disks, like the floppy disks that were actually floppy and they held
even less data? Oh, I remember those, but I never used them. I've never used them, but I know they're
real. I know they're a thing that existed. It was ironic that floppy disks were actually pretty
solid. I mean, they were made of plastic. You could bend them a little bit, but... Yeah, I don't,
I don't know. I wonder what people would call floppy disks. Well, because like Tom was saying,
I think the original versions were quite large and were literally floppy. They were like bendy
plastic. Does anybody remember the classic PSA video about piracy back in the day in the 90s
called, Don't Copy That Floppy? You remember the phrase, but I don't think I've seen it. It's a
cheesy 90s rap video about some guy telling kids, Don't Copy That Floppy. It's hilarious. Damn,
the 90s were a different time. It was amazing. That's hilarious, because a lot of the games
that I owned or got to play back in those days were bootlegs or pirated versions. Exactly,
there was no copy protection back in the day, so their copy protection was, Please Don't Do That.
The times sure have changed. We used to use rap to get kids to stop copying that floppy. Now we
use rap to get kids to smoke crack. The world's always changing. And sip that lean.
Well, shit. What a fascinating story. That was a great diversion or a great tangent. That was
absolutely delicious, delectable. I've got one other thing I wanted to bring up, which is just
what we were talking about right before this episode, which is about addictions, specifically
sugar. Let's talk about the worst part of the human condition. It's addiction to sugar.
I would argue that that's part of a larger issue. It's definitely there, but we're just slaves to
our biology to such a massive degree. We don't actually need sugar. Yeah, we don't actually
need it though, I don't think. Unless you're a bodybuilder or traveling on stuff, you actually
need a lot of energy. Yeah, that's true. That's true. But no, here we are. All of us, I think,
kind of struggle to varying degrees with resisting the temptation to eat just junk food and shit.
It's tough. It's real fucking hard. I can give up almost anything except for sugary stuff.
It's tough. Again, because I've been doing keto like Ben for the last three weeks,
I've had no sugar. I've become addicted to diet soda because it's the only sweet thing I can have.
I've been slowly easing into keto because like I still had a lot of leftover food that need to
be eaten. Like I said, I ordered the candy corn before I decided to go keto. Sure. I mean,
that's been lasting me several days, so a few pieces a day, so it's not going to be too much.
Man, there was a time in my life, and I want to get back to it. I'm working to get there,
and Huell and all this stuff is helping me, where I just, I had mastered this. I had conquered it.
I went a year without fast food. I think actually I might have eaten it one time,
and a year without soda, and I still don't drink soda like ever, and actually this time is what
broke me on soda. I just don't care anymore, but I definitely eat more junk food than that now,
and I just, I want to get back. This is an interesting thing about diet. It's like,
this is almost a problem with the internet now is that there's just so much information. I have no
idea what's true anymore. That's true. Because I've done research on diet, and I've tried to
look up things casually, just like, all right, what's the best thing to eat? And there's no
consensus. I was on Twitter, and this is just the most recent example of me thinking of this,
is I was on Twitter, and one of the people I follow on Twitter is a religious vegan,
like insanely vegan. All they do is just make art and products about how good it is to be vegan,
and fuck you if you're not vegan. They're arts great, so I follow them anyway, and I knew them
from like back in the pony days and stuff, but they've transitioned from pony to vegan.
Between two religions. Yeah, yeah, exactly. So you know, Church of Twilight to the Church of
Chicken, I don't know. So a shout out to them, they're great, but vegan.
I think all the characters, if I think about it, are probably vegan in my little pony.
I suppose- They eat milk products in pony shit. That's true. They're vegetarian though,
they're close. They're vegetarian, yeah. So yeah, so there was just a thread that they had
retweeted, and I just kind of looked through it, because I'm always interested. I'm interested
in the zealot mindset, because I want to instill it in my audience, so they'll never abandon me.
So I'm always taking peeks, trying to peel back the layers and figure out how to do it.
And this thread was just like people going back and forth fighting about
diet and veganism, and people are like, no, no, no, you don't understand, like the best,
like if you look at like ancient Asian cultures and stuff, all they would do is eat
like nothing but carbohydrates and sugars, and they'd live to be like 107. That's how people
do now. That's the most healthy thing to do. And people are like, no, no, no, we couldn't
evolve without eating meat, and meat's the most important thing. You can't have carbohydrates,
or pores that are exhaled with carbs. You got to go fats and proteins. And it's like,
I don't know which one's right. There's evidence on both sides. What are we supposed to do?
Science is not settled. It's really not.
So because I'm doing keto, and I'm like, am I being healthy? Because there's like a
huge subset of people who'd be like, you're eating the worst shit possible for you,
and you're going to die early of like coronary heart disease. And like, maybe that's true.
See, I think people, when they say like, oh, you know, your arteries are gonna get
clogged up with fat and stuff like that, because they've always considered like,
hold on, how to words? Let me words. So when you're consuming both carbohydrates and fat
in large quantities, yeah, like the fat is going to get unhealthy for you. But if you
just focus on just fat and not carbohydrates, I think that sort of balances out. I'm, you know,
I mean, I don't know. It's just, it's just someone, I'm just someone who read stuff.
So, you know, I'm no professional. I think that's the, the general like thrust behind
keto is that like, you're, you're burning fat for energy now. So it's not getting caught in
your body. Because if you're eating a ton of fat, but you're burning the carbohydrates,
your body's not doing anything with the fat and it just kind of like sticks to you.
Yeah, because the body priority is carbohydrates. And yeah, the fat just
sets in into your body. Because it's basically just sugars. Like carbohydrates break down
immediately into sugars and it's the easiest to process. I don't know. I'm not a scientist. I'm
not a smart person. So it's just like, I'm just a normal human being that is terrified of death
and wants to live long enough to make it to the technological singularity. But during that time,
I want to look swole and good and, and get some puss. So I'm just, I'm just in this,
this middle ground like, what do I do? How do I maximize? How do I biohack properly? That's
what I wanted until I can just get real technical like machine hacking with my robot limbs. I got
a biohack and we don't understand the language yet. So it's very fucking confusing because I don't
know what the fuck to do. Right, Tom? I've been going to the gym three times a week for the last
like three and a half, four months. That's great. That's tremendous. I'm trying to step it up to
five times a week at some point. I'm just lazy. Now it doesn't necessarily have to be, it's not
necessarily better to work out more times. I mean, there, there's different plans. So if it's
like easier, like with me, it's easier to work out three times a week. So I found a plan that's
like optimized for that. And you just do the workout that's assigned. So I'm just saying,
like one can, the question is not settled as like, yeah, five workouts are definitely better than
three works out. A lot of it depends on what you're trying to do. That's my point again. You
know, it's the same. It's like, what the fuck? Like how, how do you would think after a couple
thousand years, we'd figure out the baselines of like how this like system works. And we're not
even fucking close. In terms of dieting, in terms of dieting, I think during like the world wars,
they kind of falsified information to fatten people up or something like that. So and a lot
of people who are older dietitians, they still sort of base it on their old knowledge. And
but because, you know, they're the experienced people, all the newer people base it off of
their knowledge. And you know, it just kind of get passed on, whereas some newer people, the
upstarts, you know, have some new data and that's hard to believe. Here's an interesting fact
that is, it's not totally settled or anything, but like, so like if you're trying to gain muscle,
right, we all know that protein is important for that. Okay, how much protein should one eat?
Until very recently, there really was not an agreed upon answer to that. The general agreement was
a lot. And the amount that had been thrown out was like one gram of protein every day per
pound of body mass you have. I think it was pound of lean body mass. If you're really fat, you're
not going to get, you know, if you eat 400 grams of protein, that's not actually beneficial.
Because you got so much excess fat there. But it's but like just recently, my voice Scooby 1961,
who had some good time to bring him in because he's the guy who I've learned the most from over
the years. Everyone should listen to him if you have interest in health and fitness at all.
He reported in a video that there was a large, I forget what it's called, but like a multi-stage
like comprehensive analysis that had been done of many independent like protein analysis
like studies that were tracking like specifically muscle gain based on protein consumption.
And see, this is not totally settled. But the information that was assembled indicates that
the ideal amount is actually 0.7 not one gram of protein per pound of body mass, but 0.7 grams.
As in if you weigh 100 pounds and you're lean, muscley guy, then you would want to eat 70 grams
of protein per day to gain muscle. And if you can eat more, but you won't get any benefit. That is
like basically the optimal amount. And like and the other important information that was found was
that because people that speculate for a long time like, you know, like way is basically milk protein
that comes from milk. You could eat like chicken to get straight up like muscle, you know, animal
protein, or you could get like like lima beans of protein, you could get like people have lima
bean protein you can just take. And then the analysis concluded, it didn't matter what kind of protein
they ate. As long as you just get that 0.7, you know, grams of protein per pound of lean body
mass, then you will gain at optimal speeds of muscle. And it doesn't matter what kind of protein
you eat. That was like the big conclusion. And like you'd think that we would have figured that
shit out way long ago. But only now are people starting to understand any of this shit. And
there's so much more to know that we don't know. And when you bring in the question of health,
specifically, health is such a complex thing. And there's so many systems that are involved,
like there is no going to be one answer like this is the healthiest way to live.
Because it's like the problem becomes is that like health, because like, no, it's not like all
human bodies work exactly the same way based on the region you're from, like your genetics kind of
like have tweaked a little bit to like better suit that environment. And then like, within that
individuals are different as well. So like, we got to like have some fucking futuristic tech or
just scans your body and like, all right, based on your genetic makeup and shit, this is your ideal
diet to keep you at peak condition. Hey, guys, here's a here's a here's a here's a conspiracy
theory for yes, since we talked about earlier. Yeah. So the dietitian sort of people in America,
it's it's quite a huge business, isn't it? Oh, it's panic. And if in and if everyone suddenly
got thin, they'd be out of business now, weren't they wouldn't they would that's certainly true.
So they are making people not get thinner, because they wouldn't right, right. No, this isn't even
a joke. Like it's I was actually going to bring this up next is that like, I think a reason a lot
of this alternate diet stuff is even coming up now is because with the internet, you can like,
there's financial incentive at this point to like delve deeper into this shit, because if you can
figure out the next like, diet craze, you can make a fuck ton of money off it. Yeah, which people
do six back shortcuts and what exactly. So like, there's, there's all this conflicting research
and stuff now, because everyone's like cherry picking, so their program can work. And it's just
like, again, the internet has this huge influx of information. Yeah, and I think the traditional
food pyramid was definitely because like there was like excess grains and like American like
industry. So they put grains as like the most important part so they could sell more that
shit. I think I think that's definitely good. And out of this swirling chaos of information,
things will emerge. I would argue though, that I think frankly, we really know the most important
things. The problem is, they require large amounts of effort over a long period of time,
because we know right now, if people, and this is available to like basically almost every American,
if you exercise probably every day, cardio and weightlifting, or maybe just both are good,
if you, if you exercise a lot, and you like eat lots of vegetables, like that really is the key,
just eat lots of vegetables and like beans and stuff, and do not eat junk food, like just,
just skip it all. Skip cake, skip cupcakes, you know, skip all that stuff, skip candy and you
just eat. I know, I'm just saying, see, that's the thing, nobody wants to do it. I mean, the really
disciplined like what we'd lift our bodybuilder guys, like they do it, because like it's kind of
important, like for whatever reason they've decided it's worth doing, worth sacrificing that stuff
to get these. But like to your average American who's just living their life and is like,
wait, wait, why are you asking me to like stop eating sugar, just that I'll get healthy, but like
that doesn't sound fun, and I have to do it forever. What's the fun of being healthy if you're miserable?
I mean, I, that's okay, see that, we need to break the, we need to break the conditioning,
you need to break the, the link between having sugar. No, no, no, I get you, I'm all, I'm all,
I'm all for health, it is, and it's definitely a struggle, but I would like to find a balance between
I ask that question, I ask that question myself all the time, like when me and Michelle go out,
Michelle eats like a bunny, and she'll just get a salad, and I'll be like, but I want a burger,
why can't I just have a cheeseburger with bacon? Why are you bullying me to get a salad, you fucking
asshole? Why do you hate me so much? And I just think like, I don't want to live in a world where
I can't eat a cheeseburger right now, so fuck it. Just get it, just get it, the lettuce wrap, it's
basically a salad at the end. I wish they offered that in the UK, I swear. I gotta do that. I don't
think they do, I don't think they offered it in the UK. That's, I've literally been living off of
bacon burgers and lettuce wraps. I kind of live in the ghetto, so I'm not sure they would have
lettuce wraps if I, if I try, but I do need to try, at least at some point. Five guys and Wendy's
will do it. I went to Burger King and they looked me like I had three heads when I asked for a
lettuce wrap, so I just walked out, and I was like, no, never mind. There's five guys and Wendy's not
too far. I should, I should make a trip and report back. Five guys is definitely better,
and it's worth it. There's five guys not too far from me. I never been there. Maybe we should both
try in the coming week to get there and try this lettuce wrap business. But I'm socially anxious,
I'll have to actually ask something off of the menu. No, no, no, it's on the menu. It's something
you can get there. It's not like a weird substitute. They offer lettuce wraps. Okay, okay, I'll look at
the menu. I look at the menu, and if they don't have it, I'm not going to ask about it. I mean,
every time I've asked for a lettuce wrap, they've just hit a button and it's come up on the screen
and it's on the receipt as well. Okay, that's a good sign. Okay, yeah, but you're in America. Maybe
they don't do that in UK. Okay, hang on. New subject real quick, social anxiety. Why in God's name
would it be a problem to go to a place, ask for a thing, and then to face the sheer terror in
realizing they do not have it on the menu. Just imagine the horror as their as that confused
look crosses their face. I don't like interacting with people. I've slowly been trying to conquer
this because I just like what I try and do in these situations is if like if the roles were
versed, I wouldn't give a fuck. So they don't give a fuck because I don't give a fuck about
anybody around me 99% of the time. And neither do they. I try that guiding principle. Yeah,
I try that too. I keep telling myself and that that sort of helps me just move in a public space.
I feel you. I feel you. I think, okay, don't don't give me a moment here. I think what would help
mage is if someone had a gun to your head. What helps me usually is to have someone near me
like next to me like a friend or something like that. That's usually helpful.
But it doesn't work miracles though. I still wouldn't be able to ask about the wrap.
I literally, you know, I used to have some, I don't know. And I still every once in a while,
I do like sometimes I'll just avoid going to the coffee machine like at work just like,
oh, there's someone there. I'll go later, which is a pussy move. And I shouldn't do,
but I still do do it sometimes. I think I told you guys about the time where I didn't go into a store
to buy myself Pokemon plushies. Yeah, even though you wanted it. Yeah. Yeah, which is so sad.
We all need to overcome this, you know, we all need to. How can we let anxiety about what people
say get in our way? I've been getting better. I mean, like, I think I talked about you specifically.
Yeah, just saying, just saying. It's I mean, you're never it's always going to be a struggle,
but like every time you push back, I find it gets a little bit easier the next time. It's
really it's a muscle, I think. And like if you if you don't exercise it, like I've noticed this
because like, I don't know, like I have a real job, I have to interact with people. So I'm kind
of forced to to exercise some of this stuff a lot. But like if I worked at home and like,
for example, was a YouTuber, I would like never have to go out, I would probably continue to be
an awkward weirdo and you know, who would not develop these these skills and stuff. So it's
kind of good that this is why I say the gun to your head is like, I try to think when I'm in
these situations sometimes less so now, but especially in the past, I think like, what if I
had to do this or I die, could I do it? And then I think, yeah, absolutely, I absolutely could.
And then that that I find that helpful, at least to a degree.
That puts it in perspective, it feels like the end of the world until you're like,
actually, it's really not. And I really I think a lot about welcome to the NHK when I'm in situations
like that, because it's basically social anxiety, the show. And, you know, I like because there's a
character in it, of course, famously, who like, just cannot do anything. He just his social anxiety
is so bad that he just doesn't leave his room ever. But then one time, like his sister leaves and
isn't coming to give him food. So if he stays there, he will just die. So basically, there's no
choice but to leave his room and go get a job. And he does so and he lived and actually he's way
happier afterward. So basically, what I'm saying is, hire a get biter to threaten your life and
say he's going to kill you. If you don't do XYZ, then if you don't get a lettuce wrap, he will shoot.
He'll put two in your skull. When there's no guns in the UK. At least we don't. Oh, I forgot. Okay,
well, what was it like? Knife. Knife. Knife. Knife. Knife. Knife. Knife. Knife are like the guns of
the UK now, basically. Potato Peelers. Potato Peelers. Potato Peelers. That's what it was. Oh
my God, you're right. That was a thing. Hellas. Goddamn. Sad as well. It's pretty sad. Pretty
strange. Well, shit. Do you want to want to pivot into into something that me and Digi were talking
about? And I want to bring it up. Actually, I was talking to Mage a little bit about it before we
started. So I guess Digi and May have been watching Pokemon analysis videos constantly,
because we have a computer now in the kitchen. So while they're cooking, old anime or like the
new one? Like the games and stuff. Oh, okay. They've been watching like just videos on like,
because I guess like there's a huge contingent of like the Pokemon fandom that's just dedicated to
like breaking the old games and finding weird shit out about them. We saw some of that and the
Pokemon race here on the program yesterday. But there's there's a fuck ton of that going on,
apparently. So they've been watching videos like that. But then I just happened to come down
when they were watching this video about a ROM hack of Pokemon Crystal called Pokemon Crystal
Clear. I've heard of that. And it was the coolest fucking shit I've ever seen in my goddamn life.
What's what's so cool that I haven't heard any of the details. So what Pokemon Crystal Clear is,
it's a ROM hack of Crystal, where you know how Pokemon Crystal usually plays. You start in Jodo,
you go to Council, you get like 16 badges, you can fight the leaf for it, and you go to Mount
Silver and fight red. Like that's the the progress of the game. Pokemon Crystal Clear changes it
so that you can start in Jodo or Kanto, either in New Bark or Pallet Town, you can customize
your character, you can choose from 25 different starters that all have different difficulty levels.
And then they've removed all the HM blocks in the entire map and edited it so you can go
anywhere you want in any order. So the game is completely open. It's like an open world.
Are there like, are there like levels? Like if you go to one area, will there just be like level
50 Pokemon? So like, well, I'm not going to go there. I'm gonna go. I think some of them have
like that, like the levels like scale and stuff. But I know the gym leaders can be done in any order
and they scale as you get more badges. So you can like you can go fight like Faulkner as the last
guy and have like a level 60 something Zapdos. But if you fight him first, he'll have his like
level nine Pidgey. So like it all scales like that. And you can rechallenge the gyms at any time at
any skill level. Now that's what I like to hear. Yeah. So like if you if you fight like say you
fight Faulkner first like you normally would and you have five badges, you can go back to the gym
and fight him at a level five gym level. So he has stronger guys. Fabulous. So it's fucking sick.
And so it's just like the best. I can't even imagine even wanting to play vanilla crystal
anymore because it sounds 10 times better. And then you run by default instead of walking. So
the movement speed is like triple nice. And there's tons of little like quality of life things
that enhance the sprites. The colors are more accurate. Oh, is the Pokemon Crystal the one
where you had to go to the mines and mine things? That's diamond. That's diamond. Okay. Yeah. Crystal
was like the remake, the addition to like golden silver, like the second gen games. So it's like
a Gameboy color rom hack. And like they just added a bunch of other little things like that. So
it's fucking amazing. And between that and SPV three, or just like it was just the Halo mod we
played on I am Games a couple weeks back where they just took Halo one for PC, reskinned it,
added all the guns and enemies from Halo two and three into it and like rebalance the whole
campaign around it and like added to the levels. Mods are just better than games. Like, like,
like, like, like the dedication of these people is amazing because like true Pokemon crystal clear
is a better idea than any Pokemon game that's come after it. Like that's just fucking sick. I think
based on Pokemon's track record, we basically we cannot count on the Pokemon company or Nintendo
to give us the Pokemon game that like we veterans would want. The rom hacks are the answer.
But like the weird thing is like and then like SPV three is a better Halo game than Halo four or
five by a significant degree. So it's just like, why are we playing games? We should just play mods.
Like how is like one person making these better like they're just better like mods are just I
would say I think there's there's there's something to be said that and this is not a criticism of
like the mods are but like the modders do have the benefit of kind of hindsight or like they're
able to take a game that was made you know 99% by someone else. They do the additional 1% of tweaks
that like everyone has agreed like this would make the game so much better and like they get to do
that. Maybe in like modern terms like like I know that I think in Hollow Knight for example,
like people thought that like the way that you get the final ultimate super duper extra like final
DLC DLC completion stuff was too hard. So I think they did nerf some of the bosses. That's a tool
that like is available to devs now that I kind of hate but they can make some of those tweaks that
might otherwise be like something that a modder would do. Here's here's the thing though that I
would argue there. I would say that Hollow Knight, this is kind of like I think Hollow Knight in terms
of like an indie game that we're talking about and like these mods they have more in common than
like a AAA game and Hollow Knight does because like what is Hollow Knight other than like someone
having an idea of like making a Metroidvania better and instead of just modding Symphony
of the Night or something they just made their own game. Like it's the same kind of idea like we
have these small teams of like individuals who are able to take these old concepts that like
modern companies are still iterating on but do it in a better way and I think it's just because
they're more in touch with the community and understand what people want. Yeah that's a big
one and I think there's like an old expression people say that it's like like with a big company
you you have like more manpower. What you're sacrificing is the unified vision. When you've
got like a small team or or like literally like one modder their unified vision like is able to
shine. So as long as they're able to like work with like other people's tools or maybe they make
like a really small project it can it can really shine kind of like like Undertale I guess which
is like a almost a one-man project or something. Yeah it's just it's core vision completely shines
through when you play that game or or Hall of Night with its like three-man team that made that
or whatever. So there's I mean I think it's just that like corporate influence and this is why I
think like Final Fantasy has kind of lost its way because like what was Final Fantasy? Final Fantasy
was it had a fairly big team but like they still had I don't know kind of like an indie attitude-ish
where like they would take some people's like weird kooky ideas like like the Sorceress and Final
Fantasy 8 was actually originally an idea they were going to put into Final Fantasy 7 but like
there was just too much shit already in that game like all right we're going to save this one and
then they made that kind of like the conceit like the main story of Final Fantasy 8. But the point
is it was just like weird shit that like people came up with and then they implemented because
like their their main thing was let's make an interesting game with these cool ideas that we
like and it like I'm not saying that they weren't thinking about like how to make a really successful
blockbuster because that definitely was on their minds but like they didn't it wasn't a Final Fantasy
15 that was like bait like as soon as Tabata took over not perhaps not originally with Nomura but
with Tabata it was like let's make a game that people like and will want to buy and that is like
the foremost thing so it's like community tell us what game we should make like tell us what you
want because we don't fucking know we're not auteurs we're not like creative people who are here to
like implement a vision no no no we're here providing a service and that's all we're here doing
you know it's the difference between like those two visions I guess something like that yeah
mods are better play mods are better yep we agreed okay guys hey uh switching topic I guess um
have you have you guys you probably have talked in a podcast before about Goblin Slayer right
yeah we I think a little bit not not too much okay because because I just I just watched the
four episodes that are out now okay okay what do you think I hold up but first can you like
break me on the controversy like I know people were saying rape is bad basically and so the
controversy is is to summarize it's it's this basically so the entire controversy was based
only on the first episode and nobody cares anymore as far as I can tell but but it was
basically this it was that the um the depiction of the violence and especially the rape that
was the big issue that you know canonically 100% does happen in episode one of Goblin Slayer um
was like explicit did not kind of warn people about the content because the show was like
advertised is kind of like a PG-13 um and then it also though I would say the rape does not
actually happen on screen it does technically happen off screen um and then and then uh people
felt that it also kind of sexualized and almost glorified the the rape and sexual violence and
normal violence okay I disagree with that part okay because you've watched four episodes now
yeah you've done way more research than anyone who's actually like who wrote those articles or
anything what it was like they showed just enough of that part to sort of to give people
idea of what was happening but they didn't glorify it they didn't sexualize it they didn't make it
look appealing at all and people who say that they did it it's just a grasping of straws honestly
like uh I feel like honestly no one would have given a shit if that scene wasn't there and people
are just being like way too sensitive about it I think I mean I if it was like PG-13 and stuff okay
I get it like like if I had been watching and that just came up without me knowing what I was getting
into it would have probably shocked me a little bit but like at the same time like we also have
anime like Attack on Titan and stuff and there's gonna be like gruesome gory shit out there it's
it's not surprising based on what people said though I think the answer is really quite clear
it's just that people are just super uncomfortable with rape I really think that's what it comes
down to and I I get it but I mean I don't know like it's it's weird multiple people got murdered
murdered dead they are deceased and yet the rape is the thing that people more focused on like I
get it I get it it's people frankly people just care more about sexual violence than just straight
up murder and stuff yeah that's it that's really all there is to it I think it's because when there's
when there's sexual assault like you know the victim could still talk about how bad it was but
if someone's dead they're fucking dead yeah I guess there's something there's kind of a finality to
murder that makes us kind of not care as much I sort of desensitize I think I did not pronounce
that right there's no murder survivors groups like making being activists and talking about how
murder is so which is kind of that that really sucks because like we really should be we should
be I would say opposing murder more than we're opposing rape I think that's fair to say I think
one is a worse crime or at the very least equally because there is no I don't know I'm confused
they're both terrible crimes basically but okay so the controversy aside though it's an interesting
anime I I'm actually interested to see where they're going I guess like minor spoilers I'm not sure
what exactly spoilers they're gonna slay some goblins basically I really like the character of the
goblin slayer he's just like not there and he's so calm and just like uh-huh yes affirmative
basically sort of character and then later on you find out his backstory which is very brief like
they didn't go you know into weepy story time but yeah you don't really need it yeah it was just
enough to know the fact and like I think because they didn't like the way they framed it is like
it's a story that a lot of people share he's not the only one he's not the special little boy
everyone like a lot of people have to go through this pain and yet people still dismiss goblins as
like a not a big threat and therefore he dedicates himself to slaying the goblins because no one
else does that was definitely a thing that a lot of people in the controversy were saying that like
because all those characters in episode one are kind of they're sort of framed to be like our main
character party guys and then people felt so sidelined by the fact that like oh my god guys
these characters like they didn't get fleshed out enough and like it was so weird to just watch them
all die when like I get why they're thinking but that litter that is the point of goblin slayer to
have they have they watched overlord specifically season three overlord probably not i was i was in
pain i was in torment what why what happened and i haven't people died and i like those people we
barely met them and the like we knew enough about them to emphasize and and empathize and you know
with me and empathizing with things and it's just it was it was terrible like um i guess spoilers
small spoilers for season three of overlord there's this girl and she has like she she's from
noble family and um but but they're falling on rough times and her parents are refusing to give
up the noble life so she has to go adventuring to to settle debts but she she has like no more i'm
gonna take my sisters and they're like two younger sisters they're both twins it's like i'm gonna take
my sisters and leave after this mission and they go to on this mission and she dies she not only dies
her body gets divided upon like the minions of the overlord and her voice is given to like one of
the maids it's just it's horrifying and then we get the scene we get the scene where like the
the two little sisters like oh i hope she comes back soon i can't wait we're going on a trip when
she comes back and it's just like you had to you had to go there you had to go there is to pull out
on your heart strings you know it's funny this whole goblin slayer thing because i haven't seen
the show i don't give a fuck whatever um i think i think i always thought like the reactions to like
rape and stuff is is overblown because like the the the shows that they talk about it's never
portraying rape is a good thing it's always done as like a hey look how fucking bad this is yeah
exactly so like that's the thing we're all on the same page about that like like do you know
that the villains and stories do bad things that's why they're villains that's always been my position
about it like let them do the bad things that just further uh you know reinforces the fact that
these are bad and shouldn't be done and this is a character you don't want to like doing something
you don't like yeah and there's a technically a reason why they do it because the i think what
what it is they there are no female goblins so they have to do this to reproduce to produce
that's in their nature that's great all right that's see that's that's kind of like disgusting but
also interesting but like okay here's my thing i was going to say can you imagine with all this
god would sell your bullshit can you imagine if the final episode of berserk 97 aired today
the shit show the shit show would be amazing the thing is okay the thing is the rape of kaspa
sorry the rape of kaska is an extremely fappable scene if if you can just like look
past the darkness that's happening but the thing is that is that is kind of the point
because it is it is it is an incredibly complex situation and i talked about this in my like
my videos about griffith and stuff like i said before and i stand by it it almost kind of looks
like kaska is enjoying it and it's on purpose because kaska is experiencing so many emotions
she has loved griffith and she's finally having sex with him and like it's it's it
look rapes bad how many times do you have to say it but like there's complex things going on here
and that's what makes the scene like so like discomforting it's literally art it's literally
art and look i'm sorry if like you have for whatever it's a personal thing or whatever like
you just can't stand rape i get it but like other people can stand it and can like you know
appreciate the the complex stuff being gotten at here and i just like this is it's literally marge
simpson turning off the tv and saying like i don't enjoy this so no one can enjoy this uh like this
is fictional you know there is no one actually being hurt but the thing is all this is propagated on
all the outrage for goblin slayer and you know the the whole thing about berserk and all that stuff
it all comes from i do think it comes from people perceiving the sexualization of the scene and like
the the almost glorification of it because i actually do think i do think that the author
having read the manga i've read a lot of the manga i do think that the author uh is kind of
sort of glorifying and sexualizing the scene i i do think that is happening the thing is though
i just don't mind it because i'm aware that like it's like yeah he's slipping in a little titillation
into the scene that's really fucked up i i do think that's happening but like how could he even avoid
it the man is an artist he is a mangaka this is a fictional thing that's happening no one is actually
being hurt but here's the thing this is where people this is why i understand why people deviate
from my opinion on this it's because the people who are outraged they perceive rape culture to be real
and they they think that like ah okay this is it this is what is propagating rape culture and they
see it and they think to themselves this is like this is going to hurt people because this is making
the problem worse you know it's it's not encouraging how much have we seen people being killed on screen
and in video games and yada yada and like i don't think i'm sorry this is my head i mean no hi that
that's the reasonable place to go to from there it's because it's again it's like i said it's
because nobody there's nobody left alive who can talk about how bad being murdered is yeah but like
i mean like the statistics it's not just because you you you see like people killing other people
on screen or in games or joke about murder or even suicide whatever it's not like it's not it
hasn't shaped the society to be okay with it it's still bad it's still against the law and it's
still a terrible thing and like we shouldn't forget but like i mean it's it's obvious and this was
said before but like the point of goblin slayer is these things are so evil with what they're
doing the goblin slayer is here to destroy them completely for what they have done uh it like
the thing is it is a literal anti rape message i guess it is anti but the the the sexualization
nugget in it people like like feminists and people who are really you know on this stuff they'll think
like uh you know they they say that they're saying that they're anti rape but really they're glorifying
it with this uh with the sexy ladies here on screen it's like ooh yeah that's that's good let's go do
that team but it's like it literally shows uh the goblins to be a bigger threat than people to give
them credit for and like how nasty and vile and terrible they really are i think that's the point
that's why the shock is like these goblins that everyone that dismisses is just little nuisances
they are actually these cretins i think that's the word you've just got to talk like when people
disagree i always think it's important to when there's a debate to agree on the terms of the
debate and and to be able to articulate the other person's message i think people who object to the
show would would concede that like yes the fact that goblin slayer is murdering them like yes it
like it's against that it's showing in that way but they would also argue that like it is also true
that the show is kind maybe even covertly or maybe maybe they'd say it's like unconscious like patriarchal
you know uh uh whatever stuff coming out that it is also kind of sexualizing and glorifying it in
you know these ways sexualized like we there weren't any sort of specific shots that i could
really point to that we're like that's the funny thing though it in the anime because the anime
is different from the manga the manga is more explicit but in the anime like you we don't see
actual rape happening on screen though it's it's implied to be happening and going on you know
but like we do see a girl get her clothes ripped off and she is an anime girl which means that she's
pretty attractive so like how does one how does one negotiate this to like make it clear what's
happening but not to titillate the audience yeah i don't know make her attractive i guess make them
ugly or yeah unattractive or i i guess you could like not show her body as much if you like kind
of show that like clothes are being ripped off but you don't show her on screen i don't even think
that would matter i think it's the idea itself has to be purged yeah i feel i feel like even if the
author had made all the steps to make it as least attractive as possible people would still have a
cow about the scene existing like it could have just been like the goblin slayer showing up and
someone ran up to him some ran in just like my wife was raped by goblins and that would be bad enough
yeah i suppose that's true like if the show if the show was exactly the same but we we just didn't
even address the whole goblin rape question and we just showed goblins murdering people
i don't think anyone would complain i think there would be no complaints which is i mean yeah people
just get fucked up about this stuff yeah like i said like we have stuff like attack on titan have
you guys seen attack on titan yeah like nobody complains about the violence and attack on titan
even though it's it's horrific and yeah yeah yeah it's uh it's just weird it's it's a weird it's a
weird thing as a culture we just get really fucked up about like sexual stuff yeah basically my
my stance was four episodes in uh minus that whole controversy non-traverse nonsense it's an
interesting show i like it it's like i'm a huge fan of the manga so i am i am like um i'm a really
big fan of like fantasy sort of rpg sort of things and you know it's set in that sort of world
where like they have a guild they have like a like a system with low levels and and they take on
quests and there's magic and it's like it's all the things i like but it's also it's also a very
gritty sort of depiction of it and that's what i find interesting that's kind of the point that's
kind of the point i'm gonna predict something uh actually most likely no one will ever care about
goblin slayer as much again and like i doubt like just because people care about stuff that's new
they don't really care about stuff that's old but i'm just gonna like if we continue the same
train of logic of objecting to this stuff later on in the series um there is a character called the
sword maiden who is like she's like a legendary warrior and she's a total badass and she's extremely
like curvaceous and like sexualized and stuff and like that that's fine i don't think people would
really complain about that but the thing is canonically she was a rape victim of goblins and
it's like like way in her past this happened to her it was only after that that she like
got strong and like became like a badass sword maiden and then like defeated the evils of the
world and stuff but she's still kind of fucked up about goblins the thing is though like i don't
know i feel like the thing is you can choose to find a fence with anything so like here's a thought
maybe uh like rape victims will be offended by this character because like oh yeah she just
got over her trauma look at them trivializing rape victims here like but the thing and then on the
other hand this character still has flashbacks to this event so like she isn't completely over it
somebody else might say oh look at us they're telling us that we can never get over our trauma
like what a problem at there's no way to win with the topic yeah yeah yeah i don't know what the
answer is i the answer is freedom as far as i'm right no like it's libertarian mind your fucking
own business and relax it's the idea of like these because like people who are this bent out of shape
about it are just gonna say the only answer is like this stuff is off limits it cannot be talked about
cannot be done but take it seriously basically basically if you were if you felt uncomfortable
by a good good good job that's what they were trying to do i think yeah it's just a question of
people maybe don't like to feel discomfort or something i mean i i don't know like i the thing
i think people's outrage makes sense if they have a worldview that i don't think makes sense so like
right well that's that's the whole problem with discussion nowadays anyways there's yeah like
the baseline is different so like yeah that's right that's we're not even having the same
conversation as like the people we're talking about would be happy so it's like it's impossible to come
to terms yeah i'm not saying you you know you're supposed to like it or whatever like you definitely
don't have it was not meant to be liked the scene but like come to terms with the fact that the
scene exists for a reason and the reason is not to titillate people it's just i mean so don't be
outraged about people we're connecting the goblins to the jews and we're just like throwing out
that whole business really you guys didn't hear i mean i mean you know i guess i won't drop any
names but there are some videos out there that specifically said like hmm big nose little vermin
that this guy wants to literally genocide and wipe out where have i heard of that before and it's
just like guys you need to relax there are no connections here oh my god noses oh my god
that all that kind of says more about the people who are looking into it yeah i said a million times
but still iran it reminds me of that whole apu controversy oh my god and you hear he's gone
you hear that he's gone yeah yeah i love i love how there's this amazing brain dump that came out
like a week before that just like totally clean the clock of this whole thing is like yeah of
course this is ridiculous and like a week later like and it's gone it's just where does this logic
end because now now they're saying that minorities need to be displayed within a very narrow parameters
that are of what's acceptable and like who exactly is the arbiter of what's acceptable and what's not
because at this point is a well-developed and rich character and but now because he has i guess roots
in like his accent and the fact that he's voiced by a white guy uh we're just opening the door here
and uh opening the floodgates to let like people pulley this is i don't know man i just don't
think this is the right direction for the people to be going with this kind of stuff it's tiring
feels very wrong okay i'm tired i'm tired yeah okay you know what i want to go lay down and
forget about humanity for a while well hang on before we do that we've got a couple of voicemails
to listen to oh yeah okay please cheer us up let's all right let's go to it we've i think we've got
seven here today all right here we go people seven enough uh enough enough libertarian politics for
one day let's let's get over here and listen to our boy no thank you uh and by the way if you
listen to the bonus episode or the last episode no thank you is the guy who made the uh like the
halloween theme for the pcp so it wasn't that cool let's uh it's not used in the bonus episode
it's not oh okay well it's in the it's in the the last pcb episode so there you go let's let's listen
hey guys so i made a i made a little remix of the the pcp theme uh goes like this
so
i like trapped into its feet
oh no yes
oh yeah oh yeah
so
that's great thank you needs it needs to need to add that in immediately yeah we got to start
using that one instead that was i love it i love it all right moving on next is uh not
comey call mew i swear i don't know what that means not comey call mew i swear okay so maybe
comey call mew somebody else i don't know uh anyone else this one is anyone else yeah
nate hasn't uploaded anything forever ben hasn't uploaded anything forever did your
bro slowing down spooky space spooky scary bullshit month is ending hippos stopped
lethal hasn't uploaded anything in forever oh Tommy's dev stuff is about to end i'm getting
serious pcp withdrawals man i'm getting serious serious withdrawals man i feel freaking out after
patreon just to get any more content seriously fucking help help me i was gonna die all right
that's enough from this friend i was gonna say uh five dollars to the patreon to get all those
sweet bonus episodes of which there's 19 now there's at least one bonus episode coming that you
haven't heard yet friend if you're listening to this um so that's so so do that uh it's true
these are all true the content is slowing down a little bit um for me it's because i'm working on
like bigger more complicated projects and i want to do we aga with stuff more but i just don't have
the fucking time to get everything done i need to get done every week basically now he's right
but i'm working on it uh what's your excuse everybody else Nate you just gotta stop skateboarding
so much i won't i need to get that pokemon go stop every day dammit all right question why don't
you just do a we agua while you're skateboarding just record get a laugh mic and just talk about
something while you're skateboarding just you know all the time there's there's something to be said
that i've kind of fallen into a trap with we agua where like the the point of the series was to get
a video done every week about something and like to make it cool like make it good you know
reasonably speaking but the most important thing was just to get a video out every week
at the time i took the format you failed well i did for a while a good long while like i was doing
it well um currently it's not living up to its name which is fair uh but um like i just styled
it after the mea math of a content that i was doing and just kept doing that and i've still
been doing that i've sort of fallen into a trap where i'm just like now i feel i'm forced to live
up to like a certain standard where the the like quality is kind of creeping up like the last ones
i was like in hawaii for uh uh and well the one after that i wasn't yeah i i need to get them done
i think your your your old habits are creeping back in i think the whole point of we agua was
you wanted to get it done first and the quality the quality wasn't like not that the quality is not
important but like i think you're you're obsessing over the uh intimate details that aren't necessary
i think you should just go back make weekly do what you can in a week and people will be fine
with it and you just need to break your own conditioning it's like sugar you're you're
you're addicted to video sugar get off that shit protein there's definitely something to be said for
that uh and i should seriously consider that stuff right now i'm not even thinking about it because
i'm doing something else but once this current thing is done i will have to think seriously about
that there might not be one till the end of the year depending on how things go my god i i know i
know it's disgraceful but why i'm a genius yearly all right new series i'm working on it people
all right that's enough about this shit i'll get back to you we'll get back i'm still doing stuff
every week devlogs every week after you're into devtober work on the game uh it's going to keep
going uh this is my life now i'm probably gonna do lots more uh i'm getting back into doing more
3d modeling stuff once this uh this demo slash alpha slash whatever ends up being is out because
i want to be out by the end of the month will it be out now as people are listening uh i don't
think so my plan is to have something public facing out on november 8th because that's when
i turn 30 i want to have some cool out i need i need something to like to uh to to to to take
off the sting of yeah yeah that's what this is it's actually a really good goal i like that a lot
i should do something similar when i turn 30 it'll be two years people two years god just that's
cool how about you mage what's your excuse where's your content it's a very long excuse i don't want
to get into it uh okay fair enough there's a lot of a lot of small things they're just kind of piled
up together basically if you want to get us to make more content the easiest ways to give us more
time the best way to have more times to have more money i'm just saying that's true that's for you
guys that's for you guys for me it didn't didn't matter how much money you threw at mage mage i'm
trying to help you out here i'm trying to give you free money no just lie to the mage just lie to
them that's the answer i feel bad i feel bad mage needs more convincing the way to get more
convincing is give me more time to convince her way to give me more time to give me the money you
want to give her you ain't wrong brother all right now let's go to our next one here one spars
back with another message all right one spar hit us hit us boy hey guys just uh here at home walking
around sipping some coffee this morning and uh i think i came up with a uh pretty good idea for
a new pcp intro um give it a listen tell me what you think somebody once told me the world was
i've heard enough that's enough thank you one spark uh you're fired
i think there was actually something at the end of that underlying do you think there's an
underlying message here that the new pcp theme has a strong undercurrent of detractors you know
there's something going on with that maybe we should i don't know revisit this issue i'm always
open to revisiting stuff and why did you guys vote for it like you know offense to the person who made
it it was good but like you made everybody liked it no not everybody not everybody sasuke pro may
just talk in mad shit on you right now please send her a scathing email about how she's bullying
you online i'm not i just didn't like a thing as much as you guys did well fair enough fair enough
um and actually you'll see him in the comments every once in a while being like yeah thank god
you shortened it today i fucking hate my own song yeah yeah so i mean if you that was gonna be the
case you probably should uh thought about that before you decide to make an intro of a podcast
100 plus episodes deep i mean it frankly it's our fault not his i guess you know if it is truly
shit well whatever um all right here we go this does blame to go around okay here we go next one's
from i really mean it is another message all right do it members of the pcb hear me now as i whisper
to you in divine doubt you will all look yourselves in the mirror and decide who you want to be today
tomorrow and when you are no longer here we all have a legacy and i'll have fever dreams about you
guys when i am in the retirement home
oh was he playing the xylophone while he recorded that maybe i don't i don't i don't want to look at
the mirror though oh ouch i don't like i don't like the person that stares back at me oh christ damn
that's uh that's serious that's like the opposite of what that message is about it's about becoming
your best self mage for me it's like for me it's like that clip of uh of that movie sure what was
that show like time warp time leap or something where the guy is like am i retarded and then he
looks in the mirror and then like he's in like a down syndrome guy's body um that's me so i avoid
looking in the mirror is what quantum leap was it quantum it was quantum leap that's the one that's
the one mage i got a fix for you by the way quick fix for the mirror uh painted purple that's that's
a good idea let's put a put a purple filter over it yeah uh is that is that a physical thing mage
or is that like an emotional thing like both okay well that's sad uh i'd say work on that in some way
if possible please i am i am i i i make peace with my loathing of myself well that's always good to
hear uh all right next making peace is step one step two is declaring a war on it and crushing it
entirely i'll i'll i'll hit it when it doesn't see it exactly you know i actually do think about uh
his points fairly frequently like when i look back like will i look back on like for example we
aga was with much love some of them a bit some of them not as much like what i'll what i i mean
you know what's my best work you know like the for me i think my best work is like the gurren
login videos i really like my final fantasy 15 uh what is it unchained unflamed whatever it was
i love that video um i don't know some of the some of the oh the the musical stuff like the
smash bros stuff i really love uh i don't know so like so like yeah i do think about like what do i
want to like have my legacy be in terms of like youtube and then also like what's the point of
the content overall like entertainment is good and that's a valuable service but i mean whatever
i've talked about this a bunch you know i i'd like to think that i'm making a positive difference
in the world and not just you know being i mean my whole goal right now and the reason i stopped
doing youtube pretty much entirely is because i was just like well the only thing i care about
is like am i going to be satisfied when i'm dying that what i did in my life was worth it
yeah and youtube was not the answer so i was like well i won't make as much money and i by not shilling
on youtube but fuck it the money is not going to make me happy when i'm fucking dying of cancer
from cell phone radiation exposure at 45 it's like we're all gonna die that way it's a bouncing act
because like i mean for me i'm i'm currently sacrificing large amounts of my time to work at
my day job programming um which is fine but none of it is really adding to much of a legacy that i
value particularly much but i i'm i'm basically sacrificing that time to obtain the money that
i feel will allow me to springboard into you know doing that stuff more and building something that
i value and i'm glad that i worked on and stuff so i don't know like there's a balancing act i guess
you don't want to like literally die and then you like because if you literally die making your art
then well then you won't get as much made and so that might be less but on the other side if you
if you spend too long working on your normie job or whatever and you save a bunch of money and then
you switch then like maybe you've wasted too much of your life you know if you've done that and you
you're coming out below what you would have if you'd just done it say uh it's a struggle for sure
yeah well i'll also you know thought about such things but i'm sort of like like i said i'm sort
of at peace with the idea of like um i don't regret my life up till this point even though i feel
like i wasted a lot of it though you know defined wasted i'm happy with what i've done in a way but
at the same time i know that i'm just another drop in the ocean i'm not gonna break any new grounds
or there's not going to be much left of me once i leave this place so we kind of not with that
attitude mage come on but i'm okay with that i mean not everyone is born to be a name in the
history books you know take take for example like look at like toby fox for example so sure
right now undertale is a huge meme um like it's a good game everybody likes it um and you know
whatever and it's a meme so people talk about it a lot will undertale make much difference in the
long run of like humanity you know will it because like it's pretty almost objective that like
undertale for example is like more influential than like all of us so like okay fair enough
but even something like undertale like it's just a game right so like will it it was it
has been given as a present to the pope so right so it cured world peace finally was solved uh we
did it no i think undertale it does like you know we i think i think it has staying potential it's
definitely going to be remembered in many years by a lot of people and who knows when it's relative
i guess yeah like when the heat death of the universe happens like literally nothing will
remain so you know except undertale except undertale except undertale yeah him and the
pope will be floating out in space with this copy of undertale the heat death of the universe is
sans it is sans yeah it's a heavy topic it's a heavy topic i don't know just try i say i say
try to make the world around you a better place don't be a burden on the people
that you know or that you care about be be of benefit to them and there's lots of ways to be
of benefit not strictly financial there's lots of ways to do it so as long as you feel that you're
contributing and that you're making the world better around you than it was when you get there
as opposed to worse neutral is okay but you want to be a plus then let's go yeah yeah okay let's go
on to the next one this is from uh from a rupt rupt so much so much for making us happier
okay so bullying bullying do you guys ever get bullied in high school middle school or
shit like that and like i'm not trying to be repetitive because you guys probably got a lot
of this question on twitter um back the day but it's just that i don't understand how bully
works because just fucking fight the guy okay like fighting a bully is exactly a win-win situation
because either the guy can lose to you or you you can be seen as a hero who fought a fucking bully
and like people will like you because people don't like bullies in general it's just a question
just a question like i don't understand how bully works it's probably because it's a us problem
at a i live in south america but it's just a fucking question but i love you guys i'm not in the us
but okay that's true well okay i can i can answer this question yeah the people the people who are
targeted by bullies by people especially in the west they're targeted because they're pussies
and they're not gonna fight back yes that's true that that cut out for me i didn't hear
they're targeted what uh the people who get targeted by bullies they get targeted because
they're pussies and they won't fight back for the most part yeah i can tell you my story with bullying
there was a there was a girl i think she was my age i'm not sure she got on my case for who knows
what i really really no reason at all uh but and she was smaller than me so you think you think i'd
have no problem however the problem with her was she was never alone she was always with guys like
let's say i was 14 and she was 14 and she was with guys 19 years old way bigger than me at least
two of them at at each side with her at no point was i able to sort of fight her back and even
actually i did fight her back and um she she need me in the forehead with her knee
and it is it wasn't just physical you know and it was also psychological she psychologically
tormented me and the fact that she wasn't in school or in my neighborhood i could never
see her coming i didn't know when i'm gonna meet her but she was never alone and whenever i did
it was never in a public place where people could help me it was it was it was it was mortifying
it was just like i felt i never felt so helpless when i was in my life she's sort of like i think
she was kind of like what broke the you know uh jokingly why i left violence streak in a way
sure sure did you i mean uh i'm just curious did you like talk to like your parents or like
school people or anything like that school people are irrelevant she wasn't in my school
i did talk to my mom once or twice i told her about it um and you know my mom tried to help and
we actually went one time she you know saw the bruise on my forehead so she went we went out and
tried to find her and uh she she we did find her and uh she she talked to her and she was giving
my mom such a you know shitty eating grin that my mom um couldn't help herself and smacked her
across the face but because of that we weren't able to go to the police because my mom would get
in trouble for hitting a minor god all right she kind of blew it by doing that because it would
have been good to go to the police the violent violence runs in the family holy shit uh the next
time i think the last time i saw her was during camp not the not the same year as you know the
whole incident with the arms things uh but that was i should have dropped her off at sue story
i almost ended up in the same um building as her but thankfully we didn't so for the the whole week
my my mission was to avoid her at all costs to let her know that i was there but for the last
i think two days i blew it or rather it wasn't my fault it was it was my counselors of the house
fault because he was he was he was like he was almost i he was a helper so i think he was a teenager
almost an adult young adult person and there was some for lack of a better word skanks in my house
literally sucking up to him probably sucking up to him lads he yeah so he was very much on their
side and they were friends with that girl so i had no chance women's sexual uh uh advantages
can definitely be weaponized in situations like this it's a unique advantage uh like if a guy comes
to you and has an issue and a girl disagrees and she'll fuck you i'm just saying i'm just saying
you who are you gonna who are you gonna go with i did i did complain to the higher ups at the camp
and the and the person i complained to she was in charge of our house and uh uh she she said she
lived in the same neighborhood as the girl and she was like oh but you know she she she never
seemed like she was trouble and like but she is and yeah they couldn't really help two faced
bitch yeah the basically it just sounds like like to to the guy's question it's just like
there they they find people who can't defend themselves in this way uh yeah like they specifically
target people who seem vulnerable because if they yeah like if you're if you're a real bully
like if you find someone who gives you resistance you don't bully them you bully someone else
exactly yeah and i don't like i guess i see his point i guess like just i mean i got bullied in
high school all the time because i was a pathetic little bitch and uh yeah and it was not cool yeah
it's not like it's totally my fault i blame myself the bullies in the movies and children's cartoons
whatnot that they were the portrayed it looks so easy that all you have to do is stand up to them
and be top dog and stuff like that but it doesn't work out like that even if you beat them today
then you have to beat them the next day and the thing about a bully a bully is inherently
immoral with what they're doing so like if you like beat up a bully they will go play the victim
and then you have become the aggressor or or or they'll get their friends to help beat you up
the next time it's not going to be a fair fight next time i mean yeah that that's definitely true
i was never i don't know i lived a pretty coddled childhood and i was never really bullied um but
there was there was one time i had a pogo stick beating crap out of ben oh well yeah i was the bully
and that's taking him he loved it though um there was uh there was one time in uh uh element no
middle school like sixth grade or something when um in uh i was i had a pogo stick for some reason
i was pogo sticking in class when i shouldn't have been just for fun why this guy uh uh just
he he i stop he looks over me and he just calls me he's he i think he's white i could be wrong
he just calls me n-i-g-g-e-r he just calls me that and i'm just like uh what what okay what do you
mean sir what what's that about and uh i didn't understand i knew what the word meant at that
point but i didn't know what that was about but that was the extent of it he just called me that
and then moved on i didn't get like harassed i didn't get like physically assaulted or anything
of that nature so i had a pretty it was pretty lucky it's pretty lucky i feel like his he'd heard
his dad say that word it's like i want to try this out in real life yeah probably something like that
i think he was white like i i i don't know he had slightly tanned his skin it's probably like
armenian or something i don't know um yeah so that's that's it for me i guess yeah all right i
guess we'll just go on to the next fucking call here oh uh did i already play this one yeah that
was erupt okay next one is uh vacuum vacuum all right we've got two more here all right let's uh
let's get this shit rolling so nate recommended this book called the 48 laws of power it's a
fucking sick read really uh really fun to read super inspiring also no one else is allowed to
read it uh this book is cut off from the public now if anyone tries to read it i will fuchsia your
if you know what i'm saying uh i take offense to this voicemail because i'm the one who
recommended the 48 laws of power because i was reading it and it's fucking great i i think he
like i did meme like i quoted a sam hide joke about the 48 laws of power i have not actually read
the book though i would like to i've heard it uh i mean it's fantastic yeah yeah uh it's good but
you know but speaking of power just you probably are aware of this but it was interesting tom that
with that bullying thing you said that you blamed yourself um for getting bullied and like
like i i get what you're saying i get what you're saying and and surely you're aware that like
like if someone murders you because you're i don't know like walking out late in a bad neighborhood
like sure you can blame yourself but but like the the the bad person is more so the the other person
so it's like it's it's it's it's smart to take responsibility for the bad things to happen because
only you can change your own behavior but of course like morally speaking uh it's it's the
aggressor yeah morally but i yeah there's an extent of what you can do my situations the
situations i was in were were definitely exasperated by my own uh naivete and general idiocy so there
was there was a fair bit of my own stupidity that made a lot of these things happen i think it
reminds me of like there was there was i don't i don't i sort of disagree with i mean like sort of
like there's an extent of responsibility you can take but also you can't take all of the
responsibility for instance with the with my bully that storm entity throughout the years whatever
yeah like all i did was talk to her once and it was it was because i took some advice about
someone saying oh you made you know you should stand up to yourself more because you're so meek
and i did i took that stupid advice i i and you know i think what happened is like i never knew
her we never saw each other before and she had the goal to sort of call after me and be like hey
you have stupid shoes or something like that and i snapped something back at her and that's what
started it and now because of that because of that did i deserve all that did i deserve all of that
torment she gave me well i don't think so like in the Machiavellian sense like i'm sure there were
tactical moves that one could make to theoretically like resolve the situation and i would i would
never say morally you're responsible it's just that you know like maybe there were things that
could be done that if you had known about maybe if you like literally had a future site you could
know what would work and what wouldn't um and so like you know like in the grand scheme of like
the cause and effect of one's entire life like yes you are quote unquote responsible for what
happens just like like sure like a kid who's born like in the poorest fucking region of Africa
and stars to death like okay maybe there's something he could have done to like get him out of that if
you know whatever he had like known what to do at certain times but like no one would ever blame
the kid for like you know what what happened to him or anything it's kind of a yeah i don't know
where where it's not whatever you get the point you get the point so i mean yeah like there's
there's this book that i haven't read but i've been hearing more about in case you nice dad made a
video about the author recently um what's called i think it's extreme responsibility or no extreme
ownership i think is what it's called it's just about like completely owning uh it's kind of more
for like leaders in life like owning your subordinates mistakes and stuff and taking complete responsibility
for everything happens to you there's a i believe in that philosophy a lot in thinking like i'm always
saying like nobody gives a fuck about you in this world it's up to you to make it or to die in the
streets and that that's because like tactically speaking it's up to you to manage your life 100
percent like nobody else is going to do it uh and you cannot expect help um but but but there's a
separate thing to like condemn bad actors like the world shouldn't be bad and full of like
evil people who do bad things but those people have their own motivations you can't control them
you can only control yourself so it's just about assessing the reality while recognizing that things
are bad and you can do both those things at once i think so i don't know i think we all agree i'm
probably just going in circles here anyway yeah anyway that wasn't really that guy's question
what is vacuum mask again he was asking about like he was just mentioning a book he liked the
book no one else 48 laws of power right 48 laws of power that's right no one else is allowed to
read it yeah i mean the more people that read it the less effective the book does become it's true
is that true yeah because like it's about it's all about manipulating people that's the 48 laws of
power all about i believe in uh uh what's the word uh ethical manipulation of other people
the first the introduction of this book is that ethics are bullshit throw away morality okay well
you know so i i hear what he's saying but my my my compass guides me towards a better future for
all people all right which i 48 laws will work on you good to know for the future you know that's
that is kind of fascinating how does one how does one read this book and get to that first
lesson about like discard morality like like uh Machiavelli uh and the prince uh or i think it's
i think it is like another transaction whatever people know it as the prince the prince is about
like it's not saying it discard morality it's saying i think play the tactical game
outside of what says to it's the same thing it's like it's amoral you just have to apply it
as best you can like i don't think about it in terms of moral i don't think you can like that
makes you immoral to follow its advice or anything it's about what you do with it i'd say you have
to like disregard because like a lot of it if you read the book with a moral lens yeah everything in
it is like reprehensible but if you read it it's just like this these are tactics in like the game
that we're all playing whether we want to or not it's a strategy guy i was gonna say because in in
regards to the prince it's specifically made for like for like uh like up and coming rulers and
like people who expect to like control you know populations and stuff and like the thing is it's
literally impossible to be like perfectly moral when you're a ruler because every move you make
will help some people and will like sort of punish other people like for example if you're a dictator
of the world right now like what do you do about the coal industry and the fact that we're losing
coal jobs those coal workers are suffering but like we kind of don't we kind of want to get
away from coal so like what's the solution uh like i i guess the solution is like retrain those
people in jobs that like they you know can do that is for like a more you know green economically
sustainable pathway for it but like what about the people who don't want to stop doing coal and
they just won't like what do you do that the answer is nothing some people get fucked is the answer
i mean that is the ethic i think that's the ethical thing if like you're if your business goes away
yeah and you refuse to stop doing it uh then perish uh tinted obama image like like that's
yeah that's just like like you're an idiot you know uh i mean you're right like that's what's
going to happen in the real world so like you could you could choose to live idealistically
or you could think about what are the optimal ways to live your life and you know strategize
for them and i'm aware that like a lot of like like oh coal's going away just get another job
but like where that runs into conflict is like you got people who are like man
my daddy's been a coal miner and his daddy and his daddy this is why i was born to do
i'm a human man like humans to some degree are built to settle down doing something you know
once they hit a certain age and stuff it's it's pretty fucked up to ask people just to change
their whole life at a certain point and a lot of people i think can't handle it understandably
you just have to you know there's no getting around it like yeah sorry you know life ain't
fair that's really what it comes down to yeah it's not all right we got one more one more fucking
message from uh it's from drunk nard war let's see what he has for us nard war i enjoy your interviews
what's what what's up hey christmas guys oh i just wanted to say you guys are the fucking coolest
hey thanks really kind of fucking gay actually
what it's doing right this is the best friendship simulator man could ask for
i don't get out much i don't have no friends but where i'm listening to the procrastinators
podcast i feel like i have friends i feel like i feel like a real real boy i feel like
uh
where's he going with this i think i understand why he doesn't have friends yeah i'm walking in the
do do nard war i get it uh wow amazing that was an interesting call
and that's pretty intense it makes me it makes me think about the ethics of making a friendship
simulator such as this podcast uh like because let's say this podcast didn't exist and no podcast
existed and this man had like he didn't have i don't know like video games didn't have tv didn't
have podcast didn't have anything and he just sat there lonely i wonder if he'd be more motivated
to go like make friends and so we're kind of doing a disservice you know you know what i mean
where we're doing in the pursuit of power one of 48 loves power there you go tom it's not
not even exaggerating one of the laws of power they talk about is uh to to to psychologically
manipulate people is to find what people are missing in their lives and become it and that is
what we are doing that okay see that makes sense and that's fair um but again one can do that in
ethical or a non-ethical way i think like there are some standards one can arrive at like our
podcast and moral because they're making the world a worse place because people are less incentivized
to go out and make real human connections and make friendships which will be infinitely more
rewarding than listening to a podcast um like sure it's profitable for us but then again how
much of the responsibility is on us i think is a fair question to ask well i was watching a video
last night they just randomly came on i was watching one of my vlogs make sure and uploaded
correctly and then autoplay immediately went to this other video that was talking about uh
morality and what can be a moral question and the two conditions he was talking about in the
video was that it has to be a conscious act and it has to have a uh a impact on someone's like
not that standard of living but like uh something that does like with people's happiness like very
rude of something okay and i would say podcasts do have an effect on people's happiness uh but
the effect you're talking about of like making people less like interested in going out and
finding friends is not a conscious act so i don't think this would be a moral thing i think it would
just be an amoral effect of podcasts in general because no one no one's making a podcast is actively
being like i'm going to stop you from having friends okay you know what that that's true maybe
immoral is the wrong word but it is fair to ask is it detrimental to society that is probably
makes questions i guess yeah i you know i guess i just want to say to drunk nard war
try to go like he said he has no friends okay fair enough fair enough what have you done recently
to work on that you know it's the same thing i'd say to a guy who's like sad that he doesn't have
a girlfriend or whatever like what have you done recently to fix it maybe you're trying really hard
in the past but like have you like here's a thing when i when i moved out to ohio i i just focused
on work for a long time but then after a while i'm like you know i would actually like to like
make some friends and connections and maybe fuck a bitch you know out here once in a while so what
i did for a while i i never did anything with this because like i i met michelle beforehand and i
don't know just that's haven't really needed to go out and do stuff since then um but like uh
i joined a bunch there's like there's it's like meetup.com or like meeting.com or something i think
it's meetup.com yeah it's just a website where you can like go to meetings and like it's just people
who go there they post about like clubs they have and they just accept you know people who want to
come hang out like why try that kind of shit you know i think it's totally worth it yeah if you if
you like don't have like a passion that like gets you up every morning and you're doing it and you
like and even if you do have a passion but it doesn't introduce you to other people i think people
have an inherent need to socialize kind of in person agreed uh so accept that reality about
yourself as a human being and and and coldly tactically attempt to resolve it uh it's like uh
yeah it's like it's like uh the great man uh Aaron Burr said in Hamilton i am the one thing
in life i can control and that it's true for all of us so go if you have problems you can't change
the world you can't change the conditions but you can change yourself in response to those conditions
indeed so become better yeah that's really all there is and i that's really the answer to all
these things it's just you know like on an individual level it's fair to say this to people
but what i what i just wonder is like on a large scale will these kind of messages actually make
the large difference and kind of make society happier and better i don't know i mean if everybody
on like maybe people are just society would change as well i mean yeah like that's the thing
every individual could could possibly do these things but on a mass scale the question is will
they and will it make the difference the problem i've always had with going out and meeting people
and i think i mentioned this on a tweet like last year and it still kind of holds true
is that the question i had posed was how do you meet people how am i supposed to meet people when
all the people i'd want to meet are staying in their house on their computer all day like i am
good question good because like you've got to ask yourself like if you do the meetup thing
like i uh one of the things i i wanted to join i know i've said this before but was a bunch of
like atheist like uh like meeting groups and stuff like the like the like the like the free
thinkers of ohio or something oh man those guys must be great i i well that that's the thing like
who do you think is at these things like who do you think is there who who knows the atheist
activists but but you know what i mean that's probably true but here's the thing here's the
thing like sure maybe everyone there is a nerd or maybe there's some actually cool people there
because i'll tell you this my anime club in college was mostly not great people i mean they
they were fine but they were not really great friends of mine i didn't really like yeah i agree
completely at like two of those anime club meetings like early on when i first started going i met
like my all my friends happened to be there because like these were people who have a passing interested
anime so they thought they would check it out this is in sophomore year of college i met them there
and we became buddies for life and so like it's not like i intersected with people who were like the
ideal people at anime club who were always there it's that it was an opportunity to meet like-minded
people and the way to succeed on these things is to take many opportunities because you know i don't
know maybe the fucking girl of your dreams gentlemen will be like at this fucking atheist
hardcore meetup because like maybe her friend dragged her there she's not really that interested
but she is there that one day and you gotta take that chance you gotta have lots you don't win if
you go to law of averages that's exactly it i was gonna say even you can lose any one hand of poker
but it's about about winning the war long term you give yourself the chances to to meet friends
and go do stuff so for the love of god get out there and try something it's so much better than
trying nothing and a lot of people probably have who are sad and sitting at home but i don't know
try to mix it up take some of these advice i will i will say that like i've said this a bunch of
times in a bunch of different situations for me the hardest part of anything is starting uh even
things that i like like the like every day when i want to work on my game or do art or even that
like things that like i feel are my sole reason for existing for drawing breath yeah it's still
for my mindset starting and getting that motion going is pain and it sucks and i don't want to
do it i'd rather just stay in bed and do nothing and be a piece of shit just because i'm a weak
flesh prison person and it's accepting that is the important first step yeah like there was an
interesting book uh called the five second rule by mel robbins i think it was a buy you don't have
to read the book because i can sum it up for you in literally like five seconds sick uh the idea is
that like she had stumbled across this idea of like if you if you're because like what happens is
that when you want to do something that's hard your brain instantly starts making excuses for you
to convince you you don't have to do it uh there's very rarely a time when you want to do something
and your brain will make excuses to do it because we're just all lazy by nature it sucks because
we don't want to expend energy because we're all fucking monkeys at the end of the day indeed so
the idea was that you count in your mind or count out loud backwards from five and once you get to
one you immediately physically move uh even if you do the task you need to do does not require
physical movement because the the act of counting breaks the mental state that you're in like making
excuses it forces your brain to stop thinking about those and do something else and then the
physical movement puts you into a different state yeah at that point you can start doing something
those things make a big that's a good idea that's a good strategy try that everybody try that when
it comes to these hard decisions uh you know that that that also works amazingly well and it's
instantly actionable it doesn't take any longer three two one and i'm moving yeah all right i uh uh
that remind uh in the extreme ownership thing like Casey Neistat in his interview with a guy who's
like a marine sergeant or something he asked him like what's one recommendation uh he said like
to succeed and like to get up and go and take ownership of your day because a lot of what he
talks about is like success not just like owning your mistakes though that they're hand in hand
it's like he's like it all starts with the first decision of the day and like when you fail on that
you are prepared to fail the rest of the day with like all the other challenges you face and you
like won't get you done but when you succeed at the first challenge of getting up and then you
succeed at the next challenge of i don't know making your coffee or having your healthy breakfast
or or working out or whatever like every success encourages you and feeds into the next one so to
succeed from right out of the gate in the morning helps him a lot and can feed into all this kind
of positive motion and uh and productivity and stuff so yeah uh it's a good idea i'm gonna try that
i'm gonna try that all right well with that that was the end of our fucking podcast i guess
everybody any any final thoughts mage what do you think about all this oh what and that's it everybody
those are mage's final thoughts in this episode of the procrastinators podcast hey patreon.com
slash the procrastinators you're gonna want to listen to the now dated halloween episode the
spooky stories that came out on halloween on on hallows eve so go pay five dollars listen to
episode 19 and the the the the the pre coolant i was gonna say subsequent but i think it's like
pre coolant episodes whatever you get the idea uh and uh at tbcrastinators on twitter for all our
updates and episode release and stuff and like and sub and comment here on youtube as well if
you're if you're listening here uh so thanks for joining us and will you see you next week
with some more of this stuff bye
you