I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Welcome to another episode of the The Pro Crastinators podcast.
I was going to say that.
Well I said it.
It's me.
Are you gone?
Gibbontake?
Bon take have you gone?
How dare you have you gone rogue? Yeah, it's me
Be eat beans on toast beans on to your last
Was the other one there was a why yes, I
Didn't watch the entire episode. I got a little bit into it and then I skip to live any kind I get the end
I think at the end there was like there's one other word that you'd like
Bit air you like break a word and in half
Like better like better
No, no, there's like when you when you said
When you remember remember how last week on the episode you said beans on toast, but you said it like be beans on toast
Beans on toast. Yeah, those are my favorite. That's my favorite. That's what I always say is beans on toast. Yeah, what's the oh, right?
Yeah, that's that's what they call it breakfast as well
That's what they call it. That's what they call it over there
and eggs
It goes
Saw I saw a picture of a full English breakfast going around Twitter yet yesterday. I
Am I am a fan? I am a fan of the full English breakfast. I have a mini
English breakfast
Most mornings I have like bacon egg and toast sometimes with beans
It's just really nice. It's funny
You you actually you actually eat beans
Yeah, what's wrong with this? What is wrong with this? I think it I think in America. We just don't eat beans that we just don't eat
them any beans
Sure, you do. You got like
Mexican food with beans in it. Yeah, Mexicans do. Yeah, Mexican food
That's just have like a shitty bean from from Heinz
I'm talking about real Americans kib. You know what I'm saying. You know what I'm saying
Click my stopwatch we do I mean we do eat beans just not for breakfast. It's not a breakfast food
One day I'll try those like the British beans in the in like the tomato sauce
Because we don't we don't have those there. Do you have them in the like Malat? No, no, no, rarely
I guess if it's not a common thing you wouldn't see it sold
No, that that particular style of being I mean maybe you can get it somewhere but in the British aisle
We have them in the in the molasses that they have a British aisle
I remember when I was over probably there was like, oh, where's the British aisle? Where's the the the tea?
There was a little little section with British things I recognized
What what store?
I don't food line like where were we like just getting groceries
Was it in Boston?
Because we don't have we don't have food line that would have been Virginia then I I don't remember but like
What are the racons?
Wait, was right before Virginia?
No, that was
Those yeah, yeah, it was no it was it was it probably was that then that three was in Massachusetts. They had like um
Yorkshire tea, which is my favorite black tea
I like I like black. I like black
Don't like Mexican. I like black
Anyway, let's continue
Uh speaking of rad con
Yeah, we were saying, uh
The the ova is in
The channel
It is uploaded
We have not watched it yet. I dread looking at it. Yeah
Uh
Yeah, me too
Yeah, it's gonna be bad and we're gonna do a upset a ben and gib reacts
The commentary track, I guess
I think yeah, that's a bonus for bonus episode patrons of the patreon
patrons of the patreon
Yeah, that
Yeah, that is yeah, that is the plan. I expect that the the commentary to be mostly like, oh
Oh
No, I like over and over do you think we'll like pause?
Well, do you think we'll have to pause it because like it's a it's a short video
It's only we'll post it to like be like, oh and here's some background on this shot
Uh, something something
I think I think we should I think we should because I I remember it's it's only been
Two years. I remember three years actually actually, uh, no no joke. I think
Uh, Sean said in the pcp like discord
Or maybe it was in my discord or somewhere. It's been three years. It was my I think I think yeah
I think the the anniversary is like this monday like night. I think maybe I think it's
Tomorrow as of the day we recording it or like
Yeah, like this week that this this this episode comes out is like the radcon anniversary
The third anniversary
Remember life before coronavirus
You know, what's really funny is how like the um
The pcpe and the radcon 4 lore like incorporates coronavirus into it because it was like a new funny thing at the time
and then
It continued to be a thing and then it continued to be a thing
Now it's now it's still funny because it's been so long that it's still a thing
And it's funny that despite being so out of date that it's still irrelevant
honestly
here
Yeah, that's a funny way to say it because it wasn't it was never relevant
Uh, is coronavirus in the ova probably right?
Yeah, that was the story
Spoilers
Spoilers for those who have not clicked on it yet spoilers spoilers for road to radcon the novella written by
Trixie and myself
Uh, coronavirus is in that as well
if I mentioned how
How I was I reread it a little bit the other day. It's I think it's really funny
I think the final chapter is funny. I'm proud of my myself. Yeah, I remember enjoying it. It was good
It was good. It didn't feel like it was completely different from what came before
I tried I tried to match the style as best I could and I think I did a these job because
I like deliberately sort of took the the way that
I don't know if Trixie was doing it for humor or if it's just the way she writes dialogue
but she had a particular way of
being like
You know quote quote
so and so like
So and so verbed and I don't know it just it she would use weird verbs for and I think it was deliberate that there would be like
Just matter of factly stating that someone
Did a speech verb that is very like weird and idiosyncratic or would use like a whole phrase for the speech verb
or something like that and so I tried to match that and I
There were other it quirks to it too and
I don't know whatever. I'm bright. I'm just I'm just so smart. I'm just so good
um
when
I don't I don't
I do you think well, do you think we'll have it like up?
I don't know if we're gonna have it up to watch this week. Um, maybe probably I mean
Maybe it's it's there. So the only thing left is for it to go live, right?
There's no other things we need
Well, we have to get we have to put it live
And I'm it's well, it's waiting for a um, it is waiting for like a content
Id like like advertiser check for some reason it was flagged as like inappropriate for advertisers
Sure. Yeah
and
Okay, I I forgot about this
But there was also the uncensored version
Yeah, remember that
I forgot that that was kind of the joke was that there was going to be the regular version that has like beams of light and like
Sensor bars and then there was going to be the uncensored version that you can only get by being a patron that doesn't have that
and then
Yeah, so
Nate Nate put
The ova's he put both versions on the youtube channel
And they're unlisted and he like requested
Review for both of them and I unrequested the review for the uncensored version because like I don't care that one doesn't need to be monetized
That's one's patrons only it's it's it's doesn't need ads on it. It's not gonna it's not gonna get more than like maybe a couple hundred views
Uh, god willing neither of them will get any views at all. Yes
So I don't even want them to review that one because it was like it had the word naked in the description
And it's like uncensored and it looked like it's sort of designed to look like pornography
And I don't even want them to look at it. I don't want them to be asked to check. Is this appropriate for youtube?
Because what if they're like they're uploading pornography to youtube and then channel strike. Yeah
Yeah, so I was just forget it forget that one
Never mind. Don't even add. Yeah
The other one is waiting for review
and um
Uh
And then it'll be out and then that'll be it. I think you said you're gonna release the dojin in conjunction with the
OVA
Yes
They are we up on the website
And I believe I haven't actually done it yet, but I believe I now have the the power to put the website online
And so that will be uh, I'll try and put that up. Yeah, okay. So on the website the procrastinators.com
Or perfect party podcast. No perfect party perfect comic dot no perfect party
Oh my god, perfect comic party dot com. Is that it comic? Yes, perfect comic party dot com
There'll be like a link at the top for like pcp stuff and then on the pcp stuff page. There will be
A downloadable. There's a road to radcon and there's the dojin
Those will be downloadable
As well, there's also a link to uh the the dating sim
Uh, if you haven't played that I don't think I've read the entire dojin. So that that'll be interesting
I'm looking forward to that because that looks the what I've seen looks very good
I have
I mean, I have read the entire dojin because I I you know
Largely put it together
The the dojin uh, is very
Funny, I think it's really it's funny because
It was written. I commissioned who is it? It was chip wiseman never paint and aura barista
They wrote like skits for it and I and I commissioned them to write skits for it
When radcon was already like a year or more over
It was already like freaking uh radcon four is already a distant memory and everything's changed
And uh lemau I can't believe we're still doing this and that was like a year and a half ago and now
Even that feels like a distant memory irrelevant. Why are we still why did we still do this?
uh
And yet and yet since a lot of the jokes are sort of at the expense of like ha ha remember how
The pcp was gonna start pcp hq ha ha remember how they work
So how how they thought content was gonna was gonna cantant was gonna go somewhere ha ha remember how uh
What else what else they didn't used to be corona
Whatever a lot of it is jokes about that and and I feel like that stuff has aged pretty well possibly even even better
So then I really think that it was it's written by old head pcp listeners those three
And so I think if you are an old head pcp listener
You are gonna get a kick out of the gags and the stuff in there that is very very deep cut like ha ha I get this reference
kind of stuff I think I I think I
am a genius for going with for picking those those three and also
Um drinking moth who has done some sent in some some art to the voicemails
She did uh not all but a lot of the art on it and I just want to shout her out in particular
Because of how good she is and how fast she was like I appreciate so much
that I would
Tell her like hey, can you draw this page and she'd be like
Yeah, yeah, I'll do that and then she'd have it in like three days or something. She'd be like yeah, here you go
And and and in that and in life. It's not it's it's rare
It's rare to find someone who doesn't ruin your fucking life when you work with them
So I appreciate her a lot
um
What's her at is it is it at drinking moth?
On twitter at drinking moth on twitter, please commissioned at drinking moth on twitter
You there good. Yeah, sorry. I was joining no no because it was boring. I just oh so
Uh commissioned drinking I highly I really recommend drinking moth a lot is really impressed
And I really appreciate the work that she did and also, you know, there's there's a there's a chapter
There's a there's a segment that knew
Drawn by new
And there's a segment called uh, who was drawn by I mean, there's a bunch by there's a bunch by ed
I guess you remember that didn't
Things didn't go so well with ed
It's a couple by
Kaiju who did not want to be credited as Kaiju
So it's credited as k instead
I'm not sure why but that's that's how it that's what he wanted
And then there's uh, am I forgetting someone?
Am I forgetting something?
What?
Uh
There was the one that simsie drew but only simsie. Uh, yeah simsie sketched one and then Kaiju finished it. Yeah
So, yeah, let's see. I mean, I mean here I'll just go to my version of the website
By download the dojin
Here we go. There's chat. I'm reading the home page reading the front page
chapter listing
Here are the chapters. You know what? I'll I'll screenshot it
Here's a here's a preview of the
Of the table of table of contents of the radcon for paradise dojin, which I
Pain stakingly
arranged
Chapter one an unfamiliar beach drawn by written by never paint drawn by edward d. Al chapter two beach romance
Written by never paint drawn by edward d. Al chapter seven slammer eye written by chip wiseman
Drawn by edward d. Al and k
melan
Melan and self critique are like four coma. They're like four well four panel comics
Uh written by or barista drawn by simsie and k and drinking moth altered beasts written by or barista drawn by drinking moth
Have you have you read altered beasts? I don't think so
That one's really good and I think
You would like it a lot
Do you have the pdf do you want it?
Uh, I mean sure. I'll I'll go to the website when it's live and get it there. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
um
The most loyal written by drinking never paint drawn by drinking moth beach romance to electric boogaloo written by never paint drawn
By drinking moth beach day trading written by or barista drawn by new and doge con finale written by
Never paint drawn by k. So
There you go. There's the full is the full chapter list and that'll be out very soon
And that's exciting
That would be the last
piece of radcon for content ever
Yeah, the ova and this
and tech technically wrote to radcon never
released
I I I I gave backers their copies their physical copies
But I didn't I didn't like publicly digitally release it yet
So I think that'll also be available on the same
website at the same time
You can read that as well. Nice
And then the rad content is done, baby
And then the rad content is all done
And then we can start the preparation for radcon
radcon five
What's the theme what's the theme for radcon five we
Three was three was like battle arena. We were gonna go to ukraine or something
If I remember correctly
So it'll be radcon three again. We'll have but but the war is is real this yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Still with the go pros and the toy guns for everyone else is shooting us with the real bullets
Nice very cool
Um
Sound off in the commons sound off in the comments. If you want to send us to ukraine
Send us to ukraine for radcon five. How much do you think how much how much do you think a kickstarter for?
Like rat radcon five protecting democracy like like protecting nato in ukraine
Which would how much do you think a kickstarter for that would raise?
Uh millions millions and millions
We couldn't we couldn't like like stretch goal. We kill putin. We'd like live stream it if you give a if we if our kickstarter reaches
One billion
Commando like uh like rappel into
Whatever building is the main russian building. I don't know the kremlin the kremlin building
We smash through the windows live streaming with a phone on our head
You said mr. Putin
You're under arrest
Mr. Putin you're under arrest. I say bashing his head in the blood with my mace
Uh couldn't possibly go wrong
I mean if we make it if we made a billion dollars, then yeah, what what could go wrong?
Um, yeah, okay rat rat radcon five
um
Radcon five uh protecting ukraine and democracy protecting democracy in the ukraine
Uh coming soon keep your keep your isp
Ah, well, I've got a
Not really an announcement yet
Uh, we're but speaking of websites
Uh, i'm redoing i'm getting some help to get my give and take dot site
Into a state that is nice and not bad and it is good actually
Yeah, the moment it's just a little sad
And there's gonna be uh, oh
Uh, it's gonna have all the comics already have but it's also gonna have a new thing for red man comics
I'm gonna put those on there
And it's gonna have buttons and it's gonna be nice and smooth and works
And it's not gonna be hosted by wordpress
And it's gonna be and i'm learning all about the code all about the little
the json and the
Files and the things
Oh very nice very nice. So it's all gonna be easy to upload. I'm gonna be able to like
Just add a bunch of images into a folder
On my computer and then do a little update or thing in a jig and it'll just put them on on the website
Oh, that's really
That's really interesting. That's really good. I actually don't know how to do that. You know, I was
I was I made the website as simple as possible just because
Like I didn't
If I if I knew how to do that I I I kind of was gonna set it up so that like
There would be the home page and then on the home page
There would be like a link that you could click for like
The latest episode and it would bring you to the latest episode and then there'd be another link for like
Here's all the episodes
but um
Yeah, I didn't really know
How to like set it up
You I would probably I think I would probably need like json or
um
Java or something to have it dynamically have that link like dynamically altered to be like it points to whatever the newest
Like episode is
Because otherwise I would have to like upload all the every little pages individually
And I would rather just upload just just put it in the one
Yeah, it's it's really clever because it's like in the json file is like
there's
you know a
Comic name and then it's got like information about it and then pages and then it says link to this image show this image
And as long as I give it the right file name the same as I give the images
I can just put the images in a folder and then the data file will read it and just put it on the website without me having to do anything
That's really interesting. I mean if you if you once you know how to do that
Do you think you might like be able to like I don't know
Make our website do that with like our homepage just point like have a like well get the new get the newest episode
It's being built by someone else and they're teaching me how to add to it. So I don't know how to make it
From scratch. I know how to
Yeah to use the things that are already there to like add new pages and update it and stuff
I see because I am my brain shuts down when I look at code most of the time
Really really kicks out of me
Lamal
Listen, listen, buddy
I made endless war
personally
Yeah, you know, that's very good. I created him and I could destroy him
But I don't know how to use javascript to make my text link link to a different file
help
There's just a hundreds of thousands of hours of free tutorials
You just have to look through all of them and find out which one is actually going to tell you the right thing
I just have to freaking comb through thousands and thousands of advice threads on file stack or whatever
people asking how do I do this with my
You know what? I'm just probably gonna not do it
And I'm probably just gonna make the website simple
So you just click the archive and you can just see the list you can just see the list of episodes
Because it's easy um and um, um, what was I gonna say?
I I don't know
But yeah, that's that's I don't know when that's coming out from my give and take dot site relaunch
Uh when that comes out, I guess I'll be putting
Uh, my new Clarissa gunsmoke chapter on that
Hopefully before that that would be
With bscapades in the first perfect comic party
Uh
Zine
I I I just threw it. I just I just had to commit to something. I I couldn't think
You're a you're a I you're a I mean I mean you last week you said
Last week you said Zine. Well, that's how you know it's a fucking computer. That's how you know it's fucking fake
Is that it says things correctly? It's no
But oh, um the the guy who's building your website
I think we talked about I think I mentioned that like maybe he could build the pcp website and then I ended up just doing it myself
I think he was disappointed that I that I made the pcp website
myself because like
I I know I listen. I know he could have built a fancier website
I know he could have built a fancier website than I can
I'm sure he I'm sure of that
I just didn't want to
I just didn't want a fancy website
I just wanted some bullshit. That's what the pcp deserves
Uh
Just it's just a list of links if you go once then if you go to the new website
It's just a list of links that have the podcast
Yeah
It's just the the pcp website the new pcp website is just an answer to the question. Where's the podcast?
It's right there. It's all right there and that's all it is
And it's also some extra stuff
But uh, yeah, but yeah, the the perfect comic parties
magazine the magazine the perfect comic party zine is
um
In the works, I guess I'm waiting mostly on you to do some Biscopades
And then once that's done, we'll have our first issue
I mean
Wait a minute. Are you serious that like I just need to give you some pages and then it's like ready to go
Oh, no, but like I'm assuming the the amount of time it'll take for me to make the logo
Um and do other stuff will be uh equal or less than the time it'll take for you to do the Biscopades
Okay, I mean that's fair. Yeah, um, I don't know. I think I told you I told you before the show that I have not
I don't know. We thought we talked about scheduling. I know I have not been able to keep up with that schedule
I mean, there's a lot of stuff. I'm falling behind. That's fine. There's a lot of stuff happening right now, especially since the OVA is finished
Um, Radcom is taking like precedent in our minds to get that finally sorted out
Yeah, um perfect comic party
is
Cool, I like it. I like the idea. Yeah
and
Yeah, next week. I'm mostly going to be working on
Uh, the the logo for that the pdf and once I'm done with that, I guess I'll be working on chapter five of Clarissa
But then we're gonna we're gonna put it together. We're gonna make a little thing
And then you will be able to read it on the new website. Hopefully it will
It will be on the new website. Yeah, it will be on the new website. I I've made it so that it is like equally
Equally prominent
On the new website to the podcast. It has its own
It basically the the left side of is the podcast on the right side of the home page is the
It will be the perfect perfect comic party. Um, yeah, I have um
Um
What are we gonna do it needs like it's probably gonna need like a cover page
And it's probably a page of like
Thanks for reading. Here's some links to support us. Here's our patreon. Here's our ko-fi
Sure, sure. Yeah, and then and then a thank you page for patrons, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, so
um, oh, yeah, we haven't
I've I yeah the the idea of like a thank you like
Little you put names on the thing you put names on the content if you're a patron
Yeah, should we put every patron? I I think we should put like every five dollar patron. Okay
Yeah, so that's a five dollar reward tier on the patreon now
which we need to
We need to revamp that patron patron. There's lots of things like in the works to be like
Got done. So I'm not going to be like too worried if certain things get
Pushed back a bit
Yeah, I just want them to be done one after the other bit by bit things will be uploaded
Completed
of released and then
Like I don't know a little while
There'll be less bullshit
If we could just live
Live our stupid lives finally finally we can just live our stupid lives like we always wanted to
Uh, I have said
Some somehow this is all pushed
It really is like
There's a there is like a lot going on right now. I mean there's
The the the perfect comic party
Is a big thing that like I'm trying to get done and we're trying to do right now the new website
also coincidentally
Radcon stuff is finishing in the ova
You know, well not coincidentally, but also the the dojin
I think like the printed the first printed copy of the dojin is like on its way
I think I might be getting it in the mail like today
But I'll have to check uh also
slime punishment
The first printed copies of slimes punishment are on their way
And they should be here maybe maybe this week
Um, did I talk about those? Did I show those? No, I think it was just this week that I got the the images
Right?
I was not I mean I can't remember on last episode if you talked about that
All right. No, no, I I think it I did not talk about no. I did not talk about it. Maybe I did. No, maybe I did talk
I don't
Help well, let me you talk to me about uh things you're doing in preparation for the video
Uh for the kicks data for the slime and punishment book
in the
In the in the st. Ben's cathedral discord for the cop killers
I posted in the announcements a picture of me
In the uh effect makeup just sitting there looking weird
And uh, it looks really funny
I just posted it was like so
Glowing um
Um, hang on I'll I'll check my discord because I posted
Uh, uh because I posted in the announcements
No, it was on the first yeah on march 1st. I got the first the pictures
Of slime and punishment
and
Should I
Should I post them?
I don't know I could I could repost them here
I don't know
Maybe it's too hard. Maybe it's too hard to copy paste a set of images. Yeah, you know what you know what I mean
Yeah
It's it's just so difficult
uh
Wait, I'll I'll do like two
There there's one
Nice thumb Ben
What nice thumb Ben. That's your thumb. That's my thumb
I think this is the lady. I think this is the lady that ghosted me and that I had the catfish
I mean, it could be someone else that works at the the company
Hey, look look look carefully at these two covers
Uh, you just you might be able to tell that they're slightly different like color
Oh, yeah, one of them is more vibrant
I the one on the left is like
Yellower and the one on the right is like
paler
The guru the greens you can if you look at the green of the text you can see the difference
Uh, yeah
If you look at the text you can see the different greens and if you look at endless war you can see on the left
His like shadowed side is like darker and on the right side. It's like brighter
So these are like the two different like filters that I use to adjust for the greens because I mean, you know from printing the red man comics
That when you try to print print print when you try to print
Like uh, like fully vibrant green. It turns to like mud, right? Yeah
So these are the two I don't have green and
in ink
And I think these came out pretty good. I'm not sure which I prefer but maybe when I when I have them in person
I will look at them and be like
Also also
This is really annoying
But the way that like the just the corner of endless war sticks over that like the like crease line at the spine
Uh, yeah, I see it really annoys me and I'll probably like nudge him over a little bit and like maybe try again
Just nudge him over a few millimeters just to just to have him not be creased like that because I don't like it
But yeah
There it there it is. That's what it's gonna look like
It's gonna get it real soon and then I'll do a
Freaking do want to do a freaking Kickstarter about it. Why don't you?
um
that'll
That'll have to come after probably after the the
Not I can't really even think about that until perfect comic party and um the website and the ova and stuff is all
taken care of
So many things on my plate
So many irons in that fire
I do have irons in the fire
I do
um
I've got so many as well. I've got like a big long list of things
Really more?
um
well, the the mostly like additional
Inc to like oh, I I need to think about I need to talk to that one guy about
like uh
if I can
Getting in a room with a fucking producer or something to talk about chlorissa potentially being something other than a comic
Like he's he was gonna talk to me about like
um, you've got a really good thing here
Talk to me. We'll we'll hash out like a pitch and you can we we can pitch it. I'm like, uh, okay
Uh, I don't know how to do that
And so that I got to look into that I got to ask him about that and then there's also
I should probably try to get some money for chlorissa because like I'm not getting money for it at the moment
So I was like what if I sell them?
On amazon, what if I have an amazon account? What if I go through all that?
And there's just like all these little things that will not take up that much time
by themselves
And just like yeah, yeah
My weeks are always packed with stuff
And I just kind of want to draw it kind of want to draw new chapters, but there's always all this marketing stuff
I got to do as well
I I feel like
You know
It's funny you say that because I really feel like
This this week especially but in in in
many recent weeks
Yeah, it's in spite of the fact that I have resolved to draw biscapades. I I feel like I have just had this never-ending
list of like the tasks that I that I have to do before I can actually get down
to do that
Uh, and I haven't done it yet and I just
It feels like the it feels like the
The things the things that I have to do around
that are just so
daunting and and numerous
Uh, that it has kept me from actually doing it
Uh, even though I guess it should be the point
The content should be the point
But it's not
Yeah, I don't know the best way to do like the balancing of stuff like that because
There's that thing they say
about like oh
You got to do the most important things in your life first because if you fill your life with
the the minutiae
Of everyday bullshit, you'll never like if you if you spend
If you if you answer all of your stupid emails first instead of following your passions
You'll never run out spend your whole you'll spend your whole life
Yeah, yeah, so like that's that's like a priorities thing. So like even though all these stupid emails will never stop piling up
That's that means you should let them sit let them
Let them rot I guess and focus instead on the more important stuff because the emails will still be there when you come back
and like
That's true of most of the time, which is why I'm trying to focus on the drawing but at the same time
Uh
It'll be good if though if people can buy Clarissa. I should really just get on that. I think I think that's just a good thing
uh, I think
You definitely have to answer some stupid emails. Yeah
Damn, you know, that's that's a
I've heard that's a good quote and uh now i'm wondering
If maybe I've been doing too much stupid email answering lately
Uh, might maybe probably because I haven't done any any drawing
ha ha
well, I mean
It sort of consumes you because it's always like yeah
It you you want this this a magical sort of there's nothing going on
sort of situation
um
And it never acts there's never there's never nothing going on it never. Yeah, there's never nothing going on
That's only when you're like three that that's the case
Yeah
Can't get it back. You can't play video games. I mean you can no, but like it's never gonna be. No, you're right
I can't I know more video games
I mean I have time for video games because I allocate time for no work
So I'm able to enjoy myself in the evenings
Right, I think is doing a lot good for me because it allows me to like
Constantly be making progress every week
Um with like a plan of action that I write on Friday after I finished work like okay next week
this coming week, I'm like
Do the fucking logo then do the pdf get all that ready
for a perfect comic party and then
Only once those things are done. I can start drawing Clarissa Gunsmoke during the remaining workouts of the week
And then I know what I'll be doing on Monday. So it's like
and then I have time to enjoy fucking around
On every day as well. So it's like
It's time
Management it's good
That's nice. That's nice. I mean, I guess it's working for you. Yeah, you're getting
You're getting work done, which is really nice
uh
I mean I get to play video games. I do get to play video games on twitch.tv slash st comics
battle network
So
Yes, I do have play some video games. You know what?
I'm actually really liking
battle network two
a lot
Battle network one was kind of frustrating
battle network two is like a much they like
It's basically the same game
But they just like were a lot more like deliberate in how they like balanced it and executed it in a way that is just like a lot more
fun
If what I mean
Okay, do they still have random battles?
There are random battles, but they're I feel like they're less frequent
And the battles are more
Well, I what I mean the battles are mostly the same
I feel I feel like there's less of them per like time spent walking
and
uh
Here's the one of the most important things is like
in battle network
One like the core conceded the core concept of the bat the combat is that you have
This like deck of chips that you can use a certain amount of and if you have chips that are the same like
They can either be the same type or they can have like the same like code letter on them
And if either one of those you can match and you can use multiple at the same time sort of like uno or whatever
So
And if you have certain very specific combinations of them you can you can use like a super attack, right?
In the playing through the entirety of the first game. I use
One super attack ever it only ever happened one time
Uh, I've already had it happen once
Uh, and I'm not even I'm not I'm like only like a third or the way through two
And also
It just feels like I'm actually using the combos more like there were I never used like combos in the first game
I just
if
Playing through the second game. I'm finding cards and I'm actually having like oh
This card would go with those two like this card has a letter matching these two. I can use that that makes it useful
They also introduce a thing and two where certain cards are like no letter and no letter cards can be basically matched with
As long as you have only one other letter in your in your stack you can match a no letter card with them
It's like a wild card
So even if you have no matches if you have an asterisk you can use one plus an asterisk
So you it's just more it's just more possible to to think about like which cards do I want to use?
together
And there are now cards that modify other cards and stuff
and it's like they really
Took the first game, but they did it good
the second time
Uh, and it's fun. It's cool. I'm liking it more than I expected to
That's good. How long did the first game take then to complete?
I think it took me roughly like 20 hours total. Okay
And I think the second one's probably gonna be similar
I can't remember how many
How many hours I've played like the fire emblem first game
It's like I missed I missed your stream yesterday. It was in the morning and I was asleep. I I think I should stream
Later because I I enjoy
Streaming during the day because it's like, I don't know
Nothing really going on. It's just a lazy weekend. Whatever. Yeah, but um
Nobody's around so I should probably stream later
on Saturday. I think that on
Friday I should stream earlier because the stream my my
On this Friday. I had like a pretty good stream. My my my stream was kind of I mean, you know
Wasn't I wouldn't pop it popping off would be an exaggeration, but it felt like it was popping off
It had it had more people in there
For me and I I was really high energy
I was people in the in the chat were saying like
What is that? What is this like energetic been like? What is this like hyperben?
I was I was uh, I was going off
and
But like a viewership really started to tank at the end and I think it's just because it got really late
And you know, especially like especially people in europe were like, well, I gotta go to bed, you know
It's freaking like one in the morning here
So, uh, I'm probably I'm gonna try to try and start streaming maybe around like I've been starting maybe around like six
Maybe I'll try and start around like four
Or something
Uh, yeah
I was I was I was
I don't think
I don't know if you I don't know if I should say why I was so energized
In the chat on Friday
There was there was drama happening
There was there was there was there was there was fighting occurring and I won't I won't go into the details about it
uh
But I was mad
and I was uh
And I was going off about it on my stream
Uh, because I love gossip
Uh
What else are we talking about that's twitch.tv slash st comics twitch.tv slash
Hippocrite or the give and take give and take dammit. Ha ha. I never had a hippocrite twitch
Uh
Right, right
Actually, I don't remember when or why I made a twitch account
Well, obviously the stream but like I don't remember for what game. I don't really remember
I don't really remember making tea bath. Didn't you on twitch?
Right
Maybe but I don't think we ever used it
I think we probably we probably did have an account
I remember because you you have an account that like I followed
Or something
twitch.tv let me let me look twitch.tv slash
tbbb ap
There is a tbap
Do we have any videos? No, there are no videos on the tbap twitch account
Maybe just like a parking on that space in case there was another tbbb ap it was trying to muscle in
Oh, the the description on it is tbap who's ready for some shit art
I guess I was intending to to do draw streams
Oh, that probably would be it
I think I was probably
That's really funny. I must have been intending to like draw like phantom horn comics
And then I did draw phantom horn comics and it's called slime and punishment coming soon
But I didn't stream it
Uh, I was struggling
I was really struggling because I wanted to raid somebody
And while I while I was while I was streaming
Uh hazel was live and I wanted to stream her but then she quit right before I was done
Action button was live. I wanted to raid him. He quit right before I was done. I think I ended up raiding. I ended up raiding, um
jonan vasquez
Who is not huge on twitch. I think maybe like 70 people were watching him
so
I got a shout out from
from xanen v
On twitch was was kind of fun
Uh, I keep forgetting the raid function exists by the time I'm finished with the stream. I'm like, uh, I'm tired. All right. See you
Yeah, I mean me too. And that's why I was like, well, I gotta raid someone
I gotta raid someone because like you literally there's no reason not to freaking raid someone
at the end of your stream
That's just the habit I want to get into
Who is it who the uh, sometimes I see cyber shell streaming
Sometimes cyber shell streaming see hazel streaming. I was surprised to see action button streaming
Uh, and those are all people that I think it would be funny to raid
uh, but
I'm all I all my streams go too long and they always end before I do
Because I usually stream for like five hours
I think I'm going to try to keep them shorter because it was pointed out in my chat and I looked at the analytics and it's mostly true
I think my stream viewership tends to usually go for about like three hours and then it like tapers off
and I'm not sure if that's
Just like the natural lifespan of a stream or if maybe like I start to lose my
My focus or my enthusiasm my energy around that time and people start dropping off
Because I was really energized for a while and then I eventually I was like, all right. Let's all right
Let's just talk about the game and then I kind of
Yeah, and then you know that was around three hours in and then uh, I guess less
Viewers started to drop off. It depends on
Like international appeal, I suppose but also the time you start
Because like germa
Is my favorite streamer. He sometimes will get obsessed with a game and go for 11 hours
Only are very occasionally. I mean like hit this stream is still buzzing. I don't think it drops off
That significantly
Maybe it does maybe it doesn't it's just always people there. So it doesn't feel like it's like dead
Wouldn't wouldn't know
Yeah, I think probably when a when a stream is popular and a lot of people are watching and the chat is going like mile a minute
probably less people
Probably that means this makes a smaller percentage of the viewership actually be typing
Because more of them are like well my message wouldn't even get seen because the chat's moving so fast
Uh
Well, uh
All right
Ben have you seen the anime revolutionary girl utena?
No, I've never watched it
I've begun watching revolutionary girl utena in my off time and it is very good show
Oh
I remember it being the one I would watch I've heard a lot about it. Yeah, it's like swords and dueling
and
Utena is this pink haired
Girl who dresses like a prince
She she was saved by a prince or like she
Prince found her when she was very young gave her a ring
And he said oh don't cry uh, whatever and then he left and she was like, ah
This guy's so cool. I'm gonna be a prince when I grow up and then she has a sword and it's cool
Oh
gender
Gender ha ha lesbianism
That's wait wait that reminds me of
What does that remind me of
What did you say gender?
No, I mean that was h bomber guy
Um, no brand brand of tarth. I think I'm thinking of brand of tarth
From game of thrones, you know, yes. Yes. Oh, yeah, you see you're you're a
I'm a throner. You're a throne a throner
Um, I'm a throne head. You're a throne like the the angel with the eyes
You know about thrones
Uh, you ever you ever see you ever see that biblically accurate angel. That's like a big wheel of eyes
Yes, well, I haven't I haven't seen it in real life. You ever seen it in real life. That's that's a throne
aka a throne rug aka an ophanim
Because uh, it's called that because in like the book of ezekiel or inok or something
There's like someone sees the throne of god and like it's like four of these like these four like eye wheels are like wheels
Are like carrying him around or something
They're looking in every direction
Literally true
literally true
Although nowadays there'd be like 360 cameras nowadays
Nowadays those things have a million eyes and 900,000 of them would be woke
Open your eyes. I can't believe
Wokeness has gone so far that even the even the very throne of god himself has been
wokified
gotta
You've got to stop teaching this in schools, man
Um, like like like a conservative like filming on their phone like looking at god
Yeah, like feeling god like I can't believe god is woke. You could believe what has happened
God yeah, good god appears before them on his on his throne and like the freaking seraphim spread their like giant like
There's six like rainbow colored wings and they're just like, oh, I can you believe this?
Can you see the grooming they're grooming our they're grooming the spirits of our dead
They're grooming the spirits of our hallowed dead and the saints
That's in the saints that sing god's praises. They're being there's teaching crt
The holy ghost is teaching it
What are we gonna do to vote against this? Yeah
anyway, utena is great
and uh, I
remember
The one of the one of the first pcp arguments. This is a nostalgia bombshell. I remember this one
Do you remember when exactly we were talking about the steven universe clip of pearl doing that famous
Lunge into the camera
Action shot. Yes, and it being like, ah, you know what's so cool about that
It's a reference to a revolutionary girl utena and I watched the show and I got to that part and I was like, oh
It's just like steven universe. It's just like steven
Yeah, yeah, and I think didn't me and jeff poo argue
That was an epic jeff was on that episode
Wow, and someone was arguing with me and I said
homage is always inferior to the original
And someone was like, no, it's not and I don't remember if jeff was on my side
Or not. I think I think uh, trixie and jesse were there and I do remember
I do remember it being a big argument that we never remember being there
I don't think I said much on that specifically
Yeah, yeah, it was it was an interesting idea like
Like a reference
I kind of remember like references are always lesser than the original even if the original
Sometimes is bad just by itself
Yeah, I think that was my position
But it turns out the utena usage of it is better. I like it much more
Because utena it looks so fucking cool
Her her like princely she she wears like a boy's school uniform, but it's not like the other boys of the school
Um, it's like black. Oh, she's like will smith
She's like will smith who wears her who wears the his uh, his his school uniform jacket inside out to show the floral pattern
Yeah
Yeah, it's just like that
um
and uh
Yeah, the
It's like a really cool outfit and then when she goes to do a duel with swords
She walks up this long spiral staircase and there's like metal music playing
like like
It's metal, but there's like anime high-pitched ladies singing like absolute
devastation
Uh abyss and stuff and it's like
It's so like
So metal it's so cool
And they they go to this big huge area looks like a kingdom hearts level boss area
And she does a sword duel and she does that that lunge attack a couple times. There's a bits of
recycled animation, but the animation
Like generally across all of the battles is like really solid
Every time there's a new duel there's a new like set of like really cool cuts
Who is she dueling like other students?
Other students members of like the student council
Of the high school, you know, it's a classic like ha ha anime, but like what if it's school and
Things that are not associated with school for real
Um, is it like a mystic mysticism and like weird magic that is a little bit like the clubs
Is it a little bit like the clubs in kill a kill?
Not I don't think there's like underlings or anything. It's just like these individuals
Who are part of the student student council?
And then there's all of the rest of the students who are like oblivious to all the sword dueling
That's doing their thing
Uh, but like
It's great. I really like the show. I would recommend that you watch that one
Okay, it sounds pretty cool actually
It sounds it sounds like it might be good. Maybe I would watch it
Maybe how many episodes is it long? Uh, it's like 30 episodes 31. Oh, that's nothing. So like a couple seasons
And i'm already on episode like 15
No, wait, maybe it's more than 30. Maybe it's like 38 I can't remember but uh, it's nice
It's nice and it's not
It's not like um
It's it's odd because it's such a serious
feeling show with like the imagery of the roses and the
The gothic sort of architecture and the sword fighting and the princely princes and princesses and the sort of mystical
weird stuff
But then occasionally there's an episode that's like a complete farce a complete joke
Uh, where nanami who is my favorite character?
Who is like the bitchy horrible
Uh, you know high school girl mean girl
But she's also like the the pret full comic relief character who constantly is a complete idiot and gets beat up a lot
And there's just like an episode centered around her will be like
Like her treating someone like shit and then getting comeuppance in the form of a kangaroo with boxing gloves coming to beat everyone up
It's just a kangaroo. There's no explanation of the kangaroo, but it's there for like
like
I don't know
It's it's such a weird vibe that it strikes where it's so silly
And so serious, you know, I I feel like
I said I've never seen it and I've only heard it talked about and yeah, I couldn't really have told you what john
I mean, I guess I thought that it was a
romance with like
action
There's romantic stuff and there is that action, but it's not like a it's not
Serious, which is nice. I didn't want it to be like
Like super emotional and serious the whole time. Yeah, I like that. It's goofy sometimes
There's like a little mascot character. That's like a little chubby
A little chibi chubby, uh, monkey. That's the size of like a chibi chubby monkey minky
Yeah, a little chubby chubby monkey minky is like the size of like a a grapefruit and he's always doing something silly
and uh
him a
aunty aunty
the princess looking
to to utena's prince
is uh
she's
She's kind of a fucking weirdo
She's like a nice girl, but she's kind of like really autistic and laughs at stupid shit and nobody knows what the hell she's doing
It's kind of it's it's endearing in a weird way. There was this part where
She was like there was a serious conversation going on between utena and someone else
and uh aunty was
Um, you know, she was there, but she wasn't really listening and then she was making a flip book
Uh using the pages of our math textbook and then she was flipping through it
And the scene ends when she just bursts out laughing flipping through the pages and they look at her and like what?
What are you laughing at and she just kind of stopped laughing and they cut to the next scene
She's just kind of a freak
Yeah, I love it. Hmm. I like freaks
Uh, man original. Yeah 39 episodes original run 1997
man
I would have been a tiny person
I wouldn't have been that tiny. I guess I would have been nine
I'm just shit. I mean
I feel old now. No that a that the anime is ancient, but I'm even more so
I guess I'm gonna come years ago is 97
the
Yes
Wow
I'm a relic and I'm a relic it's over
So it's so over. It's never been more over than it is right now
You know, if you're an age of empires too, you would generate gold
If you're a relic
Damn, I guess I'm not a relic then because if you were placed in a monastery, you would generate gold because I'm definitely not generating the gold right now
And I'm definitely not at a monastery
Um
Radcon five at a monastery
We'll generate gold rad cut live
To rad we'll go to the priory
We'll go to the priory in real life radcon five
Yeah, vote should we go and protect democracy in the ukraine?
Or should we take a vow of monasticism and become monks in the in the real life priory?
and uh
And generate and generate gold
Generate gold for our team
Radcon five just generate just be just taking a vow of poverty taking a vow of silence
And getting on stream get and generating gold
Yo, yo, hit the dono link to generate some gold and then we have like we have the the twitch the twitch cup
It's just like full of gold coins
I don't think of like a bunch of monks at a monastery, but they all have their own like
streamer rig
So they can like live stream them praying or something. I
I know that like, uh, I know people live stream like church masses
Uh, I wonder if there's any like
I
I bet there are probably monks that stream on twitch
I bet there I bet there probably is at least one. Hang on
I mean the only monks that are really relevant
In terms of like having existence is like
Tibetan monks or like buddhist monks and they don't do technology
as much as they can
the like christian monks
Exist in the same way that we think of them
Well, I mean those are both
I was talking about like like western christian monks
Sure, but like I thought you're at your I guess I don't know what the the the the monk like title is about
Because I don't think I've ever met a person who was a monk or even known of a person who was a monk
I've known people who are priests
or vicars
Vickers are more common. Okay, they're
Okay, I think I've heard of this guy dr. K
That does it ring a bell?
Yeah, health health. Yeah. Yeah, it's the healthy gamer healthy gamer gg
That guy healthy. I mean, I think he's an x-munk. I think he's a former monk who became like a psychiatrist
So I don't know if that really counts. I'm just trying to go like active monks
Go to twitch.tv slash for active monks active monk
Uh, well, I mean this youtube channel calls how a game addicted monk became twitch's go-to therapist
But no, I'm talking about like someone like streaming live from the monastery
I mean, it's hard because when you search monk you find like
Video game monks like like d&d. Yeah
Fucking runescape monk
Well, you know, I bet I bet it's a thing. I bet it is a real thing, but it's probably they're probably not gaming
They're probably not generating gold. They're probably well, I mean, it's maybe if there's a really popular one
um
I wonder if maybe some do it and like give like
religious advice or something. Maybe they have like just a just chatting like
Yeah, you know talk to this really popular monk and he'll tell you about
What god wants you to do in your marriage or whatever. I guess that's probably more of a priest thing than a monk thing
Yeah, I think monk is like a lower level
What is a monk is basically just a freaking like a priest in training
I always thought of it as like like if they are historically like medieval or whatever
The monks would go to practice praying and discipline in the churches and the monasteries and the priories
um, and then rise the ranks
But they would mostly be there as like servants for the older
members of the church who didn't want to clean the floors and and the toilets and make all the food
A monastery is not is not a church
I think that a monastery. I mean it might have a church in it, but I think a monastery is basically just like a dormitory
where monks
Just live and and do I think it's like a freaking
Work camp basically
It's a little town religiously themed. It's a place where you
Go or are sent to just live there
And when you live there as a monk, you know you abide by these monkish rules
And and probably a lot of them do eventually become
priests or take on other like
roles in the church, but like not I don't think necessarily you're like
Oh, I'm putting in my my obligatory service hours as a monk before I
graduate I mean think some of them do probably do that
But probably not all
damn
That's just I just had a thought that like what if I was a monk
But I was just like a kind of a shitty one and I just like never
I just stayed a monk my whole life
probably would too
I probably would have no outstanding qualities and I would just I would just never graduate from monkhood. I would probably just uh
I would probably just be making cheese wheels my whole life
Maybe maybe they would put me on duty illuminating some manuscripts if I was lucky
But I wouldn't be like the the guy who illuminates manuscripts. I would just be like an apprentice
Someone else would probably be better at illuminating those manuscripts than me
I don't know. I don't think I don't think I would have cut it
I don't think I would have cut it as a monk
Just imagine that being like you say that as you're like
Like hunched over and just kicking a rock
You know in the monastery courtyard like yeah, I'll never be the guy who illuminates the manuscripts
I mean I've practiced some illuminations on my own parchment, but uh, it's just not
It's just not that impressive. I just don't know what it takes
Well, these other guys they thank god comes to them all the time. It's just like he doesn't come to me that much
You know what I mean by illuminating manuscripts, right?
Uh, like illumination entertainment the minion animation studio. That's that's it. It literally means illustrating
That's what you call it when like a big fancy old medieval text has like freaking like a big fancy letter and like like little drawings in the margins and stuff
Like that's an illuminated manuscript. It's illuminated in the sense that yeah, you've drawn little pictures on it
So, okay, what is ilu then like there's illusion there's
There's illuminate and there's illustration
What's ilu? It's like a fucking Latin word. It probably means to show or to reveal
Or maybe to see
Yeah, illuminated manuscript is formally prepared document where the text is supplemented with flourishes such as borders and miniature illustrations
Uh
Illusion etymology
illustrary illustrary
late middle english
Illumination spiritual or intellectual enlightenment
What do you mean? What does it mean?
Where's the first one? It means light. Okay
Illuminates from the verb illuminari from in upon and lumen
Lumen or lumen means light and in so so
In light so light
in
You light upon you put you shed light upon it
That's why like reading something can be illuminating for your mind, I guess
Yeah, it's it's illuminating and that it lights it up
So light being
Not physical light necessarily
Yeah, I guess light has a lot of of connotations of
like
spiritual and
intellectual like
I see the light. I get it light bulb goes off my head and I understand
My brain is on fire right now
Um, I think I think that in old in middle english and latin
As today. Yeah to illuminate something
To give put light on something had had metaphorical
meaning in the sense that it also
It all to reveals something or um
Maybe just uh
It what's the enhances or uh
uh
I mean when you're illustrating something you're illuminating in the sense and that you're like brightening it up
It could mean that it's like brightening it up like making it nicer and illuminating it in that sense
Or it could mean and because it's in like this monastic context
It could mean
Something like yeah, you're shedding the light of god upon it because the what you're the decorations and the illustrations are divinely
Inspired maybe
Light has a lot of fucking history around it light does
the word
It's as old as the universe actually I guess I suppose so
it's just funny how like
I think of light mostly is like. Oh, yes photons
You know
Or like something isn't heavy right
But then of all these all these things that it
Historically refers to a little different. I was talking um
Long time ago probably maybe months ago in my discord about like
Uh, how you would go about
Acquiring how would you how would you go about uh, basically doing dyson sphere stuff to like acquire solar energy more efficiently?
And uh, we were just we were talking about like
Uh, okay. You mean you know what a Dyson spirit?
Uh, it's a star trek idea
More or less. Yeah, where you use
You build a structure around a sun to harvest its energy. Yeah, uh to I don't know shoot lasers or whatever or whatever
yeah, uh, so like
The building like a solid sphere would be really hard
But what you could almost just what you could also do
Is you could build just a ring around it and like then the the ring would also catch the light
You know not as much as the sphere, but you know, it's a start or you could instead of putting building a solid object around it
You could just put like a like a swarm of like small orbiting bodies and like a big cloud around it
That would orbit it and like little little solar panels that would also
absorb the light and the idea then
Would be well if we want to use that energy on earth, it would have to
somehow transmit that energy back to earth
So you would have a huge swarm maybe in a ring shape around the sun of these
Uh panels and they would be catching the solar energy and then they would have to somehow
Transmit the energy back to earth and I feel like the easiest way to do that would be like
A laser they would have to fire a laser
at earth
Towards maybe like a satellite that was in space over the earth that would have some sort of receiving
a photoreceptor that could absorb the energy from
The lasers that the these photo or these solar
receptacles would be firing at it
And I was thinking okay
Well, is it feasible?
To is it feasible to have a laser that travels that far like basically from the sun to the earth?
uh and like
stays
As a coherent beam
You know because lasers are not like perfectly parallel like they do sort of widen as they travel
And I don't know I I crunched some numbers really quick and I like I looked up some
There because okay, there's a thing where like the the the beam is a parallel beam
But it's also a wave and so like there's no
There's no way to construct a laser where the lines go perfectly parallel and they stay perfectly parallel forever
And the rate at which the like the widening of the wave sort of happens
It depends on a bunch of things it depends on like the original aperture that it's fired from
And it depends on the the the the wavelength of the laser
photon
And I did some and I did some crunch some numbers around and I ended up coming up with the result that yeah
If you use like a very high like ultraviolet
wavelength laser
Yeah, you could fire a beam from the sun to the earth and you could
You could keep a beam diffusion down
And I think the result that I came up with was that you could probably do it
And it wouldn't you you could without the beam spreading over more than maybe like a couple meters wide
So you could in theory have
A beam and you could have a satellite in the in the sky
Up in space that would have a big photo receiver
And I feel like the receiver could maybe just be a few meters wide and that would be enough to like okay
The the beams are still getting into it and I was like hmm. That's kind of sounds
Pretty feasible. I don't know that that doesn't sound that crazy actually
And then the satellite will take the laser and convert it into battery energy and then shoot batteries down at earth
It's like it's like pooping a stream of batteries down
Yeah, little tiny little AA batteries and then like and then like poor disenfranchised children from third world countries
Will go and like stand with like woven baskets around where they know like oh here every day at 3 p.m
Like the the battery like the the AA battery boy come just come careening down from space
Shattering bones
Yep, that's right. That's right
I mean, I think that I think that then probably uh, you would probably have it would fire another laser
Through the atmosphere that would probably have to be received on the ground somewhere
Yeah, and you would lose some energy there to like atmospheric diffusion or whatever dispersal, but like, you know
How much of the sun's energy are you blocking from reaching earth normally?
I mean not not most of it
the sum
The sum
But that's okay. I mean, it's got to get here somehow. You got it. You got to deal with area. I mean we could build it
We could build a cord
Could we run a cord like an electrical cable from like a satellite in space
To earth to transmit like electrical energy
Where would you plug it in it would be constantly spinning around the earth? No, no not necessarily because you you can um
You can set up a satellite to orbit in lockstep with the earth's rotation so that the satellite stays directly above
a specific spot
I would say then that it's likely that a cord of that length would be so heavy that it would pull the satellite to the ground
Like it would be it would need to be
so far away
That enough of the cord is in the vacuum of space so that it's not being pulled to earth
I think you could probably account
For like, yeah the gravity of the cord. I think you could probably account for that in in like the the satellites
orbital momentum or something
I think you
I don't know
I think you could do it but I sort of thing that
Like a kid would think oh, why don't you just have
You know a really really tall thing. Why really really long wire. Just want you to make a really long wire
Why can't you build a tower that just keeps going up and up and up? It's because the weight of the thing
It's it's not really that intuitive
But like the weight of the thing as it gets taller is so much that it would crumple it would pull itself back to earth
You would need so much support or it would need to be
so tightly
Like it would be you need to be so I don't know
There's no drag in space. So it's not like air resistance is going to be a factor
No, no, because the court's not moving if you have a if you have a synchronous
Satellite in a satellite in synchronous orbit with the earth's rotation. The the cord wouldn't really be moving
So once it's up there, it wouldn't have to deal with drag
There would be a lot of cord that was like
Yeah, it would be going up for miles and miles and miles and yeah, it would be heavy
Maybe you'd have to like start the cord at the satellite and then lower it down
Yeah, you could do it that way
I
You know, it might be one of those things that like
Theoretically you could do it but like in practice. Yeah, like like the the pull of the cord would just be like the satellite
It's unreasonable to think that the satellite would be unaffected by
Yeah wind forces
And whatever else
That might affect
That might just be too disruptive to like a stable orbit
It would be funny though. What if a little little space mouse and short chews through the cord
Space mouse
Little space mouse is like right at the edge of the the atmosphere and he goes no
Yeah, yeah, they would have to watch out for that. They would definitely have to watch out for that. Oh
um
Shit wait, I want to take a picture of something. Give me give me one second. I'll be right back
Oh, no, no another dick pics
He didn't hear that a few moments later
Oh
My homey. Oh homey. It's me March
March, it's me
Oh, it's me March and this is what I say
Oh homey. Why did you have to kill Bart?
I was working on making him
The bestest son there ever was you just killed him. What are we gonna do homey?
What are we gonna do? All right, shut up March?
Dad's back from the plant
and uh
All right, so here's my here's my setup right now
Uh, this is like
This is this is how it's progressed
So basically uh on the left you have
the the original
tonic
that I boiled down
The the the diet tonic that I boiled down
Uh really really far and I let it sit and it eventually sort of congealed into a puck
So what I did to all these is I added alcohol to them. I just added like pure like isopropyl alcohol
And then in the middle
Is the one that I added baking soda to to neutralize the acid and it turned it green and it like made it all clumpy
And you can see in the original one
There's some kind of like chunky like salt or some kind of like powder or like crusty stuff at the bottom
And I think that might be like a salt that the quinine is incorporated in because the salt is like glowing really
bright blue
And then in the middle is the stuff that I added the baking soda to and you know
It's got this chunky stuff at the bottom white kind of like like goopy stuff
And then in the right is I sort of like siphoned. I used a
syringe
to to suck up
Basically the glowing green
Liquid sort of rose to the top
So I like sucked that off the top
And then I put it in that that cup on the right and I used a coffee filter to filter like the bits out
So it's like just the liquid
so um
Yeah, this is what this is for this is for the the the face paint
Not anymore
It's just for real life. It's just to have it
Just to see what happens to smear on the wall. I don't know
uh, I just
At this point. I'm just seeing what happens
Uh, I just think I think that eventually the alcohol in the one on the right will just sort of boil off
and I'll be left with um
possibly pure quinine
or maybe some combination of
Uh sodium citrate and quinine or maybe
Maybe maybe just aspartame and quinine
Um
Yeah, I mean uh and then on the left I'm definitely I'm definitely not putting this stuff on my teeth
Sure
Uh
Slime it it's just it's yeah, I just got some glowing goo
In my room. You're a slime man, sir. I'm a slime. I'm a lean. I'm a limo man, sir
We were I was gonna add because you know, I I had plans at one point in in endless war to add um
A method of you could
It was basically be like a sort of a progression outside of the regular leveling system. It would be a form of like
Something of a way that you can progress your character that persists between
Uh
Lives and it would basically it was limo mancy and it was basically like
An ability to fight
without a weapon
basically by like slime based telekinesis that
I mean on a particular given run you probably could do more damage with a weapon
But like if you knew limo mancy, you would basically have like a certain baseline combat ability
That you would always have when you respawned even even weaponless
And it was going to be something that you had to take classes on
at um
nlacu
Not not the shitty not the shitty uh, what what's what's the shitty like community college called? Um
What an endless war I had no idea. Yeah, yeah in endless war there's there's new los angeles city university nlacu
and that's like the fancy one, but then there's like there's also, uh
Neo milwauke neo milwauke state or like neo milwauke community college
and uh
Basically to become a limo mancer you would have to pay exorbitant tuition fees
It was it was basically going to be like like a money sink like like if there's nothing if you have too much money
And there's nothing else to spend your money on you just you sink it into limo mancy to become a powerful limo mancer
And that's just like a thing that persists
It's a small thing that doesn't really make you more powerful in like the overall metagame
But it gives you like a certain benefit that carries over in between
runs basically
And I don't think it was ever implemented
uh, but that's
Exactly what i'm doing slime congeals right is right you study slime
and slime accessories
Um
But I think I mentioned yeah, I put the glowing powder in the tooth makeup
and the effect
You know what I'll show the picture that I posted
This I've given I gave up on the quinine. I gave up on the tonic. It was too complicated and stupid and probably dangerous
to my tooth health
But I mean when would that stop a slime boy?
uh, but uh
So I tried the
I tried the um
No, not copy link copy image
I tried putting the glowing stuff in the tooth makeup and uh, here are the results
and uh, you can't
Couldn't could not be more pleased with the
Yeah, it's so good. It's so good
Um, so I hope to do a little bit. I hope to do a little skit with that
Not exactly sure what the trailer will hat will be
Probably probably just a little thing where like I'm thinking maybe it's like oh
The framing of it is like
Oh, the the cop killer is addressing you like uh, you want to join my oh, you're new in town, huh?
You want to join a gang? Well here read this read this graphic novel by ben sain
It will tell you everything you need to know about life here in new los angeles city
Something like that
If you hold up the book in the video will it be
Let's well enough to see what it is
Uh, yeah, I think I'll probably have to do a cut
I'll probably have to like cut to me
Yeah, because if I hold the book up in this light, it will not
You might not be able to see what it is and it'll look weird. So yeah, that is a concern
I could but I could probably do a little a little
I mean, you got a great screen. You could do a funny like floating book thing
Oh, that's true. Yeah, but oh, I could just limo man see it in the cop killer is a master limo man sir
And he just whoo an intelligent he's so powerful
Yeah, yeah, I could wear
um
Yeah, this is all
I'm just gonna film something and then I'll just kind of try and fuck around with it in vegas to like see
What can I do with this? How can I make this look kind of funny or presentable or reasonable?
Uh, yeah
Don't don't exactly know what he's gonna look like
But anyway, I love I love that like
You can just see the glow like bouncing off of the ridge of your nose a little bit
Yeah, so it's like oh it is there, you know, it's like it doesn't look like it's just a cut out thing
It looks like your face is glowing
And it because it is because it is
It's a tactile practice. So I was practical effects practical effects
I
oh
I don't like how my face looks not in this picture. I mean just generally
But that's okay
You know, they'll be distracted by the glowing teeth true
You know what would have been cool and probably some people could do this is if I could print
with like fluorescent ink
I'm sure that some printers do that
But I do think it's kind of like a sort of weird and unusual like boutique
printing
Yeah, that would cost like a huge amount
First of all most printers probably couldn't do it and even the ones that could are probably more expensive baseline
And I'm sure they would charge
Yeah, out the ass to print in specialty ink, although maybe if it was just the cover it wouldn't be that bad
But whatever this printer doesn't offer the service and it's the one I'm going with so
I don't know. Maybe if I maybe if it sells like gangbusters and I have to print a special edition
10 years from now, we'll do the 10th anniversary special edition with glow in the dark
cover
Yeah
Now that now that would be how you achieved like a real like
neon green
Print I think is if you use like fluorescent yellow ink
The highlighter ink
Never never paint seems unnerved by the
As usually that's the point
It's meant to be
Highly it's meant to scare
People away
It's not they don't pledge. It's meant to
Exactly right. It's meant to scare away those low rolling
Poor juvies without two slime coin to clink together. Sorry
Captains of industry and high level gangsters only only the real slime heads are going to stick around through this pitch
To buy my freaking book
You know what I'm saying
Still waiting on my orange green screen to come in the mail
I just remembered. Yeah that I have a single slime coin, but not two
I'm currently looking at it. I wonder um
You know, I haven't tried putting the slime coin under a black light
Some of the some of the enamel pins that I got actually do
Look really good under a black light
But I don't know if the coins do
Red band would probably be like completely black
Yeah, I don't think aside from his eyes. I guess wait
Give me go back to being marge. This will this will only take this will take less time than the first time
I know exactly where it is. I don't
My marge bit was was it was it was a spur of the moment. What else can marge do other than say help me?
Help me I'm marge simpson like that's it. That's the whole bit
Um
Yo, oh, holy shit
Alpen's
ecstatic
I heard him exclaim
Hey gamers
Oh
Yeah, I'm yeah, I'm I'm thinking we're glowing
Yeah, that's glowing. Yeah, I'm thinking we're glowing under that black light
That looks really good. That looks super good that rules
I was afraid it wasn't yeah, I guess I got to get a black light or like an ultraviolet light. Is that
similar enough?
Uh, I mean, I think I think I kind of have like an ultraviolet light like a tiny little light bulb and like a
Toy thing. I think I think that's what a black light is basically
Well, how would you do?
Uh, I have like
I have like a big one. I have two like big like standing ones now
I also have a little tiny like little little mini flashlight of one
That's what I used to use. Uh, but now I have these the big ones. So
That's really cool. It looks super good
Uh, what was it? What were you talking about?
Enough enough of me showing off my funny my funny goo
Um, I guess nothing
Hmm. I said go watch Utena
I can't wait to get back to that
Uh
Fucking Clarissa fucking this and that whatever
This and that
I don't know. I guess my my week has been mostly about redoing the give and take website
and thinking about Clarissa stuff
And playing runescape and watching Utena and that's it
My weeks are very regimented and simple and they just just keep going
But cool cool
I do feel sometimes that I'm like
It's too
Similar like the days are too similar. I'm getting amount of I've got I'm getting an amount of work done and it's all positive
But I like I wake up. I do the work and I
I relax with the things that I want to relax with which are the same things
I'm like, maybe I need to switch it up a little bit. I don't really know what to do
It's it's still too annoying and cold outside for me to feel like I can go
For a nice walk, but I think I should do that. I think I should do some more walks
Mmm. Yeah, I yeah, the cold is um cold makes me want to stay inside
It's been the cold everything sucks when it's cold
it's been colder like
now in like early march
then it was
Like it was really it was very mild like most of winter and now
end of february it's finally like like
below freezing like snowing temperatures a little bit
It was like it was like felt like it was like 40 degrees
Uh, most of the through most of winter just kind of nice. I mean I like that
Um
Uh, I guess shall we go to voicemails? How long how long we've been going an hour an hour 30? Yeah. Yeah, okay. Um, you know what?
there actually was
Oh on my stream
The guy that sent a voicemail
From last week said that I didn't read
his voicemail
Because I was too distracted by the image
Uh
That he sent so
It was it was the one um
It was the one that was I think it was called like why and it was like a picture of phantom horns, but
Do you remember?
Uh, I don't if it was the last episode. I don't
Oh, that's right. You were I mean, right never mind
Uh
Shit, okay. Well, let me um, there's one saying why doe?
Oh, where? Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, why doe?
Yeah, okay. Well, let me let me revisit this one because I told that guy I would go back
Yeah, I'm looking at the image, but let's listen. Here's the image. All right. Three two one go
I'm probably one of the three people who recently got into the pgp and ben verse
And I gotta ask is was phantom horn meant to be a parody of trans people has he been reclaimed?
Is he problematic? Oh, so why he think that's so
That's so devastating. Uh, I mean
The the the honest answer is yeah, he kind of was and now I feel bad about it
And I kind of uh
Yeah
I mean, he wasn't okay
I think I've talked I've talked about this before. Yeah, he he kind of was sort of a like ha ha
The sjw's have gone so far now an earth pony is identifying as a unicorn
Ha ha it's so wacky
What the left has the left has gone too far
Uh, and then I eventually was like, hey, that's kind of stupid
uh, and I and I
Made him cool by sending him to slime city and he became
A base dialectical materialist marxist and now he's good. He's been reclaimed. He's good now
Don't he does look pretty thick in that picture. He does look pretty he's looking. Yeah, he's looking like a short stack
He's short stack
He's literally stubby little way
I don't know why he drew him that way
He's chibi. I think I've said last week. He's just this is chibi phantom
um
Next
So is phantom just in and the swore now is he in that yeah that land?
Oh, just hanging out. Well, I don't know if you oh, this is this is a
One angle that I like kind of forgot. I was trying to type up like the Kickstarter page and I kind of forgot
And then I remembered is um, yeah, the ending of slime and punishment is like secret
And like the only way you could find it was by beating phantom's revenge and phantom's revenge is like way too hard
for the for the casual gamer
And not me though. I did it. That's right. But I think most people
Probably didn't I think like a pretty small number of people actually
did it so
Even the people that have read phantom's or slime and punishment most of them have not seen the end and that's a big reason
Why so if that's you and you're too casual you can buy my book and that has the ending in it lamau
Uh
But yeah, yeah, he um
Well, I guess is he does yeah, he posts slime and punishment. He just continues to live in uh
In new los angeles city. He he canonically lives there now
yep
Although he can he can go back to
equestria through
The night star portal which is now a permanent fixture in the uh
sky and someone devs
I hope an endless war dev is listening right now
If we can please add some functionality where you can travel to equestria
when you're on the blimp
When you jump through the portal
I would appreciate it just like twilight sparkle just like twilight sparkle
In that's the plot of equestria girls, right?
Uh, yeah
Yeah
Okay, I think the first voicemail this week is from it's called 6 30 38 from prince isolation
three two one
Go welcome back to the ben saint appreciation hour
Where on this episode a quote by ben saint
I already streamed for like two hours
And I started streaming kind of late today
So I think that I won't really go that long. I won't go like
Five hours or anything like that
Right
Let's listen to the whole song it's loud
I went really long it was a long stream
Uh, I think this is probably
Jesus the whole I really like the low quality of that really really bad
Uh, this is probably like I mean that might it was at the time when I beat the game because like I think I was just like
Like yeah, I'm gonna beat the game like I gotta beat the freaking game now
No, no that was the first stream
Of battle network
one
So I had just I was enjoying the game. I was really enjoying the game
um
the
Yeah, and I think
The one after that that I went for four hours
And yeah, I think I'm gonna try and keep my streams like four hours or shorter going forward
because viewership does not
Hold up
The whole I'm usually at like by by four hours in I'm at like half the viewership that the stream usually starts with it starts
Dip off around the three that's a historically been the case
I just want to increase the amount of time I play
I did that like last time it was a seven hours. You know, yeah
I only go through like four five
Maps in fire emblem. They take quite a lot. Oh quite a while. That's kind of
Yeah, when I do when I go six hours in a stream
partially, I'm just kind of like
Even if there's only you know, either there's only a few people actually in the chat
I'm kind of just playing it to play it because like
You know, but my goal is to play these games. So
Yeah
I don't feel like oh, nobody's watching. I gotta I gotta cut the stream. I'll come back later. I'm like
Well, even even if no one's watching I'm still getting I'm still accomplishing my goal
Uh while I'm streaming. So that's why I stream for a really long time. Sometimes this part of the reason why
Yeah
Thanks for making fun of me
Uh next one is called real
Oh, is it a a broken uh
Damn
Yeah, that's what also is says real. Maybe it was a fixed
Maybe they fixed it. Yeah, that first link didn't work for me
And then this is real question mark dot dot dot
It's got a voice attached
Yeah, okay, uh, let's um
Uh, okay, let's listen, uh, three two one go
I'm so very sorry to do this to you all. However
Uh
Let me just read it for you. This is
Yay, Ayano Koji bloated by not whole nuts on deviant art
Enjoy
Uh
Then
I thought this might be like veruca salt willy wonka, but I I mean it seems
Very similar. Um
Wait, okay, the the next one is an image
I'm sorry
glide yaito
Okay, yeah, so in mega man legends
Uh, there's this guy. There's a guy called glide and this girl yaito. I don't even know who that is
It must be like a really minor npc
And then I guess she kind of looks like
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Yai yaito and they kind of
I guess it's supposed to be the same
I yeah, I mean the girls definitely look similar
I don't even who is okay yaito mega man
Uh
Yo, there's a there's a trio called yokan. Oh
Okay
Yeah, it's one of the three women or girls that are sitting in the like village
Hut that asks you like a hundred trivia questions
To give you a freaking bonus item
That's like a fun job
Yeah, they're just at school cushion
She I think she asks you the like easy questions and then the one on the right asks you the middle questions
And then the one in the middle the sexy one
Asks you uh, the hard like the hundred hard questions
And all right, let's listen to the voicemail three two one go
I just realized I probably fucked up because I removed the image from my imgur
From the first link that I just sent so it probably didn't work
So you probably the first thing that you saw me send you related to this subject was just bloated. Yeah
I am very sorry about that. Here is the the actual reason that I sent you anything at all
the actual
interesting image post
I'm sorry
Uh, yeah
it does
kind of look
Yeah, yai is I I'm not sure if she's supposed to be like a tron bond. She's sort of like it looks like this girl yaito, but she's
She's like a rich girl like like tron bond and she kind of has tron bonds hairline
So I guess it's like they mash these
Two together and I don't know why this little girl from the school is even
Irrelevant, but yeah
Probably just like the design wanted to use it again. Yeah, we just like the design. Yeah
Um, they put her in a dress
That's interesting. I I told her
And then they put a hose upper
body and
pumped her full
air
Next one
Oh
pov
New pcp episode just dropped yo true
That's what they look like
That's what I look like
every time
I see the new episode go live. I'm like, yes another job well done
uh
The the colon d is funnier than the actual face
Just the
Just the straight text
uh next one is
Is
Something let's look at it pov perfect comic party or whatever the fuck weekly comes out
Cool story bro. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my fucking god
That's the plan
Yes, true
This is this will be you this will be you
soon
um
Next one
is
It much
You look like
One of the blessed land
You look like one of the blessed land
boy ve
um
Why is she ukraine? Is that gib? Is that you? Is that me? I
maybe
Why am I I mean, I guess I'm ukraine
Aligned, I guess if you ask me, but like it's not a big part of my personality one thing when people ask who is gib
I'm like, well, she loves the ukraine
She hates poot
um
I like your your stance in this one. Hmm
okay
Is the blessed I feel like we at some point maybe a long time ago somebody made a joke about the blessed land
About the jewish people. Is that like a term?
for them
This line you look like one of the blessed land that's from something or somebody said that and I don't remember
who
or why but
Commenters if you remember what this is a reference to it's it's something
Hang on jews
blessed
land
jew.com. Okay the term holy land usually refers to the
Territory roughly corresponding to the modern state of israel and the palestinian territories. Okay, they're all right
It is so maybe it's some why would they say blessed land? Why not the holy land?
No, I don't know this is this is a reference that I'm like blanking on
um
Next one is uh, but I do look cool in my zutsu there next one is
I dropped one piece
Oh, no, I forgot to read one piece this week. No you reminded me you reminded me and I said and I said okay
And then I didn't do it
Oh, no
Think of all the trash that you could say I could have read up. I could have been that this is literally me right now
What are you saying one piece is good actually
I
Just I really like
The complete like inversion of the reason for this mean this mean image
Oh, what a sad person who missed out on all that
Is
Is the implication that like the first 10 episodes are good
Or is it just that like all of one piece is trash and like yeah, it's a good thing you stop
I think they mean like the longer you go the worse it gets so just like if you
If you drop one piece it's good
I don't know. I just like it. I like this image how brazen how brazen to just like
One piece trash. It's all trash
Who says that true true, but also who but also true, but also how fucking dare you?
Okay
Oh good stuff. Oh boy
Let me calm down after that one
next one is um
Kong a luya for let's freaking go as gib would say let's go. Let's freaking go
It's licking go
Girl next one. Uh, here we go
But cramlings he is after you he's tough and he's got pistols too
And every night he should sense
Kong a luya
Oh
Hmm
Kong a luya
Um, um, um delightful another another another banger we got a
Are we gonna get like a compilation
When when all the verses have been performed are we gonna get the full the full song?
Maybe I would I would lull. I think I would probably laugh. I would I would sing kong a luya if we got a compilation
I would sing if we got a kong a palation kong palation. There we go
Now we're talking
Okay, uh
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go
uh
Next one is
An image
Oh, come on. Fluttershy. I got plenty common with you and viral mentalists both
Such as such as
Hmm. Well, we both hate coal burners, don't we?
What what does that smirk for applejack? What do you mean both hate coal burners? Is that a racist?
Thing I mean because it's applejack, of course everything she says is to raise it
I would imagine is that a joke, but I don't actually know the reference
I don't know what is being referred to oh
A non-black person usually a woman who has sexual relations with black people usually men
well
Now I know applejack
Applejack
Uh, uh, she's just kidding. No, it's fine. Yeah, she's just having she didn't learn anything
I didn't in woke school in crt. Yeah
Uh, I just wanted for many just one of her many quirky quirky traits
um
Okay, the next one is called give this man justice three two one go
So I just went back and skim through episode 132 of the pcp
Just because it was the deltarune one and I liked seeing everyone as the deltarune characters that gib true back
Oh, yeah
It was nice and fun
But someone left a voicemail on that episode
Calling in to make fun of Nate for using an electric skateboard
And then he did a grind on his real skateboard during the voicemail and recorded the like
Sound I remember that and uh, I forget by calling him a pussy or whatever
There's the best voicemail ever and I think it was before voice grail
So I want to let you know that you should retroactively give that guy
From four years ago voice grail
Also, uh, does Nate still use his electric skateboard? I feel like I haven't heard about that in a million years. Um
I don't know
Sorry your voicemail was just so boring
I I agree about the voice grail though
I remember that one
I remember we all cracked up because it was just sort of like just a typical voicemail
But then he did the the skateboard trick with the audio
I and it's and then it was like, yeah, fuck you. It's great
I actually don't
remember that
Almost at all. I don't think so. Maybe I I remember it was funny enough that everybody laughed including Nate. Hmm
Oh, yeah, I'm drawn a blank but sounds pretty cool
An electric vouch for that for that voice grail. All right. Okay. Let's do it. Let's freaking go
Let's do it. He's in god's gift to grinds is in
Yes, yeah
Do you um
Shit, uh
Okay, the electric skateboard is like one with a motor on it, right that like
Propels the Casey Neistat boards. Yes. Oh, yeah. I mean, I have no idea if he uses it. I haven't heard him mention it
In forever. So probably not he probably just drives
Yeah, it's a bit of a weird thing to go around using. Yeah
Having a car is inconvenient as it is in new york city, which is why Casey Neistat uses that all the time. Hmm
Yeah, I uh, I don't know. I don't know if he's it
Um, he's probably not grinding on it too much
Okay, next one is called thoughts about this
Hey, you. Hmm. Well, it's kind of gross
Reminds me of that that
I don't know what artist did it but like something something a teaspoon made of fur
Oh, and it's like a series of like what if an object was like made of a material that made its purpose
pointless
It was made it really bad at its
As its purpose like something that you would heat up being made of
I don't know bubbles or something
Maybe being made of wood. Oh, I see merit Oppenheim
Yeah, I see it's like a teap a cup and and a dish
Here I got I got the image cup and a dish and a spoon
Cup and a dish and a
Hey, I'm eating a cup and a dish and a year
Yeah, that's the one. Yeah
It makes sort of it makes it sort of pointless that it exists
Makes makes but I guess in this in this case you could cut
The non-hairy part of the cheese away any bad if you really wanted to yeah, I think that's probably how I would
Approach this this cheese problem
Is AI generated?
No, no, it's gay. I generated gay. Yo
sick
Was there
Was there some AI news
I mean I might have
I might have talked about that one clip, you know that one like really fancy looking clip going around of like the high resolution like
People playing rock paper scissors
I haven't seen that but I don't the thing that's annoying me with AI is that
Extremely unfunny people are going out in droves to make the same video over and over again
Of donald trump and joe biden and whoever else
Just like in about whatever and it's like ha ha. Isn't it funny?
Isn't it funny that these famous people that you wouldn't expect to be playing a video game
Are playing a video game and they're on headsets and that's it. I gotta admit
Uh, I saw I saw like a couple of those and I did think a few of them were really funny
It's funny once but like it's now it's now now that's so accessible
It's just gonna continually be a thing. Yeah, that's god. That's a gag. That's a gag
That's not gonna that's not gonna you got to be good at writing if you want to make something that that funny
I really think that the that tall barts
Videos of uh, joe rogan and uh, ben Shapiro and jordan peterson
Uh talking about their money troubles are really good. He's he's tall bars. Pretty good. I you guys really funny scripts
I like them. I um
I mean tall bar was making like youtube poops like sentence mixing without AI
So they clearly
they have
uh
They've they've shown that they can come up with some some funny things the AI stuff though. It feels a little
I don't know less funny. I think
Something you think you think it was funnier when he was mixing their actual words together. Yeah, because it sounds unnatural
it's the sort of
It's it's it's the it's the fact that it's it's obviously not really them
that
It something there's there's an extra element of like absurdism
in there that makes it like
I don't know. I'd prefer it. I guess
Yeah, so somebody's saying like saying
Like a like an AI generated voice of a person who you wouldn't expect to say I suck dick saying I suck dick is like
Sure, they wouldn't say that but just sounds like them saying something sounds like a person talking
But if you okay, but if you sentence mix it
There's something else to it and I like that. I think
I mean, I think I mean tall tall barts tall barts skits have a little more going on in them than just having
Jordan Peterson say that he's gay or whatever
Uh, that's a lot of it. But yeah
it
I don't know. I saw I saw
They they've started to sort of they have sort of like a narrative to them
They like they like sort of make jokes about themselves and like they have I don't know
I saw one that was Jordan. It was it was
Rogan and Ben, uh, they were they were AI generating like
Like oh now make now. Let's make well this AI stuff is so funny
Let's make Jordan Peterson say some gay stuff or whatever and then they do that for what?
I don't know. Are they just I like I think he's good and they're
I don't think they're bad. Fuck you. Fuck you. Just leave my man tall bart alone. I don't think I'm bad
That's all they are they are competent and humorous
I just I guess I've just seen a lot of it recently and I'm like, yeah
Well, where where's lamp oil roping bombs, huh? Where's my boy and dinner? Like I want more of that
Where's where's my boy and dinner? Okay. I mean sure no
I understand what you mean about like. Yeah the weird
The weird and unnatural way that it sounds when they just like are obviously cutting like lines together
To make them say some wacky shit. Yeah. Yeah, it has a different
It's funny for in a totally different way. Yeah
Um
I thought it was I thought it was really funny to see tall bark. Yeah, I had been following tall barton. I've been seeing
his uh
His mixes his videos and then when AI came out
He's he suddenly like jumped on the AI train and he started doing like
Some slight with some different ones
using this AI voice tool
And I thought that's great. I don't know. It's cool. He's like, oh a new thing I can make these videos out of well
I'll do it
And he did it and I think it's good
I think it's good
Uh next one is called
Uh, how would you send? Yeah, how to send file without vocaru
And then he sends it by vocaru
So that's interesting three three two one go
Bro, remember ram ram movers. He fucking died. He didn't make enough money. What the fuck
Just like uh maple sorry too
What the fuck life sucks
Okay, you don't need to pretend you care
Uh maple, okay. What was the Rambo verse?
Rambo verse I don't remember Rambo verse
Or whatever that could be
I guess he's talking about like I think he's saying rumble verse
I don't even know what that is. What is that?
Rumble verse was a free to play brawler battle royale video game
developed by iron galaxy and published by epic games publishing
I heard about that
It 91% liked this video game
Did it die?
It apparently yeah, I guess it I guess it got shut down
Rumble versus shut down feels sudden, but the writing was on the wall. Yeah, I guess the game died
I mean
I
Never thought about it even that was that while it existed. That was the dodge ball game, wasn't it?
I don't
I'm pretty sure I saw somebody watching it and react into it as like a trailer
Maybe it's germa and he was like, oh it looks pretty good
And it looked like a dodge ball game, but like battle royale dodge ball
Maybe it was like really like announced it like e3 or something that I can don't know
Do they do e3 does that exist anymore? I think they
I think they don't I think e3 died everyone's dead
Does that mean the packs became the new e3?
I don't know. I think everyone does
Nintendo events. Oh, yeah. Now they all now they all do Nintendo directs and stuff. There's no need for a freaking convention
Coronavirus killed everything including video games coronavirus literally killed
Someone who was working at at packs like two years ago or like a year or two ago
They they they did they did one they did packs in spite of everything and somebody died
Not so good, not so good, not so good. I wonder
Um, I wonder if they still
Do them
Packs let's let's look at packs on twitter
um
At packs twitter
No, I mean they're still going
March 3rd looking for something that packs east 2023. Okay, so they're doing packs east
Um, okay, you all you know, I guess one little death isn't gonna
Isn't gonna stop you
I mean, you know
It's kind of true a bit like
It's not it's not it's not like oh packs literally killed someone
You know somebody got somebody got covid and somebody died and I mean, I guess these things do happen
But I was hearing about it and I can't it can't be good
Can't be good publicity. It can't be good for like view. It can't be good for attendee enthusiasm
Uh, I would always hear about gaming conventions and like all my favorite youtubers would go to whatever convention
And I would see the things and they would have a little video. It's like well, I went to the thing
But they it always seemed like such a fucking
nightmare
Even though it was fun in some ways
I went to
the last day of packs east like
Maybe like four or five years ago. Maybe five or six years ago. Yeah, and then
Funny story, maybe I've told it before sheep over
You know, you're a sheep over who used to be a
Mumke's girlfriend at one point
Said that she saw me and this was post tbap and I think maybe even post pcp
She saw me and she recognized me, but she didn't say hi because she was uh
Chai or something
Then she told me later. Oh, yeah, I literally I saw you like at a food truck at packs east
I was like, yep. Wow. I was there on sunday that one year
Very funny
Um
What was the other one he said rumble verse and
Uh maple story too, I guess
I've heard of maple story
Uh, I think I did know that there was a maple story too
I didn't know that it died
Oh maple story too lives on in our hearts through its creative expression and unique aesthetic
We'd like to thank the wonderful maplers
No
We'd like to thank
We'd like to thank the wonderful maplers that inhabited its charming world by offering you the chance to keep some of what made the game special
Here you'll find links to download all kind of designs illustrations concept art and more
There's tons of art and never-before-seen assets and we invite you to take a look
We've also uploaded the music of maple story 2 onto our official youtube channel
Or you can always find it if you want to take a trip down memory lane or download and take it with you on the go
Oh my god
Why is that hitting me so hard?
It's it's it's a real big thing when it's like
Like
A lot of virtual worlds online like mmo's that they feel more than just like a video game
Uh, especially when you're young you spend a lot of time on there. They're like a virtual like physical
place
And then they don't exist anymore
People get real fucked up about that. So I know I do
I'm still sad about world of warcraft changing everything in the cataclysm
I thought you were gonna say club penguin. I mean club penguin is as well. I was gonna say that as well
And then good and and and then like runescape before they released old school runescape
Runescape had changed beyond recognition. It was just like this is not what I lived with. This is not my friend
I hate this place
That's what I say every time I look in the pcp server
Uh, yeah
Oh, I'm I'm I'm that's just that's just so sad. I don't know. I don't know. I just thought
I don't know
I can't look at this anymore
Maple story one still exists like maple story one didn't die
but I guess two was just like
I wonder why two died just the the player base didn't migrate
I guess uh, maybe the business model was just not
Damn
Best the best laid plans
um
next one is um
The philosophy nerd hour from prince isolation at twitter.com
three two one go
On episode 350 of the pro-crastinators
Men's saint does not seem to fully understand what
Vinny Vitevichy means when he says that he appreciates give and take for simply being who she is
But if he'd have read kirkegaard and specifically the sickness unto death
He'd have known that according to kirkegaard
We are constantly living in a state of despair because of the friction in our human condition between what we want out of life
And out of ourselves. That's me and what we eventually get and what the limits of the material world are
and
because of this he claims that
Everyone can live with despair in
several ways
One of these ways is despairing wishing to be oneself wherein someone
Wants to be themselves
But wants to basically change their condition of existence and continually improve and fight against their despair
In the other case there is despairingly not willing to be oneself
In which case one despairs of existence so much that they don't even want to have their own
Identity anymore. They want to basically reject themselves and their own lives. So I suppose the question is ben
Do you want to be yourself?
uh
It's a big question
um
I feel like i'm not supposed to answer seriously
uh
I've a lot of I don't know. I think I think a lot of the time most of the time. Yeah
A lot of the time, you know what a lot of the time I do fall into a state of like
I wish I just didn't exist the I have those I have those times. I wish I could just disappear
uh
But you know
It's not all the time. So I guess I guess it's a little a column a and a little a column b for me
I have both
I get you a guy who can do both kinds of despair. I guess
Little column a a little a column bang
Um
Got him
Uh, well that was educational
So next up
Well, there's an image and
Another voicemail from the ben and give appreciation hour
From prince isolation
Steeped in malice and cruelty steeped in malice and cruelty
Uh
This is what
Endless jess said my blue rays are steeped in malice and cruelty. That's the joke
Uh
Next one. Oh, no not the next one. There's a voicemail. There's a voicemail. Okay three two one go
In honor of the jessie blood feud
also
Recently ben said that um in another iconic quote
that
He becomes stronger every time someone spurns him which
Also goes hard and it reminded me of a song that I think is very ben core
it's called I think see the light by ghost and uh the main the main
Chorus of that song goes every day that you feed me with hate I grow stronger
And I think that is possibly the most ben core song ghost also has a big cathedral
Like like christio
Inspired religious
But also satanic angle. Uh, I you know ben I think if you don't already listen to ghost try it
I think you might like try that song try see the light. I feel like it's your vibe anyways, you know, bye
You know, I know
What am I
First of all, I appreciate this drawing. I love my little slime my little slime drool
uh
Although I don't wear
khakis unless those are supposed to be jeans because I do wear jeans
Um, I rarely tuck my shirt in. I'm not a nerd
Uh, but thank you. Um, do you know ghost?
Uh the lord of
No the the band
Uh, is that the one with the animator who did the little thing?
Or was that the song called ghost?
Oh, are you talking about I've been feeling like a ghost. Yeah, I guess that was the song
I hate them. Oh
uh
Yeah, no that yeah, that's a song. Uh, no ghost. Okay. I don't I've never listened to ghost
Uh, I guess they're kind of a big sort of I don't know. I don't
What I gather from seeing their stuff is that they're sort of a big like kind of theatrical sort of yeah gothic
metal
question mark
band
And I think they do like really elaborate costume sort of stage
Shows I think I think there's a lot of like theater in their
work
and uh
I feel and I
Sorry to be a hipster. I don't listen to them
I kind of feel like I see them around enough. I'm gonna be an asshole. I'm seeming to contrarian asshole
I feel like I see them around enough that they're unpopular enough that people sometimes think like, oh, yeah
I'm into this indie band ghost. I you ever heard of it, uh, but they're but they're not actually as like
Underground as people think because I feel I feel like I have seen
I've known people that like them
and uh
The fact of the matter and I know I'm being unreasonable here
Uh, I've known people that like them and I don't like those people who I have known who like them
Although maybe there's other people that I know that like them. They just never brought it up
Maybe I'm just thinking of a few people who were vocal about their
Appreciation of ghost who now I don't like and that does get and that does sour my opinion of this band that I've never heard
I don't listen to
But maybe I should give them a try and I would change my mind
And
Thoughts give
Uh, my thoughts is why is this the been and give appreciation hour? Yeah, I had nothing to do with give
I mean, I guess it's and
Yeah, this should be this should have been the been or give appreciation hour because at least one of us was appreciated
You just say ben appreciation hour if you want if you want to talk about ben, I don't mind
Or you yeah, you just
Like sometimes people just send a voicemail and it's directed to one of us and that's okay
There's nothing there's nothing wrong with a ben a good old ben appreciation hour
I guess prince isolation wants to stick to the brand of like this is the been and give appreciation hour and it will contain appreciation of
One or both of us and that's the
Uh, okay, that's what I think about ghosts
Uh, I've probably heard one or two of their songs
But like without realizing that it was them
because I feel I feel like they are
Known and popular enough that I
I do hear people talk about ghost
um
Next one is called. I hope nate is on this podcast so he can apologize to ben
Uh, three two one go
Okay, so nasa sent people that's what I
And it was this massive technical feat
And everyone thought it was impossible and they did it, right?
So you believe that but then you turn around and you say that
Well, no, there's no way they could have had a camera that could film that long like
Like do you have no imagination? You just use a bigger
Like it's good. What okay
First of all, does this have anything to do with nate? I don't think nate does moon landing denial
But I know I thought maybe he was responding to something from last episode. I wasn't privy to
Wasn't aware of I know I don't I don't think so
What is he talking about with a camera?
Okay, I I'm not sure
I've heard that specific
Thing but like yeah, I guess maybe people that say the moon landing could not have happened say well, they recorded too much footage
Yeah, they couldn't have
That much footage in a camera and that and I don't I don't know if I've ever heard people say that before
But that is the kind of thing people say
Because they are like so limited and they're thinking that they're like well any camera
That would go up on the space shuttle would be exactly like a commercial camera that I like I use
In my real life and therefore like the the the memory limits that I am subject to in my normal life
Would apply there too, right when in fact, no, they could simply make a custom camera that has different capacities
What is the argument here that they couldn't have faked the moon landing because they couldn't have enough film?
No, I think wait because because this guy's saying you believe the moon landing happened
But then you also believe this other thing
That they couldn't be enough film I'm like who's having this who what's what argument
What person would make this argument? I miss under
I'm listening to it again
I'm yeah, I am really confused are there can't be someone who is like. Oh, yeah. Yeah, the moon landing is real
but
they couldn't have actually filmed it because
Yeah, I don't I don't get it. Oh, is this like a weird like double like they believe the moon landing happened
But they believe the footage of it was faked
some for some reason
What is this have I've never heard of that didn't they'd say this there's no way
No, I don't think so. I think the title is completely unrelated
Okay
Maybe
Yeah, there maybe there is someone who is like, yes, there was a moon landing
But the footage is fake because the footage what the footage was staged because they couldn't film the real thing
Maybe somebody believes that lamau
Uh, next one is called. That's a very funny
Like conclusion to draw
from the whole thing
Like I would never have considered this idea
They probably just had funny cameras
They could put a man they could they could get a rocket into space and put a man on the moon
But they couldn't make a camera with a real big enough to film it
God could you know, it just could god
Do a moon landing so impressive that even he couldn't film it on a camera
I think perhaps
Next one is called bend.exe 321 go
Hey, Ben, congrats on beating bow network one
Did you ever have plans to play network transmission on gamecube?
Pretty sure you already know, but it's basically classic mega man, but with the battleship mechanics
Oh, in fact, it's actually got a lot of callbacks to the first game
Which is pretty cool
And more importantly, it's got zero dot exe
Which I think is just the coolest version of zero throughout the entire franchise. That's so funny spoilers. I'm sorry. I guess technically
His battle chips really fucking suck, but
You know just being able to summon zero to fight is just really cool and I just do it anyway
um
But yeah
Good luck with the rest of your battle network series and thank you
To your next lecture or whatever the hell it may be
sweet, uh
I will start working on the next lecture soon. I just as I
Oh, that's another fucking thing that I got on my plate that I have not even been able to really
Do so many irons
It's a little too many irons
Okay, that's really funny. First of all, I didn't know that that's what battle transmit or network transmission is
Um, I have I was planning on playing it because I know that it's part of the series
I didn't know what it was though, but that actually sounds like it could be really fun
Like it's like a side scroller, but with about that sounds awesome. Now. I now I really want to play it
um
And that's really funny that you say
That about zero because at least one person in my chat has told me that zero dot exe is like the worst
Version of zero and they and they hate them
So I'm interested to hear that opinions are divided on zero dot exe
So I look forward. Maybe he's like super edgy
The proto man in in uh mega man dot exe is basically I mean he looks very much like he's a he's a mashup of proto man and zero
So it's like they were trying to combine those two into one
Character and they just called him proto man. I know that there is a zero dot exe
I actually don't know what he looks like. I haven't looked him up
But someone told me they hate his design and now this guy says he's really cool
Even though his chips are bad. So
That's exciting. Yeah, I definitely want to play um network transmission
um
Probably in in release order. I should look into like what exit which what were the release order was
next one
It's a new comic. I think it yeah, it's a dropbox link. That's me
Yes, I yes my the the sniffer
Sniffed the the the I forget what is the big nose
Sniffed my boobies away
No
How could you
It's not fair. I never get what I want as soon as I am happy some goofy shit has to happen to take it away from me
They were perfect a million M and Feminine
What make them that big again my life's over. They were so squishy and snuggly and warm and it's just not fair
True
I can't go on like this. Everything is ash and woe. I'm gonna kill myself
Yeah, I'm gonna jump off the top of hq and fall infinitely into the void
Void void void void void void void void void etc
How should I do error Ari's voice?
Hey, you you want to put some clothes on is that too much? Is the inward voice too much?
I remember that from the t-bat place
Hey, you want to put some clothes on no, that's too much. That's all too you want to put some clothes on you want to put on some clothes
Void void
Uh
Whose giant butt is that is that error Ari's giant part with the heart shamed pockets going through the the the doors there
Okay, oh, let me zoom in
Oh, yes error Ari
doing a little
doing a little rarity
Oh, it's a it's a dress
making
It's the art. She's really doing the art of the dress right now
Cool. Cool. Now, let's hit those nine flights of stairs
nine
That's a lot of flights
That's looks so cute
It is cute. Uh, I look like jade
Yeah, yeah, definitely
So why do we got to find Nate again?
So we can use him as a blood sacrifice for the Nate fuckers
Wait, what?
I mean everybody wants him back on the podcast so might as well get some sweet content out of it
Can't blame him though. Nate always brought that 2017 cringy edge that I sort of miss
Why do you stop coming on anyway again? Why do you stop coming on anyway?
I don't know he didn't say and then he started the gamer zone and talking pirates
Apparently we're too cring for him to associate with let alone podcast weekly
But but podcasting easy
Oh, right
Now that's right. Yeah
Okay, I'm pooped
Battery your battery is at three percent time for a charge. Oh, it's bro. It's the bro AI
Oh, no
You got your charger on you
I have a type C. What do you take? Look at that face?
News so good. What the fuck? Yeah. Oh, I I'm looking
Why does did ever Rory always have like a giant
Thighs like this. I don't remember from the last time. I don't remember. I think they're destroying them like that
Uh
CCS
One
What the heck is that an ev charger? What?
Oh, like a tesla. Can you can you?
Can you uh, can think you can carry me the rest of the way?
Hell yeah, I go to the gym at least once a month. It's not even that much
Yo, if only I were there. I'm I'm lifting
Just hop on. Oh, let's go
Alrighty five more floors
Oh, look at the oh those are your x-ray vision of your bones in your legs. No
No
That butt's so fucking big
So fucking big
Wait the apple
I there I remember there there's some backstory behind the big apple, but
I love my faces in this yeah
Just five more
Okay, there's no way I'm pushing it
push
I'm
There's no way in piss. There's no way in piss shit in fuck and piss shit in fuck. They make it five more floors
Gotta find a charger
They open the door hello
Another fucking monster
Fuck it
Scout wait scout nothing scout nothing scout nothing
Look how freaking cute these are. They're so cute
They're so cute. I'm shimmying. Oh, no
Hey, hey close one. Is that the bear?
Is that the bear from gamer and the bear perhaps?
I was thinking it was
Beware beware of the bear could no prepare for the bear prepare for the bear much more likely. Maybe they're the same bear
Why
There's just two bears and there they are
It's just one of the two bears
Uh
It's so good. This is so good. Did we say on the show that like
Hey, we'd love to maybe put some of these uh new comics in the in the in the throw them in the in the dang
Perfect comic party
I think I should we definitely mentioned it. But yeah, I should reach out to new on twitter and like ask him like
Hey, what do you think? What do you think if we put these in there? Should we?
You you said you you have the high res of all the
The past chapters, right? Uh, yes
Okay, cool. Um
This one
This one's really this one looks really good
The faces in this one are really cool. I have I don't have enough nice things to say about news art
uh, but I think
There's uh, there is a new there is a new drawn comic in the dojin. So
That'll be funny. I need a dress like this. This is a good dress. It looks cool
This this the one where you got your tongue hanging out the the posture. Yeah, it's great. You look like
You're running me of elaine from sign film and I always liked her so pretty
Look at the librarian like a gothic librarian. Yes. Very cool. Very
Very nice
new
You've done it again
You saw you son of a bitch. You've done it again
Uh, thank you very much. I'll appreciate it
uh, next one
should be like
You know, I saw um
I saw the dick show like posting fan art. They were like posting the fan art that they got that week
on twitter
And maybe we should do that or something. I don't know
Because like yeah, that's pretty funny
Some of the stuff probably deserves to be
I mean, we don't really use the twitter for that much. Do we I don't I really don't use the twitter for for
I hardly ever do. Yeah, I just use it to retweet
Maybe things
That I tweet that maybe I want the pcp audience to see as well and like that's mostly most of what I do with it
um
Yeah, it'd be a good idea. I think probably it probably would be a good idea. Okay. The next one is an image
What is
Dang this
Dang congressman, which I had a wife who would tell me her prophetic dreams. Oh
it's um
I think
If I'm remembering remembering correctly
There's a there's a congressman called a representative clay higgins
Who just straight up says that like his wife gets visions from god and has prophetic dreams
Yeah, I think I may have heard of it. Yeah, and and he
I wish I had a wife who would tell me everything
Maybe if I had a maybe if I had a psychic profit for a wife, maybe I could have been a congressman too
Uh, unfortunately, it just didn't work out that way
I'm pretty sure it's clay higgins that I'm thinking of
Um, unless I mixed him up with someone
Because I follow clay higgins on twitter and his tweets are boring and but I just followed him for the meme
Next one is
Oh, I already posted it. Next one is called to gib from me. Please and thankles
three two one go
Yeah, I don't know if you heard yet, but ben was
racist
That the robot was in your place for
Uh, do you need skulls for me? Thank you. What what did you say?
Wait robot. You must have it must have taken my mind. You remind me how racist you are ben saint
I said that you scolded me. You woke scolded me for saying that gino samuels
Delivery was stiff and robotic. You said I shouldn't use the r-word
Oh
You said it was triggering and I said I would do better
Um
How do you not remember? How do you not remember this?
Uh, I don't know. I just you were so you were so you were so adamant. You were so
Impassioned about it
It was a rollback
I got you
Uh, next one is called. Oh, here we go. Gib appreciation. Oh, this one's not the ben and gib appreciation hour
This one's just the gib appreciation not even an hour. All right. Okay three two one go
Also on this episode of the ben and gib appreciation hour
I was listening to gib stream and she made a very cute funny joke
Where she just went like oh looking at my character stats high strength high speed. Hi. How are you?
And I appreciate that joke. It was small, but it was and it was subtle, but it was good
also also
I figured I should give a counterpart to
Music that is very ben saint core music that feels very gib core. Have you ever heard of igloo ghost igloo ghost?
Everything is really weird glitch core like
um
Bops and whistles kind of sounding music
That is like very otherworldly, but also the mascots for it are like these weird little like
clown-esque alien creatures with like big noses and party hats and um
The the lyrics I think are supposed to be like their language and it's really weird and funny and cute
And I feel like gib might like that and it just it feels gib core. It's like it's like odd and silly
and and and like nice and and chaotic and cool
And I don't know check it out
So
I get regular ghost and you get igloo ghost. I get igloo ghost. Oh, I'm I'm looking at uh, I googled it
There's a little image of the little mascot character
That is a gib core design
Very cute. I yeah, I'll give this a listen
Sounds kind of neat
I'm almost a little more interested in this than in ghosts
Because it because I've never heard of this before
And once I've heard of something that's how I know that I'm not gonna like it
um, so
I was gonna say oh
Uh, you made a cute you made that cute joke. I had a bit on my last stream. I said I was really high energy and I was really like
Uh, a hyper I I had a
A thing I don't know. I made myself laugh up roriously
Well, that's always fun. That's always good when you know
I had a I had a bit that I I meant to clip it. I think I I should go back and I should clip it or something
Uh about how like
When I don't know if the story of mega man dot exe you have to
update hub dot bat in or and you sync your and hub's dna
Because your twins you sync your dna 100 and you become
Sinked and so though if you die in the game you die in real life. Well
Uh, it was like, oh, what if what if um, what if hub was circumcised?
And land was not and that's why hub died
Like hub died because of being circumcised and so your dad is like land
You have to you you have to run hub dot bat to complete his genetic code and sync it with you
But the one downside is if you do it you'll become so perfectly synced that you become circumcised just like your brother
It's the only way
The only way to save him land. You have to be circumcised
To update the circumcised data into your dna
I I I'm killing myself again
um
It's just
It's just your dad your dad is really fucked up your dad makes you do like he's a really he's a huge freak and he's like
It's really it's actually really good that dr. Light didn't have any kids in the main timeline because that guy's a fucking sick sick fuck
um
Next one is uh an image
And there's also a voicemail to go with it. Oh, it's a little guy. Oh, it's a little guy
with his little
orbs
His little orbs
Uh, let's listen three two one go
Just as an example here is one of the mascots for the song clear tummy
By igloo ghost
Cute little guy. Don't you think I feel like he is gift core. I feel like this guy. That's what you said. I'll you any day
Okay. Bye. Bye
Yes, I agree. He had he had the same
He had the same thought uh cool
Well, that's the last voicemail
So
Yeah
I didn't read
One piece
In fact, I'm too
In fact, I'm two chapters behind because I didn't read it last week either. Oh dear. Yeah, because um
Well, what do you you want to read it right now? Um, or
Is it too? I
I've read it so
You want let me just let me just check. I mean, it might be a really could really cool one
Yeah, I remember I'm remembering it being like like oh
Like a little bit of a pog moment. I see. Oh, yeah, it was definitely a pog moment. I think you should
Okay, so
Uh, I guess I'll do that right now with that. Um, yeah, okay, so let me
No, wait, you you you did there was a break. So there's there's no um
Oh, right like last week there was a break
Was there? I mean, I don't remember. Well, I am I'm reading the most recent chapter 1076
And that follows on immediately from 1075 which we did read on the show. All right, let me um
Oh, yeah 1076
It's the one with um
There's a double color page spread of the straw hats doing a cool poses and stuff
Oh
I'm I'm a little did I did I read 10 1075 it's the yeah the gore say
Standing there with the vega punk and then
Yeah, yeah, okay. I did I did read this one. Okay. At the end of the last one
it was like
Zorro and Luffy
With kaku and luchi and considering maybe letting them free because the seraphim have gone nuts
Yes, okay, I'm reading
And I'm gonna pee while you do that. Yeah, good good good
The the shorthand I feel like Oda's shorthand for being like
The coolest old guy in the world is drinking a huge amount of sake from a big plate
Yeah, he's always doing that that shanks what a white beard what was always doing it and now shanks is always doing it
I also like how
he draws shanks
without those like
trousers
That have like they go below the knee but only a little bit
Hmm
They look really comfortable, but for some reason they're also like really badass like ah, yeah
Uh, I mean, I think they look badass because they're on shanks. I guess I guess so
But I want some
I guess I kind of have some already
Imagine like a an edgy tee and being like, oh, I want to wear those those those fluffy floral pant
pant like long shorts that like tie up on the leg
I'll look like such a badass just like shanks. I always thought I always thought
Oda knew how to draw legs that looked comfortable to be
Like Luffy's shorts the whole time. It's like, why don't they sell shorts like that?
This look cool
They sell like fake like sort of scuffed jeans and all like you can roll a jean up, but like it doesn't quite work
They're like fluffy somehow
Dory and Broggy
What?
No, I mean
Who's that big kid?
Just a kid I guess looks I like that big kid looks cool
Do you have a message for captain kid?
Tell him he can either hand over his load pona griff rubbings and scram or he can risk fighting me. Hmm
Kid lost his arm fighting
Shanks's
fleet
Yeah, I don't think it was
I can't remember if that was like him
Like before time skip. He didn't have an arm. He may have had two arms and then in the time skip
Bunch of shit happened and he lost his arm fighting shanks's crew
I thought he always had the
Well, I know he always had the the magnet power
Yeah, I don't remember
Weird
This seems weird that kid lost his arm fighting against red hair shanks who has one arm what's going on
Is that just a coincidence?
Did he steal kid's arm to replace his own?
Kid you specifically have the just the right arm
It or
Wait a minute. I'm putting it all together
They were going to build the perfect white beard clone. They made uh, they made white beard's son
And shanks was going to donate his arm to the hideous frankenstein projects
But he lost it so we had to steal kid's arm to donate his instead to stitch the this man together
What's the way sounds legit? What's the white beard kid's name?
Uh
Eugene
You oh the the edward weevil we the other guy edward we've yeah weevil weevil
Okay, uh
They won't settle for an arm this time maybe the chief's coming through
So glad to see you youtube back then oh your protection money. We don't do that
They won't settle for an arm this time. They'll take your life instead only if I lose ha ha ha. Oh my god
Wow
Yeah, so it's they're fighting about this they're yeah, um
I
All right, so I caught the uh the thing
That they gave a me little baby me hawk the dice dice fruit
That's really I don't know. It's cool. I guess the idea behind each of them is they gave each one like the best fruit
They could that's why they gave baby ginbay
The the wave fruit to turn that he could swim through anything
And they give the best swordsmen in the world the I forgot about that
Yeah, and they give this guy they give him the thing that turns his whole body into a sword
That's awesome. Yeah, it's so fucking powerful dude
Yeah, cool
So yeah, scary shit initially
They're fighting the two of them the the kuma
Seraphim and the me hawk seraphim
And it's a little too much
And they gave yeah, the me hawk the the leg
Not the leg but like the um
The turn your whole body into a sword thing
Dice dice the dice dice fruit. Yeah
And so they agree
Uh to let him out. I like how luchi is not trying to be subtle at all
Like he he's not he's not the kind of person
to like
scheme I guess
He's just gonna say I'll kill you
I'll work with you now and then I'll try and kill you afterwards
Oh, I'll kill you. Oh, I'll kill you all right. Yeah, uh, it's like help us help us uh
Help us get these guys and then let us put you the handcuffs back on okay
They're like, yeah, sure. Yeah, whatever
Yeah, of course
And he's so proud he he like
Is easily
Is easily got by the the insinuation that he's like it would be a cow and a sore loser if he didn't yeah
Yeah, you can't beat me so after this you got to fight me
and
You know
Once, you know, if you win if you beat me then whatever but like, you know, you can't beat me
So you can't you can't just do whatever you want. You got to fight me first
It's the same fight you it's similar. I guess to that moment when
He fought alki g the first time
And he said like Luffy alkegi. Yeah, Luffy fought alkegi and he got turned to ice
But because it was like a one-on-one duel he sort of like
Protected his friends by making it about like just them
And alkegi was like her. I guess I can't kill everyone
Like I plan to that's pretty cool. You got me
I
I forget exactly how I don't really remember what he was sort of like an like an honorable duel sort of situation
In order to protect his crew
But this time is a little more low stakes because luchi can't be luffy
He probably can't I mean didn't didn't they just lose didn't luchi like just get owned
He did
Yeah, so I don't know
But he did come back. It wasn't like he was at the brink of death. He came back with the through with the
With kaku and stussy
at the top
after they had retreated to
To the egg area or whatever it's called
So they're all right, they've temporarily joined forces against uh
Frickin, I think it's just the the me hawk and the kuma
sarah phim
It looks so cool
Then doing their their big attacks at the same time. Oh, yeah
And of course kaku was like a swordsman. So it's like
So it's their enemies. They're one-on-one enemies
But together
It's like crack for me six king gun
Yeah, luffy and luffy and luchi fighting together and uh, uh, zoro and kaku fighting together
I love I love kaku the fight the the zora versus kaku was one of my favorites of the whole series
yeah
The whole like fucking cutting through
The any's lobby tower and then it was like slowly shifting the entire time after that
Yeah, I just liked him him using his like giant
giraffe
body so like
You can't outreach me. I'm everywhere
I can't wait to see it return. I can't beat a neck that long
There's no what do you even do against a neck like that?
Slice it I don't think so
Uh, so so then then we're in some sort of containment chamber
With a bunch of government intelligence agents
Yeah
From various crestinator podcast
Uh, ha ha ha true
various make clones. Yeah
and um
So it seems two months back when we were meant to set sail
The weaponized seabees attacked us. We were brought to the island
Then other game agents came so two months ago something was going on
Agents were being captured and held in prison
And then other agents that were sent to get them were held in prison, which is probably why cp0 is here
Yeah
In some in some fashion because because to them this is like oh, they thought vega punk was
Doing this capturing cp9 agents and just hold they thought they thought he was pulling a trade federation from the start of phantom menace
When they were just like catching. Oh, you sent your goons to come and inspect us. Well, we'll fucking
Trap him and murder him. We'll gas him
uh
But he says he
Is not the one behind it. He had no idea and now he's in here
and wasn't he
I'm sorry. Wasn't he like a baby?
Moments ago. Yes
He what well moments
It's been a bit a few minutes. There was that everyone split up
And go look for vega punk. So he's been gone for a little while
But yeah, bonnie
Took his age out and turned it into funny little shapes
Right as one does
And I guess he got those back at some point
Yeah, and is now locked up after getting punched
probably
By bonnie, I guess. I mean, I can't think oh, yeah, he's like bleeding, right? Yeah
Yeah, he's got he got beat up and locked here and now he's learning about this thing going on
Um, damn
They said vega punk could see everything
Kid knows everything, but does he know why kids love the taste of cinnamon toast cream?
I mean why they're locking my captain kids like the taste
Yeah
Uh, he didn't he didn't even know is happening under his own nose some some genius
um
Yeah, so it's it's
One thing so who so I've no idea who the fuck could possibly I mean, I guess someone is is running things over
Maybe it was that shadowy figure that we saw
looming over one of the vega punks
before I thought that was just like a
a hint of the seraphim
Yeah, maybe it was just one of the seraphim. I didn't didn't we
Wasn't there like a like a dark figure with like glowing eyes and we were like not sure
I was and it might
Or might not have been a seraphim
Uh, I guess we could go back and check. I felt like that was like, oh, there's something going on here
What's the mystery and it's oh, it's the seraphim but like
Yeah, there's another person that was not revealed in that moment
That is probably the person who is now being referred to as leaking data to the world government
Yeah
And and all of the reasons that like vega punks like research is being outed
Um, the stuff that obviously he wouldn't let this slip himself
Stuff that would get the world government to to fucking send warships to kill him
Um, so yeah, somebody's been leaking stuff
And I guess
Who?
Is there anyone currently that we know about who it could be do you think?
Santomaru
I mean, why would he do it?
I don't know. He was already like
marine affiliated, but he was like loyal to vega punk
Yeah, we've learned
Because he was rescued like a as a baby or something
I mean
Who have we seen that hasn't I'm just trying to think of who has any authority on egghead?
I mean vega punks the guy and then there's like his seven
Clones or whatever and their sentomaru is like his direct underling
And then there's stussy who was a cp0 agent. Well, stussy just got here. I know but like
How do we know that? I don't fucking know. That's not that's not a good that's not a good theory. Um
She's just suspicious. I guess these guys have been here for two months
So someone's been here for a while. Yes, either somebody who's just not been introduced yet
Yeah, or it could be one of the vega punk like robots
Maybe maybe one could one of them be rogue and the other's not I think no
It could be but then like what's the seraphim doing killing the vega punks?
You know, but is he killing all of them? Maybe he's is there one that like maybe hasn't been attacked
But don't well all the vega punks know everything that all the other vega punks know
Yeah, that's the only thing that's a little weird. I guess we don't know exactly how it works
But that's how it's been explained is that they share
They share data
Yeah, I guess they don't necessarily share experiences because one of them
will have like
Thoughts like they'll see something and they'll have to report it by speaking to the others
Oh, so like you think they can have
Their own individual like thoughts about stuff and the others. It's just like information they learn
Yeah, I mean maybe yeah
Because like a thought in your head is not like something you see or hear or whatever. So maybe that stuff is not
transmitted
Yeah, it could be
I don't know. Lilith is evil. Lilith is just evil. Lilith is the evil one
But I mean she was with the others and she was being attacked with them
I mean the the most surprising one would be if it was shaka
But number one. Yeah
I feel like he's got more power to do that because he's like the guy who looks at all the information
He says things to everyone about what's happening
He seems the most on the level
Which is why it's like it would be the most he seems like the least likely candidate
But that makes him probably my first guess if it is one of them, it's probably him
Yeah, so
I guess at the moment we don't have much to go on other than the fact that not really where is bonnie
Um, and what did she learn when she got the kuma thing?
Did she learn more? Why is she not here? Did she do anything bad?
Where'd she go?
Because if there was a bad guy if there was a bad guy that was orchestrating all of this for two months
And then they found vega punk beat him up and locked him up here
Did they not find bonnie either?
Is bonnie just somewhere else?
I think I think the fact that yeah, I think they I think they probably
Split up. I think bonnie and vega punk must have split up and then vega punk was taken in
I mean, this is all happening. This is like happening pretty fast. Yeah
Uh, so like they're probably still look whoever is doing this probably is looking for
Bonnie or maybe they decided that bonnie is fine and they can let bonnie go
Yeah, I think it might be shaka. That's my this is my theory but it's only because
When they lost track of vega punk and bonnie
He was the one who was looking at the monitors and saying, oh, we don't know where they are
Everyone's split up
And everyone just agreed that he is calling the shots. So he would be the one who could
Throw everything direct people. Yeah. Yeah, definitely
I mean, I have no idea. I have no idea why he would do that but like
We don't know anything about him other than that. He is vega punk sort of and he is
In charge
Yeah, and also the seraphim
They weren't necessarily attacking him in that room. They were attacking the cp zero and luffy and zoro
There's enough other people there that they weren't just attacking him. So maybe he was like on the white list
Yeah, but you wouldn't notice
Yeah, he's he's he's I would say he's my suspect number one. Yeah, just because he has the most opportunity to do it
Uh
And it would have to entail that like some yeah, there's there's some
Either they don't actually know everything that all the other vega punks know or there's some mech mechanism by which one can hide something from the others
But I mean, uh, yeah outside of that or maybe sentomaru, I can't think of anyone else who would be
Doing some weird
Betrayal over like a long period of time
Well unless unless vega punk is just actually what if he's just lying
What if he's actually just lying and he put himself in jail and uh, he's he is bad and the mastermind
And all of them are are just playing a big long con
You know, it's possible. I just feel like
It would be a shame
If like vega punk was a bad guy this whole time
I agree
But what if I don't want daft punk to be evil we'll have to have to kill daft punk
Maybe he's not a daft punk after all. Maybe he's a sensible punk
What if he takes his head mask off and underneath is like
She's got some kind of fucked up. She's got some fucked up comedic villain face underneath
He's got some
big teeth or something
Yeah, like he's resentful for dr. Vega punk for making him ugly so that he needs to wear a mask
Yeah, you made all the other vega punks look nice. Well, what about me, huh?
That's why I started
spying on you and taking your secrets
Hmm. Yep
And vega punk nods and says, yep, that's exactly what I would have done. I should have known
In that situation, I would have behaved exactly the same way
Uh
And then uh, I guess we're on to yeah kid and
freaking kid and shanks at albath
the giant island
So shanks wants the pony glyph rubbing
and kid has one
and um
They're gonna freaking fight about it
Oh, this is cute. I've just realized um shanks and this giant kid
It's the same as when luffy was a kid and shanks is at the bar
and shanks is like drinking all his pirate friends and
Luffy's like, oh, come on. Take me with you. Come on. Take me with you on a cruise on a pirate adventure
And now shanks is saying that to this this giant kid
The same thing was the kid asking. Oh, yeah, there's no way I'd bring a hotheaded kid like you
Wait, this is is this a giant kid?
Yeah, it's a giant. Oh, these are the islands of giants. Oh, they're all giants
And oh, that's that's why the sake plate is huge and that's why the the blueberries are giant. Okay, this makes
Yeah, it all makes perfect sense now because like last time we heard about alba
Elbeth was um because kid had found it. He found albeth
And maybe he found it because he was looking for shanks
Because shanks was there
And so kid captain kid is fighting shanks his crew or is like causing trouble
And shanks is like, oh, well, I guess we got to go say hello
Oh
So
Is kid is kid the aggressor here? Is he like attacking shanks's fleet?
Is he trying to like get somewhere and shanks is blocking him?
I think um
It's likely that kid is the aggressor just because that's what kid is like and
seeing as he has a
a history of a shanks
He probably wants to take down shanks in the same way that he and law took down big mom and like everyone took down
Kaido and all that. It's like he's one of the the yonko. He's a target
Hey, look at this. Uh, I mean, what do you make of?
in this panel
This panel of um elbeth. I mean just look at the way that the island looks there's like a big
black like
pillar
I would say that's tree. That's like a giant tree
Hmm
Perhaps a world tree perhaps a yeeg dressil
That's a classic Norse thing along with vikings and giants. Oh, yeah
That's a good point
I I looked at the the the way that the island looks and I thought it kind of looked like
Fire and ice island or whatever that was called like it looked like some of these mountains were like melted glass or something
Yeah, maybe it's just a huge tree a huge huge world tree that would
Either that or it's like a huge
Viking elbeth giant castle the the the texture on it does look like bark
Now that you say that no, I think you're right. I think you've hit the nail on the head there
And then wait wait wait actually if you look up above the ships
Like above the ships there are like sort of uh screen tone like gray
Oh, yeah, there's like pillars like further away. Maybe it's many trees
I think these are just I think these might be giant trees
Yeah, is this like adam wood?
Oh, remember that being like the special words that the that was used to make gold rogership and then frankie bought the thousands
Yeah
Do these could be adam trees?
uh, did we
Do we know does like that come from elba?
I don't think
Comes from anywhere in particular, but we just know that that's a type of tree that's got like the best wood
And it's probably the big tree
Probably the giantest of trees
Okay, okay, just a just a just an idea. Okay, it's
Wait a minute. Wait a minute adam treasure tree adam is a type of tree whose wood is considered the strongest
It's immense rarity makes it highly valuable
Uh
Okay, no
No, I think I think we've seen adam trees
I mean here here's a screenshot that supposedly has one in it and this is from the anime
But supposedly this is a screenshot of a treasure tree adam
And it's normal size. Oh
does that that that looks like the one that um
Uh, niko robin and the the librarians of ohara had is that that kind of tree? Oh, um
I don't
I don't I don't know
probably not
ohara
I mean I had a huge fucking tree. Yeah, this is what ohara looked like
They built a library on the inside of it
I think
Frankie explained the history of this one of a kind. Oh wait. No, there's only one
There's only one treasure tree adam
What
Frankie explained the history of this one of a kind tree long long ago an endless war raged on an island
People died and the island was destroyed by a rain of bullets and left in ruins. However, the people kept coming back to rebuild
the nation near a giant tree
A giant tree the only one that remained intact and that was adam
Adam
So that big tree could be adam
There is apparently also a sunlight tree eve on fishman island. Yes, and that's what and that's what lets the light
Come down through the red line
Through its roots to illuminate fishman island. Do you remember that?
Uh
That's why there's light. That's why there's light in fit. That's why there's light in fishman island. I remember
And us up. Yeah, and and us up was like treasure sunlight tree eve. Is that like the treasure tree adam?
Fascinating
We have to know more
Uh, so yeah, shanks is having a party is drinking and eating with the giants in the bar
And uh
That he's gonna go
Because one piece is just so boring
He's gonna go deal with kid
Um, and he says hey, uh, dory broggy. Can you lend me a hand? And I also notice
Uh, oi mo and kashi from any's lobby is behind them
as well
Remember those guys
I do remember those guys were on
They were on some other island before they were on any's lobby. Um, yeah. Yeah. Yeah
They were like tricked into
Being
Allied with the marines for some reason they said they were like tricked
Um by the marines saying dory and broggy were captured and they had to do this
But then us up told them that they met dory and broggy and they're fine
And so they turned the tables
They became friends of the straw hats
Yo
It's so cool
How much stuff how much elba for we're getting nowadays
Yes, this is the next big arc. Yeah, this is the one we're we're we're
We're moving towards the elba far egg egghead is like part of it
Who do you think's gonna win between kid and shanks, uh, I mean
Shanks obviously has more strength and the backing of the giants is obviously gonna do a lot
Yeah, kid is not as tough as he thinks he is
But he's got he's got uh hootspah, you know, he's got gusto definitely definitely and he's got uh
I mean killer is uh
I mean, he's got a history honestly of like of picking fights that he can't win
He picked he picked a fight with kaito and that resulted in him being imprisoned
Yeah, true. It didn't he and he was uh, who was who else was he fighting on?
Was he he fought other people on the on the kaito island? Or am I just did did he end up fighting?
Uh, uh, the the the wicker basket guy
Hawk
Basil Hawkins basil Hawkins or was that killer that fought basil Hawkins
I think
That's a new number of people
I can't actually remember who it was that did the final fight or was it Diaz or was it Diaz drake that fought basil Hawkins
Everyone fought him who has fought basil Hawkins at this point
Such a weak boy a little bit cool hair though
Yeah, so
He he fought kaito and he got imprisoned
And he got rescued by luffy and whatever was going on in that prison break
Um, and he's like, yeah, fuck you. I don't care about you, but let's team up anyway and kill kaito and all that
Hell yeah
He clearly is coming here with a chip on his shoulder or should I say a lack of a shoulder?
His chip on his one shoulder
Ah
I mean
He's still got a shoulder
So, yeah, this this is implying that there's gonna be a fight because of course kid would not
Give them the the poneglas rubbings
Um shanks getting getting bitches
You have to see a couple panels of shanks getting bitches and drinking a huge plate of sake to know
This is the who are these women that are like jumping on them because they're not giants
Um, well earlier shanks said something like
How do you say? I guess I lost track of time catching up with everyone
um, maybe it's more than just the giants he's catching up with maybe there's like
Like other members of his like grand fleet if he has that i'm sure he has a grand fleet
We just haven't heard too much about them because why if they had had like a fleet of different pirates that would loyal to whitebeard
And uh
I guess luffy has that as well
Uh, yeah, yeah, like bar the bar not bartholomew
um
What's the name of his bartholomeo bartholomeo his his underling speaking of bartholomeo
um, you might not remember but there was a point where
He declared war on shanks under the straw hat flag. Oh god. No when
Why it was it was in a cover like arc
Bartholomeo was doing some stuff
after dress rosa and then
he took over a town and he
Set fire to shanks his flag and put the straw hat flag there in its place
and then later
This event was referenced by the the the red-haired pirates
at the end of wano
When they could have gone and seen luffy, but they didn't I think shanks just did like a a hacky from across the sea
And then they left
Just a sense that luffy was there
I can't remember exactly. I think yeah, he did he did a hacky
to the the the green bullet the green bowl
Admiral who was there causing trouble
Hmm
He was like turning into a giant tree and he was trying to fight and and momonosuke was like saying no, you can't come here
This is my kingdom or whatever
And luffy was watching saying yeah, you go momonosuke, but then shanks did a whole big electric hacky conquerors hacky thing
To the admiral and then luffy could feel it. It's like that sound that feels familiar that hacky. I'm sorry
so you're saying
the green admiral showed up
And then shanks just like from all the way across the ocean like
Disabled not all the way across the ocean. He was his ship was like at the edge of
wano
But yeah, it was a long way. It was like silly amount of distance. You couldn't see weird shanks. I
Kind of I don't know how shanks could see the admiral, but whatever and that was at the very end of wano, right?
That was a very end of wano. Yeah. Yeah after they've beaten everyone
And so they I think somebody mentioned that that does ring a bell
We can't see luffy yet
um
And also we can't forget about that thing that happened with the bartolomeo guy
We don't know. I don't think we know what happened to bartolomeo
um, but clearly
That's gonna have to be resolved I guess
True
Uh
I mean, I'm sure that shanks probably understands that bartolomeo is
an unruly vassal
And is acting on his own
Volition this is this is the part. I think where we'll we see
shanks having to be
ruthless because
If he's got a fight kid
Like I don't know if he's gonna be like nice about it
I
Yeah, I don't really see any reason why he should be
So that'll be cool. This is yeah, this is shanks like
Yeah, when he's not in nice guy mode he might
He might uh, be really
Fucking
He might even be a big meeting to this guy who's fucking attacking his ships
There's also the thing with um, like at the end of wano during that combo
Where shanks did the hacky and everything he said to beckman. Hey, isn't it time we claimed the one piece?
So that's what shanks is doing now. He's shanks is no longer just hanging out. That's so funny to just casually be like, hey
I feel like uh, you know
This comic's been going on for uh, uh, 28 years now. I think it's about time. We got the one piece
I think we should be moving we should be moving in that direction in my he's moving and shaking
It's it's about don't you think it's about time we got the fuck on with it
Um, let's go. He's just doing it. I do remember that he's gonna kid. He's gonna kill or severely
Mame kid and take his other arm
And and he's gonna have the pona cliff rubbings and then it will be like
Shanks
Might go after law next
Because law has another one of the rubbings
Yeah, so it'll be like
What and then it'll be he'll have to come for luffy after that
Does luffy have a they must have several rubbings at this point? Yeah, luffy only needs one more. I think yeah
Yeah, I guess
I guess if shanks is serious, he's gonna have to come after those rubbings
So
That'll be cool. That'll be exciting
Um, it's an airplane in my my noise. I don't know if that got noise removed
I think I heard a little buzz. Here's a question
Would would shanks have gone and after kids rubbing
If kid was not like already attacking his fleet or was it just like it just it just so happens that this kid guy is
Attacking my ships. Well, I'm gonna fucking get him and I'm gonna take his rubbing because I need that
um
You know
I think based on the fact that he's going after the one piece
he may be
Landing at albath after a kid because we know kid saw albath and there was no sign of like
Pirates being there. Oh, yeah
So maybe kid was in the area and now shanks has arrived and he's just gone up to the pirates and say hey bros
Remember me and everyone's like, how the hell yeah shanks
And he's sort of muscling in on the territory. He's just having a drink casually and then he's go, okay
Let's go get that shit now. Let's go kill kid
Knock him on the head. Right. Yeah. Yeah, he's he seems
That makes sense and it would be that like yeah, he's no he's he's actively
Going after people that have rubbings
He needs those rubbings. It's time to get the one piece. Oof
That's exciting
That's that's awesome
Uh, I'm freaking I'm freaking
This is a big pog chapter
Most a lot of these chapters have been pog
It's so like
It really feels like
It really feels like things are slotting into place for like
a real like momentous
battle or or uh
Something's gonna happen things are moving
I'm excited
Uh, yeah, can't wait for next week too bad. There was a bi-week
Yes break next week
It's a break next week too. Yeah, right at the bottom. It says that
Oh, right. Right. Right. But like by next week, they'll by our next week. There will probably be another one
Probably uh, I don't know. I don't think so
Well, I well actually I don't remember if this one was out last week or not
Was this was this new I don't think this was out last this is new I think okay
Um
There's gonna be some yeah, he's gonna he's gonna steal kid's arm or he's gonna maybe he'll take maybe he'll take his robotic arm
Maybe he'll be nice and take his robotic
No, no, I probably wouldn't do that
Like I mean he can't do that because right because it's all together with his yeah
You just make another one. What if he is like, hey kid, you're a machine
Magnet man, could you like build me an arm like that and I could just take it with me and like that would be cool
Maybe they'll become friends and kid will make shanks a robotic arm
Wouldn't wouldn't that be nice
Uh
One piece one piece more like
Fun piece. Yeah
Whoo
Uh, I love it. I loved this chapter
I'm gonna love the next one even more. I promise
Uh, all right. I guess that's us done. I guess that's us done. Um
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators. Yes, please
Speak pipe.com slash pipe speakers. Oh, I forget that one this week. I will put on the patreon
A bonus episode don't know if we'll have maybe we'll have the ova bonus content stuff up there
But we I'll definitely have uh ellias are put together a bonus episode
For us and I will have that up. It's a behind the scenes
Chat episode if you just want to hear us talk about stuff that we decided not to put in the main episode
um, some goss about people we know or some um creators we don't like or something like that
um
That's it. Yeah patreon leave a voicemail down in the description
Instructions, uh, I guess that's it
Yep, thank you for listening. Uh, how long was this episode?
Three three and a half decent
Respectable about the length of an optimal twitch stream. Perhaps. All right. Uh, see you next week. Goodbye, and it's
Thank you