Hello, welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm Ben Saint. We got Gibbontake with us as well.
Hello everybody. Hello, and our guests this week. We have another guest. Audience, commenters,
I don't care how much you hate our guests. We're going to keep doing it. Guest this week is...
I care. Listen, if you hate me, email this podcast about it, not me.
If you hate... That goes for forever. Please put that on all of your future work. Just like,
if you don't like this, just send an email to theprocrastinatorsmail.com. Anyway, this is a
Jim Storm dancer. Hi. Hello. Who I was shocked to find is your real name.
Yes. I thought it was just a Twitter handle. And then I thought, oh, maybe there's an Elizabeth
Warren thing going on, like a one-thousandth Cherokee. It was like a Native American name or
something. No, no. So when my wife and I got married, we decided we neither of us wanted to
be named after the other one's dad. Yeah. So we picked a new name, and it's really more than
anything, it's a riff on Luke Skywalker. Right. Which is itself probably appropriating Native
American style names. Probably. Yeah, one imagines. But yes, anyway, Jim Storm dancer is the creator
of Frog Fractions, among other games, including but not limited to Frog Fractions 2,
and Frog Fractions Game of the Decade edition. And I think we have on our channel a very long
Let's Play videos, Rowdyfuckers, cop killers episode, I don't know, six or whatever. For me
and Munchie, we played Frog Fractions 2. I think it was like a five-hour video or something.
Wow, you marathoned it. We did marathon it. And you know, I'm sorry to say I never actually
finished it. I was gonna because me and him never got around to doing the rest of it.
But yeah, I played I played Frog Fractions 1 back when it came out in 2012, I think,
something like that. Yeah, it was October 2012. October 2012. Right. Yeah, I played that when it
came out. You know, I saw the, you know, I don't even remember where I saw some people vague posting
about it, maybe it was on 4chan or something awful or something. Just like, have you seen this game?
I'm not going to say what it is. You should play this game. I was like, OK, I guess I will. And
I won't, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't know. If anyone hasn't played it, I recommend it.
Check it out. It's free on twinbeer.com. Right. But if you don't, if it's like three months from
now, you won't be able to play it because Flash is going away. Yeah, I went this morning, I like
booted it up to take another look and I got the notice that's like Flash won't be supported
past December 2020. I was like, oh my, oh my God. Oh no, this fucking game. But it's OK. I made it all
better because I did a remake in On Steam and it's actually it's high res, so you don't have to
stare at a 640 by 480 postage stamp to play the game.
When I, when I saw, like I heard about Game of the Decade Edition and I, I just,
I don't know how much, I don't know. Do you want to, should I skip past talking about it? Should I
not say anything about it? Is it secrets? Oh, you're asking me if I put secrets in my own game?
Is that what's happening here? No, no, no. I played the Steam version. It's just the
same. It's just for fractions again, but on, you know, preserved. Yes, yes, that's correct. It's,
it was preserved as, as closely as possible to the original. However, there is DLC.
I was going to say, oh, oh, OK, because I read your article on your blog. Yeah. And I was reading
that and I was like, wait a minute. I don't know who these characters are. Yeah. This is not the
same game. Listen, if you, you wear a hat with the DLC, OK. You pay, you pay 10 bucks and you get
this hat and your frog looks dapper as heck. Nice. While you're eating bugs. And that's,
that's definitely all it is. I see. Yeah. I mean, 10 dollars well spent. Since, since the original
was free and all. Right. OK. Yeah, I was, I was, you know, I think when you, when you posted this
article, I went and I, and I looked at it and I was like, oh, there's, there's, there's more. Oh,
no. Oh, no. And I, I'm going to get around to playing it. I haven't gotten around to it yet,
but it's on my, it's on my to-do list. I think, I think you'll find it a lot more approachable
than Frog Fractions 2 was. OK. Like you were talking about how you spent five hours on that
thing and didn't finish it. Like I had intended it to be finishable in like two or three hours.
It turns out, turns out it was a lot harder than that for most people.
There were, I mean, Frog Fractions 1 is not that long and yet, well, I, I had a lot of trouble
with it actually. Sure. There was, I remember at the beginning, it took me forever. Spoilers
for Frog Fractions 1. Don't, don't listen to this. You haven't played it, but it took me forever to
realize that I could go under the water. Sure. And then, and then, so I spent like, oh, because
people assured me like, no, no, no, give this game a chance. Give this, I'm like, OK, I guess I'm
giving it a chance. I, I feel like I spent an hour just like turning the cyber brain on and off, or
is that what it's called? The one that changes you. The lock on. The lock on. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just like, and like, you know, just doing that over and it's like, what, where is this going? What's
and then I also got stuck on the text adventure portion. I had to, I don't remember what it was.
I don't remember what part it was, but I had to look up a hint at some point.
Yeah, no shame. Nobody knows how to, like when I made that game, I basically originally made it for
my audience of, you know, I had a couple dozen friends who I thought would enjoy it and that was
it. Yeah. And I had no idea that I would be inflicting text adventures on the world at large.
Um, yeah, I mean, so it goes, I guess. That's you never know. You never know what's going to be
the thing that blows up. But then I did that on purpose with like ZZT style dungeon crawls in
the second game. So yeah, I had never. Is ZZT a worthwhile game? I didn't know about it. The only
way that I know about it is that the main frog fractions game is like a reference to it. And
I thought that part of frog fraction was really cool in and of itself. Yeah. If you did like it,
then you might. So ZZT is actually really interesting. It's a game by Tim Sweeney,
who went on to make the Unreal Engine. And like Unreal, like the game Unreal, it is a game that
like was shipped and sold as a video game. But by far the most interesting part of it was the
level editor. So it was a lot of people's first foray into game design. And so it was extremely
through the level editor. Yes, it was extremely influential in that regard. It was like early
90, like 1991 or something. Yeah. PC users found this game and made their own worlds with it.
And it's real hard to go back to now. Like just the it's not super playable. Like believe it or
not, like despite all the the bullshit I pulled in in text world, it's a lot more the feel of it
is a lot better than the original ZZT was. Yeah, like you kind of you do do some like graphics
stuff. It's not all like, I mean, I play I play some ASCII games, like I play a dungeon
Crawlstone soup, you familiar? Yeah. Yeah. Although I play with a tile set. Oh, sure. Yeah. Because
I'm weak, though. So I mean, you know, the the a bit of a esoteric interface doesn't really
doesn't really bother me too much. Well, the thing is, so what I'm talking about specifically is
ZZT is an action game, but it uses like the default OS key repeat for movement. So
you key repeat, meaning so, you know, when you hold down a letter on the keyboard,
one letter appears in the text box, and then like a second later, a bunch of letters start
appearing in the text box of the same one. Yeah, sure. Okay, that's what I mean by key repeat. So
in ZZT, if you want to move left, you hope you can push left once to move one step left,
or you can there's a second, or you can hold it down, and it'll go left once, and then it'll
wait a second, and it'll start going left in a bunch of times. Yeah, and it's really does not,
it doesn't feel good to to operate like and I actually did a frog fractions too is the same
though, right? It is, but it's tuned way differently. I see. You did it deliberately.
Yeah, yeah. Instead of just inheriting it, I suppose. Right, yeah, right.
Gib, you haven't played frog fractions too. I know I did what you play for those five hours.
That's right. I think a fun part of I think was it the first frog fractions you did like
another video where I think we did where where you played the game but like in the course of the
video, you sort of got derailed and started Google image searching things and looking at
Wikipedia's and it the video itself sort of became a reflection of what frog fractions is as a game,
which is that's beautiful, right? Because the video it's the video itself, right, right. I
remember. Yeah, there was sort of like a meta joke to that when we're like the video pretends to be
a video where we play frog fractions, but instead it is about, you know, entirely separate things.
That's right. I had like forgotten, but that was a thing at the time. Yeah, you know, I wanted to
I wanted to be, you know, wanted to be like Jim. Yeah, oh man. So I'm looking forward to
looking forward to checking the DLC out. That's great. My little brother is is also game developer.
He's he's just finished uni and he's he's working with people doing game jams and stuff. Nice. And
he made I was very surprised at this. He had a game called road toads, which was like a little
3D game where it had toads on cars driving around in another rfck video we did a road road toads
yeah through I and the the idea is you're just driving around as a toad and it's you know,
it's a fun little game, but he had visions of it being like, you know, you there's a revelation
and you find out that there's more to it and all this stuff. And I said, oh, that's reminds me
of frog fractions. And he was like, what the hell's that? And he was so disappointed to find that
someone is also done. Someone has already made a frog game with a drug game with a twist. And he
was like, oh, this is a genre. Next, you told him about frog detective haunted island.
I don't know about that. Oh, you should definitely check out the frog detective series.
Oh, it's a whole series. There's only two of them. But technically, that's a series.
Is it like, um, oh, I'm looking at it. Is it like a point and click? It's like a point and click
if a point and click were first person like a first person shooter style movement.
But it plays like a point and click adventure.
Makes sense. Makes sense. This looks cool. And I think they did that just so they wouldn't have
to animate the main character running around. Yeah. Yeah. I had a similar story from
back when I was making frog fractions. There was another Bay Area game developer
making a game called Total Toads. A lot of frog and we heard about yeah. And we heard about each
other. And I I just assumed, okay, he's making like an educational game. But he thought that I
was making an educational game as well. And was like, oh, there's a rival frog educational game
developer. And it turns out like you can't get his game anymore. It shipped on iPhone and it
doesn't work on modern iPhones. But it was a game about adding and subtracting with frog with toads
rather. Total Toads. Total Toads. So it's got the alliteration to it. Yeah. It's
pretty good. It's like, no, stop honing in on my market. Yeah. Have you have you seen them?
Do you know the catamites? Oh, yeah. Have you seen his his frog blog? I have not seen that.
He I don't know if he still does it. But he had a little blog page where he would he would rate
games solely based on like the appearances of frogs within them and stuff. So he would like,
I don't remember. But like, you know, he was like, yeah, cave stories got some some pretty
good frog enemies. You know, they don't do very they're not in very much the game. But you know,
they're good for what they are, you know, seven out of 10. Right. Oh, you know, in, you know,
whatever. Yeah, yeah, he'll just rate really rated the frogs, basically. Now I'm curious. Now I want
to find out what the catamites had to say about the frogs and frog fractions. I don't know. I,
you know, I feel like I should know whether or not frog fractions made the cut for that list. But
I but I don't well off the top. If the blog is is continuing into the future, and maybe it will,
it will in the unknowable future. I think it's probably still on Harmony Zone
somewhere on that fucking Technicolor nightmare. Angel fire. Yeah, yeah. The web ring or whatever.
Right. So how is you, both of you? How is your Halloween? How is how's how's life? Who's going
first? Well, I guess I can go first. Yeah, go for it. My Halloween was uneventful. And that's
that's exactly how I enjoy it. Usually, you know, obviously put up decorations, people come around
the door, trick or treat with COVID. Nobody did that. And we didn't put up decorations to encourage
it. Instead, I carved some pumpkins with goofy faces. And usually they're out in the front.
And then they get like, by the next morning, they're all like brought in. So we just throw them
away. But this time they were inside. And so I decided to burn them. I said to light a fire
inside the pumpkin. And that was what I did with my evening. So I just because it's a it's a vegetable,
it's got a lot of moisture in it. You just threw like wood in there. I put I put logs and kindling
newspaper and I lit them in the fireplace. And it was it was it was very scary at some points.
Because you don't need them after after tomorrow or after the day. And yeah, but the the effect was
really quite striking because it's like, it's a guy's face and it's fires coming out of it and
is getting singed to the sides. It's cool. I was gonna say I've been listening to a YouTube series
called Goose Drunks, where this girl Bailey Myers just reads Goosebumps books. But she
she takes a drink. She has some rules, like whenever stupid things happen or spooky things happen.
That just reminded me of that series that I've been getting into lately, in which I recommend,
because there's one Goosebumps book where some kids have jack-o-lantern pumpkin heads.
That's that's it. That's the only connection. Okay. What were you saying? I say interrupted
for that. Oh, I was I was going to say that if you had filmed it, then it would make it great.
One of those videos where you know how you can find on Netflix, there's like a video that's just
a video of like an hour of a fireplace. Yes, an hour of like a pumpkin face slowly melting
would be fantastic. It'd probably be like 45 seconds of a pumpkin face disintegrating. Well,
on fire. Because yeah, like I was saying that it's a it's a vegetable and it was quite fresh. I
only cut it like the day or two before. There's a lot of moisture in there. So it actually the fire
was struggling to stay alive. So I was feeding that I was literally feeding it through the
mouth of the pumpkin fuel. That's pretty cute. I did film like few little 45 second chunks of it,
but I didn't set up anything because it was like in the living room. And parents were there watching
TV. It was sort of like we had to set up a camera. Right. So you couldn't make the theatrical
theatrical screaming noises either. No, do you do you? Did you save the seeds? Seeds? Oh,
yes. Well, yeah, I did. My brother was going to make a kind of a pumpkin pie. Yeah, something like
that. Yeah. You know, they're nice. You can you just you just put them up. You just bake them.
You just season them however you want. You bake them. You can make sweet cinnamon.
You can do like garlic and herb or just the seeds on their own. I mean, yeah, you should probably
salt them at least. What we did was we we actually boiled them in salt water to in order to salt them.
It's the best way apparently to get even salting. You know,
and then we baked them just to be clear. OK, OK, OK, OK, I was going to because like I was introduced
when I lived in the south, I was introduced to boiled peanuts. And I got to say they're gross
and I hate them. Yeah, I don't think I had I don't know if I had a peanut. They're so much worse
than just just cooking them like a normal human being. I don't I don't understand what you're
saying. Is that is that roasting? Is that is? Yeah, roast them. Yeah, roast them in the oven.
OK. Or or in whatever. Yeah, you roast them. That's roasted peanuts. Typically, I get them out of
the jar with the peanut guy with the top hat on it. Well, well, they because they roasted them,
right? Because they roast them because they know because they when you boil them, they turn into
like these soft. They taste like beans like it brings out. They're sort of like like like earthy
like beanie flavor. And it's I hate it. It's the texture like it's like a like a one of a chickpea.
It's very similar to interesting soft. Yeah, OK, all right. Time for a visual metaphor.
If Mr. Peanut was was boiled instead of roasted, what would he be wearing?
Well, he'd be big, swollen, soggy.
He would look like he has. He'd look like he was like covered in like eczema.
But like he already has some sort of skin skin condition.
He'd be all puffed up and darker in color and seeping just seeping.
I don't know. It's not for you. Anyway, I feel feel very strongly
about boiled peanuts and how you shouldn't do it. I know some people are big fans,
but I don't like those people and I don't trust them. Maybe you could make a homicide of it.
You said you said hummus, but I heard homicide. Maybe I could make a great homicide out of it.
That too. Makes you think. No.
It does, though, I promise. How was your Halloween, Jim?
You know, it was great. We we never get trick or treaters.
But this year we were like, well, we're we're going to now in covid times, it's time to go all out.
And we is it if we set up a table outside with a big tray painted to look like a Ouija board
and like Halloween colored Christmas lights and pumpkins all around it and a bunch of candy on
the tray and and hand sanitizer on the table. You put it out. You put it out for no one.
So pretty much pretty there was one group like that came by as we were going to bed
that were very excited and came by and yelled up. I don't know if they knew we were going to hear
them, but they yelled, thank you. Merry Christmas. And it was very sweet. And there was it sounded
like there were like four people in the group. So like four people took handfuls of candy. So
better than nothing. OK, yeah, it's not no one. And we also had we have our two year old Winston
who we wanted like we got to teach this kid how holidays work. So we did a very minimal
like just five houses or so. Trick or treat run he and he didn't want to we had gotten a costume
so he could dress up as Mario and he was like on the day of he was like, no, I don't want to wear
he doesn't speak that well. But he was like, no, I don't want to wear that.
Yeah. But he was willing to wear his pajamas that have bones printed on the front. So he could
look like a skeleton. Yeah, you know what? Yeah. But he just he just wears that all year round.
He does. OK, I mean, it's still fine. But but the neighbors don't know.
Yeah, yeah, it's not for him. Yeah, yeah. So we went we went to a couple of houses and like
surprisingly, we did our usual thing of like, well, is the porch light on or the house lights on
is their decorations of guessing like which houses are going to be participating. And like 50% of
people that we tried answered the door and gave us candy. So like people are still wanting to
participate in this thing. Sure. Of course. But yeah, this is not a high traffic trigger
treat neighborhood. So I think like my if like if next year he seems to be ready to step it up,
we have to figure out where are the kids actually going? Yeah, you might just like make a little
evening trip out to some like more tightly packed neighborhood, I guess. Yeah, dual circuit. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. My house growing up. I yeah, I was on kind of like a country road, like not exactly in
like the complete boonies or whatever, but like, you know, in like a pretty, pretty loosely packed
like sort of suburban country town. And so we would on like a good year, we would get one
trick or treat. Yeah. Yeah. But now, I mean, now I live on a more on a more dense street.
And so we probably would have but I don't think I don't think anyone came to our door yesterday,
or maybe I just wasn't paying attention. Well, you know, I was going to have some,
I was going to have some friends over, Kazi and Munchie, give you know him, Jim, you don't know
him, we're going to be over. But then we're just going to hang out in my backyard, because like
that's what we've been doing. You know, social distancing guests don't come in the house,
we hang on my backyard. And it snowed, it snowed yesterday, and there was still snow on the ground.
And so I said, oh, and crack and shell, it wasn't just a bunch of people, whatever.
Anyway, it snowed at the wrong time. I didn't want to like squat in the snow in my backyard.
So I said, no, Halloween's canceled, everyone, go home. So I didn't do anything. I was grumpy all
day about it. But you know what, dumb holiday, dumb holiday anyway, who needs it? Right? Am I
right? Yeah, hell yeah. It's the sweetest holiday. Oh, Winston. Oh, sorry, gone. I was going to say
the other thing, the other thing that ruined my Halloween was because it snowed. I finally had
to take my air conditioner out of my window. And I had to take it out of my window and move it over
my bed to get it into my closet to store because I have like a low, well, the snow, I don't know
if you know where this is going, but the snow had gotten into the air conditioner and the whole
thing was wet. And as I was moving it over my bed, all the snow water, like poured out of it
and like soaked my bed. So what I had to do last night, I had to, I took like saran wrap,
I had to like spread saran wrap over this big wet area in my bed and put a blanket over it
and sleep on top of that. It felt dry. Yeah, some people feel extra for that kind of bed.
And you know what? I woke up in the morning and I checked and it was dry again. So
problem solved. I just hope it didn't have any like weird like black mold or fungus in it,
you know, that's like a living in my mattress now. Oh dear. Winston, when we were out walking this
morning, he wanted to get more candy. He walked up, he started walking up a neighbor's driveway
saying get candy. Yeah, yeah. I have to explain like, sorry, this is just yesterday, buddy. Oh,
okay. He thought this isn't, oh, so this is what all, this is what all those other houses are for.
Right. You can get candy from them if you ask. I see. Smart, smart, smart kid. He's a pattern
matcher. I see. I see my new angle. So this is, now I didn't tell you this. I'm springing this on
you, but it's nevertheless true that you're not merely our guest this episode. You are actually
interviewing right now to be the new replacement member since all of our other members have
abandoned us. So how do you feel you're doing? I think I'm doing great. You think you're killing
it? Well, we'll see about that. Listen, I'm here to interview you. Okay. Oh, I didn't prepare
anything. I do want to say, I didn't, this is technically a crossover with your podcast
Topic Lords, which I didn't know you had. Yeah, I guess technically it is. Yeah, I didn't know
about it until very recently as I was looking up stuff related to you in the week leading up to
having you on. And I was like, oh, he's got a podcast too. I wonder if he knows the pain.
Surely he must also know the pain of having all of his other podcast members turn on him
and abandon them to their fate. That's just part of the experience.
Yeah, so Topic Lords is a weekly podcast, TopicLords.com. The only place on the internet,
you can hear us to discuss topics. It's me and two guests. Every week, it's two different guests.
And the guests bring topics to discuss. And it's very freeform. One of the listeners described it
to me as a place for people with ADHD to gush about their fixations. Oh, there's a market for
that seems pretty accurate. But so, yes, I, the last last episode I recorded was pushed back
twice because both of the guests forgot they were recording. Sure. Oh, like, oh my god.
Like they started the episode and just there was no. Oh, no, I mean, like I was I was messaging them
on, however, I know them on Discord or whatever. And they were just like, oh, I forgot about it.
Can we do this later? Oh, sure. And then they both answered that way. And I was like, luck,
you're in luck. The other guests also forgot. Yeah, lucky you. You're not, you're not the odd man out.
Right. Technically, you're the weird one because you remembered. Well, my wife had to remind me.
Oh, okay, few. Good, good. I am very diligent. And I never forget an episode. And I'm here,
and I'm here rain or shine, because I care, viewers, because I give a shit. And you're all welcome.
Oh, yes. Yes.
Well, that's all my notes. I don't know. Show's over.
I don't know how. Yeah, go on. Yeah. Mr. Frog, Mr. Fraction.
Storm dancer. Storm dancer. Yeah, please. Storm dancer. Fraction was my dad's name.
I'm only a fraction, fraction. Okay, all right. Game development is a cool thing.
I've wanted to, oh, really? Yeah, it's cool when it works. It's cool when it works out.
Making the game is great. It's all the parts where you try to get other people to pay to play
the game. That part sucks. Oh, yeah. Oh, that's that's always been like with any art thing. It's
like, I love what I'm doing. And then you've got to eat and you've got to make the money so you
can eat. And it's like that goes in that flies in the face of art in itself sucks. Marketing is
you have to like spec some of your talent points into like being a soul sucking vampire in order
to actually make money. It's been a problem. Yeah, because I noticed business that like
for fractions one obviously was free and it was big. And then for fractions two is like
the whole idea of making a sequel to something with brand recognition is so that you don't have
to do as much work to get it seen and bought. Yeah. And you did the cool thing, which was to make it
like not put your name on it, not call it frog fractions, release it secretly with an ARG.
And it's all like really interesting and cool and unique, but not good for capitalizing on,
you know, on the things that you're supposed to do in this world.
And I was trying to do, I mean, so obviously the reason I did that was that I hate the marketing
side of things. And this was effectively like, I'm promising I'm never going to do any marketing
on this game, which is itself like it's audacious enough that people are going to talk about it.
So it becomes itself a form of marketing. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So that worked. But
I don't know. It was frog fractions two at this point, like a success in terms of being able
to get away with being so audacious, like non marketing marketing. Yeah. So it's technically
profitable. But we didn't pay the best kind of profitable. Yeah. We didn't pay people very well.
So like that's not a very high bar. I definitely would have made more money if I called it frog
fractions two. Right. Yeah. Because then people would knowing where to get it is like a pretty good
is like, that's like the first hurdle you got to clear. Yeah. But that's pretty high for frog
fractions to that right. But I also definitely would have made more money if the main minigame had
art. Like I did ZZT style stuff because I'm nostalgic for that art style. And because
it was a style that I could do without paying a bunch of money out of an art budget, which I didn't
have basically. I mean, I do like the way it looks. It's very I do too. But it's very spiky.
Like a lot of people don't like a lot of people are really turned off by that. And if I had made
that look like, you know, Zelda one, for example, I think a lot more people would have been into
that. Yeah, Zelda one or like Minecraft, something that that can. Yeah. Minecraft is amazing and how
it can get away with such, you know, low, low resolution textures and low poly things because
I don't know. It's just the game. It's so fun. Yep.
So it's always a challenge because I'm like, I make comics, but I'm not that good at drawing yet.
So I'm trying to figure out how I can make comics without really being good.
Give us hard on yourself. Give us hard on yourself about the drawing thing. But you've
improved. I mean, we've said this before. I don't want to, not to go on a side, but I really do
want to tell you again, how much you've improved and like your last couple of things like Clarissa
looks Clarissa looks like much better than Lord of Ghost, which looks much better than
Bail Jade, you know, for instance, just I can't let that go unsaid.
Have baited. I baited you into complimenting me again, you fool. Yeah, this is the one.
Yeah. It was just saying like
the with the comics, I'm not terrible, but like, I have improved. Thank you, Ben.
You're welcome.
But it's it's always been a thing where like, I'm trying to think of ways that I can
make it engaging and marketable and good and people would want to see it regardless of how
much it looks like the best thing ever, you know, you play to my strengths,
play to the things that work, because like people make snap judgments when they see something.
And if it doesn't look the greatest, you may as well make it look the most unique or, you know,
there's there's all these different things you can do to make it striking and I don't know.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So I've put a lot of thought into this sort of thing because
I'm a largely a solo developer with without an art background. My skill sets are
programming and music and writing, basically. And so I've put a bunch of
like research and thought into like, how do people do programmer art that looks good,
that is appealing to people and like the most basic form of it is something like
geometry wars, which is just geometric shapes with a nice bloom filter applied, basically.
Yeah. And I think like something along those lines might be your solution like you like you could
like you could use Blender to pose 3D mannequins or something like that.
Yeah. I thought of things like that, like like a multimedia sort of thing. I mean,
Bailhape, my first comic was like MS Paint crap, but I made up for that by having
a lot of Homestuck inspired aspects like like flashes. There's a 3D video game that me and
my brother worked on that is one of the pages of the comic. And there's a lot of gifs that sort of,
you know, pages that are gifs rather than just still images that make up for how shoddy the artwork
is. Right, right. You make it be a multimedia kind of a thing where like, suddenly this comic,
it's like something that couldn't exist in a book. And so it's taking advantage of being digital.
Yeah, I would, I think I've said before that I would think it was, I would find it really cool
to be because I do art myself. I'm a draw guy. I would love to be, I don't know, I would love to
find like some like little studio or something that needs like a dedicated artist and be like a
background artist or like a character artist or something. I'm not really an animator, so I don't
I guess I'm limited in that. But I would, that'd be really cool to just be the art guy for some
game that ends up being like an indie hit or something. That would be, that would be the
dream right there. But I've looked, I've looked on, I've looked around a little bit on websites that
are like, unlike job hunting websites, and I've found like studios in my area that are hiring,
and then, but they, none of them were looking for, the closest thing I could find was like
UI designers and like UI designers from mobile games. It's just not, it's just not that interesting.
I don't know, it doesn't sound like it is. So yeah, I mean, are you like looking at classified ads
and that sort of thing? I mean, this was a while ago, but I just went on, I don't know, I looked
on some website or something that like, like looked for studios, look for studios and like,
because I live in the Boston area, I look for like studios around Boston. And I think I just
like went to each of their websites to see, because sometimes they have like a weird hiring page.
Yeah, if you want to do indie games, and indie developers, I can't, I've never heard of one
putting out a job ad. Yeah, they almost ubiquitously hire people they've met already.
And yeah, they met, they meet people doing game jams, for the most like, if you, if you want to
start getting gigs, making video games, I think like that's actually your path forward is to
start doing jams and the people you work with, if they like your work, then they'll want to work with
you again. Oh my God, I would have to, I would have to assemble a team. I would have to assemble
like a jam team. And I could be the art guy. Oh, well, you have pro programming guy.
You could do it that way. I mean, or you could, I guess you can't do the thing that I always did,
which was assemble a team on site, because they don't have on site game jams anymore.
Yeah, but like, I presume like you go to Ludum Dare forums and they will be there will be people
like looking for group or whatever. I mean, hell, how big is the audience of this podcast? You could
send out a message there saying I want to I want to form a team for the next Ludum Dare or whatever
jam and send me an email. We've got you know what, I know there's a number of people in our audience
who are like artist types of various descriptions. You know, I hate our audience. Oh yes. But you
know, they can they can be harness their their work can be siphoned.
They can extract their surplus value. Hmm, that interesting idea. You know what, I would do it.
I would do a game jam. I guess I never thought of it because I'm not like a games guy specifically.
But I could do you know, these, you know, idiots are always looking for like, oh, I can do all
this other stuff, but I can't do the art. Oh, I don't know how to draw. Oh, the art is hard.
You know, for whatever reason.
You know, what's easy programming?
Yeah, I looked at it. I looked at it. Programming is also easy. There's a lot of text. I can't read
it very good. I need a visual indicator. This is like a like a weird thing that I've noticed
over the years. That is just I when it when it comes to a video game, at least, I love being
able to move in a 3D space, because oh, yeah, feels good. You press you press your button,
and then you instantly feel movement through an area because all of the pixels on screen
change at once. And I don't know, something about a 3D environment where you're moving around
and everything is updating constantly, you get an instant feedback. In the text
adventure part of Frog Fractions, I always like my brain breaks, like because you look around
in the spaceship, and you think, okay, here's the things I can examine. I examine each one of
them. And then the text has gone off screen. And because it's gone, I can't remember what it was.
So I have to do it again. And I just can't keep it in my head. Need that visual stimulus.
Well, you know what you can do, you can lean on the return key, and then every every pixel on
the screen just keeps moving. I just keep just in one direction. Right. That's what I'm looking
for in a game is the pixels move. I just need like a white noise like static image and like,
that's what I like. I have to say that moving through a 3D space is one of my, if not the
biggest pleasure I get out of games. Like just the being in a world and interacting with the
world in an interesting physical way. Like, I have been super stressed this year from shipping
a game and raising a kid and COVID basically. And so I haven't really had the mental energy to
pick up any new games. But I replayed the entire Tony Hawk series and the entire 3D Mario series.
Because those are both like, and those are both games that I love in part because they are about
navigating a 3D space in an interesting way. Yeah, it's just sometimes I just want to be in a
place. I've been playing a lot of World of Warcraft lately. And I've said before on this podcast
that the Warcraft sucks. The world is where it's at. And it's just so nice being in certain
locations and just being like, yeah, I'm turning the camera around. I'm here. This character is me,
and I'm just sitting down at this table in this pub in this weird dwarven district of a city. It's
cool. That was also my favorite part of World of Warcraft. Yeah. I got into it for a little bit.
And then I got turned off when I realized that, oh, I hit the end game. Now it's time to raid.
Now it's time to join a guild and start putting together raid teams and like, oh, I got it.
You mean I'm not done? You mean I have to come back and do it again? And like,
I couldn't. I just didn't have the wherewithal.
Yeah, I had a similar reaction where I hit level 60 and I was like, where do I go from here?
And thank God because I think I lost my job because of that game. And so like the fact that it was
like I didn't even kick the addiction. It just the game ejected me basically.
I only played it for one summer because like my friends at college were like, oh,
we're all going to play. This was when the Lich King came out. They were like, oh,
you never played Warcraft? Oh, bro. Lich King's coming out this summer. We're all going to play it.
We're all going to be online. We're all going to be a guild. I was like, yeah, sure. Okay. I guess.
And I did. And then summer ended and I was like, yeah, it's fine. I did it. I don't need any more.
I did dabble a little bit in game making. I made a very simple sort of turn-based RPG kind of game
in a Game Maker Pro, I think, like in GML, which was also a tie-in as part of like my
a webcomic that I was working on. And then I made, I think I would be remiss.
We got to talk about Endless War. I want to tell Jim a little bit about Endless War.
Can we do that? Yeah, of course. It was two years ago. I started working on this thing.
And now there's like a whole team. There's like a whole volunteer team that has taken it off my
hands and they're the ones developing it now. But what it is, it's called Endless War. And it is
a Discord bot that runs in this Discord server, which turns the server into basically an MUD,
like a text-based RPG kind of thing, wherein you live in this city called Slime City,
New Los Angeles City, aka Neo Milwaukee. And you got a mine for Slime, and you join a gang,
and then you engage in an endless cycle of gang warfare. You choose a team. You're a killer or
a rowdy, and you kill each other. And whoever's got the most slime is the most power. Watch out
for Slime Corp. They're ruthless capitalist dogs that'll kill you for a nickel. I don't know.
That was ballooned over time. At first, it was just like you do a command and you kill.
That's the basic skeleton. But every month of the day, you just go in the mines,
you just mine for slime. Well, you can fish for it too. You can also farm it. You can grow up.
Yeah, all right. Mines are the OG. Mines are the coolest.
I don't even know what the game is doing anymore. Me and my friend Crack,
honestly, mostly him, because he was more of a developer than me. We made it two years ago,
and now people that I barely know make it. And every month, I'll see an update that's like,
oh, yeah, we added new... Now you can sell your soul to another player and put it in a jar,
and they can keep the jar in their fridge. You can own a real estate. Oh, yeah, we added new
crops. There's new crops that you can mill for new dyes and stuff. Oh, we added a new mini-boss
or... I don't even know what this means. This is all in this text-based thing.
So this is what you do. Here's how you do the handle this. You wait till you're on your death bed
to maximize your anticipation and to maximize the number of weird features that these developers
have added. Then you play the game right before you're about to die, and you have the most amazing,
like, I made this awesome indie game, and now look at... 50 years ago, I made this bot,
and now it's moved platform six times. Now it's in VR, and I'm growing crops, and I'm hunting
beasts and stuff. Yeah, this is what I expected it would become one day. A 4x platformer.
Yeah, it's so advanced that it actually turns you immortal, and then you don't be on your death bed
anymore. Oh, no. That was it. That was the plan all along, to transcend the physical form.
And then you become one with the slime in the cloud. The slime cloud.
Which is definitely not the same as dying.
No, no, no, no. You convert your consciousness directly into slime-based cryptocurrency,
and then trade it on the stock market. That's what I wanted, my tombstone.
You feel like, oh, shit. KFC stock is rising. My consciousness is expanding. My third eyes
of... In the game, there's a stock market, by the way. You competing stock like Taco Bell,
KFC, and Pizza Hut are all... But you didn't put KFC in the game. The simulants invented it.
KFC was in the game, but I did not add the stock market portion. You used to just buy food from
KFC, believe it or not, but now it's a living dock. Now there's multiple restaurants and multiple
districts. The slime is... No, they want the slime. You pay them in slime, and they're like,
okay. You go to the mines, you mine for slime until you're too tired, and then you go to KFC,
you give them your slime, they give you some plutonium chicken. You eat it. You restore your
stamina, and then you go back to the mine, and then you just do it all over again. That's capitalism,
baby. It's a metaphor. It's, you know, in real life, that's horrifying, in a video game that
sounds delightful. It is. Exactly, exactly. Fortunately, you can't do... There's no more
Kavens now. We took Kavens out, so... Oh, you did? I think so. Maybe not. Maybe they're back in. Who
fucking knows? Remember what we said? What about Kaven mimics? You think it's a Kaven,
but it turns out to be a treasure chest. You trigger Kavens on purpose, but sometimes...
Before you notice that it's actually a treasure, you miss out on the treasure if you run away.
Right. I guess that's a reverse mimic. Devs, I hope you're listening. Devs, you better listen to this
and implement all of this right now. Put it on the to list. Yeah, you're still the project leader,
right? I mean, I can't make them do anything. Yeah, because it was like... I would hope that
my suggestions would carry at least a little weight. Right. It was a free thing. There was no
pay structure. I guess it's always been whoever's the coolest with the coolest ideas gets to decide
what happens. It's open source, and that's why... Oh, yeah. You just stole it, right? Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I copied it for my own copy of the thing for an adult version. Yeah, you could say.
You could say. Disgusting. Absolutely. Absolutely despicable. I'm glad to say. When I'm on my deathbed,
reading the patch notes for version 7.33.49.01 of Endless War, seeing all the new vegetables that
they've added, I'm glad that I'll be able to look back and say, hey, me, Endless War guy,
and Jim Stormdancer, Frog Fractions guy. Yeah, we rapped a little bit. We rapped a bit about video
games. That was the thing that happened. Definitely happened. Yeah, and here's the proof.
Are you working on anything right now? I know that's probably a pretty cliche question,
but I'm genuinely curious. What's the next video game? Can I have another video game,
Sarah, please? So I just patched achievements and a bunch of new secrets into the Hat DLC.
That was a few weeks ago. Right, right. And at this point, I can't... So it's complicated.
The game is not selling well enough that I can justify just launching into a new product.
You mean the Game of the Decade? Yeah, the Hat DLC. The Hat DLC is what I mean. It's not a game,
it's just a hat. Yeah, just a hat. There's nothing other than the hat. Yeah, yeah. Right. It's a very
nice hat. It's not selling well enough that I can justify just like, yeah, now is when I make my next
game. So I have to figure out what is next for me. In the meantime, I am doing contract stuff.
I was going to say, you do like real jobs, at least some of the time.
Yeah. Well, I mean, it's been ever since Frog Fractions, I've only done like...
And this is really neat. It's only been interesting work. It's mostly been game dev stuff,
but yes, I do contract work in addition to making my own video games.
But I've been very privileged to like, largely be working on my own games for the past eight years.
I don't know. I mean, stop me if you can't answer anything specific or anything. But like,
is it, do you do studios? Do you work for studios or is it mostly like other indie devs that like
contract you to work on projects? So I, it's always been indies. The biggest
studio that I worked for was Human Nature Studios, which was at the time making Toja
Mineral. And I was working on, they wanted to crowdfund a sequel to Star Flight. And so I was...
Star Flight, okay. Which is, if you've heard of Star Control 2...
I've heard of it, yeah. Yeah. Star Control 2 was the game that was like a spiritual sequel to Star
Flight. But so it's a game about flying around and getting in dogfights and talking to aliens
and exploring alien planets. It's a very like, try to do everything, space exploration game.
Like Star Citizen, except made in 1984 or whatever it was, in 86 maybe.
And I was working on, I wasn't working on the sequel, I was working on the prototype of the
sequel that they could film, they could screen capture to use in the trailer. So I was still...
Okay. I was still doing like game design work. I was still doing like interface design work.
But it was kind of amazing in that like, oh, if there's a bug that I...
If there's like a nasty bug that happens like, even as often as like half the time the players
run the game, yeah. It doesn't matter. Just use the footage where the bug didn't happen.
It's like, that's like so funny. It's must like, imagine like, you don't even have to worry about
bugs like as long as the game runs. Like you can make the ultimate game. Like you're freed from
this whole like vector of concern about like what's going to limit the kind of game you can make.
But alas, only for this in this context that like we'll never see a wide release because like
the game's broken. Right. Very, very strange. Is that like, is that like,
is that what, is that what Will Wright did with Spore? Do you know about, you know,
you know the trailer, the initial trailer for Spore that he did, the demo, you remember that?
I, yeah, I don't know what that was. It might have been, it might well have been a prototype in
the same, along the same vein. Like that was an incredibly ambitious project that they really,
they really cut scope on that by a huge amount in order to ship it.
It looked so different, the final game. And yeah, it was, I don't know, man, like some of the, some
of the stuff, some of this, like when he, I've complained about this before because no game
ever broke my heart, like Spore did. But like when he gets to the planet stage and he's like
finely tuning the planet's atmosphere, like, oh, the various gases in the atmosphere and the
temperature. And then suddenly organically, like life starts blooming on the planet. He's like,
oh, yes, I've tariff, the delicate control. And then you get it, you get to the real game.
And it's like, you just drop a fucking bomb on the planet. And like, that's how you turn it into
a habitable planet. And you can like put stamps on it. And that's how you just like, oh my God,
Will, Will, you fucker. Yeah, they were doing some some sneaky shit with that.
Yeah, yeah. I mean, obviously, like they were trying to make the game that Will
Wright wanted to make. And they were just like, well, we're like four years into development.
And it's nowhere to close to anything playable. Like, is my guess is what happened. So like, okay,
let's let's bring in the guy who made civilization to do the the turn based strategy part of it,
you know. Yeah. And like, they turned it into, I guess, in the same sort of way as frog fractions,
they turned it into a series of mini games. Yeah. Yeah. And I mean, the the the different stages
were always going to play differently. But yeah, like the the final like the final stage like the
conquest of space was just so like, just so like, oh, you know, just do the same thing just like
move from planet to planet. Oh, and sometimes these like Borg things show up and you just got
to kill them and they're just like, okay, it does. Yeah. Sad. Yeah. Sad times. I'm still still
still hurting, still hurting over spore. I bet I bet you could get some of that same sense out of
like a dwarf fortress or something like a war fortress. I have played dwarf fortress not in
a while. I used to play it pretty often, actually. Not in not in recent years. I was a big fan. I was
a really big fan of just going like doing world gen and then just going into like,
world history and like reading. Yeah, even that's like, I think that's why I stopped playing it
was because I discovered that like, I kind of just like reading about the stuff more than like,
you know, all the rigmarole of like, okay, well, I have to mine up have to mine iron and then I
got to I got to refine it and just steal and I need I need pig iron and okay, I need the okay to
form it into like, okay, I got to make greaves, got to make helmets, got to outfit my military.
Okay, what kind of what color cloak did I need? I need purple helmets to dye their cloaks with
like, okay, I get that. You know, let me just read about read about the let me just read about
like the goblin who became emperor of the dwarven kingdom after like, she was created when the
universe began and then spent the first like 400 years of her life, like winning a hammer throwing
contest and wrestling matches, only to become dwarven. Like, let me just read her story.
Yeah, my relationship to the dwarf fortress is similar, except that what I read is people's
stories of playing dwarf fortress. Like, like, like, like, like, it would be in I mean this in
the old sense, like, like, let's play threads where people like, yes, exactly, type out type.
Yeah, type out what happened and screenshot and stuff. I've read some of those. What's the one?
What's the one with the skeleton elephants? You know that one? I don't know that one.
I feel like it's the one like most famous like dwarf fortress story. And it was like the
it was in an evil biome. And these the outside was plagued with skeleton elephants. And at one
point, a dwarf went outside on like an excursion and it's an elephant killed the dwarf. And this
dwarf was carrying like some very like, you have like a nice like artifact piece of armor or something
or like pants. And like, because of like the waiting algorithm, all the other dwarves immediately
knew that these like valuable artifact pants were, you know, ownerless. So they all rushed out like
into the wild like rushed for these like artifact pants. And they were all just massacred by these
skeleton elephants, they just kept like pouring out and just getting crushed. Yes, exactly what I
want to hear. And then like from then on, like whenever the dwarves carved like artifact chairs
and tables, they would carve like images of dwarves being crushed by elephants. It's just like
the worst thing that ever happened to them. It's like, where were you on the day of like elephant
gate or whatever? Right. Very good. That was that one's a riot. Yeah. It's skill. There's a skill
that you have to have. And if you play a good game of dwarf fortress, some funny shit happens.
But then, you know, to tell it in a compelling way to make it a funny story to read, you know,
there's a, oh, there's, um, there's a YouTuber called Krugsmash. Have you seen him? Not familiar
now. Krugsmash basically does that he he runs these fortresses and he makes videos sort of
sort of summarizing and explaining like how the fortress is going and like what happened.
Oh, there's a great and he does his own art too. Like he draws scenes from it and he'll show them
on screen like while he's describing them. He has a great series called monster killer. Monster
killer. I won't say, I'm not going to say what happens because it would be a spoiler, but the
fortress monster killer has a real arc to it. It has dramatic, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, what's the word?
Irony something I was going to say, like build up and pay off.
Okay. There is dramatic irony. Yes. It's got like elements are built up and then they pay off in
the end. Mwah. Mwah. That's a, that's a good one. Excellent. I played, um, not to go, not to go on
and on about dwarf fortress, but I will say I had one game that I played where, uh, a guy got killed,
like I think like a were lizard attack and the guy got killed and I had built these tombs
and a guy got killed out there and I saw this other dwarf kept running
from where his body was to the tombs, from where his body was to the tombs. And I was like,
what is this guy doing? And I looked at his relationship and it turns out that this dwarf
that was running was a friend of the guy who was killed outside. And what he was doing was he was
going, the guy had been like crushed by like a hammer to the head or something. And it had
shattered his head and sent his teeth flying. And this guy kept going out, finding one of his
teeth, bringing it into the, into the tomb and putting it in the coffin, going out, finding
another tooth, bringing it back and putting it in the coffin. Yeah. Yeah, I know, right? I hope
someone does that for me. And inevitable teeth related accident when I'm eventually bludgeoned
to death by a were lizard. Yeah, yeah. Well, I hope, I hope that my friends go out with a bucket
and like scoop up a bucket of my slime, bring it to my coffin, pour it in, go out, scoop up another
bucket, bring it out, pour it in. Oh boy. Well, I don't know, we've been going for an hour. Either
of you, I don't want to want to raise any objections, any grievances, or anything else you want to talk
about on this episode of the Procrastinators podcast. This has been real fun. It's been great
having you on. I was, I was, I was actually pretty taken aback when Jim Storm dancer himself
got back to me like, yeah, Cheryl, been your podcast. It's like, whoa, shit. Oh, shit. I didn't
think you'd say yes. What do we do? Everybody, everybody clean up, look presentable, look professional.
That's me. I'm always getting on podcasts. Do you do it often? Do you make appearances?
You know, I was expecting to get a bunch of podcast invitations after I shipped the CapDLC.
Nothing. You're the first. No shit. Holy shit. Wow. Well, fuck that. I know, right? Listen.
I mean, I guess I could have, I could have like sent out a press release or something like
Jim Storm dancers looking to be on a podcast. Yeah, maybe. But I mean, live and learn. Yeah.
Live and learn. Well, I mean, fuck that. I, I have been putting it off, but I am going to go
and get the DLC because I, I'm going to play it. I would encourage our audience to do it too.
Fucking, I just really want my, I really want my frogs to look nice and dapper and it just
sounds like cute and it would really enhance the experience of garden variety vanilla frog
fractions one for me. Yeah. In my opinion. Yes. All right, cool. Well, then let's just do,
do you want to, do you want to get it? You want to, you want to escape? You want to open up the
latch and let you, let you out? Yeah, I guess I should probably go see how my wife is doing.
Sure. Sure. You're a, you're a busy guy. You're a dad. Yep. Very man. Scary. Scary thoughts.
All right. Well, thanks again. A few moments later.
Ellie is all right. Cut all that out. That's fucking horseshit. Yeah. Cut all this. Cut all this.
If even one, if even one whisper, no, no, no, no. If even one whisper of this makes it into
the podcast, I will destroy you. And then, and then Ellie is our and cut the cut out what we said,
but then leave that part in where I say that if any of this makes into the podcast, I'll kill you
and then leave so that they know that they have to get the, the Patreon bonus episodes,
right? Give them a little, just let them know exactly what's at stake.
All right. Voicemails. Okay. Voicemails. You got them up? Oh, shit. I never,
I never remembered to do that. Speakpipe.com. It's already in the thing. All right. I'm here.
Wimp. Wimp. All right. Are we ready to go? Which one are we starting on?
We are an idea for a PCP fighter. Okay. Right on. Okay. Three, two, one, go.
Mugen is a free engine for 2D fighters. It has a big fan community and it's built around being
able to easily put your own characters and moves in. It might be a good place to start
for like a proof of concept for a PCP fighter. Yes. I mean, I've, I've done Mugen before.
I was, I was, I spent like, I don't know how long because I was an idiot kid who didn't really
understand what he was doing, trying to figure out how to get like an anime character. I think
it was like Zoro from One Piece. I wanted to get Zoro in the Mugen because I couldn't find him.
I tried to make him. I tried to make Sanji, I think actually. I got, I ripped some GBA Sanji
sprites from something and I was like working on the hitboxes and it was like, I managed to make
him kick and it connected and I was like, oh my God. But it was so powerful. Yeah. But I don't think
I ever really finished it because it was like, I don't want to do that for every single animation,
every single move. Yeah, fuck it. I'll just download Fat Albert.
You know, it's, I mean, it kind of sounds like fun. I was, I was fucking around with,
did I mention I was actually fucking around with some of the VTuber software? I mean,
I can see the appeal. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I can see the appeal of like, you know, oh, yeah,
take these sprites and then, yeah, I could see that it just being like a fun little thing to do.
When they talked about the PCP fighter idea, like, yeah, the first thing that jumped in my head
was like, oh, Mugen, that's kind of like, Mugen is a program that you can make like fighting games
and I have never used it. So I don't actually know how like, how involved it is or anything.
But I've seen like a, you ever watched Salty Bet? No, what's that?
Salty Bet is, it is a Twitch stream. I think it is, I think that's mainly what it is. It's a Twitch
stream that runs basically just a series of like algorithmically generated matchups of
Mugen characters from like a database. And I mean, you know that like some characters are just like,
Oh God, I saw a video recently, or maybe I read an article, I don't remember, but it was about
Mugen characters and how like, some of them can be designed to be invincible. But it's not like,
there are like tiers of invincibility. And like, the, the basic like, sure, yeah,
you can make a character that like has no hitbox, or like, you know,
has like an infinite hitbox that hits the whole screen for infinite damages in the blockable,
right? Like, yeah, sure, you can do that. And that's an invincible character. But there are like
coding tricks you can introduce into your game, into your character that make it like even more
invincible, like that like, will just like automatically win the match, or will like crash
the program or something like that. I yeah, I remember light Yagami has an animation redraws
in his death note. And if he finishes that animation, the other player just dies.
Yeah, but I'm, but I'm talking about, I'm talking, I'm talking about like characters
that are essentially viruses that like destroy your computer. Like that's how we crash the game.
Uh, I guess I don't actually understand, I really don't understand like the more technical ones.
But, but anyway, like, yeah, salty bed is basically matchups of sometimes it's
characters like these that are just like, a human could never possibly beat them.
But like, they get matched against each other and they're like, you don't even see what
know what's happening. And like, you can bet on it. I think there's like some kind of like
game currency that you can use to like place bets on like which of these two characters is
going to win. And I think it's just runs like constantly like 24 hours a day or a lot of the
time anyway. Yeah, salty bed if if you're ever like, it's good to like put on like a party or
something like if nobody knows what to watch, or like you need some background noise, you can
just put on salty bed and you can just be like, Oh, okay. You know, JoJo is fighting Garfield
and like Garfield is like, you know, good summoning like screen clearing like johns and odys that
are like pummeling, whatever, like, you know, you'll see some some cool shit like that. And that's
salty bed. All right. Yeah, make us a video game. Oh, I didn't tell Jim about the PCP dating
sim. I'm sure he would have been I'm sure he would have been blown away. Oh, well, next time.
Maybe next time. One of these days, we might have like, we could we could maybe try to orchestrate
like a super guest episode where we get tons of guests that we've had before. Like people who
would never interact normally. Like, like who? Well, like the people are old guests. Yeah, all of
them. Just fucking all of them at the same time. Oh, you can have like a mixer. It's like, Oh,
Jim Storm dancer meet aria de mezzo. Oh, cyber shell meet fit MC. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, sure.
Why not? So wait, I'm gonna Jim posted his audio. I'm going to give him not one but two thumbs up.
There you go. Excellent. Next voicemail is called. Yeah. Three, two, one, go.
No, no, November. No, no, November. No, no, November. No, no, November. No, no, November.
No, no, November. No, no, November. Yeah. Oh, it's it's not in its N and N for no, no, November.
We're starting. We're starting it boys. It begins.
That's what it appears. Everything would be destroyed. I'd be so mad if Nate came on the
podcast for any reason. Next one is called. Blaseball greater than greater than greater
than greater than greater than endless war. We'll see about that. Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys, I don't know if my last voicemail center not, but I'm just going to send another one
just in case. So like I haven't really watched the PCP in a few months, but that is irrelevant.
I'll catch up like eventually maybe probably, but there's this thing I found that's like really
fucking cool and also better than endless war. You might be like, what better than endless war?
That's impossible. Yeah, it's like similar, but better. It's called Blaseball. Imagine like
fantasy football, but it's baseball and also like hunger games and just fucking crazy shit happening
all the time. Dude, it's pretty awesome. Right now the game is on like a month long break,
but when it goes on, dude, it fucking goes on. It's so awesome and based and epic
Blaseball. This is, this is why like I have heard about Blaseball and I have,
I have keep meaning to look into it and I haven't. Same. It's, it's one of those things that's like,
oh, I feel like I've heard of this before, but I haven't. And it's a new thing that people are
going like, oh, cool. Yeah. But like, I don't, I don't, I don't really understand it out of
descriptions, like have not have failed to really clue me into like what it is. Oh, it's just good.
Man, it's just good. It's like crazy, crazy shit happens. Like,
is it a, I mean, people have, people have compared it to endless war. So I'm like,
is it a, is it an MUD? Is it an RPG? Is it text based? It's, let's Google it right now. But people
say that it's like fantasy football. And to be honest, I don't really even understand what fantasy
football is. Like the only, isn't the only thing you do in fantasy football, just like pick your
team and that's it. Right. Blaseball play now. I got to sign up. Fuck this. Yeah. That's what I got
to the homepage. I was like, I don't want to make an account. Fuck this. Wait. Blaseball is an online
browser baseball simulation horror game developed by the game band. Horror game.
Excuse me? Sploric magazine. Well, you collect, hang on. Here's polygon.com. I'm just going to
quickly, what is Blaseball? Blaseball is a fantasy baseball game. You can play online. You collect
coins by betting on games and use the coins at the end of each week to vote for decrees and
blessings that will change the game the next week. Okay. So like everybody, but it's like a
community thing, right? Like changing the way the game will play. And then they all watch,
I guess. I heard it compared Subway to like D&D in that like the game, the game masters are
basically like running like a campaign almost, but like it's sort of like behind like they're like,
they're doing something like they're reacting to the community in some way. And I don't really
know how because I don't understand how the game works. Yeah. I'm curious if this guy just said
it was better than Endless War because Endless War is a thing that the PCP has created.
And it's just a game and it's better than this game. Or if it's a similar type of game, that's
what I'm wondering. It sounds to me like it's similar in that it is largely like community
engagement driven. You know, it sounds like it sounds like, yeah, like in the same way that like,
I don't know, maybe there'll be a contest and someone will make an entry that's popular and
maybe a dev will decide to like, okay, introduce a, you know, a mechanic that is, you know, based on
that thing, which is a thing that's happened in Endless War, you know, maybe, I don't know. I
can't even speculate on what would happen in baseball without having any knowledge of the game.
But like, I don't know, maybe, oh, a team wins that no one expected to win. And the devs say,
oh, a ghost appears now. A ghost appears. Now there's a ghost, guys. There's a fucking ghost in
the baseball. Dude, that's just like Endless War. And the ghost becomes the coach.
It's exactly like it. Only better. People like saying, oh, I'm going to vote for the air strike
to destroy the training fields for this team so they can't practice. And it accidentally kills
all of the team. And now they're all ghosts. Oh, I didn't mean to do that. Oh, shit. Oh,
but this is good, actually. Oh, I'm glad that it happened, you say, to the machine in text format.
I should probably look more into baseball. I keep hearing people talking about baseball.
Probably shouldn't be a fucking idiot who doesn't understand anything.
No, that's fine. Being an idiot is good.
Yeah, you're right. Okay, next, next voicemail is called Timmy return and update,
parentheses, guy who all other voicemailers hate. Oh, it's a minute and a half. Fuck you, Timmy.
Three, two, one, go. Yo, it's me, Timmy back. God, I fucking hate this guy.
For a few months, I haven't watched the procrastinators podcast. I sent that last
voicemail about baseball. Any voicemail since like, I don't know, mid August, all of September.
I have not sent any voicemails in September. I know that for a fact. And all of October until
like this point. So anyone vaguely sounding like me is not me because all of the people
God, I hate it when voicemailers get all protective about their identity.
So I get why it's hard to tell when it's tiny, Timmy, or when it's not Timmy, you are, you're
a nothing submission. Okay, man, I am, I'm not afraid of any of you. Okay, Timmy for voice jail.
Timmy for voice jail. He's in it. No, I'll send him to the fucking gulag. All right.
Bang, bang, bang, bang the gavel. No more. It's over. It's over. Goodbye, Timmy. Take him away,
boys. Get him in there. Yeah, fucking, we got an empty cell. You know, exactly what to do with you.
Feels good. Feels good. Yeah, Timmy return an update. Like, was that just an update?
It's just to let you know that Timmy is back.
Like no content, just an update. It's just, it's like an update video. It's so annoying.
Hey guys, no, it's literally, hey guys, sorry I haven't made a voicemail in a while.
That's literally what it is.
I'm gonna die.
Oh, good times.
Next voicemail is called, oh fuck you, Timmy. Next voicemail is called Why Ben Why.
I hope this is Timmy saying why did you send me to voice jail. Okay, three, two, one, go.
Ben, your arguments in favor of circumcision are junk signs that have been debunked for at
least a decade and a half, probably much longer than that. The quote unquote health benefits
to circumcision are not. Basically, the hygienic thing about it is easily prevented by just
washing your fucking dick like any sensible person would do. And the prevention of the spread of
SCDs is a minuscule amount that is far surpassed by the much more common and widely society already
adopted practice of wearing a fucking condom. So in closing, don't push for circumcision because
all of the quote unquote benefits of it are not. They're up. And it is a moral wrong to do it because
you're not gaining anything. Okay, listen. The awkward thing here is that there's a period
of, there's a period of like five days between like the episode, like we record and the episode
comes out, we're in like, we've already answered questions, but the audience hasn't heard us answer
the questions. So sometimes we'll get a voicemail about the same thing two weeks in a row because
it fell in that period. It's unfortunate. I already answered this last weekend, but I'll say it again.
My argument is not, we should ban, we should circumcise because these things, I was merely
saying that if the data suggests that these benefits occur, they're worth considering and
weighing against the negatives of circumcision, which really seemed to be pretty minuscule as
well. You say the benefits are minuscule, well seems like the downsides are minuscule and that's
fine. The other thing, if it's junk science, then so be it. I just need to be convinced that it's
junk science and maybe it, I don't know, maybe it is. And then the other thing, okay, I hate this,
I hate this argument that like, well, yeah, it doesn't matter that it's more hygienic because
all you have to do is wash your dick. Well, like, sure. Okay, sure. It's fine for you to,
I don't know. I don't know, man. I almost feel like, sorry if this is like too, sorry if this is
like too, if this is sort of like God winning the argument a little bit, but I almost feel like
that's the same argument as saying like, well, it shouldn't matter if the police are racist,
because like, if the, if black people just didn't commit crimes, all they have to do is not commit
crime and then we'll get arrested. It's like, it's sort of missing the point. Like, it kind of
doesn't matter. Like, oh, you could prevent, you could prevent hygienic issues if you just
wash your dick. Well, no shit, right? But like, it kind of doesn't matter. Cause like,
I would be more interested in just, in looking at a, at like data, like, all right,
if everybody perfectly washed their dick all the time, then there would be no hygienic issues.
Yeah. Theoretically, the issues of like infection of one's dick should be zero,
but guess what? It's not, it's going to happen. So in a population that is circumcised are the
levels of those things higher or lower. That's all I would need to, that's all I would want to know.
Like, I'm concerned about the data, not the like, oh, well it doesn't, the data doesn't
matter because everyone just needs to do X. They're not going to do X. They never do.
Fuck you, voicemail. Yeah, whatever. I've set my piece on this. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Cool. Next one up. Billy the Bard, 11th, 3, 2, 1, go.
Fuck you. Fuck you. Because he's, because he's dead.
This son of tears of pain will never dry.
Very nice. Very nice. Very nice. Uh, you know, uh, that samurai, dang.
Can't believe, can't believe someone would betray him and make him commit sepaku like that.
Like, that's so fucked up. But what are you going to do? You know, human nature, I guess,
or something. It's just, damn. If only there could have been another way.
But we don't live in a perfect world. It's good to remember. Never forget. Never forget samurai
son. There's a, in the sky behind me, there's like a cloud and it looks like him and he's
giving the thumbs up. It's like, he's, you know, he's giving the finger. He's giving me the finger.
Like, fuck you, Beno santo son. Goodbye, Ogozaimasu. Goodbye, Ogozaimasu.
Oh, yes. Good. Good. Next one. Logo is sentimental. Otherwise, upgrade it, y'all. Artists, come on. Oh,
I bet I know what this is about. It's probably about the fact that our logo is TPC. I was looking,
I was thinking the exact same thing this week. I was looking at the logo. It's like, why don't
we just change it to be PCP? It's stupid. Nobody calls it TPC. That's all right. Yeah. Is this only
zero seconds long? Yeah, it's just the sound of a click. Okay. Well, like, it doesn't matter.
Because yeah, I agree. We should change the logo. It should say PCP. We're called the PCB,
where the progress news podcast. We should have done it years ago, Lamal. We're stupid. That's why.
Yeah. No, no, it's really just because I don't, I don't know how it would, like,
we have to Photoshop it. And I don't have the file. I don't think I was like, do we want it to,
like, this would be an opportunity to revamp the logo entirely, not change the letter. But
I don't know what it, I don't, that's a lot of work. It's true. Yeah, because we don't have,
like, Davoo's original file to edit or whatever. I mean, we could, I could edit it well enough
that it would essentially just be the same logo, but with the, like, I could do it. On the other
hand, I mean, I've been thinking of, like, changing the banner and changing it, because, like, we've
undeniably entered a new era. You know, the cast has rotated. I was thinking, I was thinking of
doing some branding changes anyway. Just because why not? It's not exactly the same show as it used
to be. No. It's the new, it's, you know, the bold new PCP for the, for a bold new future,
bold new era. I don't know, just something I was thinking about. Next up, harassed porn artist.
Three, two, one, go. So despite what you might think and the attitude around it,
like, people actually believe in, like, the real, no, not November thing,
are actually trying to, like, stop all porn. Thoughts?
Um, what does he mean by the, despite what you might think with the attitude around it?
I don't know, I don't know exactly what that means.
I think it's, it's just like, despite what you may believe, people actually think no,
November is important and not just a funny joke that you can try if you feel like,
like, like not, not nothing is, is, is not a, like, nothing in November. It's not a crime.
And like, I don't, I guess people feel like, I've not, I've not heard any of this,
like people trying to stop porn. I mean, I know that there are people that believe in,
like, the nofap lifestyle. Right. And I guess I think, like, that's, if you want to do that,
and like, maybe you think you're happier not doing it, makes you more productive or whatever,
then like, yeah, sure. You know, as, as with everything, I draw the line, like, well, you
know, who are you, who are you to say other people can't do it? Who are you to say people
shouldn't make porn? I mean, from the name of this voicemail, I assume this is a guy who makes porn
or girl or makes porn of someone who has been harassed because they are a porn artist. I can,
I can definitely see that happening on Twitter or something. Nofap people are fucking,
you know, despite, I don't know, I just said they're fine. I'm sure a lot of them are a lot,
by and large, they seem like some real degenerates. They seem like freaks, honestly.
I mean, I would assume, like, religious, like it comes from a religious place.
Yeah, like, like, Ruth V, I think, is a, is a nofaper, and he's fucking terrible.
It's, yeah, it's these, yeah, it's a very like, um, yeah, very like conservative. Nofap before marriage.
Yeah, it's people that are like, it's people that are like, people that are like, like,
I don't know, like post-Christian, like, like weird traditionalists. I don't know.
It doesn't seem like a, again, like whatever, I'm sure people do it for all kinds of reasons,
but like, the community, the community seems bad. I've heard, um, examples of people who are like,
um, I do the nofap because when I finally do fap afterwards, it feels like so much better, dude.
So much calm. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, my balls just span to unbelievable sizes and I can't
move. And then I just let it all out all over my room. And it's like, okay, you know, if you want to
do that, that's all right. That's pretty good. The people who are like, the people who are like,
porn is bad. I don't really come across them. Um, not really come across porn artists getting
harassed, but I guess it would be through DMs. So I don't know. Yeah. But all this makes me want to
do is to draw more porn. I need to get back to doing that.
Yeah, fuck yeah. Not in November. Not November. Not November. Yeah, if you want.
Oh, wait, this is the start of find purpose November. Remember?
The first loser find purpose November. Who is going to be who is going to be the first loser
of find purpose November and then buy the shirt?
Wait, do we have a shirt? Yeah, we have. Yeah, I made the shirt as soon as we did that episode.
Oh, I had never seen it. No, you didn't. It's got a nice like font and stuff.
Eleazar show the shirt. Wait, I'm gonna. Yeah, get a link. I do really like the whole,
you know, the idea that of the of the silly things traditions we have created find purpose
November is a really funny one. That's actually nice. We
how do you how do you lose it? How do you lose the challenge to find purpose?
I put in the general, I probably should have put it in editor links, but
Oh, first of all, it's a shirt specifically about losing find purpose November. It's like,
hey, guys, I was the first loser of find purpose November available only available only on a fucking
teespring.com slash stores slash the procrastinators with dashes,
like the dash pro dash procrastinators. That's our storefront. Okay, mystery solved. That's where
you get that. But, you know, this this November, either here's what you do either at the end of
November, you call in and tell us how you found purpose, or you buy the shirt.
That's those are your those are your two options. Yes.
Um, next one. Oh my god, this one's going to be this is exciting. This next one is called
Biden as a by e d o n versus drum. So that's that's going to be good. All right, three, two, one, go.
So since you guys record this on Sunday, and it usually comes out on Friday, by the time this
episode you're recording right now is going to come out, the election might be over and someone
would have won. So who do you think is going to win guys? Oh, God, when when does the election
happen? Also, should we do a heckles for shackles during it? Oh my god. We could. Do you want to?
I mean, I wouldn't mind. I was might be fun. I mean, I was thinking about something I've had before.
Yeah. You know what? I'm down. I'm down for it.
I was like, I rattled around the idea of like, doing a stream of my own, you know, because I
I used to stream like month. Oh, God, it's been so long since I streamed. I didn't mean to not do
it for this long. But um, yeah, I used to do I was thinking like, Oh, should I stream during the
election? Like other people, other streamers are going to be doing a stream during the election.
But I don't know. I thought I think I thought it would just be stressful and I wouldn't enjoy it
very much. So I wasn't going to. But as a shackles for heckles thing, I think it could be fun. So
I don't know. Maybe by the time you're listening to this, that will have all already happened.
Perhaps. Yeah. So did this guy ask who do we think is going to win? Yeah.
Yeah. What do you think, Ben? I mean, I might my my one is of
general pessimism, because people saying Biden's ahead in the polls, which is exactly what was
happening with Hillary. And there's this, there's the there's a precedent for like Trump voters to
not say openly that they are Trump supporters, because they get, you know, like yell that.
So like, I'll just wait. Yeah, I'll wait until I'm in the polling booth. And then it'll turn out
that Trump has won by the same margin. I would I would assume just just enough.
It well. Yeah, I mean, it's not impossible. I will say I have looked at the numbers. I have
heard analysis. Biden is I mean, according to polls, Biden is ahead by much by significantly
more than Clinton was. And like, yes, the polls did the polls did over indicate Clinton support.
If polls this time overestimated Biden support by the same amount, Biden would still comfortably
win. I am more concerned. I think that it is very likely. I mean, Biden is basically guaranteed
to win the popular vote by the the polls all indicate that even given a pretty significant
margin of error, Biden is going to win the Electoral College too. It is nevertheless
possible that given that like, you know, Trump does overperform relative to polls like he did
in 2016, maybe there's some maybe the the amount would be even greater because of like these so
called shy Trump voters, maybe and then like on top of it, like Trump doing some shenanigans with
the like, because you know, early voting and like mail in voting, you know, the Republicans
really, really want they are doing everything in their power to like disqualify polls or ballots
that were sent on time but arrived late. Like if you sent it before the third, but it doesn't arrive
until you know, after that, they they really want to like, get fucking judicial ruling saying like,
no, these aren't allowed. And I mean, which is like not right, but they want to do it anyway.
And it's possible that some chicanery like that could maybe tilt it enough that maybe Trump would
steal it. Or even if it doesn't technically that like there's enough uncertainty introduced that
Trump can just kind of declare victory. And because like the public is not entirely clear on the
situation, they would just accept it, which is basically what happened with with Gore and Bush.
I could imagine like, Oh, there's we're not sure. So it's like, and he Trump would be like,
they tampered with it, not really specifying who just saying, you know, it's it's a it's a fake
election. Yeah, he's been saying that he's been priming people for that idea, like, all year.
He keeps he keeps questioning like the validity of mail in ballots and stuff. And it's all it's all
it's all a production. The numbers just don't bear it out. But, you know, this is this is the
idea introduce and introduce enough uncertainty into the election and into the validity of
votes that you can just kind of like waffle enough you have enough leeway to be like,
you know, I think I kind of win actually. And then, you know, stack the Supreme Court with
justices that will rule in your favor, which is what just happened with Amy Coney Barrett.
And, you know, get yourself appointed fucking another one, even though you didn't win. So
will Trump win? I sincerely doubt it. Will Trump like legislate himself into a coup?
I think that's much more likely. I think that's much more likely. And I'm concerned.
Hopefully. I mean, hopefully this is all sounds like fear mongering in the near future. And it
doesn't actually happen. And I just sound silly. Many people are saying this, though. I'm not I'm
not the only one speculating about this sort of thing happening. His rhetoric supports that this
is the plan. I guess you the viewer will already know if you put a gun to my head.
And you said what's going to happen? I would say, I think probably Biden will just win and Trump
will leave. But I'm not like super confident that that's what's going to happen. But I think that's
more likely than any other outcome. So fingers crossed, I guess, fingers crossed.
Ah, next voicemail is called Socialist Shinobi. Three, two, one, go.
I'm waiting for it.
There it is.
Oh, God.
Thank you. Many people are saying the proposition.
Oh, no, does he not know that he's dead?
Socialist samurai, of course, has any good socialists knows all must do their part to help
the community prosper. This is why I ask you to share resources with me in return. I would only
ask for the Kawasaki clan scroll. I think it is a most fair trade. I have an answer.
Please consider my offer honourable Ben St. Tsang. Socialist samurai. And until next time.
Oh, that's his fit.
Let's hear it. Yo, I love it. Every time, every gets me every time. Socialist samurai,
this is proof that socialism just doesn't work, because clearly your publicly funded
postal service failed to deliver to you the parcel, the letter, the postage informing you
of Samurai Sama's recent seppuku. He got the scroll. I'm afraid you're going to have to dig
the scroll up from his cold grave, sir.
Nerd fucking nerd fucking commies, commie bitch.
Hey, thanks. Thanks. You know what? Thanks for the offer, though. Thanks. Thanks for the offer.
Next voicemail is from Liam. Three, two, one, go.
Hello. Am I going? Okay, this is nice. I was on earlier. A long time ago, you probably won't
remember. I was very tired and I was saying very dumb things. You made a joke about it being the
worst voice call you'd ever heard. Ben, I believe? Probably. Anywho, hello. My name is Liam. I'm
making a funny cool comic. Ben, I'm surprised you made it as far as you did. I find it difficult
to make a comic instead of just making normal art. I do thoroughly enjoy what's it called,
the vapors. I do enjoy that. Good aesthetic is good for you. And it's depressing and funny,
you know, in a quaint way. My brain is too small to really compliment it beyond that.
I'm sorry. It's terrible. I guess that's all. Also, I have been liking the newer episodes.
I really liked the one with the sheriff lady. She's really cool, I guess. I think that was really
cool. Chow. Chow. That was a phone call. That was a message. That was a voice. That was a literal
as a phone message. I think it's interesting that you say that you, I think a lot of people
feel like this, that it's easier to just like draw a picture than it is to draw a comic.
It's easier to draw a comic because when I'm drawing a picture, I'm like, I don't know why
they would be here or what they're doing. I need context. I need context for them to have a pose.
I feel a little similarly. Yeah, yeah. When you're drawing a comic, like, you know, the moment to
moment, like what you're seeing is, yeah, it's motivated. Like, you know what just happened,
and then you're like, okay, what happens next? Oh, it's this. So yeah, in that sense, I agree. But
also, in terms of like, because I assume it's a matter of motivation, right? It's like, I feel
less motivated to just draw like a single image, because it's like, I don't know, I feel like,
I feel like what's the point? I don't know what I, I don't, it would be hard. It's hard for me to,
to imagine like, or not to imagine, but to like, I don't know, I think about this like, man,
artists on the internet, they'll just like, draw something that like, looks good. And then just
like, post it. Yeah, just because it just because it looks good. And I'm like,
then they sell, they sell stickers of it, and, and posters, and, and for me, I'm like,
if I'm doing that, I'm like, sure, I mean, I guess I could try to like, draw something that looks
good. But like, who cares if it looks good? Like, what's, what does it matter? You know?
I, I feel, yeah, I know what you mean. It's, it's, it's like, what, to what end as this picture,
like, what, what is purpose does this picture serve? The picture has to have, whatever it is,
it has to have narrative stakes. There has, there has to be some kind of narrative to it. Like,
um, when I, I guess an exception would be like, after I did the Nuzlocke Conquest, I drew the
picture of like, you know, my remaining Pokemon, like on the throne of Alola or whatever. That
was like, okay, I mean, that's, that's just me drawing a picture, but like, I'm drawing it because
it is like a narrative continuation of the, the video. It's a narrative climax. It's a, it's an
ethalogue or something. Yeah, exactly. That's, it's part of a story. Comics, drawing a comic sort
of has that inherently. And I think that makes it easier, at least for me to be motivated to want
to make one. I mean, technically it's harder because like, there's more drawing involved in a comic
technically. Uh, but yeah. Oh, that's how I feel about that. Like single images that like,
the, the bar needs to be a lot, is a, is a lot higher for a single image if you're just drawing
illustrations of stuff. When it comes to like, porn, for example, um, it's, it, you can't really get
away with having shit art if it's just a single image. Yeah. In a comic, you can get away with all
kinds of horseshit. You can get away with it. Most of your, most of your art can just be bad.
Most of your art can suck as long as the, the progression of something is like interesting
in whatever way it is. It's the story that gets people. I think that the whole thing with images
is that they imply a story that people will be like, Oh yeah. You know, like a, you know,
beautiful landscape photograph makes you think of like places you've been that are like that.
And so there's sort of an implicit story, like inherit in the beauty of the image.
Yeah. And if you don't have all that beauty, you need to, to start at point A and end up point B.
There's um, you know, there's a, there's a thing. Some, some people, some people are artists and
they just have OCs and all they do is they just draw, they just draw their OCs. Like sometimes
they'll be doing something or wearing something or maybe interacting with some of their other OCs or
whatever, you know, but it's just images and there's like no actual story to it. Well, I think
there is. They draw, I know people like that. They have like a long list of traits that the
character has and the things they would say and do the likes and dislikes and backstory.
Well, usually. Yeah. Yeah. Well, the, I mean, the backstory stuff is like,
sure. I mean, I don't know if that really counts. I mean, I think that, I think that images do imply
a story in a way like, I don't know, you can, you can get an idea of who this character is by like
the images. But well, I guess I think it's, it's a mixed bag is what I was going to say was like,
I think on the one hand, a lot of these people probably think about like, oh, I have these OCs.
I would love to make a comic about them someday, but oh, that's so hard or whatever. Like, oh,
there'd be so much work or I don't have time. And like, and I think a lot of them probably think,
or I think a lot of people might think that like, okay, a comic or a cartoon would be like
the ultimate expression of these characters, like that's what they should be for. But I also think
that maybe some characters might, there might not need to be any more to them than just what
they look like, or even just like the character traits suggested by these like snapshots, like
maybe that's the appeal, maybe, maybe they can feel it on their own. Yeah, it depends on the
character and depends on the artist, I think, but I don't think there's anything like wrong with that
either. So like, I don't know, I mean, it's not everything I'm doing that's not everything,
not everything needs to be a comic, I guess, you know, not every character needs to be elaborated upon.
But they, but they can be. And that's also nice.
Liam sent another voicemail that's nine seconds long. Let's let's see what that's about. Three,
two, one, go. Oh, also, I did want to say thank you for the brick and RCQ. That was very funny.
Oh, it's that Liam.
Huh? I don't know. I was, oh, okay. I know this guy, this guy, he's an art, he's a fucking rowdy.
He, I was, I was giving a princeps rewards from the contest or from the last two contests,
I think, the other day. And I was giving out, you know, I was making them and I was typing
them up and I was handing them out to the people that won them. And Liam was there and he was just
like, conjure a brick, because I kept like conjuring these items out of text commands.
And so I just created a new princep forum that was called a brick and its description was a brick.
And I gave to him. And now he has this like, fairly powerful, like you'd like game like
world unique item, which no one else has anything else. No one else has the same item. And it's,
it's just a brick and he's got it. And Kip, another player was like, I want the brick. Oh, I could,
I could max my stats with that brick. And I was like, sorry, buddy. There's only one.
That's fun. It was very funny. Like the, the rarity thing. If there's only one of something,
doesn't matter what it is, people want it. Jim Stormdancer would have been fully sold,
even more sold on Endless War, if I'd told him that it had a brick in it.
That would have been. It had a the brick or a brick. It had a brick. Yeah. Yeah.
Next one is called fuck Margar. And I think we can all agree with that. Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys, fuck Dibuster here. As one of the few remaining members of voice jail,
I just want to say that my cellmate Margar is really getting on my nerves with all these
voicemails he's sending in while I'm trying to sleep. Once the voice jail is fully defunded,
I was wondering if we could open up a privately owned voice maximum security prison just for him.
Thanks for considering. Man, really feeling that gap between recording and releasing
right now. This guy, this guy must not have known at the time. Margar is fucking dead.
Wait, what was he asking for? Maximum security prison, PC maximum security prison.
For Margar? Yeah. Well, I guess we should send Timmy there instead,
in his place, because somebody's got to go. Yeah, we can't build a jail and not put anybody in it.
Yeah. So we'll send Timmy to solitary confinement. We'll lock him up. We'll
straightjack him, put him in a dank hole. Just for you, buddy. A fuck Dibuster. Dab.
Next up is Agent E. Three, two, one, go. Hi. This message is with Ben. I asked that you destroy
this message after listening, but we both know that you will not do that. I am Agent E. That is
all that I can tell you now. Currently, I am in possession of two things that I think that you
might desire, Ben. One of which is the Necronomicon, and the other is the lifeless corpse of SummerEye
Summer. Also, Mr. T is here. Yo, Ben, you damn fool. I ain't no one old gag from episode 225.
I was in on this scheme the whole dang time.
Do you see it, Ben? Your downfall is near. You might have survived phase one,
but did you really think that the death of your supposed sensei would be the end? Ben,
you never had a SummerEye master. They were memories that our organization implanted in your
mind, and now, Ben, phase two begins. But until next time, sayonara.
This is like your sonichu and this guy's Christian drawing your life.
But I'm like their sonichu and they're my Christian. They're creating my story.
This is my story and nothing less.
I don't know what the E stands for. What did I do? What did I do to deserve this? This hell.
I can't believe the government, or whatever shadow organization,
was using their freaking schizophrenia machine to send me voices in my head of the SummerEye.
Why could I hear them as well? Am I a figment of your imagination?
I mean, maybe they just widened the signal beam a little bit and just got us all a little bit.
Just sent it through all the pipes. It's easy.
They have resources. Well, listen, the necronomicon, I would like it.
Hey, actually, socialist shinobi. Can we work out a deal with this? Give me that.
Do a slice, do an aeido slice, and cut Agent E's arm off with the necronomicon in it so it
drops and I like catch it and I go, yeah, thumbs up. That'd be pretty nice. That'd be pretty cool.
I don't care about Samurai's corpse. And then retrieve the arm as well.
And then one might say, one might speculate about if one were to do such a thing, what might occur.
All right, moving on. Next one is Laggars. 3, 2, 1, go.
Yeah, bro. It's cool. It's social. And we're like, yep. And the conversation ends.
It's a typical, hi, hi, how are you? Fine. And that's it. So my question is,
how do I make enduring conversation with other people, where I talk and the other person replies
and so on. And in general, when I'm with other people, what can I do that is fun and engaging
because I always freeze. I try to open a chat or something and I never know how to
start or what can I say to someone else? If somebody says, like, oh yeah,
George, you've won the first half of the battle. You are both into the same thing.
After that, you just have to ask them questions about what is their favorite character? What
do you like in the thing? Just ask them questions about the thing. The conversation can easily go
from there. That's like a basic strategy. I think I would agree. I would add that
most people really just want to talk about themselves. So yeah, if there's something
they're interested in, like genuinely they're interested in it, and you ask them anything
about it, you just let them talk. Let them talk about a thing that they're interested in. Most
people are just waiting for an opportunity to do that, right?
Take a list, take a leaf out of tierlist.com. You know all those tier lists about what's
your favorite cereal? Just ask people what is their favorite generic thing, usually food,
and that'll get them like, oh, I like this thing. I like this brand of fruit juice.
It's a good one. This is my favorite soda. Oh, really? Well, I like this.
People like filling out those tier lists for a reason, and they like talking about them and
arguing with people about them. So that's an aspect of just generic conversation starter stuff
if you don't really know what to talk about. I mean, if the conversation stops and they're not...
I mean, I guess I would say if you want to keep it going, then I guess you need to offer something
that's like, okay, well, you know, my favorite episode was this or whatever, and hopefully that
would prompt, like, okay, well, yeah, I like that one too, or like, no, no, my favorite episode is
this one, and you can talk about why or whatever. And if it grinds to a halt, then I guess I would
assume that like, I don't know, could be any number of reasons might be that maybe they're,
I don't know, maybe they're not even that interested. Maybe they just said they were
interested in it because... I think, yeah, there's times where they could be pretending to be
interested because they want to be polite. They could be interested legitimately and just also
terrible at speaking, in which case you have to carry the conversation, which is a bit exhausting
sometimes, but you know, you do what you gotta do. Do what you gotta do? Do what you... That's,
that's like ours. That's how that's what it is. You just gotta do what you gotta do.
You know, whatever it takes, do whatever it takes. Never, never, never, never relent.
Don't let society tell you. Don't let society put you in a box. All right, you gotta, you gotta
follow your dreams with a vengeance. All right, and if, and if, and if people try and stop you,
you gotta make them pay, right? You gotta show them. You gotta show them all.
What are that? I've got a mission. I got a mission for you. DM me. I'm gonna send you on a mission.
Don't tell anyone. Okay. Next up, we really be circumventing the crux of circumcision.
Three, two, one, go. Okay. So firstly, circumcisions can still be botched and that like
sucks for the people who that happens to. Even if everything else is neutral, there's no reason to
like take that risk. Also, people are quick to dismiss like the suffering of the child,
because like, oh, you know, you won't remember it, but it's like...
Yeah, it's still doesn't matter really. Like they're still paid. You're still chopping up their
dick without an aesthetic. Why is that what we think is like the first experience of being alive
in the world is, is that they get their dick chopped up? Like, you know, that's just, it just
doesn't seem nice. That's just doesn't mean. It seems what if some, what if you, why do we give
our babies vaccines that shouldn't be a baby's first memory is getting a needle stuck in it?
Like, shut up. God, like... Needles don't feel like anything though.
They hurt. Not really. Well, maybe when you're really small.
I just, man, I like, I'm willing to be persuaded. I just, I hate bad arguments. Like,
I don't even think, you know, I'm, I'm not genuine. I'm again, I'm not genuinely out here being like,
no guys, we need to keep circumcising. Like I'm, I'm not committed to that position.
But all the arguments in favour of it suck. I don't know, like, give me a good one, please.
What was the first, what was the first thing that he said? I'm gonna replay the very first
still be botched. Okay, okay. Yeah. Okay. And yeah, if, if, if there is, let's in a
situ, in a situation where like the data suggests that there is no benefit at all to it,
then yeah, probably the, the pain, which I think is pretty minor, like you're a baby, whatever,
like the pain and the, and the possibility of it. The possibility of the botching. Yeah.
Against nothing, against no benefit at all. Then I would absolutely agree. Yeah. No, then
probably we shouldn't do it. But like, there's not zero benefit. There's not.
I guess I would like to know what happens when an uncircumcised, no, when a circumcised person
never washes their dick, does it get stinky? You know, is it, is it, is it prone?
Probably less so, but yes. Because like, probably yes, but not as much. Right. It's really just
the not as much thing. I really feel like unless there's something major, it's pretty negligible
one way or the other. I just like how I am. So I like, I am in favour of uncircumcised.
Well, I mean, let me just, let me just pose you a hypothetical counterfactual here. Imagine,
imagine I showed you some data, and this is hypothetical, I don't know what the data is,
but imagine I showed you some credible data that suggests that like, okay,
in a week, you know, one in a million circumcisions is botched, and the penis is destroyed. And it's
like, okay, that seems bad. But then I say, okay, well, among people who are not circumcised,
one in a million will contract a penile infection that will require their penis to be amputated.
Right. Not like, it's not common. And it's the rare individual who doesn't wash their dick enough
to cause this to happen. So like, it's still rare. But like, those are two, those are two,
like, pretty marginal cases that nevertheless balance one another out, right? Like, if that's
it, you would look at that and be like, hmm, either way, someone's gonna lose their dick.
So like, which one, which one is better? I don't know.
Yeah, I understand your, your willingness to see the data before making a decision.
Like that, that's what that's what it would take to convince me of anything.
Yeah, I think at this point, the voicemails are still like trying to convince you
um, you know, with like, with like this weird appeal to emotion, like, oh, that's so cruel
to a baby. It's like, I don't give a fuck. That's, that's not a good, that's, because it's mean,
because you don't think, I don't know, this like, with like, oh, the babies are you implying that
it causes some kind of emotional trauma? Because I don't think so. I don't think like, Sigmund
Ford was like, Oh, yeah, the circumcision has really like fucked up a generation of babies
or whatever. Like, nobody says that that they've got some like emotional trauma from circumcision.
Nobody does. Maybe the data would say otherwise, but I don't know. I've, I mean, maybe I've never
heard, I've never, I've never heard of it as someone's like, Oh yeah, this being circumcised
gave this baby trust issues or something. Yeah, I guess it's because it happens so early in life,
you don't really have anything to, to like, you know, you don't even know what's going on,
because you didn't remember having it. You don't, you don't miss it. And like,
you might experience like a moment of discomfort, but you won't be able to, you won't be like,
you don't know why you can't like associate like, Oh, the reason I felt this was because
this person did something. You just probably like, you feel some pain in your dick for a moment,
and then for a while afterwards, and there's nothing you can do about it. I don't know.
Anyway, whatever. I just don't think it's, I just don't think it's a great argument. I just don't.
Next up, we got an email from Frost Drive. Three, two, one, go.
So I was listening to an old episode of the PCP and in it, the comic website platform,
Tapis was brought up and you guys kept saying something like Topis or Topaz. I just want to
let you guys know the correct pronunciation is Tapas. And on the topic of comics, I have a series
on there with a few thousand readers, but I've been thinking lately that's not enough. And I've
also realized that putting all of your content online for free, pretty cringe, bro. So going forward,
I'm thinking about reserving my comic series, like the main narrative for only backers on
kick starters, and it'll continue to grow the fan base online through comic strips of the series
and email marketing. That's what I'm going to do. It's pretty interesting topic to me. I don't know
about you guys, but is it cringe or based? Let me know in the comments below and don't forget to
smash like, smash subscribe for the PCP. Also, Ben, I got your comic in the mail finally from the
Kickstarter. Oh, fuck you. Very cool. Love the black envelope in the white letters. I'm definitely
copying you. Thanks, dog. Go for it. I don't know whether it is like based or cringe to keep
some content for backers only. I think that's fine. It just depends on whether that is effective at
growing an audience as much as you want. Yeah. Yeah. At the end of the day, I mean,
that's what matters. It's like, you know, you got you got to balance. You got to balance
you got to balance, like, you know, public outreach, I guess, versus like,
generation of revenue, and like, whatever way works for you, like, is fine and is probably
what you should do. And I'm not going to begrudge anyone for that. I think I think that it's cringe
to I mean, it's cringe to overpaywall and like, you know, paywall all your stuff and then no one
ever ever sees your shit. And then like, you don't grow and nobody yeah, but it's it's it's
it's to some extent, probably also cringe to underpaywall and like, never charge for anything.
And put and just do everything for free. I know that like, it carries the benefit that like, if
you're if your stuff is good, and it gets popular, you know, you accrue social capital, which is
valuable in in its own right. So it's, you know, it's not really for free exactly. But I mean,
you do have to monetize it at some point, if you're ever going to take it beyond just being a hobby
that you do. So, you know, you know, I mean, just yeah, it's it's a I think a nice base thing to
do is just whatever works. I think a nice middle of ground is is usually to have paywall for early
access to content. That's usually fine. That was yeah, yeah, everybody ends up seeing it. But if
you're really into it, you can get to see it early. Or you can get to see special behind the scene
stuff. I guess I did. I guess I don't really think of it as paywalling. But I guess I did. I have
technically paywalled the vaporettes, because they are only in the book.
That's yeah, that's a cool one. Because like, they're they're side story content. They're not
been saying original art. So it's like, I don't have to read them. But they are really cool. So
I mean, I would consider them to be, I mean, they're not been saying art, but they're been,
I mean, they're canon and everything. And I wrote yeah, yeah. So like, you know, they're just as
valid. But yeah, I guess that's, I guess, like, I paywalled a little bit. I will probably at some
point in the future, I will make them public. But like, maybe not until after I maybe have like,
another thing that's going to have like, you know, some of its own like, associated.
I hate the word but paywalled content. Yeah, interesting. It's like, it's like a,
it's one of those things that like, probably, you will never, there is no answer. It's just
got to be one of those like, two conflicting forces that one must must forever balance,
you know, in their life or whatever, or in their, in their brand.
Next one is called perpetually two weeks behind three, two, one, go.
Hey, I always let a new podcast episode come out before I watch the previous one,
some always two weeks behind. But so far, all the guests have been really interesting,
and they're intending to listen to, to keep up the good work.
Wouldn't it be funny if this guy, he's two weeks behind. So wouldn't it be funny if like,
this guy ends up being someone who gets mad about Mallory?
You know, thinking about, thinking about it, it's easy to see like the, the dislike. Oh,
we didn't even talk about, we didn't talk about last episode and the reaction it got.
I mean, we didn't really need to.
We talked about it. We talked about it. I mean, I kind of wanted to, I mean,
I talked about it with Jim. We talked about it with Jim a little bit before the episode started,
just to like, I don't know, because I, because I sort of intended to like reference it a little bit.
But um, yeah, I, you know, it's, it's, it felt like, and my emotional reaction to
all the, the, the, the, the downvote ratio and the proliferation of like,
unfavorable, let's say, comments was to be like, dang, the people are mad. The people are riled up.
I have like offended the community with this and, you know, that's, and, and, and it pisses me off.
Wait, I gotta look at the numbers. But actually, you know, on reflection, it's easy to feel that way.
But really, like, I mean, the video got, oh, it's almost, it's still under half likes, but like,
you know, the video got three, it got 113 likes so far.
Um, and 140 dislikes. So racialized, it's bad, but like, that only represents maybe like 100 people
who were upset enough to, to click the downvote button where they wouldn't have, you know? So,
you know, it's definitely, it's definitely a small but vocal minority of people that were
upset about it, upon reflection.
It's, it's, it's the last remnants of, of the waiting for Nate crowd, I guess.
You think so?
They, they, they don't like the direction the show is going and this is like the final straw,
like, I can't believe, I can't believe you got someone like that.
Imagine, imagine being mad that someone's not on the podcast, on a podcast anymore. Imagine
being mad about that at the people who are still on and not at the person who isn't on.
Like imagine, imagine coping that hard that you like, displace, blame somewhere it doesn't belong
to that extent. I don't know. It's wild. It's wild to me. Uh, I mean, I said, I said in that,
I'll put out a little thing, like, I don't think people who like Nate equals people who are angry
at the thing. No, there's, I didn't mean, I didn't mean to imply that. I didn't mean to
imply that it's like, oh, everyone who liked Nate on the podcast is a piece of shit.
No, no, no. Like, like legitimately not even true, but no. But yeah, it, it is a vocal minority
that didn't like her because I don't know what I said in the episode is like that it's, she
represents a thing that she doesn't actually represent like truly. They just think she does
and then they hate that and then therefore they hate her and they won't listen to her.
It was, it was weird to see that like, I mean, I've seen like all the vitriol she's gotten on
like Twitter. I kind of assumed that like people would just sort of, I mean, maybe I assumed that
like they wouldn't have the same reaction to like hearing her talk and like seeing her on a podcast
as they would just like, I can kind of, I don't agree with it, but I can understand how if you
are someone who thinks that like stealing is really wrong, you read the shoplifting comment
and you make get mad about it. I can kind of understand like at least the process there,
but to then like get mad at her, just her on a podcast. I didn't, I didn't think it would carry
over. It was weird to see like as soon as the first I mean, I thought it would carry over because
I saw the ratio. I was like, wow, no, it's, it's, it's, it carry, it does. I was surprised.
I, I mean, I felt like it would absolutely would because she's only known right now,
largely in circles that don't like her through those specific things we put in the thumbnail
and they're going to be like, what? I guess I just didn't and they just sort of associated
whatever they felt with those things as like, you know,
yeah, but like it's a new written in stone that this is a bad person and a bad person is on the
show. Man, he's really going downhill and they just really reacted immediately.
But even if you didn't, even if you didn't like, I don't know, just even if you didn't like the
comics, I don't understand why you would have the same reaction to that person in like a totally
different context. You know, it's, I don't know. I mean, I guess, I guess we did show the comics in
the, yeah, I can see, I can see that it just doesn't like, I couldn't imagine. I'm not sure
whether a lot of the people who reacted angrily really listened to the episode at all. Maybe
they listened to like the first 20 minutes just to get an idea before commenting. But like, I don't
think many of them would have stuck around before they were like, God, fuck this person. You know
nothing. She was a horrible person on Twitter. I don't know. It's, it's funny because like,
if you think she's a terrible person, I think you probably think the same about me. So why,
why do you listen to this podcast that I am on every episode of? I don't get it.
Uh, that's weird. It's weird, man. Damn! Damn! Um, did I have anything else to say about that?
No, not really. Strange, strange times we live in. Next one is Son of Marowak. I know this guy.
Uh, three, two, one, go.
All right. Son of Marowak here. Yeah. So I just been watching the series of videos by Lindsay Ellis,
talking about an omega verse lawsuit that's been going on for like the past year and a half or so.
I've seen those. The first video she made is just her talking about the lawsuit in question and
how much of an asshole the villain of the lawsuit is. The second video is her in response to
the villain of the lawsuit. It's giving Lindsay crap about the video that she made.
And Lindsay goes through all of the points in documents that were sent to her in regards to the
video and owns how each or every single one of them were wrong. Like this villain of the lawsuit
is a complete asshole. It doesn't know what the hell she's talking about. Go watch these videos
if you haven't already. Tell me what you think of them. Oh, that's the question. I just want to
know what we think. Have you seen those? I've seen those. I, like in terms of Lindsay Ellis videos,
I didn't really give a shit too much. Like I've watched the first one and then, you know,
the second one was like, okay. But it's like the crazy idiot who does a lawsuit that is stupid
and then gets angry at a YouTuber exposing this stupid lawsuit, you know, double combo,
is like a pattern I've seen like a hundred times on YouTube. So like for Lindsay Ellis video,
wasn't that interesting to be honest? It felt like a repeat of like everything else.
Like the H3 thing with the thing and then. Was it Graham Linnum? Was there, what was the H3
lawsuit? Oh, no, no, no. I was thinking of H Bomber Guy. Oh, H3. This sort of stuff has happened
so many times. It's like, yes, we all understand. Oh, Jim Sterling, another person, like he made
a bad review of a video game. He got attacked by what's his face. Kind of remember him. But
that like they're always stupid. The lawsuits always fail because they're stupid clearly.
And it's just like, yeah, that's another one of these. I know what you mean. I thought that,
I thought that the first one about the Omegaverse was pretty interesting. I thought it was funny,
you know. Yeah. But yeah, the second one about like now I'm being sued, it's like,
yeah, that's a funny fact, I guess. But like the story about it is, it's like you said it.
I've seen this kind of thing before. And I'm like 100% sure that Lindsay Ellis will be fine.
So I'm not like worried. Yes, she seemed more fine than most because she had like YouTube
protecting her apparently. Oh yeah, that's true. That's unusual.
It was on you. That was the most interesting part was the how much YouTube was on her side about it.
Which seems, I don't, does that make me like YouTube more or less? That they will protect
anyone or that they will own? No. Am I glad that they'll protect anyone or am I angry that they
will go to such lengths to protect someone big and do nothing for anyone else? Yeah, it's the same
old like she's big, she's a published author now, she's like a big deal and she's got a huge
Patreon. Of course they would help her. Yeah, yeah. Which I'm glad they at least do that sometimes,
but it's like it still speaks to YouTube's ineptitude on the lower levels. In this case,
it's nice that they did something for someone who is obviously in the right, I guess. But yeah, like
would I be like super broken up if Lindsay Ellis got like, I don't know, some copyright claims
against her? Like whatever, she's fine. Yeah. No, I thought the first one explaining the whole
like debacle like beforehand though and going into like what is the Omegaverse was like pretty
entertaining. Have the legal eagle man come in? I feel there's something about there's something
about legal eagle man that like upsets me. Is it the Dr. Wolf jaw? He does. They have the same,
oh my god, you're right. You're right. The first thing I noticed about him is like,
oh this guy, this is like a good version of Dr. Wolf where everything went right.
You know, I have watched my fair share of legal eagle and I think it's fine. It's fine content,
but like there's something so manicured about him and like his and like I get that like that's the
point. Of course he wants to come off as like polished and professional. His whole thing is
that he's a lawyer. He needs to like appear as like a professional. I don't know, I guess I'm like
he's just he's too plain to be like a relatable character on YouTube, do you mean? Yeah, maybe
a little bit like he's so like the fact that he just kind of shows up, does the YouTube thing
and just, you know, duly rewarded for it. It's like a little frustrating
whenever I see that. Like this guy hasn't even beaten Sans in Undertale.
I guess, I don't know, I don't know like, I guess I wonder like to what extent
professionally is he like a lawyer versus a YouTuber, do you know what I mean?
Yeah, it feels like he's so like hard in the YouTube game that it feels like this must be
his full-time shtick, but he sort of sells himself on the premise that like his job is that he's a
lawyer. Like I don't know, does he even practice anymore? Because he's like fucking, he's fucking
hobnobbing with like big, big, you know, YouTube people making like, what's that like Nebula,
making Nebula with fucking like Patrick H. Willems and Lindsay Ellis and whoever the fuck else.
I mean, I could imagine he's a, he's a lawyer that has like
got into the YouTube thing just as a hobby, because it's like, don't have work right now,
I may as well use my knowledge to make content. And you know, he's just so, he's just so goddamn
handsome that it makes me mad. It's just like, oh, of course, this guy was like, hmm, I'm a lawyer,
and I'm disgustingly good looking. You know, I should probably, I should probably flex that
to also become like wildly successful on YouTube as well. And he just does it and it just happens.
You know, that sucks. It's not to say that like he didn't, like, I mean, you know, he made the
content, I guess, I guess he put the work in, I guess, but in a way that's like,
you know, this is how I always feel. People, I feel this way about everyone rich and people say,
like, oh, I'm just like salty. I'm just like, oh, you're just jealous. I'm like, yeah, sure, I guess.
It just always frustrates me. It frustrates me whenever I feel like what I'm seeing is like a
person being rewarded in a way that's incommensurate with the work they put in. And I feel like that's
true of like basically everyone, that's true of like everyone who's rich at all. And it's true of
like most people who are successful on YouTube. It was part of a, you know, a growing up, I assume,
I don't actually know. Like, wealthy enough to go to law school at all is a pretty big step up.
To do all of the law school stuff is not easy, obviously. It's like, you know, the opportunities
provided to him to go to that sort of place is like, you need money already and can't do that
unless you live in at least a middle class family. Probably. Yeah, sure. I mean, that too.
Yeah, I don't know. It's just, it's just to see, you know, he does a very formulaic stick and it's
a fine stick. And it just frustrates me whenever I see someone do it by the book. And it just works.
That's what I see when I look at legal legal. This guy just showed up was like,
what's the formula? Okay, I'll do that. And it worked, you know?
Like Captain Christian. Captain Crispin. Like Captain Christian. Yeah, Captain Christian, I know.
I think that's his name. The video essay man. The video essay, like, perfect algorithm.
Yeah. Perfect thumbnails, perfect release schedule.
I like, I like talk shit about him on Twitter one time and he responded,
I don't know, to like call me jealous or something. And, and it's like, same thing. I just,
I just think, I just think, you know, I just think it's, it is kind of like jealousy because it's
like, everybody wishes that they just happened to do all the right things at the right time,
first try. Well, not first try. You don't know how many times these people have tried, but
like, it all seems, because that's, you know, internet personalities in a nutshell,
everything seems to be the perfect version of everything that's going on.
Yeah. Like, it's, oh, it's just so happens that everything went perfectly and I'm a perfect
person and you feel like you are inadequate because you're not me. Ha ha.
Indeed. And it's like, nobody sets out to make people feel shit, but it happens.
Yeah. Yeah. Anyway, the, the Lindsay Alice. Yeah, whatever. Cool. Next up, voicemail.
Margar is dead. Three, two, one, go.
Oh, I can't believe how easy it all wasn't yet.
Months of planning, months of hard work. Ben, all I had to do was wait for your other enemies
to set me free. And now I'm on the outside. Samurai came for me just as I knew he would.
I knew he couldn't wait that long. And when he came to my cell, I just used a little deception,
a little murder origami to create a fake copy of myself. Now I'm officially dead.
The oldest trick in the book. You can't convict a dead man. So I'm out and I'll be seeing you real
soon, Ben. Just know it didn't have to be this way.
Is that, that was Margar, right? I'm, I, yeah, I believe so. Oh, no, he's out.
He played me like a fiddle. He played you like a fiddle by being so boring that someone decided to kill him.
This is fun all along.
Well, it reminds me of two things. Reminds me of the time on Twitter that Chris Chan said that she
would be like seeing me soon. Remember that? I mean, as she said that like 10 times,
isn't that every time you cross paths? Maybe more than once, but it was at least one time that
she said like she would be seeing me soon in person and like the, yeah, yeah. And like the
implication was that she was going to be like astrally projecting to curse me or something or
maybe just to talk to me. I don't know. So, you know, that's just one more thing to be afraid of,
I guess. And the other thing it reminds me of, in, did you, do you remember the essay or do you
remember the thing that gets read in Frog Fractions when you're in the underwater segment?
The essay is about boxing before the punching meta had arrived.
Did you, did you watch, did you rewatch either of those no-clip documentaries?
I did, yeah.
Do you remember the part, this part killed me. It's not, it's not what it is. It's the way that
he said it, that Jim said it in that he said like the essay is about the idea that like
punching is not an essential part of boxing. It is only emergent from the rule set.
And that like before anyone just, that really boxing is just a contest to knock your opponent out.
And it used to be about like you just had to bore them to sleep with stories until someone
discovered that, wait a minute, actually the fastest way to get someone to be unconscious
is just to punch them. That's how like modern boxing was invented.
It's really cool. Yeah, yeah.
It's a great lateral thinking.
Yeah. Well, I guess, I guess I've been outsmarted once again. I guess this is just the theme
of the voicemails now, but that's fine. You know what? It's better this way. Who wants to know
everything? Last, last voicemail is called I miss old PCP cry face. Three, two, one, go.
Hey, you, yeah, you guy instantly commenting and disliking the last episode of the PCP
commenting on how you miss the good old days. It was so much fun and better and you fell in love
with everyone on the first 50 episodes. And now things aren't good because Ben bad and Ben
invited Mallory on and you don't like her or something. Lol.
Commenters rule number one, you fake PCP fan.
Commenters rule number one. I guess I'm a fake fan myself. Number one is the don't comment
so you watch the whole thing, right? Yeah. Like, you know,
that's the thing I was imagining most people were not listening to what Mallory had to say
before commenting that she's a terrible piece of shit because she doesn't come across like one.
You know, I, I don't know. I think that probably, I don't know if that's the problem
is that people weren't watching the whole episode because I'm pretty sure that if you came in
thinking that way and being, being like, if you come, if you, if you, if you're like,
Oh, I hate new PCP. If you're like, Oh, I hate this guest. If you hate Mallory specifically
or whatever, I don't think that watching all the way to the end, like I don't think that anything
that we said in the episode, well, I mean, maybe it's possible that something we said on the episode,
you might be persuaded like, Oh, you know, this person isn't like I thought or whatever, maybe.
But I think a lot of people would not be persuaded and they would just be like,
Yeah, this is what I, this is what I expected to hear.
You know, maybe, I mean, I would need to know what they think.
Yeah, like what their assumption was.
You know, I think, I think that no, I'm, I'm partially wrong. I think that probably a lot of
people would hear Mallory say like, you know, the new guy comic was like just kind of like a spur
of the moment thing that I didn't even really think about too hard and be like,
I guess, I guess what doesn't really matter. And like to hear her say like, okay, well,
the shoplifting thing is just like, you know, it's, you know, when you're poor, it's just about
like being poor as a kid or whatever, it'd be like, I guess that makes sense. But I don't think
everyone would be persuaded. I think maybe half and half, I don't know. So while yes, of course,
we always encourage comment to rule number one, but I don't know if, I don't know if it solves
the issue. I don't know if it, I don't know. I mean, what we talk about in the episode was more
about like how her own people turned against her, not really people who already don't like her.
Because if it were more about the other people, we would have had explanations and more like
in depth talk about like why shoplifting could be an okay thing.
It's true. Yeah, we didn't even really talk about it from that angle. Yeah.
I don't know. I think we've done a really great job of burning off the old PCP heads.
We've we've seared away the crust, the cruft, the chaff left with only the cream, the wheat,
uh, if you will.
That's not keto. I'm getting hungry. No, it's not. No, it's not. God damn. I made,
I made the most delicious grilled cheese and spam sandwich today with keto bread,
with low oven fresh keto bread. Have I talked about low oven fresh?
No. What is keto? How do you make keto bread? Is it cut of flour, dust?
Well, well, you know, I think I've talked about, I was looking for,
this is a funny note to end the episode on, but I looked all over. I tried all kinds of
different bread replacements. I tried the one that everyone tells you to make is cloud bread.
Cloud bread sucks. I hate it. There's another, there was another one that sort of, I ordered
like a mix to like mix it yourself and make a loaf out of that. That one was like, okay.
I tried ordering some like loaves online and from Amazon and like they would like,
either they would have a weird texture or they'd have a weird taste or like when you toasted them,
they would get really hard like a cracker. They had all the, all these different things. And then
I found this, this one brand that they sell, they only sell it at Aldi as far as I'm aware.
And it's called Love and Fresh L-Apostrophe O-V-E-N. And the main ingredient is,
is it wheat gluten? I don't know. It's, it's, it's got some like wheat derivative and it's,
it's perfect. It's amazing. I can't believe it. It just tastes exactly like normal bread.
All the other ones were like weird or bad in some way or just like kind of marginal,
like just good enough that like it's all right. This one's just like, no, they did it.
They, they fucking did it. And it's like three grams of carbs per slice. So,
you know, I can't eat a whole loaf in a day, but I can eat like two or four slices in a day and
it's fine. And I made a fucking grilled, spam and grilled cheese sandwich. So good. So fucking good.
I've been, I've been buying all these different cheeses, making different kinds of grilled cheese
out of them. So far, Monster is my favorite in case you were wondering. I know you were for sure.
Hmm. Yes. Yeah. So yeah. Monster Cheese, highly recommended.
Anything else we have to do before? No, we gotta say, we gotta say patreon.com
slash the procrastinators. That's right. And we gotta say teespring.com slash stores slash the
dash pro dash procrastinators. To get the first loser find purpose November t-shirt.
And we gotta say speakpipe.com slash pcp voicemail. And are we forgetting anything?
Oh, we got bonus episodes. What was the last one we did? Was that with digi?
Yeah, no. Yeah, yeah, yeah, it was, it should be coming out this week, right? It should be coming
out to the beginning of November, the commentary track. Yeah, the commentary track on the first
episode. The commentary track. I think it should be, I think it should be available on Patreon
by the time this episode is out, probably. Yes, we actually, we actually did it. And if people
like it, we will do more. So I hope that's not a complete clusterfuck, or that it is,
but people like it anyway. So yeah, Patreon for that. And I guess that's it. Thanks for listening,
everyone. Hey, I guess I should say, here's something. If you like our guests, or if you
liked seeing them on the PCP, and this, this would go for any of our guests actually, Jim,
or Mallory, or Aria, or Mary, or anyone, if it would be cool, if people would like maybe on their
Twitter or something like message them and say like, Hey, I saw you on the PCP, you know, I liked,
I liked it, liked your conversation there, like listening to you, thought it was cool,
thumbs up, good job. That would be a cool thing for people to do. You know, if you're so inclined,
if you like someone we have on, and you want to let them know you appreciate them,
I would think that was pretty based. And go get the frog fractions DLC. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I am, I am going to buy that. I'm going to buy that today. Actually, I will buy that like right
after this episode is done. And you should too. For old pal Jim. All right. Is that it? We done?
Good night, everybody. Good night, everybody. Good, good, good morrow to you so long and thanks
for all the fish. Fish, delicious. Bye.