The Pro Crastinators Podcast is a non-compatible podcast that is based on a non-compatible podcast.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of the Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Welcome to the podcast with me and you and no one else.
Welcome to the perfect cast. It's the number one best solo podcast on this whole channel.
Welcome to Digibro's decompression chamber. The only depressing shit suicide game.
Welcome to Mumkey's Countdown to Suicide, baby. One episode to go.
Welcome to Endless Jess Countdown to Suicide. It came before Mumkeys. It's the real one.
Welcome to the Suicide Squad Squad.
This podcast has already killed itself. This podcast just won the Oscar for best makeup.
We did it, boys. Yeah. Damaged. Hashtag damaged.
So, yeah, today it's a PCP episode about suicide.
And everyone here is looking forward to experiencing that sometime in the near future.
It's that brass ring we're all reaching for.
Mumkey, you seemed like you had some idea of what you were doing in this podcast.
So, why don't you do that?
Oh, okay. I was hoping you would have us introduce because I had a great bit.
So, real quick, introduce me real quick so I can see my name.
Oh, yeah. I should say everybody's here. We got Mumkey Jones here, everybody.
Goddamn it. Come on, go. Go. No.
Come back to me. I'm going. Come back to me.
Oh, I got a good name.
We got Hippocrite. Hippocrite's a guy.
I got it. I got it. All right. Hi, everyone.
Here's my gun. Click. And here we go.
Okay. Come back to me. I think I'm ready.
Okay. Here's Mumkey Jones, everybody.
I wish that I was dead.
Yeah. I know that song.
That's a good song.
That's how I say hello. Oh, shit.
StemClad won't turn off when I turned off my phone. Goddamn it.
This bit is a fucking mess.
Lovely use of my wonderful music.
Here we go.
Actually, why am I even continuing?
Oh, go ahead.
Tom Oliver as well.
I'm not going to do anything gay like with a toy gun
to make light of this serious topic.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, that's very mature of you.
You big gay. And also, Endless Jess.
Hey, everybody. Life is a precious gift.
And welcome to the Happy We're Here cast.
Boy, it sure is great to have good friends.
And it's the sun's in the sky.
And everything's going to be okay.
Shut up, Morty.
So how about I read the Urban Dictionary Suicide?
No. It's kind of long.
Who just said no?
Actually, you know what? This definition is really short.
Okay. It's suicide in Urban Dictionary.
Your way to say to God, you can't fire me, I quit.
Well, I don't believe in it. It's a shitty definition.
I don't believe in it. I'm bored by this.
All right. Here's my intro to this whole thing.
Okay.
When you want to... I mean, we're all alive.
That's one thing to make, you know...
Unfortunately.
We're all alive.
For now.
When I think of suicide, it's because I'm sad.
And then I think of the things that would happen afterwards.
And it usually results in me realizing that
I don't want to be that guy that jumps off a bridge and then holds up traffic
and everyone's like, ah, fucking dead guy again.
Geez.
I don't want to be known as the guy who inconvenienced everyone.
So I just usually just stay alive.
That's just generally how I do this.
There's ways to kill yourself without it inconveniencing that many people.
Well, it will only inconvenience at least the people in my family.
You'll be like, oh no, he's dead.
They might have you in pain for a funeral.
If you're still giving a shit about what other people think,
that's how you know you're not ready to kill yourself.
Well, yeah.
You're not at that level.
You're just too much of a normie.
I think before we get into the weeds of this argument,
we should go around the horn and each person should say
whether they're pro or against suicide,
and then maybe a little blurb about why.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Pro or against suicide as a general concept or for ourselves?
Both.
Okay.
Each one.
Did you want to start since you're already talking?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Well, in suicide as a concept,
I mean, I understand if you're someone who truly feels
that being alive is just not worth it,
I can't really blame you for killing yourself.
Like, it's going to suck for probably some people.
I mean, I'm sure there's some people who could kill themselves
and it wouldn't even suck for anybody.
There's got to be some people in that bad of a situation.
Right, right.
But you know, because every time they say,
oh, think of how it'll hurt your family.
It's like, well, there's got to be some people who it wouldn't,
you know, who like those guys, what do you tell them?
Like, I guess do it because clearly things have gone horribly wrong for you.
How about it's a beautiful life where if that guy killed himself,
he would have gotten the insurance money to feed his family.
I mean, sure, it turned out that he had the support of the community
that loved him so much,
but also killing himself was a pretty good plan.
I mean, let's be frank here.
Like, we act as though, you know, sure, life is precious.
You can't do anything unless you're alive, if you're dead, you're gone.
But at the same time, if we're thinking of this in terms of like the net gain
and loss for humanity, there's probably a lot of people who'd be better off dead
and like the world would be better off if we lost it.
Like, we're kind of overpopulated.
We got a lot of dead weight.
There's a lot of people weighing down the system, you know.
Did you, bro?
Yeah, so, yeah, exactly.
So, you know, some people, if you just, if they got rid of themselves,
it's just less of a burden on the rest of us, you know.
Are there any racial groups you want to mention in this context, Digi?
Is that where you're going?
No, I had no, I wasn't even required.
So Digi, that's your idea of suicide in general,
but what about for you specifically?
For me specifically, I have too many things I want to see to kill myself.
Like, even if there's moments when I'm like, man, I don't,
I like, I'm not really contributing anything.
I mean, granted, if I killed myself, my family would be absolutely wrecked
and I wouldn't do that to them.
But more important because I, because I care about them,
but like more importantly than that, for me, just like,
I'm afraid of dying because I want to see everything.
I would rather try to live until like with these, the,
the incredibly pale chance that the technological singularity happens
and I get to live forever.
I want that.
I want to live for all time.
You know, you'll be happy to know that I heard optimistically
that not necessarily the singularity, but I heard recently
that some experts who I completely forget,
I was listening to some podcast about it.
It was Neil deGrasse Tyson.
He figured it out.
It wasn't Neil deGrasse.
It was actually Sam Harris's podcast.
I forget which episode, but he was saying that experts have said
that it is possible that we have currently passed the threshold
of people who were born today will discover like the de-aging process
and just in our current bodies will be able to theoretically live forever.
That was the theory that he was saying.
So I hope so.
I hope that worked out.
Yeah.
The funny thing about it is that my fear of death is also
what makes me feel depressed and suicidal.
Like my fear that all of this will be for nothing makes me like,
you know, it's like, why even go on when I know that I'm going to die anyways?
Why not just get it over with now?
Why suffer all this bullshit for the sake of no progress?
Because eventually I'm going to be dead and it doesn't even matter.
But if there's that off chance that I could live forever,
then all of it is for something.
Like I can continue to grow and continue to become better for all time.
I feel like we've had this exact conversation maybe on another podcast,
but I feel kind of the opposite in that the idea that eventually I'm going to die
sort of motivates me to do things.
And if I could live forever, I would just get super lazy and be sadder.
I think.
I feel like I would.
That's always the thing in anime or fantasy stories like humans have short lives.
That's why they get things done unlike the elves who just fuck around for a thousand years
and nobody cares about them.
That's such bullshit.
That's just like humanity just like jacking themselves off.
It's not bad that we die.
It's totally cool.
We're going to be so fucking cowardly.
I completely agree.
Every time someone's like, I wouldn't want to live forever
because I'd have to watch everyone I know die.
And I'm like, you'd make a whole bunch of new friends
and get to have all these other deep relationships that go on for hundreds of years.
Yeah, well, I mean, eventually.
If I'm living forever and I have to watch all my friends die, that's sad.
But hey, there's a guy living forever who gets to keep them alive for all time in my memory.
If I died too, then everyone wouldn't matter.
Yep.
I get it, but it's just...
I mean, I'm sure living for maybe like three or four hundred years, that would be great.
That would be pretty good.
You can get a lot of skills mastered in that time.
You can be really cool and stuff.
But forever is just such a weird concept that I'm sure I would go insane by the time.
The ultimate solution to cure nihilism and cure meaninglessness from the world
is for one person, me, to live forever as a historian of all the great people who ever lived.
That's how we fix the meaningless void.
So, Hippo, what is your view?
Endless murder.
Hippo, what's your view on suicide in general?
Oh, me?
Yeah.
Well, I think generally people who seem to kill themselves...
Actually, I don't know any statistics about that stuff.
But if you're a teenager, you shouldn't because emotions are running high.
Generally, you might not have the best understanding of your situation
and it might not be as bad as you think it is.
So, people who commit suicide, do it when you're an adult and you know that everything's fucked
and if you really feel like doing it.
I guess it's not so bad as long as you set things in order before you go.
Because when I think about doing it myself, I've never really considered doing it
but I've always enjoyed just thinking of all the things that were not enjoyed
but it's just taken up time.
Just thinking of all the things that would happen.
I don't know, I took pills and I was just found and then people would be like,
oh my god, oh no, he's dead.
And then they'd have to pay for a fucking funeral and I'm like, oh shit.
I didn't want them to do that.
I should have left a note saying, don't just throw me outside, okay.
And that would dream of all the different ways to die,
each one a little more than he would dare to try.
Was anybody else being driven insane by the fact that you just realized
Hippo Crit is just written as Hippo Kit in his name right now?
There's no R.
It's driving me fucking crazy.
How long has it been this way?
This is the last straw.
Even I don't know. I don't even think it has been that for very long.
Maybe someone changed it.
I don't know.
Jesse, you go next.
I think that suicide is probably good for most people, just not for me
because living rules and there's too much stuff that I like here.
There's, yeah, I just, fuck it.
I get it.
I'll kill myself.
Living does rule.
It's just sometimes it's like,
Living does rule, but sometimes it's like,
Or it'll just be like a face, like a face of that emotion.
Well, I've got a great t-shirt idea.
That text is centered on the main chest area, but that wraps around the body
and just goes all the way to the bottom of the t-shirt around the body.
But anyways, I guess my point was I definitely believe that most people are inherently bad
and should die and should probably kill themselves.
My dream is to make as many people want to kill themselves as possible.
There's a lot of bad people in the world who are just making it worse for everyone
and deserve to be here and most of them are found replying to my Twitter all day.
Oops.
I, on the other hand, I've never been suicidal.
I don't think I ever would be suicidal.
Even at my most lowest moments and my most depressing moments,
at least happy to be alive because I know that I'm me and I'm my favorite person pretty much.
I mean, I'm not my favorite person, but I'm pretty good.
I feel like the world needs me.
It would be irresponsible for me to not be guiding humanity's hand.
I really feel like the human race would be utterly lost without me
and pretty much everyone would just give in to hopelessness and despair
if I wasn't here to brighten the world's day.
Yeah, there's just too much stuff that I love here and there's too many people I like
and I'm one of them.
I'm kind of surprised to hear that, Jesse.
I always thought you were at least a little bit of a suicide boy.
Fuck no, that's gay.
No, I think most of us, I mean, I don't know about all of us,
but like from based on things from like the fact that we're alive
and also we joke about it more than we,
because I feel like people who would do suicide don't joke about it or talk about it.
They just sort of blow it up and then suddenly they're dead.
Well, we're gonna have to get into our real suicide boys here in a second.
Monkey, you're our resident real suicide boy. Why don't you tell us what you think?
I've got a bet going. If he actually does it, I make a lot of money.
Oh, do you guys have like a suicide pool going on?
No, just me. Just me for Monkey.
I'm really mad at you with yourself.
Would you put like money in a box and you only get to open it if I'm dead?
I put money against you killing yourself,
so if you have to keep living, at least I've got some money out of it.
Right, that's smart.
I'm absolutely down to put bets on a Monkey when and how suicide pool.
Oh, I think we should. I think we should do that in this podcast.
Yeah.
But yeah, I don't think it's any secret that I have a bit of an affinity for suicide.
I have a whole YouTube channel called Monkey's Countdown to Suicide.
As did you. You did that podcast last week in response to Tommy Boy here.
And you just had to mention that YouTube channel.
And from your one fucking podcast, I gained like 40 subs in that one day on a channel.
I don't even update.
In my book, I have a whole chapter titled Suicide,
where I pretty much list my personal philosophy through the lens of that character.
But yeah, I think that suicide is a human right,
and that anybody, for any reason, if they feel so inclined to end their life,
that is their right, nobody owns their life more than they do.
It should be their decision, despite how it makes other people feel.
Because, and I said this in my Depression video, there's that stigma of,
oh, suicide is the most selfish thing a person can do.
But I think forcing another person to live an entire lifetime of sadness and suffering,
just so that I don't have to feel sad about it, about them dying,
I think that's the real selfish thing.
It's really, it just rubs me the wrong way when people are like,
oh, you're so, you know, you have to be so selfish to kill yourself.
Because what about the people you leave behind?
We'd be so fucking sad.
Well, what kind of a selfish fucking attitude is that?
You didn't give a shit about being nice to the person when he was fucking alive,
but you're gonna guilt-trip him because you might be sad if he decides to fucking end it.
Motherfucker, where were you for the last his entire life when he was sad?
Fuck everybody. You're the cowards.
It's interesting, because I feel guilty if I were to kill myself and make people around me sad,
but I would never think to impose that guilt onto someone else,
because even if I do know a lot about their situation, it just seems a bit weird.
I mean, I would feel guilty not out of some kind of moral obligation,
because society says so.
I just feel like my family doesn't deserve that.
They did a good job and they were fine.
I would hate for them to think that somehow it was their fault because it totally isn't,
whereas I'm sure for some people, you do want them to,
kind of like in Monkey's book, the main character, Mario Quintanilla,
wants his mom to know this was all her fault.
So I'm sure for some people it's easier that way.
Yeah, well, that is kind of the appealing part of it in a dark, morbid way.
I would never want to die, ever, for any reason.
That's why I'm endless.
But if I did have to die, I would definitely want certain people to know that it's their fault
and that they could have been better to me in life.
I want them to live with that guilt.
That would be the best part of being dead.
If I could haunt my own funeral, I'm like,
just appear as an apparition above my casket,
floating over my body with a megaphone,
sitting like Siam Punk, hovering two feet above my body,
and this is your fault, and your fault, and you did this to me,
just airing my grievances across the whole funeral parlor.
That would be the best death.
Maybe it could be like a stream or a YouTube video,
where when I'm dead, play this YouTube video,
and it's at the funeral, and it's like, fuck you.
Oh my god.
It's Horseshoe Finale 3, essentially.
One of us could be the first person in history to write a suicide note via YouTube video.
Yep.
We can't do it first, right?
Someone's done it, right?
Didn't Amanda Todd do that?
I don't know if anyone specifically like,
I'm talking like set a video up to upload after you're dead.
That's a pretty good angle.
Get a lot of views.
You guys just, I think David's going to do my monkey finale,
and you guys just ruined it.
That's actually the perfect YouTube video,
because you wouldn't have to see the comments.
Yeah.
Well, monkey, you gave us your broad stance on suicide,
but what about you personally?
Because you seem the most interested in actually doing it out of anybody here.
Yeah.
I think the greatest comfort.
You don't understand.
The greatest comfort in life is to accept death.
Being afraid of death, I mean, I see where Digi's coming from.
I used to be in those shoes, and that is horrifying.
It's like, oh man, what's the point of all this shit if I'm going to die one day anyway?
But to accept death and to say, hey,
the worst thing imaginable could happen to me, and it won't matter,
because I always have suicide in my back pocket.
I think it's a great comfort to know that I always have that available to me,
and that I am not afraid of it.
You got that get out of jail free card you can cash anytime.
Yeah, that's right.
Well, that's only as far as...
Sorry.
Go ahead.
I was going to say, as far as actually doing it, I'm kind of,
I'm 50-50 right now.
I'll toss a coin later and see what happens.
Is it?
I was going to...
Well, sorry.
Go ahead, Hippo.
There's a thing about the suicide.
There's the one...
On the one hand, there's people, right, and you don't want to make them sad,
but there's the other thing, which is the ease of doing it,
because I think about how easy it would be to kill myself,
and I'm like, I would have to do certain things like get something and...
I've got a perfect video for you, Hippo, the top 10 most lethal suicide methods.
Yeah, but I need, like, I just need something like right next to me.
Like, if suicide implement was right next to me, and it was very easy to do,
it would be easier to just do it than to go and get a bunch of pills or a gun or a noose.
I don't even want to go to the bank, let alone like set up some elaborate mousetrap escapade ending in my death.
I think if you have the ambition to kill yourself and you have the ambition to do anything else, yeah.
I mean, really, suicide is as easy as walking off a building or jumping off a bridge.
It's not really that hard.
Or going into a black neighborhood, if you know what I'm saying.
Sure, walking into a black neighborhood and yell a word of choice and see what happens, I don't know.
Any word will do.
Walk into a black neighborhood and yell, Watermelon isn't even that good!
Walking into a black neighborhood and yell, Moonlight didn't deserve the Oscars.
Oh no!
What the fuck is Moonlight?
I can see that shit.
I saw La La Land.
I heard that movie about a gay nigga.
I ain't gonna watch that movie about some homo dude sucking some dick all day.
Anyway, monkey, what scares me about people with a philosophy like yours,
there's nothing more dangerous than a man with nothing to lose.
Yeah, exactly.
Well, like, I've always found that hard to deal with because of the fact that you don't give a single fuck about what effect your actions will have.
Like, on some level, I know you have enough restraint to be like, hmm, well, let me make a cost-benefit analysis.
Like, I enjoy being in the PCP, I won't fuck all of them over horribly yet, you know?
But you could do it, and you wouldn't care.
Because even if everyone hated you and you lost everything, you'd be like, well, I guess now I get to kill myself.
Like, it's a win-win.
Digi, I see the basis of your argument, but it harkens back to what my dad would tell me when I told him I was an atheist and that was,
oh, without God, how do you have a sense of morality, son?
Oh boy.
What I say is, well, I mean, just because I'm okay with dying doesn't mean I have no morals.
I'm not going to be a dick for no reason.
It's not that I think you have no morals.
I just think that you would be more willing to do something amoral.
Well, sure, I would be more willing, but that doesn't mean I'm going to do it.
The real problem with monkey is that he hides behind that mask.
And here at the Daily Bugle, we know not to trust anyone who hides behind a mask.
He's a menace.
He can't say anything.
Well, I know we have another-
Monkey Jones is a menace.
I want pictures of Monkey Jones.
Parker, get in here!
Pictures of Monkey now!
Monkey, you sound relatively, at this point, you sound like your 50-50-like death is a comfort, but not something you're actively seeking,
but we do have another suicide boy here who maybe is even further down the line than you.
Tom, do you want to tell us about suicide?
Um, okay.
Well, I think suicide is totally okay.
I think anyone who vilifies it is an asshole, or at least completely misunderstanding the point.
It's like, we kind of touched on a lot of the things I was going to say, that people who say suicide is cowardly,
or people who think suicide is the worst thing you could do, whatever.
They're the other ones being selfish.
It's not you.
And we talked a lot about, like, immortality and stuff, and, like, did you say, like, oh, I want to live forever?
I think if living forever is your antithesis to suicide, you're not actually suicidal,
because I can't think of anything worse when I'm suicidal than living forever.
Does that just mean subsisting in this hell indefinitely with no expiration?
So, if you're- and, like, if you think immortality is a good thing, you're not actually suicidal.
If you're still worried about what other people are going to think or be inconvenienced, you're not actually suicidal yet.
You're not there. You're not deep enough into it, because, like, I know my family cares about me.
I know they'd be devastated if I killed myself, and I cannot bring myself to care enough to put it off the table.
Like, I'm just like, yeah, you guys would be miserable, but you know what?
I'm miserable being alive, so fuck you.
I mean, they'd be miserable for maybe, like, you know, a year or two, but they'd eventually get over it,
whereas you would have to suffer for your whole life.
I gotta suffer for another- I mean, I have a terribly unhealthy lifestyle for, like, another 30 years, okay?
You guys have- you have a year, you get numb to it, and whatever, maybe someone, like, starts a foundation
or some shit, or they get on the news and get money or make a movie deal or some bullshit.
I don't fucking know. Something gay. I don't care.
I don't- fuck it, you know? Even, like, oh, like, they're sad for a while,
but then, like, they don't have to pay for my sorry ass because I'm still living at home,
so, like, it's a net gain for everybody involved.
Tom, I thought you were- you were like me wanting to be in a robot body really badly, though.
I do want to be in a robot body.
Like, when I say that I want to live forever, I don't mean I want to live forever, and it's like this.
I mean, either- I am in- because the- I mean, the idea is that to live forever, something's got to change, right?
Either I become immortal physically, which means that I no longer have the constant fear of anything would kill me,
and I can do whatever the fuck I want. If I'm immortal, I don't have to worry about society at all.
What can they do? They can't stop me, you know?
Well, they could lock you up, which is, you know-
Well, I can-
Well, what?
Bad.
I mean, sure.
Like, remember that immortal guy from, uh, from Bakano? You know, that one-
Oh, yeah, well, they cemented him in the lake.
Yeah.
Or that one kid who was immortal who just got tortured forever, over and over again.
Well, that was not fun.
Yeah, well, okay, there's things- there's situations I wouldn't want to find myself in,
but I'm just saying, like, I no longer have to worry about putting food on the table, you know?
So, like, it's not about I have to work a nine to five to live.
I'm just going to live. I can do anything.
I can just live my passions for the rest of my life.
If you're a robot, you still got to put oil on the table.
Digi, have you seen the movie Groundhog Day with Bill Murray?
I have.
Bill Murray is pretty much immortal in that movie, and it doesn't take long for him to start trying to kill himself.
Yeah, but then he eventually becomes-
Well, first of all, he's immortal in- but living one day over and over again.
Sure.
And, like, over the course of it, he eventually gets past that part and then becomes, like, the perfect man.
Like, by the end of the movie, he's just absolutely- he's the best guy ever, you know?
Wow.
So, Undertale sure is great.
Are you guys aware that that movie is very popular amongst Buddhists?
Because it's, like, a great encapsulation of their idea of reincarnation to get, like, better and better
and improve yourself and eventually obtain Nirvana?
Did not know that.
Which is what he does.
I know that it's in my top five comedies of all time.
It's possibly my favorite movie ever, but next to the room.
The suicide part is my favorite part, though.
Because-
No, the Enlightenment is the best part.
God damn it.
Well, not unlike Monkey.
I have, like, a deep fascination with suicide.
Like, aesthetically, I just really love the idea of suicide.
Look at this.
Look at this suicide tourist over here.
Oh, it's so cool.
Why don't you go to Hot Topic, kid?
If you're yourself a joker, dammit.
You know how they have, like, transgender?
He's like a suicide seer or something.
Suicide seer!
Holy shit, yes!
Oh my god, that's stupid.
I mean, I was really suicidal when I was a teenager and I was like-
I'm just- I have a really low threshold for pain.
So the idea of actually causing myself pain was the scariest part.
Like, I wanted to be dead, but the process of making myself dead was too scary, you know?
If I was gonna kill myself, the only way I would kill myself would be something that would be instantaneously.
Because even if I ever get to the point where I'm just like, yeah, I'm definitely gonna fucking do it.
Like, if I, like, took some pills and, like, it took, like, 20 minutes or something to die,
I guarantee you, within that 20 minutes, I'm like, fuck, I changed my mind!
Shit!
Yeah, exactly.
So let me ask a question to the entire panel real quick.
If suicide was as simple as flipping a light switch, and that was it, would you be dead right now?
Did you?
Dude, everyone would be dead.
You think so?
Everyone would have done it.
No, I would encase that fucking shit in, like, a- don't ever break the glass.
I would fucking put it beneath the earth.
Yeah, I would make sure to hide it.
I would fucking take the treasure map and rip it up and swallow it, so no one could ever find my switch.
Well, I don't think it's a switch to someone else, because it's a suicide.
No, no, it's just, like, for you.
No, I picture it as something that I have to hide and hoard from the rest of the world, because they're all, because everyone's against me.
I'm hiding it from myself.
I think if there was, like, a, like, a power to just die, like, if that was your superpower,
the ability to instantaneously not live,
the only thing stopping you would be how sad you are, and then,
that would be kind of scary for me.
Dude, that-
I wouldn't want the power to kill myself.
It's easier to just get over it and then be happy later.
If I had that switch, I would fucking-
That switch actually doesn't exist.
Yeah, go ahead, go ahead.
I would hit that shit by accident while I was, like, in a rage throwing bottles around or something.
Yeah.
Well, that's kind of the thing.
It's like, if suicide was as easy as, like, your mind actually was totally committed to it, it just instantaneously happened.
Yeah, I'd definitely be dead by it.
Well, guys, that's the thing.
That switch does sort of exist, and it's called a handgun.
And the thing is, wherever handguns exist in large numbers,
suicide rights go way up.
They go massively up.
You're saying we need to ban all guns.
I knew it.
What?
That's what I'm saying.
Now, what I'm saying is the ease with which you can commit suicide
exponentially increases the likelihood of anyone actually going to do it.
That is how I would kill myself if it was a handgun or some sort of fire.
Yeah.
Are you guys aware of suicide in Greenland?
No.
The country Greenland.
So, Greenland has, like, a one in five suicide rate.
Oh, my God.
Like, basically-
Sounds like paradise.
Because the thing is that-
The thing is that, like, your likelihood to commit suicide goes up not only for the ease of doing it,
but also from knowing that other people have done it.
Like, it's a lot like a copycat crime kind of thing.
Like, when you know that, like, it's on the table and it's something that can be done,
it makes you more likely to think about it and it becomes-
In Greenland, it became kind of an accidental cultural institution.
It became a meme in Greenland and now we're up with this situation.
Essentially.
Because in Greenland, I mean, Greenland's a fucking-
That's a meme that needs you to die.
Greenland is a frozen wasteland where the days and nights each last, you know, for-
Right.
You know, several days and several nights and, like, people just lose their mind up there
because it's such a fucking- there's just nothing to do except kill yourself.
And apparently-
It's like Virginia Beach.
It's not so much that it's a- I think it was that, like, it was one in five people know someone who's killed themselves
and that's why it spreads so much is that everyone has seen someone else do it.
And so they do it.
And just the rates are, like, out of control.
Like, the country will eventually just all be dead because everyone will have killed themselves.
Most popular method, hanging, incidentally.
Really?
Yes, hanging.
Oh, so it's not like a doctor-coordinated thing.
It's just like an epidemic of people doing it on their own.
I thought it was like-
Yeah, no, it's just-
A euthanasia thing.
No, it's just tons and tons of people killing themselves in Greenland.
It's a cultural phenomenon.
It's literally a meme.
Yeah.
Here, I'll link you.
There's a whole fucking Wikipedia article just about suicide in Greenland specifically.
That actually might be part of the reason why I wouldn't even start to consider it.
Because, like, I don't really even know that many people who have died in general.
Yeah.
You know, I think someone like Ben would be fine in Greenland because he'd be like,
Oh, that's a normie meme.
This whole killing myself thing.
I don't want to- I mean, tomorrow I'll turn it over.
Dude, he would do that.
He'd be like, you know, I always thought suicide was cool.
But now that I'm seeing all these, like, all these fucking kids on Tumblr posting about how,
Oh, I'm going to kill myself tomorrow.
He's telling this to his therapist.
Oh, look at my friend who just killed himself.
Like, dude, get over yourself.
And the therapist is like, No, you shouldn't take your options off the table like that.
You really need to keep your choices open.
So can I come in and give my interpretation of this?
Yes.
Because I think I have a different perspective.
Okay.
So actually, one interesting thing that you guys didn't mention was that,
So this whole immortality thing, you know, has a certain appeal to it.
But the thing is, the universe will end one day.
It is like in billions or trillions of years, the heat death of the universe is where the universe is continually expanding.
And it will, at one point, it'll get so wide that all like planets will kind of separate from each other.
And they won't be close enough to suns to be able to sustain life is what I'm saying.
So basically, it looks like the universe is doomed for the life within it.
We're in a very temporary position right now.
So you could say that everything we do in life has absolutely no meaning whatsoever because it will not last in the grand scheme.
Right.
And in saying that, by the way, I want to say, by the way, if you're listening to this, do not kill yourself.
Don't take, don't listen to this.
I don't endorse this.
Just not take responsibility for you if you kill yourself.
Wait until at least the age where you can drink and then maybe you won't need to.
Well, okay, I mean, but that aside, here's my actual thoughts on society.
I say don't suffer because Nate wants you to suffer.
I think Nate was doing that for legal reasons.
No, no, no, I'm saying for legal reasons.
Yeah, that's my only interest here.
Shut the fuck up.
Okay, but that out of the way, definitely kill yourself.
Nate, I can't believe you would say that.
I'm sowing you.
I think that as some people were saying, we, we live in a society and when you were born into it,
things are given to you depending on where you live.
There is a legitimate social contract that you are signing into by being alive.
And that being said, I think that there is some responsibility to not just kill yourself.
I think that you, you do have a debt that you sort of need to pay.
Now it's not, it's not that simple.
Wait, wait, wait.
We're being extorted by society.
We didn't even choose to be foreign, bro.
I didn't sign on the dotted line.
Can you be on the contract that you didn't choose to sign?
You're putting us in here tonight.
I think this is the dumbest thing you've ever said.
Well, well, well, hear me out.
We were, we were born and we were given lots of stuff by our parents and the society that we live in.
And one of those things is...
Just imagine an African tribe as Nate is saying all these things.
No.
Okay.
Well, that's the thing.
It's, it's relative to culture.
All right.
So I can only speak as to like, you know, middle America culture.
That's all I know about.
So if there are places, and that's the thing.
If there are places where life is suffering and every moment is agony, you should definitely kill yourself.
Sounds like a matter of perspective.
If it's respected to me, buddy.
No, it's not.
Name, name for me, Nate, a food you don't like.
Uh, lentils.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's say that I order you out of nowhere.
I say, I call you up.
I say, Nate, I just bought you a lifetime supply of lentils that are going to be shipped to your house once a month forever.
I'm taking care of you forever.
You can live off of this for the rest of your life.
Are you going to feel any gratitude towards me whatsoever?
Um, no.
No, I see what you're saying.
The answer is no.
So why, like, you know, just because someone has given us everything, it may be important to them that they've given us so much.
But if I don't care about what I've received, if, to me, what I've received is in fact a detriment to me.
Like, like pounds and pounds, truckloads of lentils coming to your house every fucking week that now you have to deal with because you don't have space for it.
Uh, you know, you're not going to think, wow, thanks, Digi, for giving me all this food.
You're going to be like, fuck you.
I hate you.
Why did you do this to me?
Let me explain.
I'm going to kill myself.
That's not the end of my argument.
It's not like I don't think you should be allowed to.
It's that I think a lot of people commit suicide, obviously, at their lowest point.
And it is an objective fact that their life would improve later on if they continue to live.
Now, I'm not saying that's a good enough reason.
I'm just saying that this decision they're making is actually against their own best interests, even though it's what they want to do.
I don't trust people to make the best decisions about their own life.
I simply don't.
I think that what should be done for something like suicide is, go on, if you want to interject.
Well, that's what I was saying about, like, don't do it while you're a teenager because you wouldn't really know.
Right.
Like, I still think-
I don't see you there.
Well, I mean, after a certain age, I could trust people off the 23 or 4 or something.
Like, I think, like, I don't know the data on this, but I'm pretty sure that the vast majority of suicides happen in old people.
And it's usually when you reach the point in your life that you realize it won't get better than this.
In fact, it will get worse because at some point, that tide turns.
I have a complete plan for everything you're saying right now.
Okay.
If you want to face your point, go ahead.
Yeah.
Well, just that, you know, I think it's one thing to say when you're a teenager, like,
well, you know, maybe it'll get better when I'm in my 20s.
And you're in your 20s, and you're like, well, maybe in like five years, it'll be getting better.
But then at some point, if things aren't getting better, and in fact, they could be getting worse,
then you're going to go, is it, is it actually possible?
And then even if things do get better, there does come a time when it's like, maybe what you wanted to do in life is just behind you.
You're just too old.
You're too, you can't, you can't do it anymore.
And, and you've gotten to the point where you're like, I have less time left than I had.
Like, you know, if you're 50, you know that there's less time left in your life than what you've experienced so far.
And if you think, man, things weren't that great, and I don't want to have to deal with more of it, then that's when you're probably the most likely to kill yourself.
And so that's why I think it's, it's, it's more common and makes more sense in older people.
And I can easily see a lot of us going that way in our old age.
I totally see your point.
And, and I largely agree that you should be able to make those decisions.
But see, here's my thing.
Here's what I want.
I think that it should be treated sort of like a legal case where you're submitting a request.
I want to kill myself.
And here is the evidence for why I think that that's an appropriate thing to do.
And, and like this is kind of a fantasy, but what that would be based on is, you know, like your current, you know, living situation.
And it would sort of be based on your perception of your own life, because ultimately what this is about is how happy or miserable you are.
If you could, what I would want is you to be able to prove that, yes, my life is horrible.
It has been horrible.
There's no, like if your brain chemistry is just fucked and it makes you in pain every moment of your life at an unbearable level, you should absolutely be able to kill yourself.
But I don't think that you should be able to just do it at any, well, okay.
I mean, I'm not saying that people don't have free will.
I'm saying that it should be treated as a crime, because you're doing something that's bad for society as a whole.
By doing this just on the spur of the moment.
You're the only person I know who's so into bureaucracy that you would bring it to fucking suicide.
Your own is like a really shitty way down there right now.
All right, okay.
I know it sounds like there's a lot of government red tape involved, but ideally what I would want is there'd be like a fucking app that you put against your brain.
And it just brain scans your current life, determines where you are, where you're going.
The psychopaths, in other words.
Yeah, I don't have to say the simple system, Nate endorses, that's the gayest thing ever, you need to go die.
Anyway, you need to kill yourself.
No, seriously.
The problem is there are tons of things that people do all the time that are terrible choices, but are allowed to do them anyways.
Like doing this podcast as someone who's suicidal.
Probably not the best idea, but I'm allowed to do it anyway.
Should I have to hold a hearing with everybody just like, should you be talking about suicide?
I don't know if that's the best idea.
I mean, I'm obviously only talking about one thing here.
There needs to be a foolproof system of determining whether a person's life has value or if they're just an evil sack of shit, and that system should be me.
I should be the judge, the jury, I should be the arbiter of whether people deserve to die, because I'm the only one I trust to make that decision with anyone's life.
I mean, keep in mind, I'm also basically pro eugenics, but I'm talking classical eugenics, you know, where we're trying to breed the best of the best,
and just let the people with subpar genes just be sterilized and weeded out of society because we don't need them DNA.
I completely believe that you do support that.
Of course.
I don't believe that to me.
When you say classical eugenics, you talk about Hitler Youth or...
Before Hitler fucked it up, before Hitler gave it a bad name, you know?
Three Hitler eugenics.
There were good times, there were good times for eugenics.
Eugenics was pretty big in America for a while back in like the 20s and 30s.
You know, someone was just telling me, and maybe it was, I don't forget if it was you Digi, that Planned Parenthood was started to like exterminate black people?
Is that accurate?
Guys, I don't know about that.
I've never heard that before.
Someone was telling me that it was started, it was like a eugenics program.
I can't believe people want to defund Planned Parenthood.
The black birth rate.
Oh my god, yeah.
Nate, it sounds to me...
By the way, this is completely non-racial.
I just want the best of the best to continue to be the best of the best, and everyone who's shitty just go away.
Here, Nate, listen up.
It sounds to me like you're trying to develop some sort of standard that somebody has to pass in order to be able to commit suicide,
but the truth of the matter is, there's only one thing that every single person who has committed suicide has in common,
and that's that they wanted to commit suicide.
That's the only standard that there needs to be.
No, I disagree, because I think you can paint a picture.
How can you disagree with that?
That's the only thing.
Okay, that's fine, but I'm talking about how to decide, but you can paint a picture.
You can't deny that people, most of them are stupid and don't know what they want.
So, if you want to kill yourself, why not?
Yeah, I think we're undervaluing free will.
Because if I get entertainment out of you being here, I'm talking to you specifically, and no one's allowed to kill themselves because I'm the only person who matters!
Yeah, but if we've already established that there's no objective point of the universe, that it's all pointless, then who fucking cares about that?
I mean, Tom, Tom is talking about free will and all that, but will Tom, we already have restrictions against, you can't do things that hurt other people or hurt other things.
We know that suicide does cause damage to other people and society.
So we should make it illegal to die at all then.
It already is illegal.
Yeah, it's illegal.
Not allowed to get hit by a bus, not allowed to die at all days, not allowed to get cancer.
I think the only reason that suicide is illegal right now is because it was a conspiracy by the church back in the day to keep the money rolling in,
because everyone was miserable back in the few days and they're like, well, Jesus said you can't kill yourself,
so you have to keep paying or give us money.
I'm open to an evaluation of the law.
That's perfectly fine with me.
I have no problem with deciding that, but this is what I think.
I just think that everyone is a lawyer or a soldier of humanity and that you have to submit a proposal.
Even if your system was implemented and even if there was an objective evaluation, it's like, your life is good enough that you don't have to die,
because I'm pretty sure if I was subjected to this objective measurement, my life would probably be good enough.
But it's not about what my life is, it's about how I perceive those things.
Your perceptions are guided by emotions, not by logic, and I think the decision to kill yourself is not technically a logical one,
because it's not about how your life is, it's about how your life feels, how you feel.
Dude, that was the first thing I said.
The first thing I said is that it's based on determining how the person views their own life,
and if they're suffering at a significant level, then they should be allowed to kill themselves.
Why can't they be the determinants of that?
Because I do not trust people to make this decision.
Well, it's not your decision to make.
Nate, I have a counterpoint, a pragmatic counterpoint to your thing.
People who are killing themselves, largely it's because they're depressed and sad,
and people who are depressed and sad often are not very productive to society anyway,
they're just sort of existing in life, they're doing a menial job and they're just sort of slouching around
and not really adding much to society.
I think the fact that we have a population problem, like there's too many people on the earth for the resources,
I think if people who are not really doing anything except existing in a sad state kill themselves,
it doesn't really affect society as much as somebody who's really productive and great for everyone,
like someone who's really making a lot of good things happen.
If you're arguing for eugenics, what's the worst thing that people who want to fucking kill themselves
and don't do anything, shouldn't they be fucking gone?
When I say I want eugenics, I'm talking about the future as in what we should do to breed people selectively,
not killing anybody.
But why are we talking about how it affects society as a whole?
That doesn't fucking matter.
It's not a social question at all.
It's about the individual.
Like always, this conversation has gotten way too big and broad as all of our conversations do.
We need to bring it back.
The fact is, I want less people on the planet and I especially want less depressed people on the planet
because depressed people are fucking annoying.
This is an objective fact.
I think that in general, we give way too much benefit of the doubt and leeway to depressed people
or people who quote unquote suffer from depression or are suicidal because nine times out of ten,
they're just insufferable assholes.
And like, you can't help a depressed person.
You can't tell them anything.
Depressed people don't fucking listen to anything.
They just want to be depressed and they want to drag everyone down with them.
So I think that they should, you know, if you want to kill yourself, please go away and do it.
And I want less people in the world.
Now see, when we colonize Mars, we're going to need those people to ship off,
to just take up space there and build things.
We're going to need this extra population.
I don't want them to just die.
We need these human capital.
We'll have all robots to do it.
And then the robots will get depressed.
So we need people to build the robots.
Can we transition into the mumkey suicide pool?
Everyone will become robots and then we'll be, and then we'll be all,
the only thing we'll have to worry about is how cute our robot designs are.
And we can design cute robot designs.
I would like to be a little sphere with a little eye, like a thick camera in the front.
Shout out to Near Automata with the cutest robot designs of all time.
Now I do have to say to transition us.
Sorry.
Yeah. Did you guys still want to do the mumkey suicide pool to predict how and when I'll kill myself
and whoever is closest to like,
podcast just to prove a point.
That's right here.
No, we have to announce so they know so that everybody knows.
I'm putting all my money down.
I'll put.
No, I meant that was my guess.
He's going to kill himself.
All my money down, dude.
That you will never do it.
I don't have any money, so I'm just going to put my name on it.
I think everybody should put in like 20 bucks.
I would put down $100 that you never kill yourself.
Oh shit.
Yeah.
Going all in.
It's a pretty bold guess.
It's going to take a long time for you to,
to, to cash in on that one.
That's fine with me.
Because see, as long, every moment that I, that continues to be the case,
I'll just feel like I'm winning.
So it's an extra boon to my day.
I can't let Nate win.
I have to do it now.
I'm putting, I'm putting $100 on age 42 by way, by way of, by way of God.
That's very specific, but that's the most popular way anyway.
Yeah.
I don't, I don't know.
It's, it's, it's weird to, I don't, I don't want you to die.
It's not good.
But if you had to guess logically.
You don't have to participate in this.
I can make all the money and like, if my only competition is Nate,
I'm just commenting on the idea that we're, we're, you know, just even discussing it.
Yeah.
I don't like it.
Okay, Jess.
I'm going to put it, I'm going to put it all on, you know, whatever age you are currently
suicide by arguing with me in the chat too much.
That's pretty much already happened.
Just so everybody knows it, I will be cashing in on this at Mumkey's funeral.
I will be hitting you all up while you're all crying over his casket.
Actually, you know what?
I, I'm not going to cry over Mumkey's casket.
Come on.
No.
I don't think Jess would even bother to come.
I'm going to, I would come.
I, someone would have to pass out like the party.
Yeah, you'll come when you hear that I'm dead.
Actually, I'm going to put it all on that Mumkey will never commit suicide.
I don't think he's got the balls to do it.
You can't copy me.
He's calling you out.
You see these, they know, they know you're all, you're all talk, Mumkey.
You're all talk.
He's all talk.
Very little gunplay.
What's even your history with guns and ropes and.
There's only eight of these here.
So did you guess 42?
I don't believe you've ever seen a rope in your life.
Did you down for age 42, Tom for right after this podcast and everybody else says never.
Yep.
I don't say anything's so basically definitive.
So are we basing this on like whoever's closest?
Like if you kill yourself at like 30, does Tom win?
But if it's at like 38, then I win.
No, Tom is so specific with immediately after this podcast that I think if I do it tomorrow, did you still wins?
It's got to be like the closest without going over like prices, right?
Okay.
Can I bet that I will kill Mumkey?
Yeah.
Go ahead.
Of course.
Assisted suicide like Sigmund Freud.
So if we're done with that, I do have one other suicide related topic I wanted to address to the panel if that's okay.
If you could force any person.
I'm just thinking about me showing up at your house on your 42nd birthday with a stool and a rope and being like Mumkey.
I need that hundred dollars.
I need that 500 bucks.
If you could force, and this is going to seem weird with the word suicide, but if you could force any living person on earth to commit suicide, who would it be and why?
And you can't say Ben St. That's too obvious.
Just one?
Yeah, just one.
Oh boy.
You got to pick your prime target I guess.
That's like Sophie's choice for me.
Trying to decide which person should die.
I'm surprised you didn't go straight for the Trumper just to make all your...
He's going to be out of here eventually.
No, too many people would be happy about it.
Yeah, they don't deserve to be happy about it.
Is that your standard for things that are likely to happen?
If so many people would be happy, it just will not happen.
It's not going to happen.
It's good. It won't happen. I know that much.
It's fucking John Tron.
John Tron!
Agreed.
What the fuck?
Just to make the paid stop for the rest of us.
That would be good. I would like that.
No, I would not like that. I mean, I wouldn't like anyone dying except someone I don't know.
So just some random guy I don't care about.
I'll force him by...
I'll find a pen pal and then force him by writing him a note saying,
kill yourself and hopefully he'll do it.
I've got one.
I can think of a few people but I don't want to name them on stream because it would just be cruel and controversial.
Because they're all real.
No, but I can think of several like real people who I've interacted with that I'm like,
if he was dead I think we'd all be better off.
Commenters and like anime avatars on Twitter right now who I wish would die.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, yeah. I'd force anime to commit suicide.
Anime.
Nobody's going to opt out for David Clegg?
I want him alive. I need more Clegg. I need more of the circus in my life.
No one fucking cares about egg.
Egg?
There was this very...
You know, there's people in my life who like I wouldn't want to commit suicide only because I would want to kill them myself.
Right.
Like put my hands around their throats and watch the fear in their eyes as the light leaves them.
This is like a death note essentially.
It's like a death note. You make them hang themselves.
It's like your, you know, the scenario is that the person you want to be dead you just hear about them.
Oh, you hear that guy committed suicide and you're like, huh.
Like that would be most of the time it would be the, you just go, huh, yeah, well.
I think good.
Back to watching anime or whatever.
Like it's just, it wouldn't really be much of an event.
There's a few people I know of who I would like it if they committed suicide and it's not unlikely to happen.
So like, I feel like this is not even a hypothetical. I'm going to experience this in my life.
Thank God.
Is it me?
Is it Maddox?
No, Maddox doesn't seem suicidal. That dude's full of himself.
Hmm, yeah.
So nobody's opting for like people who are running prisoner of war camps or like ISIS leaders.
I don't know any of them. I don't know who they are.
Well, the thing was, I don't have to know their names.
Someone's just going to step in and take their place.
How would you be able to pick the one guy out of all those like big targets that would make a difference?
There's some research. There's like one modern game stalling.
Like if you kill, like it's like if you kill Trump, you just end up with Pence as president. Nothing changes.
I wouldn't kill Trump.
If you kill anybody in a position of power, there's just going to be the guy under them who does the same thing.
There is one person, there is one person who I think would make a significant difference if he died.
I think if Vladimir Putin died, Russia would lose a lot of its strength, which would reduce its influence on the world,
which might put America in a better position.
There's no change over here. Fucking risk. I'm talking about risk.
The kinds of people I'm thinking of are more people who are just drains on society, who are not offering anything
and are only causing problems for people, and if they were gone, it would just literally make everyone involved's lives better.
Doctor Wolf is the one. There he is.
Well, you know, you say that, but he's such a psychological fortress of a man that there's nothing you could do
to make him ever commit such a self-harming act.
I hope he doesn't hear that, even though I don't really care about him.
Somebody will go tell him that I wished that he would be dead.
I'm convinced that everyone on my Kingdom Hearts video saying that they understand the fucking story better than I do
is actually just one guy on multiple accounts, so if that guy died, it would really make my life much better
and we could stop pretending that there are people who understand Kingdom Hearts better than me.
I've done the research people. You don't get it. You do not understand.
God, the things, they don't, they say these things like they get it, but they don't.
We're on that topic of commenters, because this is not a commenter cast.
Any fucking person who fucking starts tweeting at me and starts hurling insults and trying to piss me off
and then when I insult them back, they tuck tail and act like I'm harassing them.
Anyone who's ever done that, you should definitely fucking kill yourself.
You see, it was just some banter on the internet.
It was just banning you. It was just a joke.
Me and Hipple were saying how we need to do a Twitter rules PCP at some point.
It gets to the point where it's becoming a thing.
Yeah, I guess. It could be a bit different from commenter rules, because it's slightly different.
It's basically the same thing, though.
I mean, we can use it to bring up things that we didn't mention in commenter rules originally, so there's things to discuss there, I'm sure.
Speaking of Twitter, Nate, do we have any Twitter questions for this episode?
Well, hold on. I don't want to wrap us up yet.
I thought we were off topic so much that suicide was dead.
We killed suicide. We did a great service.
We've talked a lot about suicide as a social construct and the broad sense of whether we do it,
but again, everyone laughed off when I said this earlier, but I do find suicide really fascinating,
just in the sense of it as an idea.
It's just something to think about a lot and to find an interest in.
I guess because it's death.
I mean, what is more interesting in the world?
I think I honestly legitimately think killing yourself is the bravest thing you can do.
I'm not saying that I want to believe it.
Tom, have you ever asked out a girl before?
I've asked out multiple women. I've never killed myself,
so I feel like I just proved my own point.
Yeah, that's true. Fair point.
It's not easy. Death is the one thing a living person cannot experience.
It's the most mysterious thing in the world.
I think people should have a right to kill themselves, I guess, but I don't think it's brave or courageous in any way.
I think there's a difference in saying it's brave versus courageous.
Something that gets you to be celebrated, but I think considering human beings
and all living things are programmed on an instinctual level to try and continue to survive
so they can pass on their seed and shit and procreate,
I think to stare at that face instinct in the face is like, no, fuck it, and do it anyway.
We're also programmed on an instinctual level to rape.
Does that mean I'm courageous for not rape?
Oh, I guess you're right, it does make you courageous.
Hippo, to go back against what you just said.
Every day that I don't rape, I give myself a pat on the back.
I'm a brave fucking man for not raping all the people I want to.
I would guess that there are millions of people on earth right now who have attempted suicide,
so we can't say that there are no living people who haven't tried to kill themselves.
No, I would never say that.
No, I wasn't saying that. I was just saying that the reason that he finds it fascinating,
the reason I think about it a lot as well, and Victor does as well,
he likes suicide thinking about the implications of it and what would happen.
It's interesting because nobody fucking knows, nobody could tell you what happens afterwards.
It's just like the most untapped, the bravely go where no man has gone before while they have,
but they didn't come back.
I guess it's like, because the two things that fascinate me the most are suicide and immortality.
I guess it's because both of them are exactly that.
They're both the unknown.
They're the two things that I assumably could never know,
because if I think, okay, I'm going to live for, let's say, 70, 80, even 100 years,
I can completely predict what I'm going to be doing in that time.
I can just say, oh well, for the next 80 years, here's what I meant 80 in total,
not 80 from today on.
If I think about it that way, it's like, well, I can kind of understand where technology seems to be going,
where the world's going to be going.
I'm going to eat, sleep, and shit.
That's going to be my life.
I'm going to keep doing what I've been doing for the last 25 years, for the next 60 years,
but if I killed myself, it's a total unknown, and I'm assuming there'll just be nothing,
but I don't know what that's like.
If I lived forever, that's also a total unknown.
I don't know where the eventuality is going to take us.
I guess that's why those two things are so interesting, is that it's just a different world to think about.
The closest I've ever come to killing myself was the other day when I was reviewing my 401k account
and realized I'm already planning for retirement and the end of my life,
and just thought, my god, my life is all mapped out.
There is nothing new to be discovered here.
That's when I was really like, there is no point in my existence, but then I pulled it back in.
I think the most interesting thing you could do instead of killing yourself,
if you're like, oh, nothing new is going to happen,
is just to take all your money and go fly somewhere that you don't know and just go to a total weird place.
I guess that's what a midlife crisis is, is that realization?
That does bring up one of, I think, the most useful things to anti-suicide sentiments that I've heard.
I don't know how well it actually works as a pick-me-up because I've never been suicidal,
but I imagine if I was, it might help.
You said something about your life being mapped out,
but of course it really isn't just because you're planning for your retirement or whatever.
It reminds me of a line on Game of Thrones when Tyrion says that he prefers life to death
because life is more full of possibilities than death.
Like, anything could happen tomorrow.
And it also, you know, a similar sentiment I saw once on like,
it's like a 4chan meme that gets passed around a lot of like a guy arguing against suicide.
And he, just like random anon, he raised a really interesting point.
If you're at the end of your rope and you want to die, then obviously you don't give a shit about anything anymore.
So why not just fucking do something? Anything?
Go out and live. Go get on a plane and go somewhere and start a whole new life.
Instead of ending your one life, just end it in the sense that you're starting a new life.
Go spend all your money on a plane ticket or some shit.
It's funny to bring this up because I was going to say that.
A lot of times when I think about killing myself, it's like,
oh, maybe I could just like go like full ham and just do whatever the fuck I want.
If you have nothing left, just build something new.
Instead of just pulling the trigger.
Makes sense.
I feel like that's just like the long way of killing yourself.
I think the biggest reason, I think most people who kill themselves when they're relatively young
do it because they feel trapped.
They feel like they can't reasonably escape this situation,
but they usually haven't explored other options or just don't understand the other options.
Because kids are fucking dumb and they don't know anything.
You know, I think the best way to kill yourself is the long way,
with drugs and alcohol and fast food and living.
Yeah.
If you want to die, if you want to die so bad, just wait.
Yeah, you'll get there eventually.
And you might have some fun along the way if you stick with it.
You never know.
I didn't want to present too much of an anti-suicide message in this podcast
because this is the suicide podcast,
but ultimately I think that the only kind of suicide that seems reasonable to me
is when you're old.
When you're really old and you just physically can't do it anymore
or if you're like, you know, if I was in a situation where I...
If you're like crippled or like you're covered in like severe burns,
like someone said your mom was really fat or something.
If I was trapped in a body that could not move or express myself in any way
and was just trapped there, emotionalist, I would want to die.
I would not want to continue that.
Pull the fucking plug on me.
But like, if I always think, as someone who calls myself a gonzo journalist,
I always think of Hunter S. Thompson, who killed himself when he was in like his 60s.
And he had said that...
He had said that like he always thought of suicide as empowering
because it's the one thing he absolutely had control over in his life.
He got to decide whether or not he dies.
And so he didn't...
I mean, he held on to it for a long time.
You know, he lasted until his old age
and then he was finally at a point where he was like,
well, I did it.
I mean, the guy, he had plenty of money.
He did lots of things.
He went around.
He did every fucking drug known to man,
fucking, you know, drink every kind of alcohol he got.
He did all the...
He did the fucking love Ebo Hem lifestyle.
And finally by the time he was 60, he was like,
yeah, I guess that's it, you know, checked out.
And I'm like, yeah, cool.
You know, 60 years is a pretty good amount of time.
It's a good book-ended career of life, you know.
Fuck retirement.
Retirement sounds like hell.
I never want to stop doing bullshit.
What is retirement, but just like waiting to die?
Exactly.
That's exactly what it is.
I mean, if you can do it in cool ways,
like my parents are getting ready to retire
and they've saved up a ton of money
and they're gonna like travel and do things.
I don't even see that as retirement.
Like, you know, like there's retirement from your job,
which means, which can just mean I go out
and start, I don't know, building things in the woods,
build a log cabin in the middle of the woods
and live off the land.
That sounds badass, you know.
But like, if your retirement is like sitting in a home
literally doing the same thing every day,
like playing bingo and waiting to die,
then like fuck it, you know?
If your retirement is doing all the shit
that you wanted to do for like 50 fucking years
and only now you can do it, cool.
I guess that sounds great, yeah.
Yeah, that's legit.
That's arguably better than what you were doing
the previous 20, 30 years.
Yeah, though I think people have an intrinsic desire
to feel useful that can be a problem
when they retire or something.
You know, Nate brought up a point about
feeling like people shouldn't kill themselves
because on some level you do owe the people around you something
and everyone kind of shed on it,
but I don't really disagree with them.
And I was thinking, I mean, I do think that,
you know, that generally most people should kill themselves
because most people are bad.
And I definitely would not want to discourage any piece of shit
from killing themselves who wants to go for it.
But, um, and I do think that it's selfish of people to say
you killed yourself that's bad for me because you made me sad.
But on the other hand, you know,
I do feel like maybe you could have someone who depends on you
who you don't even realize depends on you
because you don't know who you're affecting.
You have no idea the ripple effect.
And I actually have a counterpoint to my point
about how everyone should kill themselves
because I actually have a personal experience with this
and now when I was four years old,
my brother committed suicide.
And, you know, shit, I, uh,
I don't know, I think about it sometimes,
like how would my life be different if he were still around
because I didn't know either of my brothers
because one of them died and the other one was so messed up from it
that he sort of drifted off.
So, you know, is it fair to me that I didn't get to know him
or either of my brothers?
You know, maybe that's why I didn't know my dad as well.
You know, he didn't, I don't fucking know.
So, maybe he had a responsibility to me
and he checked out too early.
I'll never know.
I know how old he was at the time.
Uh, he was fucking 17, I think.
I agree with you here.
It's pretty young.
Like, when Nate was saying this stuff earlier,
I was thinking of it more in terms of just your parents
and that, like, that idea that society gave you things
but you didn't necessarily want it.
But in terms of responsibility, I do think that, like,
I always got pissed off.
There was this book called The Awakening
that we had to read in school.
That was, like, this feminist book about...
Oh, the feminist bit? Yeah.
I have that on my fucking shelf.
It's about this woman who...
It's her favorite book.
I hate it.
It's about this woman who basically is unsatisfied
with her life.
She's got, like, two kids.
Her husband's cheating on her.
She, I think, cheats back on him, but it doesn't...
She ends up killing herself at the end.
And I just remember reading it
and, like, the way they present it is, like,
her suicide was empowering or something,
like, that she took things into her own hands.
Smash that patriarch you do.
And I was, like...
You do kill yourself.
I was, like, you've got two fucking kids.
There was no way I could possibly respect this decision
because those kids are going to be fucked
without a mom for the rest of their life.
There's definitely a thing about feminism itself,
because it puts, like, not just feminism,
but, like, a lot of SJW stuff is putting, like,
individual liberties over social health
and, like, the well-being of society.
And I don't agree with that at all.
I was just, like, you know what?
Your life sucks.
But live for the fucking kids,
because maybe they'll have an OK life.
If you got kids, if you chose to have kids,
you have a definite obligation to those kids
to not fucking kill yourself.
Yeah, but this takes place so far in the past.
I don't know if she had a choice.
I mean, we're...
OK, well, that's a real case.
We've all been presenting, you know, arguments for or against
your, like, why it's OK or why it's good or why it's bad.
But really, like most things that we talk about
on this podcast, the truest answer is the simplest answer,
which is that it's different in every single possible circumstance.
You can't say for sure that suicide is OK or not OK,
because it's different.
Some people are just shit,
and they deserve to be wiped off the earth
and they should kill themselves.
Some people don't have anyone,
and they know their life isn't going to get better,
so they can kill themselves if they want.
Some people, they don't even realize
that people need them around,
so they probably shouldn't.
You know, it's different everywhere.
And I just think that the true moral of the story
for everyone out there listening,
if you're suicidal or depressed,
is just stop being a faggot.
That's all there is to it.
It's not being a whiny little bitch.
Whether that means finally do it or not.
Yeah, exactly.
Whatever stop being a faggot entails, do that.
Whatever to you feels like you've stopped being a faggot.
Do that.
Someone in my life tried to kill themselves once,
and I never thought that they actually thought it through
in the slightest.
I just felt like they were just having a bad day,
decided to try to kill themselves.
Yeah, and people do do that.
Some people do, like, impulsively.
And I'm not saying this like that all the time.
I'm agreeing with you.
It's nuanced.
It depends on the situation.
I've known people who have told me stories
usually from their teenage years,
because teenagers are fucking mentally retarded.
Stories of how they just impulsively said,
I want to die and just started swallowing pills.
People do that impulsively and not even think about it.
That's why it needs to be obstacles in the way
to kill yourself.
I definitely agree with you, Nate,
that you can't trust people to ever make the right decision
about their own lives or anything else,
because people are pathetic and stupid.
That's my main context.
Kind of think about it.
We didn't even ask this,
but has anybody in here attempted suicide?
Because I did.
I did.
That's true.
When I was eight, I tried the ultimate suicide.
Some of you have probably heard this story before,
but it was the greatest suicide attempt of all time,
because I was getting bullied at school
and I was really unhappy with it,
and so I was crying,
and I went up to my brother's shades room,
and he had this line of beanie babies all across the walls
that were held up with clothespins,
like these weird, fat clothespins
that had little nubs on them.
I was like,
alright, I'm going to suffocate myself,
so I put a clothespin on my nose
and then another one on my lips,
and I was like,
I'll suffocate myself.
Impressive.
Unfortunately, the clothespins were really painful,
and I couldn't, again,
low threshold for pain,
so I probably had them on for 20 seconds,
and I was like,
this hurts,
and I took them off.
A suicide attempt is a suicide attempt,
and they say that if you've tried it before,
you're more likely to do it again later,
and that knowledge has haunted me forever.
Don't give him any ideas.
He's addicted to killing himself with clothespins.
You know, I have often, actually,
now that I think about it,
I've often committed the slow draining spiritual suicide
of asking a girl out and telling a girl that I like her.
I think asking a girl out is the most fiery inferno
a man can put himself through,
trying to ask a girl out.
If you come through alive on the other side,
you are infinitely stronger than you went in.
It is the truest achievement of the Buddhist ideal
of destroying the self.
Exactly.
It doesn't exist anymore.
One time, I went outside in the cold,
and I had the idea to just go into the woods
and stay there until I died,
but I was too cold, so I went back.
That's exactly the kind of thing I would have tried to do,
or maybe even did and forgot, I don't know.
It sounds like a very familiar scenario to me.
I don't mean to diminish the seriousness of those,
but thinking about those examples,
I probably did try something like that.
You should diminish the seriousness of mine,
because it's hilarious.
Because it's an eight-year-old kid
putting clothespins on his fucking mouth and nose,
because he thinks he can kill himself that way.
My dad told me about one time when he was a kid,
he just held his breath,
because he was really mad at his mom,
and just would not breathe for like...
He turned blue and eventually passed out,
or gave up, or something.
Good effort.
Yeah, it was impressive.
That's what made his sperm retarded,
and resulted in me...
resulted in the best guy ever.
You just need a little bit of retardation
to balance out this incredible intellect.
You have to balance.
I got a pee.
Why don't you go, and we'll get to the questions,
and we'll see what's going on.
He committed suicide in the bathroom right now.
What if he just died?
Yeah, what a funny thing that would be.
That'd be a goof.
I pray that he does.
Twenty bucks that he does it.
Okay, here we go.
I pulled some of the questions out ahead of time.
Before we get to the questions,
I just want to make it clear that I hope
that nobody in this podcast dies,
or commits suicide,
because I think they're all...
I don't believe you.
Really smart and genius.
Even Mumki, who I hate like 40% of the time,
is a genius and a wonderful creative mind
who should live forever,
just like everyone is in this channel.
Jesse, did you wait to say that
as soon as did you was out a little bit?
Is that why?
I was going to make the same joke about Ben,
because he's not here right now.
Yes, well done.
Okay, let's get into these questions here.
Here's a goofball one.
Casey at CaseySnap asks,
if you had to pick a spirit animal,
what would it be?
Everyone's thought about this question.
I'd be a dog.
I got a dog spirit animal.
I think I know Hippo's answer.
It's a frog.
Frogs are cute and small and funny.
You weren't going to say that, you lying boy.
Oh my...
I just...
We've already...
Most of us already have an animal-like guy
associated with us.
I just realized that.
Walrus?
That's me.
I don't know what the question was,
but Walrus is my spirit animal.
What's your spirit animal?
Yeah, Walrus is my spirit animal.
Real quick, before we get too deep into questions,
while I was taking a pee, I remembered this.
I have some suicide advice for everybody.
All right, I'm taking notes.
If you...
If you want to kill yourself,
but to be able to leave money with your loved ones,
by taking out some kind of life insurance policy,
do it before telling anybody
about your suicidal intentions,
because I legitimately cannot get life insurance
because it says on my record that I have a history
with suicide attempts.
So, my dad...
It's good to know.
Yeah, my dad took out a big life insurance policy
on everybody else in the family,
but he tried to do it on me,
and they won't give me life insurance,
because they think that I'll kill myself.
How did they find out about the clothes pins?
Because I told that to my psychologist
when I was seeing him.
I think the solution here is to just not bother
the bureaucracy of trying to get life insurance.
Just go old school and bury all your savings in a chest
and give your family members a map.
I said them on a grand quest, little member.
Tighten all in one piece.
Endless justice family members from all over the globe
began the great age of fucking suicide.
And it never ended.
Yes.
Well, I did when everyone died.
Well, fuck this animal question.
I don't have an answer yet.
I want to be a fox,
because I'm clever and I'm mangy.
And everyone hates me because I'm stealing your chickens.
I want to answer two.
I think the obvious answer for me is monkey,
but I also have a great affinity for goats,
and I want to live at the goat tower,
so I wish I could be a goat.
Wait, I also like cats and dogs,
and lions and turtles and shit.
Monkey picking goats over sheep,
you fucking traitor.
It's like incest.
Hey, why don't we do a podcast about all the animals
that are cool instead of all this philosophical
fucking circle jerky bullshit?
That's when you said the last episode.
I want to fucking have fun with my friend
and talk about cool animals.
I don't like animals.
You know, really, the suicide cast
should have been an animal cast.
Who better to talk about suicide than Colt Corona
and fucking the hypocrite and the Tuscany Walrus?
An action-y draft who lives with a crippling disease
in the day of his life.
Who better than Brunswick,
who literally can't stop dying?
If you brought me on to an animal cast,
it would turn into a broad concept thing
about how plants also have different kinds of thought
that humans just can't understand.
Why do we care about plants?
What the walrus thinks about it?
Oh, I didn't need an animal cast.
I meant a podcast about animals.
I hate animals, except walruses.
They're cool.
We should bring back animal casts sometime.
Walruses?
They're the bad guy in Tusk.
There's a few other OK animals.
Reptiles are kind of cool.
Yeah, that's about it.
Demolition D's lizard's pretty sick.
I want one of those.
Hedgehogs are fucking sweet, bro.
I want to hang out.
I want to juggle hedgehogs.
I want to get a couple of hedgehogs together
and watch them have a real dilemma.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm talking about the hedgehogs dilemma.
Oh, god damn it.
The funniest part of that, and now it's ruined.
It got cut off.
I said I want to get a couple of hedgehogs together
and watch them have a dilemma.
Oh, yes.
It was better when it got cut off.
I could picture whatever funny joke I wanted.
There's a new pond in my back garden
and all the frogs have come back
and they're all...
like they're in pairs, one on top of the other.
Oh, man. Yeah.
Yeah.
That's the coolest thing about animals
is they just fuck all the time
with no... there's nothing...
there's no conversation about it.
There's no hitting on.
Every time I see...
that's the hottest thing about
animal girls,
like anime animal girls
is when they give them the one property
of animals that really matter
incessant desire to fuck with no prejudice
and that's the best part of those.
You can create an atmosphere like that
if you like...
but first you have to get a girl living with you
or move a bunch of black people into town
but you can't just go out in the world.
Just pick up some jungle sluts.
Yeah, you can't just go out and rape a girl
in the streets. I've tried it, it doesn't work.
That's the whole thing with the anime
cat girl, whatever, and then furries.
The furries have got it the wrong way around.
They got all the fur and the fangs
and stuff but they're just normal humans.
That's terrible.
They are the worst of both worlds.
Digi's point, the minks in one piece
there's like this thing they do called
garchu, they're the animal people.
They just fucking rub everyone all the time.
They're up on each other all the time.
They're rubbing and touching and groaning.
The reason I brought that up is because I literally saw
a kimono friends dojin
yesterday that was about this.
This happened and I was like
I was just looking at it and I was like,
yeah, yeah.
The concept of touching
another living being is an extremely
attractive thing. The animals do a lot.
Well, except not other humans.
Anyway, let's move on to the next question.
Yeah, let's do that.
Other members of the species, we'll say.
Here's a fun one.
At Jbud
VA asks,
hey procrastinators, how do your families
respond to the type of content you create?
Do you feel they understand the full
picture?
No.
My parents don't really know anything about what I do.
They know that I make animations,
but they call
my Gibb and take a blog
and that's what they say.
I call my channel a blog.
I have a blog.
Gibbs is not like yours, Digi.
Gibbs is definitely more...
They don't watch them, they don't really know
what's going on.
I only tell my dad
the business side of things ever,
and he's really interested in that shit,
but he doesn't know anything about
any of this shit.
Nor does my mom.
Your grandma is in your videos,
and your mom
has been in one where she was
sloshed. How much do they know about it?
My mom refuses,
they know pretty much everything,
but my mom refuses to watch them
because she doesn't like it when I cuss.
But my dad actually is subscribed
to Mumkey Jones and Mumkey Jones too.
Yeah.
He's not subscribed to Mumkey's Countdown to Suicide?
He doesn't know about that one yet.
I'm hoping he doesn't find that one.
He's missing out.
I might have said this before,
but when he watches my Elliot Roger parodies
where I pretend to be Elliot Roger talking about
how lonely I am and I want to kill people,
he'll send me a text message
asking me if I'm okay,
so that's how they feel about it.
That's really cute.
It's not cute.
That's cute. It's funny.
It's hurting people so cute. I like that.
What do your parents think?
They don't really understand.
They're always just having to be like,
yeah, this is great, but when are you going to get a real job?
Yeah.
The one thing that kind of set the tone
for how they thought about it was that
when I got fired from my job in 2013
and I started Patreon
and I got money, the first thing they said
was like, oh, now we can take rent from you
and immediately took half my Patreon money
for the entirety of like two years.
Lol.
It's good when it pays them.
It's good when it gives them money.
Other than that, they just want me to take more money.
They didn't ask for rent when you had
a quote unquote real job.
Right. Okay, that's bullshit.
As soon as I got art money,
they were like, well, we need to crush your soul a little bit more.
It's like they felt the need to stop you from doing this.
We need to do a podcast
on the topic of parents and why they should
all be exterminated and should not exist
and should not be allowed to have any part
of anyone's life past the age of four.
Ben has a real good plan for this.
It's where we take everyone's children,
we harvest them, and we send them to a camp
where they're raised independently
with our best practices.
Parents are kept separate.
It's a different society between parents and children.
That's what happens.
That's what it should be.
My parents probably
just follow my stuff more than anybody
else is in here going about what I'm hearing.
They don't watch any...
What a surprise. Did you have a great life?
My parents...
They don't watch any of the anime content at all
because they don't know the first fucking thing
about anime and they don't care.
But my dad loves
showing people my videos, particularly
the ones that are about explaining
what anime is.
He'll always show people what is the appeal of anime
as his introduction
because my dad just really likes bragging
about me.
Virtually anybody who my dad...
I have the most autistic son
in the whole goddamn world!
It's really weird for me
because he shows my stuff to everybody
he works with.
When I go to my dad's work,
everyone there recognizes me
and knows things about me.
I don't know who any of them are.
It's always that weird disconnect of
everyone's looking at me like,
the rapper guy...
Now my parents are...
because the anime stuff is hard to explain to people
they'll just show them a video and be like
here you go, my parents don't watch a lot of it
but they do keep up with all the raps a lot
more because that's something everybody gets
is the music.
So my parents will...
They both follow my soundcloud
they both follow...
Generally, if there's a video
I actually think my parents will understand
I'll post it on Facebook
and I'll go, hey, here's one
for you guys.
Here's one that's not going to confuse
and terrify you.
I think on some level
they avoid watching a lot of the after dark stuff
because they know that it's stuff they shouldn't
see.
The stuff that's really going to make them
worried about me, I think they avoid
because
generally when my parents hear something
concerning about me, they bring it up to me
and I always try to downplay it as much
as possible. They'll be like, so we heard
you were
worried that you're going to kill yourself
in the next week and I'm like
it's a joke, it's a meme.
I'm fine, that was
three days ago. Totally different
guy.
So yeah.
What did your parents think of the Asperger rap on your soundcloud?
I don't think they heard that one
or they didn't bring it up because I don't think they knew
what the hell it was about.
My parents are not allowed
to see my family
is allowed to see anything I do.
I find it extremely disturbing
finding out that they've watched a video of mine.
I don't want it.
They don't deserve to.
I don't like them.
My father is the stupidest piece of
shit in the world and I don't talk to him
and so he doesn't deserve to see my videos
and my mother is a perfect
saint and so she especially shouldn't
see my videos.
Okay,
go on, finish.
Nothing, it just creeps me out.
Especially when I'm recording
and they hear me through the walls.
That actually makes me want to
kill myself.
That's the closest I come to wanting to not be here on this planet.
Anytime I'm recording
and I hear
what might be somebody
nearby in the house, I have to stop
and investigate.
When I'm in the kitchen at night
and I walk by the living room
and my mom and she's like,
when are you yelling about down there?
When are you telling me you sound like you're mad
and I'm like, oh my god, I want a shotgun
in my fucking, I want to put the fucking trigger
on my toe and go out like Hemingway.
I don't want to be here anymore.
Yeah, Digi, that's why
doing videos in this apartment
is the most,
I get a lot of anxiety from it because I share a wall
with some dumb bitch neighbor
who's always making noise.
She's gonna hear me yelling about
the pomp today, I can't wait.
Dude, next time you hear him fucking
through that wall, it'll be like my sister
is having sex with her boyfriend through that wall.
I'm making an Elliot joke.
Oh, okay, I thought you wanted me to jerk off
to the thought of incest.
Well, yeah, I mean that too, obviously.
That's not what Elliot did.
Well, wasn't he deeply disturbed by hearing his sister fuck through the wall?
I'm not wrong about that, Emma.
Yeah, because he was jealous that she was doing it so young
while he hadn't even had kids.
Because he was jealous that he wasn't fucking his sister.
Dude, I am so sympathetic
to your fucking plight of neighbors
because that's been my whole life,
my entire career
and now you finally
understand why I don't have
videos out every Monday
and have never had a schedule like yours
because it's goddamn impossible
when people barge into your house
and you can hear them stomping around
in the other rooms.
It's a nightmare.
I wish that everyone in my house were dead all the time.
Yeah, moving out of my parents' house
was the worst mistake
for my YouTube channel because at least then
I knew what their schedule was
and when I could record shit, but here
I don't know what the fuck this neighbor's up to.
Seems like she's home at the weirdest parts of the day
and then always making noise with her day ass music
and screaming at her boyfriend to stop hitting her.
It never ends.
People don't know, but managing your recording environment
is really fucking hot.
The worst ever was filming the horseshoe finale
and just because
there was so much setup. I had to fucking put on the costume
I had to set the stage up in the lights
and slip my hair back every goddamn day to sit there
and remember those long fucking monologues
and fucking have to... there was so much stress
to get it right because I don't know
I might only have 10 minutes to fucking film all this
this time. I might only get one shot
at getting this take right because at any time
there's gonna be a whole fucking nigger party parade
upstairs stomping around for the fucking teenagers
and 20-something
dopers and fiends up
up in my house making noise. It was a fucking
nightmare. And that fucking
maybe that
added to the rage in the video
so maybe it worked out for the best.
I gotta say there's no escape
from this either because you would think
that I have the perfect recording
environment. I have a super isolated room
way across from that. I know that you do.
I probably have the best you can get
but even here, first of all
recording during the day is really difficult
because there's constant road noise
because I live on a major road which
doesn't seem to affect these podcasts
too badly thankfully but like
I can't do like a serious recording
with that going on. But then
recently
after Trump's inauguration
for like two and a half weeks there was just
constant helicopters
for like seriously every day
for like six hours a day there were
fucking helicopters overhead and that's when I wanted
to launch all these vlogging series that I've been
doing all these daily weekly vlogs
and like I just wanted
to record like six vlogs in a row and it was
constant helicopters so finally I just made it
a joke in the video that
this is the only manga review show with a constant
thread of helicopter noise because there was no
avoiding it.
Fucking Trump suppressing
free expression god damn it
by way of
just by way of increased
helicopter traffic yeah
he's crafty that one he's crafty
okay what else questions we got here
how about um oh here's one
uh by at mighty cleffa
I think you've taken a question from her before
um what's the favorite piece of
fan art you've received and Jess I know
you're a big enthusiast for the fan arts
oh man there's too many great fan arts
to even to even remember her name
I just recently got that great one of
me as like fat Kamina which
was beautiful I make a better Kamina than me
that was the most perfect thing I ever seen in my life
I did love the fatness of it
that was beautiful and then like someone like
then like it took off like a meme and more
people like immediately started drawing me
as Kamina so I just you
I just you surfed that from you yeah me and
cold corona uh boozy it'll fade
it'll fade I'm sure it will
but there's always more there's always new fan
art to spring up it's like the gift
that keeps on giving is that uh that
dude yesterday just made me that cool ass
fucking it was that scene
in Avon Galeon where Misato finds out that Kaji
died and she cries at the kitchen table
and someone drew me in that pose crying at the table
yeah uh Ukrainian or whatever
yeah like this guy's been churning out fan art
at mock speed on like the fantasy
that was shit yeah he's even made shape over
uh fan art I think shape over
is more than me now I deeply
appreciated that one especially because it's like
such a like a weird specific
like frame of animation
in the show that like no one would get the reference but me
so no one would see how cool it was
but it's super cool and then there's this guy
there was one guy who followed me for a while called spider
who kept drawing like panel cast
fan art of like stuff that I dreamed about in the panel
cast he drew me like nice he drew me
that um as like a wireframe res man
like flying through my dimension of comics
which was to my fucking
radio head music playing
like I'll just describe these inane things on the panel cast
because I'm usually like insane
for screaming about comics
and he'll just draw me his stuff and it's cool
I got so much cool fan art I got the best fan
arts in the world every fan
is bad except for the one to draw shit
that's my agreed we can all agree on that
I I really
like that fan art by that person
who drew me in a dress
with Nate oh that one so that's
um that's princess or
I forget her name but yeah princess something
oh I love that so much thank you for doing that
yeah she was scared to post it but I'm glad that she did
yeah like she didn't want
to post it I so I just asked her in the in the
discord like hey you mind if I post this I'll even credit
you but she said no but now she's
saying it was really good and she should have been great
it's great it's great yeah good
job and although
the poddy curse wanted posters are great
I there's I've got
there's lots of fan art it's just hard to remember
I okay did some really good
art of us as pirate boys oh yeah
you know that one so much fucking cool
shit she yeah she's great she's great
thanks Sammy
I like your arts
I appreciate
just I could not possibly pick
one because I've received like hundreds
and hundreds of renards for time
but I do love
I love that because it used to always be didgy
brony the character and he was very popular
himself and there's tons of great art
of that character but now that
people just draw me I fucking
love it like because they always draw me
with the shades and like
smoking or something or wearing my big
jacket and like that's my favorite
drawing me with the cool shades
the cooler the shades and the trippier
the artwork the more I enjoy it
there's a lot of people draw me like
like fucking evaporating
into a mist of colors or something
and I'm just like yeah somebody drew
a fan art of you and me didgy
um where like
they drew me in a tank top that
just said the word wrestling on it
and like
yeah I want to open a store
so I can print that shirt and sell to
people it's like
it's like the classic John Belushi college
shirt only you know retooled
my favorite kind of fan art
is anything to do with my Nuzlocke series
when people like draw the
the Pokemon that I have along with me
and I always play as a girl so they'll like
they'll draw the girl from the game
but with the monkey head
and ended that right
by having like the guest art so he gets
beautiful arts in his episode time
so I really like those
if you make those don't be afraid to send them
Ben drew a
monkey blowing up Charizard that time
or whatever oh yeah that's right
oh my god I forgot
the people they draw
Vriska when I asked for it I really like
people who do that go draw that
Vriska me and me and Vriska me
yeah I just asked for Florina
and there's colopsic you did it he's cool
I like him I like everyone
everyone's good yeah you know it's fun
don't kill yourselves if you draw
one of these days I'm gonna
just invoke an ultimate
power because I did this once before
in the early early part of the pony
days um a cousin
of mine was having a birthday
and her aunt like asked me if I could get someone
to draw her a pony oh see
so I like made a main channel video
asking for that and I got like
fucking like 50 to 100
of them or something it was like just a million
of the one I described and so
I've always known in my back pocket
if I ever like really need
100 of one piece of art
then I've got it there and I could just
unload this onto the world
and receive every fan art ever
so just everyone have your pencils ready
for when I have this need
oh yeah there was like a whole folder
full of fucking fan art
that I've gotten I like to try and save it
you know what sorry Tom I don't know
if you were gonna say more of that
do you have more to say about that
I mean I was gonna go but if you want to
finish your point go for it
well I was just gonna say that I remembered
that one of my favorite things that I completely
didn't expect at all
that's been happening recently is people
fan art of my fucking stories
like I got a bunch of fan art of
Tales from the End of the World
when I released that and then
I've gotten a lot of it for
this anime idea I had
for a show called Omar that I just made a video
like describing this show and then I got a bunch
of fan art for it and I was like
it's brought it to life now like I didn't have
a vision of it in my head and now I do
so that's very cool
that is great I was gonna say
I got a ton of fan art like I got some good
ones from Idol Yo-Kai from like
about a year ago Twisted Prism
did a couple cool pieces my favorite pieces are
when people do art of my characters
like yeah I don't matter
they matter so
that's the coolest thing I'm always excited
lives matter I'm excited vicariously
to see Sorceress Lost Fan Art
whenever I see it
me too hey I want
to give a shout out to everybody who drew
pictures of my like my one
piece OC character that I described in that
episode of the potty cast a while back
about the umbrella and the thing those were
all great because I've been saying
in the episode like for years I've wanted
people to draw this character because I can't draw
I can't make a real I need someone else to do
it at what one day I'll get
the the guy who did the Steins Gate art
and the Black Rock shooter artists to draw
that's my dream I want that guy to draw it
I don't remember at all
but everybody did that
I'm surprised we haven't seen
any fan art yet of Don Bracken
from the triflers
yeah I'd like to see
all the triflers characters chilling out in that basement
there's less probably like mental connection
between like a book character and like drawing
fan art of them you know what I mean
maybe something like that going on
I don't know it feels like there's a big gap
in the artistic mediums there
usually with a book character you need
like at least one canon
image before people will start
I mean I don't know people drew a bunch of art
of my story and fewer people
read that than read monkeys so
yeah you're an anime boy
more I don't know I think
it'll happen we just got to we just got to put
the seed of people are still trying to read
yeah if you say it right now people
will try just request it right now and
you'll you'll get some shit if you get
I mean I think only 20 people have actually
finished it so what's the chance is that one of those
20s and I'll try a fan art when I finish
it but it's just so agonizing
to read
by the way I also want to say
I love people have drawn me with my wife
who's a bunch of times historically those are all great
my favorite one was that like one day
I was just talking on Twitter about like how
much I love jury's design from the new
Street Fighter 5 and that leather tit covering
is like the hottest thing ever that like skin suit
and like and then somebody
drew just like a picture of me with all my wife
who's but it wasn't just the ones for my banner they
included jury in that and I just thought
like this person really pays attention to
what I'm saying and gets it so whoever that
was that big best guy ever thing
that I love that and then I also want to say
I looked up the person who did the
the picture of you and me
on the you know like the wedding dress or whatever
given that was Uppity Princess at
Drowsy Apricot yeah thank you that was great
I think the fan art I get the most excited
about is always when it's something very specific
when it's like I wasn't done
I also want to say Drowsy Apricot
you are super cute you should
come over to my house sometime
so we can get together and hang out
and do just what men and women
do you know when they're alone together
so there you go call me
sex with the young
24 she's not that young
she's too old
10 years too old or so
I'd say but too old for the channel anyways
what's the next question we wrapping this up
one more maybe
three questions yeah you know
are there any good ones that are worth reading
here's a question that is about
what our plans were
for the first
secret episode or the
what's the word I'm looking for
how I spoiled it
can I read this do we want to spoil
I already did
we should
the first bonus episode
go ahead read the question
I was just going to read their question
at mystic the
myself music too asks
will you ever do Shrek vs Harry Potter
the answer is finally yes
for the first bonus episode of the PCP
we are going to do Shrek vs Harry Potter
people so if you want that shit
go give us five dollars on Patreon
so you can fucking see it there you go
go do it everybody
we'll find out once and for all what's better
Shrek or Harry Potter
so you could interpret that way
I was thinking about it in terms of like a battling
as well like who's going to win
Shrek and Harry Potter
we're going to explore every possible
way that this could be taken
on this podcast so make sure you give us
five dollars or else your life is
worth who's a more powerful sidekick
donkey or Hermione
doesn't Harry Potter
fight like an orc in the first Harry
Potter book he's like in the bathroom
oh we're wasting all of our good
material guys no no don't
don't stop everybody stop this has been a preview
one final question there's
one final wrap-up question which
really is kind of actually the touchstone that we should
have addressed in this episode long ago
and this was by who else but idle yokai
asks should I kill myself
to reunite with my waifus
yes yes 100% that's
the best reason to kill yourself
every time I look through the news
I can see all the
caions over there and I hear the beat
from the song paradise by
me and endless Jess and blind sky watcher
playing in my head and I'm just like
that's that's there's the real one
that's the real paradise over there
this three-dimensional shell that we're
trapped in just holds our 2d self
we have to set it free from this
prison of a body that we live in by
killing yourself so there you go
one day and that's it
that's that's all all the good questions
keep sending questions people at tbcrasnators
send them every time send them every day
but especially on Saturday people the most
important thing of all before we wrap up
this episode
I'm crapping my pants
oh no
again
I can't believe the consistency
of this man's shit
it's so thick
and so common
goodbye everyone
we've done it thanks everybody
for watching guys tune in next week
goodbye