Hey guys, Digibro here, coming at you from my bedroom. Just doing a little vlog update, you know, to tell you all about the new Procrastinators podcast episode that just came out.
You probably know that, cuz you're watching it!
Hey, you better start believing in Procrastinators! You're in orbit!
Bestie boy, yeah.
So anyways, you know, I'm having a nice day.
When I stand on soap, I'm the slip-o-crit.
He is drunk hobo, you know, in my room.
You know, just making fun sense, throwing it out there, you know, just whatever.
But, you know what, I'm not gonna hold up your time too much.
Just subscribe to my Patreon, and give me money for my vlogs.
Another day, another dollar, another night to make a whole holler, a popper cherry, then I pop my collar!
So I can keep doing them?
I'm a vlogger now.
Send me money.
The vlogging channel, over time.
Well, you know, I've already revolutionized YouTube time and time again.
I've already been the best.
I decided it might be fun to take a stab at it.
Yeah, take a stab at being the worst.
Well, that's kind of what we're gonna discuss here.
Like, vlogging is something I think that all of us were kind of like, not at...
Like, we all sort of saw it as like a lesser form of entertainment back in the day, and now we're all doing that.
I still do, but there's value in it as well.
It's just a tool, it's one of your tools in your toolbox, you know?
It can be very good, but the only good one is his whole channel is gone, so nobody knows what good vlogging is.
Which channel is gone?
This Fresnad is my favorite, he's the guy who got me onto YouTube because he was funny and he did vlogs.
And they were like comedy skit vlogs and they were great, but...
Did he delete his channel?
He deleted all his videos.
I think there's something to do with some weird scandal with Rapen.
I don't know.
I don't care.
I don't know whether he did it, if he did it, he cares.
He vlogged raping a woman.
That's gonna shut your channel down, okay.
Something happened.
He was the coolest though.
I feel like, I personally feel like in a lot of ways, vlogging and long form content are sort of where YouTube is going right now.
I think it's become a lot more normal to sit around and just absentmindedly watch fuckloads of YouTube in the way that people used to do for TV.
And I don't know, I feel like we're headed in that direction.
And you know, it's interesting, I totally agree, but it's interesting that YouTube provides such a variety of content.
There's so much more that you can get at any time and it's all available instantaneously online.
You really, you don't even need friends anymore in real life.
They're no longer required.
You can just watch PewDiePie or whoever.
There's so many little kids who are just like, PewDiePie is my friend.
Have you ever seen that comment?
That's like, be right back, PewDiePie, gotta go do my chores.
And it replies to it, okay, I'm back.
Yeah, it replies to it like, it's a live chat or a Skype or something.
That is my favorite comment of all time.
It is, it's great.
It's fantastic.
I love it.
That's YouTube.
But I think this is an interesting conversation specifically for us to have because Nate, especially you, were really down on like this kind of content for the longest time.
And now you're doing it.
I still am.
I still consider myself a crusader for what I consider high art.
And we've had our disputes about this for a long time about, I mean, Game Grumps was kind of the one thing because it's just guys talking about shit.
And you've always been of the opinion that quantity is a great thing.
And the more of it that you get, in fact, I was just watching your vlog about the anime seasons and how you're making an argument.
Yeah, which, I mean, there's, I actually agree with a lot of that.
But just the fact that we're getting more shows and more of them are good kind of as a consequence of that, it's likely you're going to get more good stuff out of it.
But I have a different view where I prefer the like, I'm the, I'm the, you know, old school dude who's into like, like the bebop, you know, 1998, whatever.
It's got like the best shows.
So, you know, like season.
That's value.
Yes, I'm trying to think of how to say what I'm going to say.
Well, Game Grumps is a great place to start with this, because I think that it's sort of at least viewing it from our perspective.
I don't know if this is true for everybody.
And, you know, there's other entire sections of YouTube that are probably completely divorced from everything we're going to say in this.
But like, I think for us, especially, Game Grumps was like the beginning of the end for this trend happening.
Like, it was the marker that this was coming, because we had like two creators who were mostly known for content that came out rarely.
You had, you know, Egoraptor, who did these animations that took fucking forever to work on, and these, these larger videos like Sequelitis,
which were like half animated, you know, filmic, fucking heavily animated videos, essays.
And then you had JonTron, who had, you know, the JonTron videos.
He's still doing that kind of content now that he's left Game Grumps.
But there are these, these, you know, videos that take like a month or more, sometimes multiple months to make and release.
And then both of them get together and start this channel that's two videos a day for a year, you know.
And the whole thing is completely unscripted, completely like almost unedited.
It's just them playing video games.
And it kind of revolutionized YouTube in a way, like, or at least for this sector of it.
Well, it was just a super clear example of like how you don't have to do it, you know, the old way.
But it was just that these guys managed to be so funny that they were still able to build an audience,
even without having to do all the things they had to do before, you know.
And I think YouTube really incentivizes and rewards this kind of content, especially now.
There's no doubt about that, that's for sure.
As it's moved into this rewarding, like, rewarding audience retention,
rewarding just the sheer number of views you can get.
Because if you put out, like, if you put out one video every month and it gets a million views,
and then you start up a channel where you release two videos every day and each one gets a hundred thousand views,
you're still going to pass that million-view video in, like, no time, you know, and make way more money.
And so, like, this kind of fast, I've made a fuckload of videos, you know, as opposed to one amazing one content,
is, like, rewarded.
And here's the question I have, Nate, though.
Like, here's what makes it so enticing to me.
Is this idea that 90% of the effort you put into a video is really only worth about 10% of what's great about it?
What do you think of that statement?
Um, well, that's definitely true.
You know, for me, just the way that I...
The kind of videos that I like best are sort of like the...
They're like stories in of themselves, you know?
They've got a narrative arc to them.
And so, I, you know, I'm always looking for that, like, that escalation and then the climax and then, like, the resolution.
That's what I like best.
And that really doesn't have to come in, like, a million-hour long video that takes months and months to make.
You're not getting anywhere close to as much out of that as you put into it, you know?
It's totally disincentivized and...
I don't know, man.
I don't know.
Ugh, God.
It's a struggle to admit, right?
It kills me.
It kills me that, I mean, it's entirely true.
You are in no way incentivized, and I've understood this now.
You're totally not incentivized at all to make long...
You're not incentivized to make the best video ever.
You're incentivized to build the biggest channel ever by producing the most content that people like in whatever way that you could do that.
And, uh...
The only other way that you can get big is being, like, the only guy making the best points about something, like, uh...
Every frame of painting.
He doesn't post that often, but, like, his stuff is very good, so people still like it.
That's true.
I mean, it's not impossible, right?
Like, Jon Tron did it, and he's just a funny guy who made, like, one video a month, sometimes with much bigger gaps.
Very near the beginning.
Yeah.
Very near the beginning, it was a lot more, uh...
A lot more frequent.
At least, uh, one a week.
I didn't see him in his early, early days, so I don't know.
What, a week, really?
Oh, okay.
He started just trying to do it one a week.
It was, yeah.
But, um...
But, you know, with really the conceit behind my whole attitude here, and you guys will probably totally disagree on this, especially you, Digi.
I, I have this idea in my head of, like, what will people, what is the most value for posterity?
What are people gonna, like, look back on and, and find the most value in?
And I think it's thing, like, like, you were saying, Digi, that this might be the best season of anime ever.
But, I mean, perhaps just by virtue of the market being so crowded, I don't think anyone's gonna look back on any show this season, including my favorite, which is the Iron Train thing.
Right.
And, and think of it with any kind of reverence as much as, like, I don't know, even something like Lucky Star, which is starting to wane in popularity, I think will be, like, more fondly remembered, and have more, like, impact overall.
I mean, it's really hard to say up until we get to that, you know, to that point, but, like...
Mm-hmm.
If that is true, then it, it would have been true for, like, that year that Lucky Star and Girl in the Gone came out, where, like, in night, like, you know, in my video, I talked about how in 1998 we had, like, Cowboy, Bebop, Lane, and Trigun.
Yeah.
It's like these three shows that, like, really survived, and everyone still knows about them.
Mm-hmm.
But then, 2007, you know, Girl in the Gone, Lucky Star, and, like, let's say, Darker Than Black, or...
Yeah.
Deno Coil, if you wanna talk about one that's not particularly popular, but really beloved.
Deno Coil is a good example, yeah.
Right.
Um, but that season had more shows in it than the entire year of 1998, you know?
Yeah, yeah.
Like, 2007, by then, we had, like, during the spring and fall seasons, we would have, like, up to 40 shows, and it was, like, half as much.
But, you know, to be honest, anime is a horrible example, because anime is so hard to make and takes fucking forever.
Right.
So, like, really, it's not even relevant to, uh, to the point we're making.
No.
Like, yeah, to get back to YouTube and to vlogging, like...
Yeah.
I think when you look at an ego raptor cartoon from the old days, like, you know, one of the just the awesome series, and, like, something like Awesome Reach, very quotable, very memorable.
Like, you've probably seen it a good 20 times.
And then, like, and so, it has that survivability factor.
But then, if you look at, like, a stretch of, let's say, let's say that Awesome Reach took five months to make.
Like, just spitballing random numbers out there.
I don't know how long it actually took.
In five months, you would get, holy shit, I'm trying to even math this out, because there's, like, 60 episodes of Game Grumps a month.
So, so you get, like, 600, no, 300 episodes, right?
In that span, I think.
I don't know, I fucking don't listen to my fucking math.
So, let's just say that number.
You get a shit load.
You get 60 a month, you get 60 a month, and that's times five, so 300.
I mean, I gotta say, I don't really remember a lot of the ego raptor cartoons.
I actually remember more, I more remember, like, perfectly hilarious games in Game Grumps or JonTron videos.
I'm watching a very inspirational video on Facebook right now about a chicken that was born with no eyes.
And that, I think, has a lot more artistic worth than anything on YouTube.
Any, any, all the videos, this is the greatest video ever made.
For what it's worth?
That video was probably of a chicken who didn't let being born with no eyes stop him from getting slaughtered and fed to the American population.
Oh, dude, it's snuggling with a dog and a cat, it's really cute.
It's probably a YouTube video that was stolen.
Oh, no!
Holy shit!
Anyways, in the span of those five months of Game Grumps episodes,
I feel like you will ultimately get as many great things as you would have gotten from that three-minute animation.
Where, like, I mean, if you were looking at, if this is the five-month span where all of Sonic 06 happened,
then the sheer number of great scenes and quotes from that, you know, the it's no use scene,
or the one where he just loses his fucking shit over Knuckles glitching out.
Glitching out? Yeah, but what is this?
Like, and I mean, those eventually became their, like, own works of art and that other people animated them and drew them
and they've been recreated a thousand fucking times, you know, and, like, been made into something else.
So, like, there's so much stuff that comes out of Game Grumps existence,
where there's so many animations and so many animators launching whole fucking careers out of it,
and, you know, and Egoraptor being able to use Game Grumps to fund other animations
and put the money into people who are doing more interesting shit than he is anymore, you know.
I mean, don't get me wrong, I think Game Grumps has gone downhill and it's shit now, but, like...
But are you saying that, like, the YouTube as a whole is just going towards this whole quantity over quality?
Well, not necessarily quality, but just quantity over not quantity?
Here's the struggle that I'm looking at right now.
Because I started suddenly, like, basically I watched all of Ethan and Ela's videos
and I really enjoyed that they put out, like, a video at almost every day.
It's fucking psychotic. It's like five times a week, at least.
I think since I subscribed to them, they've almost had a video every single day, which has been like two weeks.
They had a goal a while back to do five a week, I think.
Right. And they'll put out a video, like, every day, and they're basically just vlogs,
but they do have some editing, you know, some little jokes in there.
Sometimes it's not that funny and I'm like, okay, well, you know, you could tell they made this in a day.
It's not, like, that thought out, but then sometimes they can be hilarious.
But, like, I was watching all those and then I decided to start vlogging just, like, every random thought that came into my head.
And so I've released probably, like, 25 vlogs in the last week and a half.
Like, I've been releasing almost three a day, a lot of these days.
And, you know, I always had this mentality about, like, I felt the entire time I've been YouTubing, I've had one rule,
which is to never make a video that I wouldn't sit through.
Like, that's my number one rule. It's just never...
And how's that going now? Still keeping that up?
Yeah, it's still true. It's just that now I'll sit through anything, you know?
Oh, yeah, right, right. I remember you making that point on Twitter or something.
It was really watching Max Landis' videos because that dude will fucking...
Like, he vlogs all the time and the quality is garbage on his vlogs.
Like, he'll just open up his MacBook and just rant into the built-in camera and it sounds and looks like shit,
but he'll make, like, an interesting point and, like, that's enough for me, you know?
And he's such a fun character to watch because he, you know, moves a lot and has a funny way of speaking.
What are you gonna say, something?
No, I was gonna say he's a crazy nigger.
Yeah.
In my, um, in my lost flow.
Get a fucking haircut, Max! God damn it, your hair pisses me off so much! Fix your shit!
Yeah, welcome to the Max Landis.
I can't take you seriously.
Max Landis has a stupid haircut podcast.
I'm legitimately, I'm legitimately really fucking sick of it. It pisses me off.
Look at him. I hate it.
I mean, I know it started because he lost a bet, but, uh, he seems to be maintaining it.
Markiplier is doing the same thing.
Alright, you lost the bet, Mark. You can shave your head and start over now.
Just, God.
You look like shit! You look like shit!
He looks like a fucking...
Come on!
He looks like a weird animal. He looks not like a person. He looks like, like, like, if you put him in a suit, you'd be like, why is that clown wearing a suit?
It looks fucking...
That's right. That's right.
I hate it. I hate it. I...
He doesn't wear a suit.
He'll figure it out one of these days.
You
Not yet recording audio, interrupting everything, to tell you that the devil is coming, and the devil will be here.
Back on the subject of vlogging now that we've been interrupted by the devil monster.
Before I got interrupted by the Max Landis stuff, I was gonna talk about my, um, my last vlog.
I mean, I don't really do vlogs on Give and Take, uh, my other channel.
It's mostly just weird joke videos.
If you like that.
But you didn't happen to do one recently.
Yeah, I walked through a park and I talked about things.
One of the things I was talking about was how I'm trying to get rid of, like, remove a time wasting, not time wasting, but just things that eat up my day.
Like, podcasts and long form content that I do like.
I just need to stop listening to it because it's just taken up, like, too much time and I've got, and I'm a guy who's got to make stuff.
So as a YouTuber, it's not good for me.
I can't sit through all these didgy vlogs.
I've got to stop doing it.
You know, you know, this is a little bit unattangent, but I just remember this thing that Jesse said a long time ago that's like,
when you're a YouTuber, you literally never have time off.
You're always forcing yourself to be doing something.
You always got to be thinking about your next shit.
Man, it's so true.
Anyway, I'm sorry, Gabe, go on.
No, that was it.
Yeah.
That was it, okay.
You know what?
This sounds interesting.
I'm going to be on this and I'm not editing it just because I made it complicated, alright?
I'm editing it anyways.
Good.
Which I was going to edit the last one, but then Nate just kind of memed you into doing it and you accepted.
Oh, really?
Okay, I guess I'll never listen to Nate again.
I should have known.
Like, I was planning to just be the editor for these because I have the time to do it and then...
Yeah, that sounds like a good plan.
Here, get my headphones ready.
Are you recording David?
Yeah, I am recording now.
Okay, good.
Welcome in.
We're going to have Jesse edit in a rant as you for the part where you came in before.
Yeah, it's going to be great.
It's going to be great.
Why do you record some of it?
I recorded some of that part.
And this is going to be the rant.
Hey guys, it's me, the DeVoo.
This is my angry voice.
Wait, why are you no longer the DeVoo Collective?
When I get angry, I sound like this.
Of course.
I'm going to dig me a hole in the backyard and make a signpost that says, I don't like my friends.
It's going to be PCP Vlogs starring the DeVoo...
Jesse Englis Jess as the DeVoo.
DeVoo needs to record his own work on Friendship EP.
We should make a whole thing where we're playing each other.
Don't you know that the DeVoo Collective can use the voice of anyone I've absorbed in the world?
That makes sense.
Have any of you heard of the broken Friendship EP?
DeVoo, do you know about that?
I do not know what that is.
Oh man, I'm surprised you don't know.
I thought I would have brought it up in a podcast way back in the day.
Now is the reason to listen.
There's a way back, I was hanging out with my friends and they were pranking me.
I was trying to get to the car and they were pretending to drive away without me.
I've always really hated being pranked and stuff.
I was pissed off and bitter about it all night.
We recorded a song together and I wrote these really emo lyrics about hating all of my friends and called it the broken Friendship EP.
I continually would write songs of that nature about how I wish I didn't have to like people because then they just pissed me off and it hurts even more.
If I had to rank the top 5 things that make me mad the easiest, it's when I go away for one second and a million things have happened without me and no one even realized.
That's me every single night.
That is frustrating.
As soon as I go to bed, everything starts happening.
Poor guy.
It was really funny because I was thinking like, I thought DeVoo was here a minute ago but then you disappeared right before we discussed the entire topic of the thing.
And then I was like, well, he probably doesn't care about vloggers anyways.
Also, I just wanted to say, the first song that I ever created in my life was one time, me and my buddy John were taking Japanese in college and he didn't have his computer one night.
So we needed to use my laptop with its microphone to record this speech he had to give to his teacher, his sensei.
So the next day, when me and my buddies were hanging out, he was off in class, I remixed that speech into a song that I wrote which was just like, I just sampled like his voice and just repeated it over and over.
Man, it was...
That means I am cunt baby.
It was the best.
All of this is on topic.
We're basically just vlogging in the middle of this vlogging podcast.
This is a vlog.
Yeah, exactly.
No matter what we say, it's going to be on topic.
So what's been said so far?
That's the beauty of vlog.
What's going on?
We've just been discussing the idea that vlogging is taking over YouTube and basically all the stuff I said in my video about the future of YouTube.
But we're discussing whether or not that's a good thing.
It's a race to the bottom.
Well, there's so many things that just don't come out well when you write it as a script.
If you're really good at it, talking naturally has its own values.
Well, okay.
But if you're not good at talking naturally, which a lot of people are, especially at first, then it makes sense to...
Then don't vlog.
But if you do, then do.
Yeah.
Well, that's why it's great.
Vlogs are a great tool for people who are already popular or whatever because people just want more of you and they'll take whatever they can get.
Exactly.
And that's kind of what I want to get into now.
And especially with Davoo here, it makes this particularly interesting because he's involved with my channel.
Davoo's job right now is full-time editing for my videos.
And so I've been vlogging nonstop for the last few weeks and just pumping out all this content.
And the weird...
Here's the weird conundrum of it, right?
Like, those videos don't have the kind of guaranteed views that the stuff on my main channel does, even though a few of them have retarded extreme views.
Like, the one about the most boring-tasted anime.
Because of that sweet drama, baby.
Oh my God.
Ridiculous, right?
But here's the thing.
For a lot of people, like, the vlogs are now basically the...
This is like the main content in a way.
I just saw on that, like, on your video, like, it was nice when Digibro was the main channel.
Right.
No, he didn't say it was nice.
He just said, remember when Digibro was the main channel.
That's right.
You know the exact comment.
Yes.
But, yes, it made me laugh.
But I thought it was interesting because for the people who are watching the vlogs, like, and who are into them, I've put out, like, hours of interesting topics in the...
Even if only, like, one in five of them interest you, that's still five interesting topics, you know?
That, like, that maybe those videos aren't as rewatchable and they won't, you know, stand the test of time like you were saying that you, you know, want your videos to be able to do.
Yeah.
But they will put interesting ideas in your head and for most people, they only watch YouTube videos once anyways.
For most people, YouTube's more of a transient thing.
I don't think there's as many people who obsess over it as an artistic medium like we do and, you know, revisit videos over and over again that we, like, feel something about.
But, like, and even then, there's some people who re...
Like, I get messages all the time from people who say, like, I rewatched your insomnia analysis video ten times because I thought it was so interesting, you know?
Like, for some people, what we might view as completely random bullshit that we just do together might just happen to resonate with them even more so than, like, the stuff we actually crafted and put work into, you know?
Yeah.
But like you've said, I'd like to think that my stuff appeals to the niche of people that really appreciates it and then I don't give a fuck about the normies who don't even care about whatever, you know?
But that's, you know, that's just not as a successful model, numerically.
It's just, it's really interesting to me to have, like, where the main, like, conversations that I'm having and, like, where, like, where, where the excitement is is kind of on the vlog channel where there's lots of content coming out, lots of discussion happening.
And the main channel has been these, like, you know, these, these well-crafted videos, but I'm not even the one editing them, Davoo's editing them.
So I feel, like, it's a little distant because it's stuff that I wrote a while ago, especially this month because most of what we've been publishing is stuff that I wrote, like, months ago that I just never got to edit.
So it's kind of like content that I'm not as invested in in the moment and that, like, you know, even though it is getting, like, a, you know, better viewership and expanding my audience, the vlogs are also getting a decent amount of attention.
So there's some kind of irony to the fact that, like, the main channel is, like, these, these more expensive, more high-effort stuff, and I say expensive in, like, a literal sense that I'm paying Davoo to edit them, and that those are the ones that are getting marked on Patreon.
You know, like, those are the career aspect, even though for some people, like, the vlogging channel is probably way more interesting right now, just because there's so much stuff coming out and, you know...
That's how Ethan and Hila feels, because...
Yeah, I was gonna say it the same.
They've slowed down on their actual videos, and their...
You know, that would have been so true if they, like, didn't come back with anything strong, but then they just so happened to make their best video ever with the boy band one, which inspires confidence in me.
But still, Ethan and Hila is clearly where the more business is going down.
Even though HDHD is, like, the main channel, but then the funny thing about it is, Ethan and Hila has, like, 700,000 subscribers.
They average close to a million fucking views on their videos.
So, like, on the one hand, you could still say HDHD is the main channel, but Ethan and Hila is also probably an even better source of revenue at this point, because it comes out so frequently, you know?
And I'm sure that was a large motivation behind doing it.
Right.
You know, it just makes sense, fiscally.
But you know, it's really interesting.
Having a game grown to them with games.
It's really interesting to me the pressures...
Sorry, let me just finish this point.
It's really interesting to me the pressure that people seem to feel, and Ethan talked about this a lot.
Like, when your channel gets big, there's this pressure, and I already feel it, even with a small channel, to, like, make everything on there perfect.
So you gotta make the second channel so you can just post whatever you want when you're just being a real dude, you know?
Yeah, that's exactly how I am at the moment.
Yeah.
The give and take stuff, I post stuff on there when I have, like, a dumb idea, but I know it's not, like, something that could be considered a good...
Like, I mean...
In the sort of traditional sense that it's, like, a big video.
It's like your resume, and then your, I don't know, your real life, or whatever.
Jochron does the same sort of stuff, except he's sort of doing the worst...
Except that his one, like, vloggy video was the best one he's made in years!
Well, not that.
I'm talking about the fact that he's been deleting videos that aren't, like, up to his level of stat...
Like, you know, the Sonic...
He's been doing that for a long time.
There's old Sonic review videos, all the Sonic T stuff.
The Sonic Team videos are the best fucking things on his channel.
They're all gone.
He deleted those, that fucking bitch!
I know, he's a fucking idiot.
Dammit, I hate, I hate John Trun so much, I wish he was dead.
Historical revisionism.
At this point, he's only doing damage to his, his legacy.
He needs to stop.
And you know, I think, possibly, that a new great, like, one of the best forms of content is, is that they can go half-vlog, half-edited.
A lot of what Jesse makes is, like, done live, or done impromptu, and then, like, stapled together through editing.
That's kind of the best of both worlds.
That's essentially Frankenstein Monster from hell.
That's essentially what Ethan and Hila is.
I don't think they're as good as Jesse just because Jesse's off the cuff is so...
Like, even just the unscripted part is great, and then the editing brings it up to another level.
Whereas, I think a lot of Ethan and Hila videos would not really be funny before the editing.
Because, like, back when I was doing videos back in, like, 2008, which I've all unlisted, but you can find, but don't watch them.
Your eyes will water from my voice.
It was all, like, live.
It was all just me talking into a microphone and then editing the audio and putting on visuals.
Because I thought that will come out more natural than writing a script and having to make it sound good and feel good.
I didn't really know how to do that at the time.
But then when I got into videos, like, as a professional thing, I started doing pretty much the same format that Digi does,
which is just write the whole thing, record the whole thing, and then edit the whole thing as, like, a layered process.
But more recently, I've been getting into doing things more the way that Demolition D does or YMS does.
Specifically with my debate with a commenter video, I just started, like, putting together individual pieces of that video
because I didn't really plan on what exactly it was going to be.
I just started, like, I wrote some sections of it and then I impromptu, like, just started ranting about other sections in it.
And then I just did a whole bunch of editing that, like, stapled it all together.
And it has a lot of raw energy in it and a lot of natural flow.
Is this already out? DeVille, are you still working on it?
No, my debate with a commenter video.
Oh, that one. Oh, okay. I missed that.
It has a lot more of, like, a natural flow than a lot of other videos I've made have.
And that's obviously one- the best thing that Digi's vlogs have is that naturalness to it.
That a lot of- like, Digi, I want to bring up the whole voiceover conundrum that we've been having this month.
Do you want to introduce that topic?
Yeah, I've had to redo the voiceover on, like, most of the videos that we did this month because of the fact that I'm reading posts-
Like I said, it's mostly been videos that I wrote months ago.
And, like, for me, it's really difficult to, like, recapture what I was thinking when I wrote it, you know?
Because, like, every video I write is written in a certain voice.
There's, like, a certain rhythm to it and a certain cadence to it.
Oftentimes, it's actually based on, you know, other YouTubers.
Like, I'll have someone else's voice in my head and I never copy them in the actual voiceover.
Like, because I just can't, you know, it naturally comes out sounding like me.
Like, actually, one of the voices I get in my head the most is Hyperbit Hero.
Like, the way he reads his- Shout out to my boy.
The way he reads his scripts when I'm reading back to myself, like, when I read through my script to myself, I tend to use his voice.
Which is funny, because I actually don't really like the way he reads in his videos, because every sentence sounds the same.
Dude, dude, hang on, let me cut you off.
I love when he starts his videos with that, top of the morning to you laddies, this is Hyperbit Hero.
Happy to bring you home and back to another video.
I love that, I love that.
But, like, he kind of, like- No, that's him.
Every sentence he has has kind of the same lilt to it.
Like, they always kind of have the same downward cadence towards the end, and it can get tiring.
But, like, for whatever reason, that's the voice I tend to read a lot of my scripts in.
And then, like, I just read them slightly differently when I perform, because I don't actually sound like Hyperbit Hero.
But, like, I very often have some YouTuber's voice in my head when I'm writing my script.
Okay, so I get the point. So what was the problem with your recording? I don't understand.
That these videos were written so long ago that I don't remember what that was, like, about.
And it just comes out kind of awkward.
Yeah, it comes out like, this show is like this, and I think that it's-
I have a kind of, like, a default, like, voice that I use, which is like the-
Oh, we know it.
You know, the, hey, everybody, I'm watching this show, and it's great.
And, like, so when I don't remember what the original, like, feeling was, then I just try to do whatever, and it comes out really awkward.
And so, like, almost every video, Davoo had to, like, send me a sample of what it was going to sound like,
and I've been like, no, that's terrible. Let me do it again.
Yeah, like, the ten directing tricks in Avangelion video, you used to just read it,
your first version of that video, you read it like a normal video, which was pretty fast,
and it was just too fast for a video that was that intricate, so you recorded a slower version.
Well, you say first, but that's, like, the fifth or sixth different version, because I wrote that back in December.
Yeah, voiceover is a total bitch, with my, like, two of my more recent videos,
I just spent days on the voiceover trying to get it to be pretty good.
It's so hard to get that to come out natural.
You know, I know you guys accuse me of slurring in my words, because I rushed too much,
but my voiceover has gone pretty quick.
I prefer slurring over sounding awkward. That was a decision that I made at one point personally.
I would prefer not understanding, like, 0.5% of the words that a person says,
in exchange for them sounding way more natural.
Fair enough.
I also do have a trouble with, like, the, when I write something,
and it's, like, months before I actually start recording, because I take months to write anything,
and I can't remember what, I mean, I used to not remember what I was going for,
but now I go into intricate detail in describing how I'm supposed to say the thing in the script,
when I'm saying it.
So I write down in a voice like this, like in brackets or whatever.
Do you also paste links to relevant things that remind you?
Yeah, yeah, all that sort of stuff.
Just stuff that puts me in that, like, remember, like, makes me remember,
oh yeah, that's the sort of thing I was going for.
Like, if I sued, like, an early tag, like, early John Tron voice or something.
I'll figure it out, you know? It usually works.
Yeah, so maybe we should start, Digi, maybe at some point we should start doing more videos.
They're just sort of like a bunch of stuff that gets stapled together and made good through editing.
The only stuff I've really done in that style is, like, the Migraine and Insomnia analysis videos,
where, like, I was copying Jesse's style, and those are just, like, I would record a shit ton of random footage
and then just, like, put them all in whatever order made the most sense,
which is usually pretty much chronological order anyways, but, like...
Well, Nate, I appreciate what you said, how, yeah, doing it between two people over the internet would be impossible.
I agree, I'm glad you brought that up.
Because go to digibro.com slash binstainpatreon to give him more money,
because, like, at the rate that he's making money, we'll be able to, like, work together in person
before much longer.
That's very true.
You can get his, like, his Patreon to, like, what, like, I don't know, a thousand or maybe twelve hundred dollars per video?
Yeah, I was about to make it the, like, eleven hundred dollar goal that I will just straight up move you up here if we hit that goal.
Yeah, and we can work in person. There'll be so many benefits to it.
We could do videos like that, we could do, like, videos about, like, video games more easily,
because we were about to do one, but we scrapped it, because it was just too hard.
Alright, before we get to it, I want to talk about who...
Well, just go to his Patreon, do it.
As usual, the person who I think is pushing forward the medium here is our good friend, Endless Jess.
And that's because of the way he uses Patreon, which really fascinates me.
And I've been trying to, like, figure out, like, debating with myself over whether I want to try to do the same.
Jesse, do you want to talk about how you use Patreon? Are you still there?
Yeah, what? How, I mean, what do you mean?
How you, like, in the last six months, you adopted this new method of how you post to Patreon.
Like, it used to be that you would only patron, like, certain videos that you thought were, like, the best ones?
I would worry that, I would worry that, like, people would patron for a certain thing,
and my stuff is so all over the place that, inevitably, I would post the wrong thing on Patreon, and people would un-pledge.
So, to skirt that issue, I just started posting everything I do on Patreon,
but, like, in chunks of, like, three or four or five things at a time, so nobody can complain because it's just a shitload of content.
Is it like a text post with links?
Yes.
And you ask to pay for the post?
Yeah, because I've been a Patreon of everyone else in this call, and, like, or this whole group,
and, like, for instance, Tommy Oliver, he was the one who actually started it first, but he started doing it by week.
So, it's just whatever he put out that week, that's what he would patron.
So, he has it set to, like, you know, a, like, because when you start a Patreon, you either go monthly or you go by each post that you mark.
And so, he would just make a marked post at the end of each week, and whatever came out that week he would mark,
and that way, he didn't have to worry about whether Tommy Oliver or Rebel Pixels was the main one, it was just both.
And then Jesse started doing it, so it's basically just whenever he feels like there's enough content that it's worth marking.
So, sometimes it'll be, like, eight fucking Blue Glow videos that all get marked at once,
and then sometimes it'll be, like, I made this cool music video and also here's one Blue Glow video,
and it just kind of always feels like, I never feel like I'm getting ripped off anymore.
It's basically just, like, once I pass the threshold of, like, okay, this is enough, this is worth it.
This is worth your fucking money.
And so, like, I was considering, like, because with all the vlogs I've done this month,
I'm like, there's no way this is worth less, like, altogether than one, like, fully edited video.
Like, I've made fucking 30 vlogs, a lot of them are really interesting.
Some people have been saying that they find them as interesting as my mainline content,
so, like, you know, I haven't decided, I want to warn my patrons first,
and knowing me, because I've always been really strict about what I patron,
I've even had, like, main videos that I haven't patroned before,
just because I didn't think they were quite up to the, you know, up to the standard that I set for myself,
but, like, at some point, there's so many fucking vlogs that it has to be worth it.
Like, even if it was just once a month that I actually marked them, I mean,
because surely a lot of my audience isn't even holding me up to that high,
like, the standard I'm holding myself up to, you know?
For sure, yeah, definitely.
You know, my downwell video is, like, two and a half minutes long, so I didn't patron it,
and I'm like, well, as soon as I make another two and a half minutes long video,
then I'll patron them both, and I've been waiting for, like, six months to make a video like that.
Yeah, I don't mind so much if it's short, if it's got a great point, you know?
We can ASMR fart video. Those are big these days. Just do that.
Like, for instance, the ten directing tricks in Ava video, like, because of the way we edited it,
we slowed it down considerably, and it ended up being five and a half minutes,
but the original way I had written it, it was supposed to only be a four-minute video,
and, like, when I was trying to edit it myself way back, it was gonna be four minutes,
and I was like, I'm completely comfortable patroning it because it's fast, but it's incredibly dense with information,
and all of it's interesting, and it's exactly what people come to my channel for,
so, of course, it's worth patroning, you know?
But then with vlogs, it's like, it could be the most interesting vlog in the universe,
and I don't know if it's something people want to pay for.
Like, it's the hardest thing for me. It's like, just figuring out, like, do people care about the editing,
or do they care about the ideas, you know?
And so, like, I've probably made...
Yeah, that's fair.
Like, through Ad Revenue alone, I have probably made $150 off of all these vlogs that I've put out in the last couple weeks,
just because there's so fucking many of them, you know?
So, like, they're definitely becoming, like, a second revenue stream for the channel,
but it's a question of, how far do I take that?
Do they need their own Patreon, you know?
Because I think that's...
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I don't think anyone would protest paying for that, those secret pics of you as a loli showdown.
That was invaluable insight.
But yeah, like, I mean, obviously I wouldn't want to mark every vlog,
but I really feel like if I keep doing things this way,
like, if it gets to a point where this vlogging addiction doesn't go away,
and I'm still posting, like, even one vlog a day,
I would definitely like to adopt Jesse's method of, like, here's everything I put out this week,
and surely that's enough to be worth paying for, you know?
Which has been working for Jesse.
His Patreon's been climbing back up after it was kind of falling from exactly the problem he was describing.
People not, like, you know, people getting things that weren't exactly what they wanted,
and now it's like, well, now you're just getting everything, you know?
And even for me, like, I reduced my pledge back when Jesse was doing that,
where sometimes I was like, I don't know if some of these videos are worth it,
but now that I get, like, 18 fucking videos at once,
then I really, like, one blue glow would definitely not be worth the money.
But ten of them I can't argue with.
Like, there's too much of good in that number of blue glows.
And since you lowered your pledge,
that means you've been missing out on all the fantastic Patreon-exclusive $3 My Little Pony vlogs
that you find folk can see right now for a $3 pledge every single week.
Since I'm the only one of these J-Brones who still gives crap about My Little Pony,
I'm watching that shit every week.
I'm talking about all the cool fucking, talking about great vlogs, the best vlogs,
the only vlogs that anyone really wants to see or needs to see,
is fucking pony vlogs available only on my Patreon-exclusive only for patrons,
and nobody else can see them.
It's a secret to everybody. That's a video game reference.
I got all the references, motherfucker.
And it's great that those are only for patrons,
because you don't want the mainstream getting access to your opinions on pony episodes.
That's right.
They don't deserve it, do they?
The world doesn't really deserve it.
The patrons deserve it, man, because they fucking...
Did you imagine if your most boring taste in anime video had been exclusive to patrons?
That would have gone over a lot better,
because only people who get where you're coming from would have seen it.
Yeah.
Would you agree?
Uh, I guess so.
I still think it's worth being out there, just because it's...
It's also, like, on the one hand, while, like, the amount of drama it caused
was, like, ridiculous and stupid,
A, I made $60 off of it, at least,
and B, it's pretty fucking hilarious.
Some men just want to watch the world burn for $60.
I've been having some back-and-forths with people,
and one guy in particular, in trying to debunk your postulate there,
pretty much confirmed everything you said.
He was like,
Well, you know, you should look at your tastes beyond personal enjoyment.
Oh, yeah.
There's more to it.
There's more to just how much you enjoy something.
I'm like, all right, right there is a mentality that he was talking about
when he was talking about this boring perspective of media.
Yeah, it's pretty funny.
I think that was true for a lot.
Like, there was a lot of comments that were...
Because this video became, like, a meme on 4chan,
like, where the 3x3 threads have been infected with people talking about it for fucking days.
Yeah, they saw that.
And, uh, like...
They're still doing it.
But the funniest part is, like, people who were saying, like,
this guy's just butt-hurt because people don't like...
Like, people don't like K-On,
and so he's, like, defending it by, you know, insulting other people's tastes.
And, like, that is literally what I'm commenting on,
is that people don't feel like they can, like, you know, put a show like K-On on their list
because people have this mentality.
So, like, that's exactly what I'm saying.
Yeah, I'm surprised they didn't understand your point.
I mean, you know.
You two commenters not understanding the point.
I don't believe you, sir.
Fighting the ocean.
Talking about the upper echelon of the intelligentsia.
Yeah.
But, yeah, so, like, to some extent, it was, like,
it was fascinating and hilarious to watch it happen.
You know, like, there's two levels.
There's a level on which it's happening to me,
and that's annoying,
but then there's a level on which I'm standing back
and watching it happen and thinking it's really funny.
So, uh, yeah, I could appreciate it being out there.
But, yeah, speaking of Patreon, if you pledge to our Patreon,
me and DeVoo, we do this series of three-hour commentaries
on all the videos I've ever made.
That's what we're doing.
Oh, yeah, which I've still never seen any of.
Are any of those available as, like, a sample?
No, but I could make you one if you actually want to watch it.
I want to, like, end some video with a...
No, I figure you would.
I'm just asking for the folks back home.
Yeah, well, I want to have some Digi video
that ends with a big promotion of all the Patreon rewards,
and it'll have a little couple minutes of sampling
or a couple seconds or whatever, showing what it's like.
That is a good idea.
It's the definitive insight to every detail about his content.
Yeah, it's me and DeVoo ranting about our videos
for hours and hours and hours.
Oh, just yours.
I mean, you know, the ones I worked on as well.
Well, in the ones that we work, like, that DeVoo edited,
DeVoo does more of the talking
and is very proud of himself for all the things he's done.
I just find it really entertaining how, like,
how proud of yourself you can get in some of those moments.
Well, at least in the Sword Art Online 2 ones,
where that was the ones where I put the most...
I blew the most time per second.
Yeah, when you edit a video, which I know a thing or two about,
you, like, every frame on screen comes with, like,
hours of thought, of concentration about choosing why you chose this one.
Man, if I did a commentary on my shit,
I'm just saying, like, I could talk about any frame extensively
as to why I chose that particular one.
Yeah, I definitely believe that with you more than anyone else.
Well, I don't know, mostly just the Sword Art Online 2 ones.
Those are the most dense ones.
When we eventually get to the Astroscore videos,
it'll be a lot more sparse.
Alright, well, I don't know if anybody else has anything else to say about vlogging.
I just want to say I plan on doing more because it's really fun.
Yeah.
And I enjoy it.
I just kind of like, I like that this is where YouTube is going.
You know, it is kind of fun.
I enjoy the improv comedy of it.
Me too.
I like it as...
Like, remember when that video when Ryuko fell down?
I didn't plan that shit.
That was hilarious.
And that was pretty funny.
That makes me laugh.
But that's the thing, and that's what people have to appreciate.
It wasn't just funny because she fell down,
but the thing you said was,
because you said, oh, she knew she didn't belong,
so she got out of here.
I thought that was pretty hilarious.
Yeah, right.
And you know, and this is going to be,
I'm going to drop a bombshell here for the end of this.
Okay, I'm ready.
So, I got to ask,
haven't we kind of exhausted the genre of heavily edited videos?
Like...
No, you can never...
That's like asking if we've exhausted the genre of heavily edited movies.
The answer is no.
You can just make more.
What do you mean heavily edited?
Do you mean like text flying all over the screen?
What I mean is like...
I know what you mean, you son of a bitch.
I mean, are we doing anything really that new and inventive
by making like, you know, another 40 minute video with like all the same,
and then we say a joke and cut to a big explosion.
Like, we kind of covered it at this point.
I'll tell you straight out, Digi,
I am not really concerned about being a genre trendsetter.
That is not my primary goal.
My goal is to make the videos that I would enjoy watching, probably.
And it's true, you do get burned out.
Like even at John's heyday, I sort of was getting bored of them
because they sort of were just the same stuff repeatedly.
But I kind of think that's inevitable with all art.
Like you've got to...
I'm sure one day, if I start doing this professionally
and I'm grinding away every day,
without a doubt, I'm sure I'll get tired of doing that kind of shit eventually.
Digi, by heavily edited, you mean like demo, right?
Or like a sort of online...
You mean like comedy reviewer editing.
Yeah, comedy reviewer editing is really what I mean.
I mean like, there was a time back in 2012...
I fucking hate demo editing style.
I'm so over it.
Over what? Over who's editing style?
That whole breakneck, everything's flying at the screen at once.
Every half a second, there's some non sequitur shooting out of the side of the screen.
Because like Nate, to be honest, when I watched the Undertale video,
it was really well done, but that video felt to me like,
this is the last one of these I need to see.
Like from now on...
For Undertale, that's absolutely true.
I mean, I'm excited that you're not going to keep doing videos that are that extreme
because I've seen this now enough times.
I got onto YouTube in 2012 through Sequelitis.
Sequelitis was my introduction to the idea of being subscribed to people,
to follow their content regularly.
I had the Sequelitis videos, I had the JonTron videos,
these highly edited jokes and gags thrown into a review kind of thing.
And back then, you needed all that to get people's attention.
And it was always like, I mean, those were all funny at the time,
but like the entire idea of that is like, I get it now, it's done.
Like we've done all the fun.
I totally feel you.
And this is why it's going to be so important that people see my next video,
because I think you're going to see some things that are happening
as to my...
I've had a grand vision all along for what I do with these things,
but you know what, forget me, I want to ask you a question about this exact topic.
Why is it that...
Okay, I understand your point, but let me...
I just want to ask why knowing all that, feeling the way that you do about this stuff,
why is it that you're still interested to get a new Plinket video?
You know, what is it about that makes you want that?
I'm not that interested to get a new Plinket video, really.
Well, in your other videos, you said like,
you know, we might not have gotten a new Plinket video,
but at least we got this guy ever...
Well, that's the thing, that was before it was done.
Like, Undertale was the last one I ever feel like I need.
Like, I don't...
Okay, okay.
Like, there was a point, like for instance, back when we did Pony,
like, you know, you love Anthony C's Cantorlot wedding video.
Sure do.
And when it came out, it was really big and beautiful and a great idea,
but then, with Anthony C, he continued to, like, you know...
He only puts out a video, like, every four months,
and it was always a 15-minute video, and it was always highly edited,
and I was always like, dude, I don't care anymore about the editing stuff,
like, because he would make a video where the point is, like, one minute long,
like, the actual analytical point he was making.
Remember when he edited it in?
I don't know if you've been watching him recently,
but he did, like, this, like, musical skit in the middle of, like,
a review of, like, season five or something,
and, like, it was just like, can we please hurry this along?
This is so boring.
Right.
That was...
You know what?
I think I know what it is.
Super dense editing videos.
And no offense, Anthony, I love what you do,
but I think you could freshen it up a little bit, if you happen to be seeing this, you know?
Yeah, yeah, fresh.
Fresh is important.
You know, I think that super dense editing in videos is, like, super fast rapping.
That is a good comparison.
In rapping.
Yeah.
It's like...
It's the best that should happen all the time,
and the whole song should be comprised of nothing but a twist of baby.
But, like, you know, if you have really conservative views of it,
sometimes you can use density to, like, make a point.
Like, we sort of did that in part one of Digi's Nanoha retrospective.
At the very beginning, where he mentions that this is such a huge franchise
with so many different little facets,
I just showed every image of everything in it all at once really fast to make that point.
I think a better example would be...
I think, like, for me, like, going forward,
I think Asterisk War was, like, the perfect level of, like,
it wasn't about dense editing.
It was about making this point and always feeling, like,
like, what was on screen was, like, the amount that needed to be there.
It was...
Yeah.
There were times where I said, like, every A1 pictures show looks the same,
and we had to show 40 different pictures of someone's face that all looked the same,
and it was this really well-edited segment you put together,
and that was perfect for that moment.
But if there's a part where I'm just literally describing what's happening in an episode,
we don't need to show anything but show footage, you know?
You know, dude, I hear what you're saying, and I agree,
but, you know, I just don't think that my personal intentions are as...
are kind of... are the same old thing that you've seen in all these.
I think I've got some new ideas people are gonna see, like,
like, when you did that McDonald's bit in your Asterisk War thing,
that was, like, the best part of the whole thing by a huge margin.
But that was just so fresh.
That was just a little segment, though.
That's, like, I'm saying that that's what makes this perfect.
That's right.
I think what...
I'm not saying don't do any editing at all in your videos anymore.
You want a variety in speed.
Right.
That's basically it.
You just... you want to do...
You want to be using things that are appropriate.
Like, if there's first things you gotta do, you gotta do them first.
I'm completely...
You need to slow down at some points.
I'm completely with Jesse about this whole Demolition D thing,
where, like, because what was so exhausting to me about his last video,
the one about Himoto Umaru-chan,
was that it was, like, every second of it was so dense with stuff going on,
and the subject of the video was so uninteresting,
that it was, like, why is this happening?
Like, why are we...
Why are you putting so much into, like, this...
Like, every second of this, when half of it...
You're not even saying anything.
Like, he just...
Well...
Cut away constantly to make little...
There's always gonna be a place for stuff that's, like, really fast and flashy,
because kids just, like, seeing bright colors and...
It's not about kids.
Demo's videos are more...
Well, sometimes.
...flastic-jontron than they are, like, DigiBro,
or ReviewerX, whoever the fuck they are.
Like, they're about the spectacle of the thing, like, a little bit,
especially that last one.
Like, the point of that video was that it was cool to watch,
that, you know, there was crazy stuff happening,
and then, like, also Himoto sucks, you know?
I don't find the spectacle of it impressive, though,
because, like, for...
For JonTron, the moments you remember are, like...
Not that it was, like, every five seconds there was a gag.
The moments you remember were the big gags, the ones that, like, the fact that the...
Like, when Banjo3, like, takes over his shit and, like, the Eye of Sauron appears,
like, yeah, that was great.
Like, the Banjo-Kazooie video is perfect because there's a long section in the middle of it,
where he's just describing the history of Rareware.
There's not, like, a ton of, like, stuff happening.
Like, there's one shot he lingers on for, like, a whole 30 seconds
of just a guy holding a controller in front of a TV.
It's, like, literally the Blue Glow.
Like, it looks just like Jesse's, uh, like, Blue Glow avatar thing,
but it's, like, a photo of just a guy sitting in the dark playing video games,
and he's describing the feeling of doing that when you're a kid,
and it's this incredibly long shot.
And then it goes right from that.
That's what I'm saying. It's the ebb and flow.
Well, it's the action and then the passivity of the thing.
Honestly, when you talk about the long shots, I think the long shots were because of budgetary limitations.
That's why they held on to 30-second shots without moving.
Oh, no, I just had to have John sit there for 30 seconds,
because he ran out of budget to film more footage of the Ava's punching.
But, yeah, like, in that video, in the nuts and bolts video,
the moment that you remember is when it all builds up to him,
cars, cars, and die!
That moment is so dense,
and because none of the rest of the video is that dense,
there's, like, you know, suddenly there's five layers of video on top of each other,
and he's screaming, and there's sounds and fire, and, like, it's intense.
And if Demo tried to put that moment into his Himoto video,
it would just be static, because the whole video's like that already.
It's all fucking shit happening.
Another great example, fantastic example, to go back to, is a horseshoe finale.
That video is like, I don't know, at least 50% like, guys sits in front of the camera
and talks a script.
But then there are, like, all these different moments with lots of original graphics
and an occasional moment and a bunch of fast editing.
Yeah, if you're trying to make an argument for, like, a rising and falling action
throughout a video, then I couldn't agree more.
That's absolutely essential for a good narrative.
You've got to have that.
I think a perfect example of, like, a really fastly edited video
is another Jesse thing, it's the Madako Magica thing on my Japanese anime,
where it's just really fast, really, I think it's the fact that he's doing all the,
like, the Dr. Seuss rhyming stuff.
God damn it! It's not Dr. Seuss!
One more fucking person uses that analogy!
Oh my god, you're banned from my friends list, you're banned from the CCP!
What would you prefer if you referred to as Jesse?
I just fucking can't stand redundant, unoriginal fucking people who,
they see, like, the title of the Reddit post and they all got to say the same fucking thing.
Like, God damn it!
The video was posted on Best Guy Ever.
Like, really? Is Dr. Seuss the only person you can think of in history
who ever came up with rhyme schemes or, like, a complicated fucking rhyme scheme ever?
You've, like, never heard of it?
I thought of it as more of a rap song when I first heard it.
Yeah, you know, there's this entire genre of music.
It's kind of like this huge phenomenon for the last, like, 35 years called rap.
You know? Oh, and there's this other thing.
You know, I think it actually existed before Dr. Seuss.
It was called poetry.
God, how long has that been around?
About 11,000 fucking years?
You goddamn simpletons! You rubes! You fucking idiots!
Oh, man, he's like the Dr. Seuss of anime.
Oh, man, Dr. Seuss, eat your heart out.
This guy's like Dr. Seuss.
Monika, Monika Magica!
More like Monika Dr. Seussica!
Ugh!
Fucking!
Fuck us!
Yeah, uh, I agree.
I'm guessing, Hippo, that you didn't know that people constantly compare that video to Dr. Seuss.
No, I did. I said it on purpose.
Oh, you son of a bitch!
You activated his trap card.
He's like a damn fiddle!
It was him, Austin! It was him all along!
You all bought it, hook, lied, and sinker!
Your own family bought it!
Why, Triple H, why? Someone tell me why!
You know, that's a good point.
You know, like, wrestling is mostly like, what, half scripted, half live?
All those promos are like vlogs. There's no tight editing in the WWE.
I mean, the entirety of reality TV is pretty much this, although that shit mostly sucks.
But like, yeah, I don't know.
I think that's the future we're going into.
And I like it, and I like this idea of, like, longer content and not everything having to be as...
Like, if you go back and watch Sequelitis now, I promise you that as great as it is, as great as the points he's making are,
there are ports where you're just like, alright, get to the point.
Like, if you watch it now, the flash is the least interesting element of it.
The parts where...
Okay, but if you want someone to get to the point, watching like their entire Let's Play history is kind of the opposite of what you're asking for there.
Well, the point in the Let's Play videos is chilling out and listening to people talk,
and you don't really have to pay that much attention to it, you know?
But like, I just think that if those, if the Sequelitis videos were made today,
they would look more like a Mr. B-Tongue video, where like, there's jokes,
there's stuff to make it flow in a certain way, you know?
His videos all have, like you said, a rising and falling action, they feel like a story,
but they also never waste your time.
And there's no jokes that are just there because there had to be a joke there, you know?
And I would defend...
Anybody who puts a joke there that isn't funny, or is just like,
now I've got to go from one paragraph to the other, let's put in a lame joke.
Those people...
Yeah, I can't stand that shit.
They suck.
They watch the Peanut Butter Gamer style of video.
I hate you, Peanut Butter Gamer!
No, he's just...
Hold on, hold on.
Don't be a hero to Peanut Butter Gamer.
He's mediocre.
You have to have actual points in between the jokes.
It can't...
Yeah.
And some of the jokes have to be funny sometimes.
Well, that's...
That's for sure.
I don't know, you know what?
I'm totally willing to admit that a lot of this is just anger
at people who are successful doing things that appear to me to be low effort.
That makes me extremely angry.
I want people to fucking work themselves with a bone
and fucking be destroyed on the path to greatness.
That's what I want people to do, you know?
Yeah, well, there is a lot of thought that goes into just editing footage,
like all those videos I've done...
Oh, no, I mean, if you're talking about somebody like PewDiePie,
that's absolutely true.
He edits the shit out of those videos, and it's usually pretty cool.
I'd put PewDiePie significantly above Game Grumps, even at their best,
in terms of what I, you know...
Well, you know, I think that there's certain people...
Like, sure, some people are famous, and it can be...
Like, you watch their videos, you know, like, how the fuck is this possible?
But, like, for people like Game Grumps,
I thought their show was usually pretty funny,
and they were always, like, they refused to ever be silent.
They were always talking, they were always trying to make new points,
up until more recently, where they've totally fallen apart,
because they're not doing this anymore.
But, you know, they always had stories, they always had stuff to do,
and both of, like...
When I say both of them, I mean, whichever combination you're talking about,
they're comedians, like, they're trained comedians.
They're people who've taken improv classes.
They've all taken classes, they've all taken improv classes,
they talk about it all the time.
Oh, yeah, and I took Spanish classes in high school,
and I can fucking speak that shit, like...
Like, Mocholoco, Spaniola.
My point is, they practice at it, and they cared about being funny,
for a long time, they cared about...
They cared about at least being interesting.
They don't care anymore, they're just in it for the money now.
Like, there was a long period where they cared about being funny and interesting.
You know, DJ, I'm not contradicting you,
I just want to say that the change that guys like you say
has happened in Game Grumps that they're shit now,
to me, I just don't see a difference.
I don't see what changed.
That's because you weren't here for the John stuff.
That's true.
Well, also, even a lot of...
If I showed you one of the best episodes of a Dan Let's Play,
and then a current episode, I think you'd get it.
There's moments in Bloodborne where they'll tell a really compelling,
interesting story about something they were doing,
and now it's just nothing.
It's literally nothing.
They'll start up an episode like, hey, we're...
Mario Maker Episode 725.
This level was sent to us by this guy.
I ate a burrito today.
If we bring on Rob Schneider, that will make us relevant.
Yay!
For me, again, my rule has always been,
don't make a video, I wouldn't watch,
and the only reason I do so many podcasts and vlogs now
is that I feel confident that I'm fucking good at this.
I've always been good at manipulating my voice,
because it's just something I've been practicing my whole fucking life.
I've always been singing, I've always been doing voices.
My mom does voices, so that was kind of instilled in me at a young age.
You still can't do an English accent, though.
What?
Not well.
Oh, I'm crikey, mate.
I can do an English accent as fucking all day.
You know what I'm saying, governor?
That's my English accent.
Well, if I was almost worse.
I've got a lot of different types of English accents
that I tried to do.
That's cool, mate.
At the L.O.L.S. which...
I don't know.
You've got to hold your nose.
Hello, governor!
Yeah!
But yeah, like, for me, it was like Scotland.
It's just I!
Welcome to England!
This is how we talk in the great L.O.L.
where the English people live.
Who invited the bop-a-dook on this show?
Get the fuck out of here.
Um, yeah, so...
But yeah, like, as I was saying...
Wait, no, that was the bloody dead man.
No, I don't know.
I feel very trained, especially from the pub crawl.
Because pub crawl was like two hours twice a week
for fucking three years
that I've just been talking unscripted forever.
You know, and then doing Digi Bros.
just, like, stacked on top of that.
And if you compare, like, GameCube chats
which was the Let's Play show I tried to do
back when I first started, like, YouTubing,
it was fucking awful.
Like, none of us knew how to talk.
None of us knew how to, like, you know,
keep a subject going.
I would edit those videos to, like,
cut out all the boring parts.
So they were completely incomprehensible.
It's boring parts.
So I would cut, like, I would just cut to the parts
where we're talking.
And it would be nonsense.
No one knew what the fuck we were doing.
So then, like, with Digi Bros.
when we started it and it was actually good,
it was like, oh, my God, this is watchable.
Like, people will sit through this.
I'll sit through this.
And so, like, you know, like,
even though I'm vlogging now
and those vlogs may seem like, you know,
just a low effort thrown together content,
especially because I've got, like,
what's what got me to start doing it
is that I stopped hooking up a microphone.
Because up until recently,
I've been, like, such a stickler for audio quality
that I, like, would always, you know,
hook up my nice mic and everything.
And, like, I'd have to move my whole setup
and put everything there.
And so finally, I just made the decision that, like,
you know what, the camera audio's good enough.
No one's gonna complain about it.
Fuck it.
I'm just gonna turn on the camera
and talk directly into it.
So that's what all these vlogs have been.
But, like, I think that at this point,
I have enough camera presence
and I can talk unscripted well enough.
I mean, listen, I've been rambling for fucking
seven straight minutes now and, like, uninterrupted
with no pauses.
I don't even think I've said um in, like, a while.
So, you know, I think I have the skills to do.
I'm not even here right now.
My asshole is so itchy.
It's, like, it's just white noise, you guys.
I'm in a world of fucking...
Of ass itch.
Of just, like, please stop talking
so I can get in the shower.
Just share it, too.
Let's all take showers and jack off at the same time.
That's a good idea.
We'll try to synchronize it.
I think that's what killed the Ghostbusters
jacking off at the same time.
Isn't that, that's what happened, right?
If we can all come at once, we can close the portal though.
Yeah.
We're not talking about, like, more basic editing styles,
not having layers.
Why has no one made that porn?
Crossing the streams.
Holy shit.
I think they have.
Like, you know, making layer after layer
of, like, editing and visuals going on.
If you just, if you do just basic stuff,
like cutting between footage or just having a few images
at a time, there's a lot of craftsmanship
that goes into that, too.
And I think a lot of people are realizing this
with people like Nerdwriter.
His videos never have so many things going on at once.
It's just he always, he obviously has memorized
every friggin' Adobe Premiere filter.
Yeah.
And...
Yeah, Nerdwriter and...
What's that new guy?
Captain Christian?
Oh, yeah.
Nice guy, man.
Like, knows how...
Like, the perfect sort of...
His videos are so fuckin' pretty, man.
It makes me mad how pretty they are.
I've never made a video that was as pretty
as I wanted it to be.
One day.
The fact that Captain Christian can do that shit
in two weeks, that right there is like...
It's impossible.
How is it possible?
You know what it is?
You know what?
I bet he is a professional editor who has decided,
like, Jesus, I can just make YouTube videos
and I'll do way better.
He left a comment about that somewhere,
that, like, he said he went to school for it,
but he actually responded to Nino.
Like, he said he...
Whoa!
Because Nino was saying that, like,
sometimes people show up and they...
You can tell that they've had experience with YouTube,
or, like, that this isn't their first channel.
Yeah, yeah.
And so he said that to, like, me, that guy,
and someone else, might have been every frame.
And he was like, you know,
I know every frame is trained,
but I don't know about Captain Christian.
And Captain Christian said,
I went to school for it, like, briefly,
but I didn't learn as much as I learned
from just watching YouTube.
So, he's a really self-taught.
He's a really self-taught.
Who we should all fear.
It does sound like that's kind of genius level.
Oh, wait, we need to make him a TPC member
so we can absorb him before he goes wild.
I'm fine with that idea.
Who was that?
I don't know.
I have no idea.
The guy who did that X-Men video about the Coliseus.
The Coliseus video was great.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's literally the perfect YouTuber.
Like, everything he did was perfect so far,
and he's gained immediate success and fame for it.
Well, there's one big problem with his content.
It's not a vlog.
And with that, let's wrap this thing up.
That's all.
Yeah.
Let's all say goodbye now.
Oh, wait, we've got...
Oh, yeah.
Let's say goodbye, but don't stop recording.
Okay.
Bye.
We're going to say goodbye.
Goodbye.
Okay, we're done.