Hey everybody, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. The show that is, is, the pro is, we're procrat, er, we're, and I, here's the show. It's me, Gibbontake, and we got Ben Saint.
Yeah, yeah.
And we got some guests. We got a returning guest gamer as Tevin.
Er, two antennas met on a roof and got married. The ceremony wasn't much, but the reception was incredible.
Did it again.
That's a good one.
You did it.
Yes, you did it.
Thank you, thank you.
Gamer's Tavern show on YouTube. Check it out.
Classy epic. And we have Tectonic Improv as well.
Shout out to large chat.
Tectonic Improv, who I have mentioned, once or twice on the show, specifically for being the guy,
Well, he's got a YouTube channel and I've mentioned you because you did the
the PCP style lecture on
Linkart no on a top the fourth wall. Yeah, oh
I've seen like a bit of that. I keep thinking I'm gonna watch the whole thing, but I never get around to it
It's okay. Um, it's it's it's it's I kind of I kind of want to talk about that a little bit
Oh, yeah, I want to say it's a good. It's a good lecture. It's a good choice of topic for a lecture
and
Just I don't know. It's very it's very funny. I
I I knew I knew there was lore. I knew there was a top the fourth wall lore
But like I don't know just here hearing it described
Lynn in like a linear sequence of like this happened and therefore this happened and thus this happened is very very amusing it is
especially for
It feels like the perfect like lecture topic because it's yeah, it's very esoteric and
Yes, just
Like I was I
Was I used to watch Linkara like way back in the day when I was into like channel awesome and all that
So even back then I was like this is like kind of crazy. There it is. There it is the car running gift
I love this gift
Wait, I gotta I gotta see
Fuck I went to a different. I went to a different discord server. Why am I not looking at the right?
Okay, just go just go without me. Just forget about me Linkara's a funny
Gentleman he's he's interesting. It's not like on purpose. He's just yeah like that
He's I is he never funny on purpose? Um, well
He has moments I'd say
Like me
He's like I watched a bit of his videos back when I was like a that guy with the glasses head
And I was on that site and I was like, oh, I love
reviews
But I wasn't that big into comics. So I love when someone will watch it. So I don't have
Yeah, I I recall Linkara being like less funny than Spoonie and
But he was like considered one of the big three. So I didn't watch really anyone below him on the on the hierarchy
Only the only the choice the cream of the crop the few the proud
Haven't seen any of his stuff. I mostly watched
Guy with the glasses or what did he call himself dog walker or something?
Stolic
Nostalgia critic I've seen you know, do you know who link? Do you know who Linkara is I?
Know a little bit about him, but I haven't seen any of his content
He talks like this and he reveals comics
Kind of the thing. I'm I
Like I never watched that guy with the glasses or any channel awesome stuff like in its heyday. I just like missed that entire
Content train good the the most Linkara ever at one point
I went on like a very short atop the fourth wall binge
I just one day I put it on play for a while and I watched some and I was like, okay
This is fine and then another time I watched his Power Rangers series
Which is really good actually I was very because I was a big Power Rangers kid and I was like hmm
I remember Rita Rita repulsa and I remember Lord Zed and then I remember there were some like
machine cog people after that and I like what happened after that and
Now I know there was one where they were all cars. I
In case you remember they I remember really liking that retrospective. I used to watch it a lot
Yeah, so did I think I was like I
Was the one thing I was similar like I had seen the Power Rangers the movie with the ooze with Ivan ooze
Fuck yeah, Ivan ooze. Yeah, I saw that movie too. There's like what it was easy. So good
It's so good
Yeah, didn't you go like big giant robot himself?
Vote mode and like he was bigger than the planet and then they killed him
Yeah, that happened at the end
No, no Ivan ooze
Did that as well
Kara becomes like
He would he would I think it was actually he was piloting like some robot from a comic he read
I think that's what happened. I don't know if there's any sort of any sort of giant Linkara
Maybe there is cuz um
Cuz I finished I finished the lecture where there was like he was like halfway through a new saga
So I was like I won't cover. I won't bother covering that one
So maybe there is a giant Linkara. I admittedly I haven't watched
One can hold any sense. Yeah. Yeah, right. I mean fingers crossed. He's done pretty much everything else
It's it's been a while. It's been a while since I saw it. Does the lecture cover
Linkara lore that does it does it include um the the Vekai with the glasses like movies like too boldly flea and all that
I think I mentioned them
Uh
Like very are those cannon are those cannon to atop the fourth wall they kind of are
Sort of like they don't really matter in the main in the grand scheme of things. I think uh, I
Think to boldly flea has some has some connections to the main plotline because it like it
I think it's the cannon introduction or reintroduction of mechakara or something like like the point of to boldly flea and whatever the other
Movies are called the point of them is that they are like an avengers style like like meeting of all these characters together in one
Young it was cool. It was just legitimately cool. It was great. I dreamed of being part of I it's very funny
But I get it. I get the appeal completely. It's very of its time
I think um some of the things that like he has
Before the avengers though, right well a little bit and just was in a comic form before that
surely oh
I guess that's true
But like I feel like cross when I when I say an avengers style
Avengers have been around for decades. I think
Okay, but more more people are familiar with the movie version and like or like the idea of like all of these internet
Like video people
Coming together to do something together was sort of what was on a little bit unheard of at the time
At least at the scale that channel awesome was doing it. So and that way it's kind of cool
It makes way more sense for someone like lincara who does have like
Storylines then it does for someone like I don't know Todd in the shadows. Yeah
I don't I don't know if it was like this back then but like he doesn't have any plot in his no
He never has no, okay. Well, that's very weird. Just like that's like, oh my god
a
Galactic like like villain has appeared like the universe is in peril. Oh, thank god Todd in the shadows
Thank you. Todd's gonna save the day. It was really like reviewers are the best heroes
Christ it was it was like the I've watched all of the the meet-up films
Including the first one where it's just they were in a hotel
Lobby room fighting each other and it was like nostalgia critic versus the angry video game nerd, which is like where it all
Spiralled out from because they had a few because they were big at the time
It was it was really just nostalgia critic trying to make himself more popular by attaching himself to the angry video game
node, which was
a very smart move
Yeah, but like they had the first one was just a fight with everyone
Everyone just turned up. It's like who are you? I'm gonna beat you up and they just beat the shit out of each other
And it was very silly
The second one was like an attempt at actual like filmmaking
Uh, and it's laughable and it's it's kind of cute actually
um
There's a lot of funny stories of behind the scenes of these productions
That's like half the fun
But yeah, that one wasn't really like a super lore thing
It was just sort of like they understand that they are all part of that guy with the glasses
And the the joke is that nostalgia critic just says hey come over to this thing
He calls everyone and they're like why are we here? They just don't know they're just people
And they you know, some of them just happen to have super magic abilities or guns or whatever and they use they use their funny
reviewer gimmicks
in whatever happens
and then the third one
That was the the suburban nights, which is like a d&d thing in the suburbs
Wait, how many are there? There's this four
Okay, the suburban nights, uh
It's the same sort of thing like nostalgia critic calls everyone say hey
It's gotta do this thing and they're like fine. I guess I'll be in your review movie
And then it's the fourth one
To boldly flee is uh space. They just do the thing. There's like
Lore wise
Lore wise it makes no sense and they address that I think and but you know
When they have characters in their own reviews that are recurring lakara, especially he brings them in for certain things
I think lincara out of all the reviewers
Probably works the best in these crossover movies because he's the one who leans the most in on lore like spoony sort of did it
But not really to the extent that lincara did
I think lincara just really likes doing the lore stuff and honestly, um
Uh, I I I ended up really kind of like respecting it in a way. I just kind of liking it because I mean it's it's dumb
Yeah, but it's also
It's it's also kind of fun like it's it comes through like watching the lecture
I I started kind of respecting it too like he's real like he's really dedicated to like
Something will catch his eye and something he reviews. He'll decide that it's cool. He'll he'll you know
Uh co-opt it and put it into his own version into his like persona universe
Yeah, and then it will stay around and it will continue to get referenced like over and over again like for the rest of time
I and I think that's
I think that's kind of something that if like if anyone's like interested in making a lecture
I think you sort of have to in some degree respect or even like the thing you're covering
Because yeah, because if you come across if it comes across that you're like
you're you're not being
There's something lost if you like genuinely don't care or if you're or if you like dislike what you're talking about
Uh, yeah, like I had I had an idea
I I have ideas for like other lectures, but you know, there's like coven and all that crap
But um, but there was one idea I had in particular. Oh, yeah, I forgot about coven
Everyone did everybody forgets about that
I I had this idea for a lecture where I would cover um, I'd cover the game over thinkers story
And which is really funny. I was gonna say I was gonna say devoo used to talk about that he
She was gonna devoo came out like this week lamel
Uh, devoo was gonna do
The uh the uh the game over thinker lore and she never did and I always wanted to because I thought just like lincar
I was like, that's a perfect. I yeah, that's a perfect topic for it
I would love to see a game over thinker lecture, but the problem with me doing something like that is I uh,
I I fucking hate movie bob and I don't I don't respect him in the slightest. So if I I
I think I think I could hate movie bob, but also
I don't know if like I think the game I'm not super familiar with the game over thinker
but my impression of it is that it is very stupid, but
I I do find it genuinely amusing like when I like for the wrong reasons, maybe
But yeah, because he genuinely likes them or liked them at least at the time he would defend them. I think
Bob. Yeah, I mean bobber. Yeah
Bob
He really would like he really thought he was making like high art here
He really thought he was like elevating like people would say like bob
I just I just want to watch you review like movies and games and stuff
Like I don't like these skits and he's like, oh, well if you don't like it that I'm sorry
You know, I'm doing this to elevate my fucking craft. You know, you just don't appreciate my work
My I'm do this for you and you these pearls before swine. How can you not like the dark game over thinker?
All right, it's the most
It's the most intricate plot and loan to man
There's a man frozen from the from the 90s and he's back and he's going to jump off a building
I just it's high art because he came up with it while high
exactly
I just love movie balls probably like a straight edge. Oh, I was I was gonna say Bob would never do drugs. That's like
because
God
Did you I this week? I've been seeing that his old tweet floating around that's like that's like
I was supposed to be on a starship
Conversing with sentient robots and uploading my consciousness
Into a fucking robot body. I'll never forgive. I'll never forgive the people that took that future from me
I love it when when Bob accident accidentally
Just uh just inadvertently wants like eugenics and talks about it online. I think it's really funny
You know, it's it's it happens. He's not the only one that occasionally slips into it. But yeah
He does
I'm sorry. I'm sorry give. I think I cut you off earlier. What were you saying?
Yeah, I was just gonna say like the the stuff with linkara and and
movie bob and and all of these that guy with the glasses era like
Terrible like awful but like sort of endearing
Um attempts at making you know, they review things and they try to make them the things themselves in a way
And they always suck in the in the in this sort of style
And it's just it gives me the same vibes as sonichu. But in in a way that I you know, I like sonichu
I kind of admire game over thinker is very sonichu
It's it's how it's like it's so bad
But the fact that they care about it and work really hard to make it. It's just sort of nice and I just kind of like it
Link link like ironically cars. I think link cars is a little bit more like
It's more high after I'd say
Especially later on I would say link cars is it's a little it's more high effort
But also I get the and this is it's amazing to say this about linkara
But I genuinely think linkara is a little more self-aware that like what he's doing is like silly than bob is
I think I think so too imagine come across too much to like uh onlookers on linkara and his persona
But I do I do think like I mean he actually commented on my lecture
Like really? Yeah, I think I saw that. Yeah, I pinned it back when he watched it
And it's just uh, he's like talking or he just like quotes the video
uh, we're like people just
All right, I think one of one of the uh, one of the people who was in the audience for the lecture
It was just like shocked at the fact that I had been talking for I think like
20 minutes and we were only at like the first part of the story
Yeah, I I think I I think I should probably talk about this because um
Because uh, I I've noticed like a lot of comments about this lecture
Whenever whenever people talk about it
And I think you per you were probably gonna bring this up to ben about how like the audience
Probably kind of wasn't really into it
I was gonna mention it
I could I can tell that like you you shanghide some of your friends into sitting down for this thing
And they did it and you got them to agree to it and a couple of them were maybe like not
Actually prepared. Yeah, and I so like I
I told them I told them ahead of time like hey
Do you can you guys help me out with this like this like lecture idea?
I have where I'm going to like explain this stuff in front of like a camera for whatever
And uh, I I think I gave them your sonichu lecture and like this is what it's kind of gonna be like
and uh, I
You know, maybe they didn't watch it
But also on the other hand like I I made them sit down for two and a half hours to talk about something
They don't they don't fucking care. They don't care about we cara. So like
I I feel I feel kind of bad
Um, I don't because because I see people in the comment section sort of sort of like blame my friends too much
And and I I gotta you know, I gotta play defense because you know, they're my friends, but
Yeah, I mean
I yeah, like I I get it
I get I get how
It's a little annoying that some of them seem to be kind of not some of them some of them seem to get a little annoyed
But yeah, I can understand like thinking about how you set up an event like this
I can understand how it comes
Or to this I don't know
It's it's kind of just funny like when you and that one guy sort of like get pissed at each other
It's just pretty funny actually. It's like oh, oh, what's this? Oh, what's gonna happen? Oh, it's okay. Oh, it's okay
It's okay. Well, I I appreciate that at least someone likes likes what the the emergent narrative
Of the lecture. That's how I that's how I see it. Uh, I
You gotta do a lecture about this that
Oh man, uh, uh, one of my friends feels really bad about uh about how the lecture came out
And I always have to tell him that it's like it's fine. It's not a big deal
Yeah, it's not that big. It's not it's really not and like I would I would love to do to do another one with them
And I I think I think they'd be a lot more behaved
That's how that's how you do it because now you've um, you know, you've broken their will. Mm true
Now now they'll be docile. They know what they're in for and uh
No, hopefully they'll be more behaved next time
I had another question. I know the youtube question for you. Did you're um you the the fucking um, oh god
The dx video game man
Oh, oh, oh that come back that that's the other that was the second videos of yours. I saw and I liked it
um, all right, so uh
To anyone unaware which I assume is both give gamers tavern and most of the people watching this, uh, I uh want to like
I started making videos back in
2017 I think and um one of the first ever videos I did was uh, it was like a
A recommendation video for this this japanese television show called game center cx
I heard of that which which is uh, uh, I think
I think most people would probably be familiar as the source of the his smile and optimism gone
Yeah, it's it the premise of the show is that this this uh,
Japanese like comedian plays retro video games and tries to beat them in like a day
And uh, you know like comedy
Comes out of these situations. He has to like help
Yeah, he has to get like his like producers or directors to like help him out in certain sections
It's a really good show and uh, I wanted to make a youtube video kind of just like recommending it to people
As a recommendation video, it was good because it really did make me want to watch the series
But I never actually did that the so I guess it wasn't good enough
It it it's fine because it's kind of hard to find online at least nowadays
I believe the the guy's name is arino or something arino. Yeah, uh shinya arino
Yeah, I've seen a lot of his stuff
He's pretty good pretty cool. He's really great. I I love the show a lot and um
the
The basic idea of the video was that like I pretty much give a rundown of the plot
Of of the show why I like it and I gave a bunch of like recommendations for
Several episodes if that video sounds cool and you wanted to watch it
I'm sorry, but
It got taken down like a month ago
On uh, it it got copyright striked by uh by the people who own game center cx because you know, I
Use footage from the show in the video and like I I can't really be too
Like surprised about it. I'm disappointed obviously, but like
Back in like 2014 or 15 or so like uh, the rights the rights owners. I think fuji tv
They started they started going like really draconian on game center cx on youtube
so
It was only a matter of time before it uh, it got struck it got struck
And I think the reason why it got struck now of all times is I recently passed like a thousand subscribers
So I got monetization on my videos
So I that that might have that might have uh tipped them off
The you you attract you drew the eye of sorrow. It's yeah
We know how it is uh fair use doesn't exist on youtube it exists only in the courts
Yeah, well what what sucks even harder about it is uh
Is I also got copyright struck for uh for this like amv I did a few months ago around the same time
I I got monetization obviously I didn't monetize that video but
So I have two strikes on my channel
And uh, if I make another oopsie within I think the next like 10 days, uh, my channel's gone
Oh, that's not good. Yeah, uh, so I'll have to be a little more careful. It's it's not it's not that bad
I'm more just disappointed that um
I wasn't really that disappointed when the amv got taken down because you know
It was really more of an like an indulgent side project
But I was really sad when the game center video got taken down because that was like that was like one of my first videos
Where I was like, yeah, I really like this and it was one of the
It was one of my only videos that uh from early on that isn't like
based off of other people's work that is
That that that did good
In like the yeah, I saw I saw you tweet that it was down and I was like, oh fuck
I remember liking that video and uh, just I don't know. It's damn shame
I'll have to find some other way to like upload it, but whatever. Yeah an archive. It's somehow. Yeah, it's still on my computer
You know, it's uh, I played actually a game based on the game center
Dx show back in 2009 for the ds retro game challenge. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, I've actually never played that game, but I heard yeah, I've heard it's great
Uh, I have a review on it on my website actually
I'll have to read that I published a view. What did you give it? Um, I don't remember. I think like an 80%
or something. All right, respectable. Yeah, respectable. Yeah, I published a review back. Um
Uh, I published a review actually back when I played it in 2009
damn
I forget how I always forget that like you've been doing this for a really long time gamers 7
Like yeah, for some reason I've been doing it for too long
Sometimes I feel like I've been doing this for too long
So coming coming up close to the 20 year anniversary
Are you gonna throw a party?
Uh, just a website itself or the brand I guess you can say
Yeah
You should have a party you should have a
Zoom a zoom call. I'll come I'll come to the zoom party. Yeah, that's a good idea
Maybe you could do a stream
Yeah
Yes, hopefully hopefully covid would be done by then
Hopefully
God bless god willing
mwah
So, uh, I don't know what else? Um, well, what else is up? I can I can talk about this thing that was going on
Um, was there any more to say about about the any of that before we move on? Oh, oh, please continue talking about my
Yeah, no, it's it's okay
Uh, check out gamers 7 on youtube.com. Okay
Yeah, I mean tectonic impromptu. No, fuck gamers 7 never sit
Okay, okay. Yeah. Yeah, sure everyone check to do it. Just spread it out spread love. Sorry
All right, fuck me. I'm sorry. I'll leave. I'll go. I'll go. I apologize
by the uh, so I have been
um
Past month past few weeks helping my brother to clear out his room
Uh, because it is I know about this because I listen to the money spenders podcast. Yeah, the money
com slash give and take
Give and take the money spenders podcast the only place where you should spend your money
Um, it's a great place to do that if you're looking for somewhere
uh, but uh
Yeah, I've been helping him clear out all of the junk
We've been going through all of the shelves and things and like holding them up to his face
Like do you care about this? Is this important to you? It's like, uh, I guess I don't know
Bags bags upon bags of trash. It's great
It's really satisfying to see it being clean and he's obviously happy that he can move around in there
And then I was looking at my room and I was like
I gotta do the same thing to my room. Even though it's not as bad
It's still like there's there's shelves of books here that I've never read
And I always say to myself, I'll read these
And I was thinking how do I gamify because I'm like I'm stupid like I like I can't do things unless there's a video game
Involved need to have achievements
Yeah, I need I need like to gamify reading all these books
And so that I can get rid of them and have shelf space to put more video games
Or something stupid like that
And I was thinking what if what if I like
first of all
Because I I like listing things
I was thinking of like making an itinerary of everything I have
And then doing like a list and being like, all right, let's
100 percent complete these books by reading them and then I don't know rating them on a youtube video saying
This book sucked. This book was good. And then throwing them away. Finally after all these years
I can get rid of these this trash
You can uh, don't eat garbage
Can't you burn the books?
I do when I get rid of them. I donated like charity shop thing to the trash that is
Yeah, don't make them back to the earth. My scuttle read too
Um, so I throw them in the in a in a pit. Have you have you done any book reading? No
Okay, look, look, she's only introduced the concept. She she still needs to she still needs to work on the execution. It's fine
I have I have I have a certain I have a gripe
I have something you know what really grinds my gears what really grinds my gears
Stop me if I've said this on the show before
Um, but fucking fucking uh last year for christmas
I gave uh the conquest of bread by kropotkin to my sister
My brother to my to my brother nate and to nate's girlfriend michelle. I heard about this from michelle
And yeah, good and michelle. Well, you heard about it from her. Uh, yeah, I think so on like your twitter or something
Oh, yeah, yeah, um no clue
And she maybe in the discord uh she she and she said she was gonna read 50 books this year
And she's like she she's like almost there. She's read like 40 something books. It's almost the end of the year
48 and she has not read
She's read 50 books. She has not read the book that I gave her the conquest of bread. It's literally like 100 pages
It's like shorter than a fucking animorphs book
She has not read it
But she keeps posting the book she's read and every single book she's read is some stupid self-help book about how cleaning your room
Will make you happier. That's every single fucking book
How many how many books do you need to read that tell you to clean your room?
Just fucking do it or don't we're all those books written by jordan peterson
No, she reads the girl version Marie condo
Marie condo, I mean, I've heard those are youtuber. I was watching and he cited that as like, oh, it's a really good book
I'm sure it's a great book. I'm sure it's a great. He disseminated all the information in that book into one sentence
So now I don't have to read it. He said
In the book they say look it around to your room and
See if what you have sparks joy and if it doesn't spark joy, consider getting rid of things
Consider fucking get ending it all
What if like I was like looking and owning things just makes me feel good
I love
Looking at things like I have a bunch of shit in my room. You're like a dwarf. Well, yeah
You're like a dwarf who gets happy when they observe a masterwork craft
When they see when they see like a nice like a really like nice like artifact like great in the floor with like
With like engraving. It's like masterwork quality with like engravings of carrots on it. You go. Ah, yes, the neurons are firing
Um, fuck you michel
Don't
At least she's doing it despite you
Uh
Just fucking bread books a good book. It's a good book. I it's short. It's digestible
I used to have I used to have a problem where like my room would be
hopelessly messy
And I don't know what happened, but just like one day I was like, I'm gonna clean my room
This is way before jordan pierced and by the way before he was even born and uh, I just spent
I spent the day I spent the day cleaning
You were the original jordan. I really was I really was I spent the day cleaning my room and it looked I mean it looked
Decent it looked fine. It looked fine enough. There were there were places to walk around
There wasn't clothes strung along the floor and like ever since I've never really had a problem with having a dirty room
It's not yeah, it's not in the best shape right now, but it's you know, it's presentable. I guess maybe
I have um
Because I just I basically just finished up um all the um all my kickstarter stuff
I had all these boxes all around my room is pretty small and I had like half of it just taken up with like
Boxes and like packing materials and like piles of envelopes and piles of books and stuff
And I I have only just like like yesterday on the day before I like
You know packed all that shit up and like put it in put it in in the closet and stuff
And like put it in a stack and put it like behind my my little like side room curtain or whatever and uh
It actually doesn't feel much different
um
Uh
I don't know i'm i'm
I feel like it felt like it was all cluttered
And so I put everything away and honestly it doesn't feel that much less cluttered and i'm a little disappointed frankly
The change I didn't the change wasn't drastic enough
It wasn't drastic enough
It wasn't like because I I was keeping a lot of it under my my like table
so
Like you know, it wasn't like space that I was losing
Yeah
Now the now the space under my table is just empty and it's just wasted. So like whatever
I don't know. I thought it was gonna be like, uh, I'm gonna feel so much mental clarity after like I remove all this clutter
and I put it away and
Oh, no, my mind is still cluttered
Fuck you can organize your room, but you can't organize your mind
What do you mean do I live in a triangle then you have like a like a triangle room is really small from what I've seen
A triangle room
The ceiling is slanted, isn't it?
Oh, um on one side it is. Yeah, I used to have one of those kind of rooms
They have like a name for them. It's like something about it's like it's not like an attic room, but it's
My room is not my room is not a bedroom
It is um
It is it is technically like a side. Although it's not although it's not much smaller than the bedrooms
Um by floor space, but I guess in terms of sheer volume
It is smaller because it does have the the slanted roof. I think it just sort of makes it feel
Basically, I haven't been there, but in video. I've seen
That one video where it's like it feels claustrophobic, but I don't know
I think there's like a zoning thing where where like a bedroom
Can only be considered a bedroom if it's like something square feet and has like a window
Your room has a window, right?
My room actually has very nice windows. My room it has
It's it's about the same size as the as like the regular bedrooms in terms of floor space
It's it's missing volume because it's got the slanted roof. It's got like a half closet like a low half closet
Um that you that is only like up to like my my chest height
Um and that's next to my bed and then it's actually got it's got a little side alcove that I have some bookshelves in
And I have a hanger bar between the two ends like between the two walls of this little like side alcove
The alcove also has a little slanted roof and I have a nice piece of modern art
Uh, uh nailed to the the slanted like like half roof up there. Oh, what's it's name? I?
I it's nameless uncultured. It's it's it's but it's but it's an original. It's an original
Your room is uh your room is missing volume like a lost book
You know lost volume. Oh got it. I thought you were gonna go
Sound decibels. Um wait. I gotta finish but then the alcove
I have my little hanger bar and I have my I have like sweaters and jackets hanging on that
And it makes like a nice little curtain to sort of cordon off that little alcove. It's really nice
It's really I planned it out so beautifully and the behind that I have bookshelves and then on the wall
I don't just have one window. I have the nicest windows in the whole house
I have a big like three window thing
I have one huge window that like takes up half the wall and then I have two little windows to the sides of it
My like front wall is like all window. It's like mwah. Mwah
And then because I need to sleep until like 6 p.m
And go to bed at like 10 a.m. Every day
I just have all I have them all blackout curtain. I have like stuff like
Hanging up over the window so I can't see out of them and no light gets in
It's a very economical setup. It really makes a whole lot of sense. I had um, I had blackout curtains for a bit
They were pretty cool, but I didn't really have much need for them
I didn't have them for a while because I was on like a reasonable sleep schedule
But then like a month or two ago, uh that
Changed and now I need the blackout curtains again lemau
Well, my room is pretty organized
uh at all times
Kind of a bit of a neat boy neat freak
Really, I just imagined gamer's tavern's room kind of looks like how ridin's room is described in middle gear solid 2
It's just the bed and the desk nothing else. Yeah, that's pretty much it
It's um empty and sterile just like my soul
Spartan
Yeah, I mean
You don't have you don't have the vice the vice of possession holding you
You don't you don't feel the need to have things in your room to fill the void in your heart. You just have puns
Well, I used to uh own a lot of uh video games, but a couple years back
I sold I think over 300 or 400 games
So that really freed up a lot of space on this
I I just hate the idea of games being sold. I don't I don't know why I even if they're selling anything
I I hate when I'm getting real stuff
when I was fucking um when I was like uh
In high school or something or maybe earlier. I don't remember. I think I was trying to get money
Me and Nate were trying to get money for a I think was for a playstation 2
Oh, yeah, and so we sold and so we sold a bunch of our old nes games
We sold them to gamestop and gamestop gave us like the worst fucking price for them
Like admittedly a lot of them are genuinely just worthless
But we had an original nes copy of kid Icarus
That actually is kind of rare and like actually we should have actually gotten like a bit of I think they give us like eight bucks for
Yeah, you should never uh sell anything to gamestop. That's a complete waste of money. Yeah less than learned
Yeah, less than learned that like around the time the playstation 2 was new was also like the
Probably like the time when like nes and super nintendo games were probably at like their lowest value
No one gave a shit about them until like
Well, um, uh, probably around the time that video game reviewers started popping up on youtube
It was that really was that before that was a thing. I don't yeah, I think I
I know that um, they contributed to the games now are quite uh quite pricey. Yeah
Let me see what it what it would cost now kid
Icarus nes
Nes games actually are not too expensive now, but for some reason super nintendo games have gone up a lot
Well, they're it's the best console. So
Of course, yeah, I agree
PS2 is the best one because I I'll concede I'll concede the ps2. In fact, you know what um here
I'm going to shill a friend of mine's channel
uh
Who the who is reviewing every playstation 2 game known to man
Oh, is it um, is it no? Yeah, it's no no
Yeah, no toxicity
Another friend of the show we all I I you you and uh, and and uh him or both
I I mostly know you from my discord. Yeah, we're you guys are long time
Uh hangers out in there. We're from we're from way back the from from the way way back the dark ages
Uh
Yes, and I I saw he just passed like a thousand subs too. He did I'm I'm really happy for him because and like
I have a feeling reps to gog is like very close to to kind of blowing up in a way because the concept of the channel
What does it stand for? We review every ps2 game. Oh god
Okay, it's I've seen that and recommend it. I'm surprised. It's only like a thousand subs
It's he he only started it like um, like
Maybe
Six months or so ago
It's it's going it's going to blow up because the concept is so
It's just so like as an idea for a channel. It's only a matter of time. I was like, oh cool
I I would definitely want to get around to that. I assumed it was already a big channel
Just because I I don't get recommended small channels usually
It's it's really funny how the how the idea for like reps to gog started because me null and
A couple of other friends were just in a discord call it for in the morning
I don't remember who it was who brought it up
But like someone was like what if what if we made like a youtube channel where we reviewed every single playstation 2 game
And of course it was like 4 a.m. So we're like, oh, this is there must be like race idea ever
There must be like a thousand games on the playstation 2. It'll be quite an honor taking
I think it has the most besides maybe the we yeah
That's that's part of the appeal
I think the other thing is
It would literally go on for like 10 years
If you did one every week, I think I think he did the calculations where like he would be finished with him in like
In like over 70 years if he did a video
Yeah, because a lot of these games are like uh 50 hour rpgs
Yep
Yeah, he just he just recently finished a video of a um
Of like a tactical rpg
And I think I think it's his best video he's made so far
So if you're interested then yeah, check out his uh his review of eternal poison
Eternal poison. Yeah, I'm surprised I've never heard of that because tactical rpgs were my favorite genre back in the p2 era
It was like a it was like a late release. I think it came out in like 2006 or seven
Okay
Hmm
neat
Yeah
Yeah, continuing on the idea of like 100 completing my shelf
I have
Had a like list of every game that I could conceivably play at any time
Uh, which is like all the games I physically own all the games that are downloaded on my ps3 and ps4
All the games in my steam and epic games libraries and all that
And I'm like sometimes I just go to that list and I look at all of the things I've I've like
Organized it so that I can search by release date and and stuff like that and I've always wanted to like
Complete all of them just because it sucks to have things purchased and never played and never done anything with even if
They suck and I would not like them. I just want to say I did play them. You need to get blood out of that stone
Yeah, I feel the same way
A few years ago. I started an account on backloggery. I think it's backloggery dot something
Uh, so I've been keeping track of everything I've finished and need to finish on on that site
And it's pretty useful to that end
Yeah, like making reviews is a good like I
It's a very good concept that we review every ps2 game because it's just like a very good, you know
Excuse to to play a lot of ps2 games that you would have never given a second thought like I'll get around to that like 40 years later
Yeah, it's turn to dust and you've also turned to dust
So it's like it does seem a little bit unrealistic though. Um
Yeah, the the iconography of the channel is supposed to be like sisyphus pushing the boulder up the hill
Yeah, so so like in that very clever
I I think you're
The at the point the idea of the channel at least for for for my for my lens is that uh
Is that it's like you everyone is aware that this is like
Impossible, but you want to see how far it can go anyway, you know
Hmm
I mean the the right thing to do if you wanted to actually complete it would be to have like a team and
Certain people only play and review certain games and you would have that's that's kind of how this started
Was uh, you had a crowd source it because I because me and a couple of other friends were
were uh
We're supposed to also do reviews in fact if you go like early
Early into the channel's life you can see that there's a couple of other
Other people reviewing the games like I I made a review on Unreal Tournament for the ps2 on there
Uh, and I think I also reviewed a this game orphan scion of sorcery
Yeah, I played that I know that one. It's not good
Yeah, that's uh, that was one of the first ones I got for the ps2. It was yeah, it was a launch title
um
So and like that was that was the idea that like we all we all pitch in and make like reviews
It's like a collective thing, but like, you know
We just kind of all sort of fell off except for null, you know, god bless him. He's the only one who's really kept the torch alive
I I just kind of wanted to focus more on on like the main channel stuff
but um, yeah, I
I'm definitely open to making more for his channel because
Because I like the I like the concept so much and I would love to write his coattails when he gets popular
Haha, that's how you do it. I think somebody has already done this idea for NES games, uh, probably
Which is a lot more doable. I think it was devoo. It was devoo
She was um, she had the idea to to let's play to let's play every NES game
And then they they had a few episodes where they did let's play is what back when let's plays were a thing everyone was doing
Remember let's play and she would have she had like a big master file of every NES game
And she would just play one for like five minutes and be like, okay got it next one
Okay, this sucks or this is fine. Uh, but I get it. Yeah, and it's like per per episode
There was like, I don't know three or four they would do because like devoo actually wanted to like
structure
She wanted to structure it in a in such a way that it could actually be feasibly
Completable, but I don't think they got very far
Um, even though they were only doing a few minutes on each game
Well, there is a there is a let's play. I've been watching brother. I remember like
I think I remember that devoo's brother was really annoying
Or maybe wasn't her brother. Someone was really annoying and would like yell and I found it very off-putting
Is that the brother that like broke a hole in her door one night or something?
I don't know that story, but maybe I remember I remember her talking about it on the pcp a long time ago
Oh nest quest nest quest was what those were called and someone would yell and I hated them
We need a reboot player late
Well, uh, there was a there's a let's play. I've been following for over 10 years now named zeta plays
And uh, he's been trying to play every single uh, super nintendo nes and genesis game
ever made
How far he's been doing it for a while
I think he has around 10 000 subscribers now. That's cool
The lifelong endeavor there's there's this other guy who who makes um
Who who makes like uh retrospective videos his name's uh, jeremy perish
He he's oh, yeah, I know him. Yeah, he has this uh
He has these retrospectives called like nes works gameboy works and all that stuff and like the point of them is to
Chronicle every single game and he he has he has like a lot of production value behind him because uh, he's like one of the
One of the guys behind like retronauts
Uh, he used to work. I think he used to work for one up. He did. Yeah or something, right?
Yeah, so he's he's like he's like legit site
And he's done he's done like all sorts of other
Retrospectives like he he has covered every single virtual boy game
Like he just spent like a year doing all the virtual boy games, which admittedly it isn't much, but
It's uh, it's still they're great videos. I'd recommend it. I I did the the same thing on my website
I reviewed every single virtual boy game one year
Oh, yeah
Yeah, even like the japanese only ones
Yeah, and I also reviewed some of the prototypes that were never officially released. Oh, yeah
That's the virtual boy is like weird because
It's
Wait, wait, wait. I okay. I swear. I've seen a video from like the the gaming historian
And I think he went over every virtual boy game and there's like eight of them
Uh, they're am I am I crazy? I think there's like 20 something, but there there really isn't a lot
Yeah, I think there's around 16 to 20 something
probably around that much
It's you know, it's not as impressive as reviewing every ps2 game, but you know a lot of these virtual boy games aren't that great and
Yeah, that's that's the entire reason why I reviewed all of them because I figured there's not that many of them
Might as well just do them all. Yep. Yeah
For all the like people that still own a virtual boy
Yeah, why is why is completing things so fucking satisfying? It just feels so fucking good. It's on our bones
Even if it would never happen the idea of somebody cataloguing all video games like there's too many
There's too many of any one console for one person to play in a reasonable amount of time
And then also talk about them. But the idea is just so tantalizing
I I love it. I want to do it all the time
I think part of it is the is like the idea that like
Uh, like for the viewers like
Oh, eventually
He will review or they will review the game. I like and I can't wait for that
And whereas like the person
Making them or or whatever
They it's just it's just a good way to have like
A structured channel and like a body of work, right?
Yeah, it gives you plenty of content. Yeah
but um
You know yms your movie sucks. Yeah. Yeah, I know him he he does those the videos of like best movies of x year
And his gimmick is that he watches every single movie that came out in that year, which is why they're so late
And they come out years after
They come out like yeah like years late and that's crazy like that gimmick is why I really am
Hype for those even though I don't care about
Basically everything he talks about right movies. I don't care about all of the art house films
It's nice to know it's just nice to know that he has watched everything from that year and this is his favorite
I think I find yms's taste in movies a little dumb
Honestly, I don't know if I really agree with
Like some things that I that I like but there are definitely some movies that he likes that I think are stupid
Have have you ever?
Uh, jeez. I'm gonna open a can of worms with this. I can tell uh, have you ever seen anomaliesa?
Have not it's it was a um, it's like a
It's like a stop motion. I think stop motion like puppet movie by a is it
Yeah, who's it by uh, uh charlie kaufman. I think
Okay, or and it's it's also written by like one of the guys who did moral oral and um
Yeah, that's like one that's like one of yms's movies like favorite movies ever and I knew this
And I was recommended it like I think last month or so to watch it and I watched it and I was like
I I could like kind of see why people like it
But it it definitely was like
Not for me and I feel like that's the case for a lot of a lot of adam's tastes
Yeah, but it's like but I respect it. You know despite despite not having the same movie taste or even caring so much about movies that
It's the completionist aspect that really gets me interested like knowing the fact that he has seen
Every single movie it kind of puts it kind of puts the list up on a pedestal, right?
Like even if you don't agree with this, it's an interesting idea
But kind of crazy
Yeah, I kind of wanted to do the same thing for like
um
Like playing all of the games from a certain year or at least all of the ones from a certain year that I own already because I
That's too many games come out every year for that to even happen
Like the idea of it's less like I could I could do that like I play every game that I owned that was released before I was born
That could be a fun project
Yeah, that's cool. Just just something's like
It's like pointless. It's pointless and it doesn't mean anything because it's only
It's only for me to like check boxes and like I just is autistic
Well, if it makes you feel just you just described all human endeavor. Oh, no
It makes you feel good. Yeah, that's not that pointless
Do you do you like um, do you like the completionist? I say pointless to like I say pointless to like
um
To distance myself from from it so that I don't have to admit to anything. Yeah. Yeah, like so I don't have to admit to liking something
But yes, it's not like uh, like the um, what's his name? Gerard something the completionist Gerard
Khalil the completionist eyes. I have watched some of his videos
and I
just
I think there was something about him
He's very standard like game reviewer, you know, he he was his gimmick of completing a game 100%
I I've always felt like it wasn't
It was sort of false advertising. Yeah more of a marketing gimmick than it is an actual thing
He does because like technically completes the game
But what he says is basically a simple review about what is the game and what how it's good or bad
And he you know, it's just very standard. I wanted him to go into like how difficult it is to to complete the things
I don't know. It feels like he doesn't go into his gimmick enough like he he leans too closely into
like the standard game reviewer instead of being like
Like he I think he has like his own last I watched him anyway, which is a long time ago
He had this like his own this own like section just devoted to the completionist part
But then but that's like only a piece of the video the rest of the video is just a review and I think I think a channel
That uh that leans more into that completionist gimmick. It might not be as popular, but I think it's more compelling
It probably just does it for the marketing purposes. Yeah, yeah
Like an interesting gimmick
He seems like a cool guy like um, I remember a few years ago
like he used to have a partner that worked on videos with him and uh his partner like left
And he also like when he left he was like, yeah, you need to take down all of the videos I was in
Uh, because I don't want them on the channel anymore
And he was like and he like complied even though he really didn't have to because that's like that's such a stupid request to make
But like uh, I think his name was uh, was it greg?
Yeah, greg that was his name
It yeah, I heard about that. It was uh, kind of like another jauntron situation
It kind of was
And I might be misremembering things because this was a long time ago and I'm not like a huge completionist head
But uh, but that's at least it wasn't at least it wasn't a ronnie from uh game game theories situation
I don't even know who that is. I only know the guy who killed himself. Oh fuck. Okay
The original editor of game theory who killed himself. Yeah, my god
And he was and he was the guy who made um, oh he had his own series on the channel
uh
Side quest digressing and side questing
Uh, I never never knew about that one. You know, what was kind of sad about um
From my perspective any anyways what we said about uh, greg leaving the completionist is that
There weren't very many comments being sad about it. Most of them actually were like, uh, good. I'm glad he's gone
That's kind of why that's always kind of awkward. Why would they be glad he's gone because uh for some reason
It seems like um, a lot of the comments didn't like greg even when he was on the show and they were constantly complaining about him
Uh, so when he left a lot of people. Oh, so he was so he was kind of he was kind of the ben saint of the whole
Yeah, basically
Did he did he leave in in a huff or was it something else? Yeah, he left in a huff. There was a problem
He actually like I don't know the details of what happened, but uh, I think he was upset. He wasn't being paid enough or something
I'm not sure
Yeah, again, I I I'm I don't know the details exactly
but uh
It's just a kind of situation and gerard really came out of it looking like the the bigger man
Yeah, but it's still kind of I still kind of feel bad for him because uh, you know
When john left when john left game grumps, everybody was really sad that he left
But when when this guy left the completionist, it seems like nobody cared or nobody was sad about it
That is kind of sad
Yeah
So the fact that nobody was sad actually kind of makes me sad about it
That just means yeah, I want you to be gamers tavern
Yeah
Oh, there's this guy more men like you this one guy
Similar to the completion. Well, not really similar to the completionist that I watched. Um called lord cat
Oh, yeah, okay. Wait, wait, wait
Okay, I know lord cat only from I had a chance the down the rabbit hole
About a spoonie. That's the only thing I know about it. I haven't watched that video
But he's he's a that guy with a glasses person
I don't know much about him personally, but his review show that he had was got a small dick and you're fucking afraid of it
Yeah, epic, um, I was gonna show
His show was called uh until we win
And it was strangely compelling. I don't think he was very popular
um
but his videos were like
He takes a really difficult game like battle toads or something some old nes game and he details
his his like
Struggle and strategy and eventual overcoming of obstacles to complete the nes game
No matter how difficult it is and we're gonna play it until we win and then like rock music plays
That's uh game center. That is kind of like game center. Yeah, it's basically the same idea. It's it's a good premise
Um, I I enjoyed that because it's a good premise if you're bad at games
Yeah, well, he was quite good at games as far as if you're a pro gamer then like what's even there's no there then that's like no gimmick at all
Like of course you'll win
The thing is that he would play like games that would stump other people and be like
Like like really annoying and no one would ever go through getting through this like pumpkin head
I think he played which is like this early pc or
or something 3d game that was
Had you know like a lot asked of the player in order to complete it, but he did it and it was like that's cool
That's what I wanted out of the completionist more of that sort of that hype moment, but it was very
Sort of clinical and uninteresting kind of milk test
Yeah, I think I think one of the reasons why false advertising
Yeah, I think one of the reasons why lord cat never really got that big is because like
He he has a break his personality is like really abrasive and you can tell just from like watching him for a short while
But it's not like it's not abrasive in like an endearing way like spoonies was
Mmm, we're like spoonie spoonie is like abrasive, but he's also pretty funny too
And so you can kind of like you can kind of like take it in stride, but like lord cat is
Lord cat almost feels like too mean in a way
Lord cat's a brute spoonie is like a witty witty snark. Yeah, he's like
Spoonie is he's like a loser. You're a loser
I'm sorry, that's the only that's that it's it's funny that you describe him as like being aggressive because the one thing
That I've ever heard of him is he's like on his furious rant about how much he hates spoonie. You and that idiot Joe
That's a coincidence
Uh
It's good stuff. Did just the ancient lore behind all that stuff
Mm-hmm
Uh, what I guess is that it is that all we have to say about uh, what are we even talking about?
Uh, has anyone heard of the piss the pissed off video gamer? Does anybody know that guy? That's just sounds like
It's very generic. I think that might not is that a real person. Let me let me check
It's it's this incredibly obese guy that was like clearly inspired by the angry video game nerd
I think I've heard of this
And he is uh
I thought you were joking. I know the irate gamer
He's worse
Wow
Wait pissed off gamer is worse than the irate gamer. Yes. It's it's more of like a lol cow situation that it is like a
content creator
I think I think I've heard of this guy
I just always assume with stuff like this that that he's like
That it's like supposed supposed to be satire. Maybe that's
Maybe that's just me like protecting myself
but uh, maybe um
The thing with this guy, it's he's just kind of funny
um
He's made this this this this video about the the nintendo shitcruel
and uh
He's he basically
I don't want to be too mean
But he's breathing heavily and he clearly doesn't know how to speak very well
And the whole review is just him sort of like saying
the nintendo
shitcube
is
Not good
It sounds pretty sounds pretty good
It's it sounds like me. I I kind of love it. I kind of love listening to him
It kind of reminds me of uh francis trying to do like a bit
But it's it's hard to tell what is a bit and what is him
because I mean
He's not in the best way
Reminds me of uh, which is named boogie when he used to do those francis things. Oh, yeah. Yeah, but like actual
I think he still does that
Oh my god
Is this real is this real this guy? I think he is yes
Is this is being serious? Okay
This isn't even like that early
This looks like it would be from like 2007. Well, this is a real
This is a real. Oh, okay. Okay. Okay. So so like if it's that early on I'd
Not to say that satire wasn't invented until like 2010 or anything
But I I think back then there were a lot more people like genuinely trying stuff like this
Yeah, you should know that uh
Maddox invented satire in 97
Oh true true. I forgot about that. Did he I forgot. So I guess did he say that or something?
Yeah
This was him actually
Wow, you know, he lost a lot of weight and uh, yeah, good for him
I'm just what oh god. Oh god. Oh no, this is depressing
On the reason I call it the nintendo shit cube
is
That is a piece of fucking shit
It's pretty good
He's telling like it
You should just make like a like a parody of this video
No, no
I can't do it. Not nearly as good as other people. Well, first you have to get really fat
I I yeah, I gotta pack on the pounds. I just buy a fat suit
Commit no, no, no, you gotta be you gotta be uh authentic
Method act as the pissed off video that's called production value
I gotta get a really shitty camera. I gotta get a terrible mic
Hmm
The scour the all of it daniel dameron. I gotta I gotta paint stakingly recreate his room as it appears
Well, I mean you are saying that you cleaned your room so and his room's pretty clean looking
So you're already you already got that down
Yeah, his room is not too bad. I can't even understand. I've never come to think of it
I've never seen game give and pissed off video gamer in the same place at the same time true true
I think we're I think we're on to you really makes you think
Um, well, I mean, where is your proof, huh? Where is your proof?
Burden the proof lies on you slams desk objection evidence, please
No, you need to proof read your proof
No, you she can't do it. She can't defend herself. She's got nothing looks like we want this argument then
Going for the kill
Stop killing me
You would like that wouldn't you
I would I would like it if you stop killing me stabs
No, this is worse than
Being in hell. This is terrible. Oh, you want me to stop executing you sounds like someone who's guilty
guilty would say
You've walked right into our trap
You've walked right into our life is a cage and death is the key
Ah, that's a good one. Would you find that one? Would you come up with it yourself?
I think I got it from a real cool person
Wow
Hey, hey, hey gibb. Yeah, fuck you. Okay. Fuck you. I'll get right on that
No, fuck your whole country. I mean, yeah, sure. All right. Piece of shit. Uh, uh, vat tax
Uh, uh, it's bullshit. Oh, yeah, that is I hate it so much. It's it's so shit. Let me just let me just complain about this
So I get done I get done sending out all the rfck kickstarter stuff and
and it turns out and in in
You alerted me of it and I guess this is just a uk thing and maybe there were some other countries to do it too
but because of the vat the import vat tax it costs
so much
to just fucking
For you I already paid the postage to send the package to you and it just cost you like
60 fucking dollars just to merely accept it to just have it be delivered to you even though it's already there
And um, I don't I don't really understand
Why I don't get it and I'm and I'm pissed off because I already charged a
I already charged a small like shipping fee for anyone outside the country
So I said to everyone in rfck like if you have to pay this I will cover it
I will cover it out of the the funds because I don't I already charge you for shipping
Uh, uh, the other one
Kola the one that made the the biggest order she got it's it's it's gonna be it's like a hundred and it's like a hundred and fifty dollars
Or it's like over a hundred fucking dollars just for her to like accept her fucking package
And I'm so fucking pissed at the government
Fuck the government. I'll agree. So wait was the
the um
How much was my pin amount like because I think it was because of how you've you you labeled the
Value of the items and they say oh, yeah trading valuable goods. That's we're gonna have to
Take money from you for that
You're I don't remember like
I think your pledge was like 70 bucks or something. Yeah, and so I don't remember I don't remember like how much
was uh like look I get to the post office thinking that I'm just gonna send these packages and they're like
No, no, you have to fill out a form you have to fill out a customs form and I'm like uh
Okay, and I'm in line and there's people waiting behind me
And they're like they're looking at me and like I'm holding them up and like I'm I'm sweating
Like I'm actually like sweating standing there
I'm just like frantically trying to fill these customs forms out to just get my shit sent in the mail
I I don't even remember what I put for the value. I probably just like put like
It just probably just picked a random fucking number and put it down there
Uh, uh, and um, maybe I put like a hundred dollars or something
And probably you should have put one dollar
I I should have yeah, I should have
Because like I thought that putting a higher value would maybe like ensure the package for more
And I thought that that would be covered by postage, but it's not it's just it literally the quest there
I'm them asking for the value is literally just like how much should we fucking
How how much should we extort out of the person you're sending this to because you're sending it to them?
But I didn't know I didn't know that's why they were asking or I would have undervalued
I think I probably overvalued it and I don't know it's gonna cost me a
It's gonna cost me an arm and a leg, but whatever
Live and learn I guess
Piece of shit never be on never tell the government the truth. That's what I've learned preach
Uh, uh, they will they will use it. They will use the truth against you
Oh, speaking of the government. I gotta do my taxes soon. I keep thinking about it. Oh, yeah
Keep thinking about that old document thing. Really? You have to do your taxes at the end of the year
We have like four months to do them. Well, they said you got until the end of january
But you may as well do it now. So I'm like, yeah, I guess I may as well do it now
You haven't done April
I still haven't paid my taxes from last year
Because they were due in april, but I got an extension to october
didn't ever and then you
Uh, I had to apply for it, but it was like very easy to apply. I literally just like clicked a button and they were like, yeah, you've been approved
Um, no, there was everyone got an extension till like june or something right?
That was like a further extension that I that I applied for till october. That's interesting. I think for for me
They said, yeah, you don't have to pay taxes for
We just like you're off the hook give just you no no not not for 20
Well, those are no those are my 2019 taxes
Whatever the the one that like they're saying you just
For the for the tax year of something to something you don't have to pay that one
But you do need to pay this next one. So I'm like, was that because of like a covid relief? I I'm pretty sure it was
Yeah, god fucking dammit. Why is america so shit?
Why is america such fucking dog shit? Holy fuck
God damn. I have to pay like 2000 fucking dollars in taxes for 2019. It's a nightmare. I get money Jesus cry
I love doing my taxes
Oh my god, but that's because I love doing when you think of your self-employed taxes are the worst fucking thing in the world
I think when you're self-employed you get screwed in taxes more
Yeah, it's it's so bad. It's so bad
I like doing my taxes when it turns out that I don't have to pay them. It's like I can write everything off
Oh, that's nice. Love to say it. Taxes are very taxing
That's why they call them that
It's true. I have to pay
I have to pay I had to pay a ton. I had to pay a ton in taxes. I'm hoping
I'm gonna claim like so many deductions. I'm gonna claim like every fucking deduction from
The all these kick starters and stuff. I don't know. I'm hoping to have a lot to write off
I think uh, I don't know uh too much about this
But I think in order to get around this issue when you're self-employed is to start an LLC
I don't oh god, haven't you all talked about making the pcp in LLC?
Like a while. Yeah
Yeah, somebody floats the idea every once in a while or they or they used to back before uh back before
Back before everyone just left. I feel like I'm just left for no reason. I feel like the only person who would have done it
Uh, hasn't been on the podcast in five months. So
Um
Nate would bring it up. I think Tom would bring it up or something. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, did you mentioned it once or twice and but like but none of us knew how to do it
Um, so it cares to learn because it was like
I gotta
The idea would come up
One of us would be like, you know, that might be a good idea
And then that would be like it. It was it was mostly just the idea of like
Oh, if we're all gonna like move into the same area to do making videos and all that funny stuff that will never happen anymore
maybe um
Then uh, it would be handy and very
much
Like smooth the process over of like me coming to america if it was an LLC that could hire me on
Yeah, you'd get a work visa rather than me having to like get an immigration something or other
There's a there's another podcast that I used to listen to years ago that had that had a similar plan
Uh to get someone from australia over to california on like work visa
Was it game grumps? No. No, it was I um, it was like a I thought it might have been ross
Also, none of them did do that. Yeah, it wasn't it wasn't yatsi
I'm I'm I'm convinced have I have I said my conspiracy theory that ross and holly's marriage was just a green card scam
I think you have back when like the pro-jaret stuff
Yeah, I think I heard you say that was holly canadian
Is
Is ross canady sounds a little bit
I don't wait
Did holly no holly lived in like
Portland
Ross I think and ross was living in america. So no no the holly was american
Can you like stay in the u.s. If you are on like green card if you divorce your
american husband or wife?
I'm not I think if you've been here long
I think if you've been here long enough you can probably
Apply for like citizenship to something. I don't I'm maybe I don't fucking know
Maybe there's like a timer
Clearly it's possible to do something like that because people appear
And they stay people up here. Well, I think uh in order to apply for citizenship
You have to have been living in the country for a certain amount of years, but I'm not sure how many years
Yeah, yeah, that's that's what I mean like if if he had been here with holly for long enough that would even if they got divorced that might
Might make it possible. I don't know. I don't know how it works
seems plausible
But the u.s. Is one of the easiest place to get a citizenship and as far as I know
Wait, what that can't be true
Um, I know the test it's the test you take is apparently really really easy
Like it's just like when was america founded?
Who is the first president?
What colors are on the flag and stuff like that? I when was america founded? Oh july 4th
Uh, um 1997 when maddox invented satire. He created the united states
Yeah, exactly as a joke as a bit
He did both sides of the war. Yeah, that's centrist maddox
I remember the the the bit from that episode of the simpsons where up who is applying for citizenship and the they ask him like
Why what was the civil war fought over and he gives like a very like nuance like detailed answer and the guy's just like
Please just say slavery
It makes it a lot easier
It's possible that uh citizenship in us has gotten harder now or maybe easier. I'm not sure but
I can't imagine why
It's not
Yeah
It's I mean it's not easy because you know, it's a whole fucking it's a whole fucking thing
There's like a million fucking people that want to come here and get citizenship
But can't and there's a million fucking people. I didn't say it was easy here on expired green cars that uh
That it's easier than in most other countries because a lot of other countries are really difficult to um
Immigrate to I don't I've I've heard that japan is particularly difficult to get into like to stay forever
There might be some countries where it's harder
But like at the uk is quite difficult as well
Commenters, please don't take this discussion too seriously. We're not informed. Yeah, we're just don't go right
I don't I don't take all of us what we're saying and then like repeat it and then assume that
I look at this like what ben said in this episode. He really needs to stop running his mouth about things. He doesn't understand
I I know I need to do more of that if anything I need to be bolder with my stupid opinions could be wrong
No, you couldn't be wrong. It's impossible. No. No. No. No. No. No. Don't say that you can't yeah on the pot on the pcp
We're never on the pcp. You fake it till you make it true. You say it's it does make sense
Uh, that the country just say that's what the pcps model does make sense for the countries to have uh,
A lot of social programs to have tighter immigration laws
Oh, social programs don't have this
Well, I mean countries to have like yeah, so I guess it should be easy
That was a joke. Yeah, I'm joking
Yeah, yeah, um, yeah, Japan
I think they just don't like non-jeffins
Yeah, and I mean who can blame them. Yeah, like they want people to come in like they want to like dilute the manga industry with like
The wrong types of drawers
The wrong types of cartoonists. We've we've all seen what happens when white people take over so
You don't want that shit if you're a japanese older brother broke his knees. Do you still call him nishan?
Wouldn't it be nishan?
Yeah, it was nishan. Uh, oh, they said sorry. Sorry
He's he's nishan nishan. It's like you like the car car. Yeah
Oh, exactly. This is all coming together. I'm gonna go pick up my nishan in my nishan from the airport
Excuse me
I'm loving this
How you're excused about
How about ebay?
You guys ebay. How about it?
You guys been on ebay lately? I've never been uh
Never actually ebay is where I uh, I don't really look at it before amazon ebay was the place to go to get things on the internet
I remember way back. I saw a lot of stuff on ebay, uh, like my entire gaming collection
I
I was because my my my tablet broke actually yeah, my tablet broke
I mentioned this before and so I needed to get a new one and I was looking for it on amazon
And it's like a thousand fucking dollars on amazon, but like this is an old-ass model
So it should not be that much
So I went on ebay and I found it
And I and I did I had not done this for years, but I I I haggled I fucking haggled
And you know what I came out on top like a month ago a month ago
I went on ebay and I made and I found a an item for sale and I was like that's a little too much
I think I can squeeze more out of you. They were asking 175 plus 65 dollar shipping for this tablet
And I was like, hmm. Fuck you. So I I I so I made an offer
I didn't I did I've never used this feature on ebay before I made an offer for like 125 dollars and they were like
No, they they made a counter offer that was like 165. They're like, oh, I'll shave a little like no
I'll fuck you. Fuck you. So I made a counter counter offer
Okay 135 and they just flat rejected it. They didn't even make a counter offer and I'm like, oh, no
I've lost it too hard to get
Well for the at the time I go back on yesterday the item is still there
It's been up for a month. This person is fucked. This person is in dire straits. They're desperate. I can use this
I have the leverage now. I have the upper hand. So I make another reply
145 dollars. Bam approved. Got it. Shave $30. It's a clean $35 off of the asking price. Hope to see it. Fuck
Fuck you, uh
Whatever you need. I haven't um, I haven't used ebay much to buy stuff
But I use it a lot to sell things and it's a pretty good way to sell your games way better than game stop
I guess I'll have to sell my current tablet um
As is for parts and probably get like 50 bucks for it probably literally pay more to ship it than I would even get for it
It's like a cintiq, isn't it?
It is it is
It's the it's the oldest model. It's literally the oldest model. What's wrong with it again?
It uh, as far as I can tell the only thing that's wrong with it is that the screen simply doesn't work. Oh, uh, which is pretty bad
Hypothetically if you could fix the the display it still works fine
Like it's still like like receives input and like knows when you are like, you know moving the cursor on it and stuff
Uh, it's just the screen doesn't show anything. Um, so if you could fix that then
It would work, but like it's such an old model that the the Wacom doesn't, um
Uh, service the model anymore, and I think it would probably take
Because it's so old. I think it would probably cost more to repair than it would just to fucking replace the thing. Yeah
um, yeah, so yeah
Uh, it's probably just fucking good go in the trash. Oh, no, whenever I uh, I couldn't bear to put it in the trash
It would just feel whenever I sell stuff on ebay. I don't like shipping to anywhere outside of the us
So I avoid yeah, because they've send it to fucking uk
You send it to the uk and they put a fucking vat tax on it and it cost them 100 fucking dollars to receive the package
Hey, fuck you andrew yang with your vat tax. Uh, you be I terrible idea never gonna do it
Can't believe I buy I own a shirt with your name on it. Uh, uh, it's a it's a mistake
It was all a mistake. I gotta say it's it was really funny seeing how fast you turned on andrew yang
Back went back like before the uh
Before like the primaries or whatever because there was like a solid I want to say like a solid couple
Maybe like two months
Or where where you were you know, it was two months. I think and then I think bernie started running you were like, all right
Never mind. This is this is just a bit. I was just kidding guys
I owe I owe yang I owe yang a lot when when when yang started running and I heard about the ubi thing
I was like, wait, what I don't know
Just like that that whole idea and having it be like seriously proposed like really got me thinking about like wait a minute
Hmm public policy can like impact people in like a material way
Huh, and it just got me thinking like more seriously about
About issues man public policy
That's weird
Hmm. It's like it's almost like it's almost like uh, uh, uh, you know material conditions like affect society
He got you on the on the public policy pipeline
He did the ppp. He did he
He got me on the um
What's the like marxist thing like materialism like dialectical materialism. Yeah, he pipelined me to dialectical materialism
And it was fucking based
Thanks, andrew
Thanks, andre yang. Thanks. Yang is thanks, andre yang
Should get him on the podcast sometime. Oh, that would be fucking fine. Please get andre yang. Thanks yang
fang
Um, we should get Biden on the podcast and see if he dies mid mid show
Could you imagine dude imagine if we were the podcast where he fucking died?
He'd drop a lot of experience points, I think yeah, I mean that'd be huge for the channel
Uh, like he's very high level with a little minecraft experience orbs. We suck them up
You didn't know a lot of levels with that the pcp's xb bar. We're just fucking go skyrocketing for like eight levels
It would be it would literally be like when like your level five badoof gets the last like quick quick attack on on a
Rayquaza or something and it's just like
Uh, that that's that was secretly the best the best inclusion to pokemon was uh was having a little experience bar at the bottom
It it's good
It's so much it's so much more satisfying
What do they add that like gen two? Yeah, that was gen two. I think
Okay, now I'm just thinking
Like the idea the concept that all people have more experience. So it's more worth it to kill them
Well, yeah, they're like level 80
They're high. Yeah, they're higher level
And also also biden's and like uh and specced into a high class. So that just adds even more experience
He's he's a prestige class true. Yeah
He's um, he's got uh, he's he's like uh, he's like a legendary like raid boss, you know, he's like a he's like a higher level instance
Uh or something
So he's a he's a unique mob
So it's got like a gold
Oh, no, yes silver dragon silver fox thing round his icon not not the word I would use to describe joe biden, but
Uh, you know, come on. I mean, come on. He's he's got that he's got the animal magnetism
You know, he's got that there's something about him. You think he's a furry
What he's just got that gen s a qua. He's just got he's just such a
You know, like we said on shredded, you know, he's he's such a he's a he's you can look at him and you can tell he's a cake eater
What the fuck does that mean? Yeah, what the fuck?
That's a weird thing to say
This is a thing on on the on the shredded episode we tried to decode they they kept talking about people being cake eaters
And i'm pretty sure it just means like someone who
Enjoys life but more specifically in the context of r slash adultery
It means someone who has their cake and eats it too i.e.
Is just like fucking live in the high life fucking their spouse, but also their their af or adultery partner
Or sorry a fair partner. Sorry. Would it be ap? Um
Seems like uh, that that subreddit really had an effect on you
Um, it was very funny. It was very that's how it starts. I may be angry starts out funny
Then I get serious
Uh, I it's I'll have to do a lecture. I'll have to do a lecture on um on the uh r slash adultery lore
Uh, the thing about like they talk about like there's code
Where like oh
Yeah, I was walking around in the parking lot with an upside down pineapple in my shopping cart
And everyone knows like that's a secret sign that i'm like on the prowl for an elicit
extra marital
Freemasons pizza gate emails came out or all these like all these like politicians of talking about getting like
Spaghetti with extra sauce and cheese pizza like what what is what this like weird coded language?
Mmm. Mmm. I mean wait was that pizza stuff like I have I was that I have no clue
I have no clue. Okay. I'm I'm I'm not one of those people who like thinks that there's
Like I mean, I believe that there was
I don't believe in the I don't believe in the satanic pedophile ring. I mean, well, I do
I don't believe that it just is like only the democrat. Yeah, I'm sure they're all fucking kids
They're all they're all fucking kids and drinking blood. Yeah, obviously. Yeah, it's like eyes wide shut
That's why they had the kill. That's why they had to kill uh, uh, Kubrick
I thought you were gonna say epstein, but yeah, well that too
Yeah, I've never seen eyes wide shut. Um, but I can use my context clues to infer
What it's about that it is a movie. Yeah, it's it's it's a little flick. It's got tom cruise in it. Yeah
Oh, I'll have to check that. Yeah, I know how much you love tom cruise
I I am a notorious your notorious tom cruise appreciate your real cruiser
That's as we like to call them cruising for as we call it on r slash the cruise
Fuck what are we talking about tom cruise something. Oh, yeah, love them
Okay, what else
Um, uh, I don't know. I think
Uh, I guess I tweeted about it's similar sort of like list making stuff, but I've been seeing a lot of simpsons
Classic simpsons clips on youtube recommended and I've got into a big old thing just clicking on those and being like ha ha
I remember that bit. That was funny. Hmm. And then uh idea popped into my head like
I've always wondered like
How when the simpsons gets bad? How does it get bad and how quickly and I was like
What if I watched every episode of the simpsons and I I
Noted every time there was a joke with a punchline
That it was like a joke that was good or a joke that didn't land and then I went through every single episode in that way
You mentioned this graphing thing before but when you say it like that it's like
Oh, you're trying to like see exactly when the downfall was
Yeah
Oh
Well, I mean, this is a this is a great question
Uh, uh, I mean the the general consent it seems like the the
The general community consensus is that the decline happens somewhere around season 10
Nine nine or ten
But there are some hardliners that say that actually the golden era was like season up to season three
And the decline actually started after that and was only like fully completed around season. Well, I remember the the first time
I hated watching the simpsons was in uh the year 2000
I watched one of the new episodes that aired from the new season on sunday
And I I didn't like it at all and I stopped watching after that
2000 would have been like season 20
No season eight
Season 12 something like that. Yeah
Which would be like
post peak simpsons, but not like not like late simpsons. Exactly. It would be like middle air
I I I remember I think I've talked about this before in the show
I have heard that it I have heard that it got bad that it got worse before eventually kind of getting less bad
In like the late later seasons. That's what I've heard some people. Yeah, I've seen a few things like that
um, but I remember
Rewatching the simpsons up to like season 12 or 15 or something and I still
Was enjoying myself. I don't think it was like
The later ones were like as good and I can tell there was like a little bit of difference
but it didn't like
Piss me off as I was expecting some of the episodes to like just just based on hearsay like, uh, you'll hate this one
I'm like, oh god. I don't want to I don't want to hate anything and I didn't so I was like
um
Yeah, I kind of want to go all through through all of them instead of like stopping
I think it's so much to do. I think it's a really funny gimmick to have like
um to have like this
what what sort of
You might call like a scientific like beta driven approach to to it. I think that's funny is
Which like scientist man discusses like terminator or something
I'm trying to yeah, yeah, but like but but to have like a consistent like rule set that you were abiding by as you go through
Yeah, I think it's funny. Yeah, it's funny because it's like there's no way I could like
Prove that a joke landed based. It's just whether I liked it or not whether it was a good joke to me
Yeah, that does sound pretty cool. I hope somebody does that to my stuff someday. I think a challenge there would be like
Even like counting jokes at all because like Simpsons will have I know
Jokes that like like jokes within jokes
So like like a punchline comes and then another punchline comes that you didn't expect and then another one
It's like, oh, that's such a clever little writing thing
You think it's gonna happen this way and then it doesn't and then something else happens and it's like if
If you're pausing like every time there's a joke to evaluate like did that land or didn't it?
You're gonna be like making a lot of fucking notes. I know it's such a stupid idea
And I just couldn't I just like
Part of me wants to maybe you can practice on my stuff first before you move on to the simpsons
Yeah, I could those are very clear jokes. Oh
For a while
Oh fuck for a while. I was listening to
I think it's called worst episode ever the simpsons podcast
And I I fell off listening to it and I don't remember why
It must have been the worst podcast ever
Um, have
Have any of you read?
um
The dead homer
Have you ever read like ever
Just memorable remember
All right. Well, well to give a basic rundown reading is like when you look at these things called words and um
And there's a collection of words on this website called the dead homer society
And they've heard of this. I've heard there's there's like a section
On the website called like zombie simpsons and it basically is like it's like a novel explaining
Like when the downfall of the simpsons happened. It sounds a lot like Gibbs idea
Uh, it's I remember reading it like years ago. It's really good
Wait a minute. We got we got okay. I'm looking at this page. This is exactly. I I think I'm okay
I've seen the dead homer society. I've never seen this specific page, but like
I really like this and I'm definitely going to read it. It looks really interesting
Wait, I'm but it's not okay. Are these like links in the middle are two like chapters. Yes. Yes
Okay, it's okay
Reading but nobody does that anymore like line charts. Well
It has charts where it even even has charts in the first part. I would like to see that's
I like the the okay. I'm looking at the first part is called. There it is. What is zombie simpsons?
Average stars. Okay. They I mean they didn't do it by jokes. No, they're not doing it by jokes
Gibbs is a lot more. Um, is a lot more
I really like this family. It's it's funny
Yeah, it's good. I like it a lot it the the website itself is very like old internet
In a certain way. Yeah, I remember I remember the zombie simpsons thing being a really good read
Especially as someone like myself who like by the time I was like watching like shows like the simpsons
The simpsons was like long since bad. So I don't have like this attachment to the show that a lot of people do
I I've I've grown up with I had the box set of season two
I am exactly as old as the simpsons
Wow, so you're like the perfect age almost that's that's pretty lame then
Wait, what?
It's pretty lame
No, cool. Yeah, no, he's right. It is kind of lame. Nah shut up
Oh, you know those are funny because I I grew up watching the simpsons
I think I didn't realize that like even as I was watching them as a kid
They the episodes I was seeing were already like, you know, five or ten years old
I just kind of watched them and thought they were new, you know for a long time. Yeah, I had the same experience
Yeah
Uh
Same same with like same with the the nes the nes came out the year that I was born
And I didn't get one until I was like five or six
And then like later I got a super nintendo a little later
I didn't realize that by the time I got an nes the super nintendo was already it was already obsolete
But at the time I just I just assumed that it was like new and then like I found out later at the time
I think in the u.s. Uh, the nes came out in 1985. You were born in 85. Wait
When did it come out in america in america? It was 85. Um, wait, am I stupid? I thought it came out in like 80
Uh, the famicom was 83. I think yeah
Oh, okay. Well, I'm well that just makes my point even harder then is that you know, I got
Yeah, it was like almost a decade old when I got it
But I thought it was the new it was new and I just kind of assumed that to be the case until like for a long long time
Yeah, your parents tricked you
They probably I mean they probably didn't have to I'm sure they didn't even have to lie for me to just assume
um
But it was just surprising to be like, oh wait, really? It was that old even then? Holy shit
Weird there was this other thing I was thinking I probably also stopped me if you heard this one before
um
but no uh looking through the simpsons and then adding up
the day night transitions and and like and and and like time passing
moments so that you can accurately say
How old Bart and Lisa actually are in like the canon of the simpsons
Have actually thought about that. I feel like that's something simpsons fans would have done like wait, wait
What's the question? The idea is like the the the show has been going on for a very long time
It's like oh Bart and Lisa wouldn't be that old
But I've always wondered like could you fit like all of the episodes
Into like a smaller amount of time than it's actually elapsed in real life. Like how old would they actually be?
this okay, there is a
I there's a youtuber called the real gyms who does
Simpsons analysis like this and he has some series called
Uh, I think like the simpsons timeline. It's like there's there's one about the past timeline
One about the present timeline and about like and and the future timeline and I think it's in the present one
He talks about it and like I think like yeah, like there's more
There's like like like Bart and Lisa have been 10 and 8 for all this time
But there's more episodes than there are like days in the year
So you would have like for it to work you would have to assume that like certain episodes are like happening concurrently with each other
like on any given day like the plot of the plot of uh, uh
I'm trying to think of an you know the the plot of one episode unfolds sort of in between the
Unfolding and you would have to like cross-reference the characters to make sure that there's no like contradiction
Yeah
There are there are there are contradictions though the funniest thing is that like
Every the simpsons always takes place in the year when Bart is 10 and and Lisa is 8 and yet like multiple different episodes have like
You know the school year ending or like them going to summer Christmas and it's like pretty sure uh the show makes fun of this fact
at certain points
About Bart and Lisa's age how'd they never age?
Yeah, isn't like one of the isn't like one of the inconsistencies is like the show started where uh
Homer's dad was like a world war two vet, but now he's like a korean war vet or something
But like a vietnam. Yeah something. Yeah something like that because because like yeah the the simpsons is
The simpsons is always happening in current in the current day
But the characters are always the same age
So like their past keeps like floating forward
It's like if you really think about it every single episode is a completely different universe
Where they're like a day like a week older
Because it's like springfield is like in a time bubble
But but but there's but there's a weird there's a weird wrinkle to it where like
Homer and Marge's uh, I think their prom always happened in a specific year
And like oh, yeah like that like completely throws a wrench into it
Well, no that episode where they say that is like a different universe from the other episodes
Yeah, true. That's all right. It's all it's all not canon with itself. And there's all you know the
Did you know that it's actually all just fiction and none of it even really happens
You know like the the zelda timeline where like it splits after a certain point
There's like a point in the home and the simpsons where like Homer starts a band
Homer doesn't start a band and that's where like the timelines diverge
The b sharps
Is it the b sharps because because there was the band because I know I haven't seen it
But I know that in a later season they do another like Homer and Marge like meat story that's set in the 90s
Yeah, and it's like a complete reimagining or whatever. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and it like completely rewrites the history
They're gonna do that eventually where it's like um Homer and Marge, uh, remember that I hope they don't I hope the show
Where they reminisce their time where they met where they were playing fortnight
Right they met on fortnight all those years ago probably during COVID-19
Do you remember when Homer subscribed Homer subscribed to Marge's only fans during during the quarantine? Yeah
Remember when you made Undertale, sweetie
But it is weird how uh
The world of the simpsons still looks and feels like it's based on 90s stereotypes even though they have newer stuff
Like I watched one time an episode where they had uh, I think uh, mr. Burns was playing the Wii
It just looks weird. It's like you're seeing the Wii in the 90s
Yeah, like a lot of the character designs like ironclad. This is what they are
I mean, they're pretty generic just like clothing wise, I guess
I don't know. Yeah, I don't know if I agree like
Yeah, like I don't like this does the world look particularly 90s though
I think the characters do like homers. It is the stereotypical dad from the 90s and
No, their entire family is like the stereotypical 90s. No, you're totally wrong. You're totally wrong. I think the only thing
That would be different. He's just wearing a shirt and jeans. It's the only thing that would be different
Um now is that all of these shirts would have like stupid
Text on them that sucks and isn't funny and there would be nothing that doesn't have a logo
Not on a sitcom
I mean
No, I think the character designs are timeless enough
Uh, they they look fine in any era. I mean like people in
I mean their house
I mean people today people live in houses that were built like 10 20 30 40 50 years ago and like it's normal
Um, but there's definitely some characters that are extremely 90s like um, the bus driver remember that guy
I don't remember his name
Auto
Yeah, okay
You know his his accent the way he dresses. I guess there's there's fucking there's fucking like long-haired waistoids in every era
Like the specific music he's like talking about maybe this because he talks about music. Yeah, he just talks like a 90s guy
A little bit
Yeah, that is yeah, I guess that's the most obvious one
um
I am like what if like nuclear power in the future just stops and becomes obsolete in the real world
Will they change mr. Burns and his nuclear power plant or will that stay?
Why would he runs a solar power plant? I'm just thinking of stuff
I'm just thinking of things that the simpsons has like very
Deeply ingrained and then like in the real world could change could anything change and then simpsons would have to change to keep up
I don't know if there is anything
I think they also drive the same car don't they?
I guess that's more of like a meta thing though not written necessarily
Yeah, they just the character himself. Did they get rid of the character or did they change the voice actor? I can't remember
I think they recast them
Okay, well, did they did they I thought they got rid of them
Uh, yeah, I don't know
Um recasting him is probably the right thing to do
I don't I don't know. I think if they I didn't see that there's much of a problem of it, but like
I yeah
I
I don't think yeah
I remember I remember watching why people didn't like it, but I do think that like apu's voice was
Hanka's area
and like
It's what what do you do at that point? I don't know my my take on that is really been a problem
If they had just like not made a big deal out of it. I don't think it would have yeah
I I remember watching hot diggity demons
The apu that I know video, which is a very good video where he goes into like why it's good
But it has some really cringy stuff in it
There's a few cringy moments in it
and I think the the thing that like
I disagree a little bit on is like he knows all about how apu because he's a big simpsons fan
and um, you know, if you look at apu
And you really understand everything that's going on with him
You you realize that he's not like a negative stereotype and it should be fine
the the thing is that
The people who it affects in like this the playground like not everybody notices
The the the subtle joke of like subverting the negative stereotype trope of the the immigrant who's like
I don't know. Well, he's not stupid. All right. He's like extremely intelligent and all and all these cool things
And that was what the show initially was doing because it's like
Progressive in that way. It's always been a little bit progressive
Yeah, but uh, the the average person doesn't necessarily understand that and they will still make fun of
Indian people by comparing them to apu from the simpsons
Regardless, okay, okay, okay, but let me I mean imagine a world in which apu was
The same idea. He's like an he's an immigrant from India
But you know, he's he's voiced by an Indian
Uh, and he's like, you know, he's he's all that and stuff and but he's otherwise like the same
You know, he's a convenience store owner
But he's got all these like things in his past that are interesting about him and he's he's
mostly the same character like
you you would still
I mean, he's it's such a popular show
And and he's like such kind of a fixture of it. I mean, I feel like there's no way that you could avoid
Indian people getting associated with this character who was like the only
You know, I feel like people would still make jokes about if they saw an Indian kid
They'd be like ha ha come again because that's what the guy says, you know
Like come again is not like a really stereotypical thing
But it's just that's the association because of this such a such a well. It's the it's the fault character
It's really just the fault of the simpsons being so successful and so widespread
That it's like even if even if you as a as a fan of the simpsons
You can recognize that he's not a negative stereotype. You can't stop people from doing it
When it's it's like on a surface level, they can see the similarity and they will say the things
So like I think both sides of the argument are kind of true
Like it doesn't it doesn't matter to you shouldn't try it. It shouldn't need to change
But I get that people
The problem the the problem of like oh people call me a poo
I don't know if there's any like way that could have been avoided
Other than just like not having an Indian in your show, which like that's stupid. Yeah
Uh like having an Indian voice actor wouldn't have changed that. Uh, yeah, I wouldn't have so it's like what is
Done, but I don't know. It's it's kind of dumb. It's kind of dumb
I I really think if the simpsons had like simply had simply not
Addressed the issue. I don't think they really would have had to change anything not that I think it's bad that they recast him, but like
I don't think they had to really probably probably would have blown over it would have blown over as these things are to do. Yeah
Maybe people were just uh overthinking it. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. I'm looking and it says
I'm looking at wikipedia
No, it says voiced by hank azaria 1990 to 2020
Wait, are you still doing it?
Simpsons creator mac grading stated in august 2019 that a poo will remain on the show. So I guess they didn't
I guess we're just stupid. Well, they just didn't do any of that
Faced I never I never really looked into it. I just heard about it. So no, I don't know. It's it seems like they didn't do anything
Okay, well, I thought uh, they were going to do something, but I'm not sure if they actually did
They might have said they were going to do something and then waited for everyone. Yeah to stop listening. Yeah
Oh, we're definitely going to care about what you just said
Well, no
Um, yeah, but in that situation, they probably should have just not addressed it at all
Yeah, the the the the bit with like, you know the bit where like lisa's in bed and she's got the picture of a poo on the table
Oh god. Yeah, that's it's so weird. It's such an awkward. I've seen that clip. It's embarrassing
What what clip? I don't know this
It's hard to even describe because it sounds like a fever dream
There's there's like a there was like a subplot in a in an episode that was like that was totally
Totally not about anything in particular guys. Although well, I shouldn't say like that
It was about the whole up who controversy here. Let me let me see if I can find it
We're like lisa's
Is like talking to marge and they even like look at the camera when they're like talking about how like, oh
He's it's from a different time. There's there's nothing we can do about it one of them
They say that and then it was bad
But but they also like don't really say anything because she says like
These issues will be addressed at a future some issues will be addressed at a future date
If at all and then marge like looks at the camera gravely and nods and I just don't know what the fuck they were thinking
But I guess I don't know what the fuck they were thinking
Like the thumbnail yeah, it's like I feel like I'm about to get apologized to by
I don't want to see it. I don't want to have like youtube rip like apology energy
It looks you know what it looks like people talking about it never mind
It looks like an antoons video about like the characters are at their funeral
You know now, you know why into symptoms is bad now
It's because it seems like this probably it's like you can't find the clip
I also don't understand. Um, I mean it's it's similar to did you see that like the song like the donald trump song with like the squad?
I I've not uh, no
I didn't see that during the democratic primaries and it ends with like a fucking like conga line of all the democratic candidates
Like dancing and it's so embarrassing. It's so it's the worst thing i've ever seen. It does sound pretty embarrassing
it's the squad like
Doing a fucking musical number where they all like chase trump around the white house and like
Wag their fingers at him and and stuff and he's like, oh i'm trying to bumble my way around and oh
I tripped over some some stairs and oh i'm trying to get away from these these women because i'm scared of them
It's so it's a nightmare. It's just a nightmare. I I let me listen
Let me I feel like maybe I haven't made it clear in the discussion
I hate the simpsons now and I want it to fucking die. I really do
Yeah, I wish it had died along. I haven't really delved into like i'm not a simpsons apologist at all
I haven't really delved into like the latest stuff and I don't keep tabs on it. So
um
That sounds I don't I don't care if it's I don't care if it's less bad than it used to be it's trash and it should be dead
uh, I'm thinking of like what they would usually do when they wanted to make fun of a
president or something they would just have them be in an episode and say
Or do something evil or or
Not evil, but like um
I don't know like
They've had bill bill clinton with mr. Burns. They would they would just have just have them say a funny line
That's like oh, yeah, we all know about that
controversy. Yeah
Yeah, just like pop in for like a little like one-line gag or something
It's I mean they they had the episode where um, uh, george bush moved in next door
Is it which was just a big
fucking um
I don't know
But wasn't that one of the newer episodes that sucked?
I've all of w then. Yeah
You know, no, it was george. It was george hw. It was first first bush. Oh, then that's the golden. You don't know
That's the one with that's the one with two bad neighbors
You don't know about I don't have watched that. I don't really remember. I don't know if I've seen that one. They um
George george bush, uh, uh really hates uh homer and bark
And so he he does some mischief. He spray paints too bad neighbors and like their faces
But he spray paints it on his own house so that they can see it like from across the street
Um, and that's it. That's the joke. He spray paints his own house to get back at them
Very clever. Yeah, I don't know. That's why that guy was ahead of the cia
I feel I feel I feel like that episode is kind of light on actual commentary
Uh, I mean it's been like it's been like talked about before and I don't want to go too deep into it
But but like it feels like trump just like broke a lot of like comedians brains
Yeah, the the reality of the situation is like almost too absurd to make jokes about so the sentence is a comedy
I
Thank you. Good night, everybody
Hope you had fun
I saw a clips of like the the like the episode about voting where homer goes to vote
And it was stupid. It wasn't as bad as the as the song, but it was really stupid
Yeah, whenever I see uh, I saw the clip
I saw the clip of like baby bernie sanders having his goons like beat up other kids in the playground
And I was like this show needs to die the show needs to die
This is whenever I see uh clips of the newer seasons. Uh, I was cringe
Uh, it's it's it's it's it's a nightmare. Honestly. I'm getting depressed. It definitely wasn't based. That's for sure
Definitely not based. I don't think any show should go on for that long
No, it's been like what over 20 years now
30 30 30 32 years
Going on 33, baby. That's ridiculous
It's it's unacceptable. It's a it's a thought crime. It's art crime is what it is. Make a new fucking show
Make a new fucking show you cowards
Wasn't uh, wasn't that what future drama was supposed to be? Yeah, that's better than every way
Especially then in the the way that it didn't go on forever and ruin itself
It almost did it it does it does have that going for it
And you could you could argue that like some of the comedy central seasons aren't as strong
But it did end before it got too bad. Yeah, I'd agree
There was um, was it there was another Matt Groening show from like a few years ago on netflix game of thrones
Yeah, game of thrones. That was it
I I never watched disenchanted. Uh, me neither. I heard it wasn't that good. It looked dumb. I didn't want to see it
I remember when uh future roma first came out
There was a lot of hype for it and I thought it was going to replace the simpsons. I thought the simpsons was going to end
Um, but that didn't happen the plan. Yeah back in the day anything could have happened
Um, but it didn't instead nothing happened
Um, yeah, I remember being hyped for future roma
Uh, future roma was good. Don't get me wrong
But I wouldn't say that like
The best future roma is better than the best simpsons
That's kind of just that's kind of just the zoomer in me talking because I've seen way more future roma than I've seen simpsons
Oh, no. Oh, no. Yeah, the best
Sorry, I'm a little baby boy
Simpsons is funnier than future roma was definitely like peaks peak simpsons is funnier future roma has other things going for it
It's got more of like an arc, which is nice. I guess it's more of a of a narrative show the simpsons is more of
Here's a concept and let's tell jokes while we explore it for a few for like 20 30 minutes
Yeah
Well, you know me i'm a big fan of jokes
What what
What
What tell tell us a joke funny man
He has been the whole episode. Yeah, make us laugh
I make us laugh clown
I couldn't think of anything on funny to say
Oh, that's right. I'm sorry
Um
Now what voicemail
I can't think I don't really go anything else to say. Yeah, we we could voicemail
All right. Yeah, that's probably a good idea. It's been two hours very based very based
Uh, let me pull them up and we will get to going right. Okay, not to sound green. Um, how do you like?
You activate voicemail. Oh, oh, it's easy. You'll see. Um, I'll just post it in the chat and you just play it in the chat
It's fine
Oh, I see. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, that's all there is to it. That is easy
Um, okay. Uh, let me see. This one is called
Hold on I gotta get back to
Reality oh there goes gravity
Um, this one is called
The worst accent. Okay, three two one go
Guys the worst accent occurs either when Finnish people try to speak English or when Americans try to speak French
Like you think Ben desperately trying to pronounce the words croque monsieur and croque madame was just embarrassing
Wait, I I said I went at length after I tried to say that I went at length or maybe it wasn't then but
Like recently I went on at length about how I don't understand
How french is pronounced and I think it's a nonsense language monsieur
Madame the yeah, the the sandwiches
The croque croque croque monsieur and croque madame. What are you just doing like a like a I hate this person
This is their argument voice
That's right. Well, what's your point? The worst accent is uh, whatever I've got I guess
What is your accent?
Uh, I don't know. I assume midwest. Gamers accent. Yeah, it's gamer
Well, there's not enough there's not enough bad words and gamers tavern
So you have you have a he's speaking like a gamer gamers tavern. You have a you have a uh, uh
I don't want to say unusual because that sounds negative, but you have like a you have kind of a
Unusual cadence to your voice. Where where are you from?
Uh, the u.s
Just can you be any more specific press him?
Okay. Gamers tavern values his privacy. Don't dox. Don't dox yourself. I guess
I guess if I had to guess I would say midwest
You can say I'm from I'm from the south
Oh
Mexico
Yeah
Is that why you were talking about green cards earlier? I don't hear the south at all. I don't hear southern at all
Yeah, uh, where where I live. Nobody has a southern accent. Um, even though it is technically in the south
New york
Very mysterious south to me
Hey, it's somewhere and that's all that matters
It's south to someone
Yeah, everywhere south to canadian
canadia
I don't I don't know what a finished accent sounds like he said he said the worst accent is a finished
His accent was he finished? I don't think he was that he was finished. Yeah
I guess I think he was french because he took such issue with me
mispronouncing french
But who knows he didn't sound I couldn't I couldn't quite tell I don't actually know what finish sounds like
I know what swedish people talking english sounds like
I had um, he didn't sound finish
There was a girl in my high school who was french
But she didn't I mean she didn't have an accent or anything
When I was when I've like met french people
I don't know like there's a very like sort of cartoony idea of like uh-huh
Monsieur that like sounds very french, but when I've actually met french people and heard them talk
They don't sound like that. They just have like a things are not like a much
They have a much less recognizable accent that I honestly have a hard time differentiating from like a german accent
I mean france is a very big country. There's probably multiple dialects that they have
I know I know a bit of it's like english, right? Well, yeah, but english
No, yeah, I guess it would be
Accent like sheffield. I've got uh, I've got relatives in canada who speak french, but I don't speak french myself
french canadian cock and bush
That's not terrible. It's awful. That's god awful
um
spaghetti
That's italian. Wee wee spaghetti por favor. Wee wee spaghetti marion prussian
Arigato gozaimasu
Thank god for brexit because otherwise
Otherwise, uh, they would they would be easily able to travel over to the uk and kill me
But no longer they would like nothing more than to do the the pcp sleeper cells are on their way
Um, okay, the next the next voicemail is called um
Dana wilson, okay
three two one go
So my husband of 14 years is super bummed out
Uh, he had me do one of those Kawasaki scroll things and like the tiny like
But I he just handed me like a piece of paper and said I need you to read this and then threw the phone in my face and so
You guys only like did a second of it and he was like
I mean, I guess it was appropriate, but like I'm kind of bummed out
And so I feel really bad. I just kind of wanted to let you guys know that like we're happy. It's over
If it if it's actually over
They still really sad though
So if you could just I guess do a voicemail shout out it took me and you know
It's funny is the only way that I figured out who you guys were because I said, oh
What what's the show thing that you like and he's like, oh, it's procrastinators
The only way I figured out how to find this website was by entering Kawasaki scroll
And I don't believe that's how I figured out
What your whole podcast was called?
So yeah, just shout out to my sad mopey husband. Oh, shit
Oh, he's coming back. Anyways. Yeah, just just in secret letting you guys know. Okay. Bye
That's that's epic
I don't remember my head. Do you get it give? Um, well, it's one of those one of those samurai scroll
Things there was a high pitched voice
And we didn't I can't remember if I was there even but I remember it
And was this from a voicemail last week voicemail last week or the week before or something and um
At that point the whole Kawasaki scroll ninja scroll thing
Uh was sort of played out and we were kind of tired of it. So I think we may have skipped it
That's course
So, I don't know
Uh, I uh, that has not explained it. Big gomenosai to this feels like so this feels like a
hugely meta like big brain like step
That I feel like part one of six of a new arc and I'm not I'm worried
I do you think someone who watches the pcp has been married for 13 years
I like I get gib I
Yes, I under obviously I understand that this is connected to the samurai because it references the
Kawasaki scrolls, but other than that, I I do not understand how it relates at all
Well, we're gonna need a lecture on the samurai thing
I mean the the reason it's gotten so confusing is because I think
Like I'm still not even sure that there were multiple people trying to be
the Kawasaki scroll ninja like
Cool funny well the samurai said last time that that's not true and that it yeah
Is at least mostly all one person so like this person who who who had his wife do a bit
And maybe it wasn't the original and he was trying to make it like I'm gonna do this thing
There's no wife. This is this is a fiction. You've been duped. Huh?
I refuse to believe that this is someone's wife
Yeah, me too. Yeah, at least in this context. I'm yeah, maybe he's happily married. How can that?
Why is that the most confusing part? No one who listens to the pcp could be happily married
And there's no way a pcp fan would be married
This is um, yeah
All right. Yeah, okay. It's too much. It's too much. I can't let's just say let's just say the pineapple is upside down
Yeah, exactly
Yeah, there it is. I hope so. I hope so DMs are open. She sounded cute. She had a cute voice, so
You know
Uh hit hit me up hit me in the DM
No hitting my DMs. I said pineapple first. No, no kill give no kill give
Um, next one is called. Um wandering through dead fandom. Oh, this one's long
Yeah, three two one go
so I've been uh
replaying some old video games that I never really got around to experiencing and uh
One of those games was shadow of the claustus. I played the ps4 remake and
I've run into a bit of a problem where
The game's so good and I really want to talk about it
But everybody's been talking about it for like 20 plus years or whatever it is. Yeah, and so
They like everybody knows everything about it. There's nothing that I can add to the conversation. Yeah, so like
I feel this there there's like an avoid in my soul of talking about something that's really cool
That I just can't fill because nobody wants to talk about the 20 year old game, you know
Uh, so I'm wondering. Uh, is there anything that you've experienced?
Far beyond its popularity that made you feel that way that left that pit inside your being
Of expression of passion
Um, also mr. Saints. I want to apologize
Few episodes ago. I was I uh, I was naive. I hadn't been up on the
The lore and such and I I just went ahead and uh sent in a voicemail about foreskin and I uh,
I want to apologize for adding to the
You should we were doing so good. I appreciate I appreciate the apology. No, no, it's all abysmal
Beating of that dead horse. Absolutely disgraceful. Yeah, I'm good. I'm beating
My foreskin just the foreskin though. Well, I don't have that
Oh
So with regards to that the only thing that comes close for me is I got into the game of thrones tv show
Um, well after it had been going
And I got like up to it was like the the last the second till the last season was coming out
I think or like the the second to last season was wrapping up and I was getting into the show
And I was learning about all the stuff that had been talked about
Four years prior to this and I was like, oh now I get what they were all talking about
But I didn't feel like an empty void in my soul. I don't know
Um, it's it's fine to just talk about something to no one, isn't it?
Just make a blog. I think this person will find that um that like
Even if what they're saying isn't exactly new fans of whatever will will just like the fact that you're into it as well
I
When I made the sonichu lecture, I was like, this is all well worn ground. Everybody already knows this stuff
Like none of what I none of what I say is new. Yeah. Yeah, but I really like that's true of like literally literally every fucking video on youtube
Is someone like looked up some shit on wikipedia and just like wrote it down and then like read it to you
Like nothing is new
Right. Nothing. I'm having a similar sort of problem that he had
Uh, we're like, I'm coming to something so late like I'm working on a video right now
And I'm talking about like a bunch of like these old these like pretty old games that are critically acclaimed
But like at least I have like some sort of outlet to talk about that and like a youtube video or whatever
For someone like this. I I think just talking to your friends about it would suffice just fine
It's pretty good advice
I often have this uh issue because uh 99 of the games I play are either 20 to 25 years old
Yeah, so, um
I have a friend I talked to who is also into
Retro games and every once in a while when I play something I'll
I'll just talk to him about it
Um, I mean sometimes even when I replay stuff, I'll talk about it too
Is is this person like looking to like make content out of their talk?
Or is they or are they just like they just want to talk about it to someone
I guess that's like they can't find a discussion to involve themselves in that that's a little different
But yeah, that's that's unfortunate. I I feel that I don't think there are content creator
This is this is why people will go and like be like and like make someone play a game that they like
It's just because I need someone to talk about it with like, oh, oh, you never played. Oh, you gotta play
I gotta I gotta live my experience. I'm pretty sure there are communities online dedicated to this sort of thing
Like on reddit or on various forums and stuff
I just I just watched um a video this week about like this the search for the last secret
That's like that jaco geller video, right?
Is that who it is?
Um, I've heard of that video. Yeah, like blue point
In the remake added in some sort of like urban legend thing that was yeah
Yeah, they added a thing behind the door in the shrine of the of the the small colossus
Yes, it's funny because they did the same thing in the demon souls remake
Did they?
Yeah, there was like this um, there was like this hunt to find to find like what was behind some door that was added in the remake ended
Um, uh, it involved like playing the game and like the new like mirror mode or whatever and like finding these like
These coins on the ground giving them to the crow
And then you get like a key and inside of the room is uh is like the penetrator's armor
Which is like a an armor set from that that that was from like a boss
That wasn't really original game. It's really interesting
It's really interesting in in the shadow of the colossus
There's like there's really strong evidence that like a secret should be in this spot
Like like if you hear the case laid out, it's like yeah
It really looks like this is like a map that is pointing you towards something secret here in the spot
It's kind of a lost art because there was a lot of stuff like that in games
Like uh, like like the mu under the truck thing is but yeah, but there's but there's nothing
I'm sensical
Yeah, but like there there is a truck in that area of the game and it is weird. Why is it there?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly
Yeah, sometimes there's like things get removed from games before they get released
Yeah, there's these there's these four
points on the map
And there's there's references to like there's references to
Intersecting points
And there's these four points on the map that just happen to be arranged in a perfect cross that makes a right angle with itself
And there's a shrine exactly at the intersection of that cross
And that shrine has this weird looking door in it that is not there for any discernible reason
And it's like yep
Looks like there's a secret here. That reminds me of yeah, it might be cut content
It reminds me of the door and banjo kazooie and the ice key and all that stuff
Yeah, fucking cyber shell cyber shell did a video on on like the stop and swoop stuff
And like that shit controlled my life for like a month. I was so obsessed with it
I might only know about that because of cyber shells video. It's a good vid
Uh, I've known about that since uh the game came out because I I played it back. Yeah
I know I wasn't an n64 kid
So I didn't have banjo kazooie, but I know what you're talking about now
It's it's just such a it was like such a cool idea for
For like a secret in a game and it just like it never ended up truly being what it was meant to be which is which is a damn shame
And that that ice key really kept me up at night
It's it's a lost art nowadays
You can't really you you you can't really do the same sort of stuff that you could back them because like the internet and
Ah, shit. Sorry internet and like data mining and whatnot
Yeah, uh, I think like the binding of isaac kind of tried to do something similar with like the lost
But um, yeah people people like they fucking dug into the files and figured it out data minded. Yeah, I heard about that
Much to uh edmund's uh chagrin
Yeah, but I mean of course they were gonna do I know yeah, it's it's it's kind of like
It's kind of like when my like like my video got copyright strike like I'm upset, but I'm also I get it
Yeah, yeah
Technology is too strong
We we uh next one next voicemail is called. Um
Uh
Nate's holiday message
Okay
I don't know what this is three two one go
Hope you guys have a good holiday
Merry christmas and all the other shit. Oh you jews
You and your hanukkah. Oh god. Get a real holiday
I'll fight your hanukkah with my christmas bro
And uh have a good one
I don't know
See you in the new year suckers
suck on my
toes
This feels like the the the bizarro version of that germa Thanksgiving message
Oh, is that the one it's it's it's the one where it pans. Yeah with the mirror. Yeah
Yeah, look anyone look it up if you don't know what it is you you just just watch it don't
I will say nothing further germa. I guess we've already heard from Nate
I can't remember
All right, hang on. I I saw it this year. I don't know if it's from earlier
It it was it he posted it like late Thanksgiving. I'm gonna
Yeah, I'm jamey jamey pull that up
Yeah, all right here it is
Yeah, I've
Saw this on my timeline this year
And it was at first I thought it that was the that email was someone like splicing Nate clips together
But I think that's just from a stream
Or maybe like his podcast. I don't know
I have no yeah, I don't remember that
Yeah, I have no idea where it's from. I it might be spliced together. It might just be from somewhere
Maybe it may be like something they would say on the stream. Yeah, it does. Yeah, it does
Well, so the only way Nate will be on the pcb is through voicemails, I guess
But he would he would he would never he would never stoop to saying it on the on the pro crass natives podcast though
We have to get we have to get his second hand
It's a deep fake ass
I think we put like cushions in there or something. I was gonna ask is that did he just stuff it or no
That's is that was that part of his joke or was that something someone else? No, no, that's part of the original tweet
Okay
Yeah, okay, but it's delivered what I mean. I think germa's probably just had like a dump truck ass this entire time
We just never seen it. Definitely. I mean, when when would you have seen it? Yeah
How would you know?
That's a big reveal. I gotta start following germa 985 on twitter
Germa's fucking great
He's so but you are all good. Yes
I don't know anything. That's just because you're stupid ben
No, it's because you're no, it's no, I don't know anything because you're stupid
Uh, that's a good point. Let me let me get the next one. Okay. The next voicemail is called
wait
Oh, uh, yeah, the next voicemail is called. Uh, thank you
God, it's a minute 30 three two one go
So to cut to the chase through all the emotional bullshit
I really just want to know. Yeah, how do you feel about the past seven years of your life?
me personally
Um, it's been a nightmare. You know, I've been growing up. I was like, uh, I was in middle school when I first found
Digi's videos and soon after, you know, within months
Found you guys's videos and I didn't really care about anybody's videos. I just like my little pony and fan base
But beyond that, I'm mostly I'm just wondering how do you guys feel about spending?
You know seven years of your lives devoted to your internet career
I mean, obviously you've been doing it since before that
And things have always been the same for you. They've they've changed dramatically for me
But I understand that you live the similar lifestyle that you did back in 2012. Well, does that mean? Yeah, just
I really enjoyed your stuff. I take it for granted way more than I should
and just
You know to make an interesting pcp voicemail to start a discussion like how do you feel about
The seven years that you've spent
And the ride you've taken with the algorithm and how it's really affected your career
And your outlook on things
And how it's changed over time
I'm really excited to know because it bring a lot of context to
What I'm thinking it's almost done and what I'm you know, just what I'm projecting on to you. So thank you
Well, uh
Um, what do I think about spending the seven years doing whatever? Uh, well, I wish I had the seven years back
Uh, but uh, I would think that no matter how I spent them. So whatever seven years ago. That's like 2013
2013 I don't think I started hypocrite back then. I don't even know
No
Seven years was like pre seven years ago was like pre teabab
Yeah, what if 2014 was when we started pony stuff? Um
Yeah, I don't know. I started back then I was still in 2013
I was still pre pre like
Further education. I was just out of like secondary school and I was like
I don't know what I'm doing
Now I slightly know what I'm doing. So that's good
I have I have like talents that have grown a little bit
And it's it's all right
you know
Can't complain too much. I'm making money. Is it I'm making money talking about stuff with ben saint online. It's pretty good
Now that's the dream right there
Wait, didn't didn't you uh, uh, discover my stuff in 2013 or was that later?
And I can't remember. No, it must have been later. It may have been a little later
Not too much later though
Because uh, I think I started this channel in 2012 and the first video I uploaded was in 2013
I feel like I found you like maybe four years ago
Jesse found him first right jesse and good
Yeah
Yeah, just see I think posted something in the chat and I looked at it and I was like, oh my god, this is really funny
Isn't that great when you just find like a when you just find a channel
Through the help of no one in particular
It always feels good. It kind of feels like a it almost feels like a secret club
Yeah, I definitely uh felt pretty good for me
Eh
Cool. Yeah, that's that's that's all it's also cool too when like people you people you respect
You find out that they watch like your content. I remember um
I remember I was watching like a running shine stream like a few months ago
And uh, and like I was talking in this chat and he was like, oh, it's a tonic improv. I love that guy and it's like, ah
It feels good
It's nice to get validation from people you respect
Yeah, well it was weird for me because I didn't know gib or jesse when they first left comments on my on my stuff
And um, I checked their channels out after they left comments and I was like, whoa, these guys have a lot of subscribers and they're pretty good
Uh, it feels real nice to get complimented by them. I suppose
Yeah
I'm glad it was it was nice
So it always feels nice giving a good comment when you mean it when like I don't comment that much
like, um
I I always try to comment really positive things on on on channels
Uh, just so that because like a lot of comments now suck. They're just like repeating parts of the video
They're not very interesting. They may be positive generally
but they're never like
in depth enough to warrant any sort of like
I don't know thought
Just sort of like
So I like to give like a like a very appreciate
Uh, appreciate it. Yeah, like a more in depth kind of you got shouted out by by running shine
Yeah, we we we talk in dm sometimes or that's awesome running shine. That's awesome. I love running shine. Yeah, he's great
Who's that?
I want him on the podcast. He's uh, he's like I've been meaning to ask him, but I'm too chicken
He's one of the game he he does like gaming videos. Um, he made a he made like a
I think an hour and a half long review of that like yick game y2k
That's how I found him
Yeah
While my friends tabby tabby nickel like linked his review and the uh, or their review because it's like a bunch
It's a couple of people but uh, wait, wait, wait running shine is more than one person
Yeah, yeah, um, there's uh, two people write the video uh mellow and tropics mellow is the one who like narrates them
What and there's a couple of other people who do like the music and stuff. Yeah
Oh, I just thought it was one dude
Yeah, well, uh, that sounds pretty uh professional
Yeah, it it's he's they're really funny and also informative. It's just uh
That's a really good video the yick video like kind of blew up and that's how I've watched I've literally watched it like four times
Because I'm stupid that reminds me of uh, I was talking to a friend of mine one time about my content and he
He offered to write the scripts and I would do the voicing
And I was like, uh
I would rather do it the other way around I write the scripts and you do the voicing because uh, really I'm more of a writer
I'm not very good at talking
Huh, but I ended up doing everything myself
Um, if I got a good man, if I had a good script writer
I would love to just like read some shit that somebody else wrote because I hate writing. Um, it's boring
Like you said, um, I hate it when it doesn't go anywhere
Yeah
No, that sounds like a sweetheart deal honestly
Uh, yeah, I'd fuck I'd do that
Yeah, it would be cool if I could work with someone who had a good voice to read my scripts instead of doing it
But I I have no choice to gotta use my own voice
Tragic
That's just uh, to me, that's your brand
Well, it is now it's so integral to your brand
Just wouldn't it wouldn't be gamers
You're dry delivery that really sells the absurdity of what is happening in your videos just the constant barrage of the puns and jokes
The way wouldn't I don't know like whether it would be better if it was someone else's voice at this point
Are you guys ready for the next voicemail? It's called thank you too. Oh, no again. Yeah
Three two one go
Also, by the way, um as an amendment horseshoe finale obliterated taken down gone
The wwe claimed the video
It only happened like a month ago or a month or two ago. So very recently
Um, yeah, that legacy is tarnished forever
It's probably never coming back because I don't think jesse wants to deal with all that
I don't I don't really know what the process is like, but it sounds like a nightmare. So
Yeah
Sad day
Um, at least we have new horizons to look at
It's not like anybody fucking wants those horizons though. It seems like everybody's in a fucking nightmare shit hole
Uh, no offense to you or anybody else. I mean, I'm a I'm a loser
Compared to that. I have no room to talk not to talk about me, but just to say damn
Sounds like a fucking nightmare
Uh, I don't know what he means by that like new horizons. I don't know what he means by that either
I think he just means like the future of youtube and everyone
It just you know one of those like pcp. That's that's really that's really reaching is dead comments. I'm not sure
That's that's really reaching for uh for uh for a silver lining. It's like, oh, yeah, everything sucks
But hey at least the future will occur like yep, this too. It will
Yeah, um
I did did horseshoe finale get taken down. Yeah, I I heard about it a little while ago. I was like, oh, that sucks
Um, yeah, that kind of sucks. I don't have to do another rewatch of the horseshoe reviews
It's been a long time since I've watched them. I don't even know that maybe someone has reuploaded it
It seems like something someone would have downloaded
now
I kind of thought that like the more time passed and the more times I revisited it
The less I liked horseshoe finale. I kind of thought it was getting worse the longer it it existed
In hindsight not to not to speak for him, but I feel like jesse would probably agree
I don't think he's particularly proud of of a lot of his videos
Maybe horseshoe finale is different because you know, it's it's horseshoe finale. It was very cathartic
um as
It was happening because it was like take making fun of people
Like josh scorcher who is like so irrelevant now. It doesn't matter
It's one of the it feels like one of those you had to be there kind of
It at the at the time it was an it was like a very impactful statement that meant a lot
To a bunch of people now. It's like, yeah
Removed from that context. It's a very strange cultural artifact
Well ever since I was cool in its own way actually actually describing it like that makes me like it more
Ever since I discovered jesse's content. I've been a big fan of his so
It does bother me to see anything. He's done be taken down. Yeah
It's a bummer. Um
Wait, there was
Was there something else to the voicemail? No, it was just like horseshoe finale gone. Also new horizons
I thought he was talking about animal crossing for a second a little bit
Like someone made like a horseshoe finale for animal crossing
Oh, I want that would be interesting cult corona in in animal crossing. Is he in there?
Can I be in this got to be a horse?
There's no horse. What's the point? Well, there's got to be a horse
But it's cult corona. Is there a horsey sauce?
Wide a long face
Let's let's let's let's move on to new horizons. The next voicemail is called
Uh, well, it's a youtube link. So I guess let's just listen to it three two one go
So pcb. I'm just here to chill amori, which is one of the most pcb core things I've seen in a while
It releases on christmas and it's on steam and I think it will be pretty good amori
It's it's like a it's like a oh, I've seen like rpg
Okay, I've seen um this around
Is this pcp core? I don't know. It's kind of like earthbound core or like yume niki core, which I feel like aligns with
PCP looks like yeah, I've seen it around and I thought it looked like it could be neat. Um, yeah
Okay, that's fair. He looks all right. I like come out because I'm always a big fan of interesting
Art bits here and there
I'm always a big fan of earthbound
Whenever I see whenever I see like a Kickstarter game
That's like, you know getting updated and like I just kind of start ignoring it because I'm like, you know
Maybe I'll hear about it when it's done in like four years
And until then I don't care
Spooky slow ghosts. Oh shit. There he is. There he is. Are you gonna sue?
Uh, no, I'm gonna sue for peace. I'm gonna give them money
Uh, uh, okay, uh, uh, okay, everyone. Uh, shut the fuck up. Uh, the next one is called, uh, the next upload is called
Everyone is fuda
three two one go
I've been thinking about my question is digi fuda and I've come to the realization
That penises are just inside out vaginas
We all have a vagina in us
And I guess because vaginas are disinverted penises, that's right
Then all girls just have penises inside them, which I guess means they're being raped assuming they don't want
Their own dicks inside them without their own content
But anyway, uh, I think that makes
Everyone a fuda girls are just constantly being fucked by themselves because their own penis is all up inside of their vagina
That's such a stupid like
Like it means nothing
I don't I think it's a joke. I know it's a joke and it made me and it made me laugh
So you know what it worked. Good job. I guess we know who is the philosophy major
Yeah, yeah sounds like me sounds just like me
Okay, that was great. Hey, love you. Next one is called voice voice grail. No voice grail. No contestant contestant
Okay, damn. Damn it. No, I'm not feeling it
Next one is called read theory libs. I'm excited for this one. Uh, this is gonna be good
This one's goes out to fucking michelle's put down your fuck put down your jordan peterson mary condo bullshit and pick up some fucking
Pick up das kapital
three two one go
Go on it's difficult for me to imagine what personal liberty is enjoyed by an unemployed hungry person
True freedom can only be where there is no exploitation
or oppression
Of one person by another where there is not unemployment and where a person is not living in fear of losing his job
His home and his bread
Only in such a society and in any other freedom can exist for real and not on paper
Is this from running your communist? That is from
probably economic terrorism and
the oil owners
uh april 21st 1908
By joseph fucking stallin
fucking based
Fucking just absolutely based. Yeah, amazing theory. I mean, yeah guys born in the 1800s
Rob's banks overthrows an evil king kills fucking nazis
Yep, creates space travel or well, you know sets up the organization that creates space travel
Wait, yeah, and it's what you're saying is stalling. It just blows my mind how fucking based it is
He'll edit you out of pictures though if he doesn't like you
Didn't yeah stallin
And hitler team up in that war
In the beginning they can't uh the relationship soured
Well, uh, nobody's perfect. What am I thinking? Yeah, no one's perfect
Look, we all make mistakes
I guess um, they did they did kill a lot of nazis though the soviet union did uh do a lot of that
Which is pretty basic. I think we need to yeah, we just need to like measure
Like and I mean, that's good theory. That's good theory. Well, uh, he was spitting straight facts there
You know, you can't you can't deny. It's like there's there's no way that this can exist without oppression
And that's the just the way I like it. You know, that's what they said theory
I don't think so
What are they what what did they say what did they say?
Well, they say nothing. Thanks for watching
Okay
There's a good way to wrap that one. Oh, that's that's his next challenge to nothing wrong. Dab, dab, dab
Matt's gonna do a new channel or it's gonna be hey guys. Welcome to theory to
political theory
Hey guys, welcome to theory theory where we talk about how you should kill your landlord
Is jeff gonna write on that channel too
Jeff Bezos
Oh
Ben yes
Cool. Can't wait to jeff write on game theory. I think he said so. Yeah. He has for a couple
At least yeah, that's pretty funny. Um, that's pretty funny. Uh, good for him
Uh, next one is called dat dag zag. Wait, wait, wait before we go on the next one. Oh, am I stupid?
Yeah, um with joseph stalin. Was I thinking of mousselini? Was I was I was I actually doing that mousselina is the mousselina
You know mousselini is the italian fascist. Yes, and he was with hitler and they were with japan and we were able to okay
Stalin is different man different man
Well, apparently I mean apparently they was he all right. I didn't I actually didn't know that
Now you're just stalin for time. I am
I just want to clarify because uh, I just want to make sure people know that i'm stupid and that we can move on
Okay, well, apparently you're smarter than me because I thought they
Never did that but apparently they did accidentally smart
Listen, anyone getting their theory from the pro cast in the air's podcast
Look, what did we say everything? What did we say before?
We're always right and we always have an opinion and you always have to listen to it
And you should always always always clip it and quote it out of context
And take it as fact
Maybe you guys should read some history books
Maybe you should clean your fucking room
Yeah
Next next one it's called dag zagals is coming for yo gummies
three two one go
Ben since you're so worried about people getting their student debt cancelled and subsidized by the taxpayer
Why don't you just go ahead and get yourself incorporated so you can get your stupid goddamn keto gummies?
Subsidized by the taxpayer because it only costs like 150 to 250 dollars to become incorporated
And after that you can write off literally everything related to your goddamn keto gummies
As an expense
And then you will also be forced to sell them so I could buy them and enjoy some of these delicious keto gummies
That you are allegedly producing like a mad scientist and also you need to write down everything
You're fucking morian
You dingus write down everything like a mad scientist like a mad alchemist
Attempting to turn lead into gold
It will be the newton
A key to go down last time don't worry
Just start writing it down turning a lead
Fucking slime corp and then a government office has to have documents about an actual business called slime corp
Water just do it so malt oligosaccharides
I some not yes, that's nice. Yes. I I some alt oligosaccharides aka. I am. Oh, that would be a really funny
Cool idea like if if ben like started a business literally called it slime corp and made keto gummies
Under a sliver just make the champion chapter two
Yeah, or maybe I could just do that
um, um, okay, I mean the thing like I all
Since I like have sort of tentative plans to maybe sell candy in the future
I'm already planning to write off all my gummy related expenses. Anyway, so like whatever. I don't I don't need to be incorporated for that
um
Uh
Other than that I actually have not been making the keto ones
I've just been off keto and I've just been making like sugar gummies
I like to the ones you shared on twitter recently the ones that look very opaque. They look good
Those ones came out really good
But and I and I and I part of me wants to try and replicate that recipe but
I made those with sugar
But I kind of think that maybe I should switch to using syrup like glucose syrup
I think it might result in a smoother product
Um, because those ones were pretty good
They were like 95 of the way there. I think switching to syrup might get me the last
The last way there. I don't know. Maybe you should quit comics and just make candy
That's like the opposite of what tectonic improv said
Yeah, please don't so one of you is wrong
And time will tell
Who do I shoot?
Whoever wins we lose
Next
Next one is called next one is oh next one is riddle my ass batman. He's back
He's back, baby. I'm honored to be on an episode riddle my ass batman
I had I had a funny exchange with riddle my ass batman in the comments on the last episode because riddle my ass batman had pledged to the vapor's two kickstarter
For like a lot. He had gotten like two signed copies, but he had never responded to the
Thing and I had messaged him on kickstarter and I never got a response
So he commented on the last episode. So I just replied to his comment being like, hey, what's what's your mailing address?
Like what's your like like what do you want on your doodles?
And he I didn't ask what I like I didn't expect him to reply there
But he replied there in the comments like with his mailing. Yes, he did
I I copied the the address and I removed the comments like because like okay
He said like oops, I did dox myself, but he didn't remove the comments. I had to do it
But I got it. I got the request so it's all good. That's good. Okay, three two one go
I know I'm someone who promises new voicemails a lot
But this time I promise and if I don't deliver you can cut off the end up
Ben sains dick and circumcise them. Okay
You're delivering it right now. There'll be a new voicemail series the quest for cold corona coming out speaking of cold corona first of this year
Now I already have all 26 episodes recorded. Oh my god written out. So I ought to do his record every week, you know
Not big deal. What I have to ask is I want to do a comic alongside it. Oh my god
The comic is not finished, but I think I can keep up with demands as I go
So should I do
One week of voicemails one week of comics or should I release all the comics?
in the first half of the year and then
The voicemail and first voicemails in the first half of the year and in the comics during the second half of the year
Thoughts discussion and there's a funny voicemail coming after this to whet your whistle. Okay
Same time same piece you can't I can't I can't believe it. I'm just gonna say this as a as a viewer
Slash us unfortunately a fan of the pro kresners podcast
Whatever you have planned riddle my ass batman is too good for this podcast. Just release it separately
I would say okay if if I would
I would say one of each
I would just say just if you've got if you've got
If you've got both just release one of each
Uh, it would be my recommendation. It sounds like way too much. I mean the voice mails would be like a good
Prompt to go look at the comic
If you have like another issue if that's that's true
So it'd be like, oh, we'll listen to the voicemail and then remind everyone to go look at the comic
I think that would work
Sounds like way too much effort for voicemail. I know you should just create actual contact
26 episodes
He's got them recorded already. He's basically making a show and we're the broadcast network
Yeah, that's basically it
That's that'd be 26 weeks
God
Damn
I
Get excited
It is too good for us. There's no question. There's no question
um
Yeah, I I like that. I like the idea that you released
Okay, I was assuming at first that like the comic and the voicemail were the same
Like it's a comic version of the voicemail in which case I would say release them together if they're separate things
Then yeah, I guess I guess still like just release one on your
Website or on tapas or wherever you're posting it and then we'll hear the voicemail and it'll be a
Reminder to check out the comic that yeah, that sounds reasonable
Let's let's hear. Let's hear the first one. Let's hear his fucking voicemail
The next one is also called riddle my ass batman. Here we go. Let our whistles
three two one go
As promised the funny voicemail now. I got I know you guys play dream stories and here's a good one
Uh, I was being raped by donatella. Oh my god
He's like, hey, man. They be sick of those tits and then uh, I was like, no donatella
No, am I you know like where my ass batman voice? I was like like I was really dreaming as sort of my ass batman
And then cold corona
came in and
He kicked donatella's ass joined in and then started raping him. So uh
That's calm. Yeah, and then I woke up. That's about all I have to say. Yeah. I uh, yeah
Got raped by cold corona because donatella's trying to rape me and cold corona's a hero and thank you. Thank you
Co-corona you uh saved me from dream rape
You're a hero. God bless. Thank god. Let's be my horseman. Okay. Thank you. See you time. Thank you. Bye
I'm so glad. So I have one big problem with this with this voicemail. Uh, the corona cannot be donatello
You don't think so. No, but he's the cutest and the strongest remember
He is the cutest and the strongest
That's true. That's true. Um, uh, I don't know
I mean
In a horse really beat a turtle. No, I think he could beat him
I think he could beat him if he got the upper hand if he got the drop on him
Like if donatello was in the middle of like a really choice rape
Uh that he was distracted enough by I think I think cold corona could use that to do his ambush tactics
You're right. It's not a fair fight. It's not a cold corona fights dirty
Not as dirty as donatello not as dirty as donatello, obviously
That's a good point. Remember my ass batman. I'm sorry that happened
Well, is this the dream?
I don't know, but you know, it's a nightmare. I guess it's this it's all you can say. It was a prophecy
I guess it did have a happy ending
He didn't that's true. That's true. God blesses everyone
um
Next voicemail is called poop balls lemal
I'm lovin this two
one
ago
Yes
I accept what was up with that life for some apology. Yes, but you
You resist I did I not forgive for that
Fuck you
So
I think I think that's the original man a person
Yeah, definitely. I just want to say the samurai is definitely my favorite
PCP voicemail character all the other all the other ones they're junk not a fan
But every single time there's this non sequitur email and it's like
Konnichiwa. I lose it. I just lose it. It's so good the samurai. Yeah, it's just it's it's it's half the voice
Right, like it's the the the the konnichiwa and the until next time is like, it's so satisfying
It's it's just whatever happens in between those two things is fine. Thank you
Well, he's thank you samurai. He's basically a member now, right?
Thank you for not forgiving me. I'm a little shocked that there's been no fan art of the samurai
Like he's he's been such a fixture
I guess there's been no like mention of any descriptive things. There's no items that you could have
He's just a samurai. Yeah
He's just a samurai and he and he scrolls. I guess he has scroll. Oh, yeah, he doesn't know. He doesn't have a scroll. That's right
That's distinctive, right? Like a samurai without a scroll like
Like I've never heard a subscriber character as being like like. Oh, yeah, and he doesn't have this
Okay, so so so look draw him being sad about the fact that he doesn't have something that and his hand is open
But there's nothing looking looking
Looking wistfully at his at at something
That is gone. He's got like an perfectly scroll shaped space on his shelf that is unfilled
That's his defining trait
Draw him. Oh, he's also got the necronomicon draw him on a computer without any scroll bars on his windows
Oh true
That that's that's the real Kawasaki scroll
The Kawasaki that's the technique is to scroll the web page real quick. Yeah scrolling on twitter
That's the Kawasaki scroll that ben saint stole
No, this is on twitter all the time the technique of going down the twitter feed
All right, I've heard enough of this nonsense
Uh, what next voicemail is called
That is another one. Oh, yeah, you
What you posted to but you haven't played the first no, I didn't
5 2 3
We didn't listen to that one. Oh
Wait, did I okay? Whatever. Okay, 5 2 3. All right, 5 2 3 is called spitting image
3 2 1 go
Welcome to the procrastiners podcast. My name is ben saint. Um
What's up game as we have all the guys are here tonight. We have a fucking
Sagan of a car. We have fucking the nostalgia critic. We have
The the screaming lady from the youtube thumbnail is on the red feminist
I don't have the troll face
We have the Zora killer who we have
of a little
Gollum made of months shooting piece
All the stars are here tonight
Okay
Wait with the screaming lady
Does he mean the lady that screened when trump won or does oh big red. Oh the other one
I was gonna see sargon of
Anita sarkeesian
No, the woman with the glasses and the red hair who there's all the like pictures of her screaming
Oh, yeah, I know who you're talking about
Yeah, I have no idea what her name is. I don't know. I never actually looked into it
Okay, okay, good. I'm glad she's here though. It wouldn't be the same without her
Um
Next the next one is called the same joke again
Three two one go
Welcome back to the pro president's podcast. Yeah, let's hear it. Virginia
And I would like to say to our guest
Jar Jar Binks
I
I will respect you and your marketing genius and the and I love you and I respect you so much
Oh, you don't think you want Jar Jar Binks? Thank you so much
Next guys fucking hiv
Wow, I don't have retards on the podcast
Why don't you have a cwc on quite quite literally the most famous retard of full time?
Oh, come on. Why don't you have any on again?
I don't know where this is going. I don't really understand like like it's I guess it's funny
I feel like he's trying to make a point, but I don't know what that point is. I think the point is that
Well, I think he's making a point with the jar jar binks
Uh, but I don't think hiv. I feel like hiv was improv
Well, you know what they say everything is positive even hiv
Is is the point that we have bad guests. Does he not like our choice of guests? I don't think that's I think
with with the
um
Well, maybe it is but with the digi thing
I think it was just him making fun of how digi called moralogic and marketing genius
Oh
By the way, that was good
I'm I missed that it was even about that that one was digi. Okay. Yeah, he did say digi at the beginning
marketing marketing genius lamal
Uh, okay. All right. Whatever fucking great. Uh, next one is called. Uh, you have to have moralogic back on
You have to three two one go
Holy shit, holy shit, you guys I remember this guy from back when he went by sato asami the first time he got banned from funny junk
Like yeah, no, I haven't even scratched the surface here. Like not only did he get fired from his job
He he got fucking disowned from his family over this shit like for real
I don't think I'm realizing this is like a prime law cow you have right here
Oh, well, I don't think he'll come back, right? Oh, he'll come back. He's desperate for attention, but like I don't know
What it I guess we okay
Go on go on. I I gotta say like I was listening to the podcast and like it was it was funny
It was funny the stuff he was saying until it wasn't but um, yeah, but I I got upset when he started making fun of janitors
Not like the forum moderator janitors, but the real life janitors because yeah yours truly
Is a janitor. No shit. Yeah, that's right. I think I I I heard that mentioned on twitter
I clean I clean schools. I clean them. That's that's fucked up. So
So here I am. You do you do it for free. You do it for free. I don't do it for free
I do it for money, but it's it's funny because I'm like cleaning light shields or whatever
And they just start shitting on janitors about how their lowest job ever. I'm like
Ah, now you made a personal mere logic
I'm pissed. I'm pissed. It's not fun of janitors in that way is like
It's like what are you doing? He hasn't worked very much
Just like normal like labor
Doesn't understand he doesn't respect it like you should because it's it's difficult and people need to do it
I don't think that mere logic
Likes us very much. I don't think he will like us very much anymore
But maybe we could get him maybe he would come back on to like defend like to argue against us to like defend himself
Maybe we could maybe we could finagle that
I think it'd be funny if we everything if we frame it the right way. We could make it happen
I mean, I don't hate my logic. I just think there's I could be uh
Yeah, if I could be on an episode with on him, there would there would be kind of funny
I want to play gamer's tower versus mere logic. There's I get I think just those two
just
The battle battle of the century
um
You know, there was a lot of
Honestly, there was a lot of anti-mer logic sentiment going around in the comments
But in my opinion in my opinion, he was a worthwhile guest. He was pretty funny
Yeah, and I wouldn't I wouldn't be opposed to to a to a round around to
uh, maybe
um
Next one is called
Next one is called red five rainbow
I know them three two one go
Hey, uh, just calling in to let you guys know that you might be able to get dream as a guest on the pcp
Since you have a connection to him through fit
since
dream knows fit because
It is in the challenging 25 youtubers to a fight for a $5,000 video on his second channel. So
I don't know. Maybe dream as a guest would be cool. Um
It's it's funny that this voicemail comes in
I'm I'm new to this but dream is like some minecraft youtuber. So I assume that's how fit mc knows him
But um, there was actually something that came out recently about this guy that he apparently
Like cheated or something to get uh to get like some sort of minecraft world record
I saw a video that was titled like our dreams
Like speedruns cheated
Yeah
And I didn't watch it and like I don't I know that dream is like some guy who has become really famous like very recently
I guess he's blown up in like the last few months and other than that
I just know that he's a guy who's become famous recently and he does minecraft stuff. Um
Uh
This is that just what a coincidence though
Yeah, I don't I don't I don't know anything about honestly
For me. Yeah, it would probably be good and like a box office draw to get dream on the podcast
He's got a lot of subscribers. I think he has like over a million
But I don't know who he is
And I don't
Know what I would care to even discuss with him. I don't I don't know uh, maybe
Sounds hard and I don't know what I'm gonna do it. You gotta chase the numbers, Ben
Oh, I don't that guy. I know his uh, I think I've seen one of his videos before
Frankly, I'm not motivated to make it happen
Frankly, frankly, I don't know if I give a shit. I know uh fit mc, but I never heard of dream
They he's kind of new
But I do have dreams video I watched was like I'm playing minecraft and um, there's a there's like every time I get hit
Everyone else in the server like gets launched a hundred blocks in the air and then they fall
And and that's the gimmick of the episode and there's other ones where he's like
His friends are trying to kill him or like the world is crumbling and he's only got a few minutes to like try and beat minecraft
Just like little little things like that
comedy
Cool, so what you're telling me is uh, if I want to get a lot of subscribers, I need to play minecraft, right?
Yeah, I mean to be I mean to be honest. I didn't know who fit mc was either until he came on
And then I was like, okay. Well, it's a whole it's it's a section of youtube like there's lots of
There's lots of sections of youtube that are like
Um cut off from others, but
Some of them have larger audiences than others
Yeah, sure. So like educational channels generally do very well
Overall because it's just like interesting things like minecraft work with with zoomers a lot
But not necessarily for
Uh people who don't play minecraft all the time
No, shit
Just just you know, just my insight as a you know kidding. Is that is that a fact?
Did you know? Yeah
Just a theory, uh, all right next voicemail is called sucking dick in the street three two one go
Benjamin, I love you and they're my best friends, but I have something to tell you that I think my offender
Yeah, I think the over publicization and the overexposure to social matters of lately is probably one of the causes
To the creative crisis that you've been describing for many episodes now
I think this idea that you have to create art that's both relevant and conforming to the
Small window of the world that you've been consuming
I think it's a stupid idea and it's probably creating an unachievable goal
for you with your art
And poisoning you well and I think the stupid damn
I think I think wait wait. It's not done. I seek help seek help
Damn, that's that's a real show knows this though
Explain
Well, like that social media sucks. Is that what he's like saying or that way you're saying specifically
Like he's been saying usage of social media is the reason he's got creative drought or whatever
He's saying it specifically in reference to me in reference to the the way that I've been talking about stuff. Yeah
Need to seek help from twitter
Yeah, yeah, like the the whole like oh get off twitter, bro
It's like I think I think
You know that then
It's it's just like. Yeah
I don't know. He said then done. I suppose it's I I understand. I feel a sense that in the abstract
My attention is not where it needs to be in order for me to be productive
but I don't
I lack I don't have like a clear like sense of like
Instead of what instead of me focusing on this I should be focusing on this
Uh, I don't have like a clear idea of like what?
I know I should be like making stuff, but like what?
What exactly should I be focused on? I don't know, you know to this
I actually just last night I started in on the on a big project that I've been meaning to start in on for a long time
Uh, and it was kind of fun getting started on that. Um, so maybe maybe maybe things are gonna turn around for me
I want to uh, uh really focus on that for a little while. Uh, so I guess
I I just think this guy's right. I think this guy's right and I know it
And I think he's right too
Yeah, I I think I guess my problem is just that is just like the a lot of people will like say stuff like this as if they're like
giving you
Uh new info not you in particular, but just like in general. Yeah, I think well, I feel like it's it's worth saying
in
Just to remind someone because like even if they say it to themselves hearing it from the outsides is like
It's a little extra motivation to actually think about changing something
It felt it felt personal enough to me that it didn't just feel like some some like some general like
General knowledge bullshit
Oh one thing's for sure. I have been I have been describing a sort of specific crisis
Uh, recently for sure and getting into fights on twitter is a complete waste of time
I will probably never quit that entirely
It's about it's about moderation everything in moderation
I mean, I do like how like curt you've become instead of like
Like I see your applies to people and and you're like, uh gross stupid like idiot
Like you just kind of fight and and they don't really start a response because of how like
I don't I don't really say anything but you do let them know that what they said was stupid
When a tweet makes me really angry
The last thing I want to do is give them a reason to like continue to say what they think
So like to me the obvious play. Yeah is to say something
Say something that is that is dismissive that that diminishes what they've said
That leaves them no room for like a serious like discussion or rebuttal to me
Uh, uh and and just lets me feel
Let's me feel as though I have harmed them in some way even if it's insignificant
Uh, that's all that's all I want out of a twitter fight and that's the easiest way to get it
It's literally like so on the on the on the quickie. I remember reading
I was reading the quickie years ago and and it just described um a trend
in which like as sonichu goes on the like
The the series starts with villains that are like more
sort of fictional
And you know the the characters have like continuing battles against them
But like later on
Chris starts to introduce these real life people these real life trolls as antagonists
And as the story goes on the conflicts with these antagonists
They actually become shorter and less climactic
because
Do you do you know where i'm going? Have I said this before? I don't think yeah
Are you are you going to like
She was inspired by real life events. That's what she was taking them from
Near the end
Is that where this is going?
No, the the the the reason posited in this quickie article and it sounds true to me
Is that the the battles against these real life antagonists become shorter and less climactic because
chris
Genuinely hates them and feels genuine anger and wants to use their presence in the comic not as like
A narrative beat for drama
But because chris needs to just defeat them
Like you know in a way that is as final and as
And as and as you know serious and as indisputable as she can
She just wants to feel that this person is dead and destroyed and to let her audience know
I have won this person is lost. They are gone. They are nothing to me
Which is why someone like ian brandon anderson will show up for exactly one panel
Before sonichu just will utterly obliterate him in a single blow and then he gets dragged down to hell by trolls
And that's the last you ever hear of him because that was like such a serious conflict that it was like
There's no fun and games here. There's no this is not like a ha ha. This is a villain like oh, we're rivals with each other
No, fuck this person. I kill them. That's what needs to happen. The monsters and that's how I feel
When I see some dipshit on twitter say, uh, I don't know
Whatever I don't know man. This uh, this sounds kind of like school shooter talk to me
You sound kind of like school shooter talk to me
I should shoot you for saying something like that
I could shoot you
Next voicemail are we done? How many more do we have?
Only like four I think four or five cool. We're getting there. Um
Next one is called mr. Miracle. Wait, why wait, why was that last one called sucking dick in the street?
I
It's evocative against the people going. It's true. It drew my eye. Okay. This one's called mr. Miracle three two one go
Hey, Ben, I have a comic book recommendation for you
It's called Mr. Miracle by Tom King. Tom King is one of the biggest names on mainstream comics right now
And mr. Miracle is a DC comic character created by Jack Kirby a huge visionary
She's made freedom mention him on the last episode
But you don't really need to know anything about DC comics continuity to to get into it
It reminds me of the champion that you mentioned you were interested in writing again has sort of
some thematically
Some similarities it's about this guy who's a literal champion from this cosmic kingdom
But um, it has a lot of emotional depth to it and and the art I think is pretty good
I think you might might like
Give it like a
seven out of ten
Look look it up
Seven out of ten would you recommend the seven out of ten? I guess I have before
um
You know numbers are very hard to know what they mean true
If it's like seven out of ten in general, but I think this person would really appreciate what's good about it
Maybe yeah, all right. Yeah fair enough
I've never heard of this though
I've heard of mr. Miracle. I know absolutely nothing about him. Yeah, I guess he's a super escape artist
This is like his power. Oh like Houdini
Or like chris angel mind freak
Powers and abilities like all the new gods scott free is function. I guess his name is scott free is functionally immortal
Uh, superhuman strength ability reflects a stamina
resistance to blah blah blah blah
Genius level intellect
Oh, he was he was trained
This this fucking sentence scott was trained by granny goodness as an arrow trooper
Well, you know, he's he's a man for the job
I'm not that into comics, but I can never take me like granny goodness seriously whenever she'd show up in like the
Justice League cartoon or whatever. I'd be like
We really using we're really using someone called granny goodness. I take I take gorilla grot over her
Wait, is he a
Okay, he's a good guy. Why was he trained by yeah, he might have defected is granny goodness is a bad guy
bad girl
Sure, um
Everyone any anyone can be a bad guy
Bad guy is gender neutral like uh like billie eilish
Yeah, exactly eilish is gender neutral
And and so are and so and so uh
Are you dear viewer?
It's we should get we should get billie eilish from the pcp
I agree and that would be great
I'm sure oblivion fall knows her
Wait, why?
Yeah, uh, he does like music, right? Everyone in music knows each other. Oh, that's small
It's small in small world small world
I picked up a guitar and I already I instantly had ringo star's phone number
It was recent love the back love
peace and wolf
This ringo star wrote every wrote his number on every guitar in the world because it's like if you're doing this
He wants to get to know what you what you're about. It's like call me. It's like that story of um of jack white
Hiding like records of unreleased demos and used furniture. He gives away
Just like a true by the way
Honestly that I have I that voicemail and the
Wikipedia article has given me like no sense at all of what mr. Miracle is
He might be talking about a specific run
Like a recent run by um by tom he did say I think is what he said
He said um, he said tom, um
Uh, yeah, tom king. Okay. All right. Well
I probably should check it out, but I I don't know if I'm going to cheesy probably knows something about it
Maybe he would maybe he would
um, all right next voicemail is uh called um, what is it called? It is called
Mr. Miracle 2 big barda
I know from the wikipedia article that big barda is mr. Miracle's wife. So
That's context. I think big barda is also linkara's favorite comic book character
Really, I think so. Yeah, it all comes back. It all comes full circle
Uh, three two one go
So just one more two details that could convince me to read the comic. Um
One tom king's a huge lefty. He is an ex-military but has no love for that bullshit. That's cool. And um
It features one the sexist woman on comics. Um big barda. She's like a huge amazon lady who has big tits and big s
And now you have my attention and give google her to big barda. I'm gonna school. I'm gonna google it and she's
Mr. Miracle's wife. So she's the whole comic
I do I do not believe you're fucking cool. I do not believe for us. I do not believe for a second
When I have to read it
I do not believe for a second that a woman who first appeared in a silver age comic book
I would ever find them hot. I think it's impossible
But I'm gonna google it and let's let's find out shall. What was her name? I think I get what you're saying big barda
Big barda
No, what is this? What the fuck is this? What the fuck?
What the fuck I don't get it what?
What is good? What is appealing about this at all? She looks like she's got a fucking like
Feet
Pharaoh's helmet. She's looking like full body armor and just like a girl with a face
What the fuck?
She's literally just a girl with a face
What there's just a lot of different iterations. I don't know which one he's talking about
I mean, they're all they're all the same. Well, I personally
She's wearing a suit of armor. This sucks. I prefer my girl's not to have faces
I
Cannot understand I cannot understand why you would look at this and be like, uh
Uh, this this girl who looks literally the same as every other girl
Except
She's wearing armor. Look, there she is. She's not wearing armor. She's she's just tall. I guess
Oh, wow, it's a girl with a face
This sucks. She looks pretty good. No, no fuck this comic. No fuck mr. Miracle
I miss you
Miracle, this is my perfect excuse that I needed not to read it. I can pretend to be outraged about this
Uh
No, this is tecno tonic. Are you gone? Wait a minute tectonic said he'd be back. Um, but he said go on without him
Okay, wait, what the fuck hold on. I just found this on google and I just want to show you
That's fucked up
This is fucked up superman in a porno. They're gonna fuck they're gonna fuck for money
Pretty cool. Uh, I wonder what the context is for this one. Do you think if superman has sex that his, uh
Pee-pee jizz would go zap and kill
Listen, listen, you listen you stupid motherfucker. Obviously
Of course
Um, didn't didn't superman get lois lane pregnant in one
iteration
And I've heard people say that like obviously it's impossible because like super sperm should be like stronger than steel
And she just like obliterate her uterus, right? She just like the sperm should just tunnel through her body and like fill her with a
Micro it's easy. All he needs to do is do it at an extreme distance. So the air is
Resistance will slow it down to the point
Where it will not kill her. So she's like 40 like 40 miles down the road and he goes
Wait, can't he just have kryptonite around him?
Yeah, he could just wear like red kryptonite or whatever. Uh, autoerotic kryptonation
I think it's red kryptonite. I think it's a red kryptonite that doesn't hurt him
But just like kind of turns him normal. So just use that
That's what you need. It's like honestly
I kind of think that there might be like an in now that I say that I'm thinking that maybe there is like an in-universe
iteration of superman where he does get lois lane pregnant and he only manages to do it by the use of red kryptonite
Yeah, I could be like hallucinating this right now. That's his like j.o. Crystal
No
Yeah, exactly
Okay, all right. All right. This is this is fucking this is degenerate. This is degenerate is what this is
um, next one
Where are the chibi bakas you baka faced horse scrotum?
three
Wait, there you go. Three two one go
Yo gib
You said like a billion episodes ago that you and monk. She did a cure a chibi bakas episode
No, you never released it. I never did what happened. Where's the chibi bakas?
Where's the chibi bakas gibbon? Where's the bloody I'd love to see it
I I I oh
I love to watch chibi bakas on me on metelli is well between sweet and chimneys
We got a nerve struck a nerve have I know it's just really really bad. Um
Um
Too close to home too close to home too close. It's just from my flashbacks to my literal everyday life
This is just
Everything sucks about the uk the vat tax is out of this world and everyone sounds like that
um chibi bakas is is is sort of like
On like permanent hiatus, which is to say that there's no plans to ever make an episode again
But I did say that I recorded that
Yeah, I've looked at the footage before and it was just like not very interesting and kind of like lame and I don't like it
Wait, what you mean like the audio?
Well, I recorded it in video form and audio
Um, because we because munchy was literally there. It's like oh, it's chibi bakas live
Wait, was that for was that ragcon four? No, that was when munchy came over to stay in my house
Right, right, right, right. I mean the the discussion just will release it
Well, the thing is I have to edit it because it sucks and it's like we don't really have much to say
I was just like that was weird wasn't it? Yeah, if I had weird
I think people would appreciate it. I don't know. I don't know. I can tell you what to do
But like I think it would it's it's probably it's probably worth posting
Okay, I'm I'll think about it. I'll have to I've remind I was hoping everyone would have forgotten
But there's one guy he's fucking ruined my plan
If you already have the footage you may as well release it
But I don't want it to be cringe. I gotta un-cringe it for it. It's too late. It's too late
I gotta I gotta up the contrast mac
The thing about that is not releasing it is even more cringe by definition. You're really damned if you do damned if you don't
Maybe
Maybe maybe I won't be cringe, you know, maybe maybe I don't know. I doubt it
uh
Next one is called um make pcp wholesome again safe place. Oh wait, I didn't put it in the chat. Um
There it is make pcp wholesome again safe place three two one go
Guys there's nothing healthy wrong with being a talk
Oh, no, if a black man has exude your wife for instance
Why not been a little more inclusive, you know, I'm progressive
I think that he's a young
masculine
brave man
And he's doing great for this podcast and for our community. So people, please
Stop making fun of ben sainte
You should know better
It's always you
Thank you
Yeah, you're the butt of every joke ben
That's what what did I say? Who was the guy who left the podcast and everyone was glad he was gone that I compared myself to
Uh greg from completionist
Yeah, lemal. I don't know. Oh, yeah, that guy. I like that. He sounds like he's
He's like talking in front of a huge audience like the echo it makes it seem like he he's doing like some sort of state of the union or whatever about
It being okay that you're a cock
Didn't uh maddox do that one time
He did for a second. I I thought that was a thought
This was a maddox thing, but no
Yeah, but when maddox defended cucks he like
It's like he thought that the only
Meaning that the word had was that you were like a cuck fetishist
And he didn't like
He didn't read no, no, there's nothing wrong with being a cuck's like it's just a fetish. He missed the point
He missed he didn't read the room. I guess. Yeah. Yeah on that one
No, we're just sort of maybe it's one of those language
purists whereas like if it was
Language can't change if people use it differently. It has a definition a word
A word can't have more than one meaning in different contexts. This is so stupid
uh
Next next one is called cross
Uh important question
Three two one go
What is your favorite font and why?
Uh, comic for the uh, no, um, I guess courier because it's the the font that homestuck has I think
Ah, that's the that's the typewriter font
Yeah, courier courier new
Yeah, that's a good one
Well, the the font I use on my website is uh aerial I think
I
I classic there's a font in um in sony vegas
Called, uh, I think it's called bond shrift condensed bold or something
It's I can only find it in vegas like I try to use it other places and I can't find it anywhere. Let me
Let me see get it. I mean, I I will say, you know, everybody knows that I love, um, showcard gothic
Yes, everyone knows about the showcard gothic and that's a that's a big one
Um, great font that I never hear anyone talk about is ukari mobile
ukari mobile is a super good font and which I found
Uh, because it was the font that they used in the promo materials for fighting is magic
The the the game that would go on to become, uh, them's fighting who herds them's fighting herds classic. Oh, yeah
Um, that's a super good, uh
There's one called there's one I use all the time called trash type dk
Um, which looks it looks like courier, but it's all like messy and fucked up and like grungy looking that one's like
I love that one
What else to it as a kid my favorite font was sylphane
Because sylphane looks like times new roman, but it is slightly bigger and therefore if you write your essays in it
You can get away with writing that
Yeah
uh
I like
I like all the fonts from pokemon games. I use those a lot when I want to use like some like
Computer looking texts. I like the um the cave story font too. That one's nice
There's too many fonts to keep track of I have no idea
Uh, riveting uh riveting a font commentary
I mean there's a font of discussion people are interested in people are definitely interested in fonts
And I am one of the gamers who is who who has like
I don't know difficulty
Remembering fonts or like distinguishing them. I mean, there's so fucking many
There's so fucking many but I've always felt like people are always like into something about fonts
And I just my brain just doesn't perceive them in the same way fonts are interesting
Because they're like a thing that everyone is oh, I just
A bit of an outstretched pick but uh karima
Karima is the font that andrew hussey used to like it's the font that like the title of like planets appears in in homestuck like
Durs and prospit and like land of wind and shade
Is karima and uh karima is pretty cool. Um
Uh
Fonts are like a thing that like you see everywhere and probably for a lot of your life
You don't even like think about or question at all
And then when you when you discover that like these things have names and like people design them
And like they come from somewhere and there's all these things to consider about them
that like uh that you'd never even thought about like spacing and and kerning and and um
Serifs and and all that shit and it's like a whole rabbit hole
That was like right in front of you the whole time. Yeah, and you never even thought about it
That's what that's what's interesting about fonts to me. I like I like wolf
uh fonts
wolf
Yeah, wolf peck is a band that I like and the the leader of the band is also very into fonts and he's made a font
Um that he uses in all his youtube videos
And he's very like knowledgeable in all the different aspects of font design
I see and it looks nice
I see I think it may be a series of fonts. I can't remember
well
Oh, I have I have one
That I used in the champion that I thought was pretty nice called knight warrior
um
That's just kind of a fancy looking one that I think is this is nice
Oh, yeah, this is this is a funny kind of gothic
This jack stratton leader of wolf records doing a font video. He's funny
He's a funny guy
Font calculus
Tectonic, what did you what did you post the um the my name is tectonic improv video for oh, that's that's um
The title is the bond shrift condensed. Oh
Oh, yeah
I remember when I when I started making videos. I was like I need a font
So I just kept testing out fonts and videos and I eventually found this one. I was like this one's cool
Don't take this the wrong way. Were you inspired by digi being really into blue highway?
No, what what font is that is is that close to this one?
I
No, I mean sort of but not really no just I remember digi was like very for a while
She was like
Blue highway was the font she would always use in all of her videos. Oh, you mean just like having a font
Yeah, just having like a font. That's like your font. I'm sure I'm sure I was inspired in some way
Yeah, I remember her talking about that and I thought like that's a good idea that makes sense
um
She's not like she invented the concept or anything, but yeah
Uh
All right, anything anything else to say about fonts uh guys or shall we please watch that wolf sans video?
But yes, I think they're fantastic
Guys the next one is uh, super good. Uh, it's called uh, george soros CEO of antifa llc incorporated
Oh, they incorporated
Well, they made an llc good for them. They can write off so much on their taxes
Three two one go
Mr. St
Yep
It is with her breath that we inform you that your employment with antifa llc incorporated has been terminated effective december 13th
2020 oh no my health insurance you'll receive your final paycheck of soros bucks in the mail
You are being terminated due to your conduct beginning on december 23rd 2015
The most recent of which includes your use of racial and ableist slurs
Yeah, your association with individuals who use racial and ableist slurs
Yeah, and your application of drawing a youtuber's profile picture in a pornographic format. Yeah
Wait, what request that you return any and all property that was generated or obtained during your employment with
I didn't think it was bad to draw what this includes any documents
I thought you were saying you drew your leftist id badge. No your leftist card
Your company gun this card any manuals computers software keys or security cards that have been obtained during your paid protesting
And any other items
acquired during your work like the company car that I used to drive big
Thank you for for your slurs the cause super soldiers to a desktop will be sent to you shortly
Okay. Hey, george. Hey, it's been a pleasure. Mr. Mist. Sorry. Mr. Soros now
We're no longer on a first name basis. You can't say he doesn't conduct himself with an air of respect
Can't say it can't say he doesn't do that
Uh, uh, dignity, you know the word I would use dignified. Um, it's been it's been an honor. Uh, sorry about all the n words
Does a does a lefty company car drive on the left
I think that's only in the u.k
No, like like everything of the cars on the left is a motorbike. It's all on the left
It's just in the you're in the little the side pocket the side pocket of the fucking
If you try to pass anyone for being too slow you get pulled over and then and then taken to the uh, to the right wing camps
Where they're all taken
Passing on the right. Hmm. Not if I have anything to say about it
Okay, guys, that's it. We listened to all the voicemails. The nightmare is over. Wow
Wow
So, um
How you guys how you doing? How we feeling vibe check vibe check vibe check is we've been going for three and a half hours
God another one a long one. I hope that I hope that you appreciate it
Another long ass episode. I just remember you're on the pro
Spongebob remember youtube.com slash gamers tavern show
That's true
tectonic
plug yourself
tectonic improv comm it takes you it takes you to my channel
Does it actually yeah, it actually does
Uh, oh good a friend of mine bought the domain to I make videos on games. I have this whole long
long series of
Compiling this old text lp talking about you have you have more you have more
You have more stuff on your channel than we talked about on this episode. Yeah, you have a bunch of I got a bunch of stuff
It's mostly about games
Um, mm-hmm
You'll love them. I know you will
Uh
There is um
Go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators to give us cash
And send a voicemail at the speakpipe.com slash pcb voicemail
and uh
Anything else? Is that did I forget anything?
Did get a plug?
Oh, give and take dot site. I mean already fucking
You can't
Yeah, there's nothing on there. No, it don't matter cares none of this matters
None of this fucking man none of this fucking man is uh
Oh, no, is it really over? Have you really come to the end? No, no, it doesn't have to end then
Oh partying is such a sweet sorrow. Goodbye
No, wait, I I want to talk about circumcision