And without further ado, welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
It's Ben Saint, and we got Gibbontake, and we got Tom Oliver is back from the grave.
Rise from your grave.
Classic altered beast for the Sega Genesis, the best console of the 90s.
Shut the fuck up. It's the SNES, you motherfuckers. It's the Super Famicom.
Sorry, there are like 32 bits, colors, 16 billion dollars.
There are these magazine advertisements that told me that Sega does one in 10 down,
and I believe my my superiors when they market to me.
That's not that's not true.
No, gaming, the best game ever made was A Secret of Mana for the Super Nintendo,
and it was all downhill from there.
They'll never change my mind.
Why don't you review it then, huh?
Fuck you.
Why don't you show me?
You are too, your old 3D graphics are too fucking modern for me.
They are they are Zoomer shit. The shit you like is dumb, and it's too high tech.
Got reject modernity 3D graphics, embrace tradition, Secret of Mana.
It's like no, reject modernity, and it's like PlayStation Banjo-Kazooie or Crash Bandicoot.
It's like reject modernity, embrace tradition, yeah.
Like only five years apart from each other.
It's all takes.
Where you been, Tom? What you been up to?
I've just been dying entirely and playing too many video games.
I beat all of Ghost of Tsushima. Man, that was a fun game. That was pretty cool.
Oh, yeah. Talk about that because that I saw that in the game awards when they because,
you know, because I'm stupid and I watched that.
And I saw some of the cutscenes. I was like, hey, that looks not bad.
I wonder what that is.
It's the newest game by Sucker Punch, which I'm sure you're aware of.
They did the Sly Cooper series, and then they did Infamous for the PS3 and PS4.
And this is the game they've been working on for the last like five or six years or whatever.
It's like it's like an open world samurai game, and it's really fun.
And I enjoyed it a lot.
It got passed. It like sinks into a lot of like the open world kind of bullshit,
where it's just like go to this camp and kill people and like do that a bunch of times.
But like the side quests are pretty good because like instead of having a bunch of
random side quests, you meet like four supporting characters and they have like a long quest
that's like 10 parts each as you go through the campaign.
There's like these mini campaigns with these characters going along on side of it.
So they feel a little bit more substantive than just like go here, do a quick thing and like
tick the box off your map. And it was cool. The combat was fun.
You have like different stances to fight different kind of weapons and the skill tree is cool.
And you're a samurai, so you can like challenge people to showdowns and kill them in one hit
if you find everything right.
Yeah, yeah. I was thinking, I was thinking about him the entire time.
We now know the samurai's name is Jin Sakai. That's who's been calling us this whole time.
I figured it out.
Is it like like Japanese the Witcher?
Pretty much. If the Witcher was like had way better combat, it was more fun to play moment
to moment because like you can choose to be a samurai guy or you can be like a dishonorable
ninja guy and reject your samurai code and murderously backstab people and poison people
and just do whatever dirty tactics you have to to like kill the Mongol invaders and it's
really fucking cool.
That's what happens when you embrace modernity.
How true to life is it? Because samurai were like
it's true to my life.
It's true to my lived experience, 100%.
Like they samurai like if I, as far as I understand, they like had bows and they would
ride on horses and they would shoot from afar and only bring the sword out when it was like close.
You can ride a horse and shoot bows.
In fact, I mainly used bows because it was so much more fun to just snipe people from afar
and then clean up what was left after you've exhausted your arrows and stuff. That was pretty cool.
And there's like armor sets that give you bonuses to like using bows and stuff because
there's like you go around, you find these like storytellers.
These like musician guys who are like telling like fables of like ancient artifacts of like
legendary warriors from Tsushima's past.
You can like track down those locations and get like mythic level armor of like these like
legendary heroes from hundreds of years ago.
And that's pretty fucking cool.
Sounds just like my favorite.
No, the best video.
The best thing is like this game is like super colorful, but like because it's a love letter
to Kurosawa movies, there's that a Kurosawa mode that turns it like grainy black and white
like a movie.
And that's Kurosawa.
Yes, that's pretty cool.
Yeah, it's pretty pretty dope.
It's pretty based.
I liked it a lot.
If it's inspired by that, then it's got a better or worse.
Is it better or worse than Cyberpunk 2077?
Well, I haven't played Cyberpunk, but I'm going to assume probably better than it is in its current state.
Even though I secured a 3060 Ti, so I do have a good enough graphics card to play it.
I just haven't yet.
The only thing I know about Cyberpunk, aside from glitches, is that one like funny video
where somebody like made it so there's the guy on the train and he's like,
oh, something, something, Cyberpunk.
And then it reveals and like the title comes up as like shitty PS1, like low resolution background
and it stutters and then it crashes.
You know that?
The no man.
You talk about the no man skype redo thing that they did where like because like they
initially did this with no man sky, but then they like redid it on Twitter for like Cyberpunk
because like the reveal from like the E3 trailer to the actual game is like totally different.
It's pretty.
Yeah.
It's pretty good.
The music seems cool.
That's like the best part of the game so far from what little I understand is that the soundtrack is
pretty, pretty dope.
Best part of the game is not the video game part.
Yeah.
It's weird.
Like what bothers me the most?
Wait, are you talking about Tsushima or Cyberpunk?
Cyberpunk.
The soundtrack in Tsushima was serviceable, but not like outstanding.
I didn't.
There's no like particular track.
I remember.
It's funny because like the advertising campaign for like Cyberpunk has been like counter
use like what defines a criminal in Night City getting caught.
I'm like that's that's just the real world.
Like you can do whatever crimes you want as long as you don't get caught.
That's true.
You're not charged with the crime unless you're caught.
Like this is a dumb campaign.
Great commentary.
Yeah.
Great commentary there.
I'm just like Ben Strupp lifted multiple times.
He's not a criminal yet.
Have I have I admitted that?
Have I admitted that on the podcast?
Yes, you have.
Did you just out me?
Okay.
No, you had.
Remember you talked about it like last year and had like a mini crisis like,
should we cut this?
Should we cut this?
And then you're like, fuck it.
No, no, no.
I think you're conflating two times.
I think there was one time when I did talk about it and then afterwards I was like,
no, no, cut that.
We got to cut that.
And then I think later on we talked about it again and I said like,
last time I said cut it, but this time I don't care anymore.
Maybe.
I thought the first time was like really early on in the PCP.
It was pretty early.
It was a long time ago.
Things have changed.
Ben's been radicalized.
Radicalized hardcore.
Now shoplifting is a badge of honor.
Nothing to be ashamed of.
I was shoplifting before it was cool.
Speaking of music and video games, why is Pokemon Black and White 2 just the best game ever made?
I was listening to, I was looking for some good video game OSTs and I was looking on Reddit
because I like googled question like underrated video game soundtracks.
And I got a bunch of like Reddit threads that were the results and I like was just going through
a bunch of the results and Black and White 2 has just has the best music in any video game ever made.
And also the best graphics and just is the best game period.
Hands down.
Not Pokemon Peak there and so did gaming in general.
I know I said it was Secret of Mana, but that was Red Hair.
That was a secret.
That was a trick.
God, it's so fucking good.
Man, the way this is gonna gush for a second.
Just the way the way that when you get to that the music changes when you're fighting a gym
leader and they get down to their last Pokemon, it's just from like a tense battle theme to
like a like triumphant theme.
It's so fucking good, man.
Black and White 2, the ones where they replace the like annoying beep when you're
Pokemon's low on HP to like the stressful music, but like it might work.
That sounds like probably I don't know.
That was fucking sick and I like that sounds like something they would do.
Yeah.
Oh, and I had the best.
It had the best sprites.
It had the best animations.
It was right before they decided, you know what?
Fuck everything.
Let's just go 3D now.
And that was the downfall.
That was the downfall, the switch to 3D, the switch that everyone says.
Oh, you Mario, this is a switch to 3D.
Oh, it was a big challenge for the video game industry.
Well, guess what?
They didn't survive it.
Video games didn't even survive the transition to 3D.
Video games are a dead medium now.
That's true.
There are no real video games anymore.
They're dead.
They died.
They died in 1996 or whatever when the Nintendo 64 came out.
3D did make games mainstream, which did ruin them.
So that's right.
Thank you.
Yes.
We have to go back.
We have to reject modernity.
Many people are saying this.
Man, I can't wait to get a PS5, guys.
It's going to be so good.
No.
What even video games are on the PS5?
Literally, it's just another...
It's Demon's Souls machine again.
Why?
Just like the PS4 was just a blood-borne rig.
This is a Demon's Souls rig.
It's the only game.
Why?
The best thing about PS5 is that you can play all your PS4 games at 60 frames.
I already played those video games.
I want to play Ghost of Tsushima again at 60 frames per second and no loading.
I want to fucking kill myself.
I can't wait to have something that I can plug in and is a big piece of plastic and metal.
Yeah.
I can't wait to consume this content.
And consume...
I've resisted buying a Nintendo Switch for this long.
How could I possibly purchase something so shit as something as a PS5?
I'm not going to get a PS5 until the slim version comes out,
because this current one is some ugly monstrosity that I detest.
It looks like...
I think it's kind of cool looking, even if it is the best thing.
It is a bit strange.
It reminds me of when you get two Pringles and you put them together so they curve outwards.
The best thing people have done with a PS5 is someone 3D printed a head of Setokaiba
and put it on there because it looks like Setokaiba's coat from the second arc.
That was the best thing.
Seen something like that.
That almost justifies how ugly it is, but not really.
Looks like a weird clam thing.
No, really, though.
What fucking video games can you play on the PS5?
Are there any?
Literally the only games that anyone should care about right now is the Demon's Souls remake
and Spider-Man, Miles Morales, which is also on PS4 because I bought and beat it on PS4.
What the fuck is the point of the five?
You get no loading times.
It's got that SSD.
It's just stupid.
It's tradition.
This is the embraced tradition mindset.
If you embrace the tradition of creating new consoles, then you get this.
No, this is the modernity.
I thought tradition was what we want to go back to.
That's the thing.
Sometimes tradition is bad.
Oh, god.
Are you saying that there's new wants to things in the world?
Yes, there's no.
Wait, are you saying that the PS5 is modernity or tradition?
It's tradition because there's always been a new console cycle to iterate.
Tradition, the tradition is to just endlessly iterate and follow the cycle.
Everyone says that the coolest thing about the PS5 is the new controller because the trigger buttons
have sensitivity, so you can program different guns and stuff to feel different.
You can have really effective haptics.
There's a game that ships with it called Astros Playground or whatever, whatever the fuck it's
called.
And depending on whether you're walking on sand or metal, the vibration is different,
so it has a really expanded sense of tactility to everything you're doing.
And everyone's like, this is the coolest thing.
This is the best.
Fuck graphics.
This is the coolest shit ever.
Oh, Astro's Playroom?
Yeah, that one.
I think I saw an article somewhere or a tweet or something that said that
the best thing on the PS5 is this free demo.
Yeah, that's the one they're talking about.
Yeah, but it's the only launch game that actually makes use of all the weird functionality.
No one else is going to do it except for Sony themselves to convince you you didn't just
waste $500 because you could only play Demon's Souls.
This little guy Astro reminds me of, did you guys try out the Oculus Rift at the Radcon 4?
Yeah, we all brought it.
Play Beat Saber.
Yeah, did you remember the demo when you booted up with the little robot?
I didn't play the demo part.
Did you see one of us playing it?
There's a little intro sequence where you put on the helmet and then you're in this room,
this kind of junky room, and this little robot wakes up and comes over and says hello to you
and gives you a bunch of items to fuck around with and disks to load into slots to load data.
Interesting.
I don't know.
It's very cute, and this guy looks like that.
If you want to spend multiple hundreds of dollars on a new video game thing, buy a VR set.
There's so many games out there that are good for that.
Haptic feedback, I think, is pretty good.
That's a pretty nice feature to build into a game that's also very unintrusive,
unlike motion controls.
The more I start playing video games and thinking about them more critically
because I'm making games now, I'm just like, haptic feedback is so important to making combat
feel good.
Every time I play on mouse and keyboard and there's no haptics, I'm like, this sucks.
I don't, I mean, what kind of games are you talking about?
What?
Do you just mean any game?
Like first person shooters?
Like any game on PC, because you're playing with mouse and keyboard on a PC,
there's no rumble built into your mouse and keyboard.
So like you can shoot something and there's no like forced feedback and it sucks.
It's a weird thing to say to me because like video games, video games thrived
before haptic feedback was invented.
Sure.
But it's just so much better when you have it.
That's my only point.
Really?
Yeah.
I mean, I feel like when you're playing like a visceral action game or a shooter or something
and you get like a kickback from like, I don't necessarily think that it is kind of game,
I guess.
It sells sensation way more.
Are you saying that like now that you have it, you can't go back to not having it,
it doesn't feel the same?
No, it's just categorically better to have it than to not.
It doesn't ruin the experience, but it doesn't detract anything from the experience by having it.
I guess it doesn't detract anything.
I just think you could get basically exactly the same level of like interest through visual cues
and like animation and stuff.
Like I'm thinking of like Paper Mario, how it feels or like Super Mario RPG,
how it feels like really good to time the button presses to whack an enemy.
And it's like the sound effects and the animation and stuff.
Like you could have all of that and then controller rumble.
And it would be like you could have you could have everything that makes that satisfying plus.
I don't know that it would be necessarily even.
I don't know.
I don't really care.
It doesn't bother me that playing TF2 feels just as satisfying with a mouse and keyboard
as playing a different game that has the the rumble stuff.
I like rumble putting it in all my games going forward.
I've decided.
I gave it some thought and it's good.
Can you do that?
Yeah.
You can just like use code like stuff in for rumble and shit like that.
You just got to like make it work.
That's so that's so weird.
How do you think?
How do you think equals?
How do you think Sony does it?
I I don't I don't fucking know.
They have magic controller proprietary device.
The bushlaw controller rumble.
I don't know.
They own the means.
They own the means of haptic Xbox controllers to it.
It's just controllers.
They all do well.
Okay.
Yeah.
I guess I'm just saying it's it's I guess I can understand that there's no reason why an indie dev can't.
Well, it's it's it's just like a make use of a of a first party controllers haptic functionality.
They have in like things like Unity.
Like you can you can say set up a control scheme for an Xbox controller or or you know
so and that like would automatically map to a PlayStation controller.
I hope they'll maybe they'll maybe for mouse and keyboard nerds like me.
They'll make they'll they'll make a mouse a mouse with haptic.
There has someone has to have done it.
There has to be like a haptic mouse that exists.
Probably now that I know that I say it doesn't actually sound that weird.
I could imagine it being like if you did it badly.
Like if you're you need precision clicking and then like the rumble makes you move over like
you would probably need to use them like a special mouse pad or something.
Because if you just use it on your fucking table, it's like I'll rattle your table and it vibrates.
It's a feature not a bug in war when you're shooting.
You'd be really nervous and you wouldn't be able to keep your your aim steady.
So we're just replicating that with force feedback.
Yeah, they should they should like like tape guns to your computer
so that when you get shot in the game, it shoots you for real.
That's the ultimate haptic feedback.
Well, isn't there a story of someone who like put an IV in them and like it like drained their blood
when they took damage in like the game.
What the fuck?
That's not I remember reading that story years ago.
What do they think would happen?
Bad things.
They died.
Did they die?
Or like what's the I don't remember.
The end of the story.
I could very well have made this up, but I'm almost certain I read this at one point.
It does sound kind of like a nightmare fever dream.
That sounds like a sort of like cryptid thing.
I don't want to I want to think about it.
Yeah, it sounds like a pretty gamer moment, you know.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, very, very gamer moment.
I was playing Sonic the Hedgehog and something seemed off.
There was an IV feed stabbed into my arm.
I didn't think much of it at the time, but I just kept playing.
Every time I lose rings, I just like pull the needle out.
My blood spray is everywhere to simulate the sensation.
I got to run around and collect all of them.
But if I have at least one blood, it's OK.
No blood, please.
Keep keep the blood out of video games,
by which I mean drain it entirely out of my body when I play them.
Thank you and good night.
You know, video games is a good interesting, not interesting.
It's not an interesting topic, but it's definitely not interesting.
It's a good topic because I have recently just been
I think I've talked before about the list of video games
that I've made of all the video games on all the platforms that I own
and the ones I've played, the ones I've like beaten to completion.
And I've been going through it because I've got like the release dates.
And I'm like saying like which of the games I've played
from like 2003 is the best game of that year.
And I was thinking of doing like a big funny stupid list.
Do it.
I've got like 2003.
Here's a list of the games I played.
Aladdin's Maths Quest, The Sims,
Ape Escape 2, Rayman 3, Metroid Prime,
Donkey Kong, Country, Game Boy Advance, Pokemon Sapphire.
You know, there's all these Wallace and Gromit in Project Zoo.
Whoa.
Simpsons Hit and Run, Broken Sword, Lord of the Rings Return of the King, Puzzle Pirates.
I just thought like I love lists, guys.
I like putting lists and games and putting them in order.
It's very...
I'm playing with blocks here.
There's like a weird like human desire to like bring order to chaos, you know.
Like when you when you do something that's structured, it feels good.
You're just like, yes, I've taken this malformed chaotic mess and presented it
in some sort of like structured way.
I've applied human intellect to the chaos that is natural life and it feels good.
It's just an illusion.
It's totally an illusion.
You're just fooling yourself.
Sure, but all the pixels on screen are also illusions, Ben.
No, no, those are the only thing that's real.
The entire state of society is an illusion, Ben.
We're all just masking the state of nature.
We're all playing an elaborate game to prevent us from just like killing each other with clubs.
It's like I'm collecting data and arranging it in a way.
And it's kind of a video game in itself.
And it's really like it like on the face of it.
It seems like why would you ever care about such a thing?
And it's true.
Why would I?
I don't know.
Well, you know, if it makes you happy, it makes me more happy than playing any of them.
Metroid Prime is so good, though, bro.
Like I like I've got all these games and I'm like, yep, that's the list.
Look at that list.
Well, good time to go to bed.
Time to just sleep my days away.
Why would I boot anything up and be entertained?
It just doesn't make any sense.
I agree.
I unironically agree.
I hate the idea of being entertained.
When I look at when I look at Cyberpunk 2077, what I see is like,
I don't I don't understand.
I don't understand the appeal of something like that at all,
because it looks it just looks like I see this is a this is a contraption that has been
that has been constructed to distract me for like, you know, 60 or 100 hours.
Yeah, it's that.
Hey, guys, the new day care just dropped.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's kind of how I feel about it.
I don't want to be distracted.
I need my fucking wits about me.
That's like fucking danger.
I know.
Yes, I agree.
I know that that's a stupid thing to say.
And yet I say it on ironic.
Ben, Ben, you're an artist.
Your whole life is dedicated to.
I hate art, Tom.
I fucking hate art.
I hate art.
I don't believe in it.
It's a fucking ruse.
It's a scam.
I kind of agree.
I've been thinking a lot about like the fact that like I think back.
I've been grappling a lot thinking about just video games in general,
because I've been spending so much time with them for the last like two months
and how much time they take away from me.
And I'm like, yeah, do I want to make video games and subject other people to this time sink?
Like am I participating in like a negative thing?
But then it's like it's all it's not none of it's compulsory.
People choose to spend their lives this way.
And not everybody has the desire or the capacity to make things.
Some people just want to be entertained.
And I say, I say, I say all this like I'm above it all or whatever.
But of course, no, this is just things that I don't like.
And then you're in the trenches with everybody else.
And that's why you relate to it so strongly.
Because like you're personally affected by it.
It's just there's some other some other thing that is the thing that I choose to
be distracted by like Dwarf Fortress or whatever.
It's just some some different thing.
We all have our voices.
No better.
Right now my my thoughts are all about like completing art.
Like I've got all these games in my steam library that I've never even fucking opened.
And to me playing them is not like interesting because I I mean maybe something would be good.
But like the idea of completing the list is a more interesting and fun game
than like playing the games.
So I feel compelled to play them just so I can tick them off, which is really like
it's like Skinner Box like that I built for myself.
But I kind of like it.
You're gamifying your collection of games essentially.
Yeah.
It's like a metagame.
Like it's like at a like first glance it seems like I'm adding to like distraction in my life.
But really I'm just sort of this is the distraction.
Otherwise I would be playing one game or another game.
And this is the game I decided to make is a game about games and gaming.
And God I hate that word so much.
I heard it in my head.
Gaming.
Such a stupid word because it's been made into a joke.
Yeah.
It's made into a joke.
Just the saying it is funny apparently.
See.
Oh man.
Did I talk about did I talk about my dwarf fort?
Oh I not recently I guess.
Did I talk about the that I started the the succession game with my with my roommates.
And I don't have a little accident.
No everything was going everything was going so good.
Everything we did a succession game is when like one person plays an in-game year
and then they pass it off to the next person and you and you take turns playing a year.
Our fort is so much gold.
There's gold everywhere.
Like all all the walls have gold in them.
There's like gold nuggets like littering the floor because everywhere we did.
We just keep finding gold gold gold gold.
But we don't have any like talented metalsmiths.
So like my whole thing has been like trying to get a bunch of metalsmiths.
Practicing making copper stuff so they can become extremely good metalsmiths.
And then they can make like really expensive gold crafts and sell them right.
Because if we just if you make crappy gold stuff and so that'd be waste of money.
You want to make good stuff out of it to maximize your return.
All right.
So that's that's what I wanted to do.
So by the time it gets to my year you know I fuck around.
Like we get attacked by a monster a giant tick or whatever shows up.
Had a very funny very funny battle.
This this forgotten beast that's a giant tick shows up.
And he is coming through the caverns and there just happens to be one dwarf stucos out in the caves
hunting like a kangaroo or something.
And this tick this giant tick beast just runs up to him and stucos leaps on the tick and
starts biting its legs and latches on with his teeth.
And then the tick breathes a cloud of freezing dust to I don't know to do to harm stucos in
some way but in the cloud of dust it like trips and falls and hits its head on the cave wall
and just splatters its own head open into pulp on the wall and just bursts its own head
with its own weight I guess.
And it just dies and stucos fucking did it.
And that was fine.
No problems.
No casualties at all.
But then one were horse I think shows up.
And our can our fortress is on a canyon.
There's a river and it's a canyon.
And there was a bridge that goes over the canyon.
And that's like a main supply line for our fortress.
And this happened to become the full moon.
I guess it's just the wrong time.
And one were horse went crazy at the full moon on the bridge and our whole military rushed it
and they fought him on the bridge and he just like laid waste to one dwarf after another.
And everyone like rushed the bridge and they all fell off into the river and died.
Like 60 dwarves just like died in the river because one were horse like got angry.
Just pummeled them all with skull crushing hooves.
What is a were horse?
Is it a horse that turns into a dog?
That would be smaller.
No, no, it's a dwarf that turns into a horse at the full moon or a horse beast.
So it like it halved our population.
It went from like 120 dwarves to like 60.
You needed to get a cowboy dwarf to bucking bronco it like right at like a tain it.
We need something.
All right, you know, things aren't things aren't looking good in in in fern relics.
That's our that's our our fort.
Okay, just wanted to update you on my dwarf situation.
Now you know, I was playing or trying out this cool game that had dwarves in it called deep rock
galactic.
I've been marathoning a lot of skill up on YouTube.
His videos on games are really fucking good.
And one of the games you recommended was this game called deep rock galactic.
It's like an indie multiplayer like four player game.
I've seen this it's it's some dwarves in space mining space rocks.
Yeah, it's like actually like pretty cool.
It's it's like all the stuff's procedurally generated and like you can destroy any part
of the map and create like your own custom tunnels and you're looking for like gold and other kind
of like precious resources while fighting off like swarms of aliens that come and attack you.
And there's like four different classes.
And it's pretty cool.
I only played a very little bit of it because there's no demo and I don't buy games without
trying them.
So I pirated it.
Sorry, indie devs.
I will buy it if I like it.
But I play a little bit of it and it runs pretty well.
It's pretty fun.
And there's a bunch of goofy drunk dwarves.
And yeah, if you if you like those multiplayer games, class based multiplayer stuff like PvE,
it seems like a great recommendation.
It's apparently like in the top 100 highest rated games on Steam of all time,
despite being like a very new game by a small team of guys.
So apparently it's pretty sick.
And it's kind of cool.
Looks kind of neat.
It's pretty fun.
I'm looking at images.
All right, I'm amenable.
I'm amenable to what I'm seeing.
I'm just saying if you had those dwarves in your fort, you probably could have killed this fucking
warhorse with ease.
Don't stucos the if stucos, the bug hunter had been there.
If he had been the first on the scene, I'm sure everything would have been different.
But instead, just our stupid ass military who doesn't know what they're doing got their first.
And of course, the slaughter that ensued was legendary.
This is why we have to redirect 90 percent of our nation's budget to defense.
Otherwise, the war horses will come and kill us all.
That's right.
If only I if I'd invest more.
Oh, the other thing about our fort is that we have no good medals.
We have no iron for making steel.
We don't even have any tin for making bronze.
All your weapons are gold.
They're fucking copper and whatever and whatever we've been able to trade for.
I've traded for some steel, but like it's there's not that much.
So, you know, it's it's our military is like they're where they're all got like
silver hammers are the best thing we can have.
Silver hammers and maces are pretty decent.
But other than that, it's like it's just not it's just not a lot of good shit.
It's very sad.
Tragic, even.
OK, I was going to talk about something else, but then I got distracted by my dwarves.
Too many dwarves.
And I and I yeah, so OK.
2016, the only games I bought in 2016 with Dark Souls 3, Pokmon Go and Pokmon Moon.
I guess I didn't buy Pokmon Go and buy Pokmon Go.
Yeah, I was.
Did you tell me if you get the new if you get the Pokmon Sword Shield?
I got Sword.
I was gifted it.
I would not have bought it of my own volition.
I had fun.
Yeah.
Yeah, I didn't get it.
It's more Pokmon.
It's like definitely not worth being the first console game.
Yeah, I feel like when it comes to like I need more Pokmon, there's plenty of
ones that from the past that I haven't played yet, such as Black and White.
I kind of want to play.
Not not.
Yeah, Platinum.
Is that the one with Giratina?
I don't know if it's not the first 150 Pokmon.
Is that Gen 4?
Yeah, it's Jen.
I think Diamond and Diamond Pearl and Platinum Platinum is the third one of that.
I like I didn't I played Pearl and Pearl was like, OK, I didn't love it.
And then and then like I didn't I sort of skipped Gen 5.
But at the time anyway.
But like people say that Platinum is like much better than Pearl and Diamond.
So I think I don't know, maybe it would be worth going back to revisit.
I think so.
I think I've heard that it's just like all of the the little
annoying frustrating things or at least some of them were like addressed in the third.
Yeah.
Yeah, I played Platinum.
I played Pearl in college and I was like, this is fine.
Yeah, I was playing Pearl at the end of high school.
And I think that's the game that disillusioned me from Pokmon.
I'm just like, yeah, it's fine, whatever.
I'm too old for this apparently, but I wasn't too old.
The game was just not good.
I skipped Gen 3 and then I got Gen 4 as like a retro like a throwback thing.
It was like a nostalgia thing because like all my friends were getting it.
And then I think I did get Black when it was new.
But I didn't like finish it.
And then of course, much, much later.
Getting sword and it was based.
Was the first game I got when it came out since Pearl.
So there was a huge gap and just me not playing any Pokmon games.
So it felt kind of fresh because I'm like, oh, you can just like hit a button to throw
Pokball without having to go into the menu.
How black?
How a revolutionary.
Black and White 2 really is the pinnacle of the series.
That seems to be the general consensus from what I understand.
Yeah, X and Y.
Everything I hear about them makes them sound bad.
Yeah, I think I got one of those and I tried to play it.
And it was just sort of like, I don't know, it's kind of cute that you can roll a blade around.
And I don't like Pokmon, so I stopped playing.
Le Mans.
It was normal to like see everything in 3D for the first time since I've seen it.
Pokmon Moon was like quite good, I felt.
Yeah, that was alright.
Like just, I don't know, like Gen 3 was like my first one.
And Gen 4 immediately, it was like, I don't care.
It's 3D, I like the sprites, whereas the sprites gone.
Yeah, you didn't think that X and Y had like the charm of like the PS2?
I felt a lot of like the PS2 charm.
I didn't play X and Y.
X and Y had like on the surface is like, oh, cute low poly 3D stuff.
And it looked nice, but the locations were just so boring.
Yeah.
I just didn't care about anything that was going on.
It was weird playing X and Y, where like the game felt for the most part,
like the locations were still designed with like a tile set of like a sprite based game.
Like they didn't take any advantage of the dynamism 3D offered,
where Sun and Moon, like the worlds felt a lot more organic and like took advantage
of like polygon graphics, which I think made it feel a lot more immersive.
With X and Y, the fucking roller blades, you use, because it's the 3DS,
they have the joystick, the, you know, analog stick.
And so you could move in an analog way around the place,
but as soon as you took them off, your character just sort of
zoomed into the nearest square and then it was grid based again.
Yeah, I just didn't like that.
That was really dumb.
Now, I didn't play X and Y and they don't look that appealing to me,
but I will say one thing I do know that is good about them is that the X and Y,
the Kalos Champion, Diantha, has an absolute banger theme, like battle theme.
It's super good.
It's super fucking good.
I never got there, so I wouldn't know.
Excellent.
I'll take your word for it though.
I think I, well, I'm not, I won't bother trying to describe how the song sounds.
It goes.
It's got, no, it's, it's got a real nice mix of sort of like ethereal like bells
and like soft parts and chimes and piano.
And then it kind of like switches between that and like a kind of like electric guitar thing.
It's so cool.
It's very.
Do you like kind of miss Game Boys?
I kind of do.
No.
Um, why?
Um, because like the Switch isn't a Game Boy.
It's like really expensive and like the games are designed to be like big games.
The Game Boy was pretty expensive when it first came out.
Compared to consoles though, it wasn't like the games were half the price.
The console was like a half to a third of the price.
The games were shorter and simpler.
It felt like there was like a platform for like these simple games.
You could just kind of like take with you anywhere.
Nowadays that that stuff is like indie games on Steam rather than handheld.
I'm not going to like fucking bring my desktop around with me to just like
dig around and play a simple game when I have like a couple minutes.
Or mobile games, I guess.
And mobile is like way too monetized and like the free to play model.
Like, I don't know, there was like a weird niche that the Game Boy had
that I didn't realize I liked until it was gone because I took it for granted and it kind of stinks.
Yeah, I will say if you can get like GBA emulation on your mobile phone, it is very fun.
I played all of Fire Emblem 7, the first English translated one,
a few months ago on my phone.
It was just like, it's about the same size as the Game Boy Advance SP.
It's just felt like I was playing it all over again.
It was great.
Yeah, Fire Emblem, the first Fire Emblem on GBA.
Like you're tucked up in bed, everybody has their phone in bed because they look at
fucking YouTube videos and tweets like idiots like me.
Not me.
And so it was such a natural like, oh, instead of looking at Twitter or looking at YouTube videos
that I've seen already, I'll play a video game that I played already and that's much better.
I don't know, is Fire Emblem good?
Yeah, it's fun.
Yeah, Fire Emblem 7 is like classic, classic, classic good game.
The sequel, The Sacred Stones was very good as well.
And then in three, and they sort of, with the advent of three-dimensional polygonal
graphical shit, it sucked and it looked bad because the sprites were so...
Agreed, reject modernity.
The sprites were just so beautiful and so well animated and then they came onto the GameCube
with one and they had no flair at all.
They were just like stick figures going up and swinging a sword in a very normal way.
It sucked.
It's true, the catharsis of those animations in Fire Emblem were like really good.
I will never ever forgive Sakurai for putting all of the Fire Emblem characters in Smash,
except the only good games were Snubbed, the only ones.
Why is Linda?
7 and 8.
I guess it's tired and I probably don't need to say that there's too many Fire Emblems in
Smash and they all look the fucking same and I hate them.
Yeah, I hate them as well.
They're just bad picks.
They're just picks based on whatever is currently there.
I was thinking the other day, you know what would be better?
Is if there were just one or two Fire Emblem characters and you could pick a different,
just like each new Smash game could have just a new Fire Emblem that would be the same as the
last one, but it would look different and it would be just some other girl with a sword
who plays identical to the last one, but just has a different name.
That's just the annoying thing is that Fire Emblem has such a variety of types of fighters
and they always choose whoever is the protagonist or the main character,
which is a similar sword-wielding lord usually and there's all of these like
incredible diverse characters they could take from any of the games,
but they always take the main character.
There should be one character named Fire Emblem and you can choose to be like an Axe
Man or a Sword Man or a Magic Man and their moves that would change.
Like Pokemon Trainer?
Yeah, that's what it should be.
There should be one character named Fire Emblem.
That would be cool.
I would like, if I had the power, I would model like three-dimensional versions of
all the Fire Emblem classes as they appear in sprite form and then I could make like Smash,
just Fire Emblem Smash though.
And it would be actually good and people would be like, ah, yes.
We already have a Fire Emblem Smash, it's called Smash.
It's true.
LaMalle.
It's been colonized.
But now they have Sephiroth, so like all is forgiven.
Sephiroth, he's pretty good.
Sephiroth looks pretty cool.
It's pretty, you know, as these things go.
Did you see?
He's no Steve.
Did you see Sephiroth's little Let's Play video where he plays as Sephiroth and shows us how he plays?
Yep, yep.
That was fun.
He does one for every new character, right?
Yeah, it just sort of, it's sort of cute.
I don't know, something about the way he was doing that.
So I just felt like he was Let's Playing.
He's a good man.
There's the part in it where he's like, he's talking about like frames.
And then he's like, wait a minute, I don't care about this.
I'll leave that to the tournament players.
Let me just say, it feels fun to do this.
Yeah, it's like he clearly like does care a little bit.
And he's like, wait, Smash is not a competitive game, haha.
Yeah.
I mean, it's funny because if you watch his play through when he talks about Terry,
it's obvious that he's like a hardcore fighting game guy.
He knows all this shit about King of Fighters and Fatal Fury and Street Fighter and all this
shit.
And he's talking about all the different really obscure movesets and stuff that he integrated
in all the references to all these obscure SNK games.
He grew up in the arcades.
He's clearly like a hardcore fighting game community guy.
But he was tasked to make a fighting game, or a party game.
And that was the initial idea.
And it's just like that DNA is like in him, but like he has to play it like closer to
the chest.
And it's just like pretty funny how like this party game was taken and became like treated
communally as the genre that he clearly has a lot of love for, but wasn't setting out to make.
Yeah, it's nice to see that he seems to have more control over this current game than he
did previously.
And he's happy about it.
Yeah.
There's Minecraft in it now.
There's Steve in it.
That's all you need.
That's so cool.
There's Minecraft in Super Smash Bros.
It's pretty good.
But you know what?
I'm not going to play it because I actually don't like playing Smash Bros.
No, neither do I.
I just like looking at it.
I kind of like that it exists, but I'm not going to play it.
And I actually don't care at all.
I'm like, I get much more enjoyment watching like Maximilian Dude react to like New
Fighters added to Smash than I do playing the game.
You know, like if you watch his reaction when like Cloud was announced, it's like the most
entertaining good feel thing of all time.
Watching this grown man flip his shit for a character in a video game.
What did he do about Sephiroth?
He also flipped shit, but he was like three other people.
So they were all just like geeking out.
I'm like, I don't know who any of these guys are.
Man, I thought Sephiroth was so cool when I was in like eighth grade.
And you still do.
And I still do.
No, I wanted to, I, when I, I grew my hair out really long and I think part of my motivation
for doing that was that I thought Sephiroth looked really cool with long hair and I wanted
to look like that.
Same with Zero from Mega Man X.
Those were my two like long hair goals at the time.
Were you going to dye it gray or silver?
I thought about it.
I never like really, occasionally I wondered like, what if I dyed it gray?
Little did he know Ben's life would be so stressful.
He'd start growing gray naturally.
Yeah, yeah, like all I had to do was wait.
I can, I can see Ben like young Ben with long dyed gray hair and a leather trench coat.
It's really funny.
Ben dressed up like Sephiroth with like the long hair and then Nate with his vampire
Hunter D hat.
Just like the ultimate, the ultimate, pure weaponized cream.
Embrace tradition, guys.
You know what, you know what, I was, I was, I was cleaning my room the other day.
I was cleaning my room.
This is, this is going to sound really stupid.
But I guess I might as well say it because where else am I going to say stupid shit other
than on the procrastinators podcast?
I've seen your Twitter.
I was cleaning.
Oh, no, I only, no, fuck you.
I see smart things on Twitter.
I'm the only smart one there.
God, I don't want to talk about that.
I don't want to talk about Twitter.
Fuck you.
The, the, I was cleaning my room and I found behind some shit on my dresser.
I found the like makeup stuff from, from Radcon.
I found like, you know, the eyeliner and the, and the lipstick and stuff.
And I was just thinking like, and I, and I just remind him is like, yeah, uh, uh,
uh, fucking the, the goth thing, the whole like, the goth, like eyeliner, E-boy thing,
you know, it's kind of cringe, but I, you know, deep down, deep down, I think it's kind of cool.
And, uh, maybe I should pull a Hussie.
Maybe I should pull, like, I think Hussie, Hussie just became a clown.
Like, you know, like he always wanted to.
You became a chocolate.
Yeah.
Maybe I should just become a goth E-boy again.
Embrace, embrace tradition, reject modernity.
I was thinking about similar things because I have some makeup now and I haven't tried it yet.
I've been thinking, ah, God, dang it.
I want to, I kind of want to be like an emo scene goth punk girl.
What better time than now to experiment?
You're not going anywhere.
You know, you don't really risk anything other than the people immediately around you
seeing your, your awkward, like figuring it out phase.
And then you can emerge from the pandemic, like a fucking God of aesthetic.
It's true.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, shit, we're most of the way through it now.
Exactly.
Now's the time before the window of opportunity passes you by.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um, I don't know.
But, uh, but then I think about like, uh, man, look at myself in the mirror and I'm like,
oh, but I look like that.
Oh, but, but this is my face.
Like if, if a person that looked like this tried to do, tried to try to like look cool
in any way, that would just be like such a mismatch and it would be so cringe.
You got to just commit to it so hardcore.
It turns around and becomes based again.
I think so.
Yeah, I think, I think there's, that's true.
If possibly you can do it, anybody can.
I don't know.
Um, I mean, I don't want to be try hard, right?
No, you have to try hard.
It's, it's, it's now, it's now, it, I feel like it's, it's cringe to be what, I mean,
kind of always has been cringe to worry about what other people think too much,
but it's also cringe to not go hard enough.
Well, that's the whole thing is like, you can,
there are people who can pull things off naturally and like good for them.
And then there's like the people who are tryharding,
trying to like fit into something they're not supposed to be.
But then like, if you try hard so much, you become like so fucking hardcore,
like committed to the cause, it becomes cool.
Yeah, even if you don't like really get there,
the fact that you're trying is like, it's kind of cool.
And I wouldn't sell yourself short.
I don't, I wouldn't like throw the entire idea under the bus,
just cause you're uncomfortable with how your face looks.
I'm sure it's not nearly as bad as you're making it out to be in your own mind.
I mean, I think there are ways to try hard that are more embarrassing
and there are ways to try hard that are less embarrassing.
Sure.
The most embarrassing thing is caring about people thinking you're try hard
and reducing your own happiness because of that.
So go go ham, my dude.
Okay, well, I guess I will, whatever that means.
I mean, at the end of the day, Ben,
you're already immortalized on YouTube forever and videos that are out and more to come.
So what's the worst that could happen?
I guess next next next lecture, I should just do it in like full like goth.
I agree.
Wait.
I found, I found a bunch of like rings that I used to wear for like a little period there
when I was maybe like 23 or something.
I was like accessorizing, I was wearing like a bunch of like rings
and I had a bunch of like fake like piercings that I would wear on my ears.
And I found the box in my closet that I had all that stuff in.
And I was like, that was so lame, but also that was so cool.
Maybe it was kind of a little bit cool.
I don't understand why I never like
try to experiment with my aesthetic in real life more
because like I'm always interested in like character creators and video games and stuff
and like aesthetic, something that interests me.
But for some reason, like I never considered myself being a worthwhile canvas.
And that seems like such a missed opportunity.
I know what you mean.
I know the feeling.
It's it's the what is it, the expectation of like men to be like normal and not maybe
not really that flashy and to be flashy is to be homosexual.
Well, I am pretty gay.
So I feel like that barrier has been crossed at this point.
Well, shit.
Well, like I don't want to be gay.
Oh, well, that's where I don't have to be fucked up.
That like deeply ingrained toxic masculinity.
There it is.
It's like you got to you got to dress like everyone else.
Otherwise you're not.
I mean, I mean, like in in high school, I was like, I was very I did like,
I was I was pretty try hard.
Like I did.
I had I had like coats and stuff.
Right.
I have like I have like not like a trench coat, but I had like like leather coats
that I thought were like cool and weird and that were like sort of like my like signature
pieces and stuff.
And I was like, oh, man.
Yeah, I have this coat like nobody else has coats like this.
Nobody else has like a I don't know, you know, has like hair as long as mine or whatever,
a fucking hat like this or whatever, you know, whatever the fuck.
I did a lot of that.
And then but it was cringe.
It was definitely cringe.
No, I like I didn't have a space like that.
And I wish I did.
Yeah, same.
No, it's it's a I don't know.
It's such an action is cooler than inaction.
Almost it constantly.
I think I think it's true.
It's not a good it's not a good thing to be like really like trying to have like quirky
affectations.
Well, I don't I feel like even if that in and of itself is like cringe and awkward.
That's like a necessary stumbling block on the path to finding your own aesthetic and
being comfortable with like your self presentation.
Yeah, you know, what I really mean is just like it's it's based in as like compared to
being afraid of people looking at me weird and and not doing anything with myself at all.
Right.
The the the stages may be cringe, but the process and the results that come from it is based.
I mean, I'm I'm not I'm not afraid to like look weird at all.
I'm just I don't know.
I feel like I'd be so much more willing to experiment if it was like like in a video game
where like you could just like pick a piece of gear change and then change back.
Like if you want to like experiment with like I'm going to change my hairstyle,
you got to like commit for like two months to that until it like grows back out,
even if it looks bad. Where's like, you know, in a video game, it's like score back to option
four, option three did not work, you know. Well, it's because that's low effort.
It is. Right. It is because in real life, if you have like a very particular look,
it means that you went about achieving it and it probably took some doing.
This is why we all need to be VTubers and like abandon our physical bodies.
Then then our changes are that easy.
It means it means that you were committed to it and you really you pursued it and you
thought it was a good idea. So if you like look a certain way in real life and it's like,
oh really, that's what he decided to go with. Like, oh boy.
But it's just part of the learning process, like in real life, too. It's just like you just
well, I know. Just tried. Sure.
So I think we all should give our fellow man a bit more benefit of the note.
Sure. But that's not fun. I'd rather make fun of everyone on the internet because I'm a
jackass. I mean, I'll fucking judge someone if they look stupid.
Well, of course. With the thing about like it being cringed to pretend to be quirky,
do you feel like it's like it would be cooler if you just naturally felt like doing this thing
instead of trying to do it? Is there a difference?
I don't think so.
There's kind of a difference. Like, I remember on the Ricky Gervais show, there was one
Stephen Merchant made like a joke or he was talking about, they got like a male.
They got like a piece of male from someone who they thought was like a big fucking dweeb.
And they decided that this guy was like a big nerd who thinks he's cool. And he described him as
like, oh, he's the kid. He's the kid in school who he only wears bowling shoes, right? Because
it's like quirky. And like doing that for no reason, like just to do it because nobody else
does it is like stupid. Doing it, if he if he just like liked bowling shoes, that would be
something else. Sure. I think that's a different thing than what we've been talking about, though.
If you're if you're experimenting with an aesthetic simply because you want to
differentiate yourself from people around you, that seems like an empty pursuit. But if you're
just trying to find your own self expression, you're doing it specifically for your own
satisfaction and you're weighing that against how you'll be perceived, that's a completely different
thing. Yeah. Yeah, sure. I mean, I don't think I think it's I think aesthetics are fine. I don't
know. I don't know how I feel. I'm not sure. I'm not sure. I mean, maybe if I had like more
places to go, maybe if I ever like went out ever, maybe then I would put more thought I never have
any cause to consider like how will I look? How will I present myself? It's just such a it's
it's depressing, actually. I wish I wish there were more opportunities for me to even think
about such a thing. And then maybe I would experiment with it more LeMau.
What do you think about that? I mean, I feel similarly I've had like makeup nearby, like I've
been thinking mascara, like eyeliner, like I don't know how this was stuff works. I gotta look at
YouTube videos, and I gotta try it out and fail a bunch of times. I just have no reason to because
you know, I don't need to look good for camera. And I don't need to go outside. So like,
what am I going to do? Here's here's what I think. Here's what I think. I think
here's why I'd be a little uncomfortable with something like something that I think is
a look that I think is cool, like, um, like like a long hair or like eyeliner or something. I think
something like that. This is just my opinion. I think something like that looks good. It's like
kind of like a feminine detail or a feminine affect. I think it looks the best on like someone who is
very traditionally masculine. And it's like, to the point that like it's sort of like a deliberate
contrast. I think that's interesting and looks good. I think that I am too shlubby looking.
I think that I'm like too normal of a guy. I'm not like, if I think you'd need, I don't know,
I think to pull off a look like that, you need like to be tall or like have a strong jaw or
something. And I don't, I'm just normal. Uh, I don't know. When I imagine myself doing something
like that, I think it's like, that's weird. It's cringe. Hmm.
I don't know. I wonder how much of that is like internal versus external, like just kind of like
conditions you've put upon your own kind of, uh, uh, expectations of what that should be versus
like objectively what it actually is. Well, I guess I don't, I don't know. I mean, I have the same
issues with myself because I always feel like, you know, I don't look properly for aesthetics I'd
like to do. And then on top of that, it's just like, I also don't feel like putting in the time,
effort or money to figuring it out. But then on the other hand, it's like, would
addressing how I look and like make myself more aesthetically in line with how I would like to
be or finding out what that even is, would that help just make me feel better in general?
You know, like such a huge part of like the self that I've never explored. And like,
perhaps that would help just make myself feel better if I actively took a step and like
presenting myself as I would like to. I don't know. I mean, it's something that's been such a
non part of my life. Like I've just, I've had like all the same clothes since high school where
it's just like a T-shirt and jeans or whatever. And I just don't give a fuck. And I don't know if
that's was a mistake. I mean, I think there's probably like a, like a self reinforcing loop
there wherein like, if you put more thought into your appearance and then, and then, you know, you
have, and then you actually like go out in situations where like presentation is matters,
then that like act of going out and like being presented, like presenting yourself to others
will probably make you then consider your appearance even more so, right? And these things
will reinforce one another, right? Yeah, I would assume so. Yeah. Same with like working out,
honestly. Same with like, when I was, when I was like going out more, seeing more people,
I was more, like when I was more social, I think I had more of like a drive to like
work out and be active and like, you know, keep myself from getting fat and turning into a fucking
piece of shit, right? I mean, I was like in the best shape I've been in a while,
like by rad con for, and then COVID happened and I definitely let myself go.
Yeah, same. Yeah, same. It was all downhill from there. I'm desperately trying to like recover,
like the last couple of weeks I've been like really strict on diet again. I'm like, no, I have to,
I have to get it back. I feel like completely, I haven't gained like that much weight, but like,
I have like, I'm off keto and I'm just like, ah, fuck it. I gained a significant amount of weight,
especially in the last like two months, just like, no, I can't do this anymore.
I gained some, I gained a bit in like the first, the first bit of quarantine, and I've basically
just kind of been stable there for a while. Yeah. Yeah. Pretty lame.
Part of my personal aesthetic is not being fat. Can't have that must destroy.
Yeah. Yeah. I should, I should, I should get back on keto, but I just bought some loaves of bread.
Gross. I just got on. I literally threw out all the food I had.
I just was like, you know what? Sacrificing on the altar of like being a keto boy again.
I just dumped it all, dumped all the bread, all the bagels, all the dumps should I had bought
that was cheap. And I'm like, nope, we're getting, we're getting back hardcore on the bandwagon.
You know, that's a good way to like mentally reinforce that like, no, we're taking this
seriously now. And to show how serious I am about it, I'm going to like, you know,
basically throw out some money, right? Basically spend money by tossing all this food that I
shouldn't have bought. Yeah. It's like back when I used to smoke, sometimes when I would try to not
smoke anymore, it would be like, it would be a little more effective if I didn't just like
finish a pack and then not buy another, but for me to say like, no, no more and like throw out
like, you know, the half a pack or whatever I have left. Right. That means the decision starts
right there, not when it's more convenient. Yes. Yes, exactly. It was a deliberate change,
not just, oh, well, I guess, I guess it's done. I've quit, I've quit smoking though,
like that's pretty good. That's like, you know, for all Coronavirus, they say it's
bad for your lungs, but for me, it's been great. Pretty based, pretty based.
Do you still vape? I haven't heard you vaping in a while.
I have, no, I just haven't done it. Oh my God. That's like your main character trait. I don't
even know who you are anymore. I don't have any stuff. I mean, I guess I would like,
I don't think vaping is that bad or anything. I just because they like along now at this point,
it's been a long time since they stopped them. They wouldn't ship a vape shit to Massachusetts
because it got like restricted or something. I think it is still technically restricted. I don't
know. I haven't tried to buy any. Yeah, they wouldn't ship it to me online and it's so getting my
hands on it became a hassle. So I just stopped getting it and it's been a long time since I've
had any and that's fine. Lamal. Well, you're probably saving money. There's nothing else.
Yeah. I mean, vaping is cheaper than smoking, which thank God, which was one of the,
which was one of the, one of the reasons why I switched to vaping in the first place
is because like, hmm, you know, I can actually, if I'm smart about it, I can, if I, if I vape
instead of smoke, I can actually spend less on it. But yeah, I mean, vaping does cost
something. So, you know, nothing is cheaper than either. So yeah, very good, very, very clever,
clever allocation of resources on my part. I congratulate myself.
You know, speaking of lighting a little bit of paper on fire with leaves in them,
I feel like I thought recently about how I think I might be like a,
like a minor pyromaniac. Like a little bit of a, like I just, I'm a little bit too excited
to burn things to get rid of them instead of throwing them away. Because there's like,
I was clearing out stuff and there's a piece of furniture that's like, we don't need this,
it's taken up space. We'll put it outside for now and think about what to do with it later.
And I was like, wouldn't it be cool if we just burn this? And everyone was like, uh, I mean,
it's still functional. I was like, yeah, but like, I don't know, I just thought we could like burn it.
And I realized then I was a little bit too eager. And it was funny. I just love making fires and
looking at them. It's all that dark souls. You just want to light that bonfire really bad.
I do. I mean, fire is cool enough, I guess.
It's, it's, it's kind of like a thing, like a stoked about it. Like you go out to, like some
people, they go out to a party and they like dance or something. I go out to like a bonfire and I
look at the fire all night and I'm like, well, that was fun. Go to bed. I mean, sure. Fire is
I can watch a fire for a while. It's like, it's the same though. It's pretty much the same. Fire
is much more entertaining when you're throwing things into it and watching that thing get destroyed.
Yeah. When I'm in charge of like keeping it fed or like half in charge, it's just so like,
yeah, we got, we got all this scrap wood and we're not going to use it for anything.
We're going to not going to build anything out of it and it's a nice night to do a fire. So let's
burn some stuff. It's just like, yeah, put stuff on there. We usually after Christmas, we get the
Christmas tree because all of the pine needles on those things have like a lot of oil in them.
So they burn really, really hot for a very short time. It's kind of like,
so we chop that up and we have like a Christmas, like end of Christmas bonfire, which is cool.
I just love fire, guys. Fire is pretty dope.
That's fine. Nah, it's all right, I guess. What about if it's a government building, Ben?
Well, no, you fucking moron. Some buildings are good, actually. Not all buildings.
What? Which one? Hashtag not all buildings?
All buildings matter. Oh, yeah. Yeah. If it's cops or a bank, maybe, I guess.
I don't know. So the bad ones, yeah. But if you burn the bank, all your money goes up in smoke?
You know what? I hadn't thought. I don't want to think about it. It doesn't matter.
I just hope fire destroys whatever is the best thing for fire to destroy.
That's why I said all these buildings on fire, just on the off chance that one of them did that.
Fire is a tool. It's neither good nor evil. It is used as the human that is as good as the human
that wields it. Life lessons with Benzane. When I think of return to monkey, I usually think of
build fire, ooke-ooke first thing. Even though monkeys didn't necessarily do that,
I guess one of them must have at some point.
Um, no. Has a monkey ever made fire? Do monkeys make fire?
I don't think, well, I'm trying to think of the technical name.
I mean, in Jungle Book, like Homo Sapien.
That's like the whole plot of Jungle Book.
Like there's a Homo Sapien Neanderthal and then Homo Sapien Sapien. I can't remember which way it goes.
The Cro-Magnon Man and the Homo erectus, my favorite.
No, I don't remember any of them either, but I know you're talking about like primitive
version of man first discovered fire. I don't know which one it was.
Yeah, you have to be a man to obtain man's red flower. That's what I learned.
I feel like it's not the first time you've mentioned that on this podcast.
Would you guys never see fucking Jungle Book?
I know exactly what you're talking about.
I know. I love Jungle Book. I feel no reason to say it.
You guys are so silent. I was like, who, who, who, who, appreciate.
I just, I just, I was happy like deja vu. I got,
because specifically remember you saying that recently.
King Louis has my name. So I, I was like, oh my God, it's me.
It wasn't that, that's where your love of fire began.
It wasn't that recently, but a while ago I did go on a thing about how I think it's so cool
that they, that he, he doesn't know what it is. So he calls it man's red flower.
I just like story telling.
I learned that whole song of by heart when I was young,
like all of the beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, all that stuff.
I watched that movie a lot as a kid, a bunch of times. And then I never thought about it.
And then as an adult, I like remember, I think I heard it again.
And only then did I appreciate that, that metaphor. I was like, hmm.
Yeah. Nice.
Bass, Disney.
And maybe the multinational corporation is pretty good.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, let's not get too ahead of ourselves.
Maybe, maybe, maybe I spoke to Zinn.
Hey, have you guys seen your movie sucks has been streaming his editing process for the Lion King
remake review for the past like 17 months?
Yeah, I've seen snips of it here and there, but I haven't sat down and watched the whole thing.
It's a lot of, it's a lot of time he's been spent editing this Lion King remake review.
I can't believe it's been so long.
I'm kind of like strangely hooked on these streams because they're so repetitive,
they're unbelievably repetitive. He says the same things over and over again.
Wait, what thing, what do you tell, what is this?
It's YMS, right? You know, your movie sucks. He's editing on a stream.
And then there's like stream clips of him editing the Lion King review,
Lion King remake. And he's like, there's so many of them at this point.
It's just like such a like, probably like, I don't know, 14 hours of like content of watching him
edit and talk about how the Lion King remake sucks before he's made the actual review,
which is looking to be more than two hours long itself.
What a bad man.
He's such a content machine.
Indeed.
I just sort of...
Human content machine, Adam. What's his name?
Adam Marshall.
Adam plays. That's his full name.
That's what I was going to say. That's what I was going to say.
Adam Johnson.
But I went with the Star Wars reference instead.
Like it.
I hate streams.
That's what the people want. They want streams.
I love streams.
I guess they do.
No, I hate them.
I hate them for, I literally, I feel the same way about them that I feel about video games,
which is that they just waste your time.
But like more so.
It's not even, it's not even like crafted content that they're wasting your time with.
It's not even like a deliberate experience.
It's so efficient.
It's just like some, it's just like some accidental bullshit.
Not every streamer is as good as others, but I love German.
German 985 because he's like on the ball witty so often that there's usually like funny things
happening every minute or something.
I mean, when I was like, when I was into, when I was into Destiny or then when I was into Vosh,
like I never watched them live.
Oh yeah, of course.
Because like, why would you do that?
Like they'll, they'll, they'll put the best stuff on their fucking channel as clips.
Just watch that.
I think it's people who just want to participate.
It's the participation aspect, being able to be part of the chat and contribute to it and like
being there when things happen live, which personally does not intrigue me at all.
But I can understand why people would want to be part of something.
I definitely have that feeling with, with German.
Like the reason I watched the Game Awards was because German was streaming it and it was just fun.
Like hearing his like funny commentary over the being sporing stuff that didn't matter.
Obviously, like the answer, obviously the solution here is like, like with everything,
do it in moderation and it's fun, right?
So, you know, don't think you're smart for telling me that answer.
I already know, but it seems like, like to be being like the kind of guy or like
being someone who watches live streams regularly just feels like a job.
Just feels like a job you don't get paid for.
Well, if you're having a good time, I guess it's not a job.
I guess.
Some nights I'm just like, I could go into a discord call just to hang out with a few people
or I could watch a German stream and it feels the same.
And I just, I just need to wind down and just listen to someone.
I think I don't usually stay for the entire thing because it goes on for like five hours usually.
I think the problem is we all like fancy ourselves content creators, you know.
And so every time we do something that isn't working, it's always like a calculation.
Like I could be spending this time being productive.
We're like 99% of people don't have that problem.
Like as soon as they're done with their job, their time is there to do whatever they see fit
because they have no autistic inclinations like we do to have to like do something
greater with their lives and bless them, bless them for not being cursed like we are.
I mean, I feel like I'm less and less like a content creator mentally due to me not making
content for a long time.
The last two months playing games, watching streams and like sitting around and doing things.
It's like I'm a little sad about some parts because like, oh no, I'm not, I'm suck.
But part of it has just been like, I feel more like a consumer or an audience member of things
rather than someone who could potentially make an analysis video of whatever I'm watching
or playing.
Like that stuff doesn't enter my mind as much anymore, which is, it feels good.
I have again become that person you described, Tom, who must be creating at all times or
they're wasting their time and they're a loser.
I mean, I'm always like that.
I like, I've been like trying to come to terms with the fact that like I enjoy playing video games
and like shouldn't feel bad about it because like I like for decades, every time I watch a
movie or play a video game for more than an hour, like I'm just wracked with guilt and
it's been this way forever and it's so bad.
Tom, you deserve to exist regardless of what happens.
No, same for you.
You're not paying for yourself.
You're not, no, you got to pay your own way.
Well, you're not contributing to the academy.
Ben, you're valid.
Okay, fuck up.
No, I mean, for the last, listen, you said two months you haven't been on the ball.
Well, me either.
You know, I put out fucking, I put out that their Slime and Punishment video in like August
and then I spent a long time doing like fulfillment stuff on my, on those two kick
starters, which is something.
But other than that, I have gotten very little done and I feel pretty bad about it.
But, but I also feel liberated.
I feel a little bit liberated by low expectations, right?
Because I feel like at this point, it's been so long since I really did anything.
Since I really made anything and put it out there that was like worth a fucking a damn
at all that like anyone who's still following me probably has their expectations are rock bottom.
And they're, well, wait, that sounds, that's not exactly what I mean.
It's not not for like quality, but like they're not expecting anything anytime.
They're patient, right?
They're patient, which means that like, okay, I have, I have embarked.
I have embarked upon a new construction.
I have embarked upon a new project.
And it, and the thing about that is that they've been here this long.
It's, it's been this long since I made a new thing.
Like if it can take me however, however long it takes me, it's fine.
I don't have to worry about like, oh, I have to get it done by the end of the month.
If it take, it's going to take me however long it takes me.
And if it takes me two months, then so be it.
Like it's, it's not going to be, it's not going to be a disaster,
any more of a disaster than the gap since my last thing has already been, which is exciting.
I have been, I've been, I've been like trying to work 24 hours a day.
And I can't, guess what?
Shocker, I can't do it.
I'm in a terrible brain fog and I can't sleep.
And I can't focus on anything.
And my eyes hurt and I woke up, I keep waking up at weird hours
and trying to like get back into it and then just staring at my screen.
And it's like, oh, I can't, I can't remember what I was doing.
So, you know, it's going good is what I'm saying.
Excellent.
Things are, things are, things are according, proceeding according to plan.
I mean, I felt like entirely the same with regards to last thing I did was in August
and then nothing and fuck.
Last few days before today, I was feeling really bad and I just stopped feeling bad.
I guess it's just one of those chemical things.
It's just the depression juice ran out and I guess I'm fine.
But like, I don't know, it's, it's okay to just not do anything, isn't it?
Yep, it is.
I do like the idea that, you know, knowing that I still want to do it, it'll happen eventually.
And I don't know, there's just earlier in the year, like at the very beginning of the year,
in fact, I was like, this is going to be the year where I do a fuck ton of things
and I'm super productive and I become a real mangaka and I didn't do that.
I did a lot of ghosts extremely fast in one month or two months, I think.
That was so much for one month.
You really did crank that out.
And then like, I think it was immediately then it was Redcon 4
and then COVID and that was fucked.
But then I sort of picked myself up near August and I was like, let's do
another thing, let's do the Clarissa Gunsmoke and the Bandit King
comic for the contest.
And I did another month of extreme intense work and that's like two out of, or two and a half out of
12 months of actual like real work and the rest was just being deceased.
And on the whole, it's like, it's not terrible because I did do stuff and it's,
but it's not good because so much of the year was, I don't know,
riddled with anxiety and terrible other stuff.
And I guess transitioning was a big part of my focus.
Yeah, I definitely feel like I did get some things done this year,
but I think I thought I would get more.
There were things I thought I would have done by now that I didn't.
Shocker, COVID was not a great motivator.
No, then I don't know about you guys, but as soon as it starts snowing,
I'm done.
Like I can't, I can't handle winter at all.
So now that it's snowing, I'm just like, that doesn't really affect me.
Oh God, I can't really have much.
I'm surprised.
No, I can't.
That's that.
I don't care about that.
That's the reason like the last like two months.
Why?
I don't know.
I just hate the cold.
I hate the cold.
I hate the snow.
I do hate the cold.
I always forget how annoying the cold is.
Okay, the word what's really bugging me is that I have a space heater in my room,
which is fine.
But like when it's on, it's too hot.
And when it's off, it's too cold.
Like I have to like turn it on and off every like half hour.
You never worry about air air conditioning.
Air conditioning gets you exactly where you need to be,
but like you can never balance the heat when it's too cold.
It's always uncomfortable one way or the other.
Yeah.
Fuck the snow.
I hate having to dig out my fucking car,
which you don't have to deal with obviously,
but like you need to go somewhere.
Well, I got to fucking dig out my goddamn car.
It's buried in fucking snow and I have a broken back,
which makes it even harder.
And it's just like, yeah, that's a fucking shit show.
Where are you?
I mean, do you have to leave the house for stuff?
I mean, like going grocery shopping and shit.
I don't have to.
I don't go a lot of places, but it's just like,
I can't I can't use my EBT with fucking Instacart.
So if I want to like use my fake money,
I got to like dig the car out and get going.
Just just just say just save the just save the EBT.
You can use it later.
It doesn't expire.
Yeah, I suppose.
But then I have to spend I have to spend real money,
which is very valuable.
What?
Yeah.
Money is valuable.
What the fuck?
So I've been told.
I feel like we've all been tricked into thinking that,
but in the current paradigm, yes, it is very important.
What a nightmare.
Well, if you say so, if you say so.
No, I never leave my house.
I've been Instacarting.
It's it's based.
The only cool thing is when I do get Instacart
and I come out like with with my cane,
their demeanor goes from my hate serving,
like obnoxious white people to like,
oh my god, can I help you bring these in?
And I'm just like, I never,
I never meet the deliverer at the door.
I don't want to.
I don't want them to look at me.
I want to just I can just I'll just go down
and find the shit on my doorstep later.
Please start doing their makeup stuff.
That's going to be your fucking like litmus test
for how good they're doing.
Just answer the door and see how it goes.
I don't want to have to say like,
oh, yeah, yeah, just leave it right there.
Oh, no, you don't have to let help me take it in.
No, I'll get it.
No, thank you very much.
Yeah, you know, I have a good day.
I don't want to do that.
Like just just fucking put it on my step.
Just leave it there.
I'll take care of it.
And and I and and I don't make me tell you that either.
Just do it. Thanks.
All right.
You can leave a note for them to do that, right?
I mean, that's just what they do by default.
They do it now.
Not that they're not used to.
Well, I mean, before COVID, like they were usually like,
like you'd answer the door and shit.
But now it's maybe you know, maybe it has changed
because they would like.
Yeah, maybe it has changed.
I mean, I just eventually I mean,
I just stopped answering the door.
Like they ring the doorbell.
I just don't answer until like 15 minutes have gone by
and I am confident that they're gone.
I don't need to have a conversation with them.
It's not productive.
So fuck it.
It's fucking Instacart.
I tip them and I tip them and that's good enough.
That's the only conversation they need.
Yeah.
What more do they want?
I don't.
Frankly, they probably appreciate it.
Like what do they need from me?
Nothing.
That's true.
Just your money.
I don't do that many favors by making small talk with them either.
No, who gives a shit?
I've recently just now I'm on Twitter and apparently Andrew Hussie is
he's got a trailer for a thing that is new and is not homestuck.
No.
It's it's apparently a visual novel that is coming soon.
The trailer is like four minutes and 40 seconds long.
You can't milk Homestuck anymore.
We're all stuck at home now.
Yeah.
It looks like the same sort of art style because it's written and drawn.
Entirely by Andrew Hussie.
So that's like good.
Oh, really?
Yes.
That's exciting.
Is it clown related?
I think it has a clown guy in it.
Okay.
Is this like an onboarding part?
Can I finally get on board with it as an Andrew Hussie project?
This card theme seems to relate to his most recent juggler photo shoot.
It would be cool and not like unlike him for that Instagram thing to be like
clues to whatever this is.
I think it's definitely related at least thematically.
Oh my god.
This is I'm it's it's it's Hussie art.
This is Hussie art.
You can tell.
Yeah.
This is a real deal.
It's none of this fucking bullshit.
He's drawing and writing a visual novel and I am excited.
I want to see the next thing the man has made.
A chance.
It's been so long.
Oh my god.
I didn't know.
I didn't realize I would be excited for the next Hussie thing.
But I am.
This is great.
I'm just fucking stoked.
That's a retweet for me.
Yeah.
You know what?
Fuck it, me too.
No, actually, I'm just kidding.
Can't let people on that.
I'm excited about something that's so off brand.
I mean, I've always said that like all of the stuff about Homestuck
being like half written sort of by Andrew Hussie and mostly written and made by other people
and it just doesn't feel the same was annoying.
And I wish he would just make a new thing.
And now this is a new thing.
So I can't help but be excited.
I mean, I wonder.
Yeah, it's like, I guess maybe he's just been doing this instead of while the other guys
like deal with Homestuck too, which like, yeah, makes sense.
I mean, I'm glad he's just he's not just not doing anything.
But I guess I'm not surprised.
Like when you're Andrew Hussie, you can never stop, right?
You can you can never you can never just quit quit.
It always it always felt like a such a sad ending that the idea that someone's so prolific
and so genius that they would make one thing and then stop creating forever after that.
And it's like, no, there's got to be something more.
It's so it's so weird.
These are like, oh, God, these characters.
Yeah, they don't look that great.
They still like they look straight up bad.
But like, I'm okay with that.
It's it's it's like the way Andrew Hussie's style for this sort of like lo-fi MS paint drawing
in in act six of Homestuck sort of changed over time into something that looks like this.
I got to say, I don't like know what this is.
I guess I'm only halfway through.
I don't this guy spinning guns.
This is it looks it kind of looks really bad.
But like, I that's like good.
I like that.
I genuinely like that it looks bad.
That's because like because it's never it was never about how it looked.
Homestuck looked good sometimes.
But your first impression of it would be like, oh, this is kind of strange looking weird little
Yeah, yeah, that's the clown.
This is the clown in this trailer is the guy he's dressed up as in his profile picture and stuff.
Yeah.
Oh, this is a new YouTube channel Hussie Tube.
It's just got this one thing on it.
Yeah, I really I'm still watching this trailer.
I got I got a minute left.
I don't really know what to make of it.
Very, you know, I think it's interesting that it's it's
visually it's all Homestuck and it's no like his old art style, you know, like whistles or
one of his other like traditionally drawn.
That stuff's too hard.
Maybe I guess he's just completely embraced the Homestuck aesthetic is that's just how he does
things now, probably just because he realized that like when he draws like that, he can just
make content like so much faster, right?
He probably used to spend like days on a page of a comic and now it's like, why fucking do that?
Why fucking do that when this is what you're also you're known for and is so much easier to do?
Yeah, for real.
Well, maybe Bale, maybe Bale, Jake shouldn't get better.
Maybe you should stay as shitty as it looked before.
You say, well, it art always gets better.
It can't it can't help but do that.
That's true.
Like if you just like purposely tried to like keep it at the same level of quality,
it would still slowly get better, just not intentionally, I suppose.
Yeah, all we all you can do is be like,
like you can like you could you could be like scribbling it out like just as fast, right?
Like spending just as little time on it, you would just you would get better at
doing it fast and loose and sloppy.
You know what I mean?
I think the most distracting thing about these character designs is that the bodies
are pixelated, but the eyes are smooth and it's drawing.
Yeah, they're just less pixelated.
That's just a little are they are they alias?
I don't know if I'm watching it like in a tiny window.
So I can't tell if they're alias or if they're just higher resolution.
But either way, they are not congruent and it's very strange.
It's it's hideous.
I don't know if I'd go that far.
I think I would.
All right, all right.
I think I would drop the H word.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
OK, at 206, at two minutes and six seconds.
Yeah, obviously, like her body and hair is that like is low res and the
hair, eyes and mouth are like, yeah, God, that's disgusting.
I know that's a nightmare.
I don't understand why you would do that.
Or is it like recycling like face rigs for all these characters?
So you don't have to continually read?
I mean, I don't recognize those expressions.
So you probably just drew them again.
But I think I think it's just that he probably drew like the the scene like the
next character at 210 looks like it has the exact same kind of eyes.
I imagine he drew the scene in like a certain resolution and then he zoomed in on the character
and drew the face at a different resolution.
Yeah, he's like he's he's zoomed in.
He's zoomed in shot in here, which is interesting.
I'm just skipping through now.
He's zoomed in the shot and then drew the eyes and drew the expression at the original
resolution, which then looks higher resolution than the zoomed in pixelated old stuff, right?
Oh, God.
Oh, God, this is, you know, what this says to me, like, this is the trailer for your project.
Like, clearly, he does not give a fuck if it looks good.
Like, like, like he doesn't care and like good for him.
And thank God.
Like, that's that's clearly not the priority here.
This is not it's not like my new corporate enterprise.
It is.
Here's a funny thing I thought of when I made it.
Yeah, for sure.
Oh, that's great.
Oh, this is so good.
Well, I'm fucking I'm fucking stoked.
I'm fucking hype for this shit.
Whatever it is.
I wonder if the clown is hussy.
You know what I mean?
It might be.
Yeah.
Or maybe it's like cosplaying the clown.
Yeah, like either either hussy is cosplaying this clown character or that clown character is him
and he just depicts he just is a clown now.
Like this is what we're meant to know about him.
The bit at the end was like this does not happen in the game.
Wait, where does it say that?
With with.
It's like 313 or that sequence there.
Oh, this does not.
We're Violent J, Shaggy Tutto with Dragon Ball Z, Scouters and what's his face for the AK-47
and Kojima.
Oh, OK, so this is just some shit that's in the trailer because it's funny.
Yeah.
And it's not I am sorry.
OK, if that's true, then yeah, I think this is just hussy.
This is just clown hussy and Kojima and Shaggy Tutto open Violent J and
it's not Guy Fieri.
I don't know who this this guy in the blue blazer is.
The blue blazer.
No, no, that's that's I forget his name.
He's big rock rap guy.
I forget whatever.
Oh, I don't fucking know.
He has some sort of a name that is a name.
Is he like a is he a sad rapper?
No, he's like something I don't know.
I don't know knowledge about what he does.
Perfect.
Someone mentioned Post Malone.
Is that Post Malone?
That's what I was thinking.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking of.
That's who I was thinking of and I just couldn't place the name.
And all I remember is that he's got like a sad rap song that got really popular.
Anything about anything?
It is.
Damn.
How did I fucking know?
I've never I don't even know fucking.
I couldn't name a Post Malone song, but somehow in my lizard brain,
I associated this face with that identity even though I couldn't place the name.
Stupid.
All right.
Enough about this.
Yes.
Fuck Andrew Hussie.
Fucking hack.
Gigapause was too long.
Truth.
Well, should we go to questions?
I mean, do we still do voicemails?
Holy shit.
We do.
Believe it or not, I have one more thing that I wanted to complain about before we go into voicemails.
And that is I got so a while ago, I've said this before, my tablet died, the screen died.
Press F.
So so I bought a new one.
Not an almost as old model, a slightly upgraded model.
It's still like a decade old at this point.
So like, you know, kind of old tech.
But I got a new tablet, a Cintiq 21 UX DTK upgraded from a DTZ.
But it turns out, and I remember I had gotten, when I had got the old one,
an old, a previous patron of mine, Artemis gave it to me.
I guess he's had an extra one.
But he so he gave me the tablet and I didn't have a stylus.
So I went and I bought a stylus and it didn't work.
And I asked him and he told me, oh, yeah, that's stylish you got.
Sorry, that doesn't work with the DTZ with the DTZ.
That only works with the later model, the DTK.
So I had to buy another stylus for that.
And then I got this one, it's the DTK.
And I had previously bought a stylus that only worked with DTK.
And I don't know where it is.
I can't find it.
That's why I was looking through my room when I found the makeup.
I was looking through my shit trying to find that old stylus.
And it doesn't work.
So now I have to buy a third stylus to replace the first one
for the first tablet that didn't work, that I need to replace with the second stylus.
And so this thing that I'm trying to make right now,
it does, it's going to involve drawing some stuff.
But I can't draw anything until I get the fucking,
until I get the freaking thing in the mail.
So I won't be able to do that for like a week, but it's okay.
I'll have other stuff to work on with it.
Do you have pencils and paper?
Shut the fuck up.
Oh, it's a, I need, I need to produce digital.
I need to produce digital images.
I mean, you could sketch them maybe.
Just so you have them,
then you don't need to think when you're drawing them digital.
Well, no, well, okay.
Yeah, in theory, I guess if I need an image,
I could sketch it and then scan it and then put it,
because I need sketch it and then scan it
and then like trace it in my computer.
No, there's no point.
There's no point at all.
In fact, there's no point to anything.
You know, we're all just going to die one day, actually.
Yeah.
Why don't we just do that now?
I don't know.
Now you're speaking my language.
All right.
Let's do voicemails, right?
Okay.
Oh, man, I like hinted at that,
but I didn't get into specifics.
My sleep has been really weird lately.
I've been waking up at the same time,
no matter when I go to sleep.
And like it's really bad.
Like it's early.
Like I've been waking up at like 6.45 a.m.
Pretty close to that every morning,
even when I went to sleep at like two in the morning.
I can't seem to get a good night's sleep for the full eight hours,
unless I would have to go to sleep at like 10.
And I don't want to do that.
That's stupid.
8 hours seems like too much.
8 hours?
What do you mean?
Like going to bed at 10.
Oh, I guess if you're waking up at 6, no, no, it's fine.
8 hours is normal.
Going to bed at 10 seems like so early, but if you're...
Yeah, I would rather shift it.
I would rather shift it.
So I'm going to sleep sometime between like midnight and 2
and waking up sometime between like 8 and 10.
Waking up like before 7 in the morning just seems like...
There's no need for that.
It's not 10, man.
No.
The early worm catches the bird.
I don't know.
So I keep staying up a little later than that.
I keep staying up until like midnight or two
and then I only get like four or six hours of sleep
and I wake up and I'm bleary the next day and I can't focus.
I'll figure it out.
Okay, are we ready for voicemails?
Yeah, is a truth teller?
Yes, the first one on the second page.
Oh, boy.
Because there's two called truth teller for some reason.
Here we go.
A truth teller.
Three, two, one, go.
That's me.
He loves what?
Anal.
Oh.
This is really what I come back to after like five weeks of not being...
Being here.
Good to know some things never change.
Like the quality of voicemails.
Even better.
We've got another one from truth teller is our next voicemail.
I hope it's him profusely apologizing for the previous...
Three, two, one, go.
He just did it again.
With better mic quality this time.
I want to like file criminal charges for wasting my time like that.
I mean, this is supposed to be amazing grace, right?
Yeah.
Well, why didn't he complete the fucking stanza?
Because he's...
What the fuck is this hack work?
Voice jail.
Like me.
You didn't do the like me.
Fuck.
It's so annoying.
I'm so glad that I'm here right now.
Next one is called ABA sends its regards.
Three, two, one, go.
And you'll pass in the shadow of your past childhood.
The jet fuel can't melt steel beams.
Fuck off, you man child.
You fuck tard.
You loser.
Fuck off.
You master of lies and deception and die.
Pop filter, please.
Okay.
Was that an attempt at like a Pink Floyd lyric?
The ABA, does the ABA refer to the rhyme scheme?
I have no idea.
Okay, well, terrible.
We're doing great guys.
We're doing great.
Next, we're just going to be good.
We're just going to be good.
Next one is Liam.
This is like if NWA was good.
Three, two, one, go.
I was like not going to like do another call ever again,
but holy shit.
Let's the fucking garlic house.
Fucking the fucking the what's it called?
The Brad Garling house.
That's right.
Distract, dude.
I hate it.
I like it.
I don't like it at all.
This is fucking stupid and terrible and not good.
And it's amazing and I love it.
And it's bad.
And the munchy verse was kind of unironically
actually wicked, but it's stupid and bad.
And you should never, ever make music or be allowed
in your microphone with a beat playing ever again, ever.
I'll kill all of you.
I love it.
This is bad.
Pais.
I'm fucking, I mean, I'm like reading the comments right now.
Like let's read some fucking comments, dude.
This is like if NWA was good from this guy blank.
That's that's probably, that's like, this is like,
this is like if NWA was good.
Whatever, dude.
I fucking hate all of you.
Basically don't make music.
So did he not like the song?
I don't know.
All I know is he probably paid for it.
So that's pretty funny.
He's like in a critical state of, of cringe and bass
and he's like rotating like unbelievably fast.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can't tell which way he's looking.
Wait a minute.
Fuck.
There's um.
I don't know what NWA is.
It's it's it's niggas with attitude.
The band.
Oh.
It's EZE and Dr. Dray.
And who's the third one?
MC Rand.
Mr. Attitude.
Yeah.
And I know that because I know, but I know fuck the police
and they say their names.
They say their names in that song.
Lamal.
Okay, whatever.
Cool.
Next voicemail is called Liam.
Ben equals Dreg.
Three, two, one, go.
I almost forgot to say this earlier.
Ben, you also sound like fucking Dreg in the diss track.
Like when fucking Dreg's doing his funky bad music things.
That's what you sound like.
Okay.
Everyone says that my verse is the worst.
Nobody likes my verse.
Well, guess what, losers?
Did you wrote it for me?
So fuck all of you.
I wrote like the first two lines and then I couldn't write anymore.
And did you just wrote the rest and I just wrapped it?
Lamal.
I don't remember.
I don't.
What a boy.
The best part.
What a boy, guys.
Nobody likes mine.
I think mine was the best because they got bowtoy in it.
Piece of shit.
Honestly, I saw a lot of people saying that Munchie's verse was the best.
And it's just not.
I'm sorry.
I can't even remember everyone else's.
Munchie's verse is not very good.
It's like the worst one.
I think it's worse than mine, to be honest.
Yeah, I said it.
Yeah, I fucking said it.
Fuck you.
Rap battle.
Two bad ones.
Next one is called Voice Whale.
Three, two, one, go.
That's W-E-I-N.
Yeah, I get it.
Because last time we had the whale like the aquatic mammal.
And this time the whale like the vocal vocal.
What is with the, I mean, I ask what is with the shit quality of the voicemails this week, but.
It does seem particularly bad.
They knew I was coming back and they were like,
we've got to make sure he never comes back again.
It does seem especially cringe this time.
When are we just going to stop taking voicemails?
Over our cold dead bodies as well.
Motivation to murder both of you.
Sick.
Oh, thank fuck.
I don't have to do it myself.
Just looking out for my bros.
That's it.
And I'm back.
What's the next one?
Fake fan mage stan.
Three, two, one, go.
So I don't follow any of you weirdos on Twitter.
So I probably missed the info from there.
But I swear last time I remember mage being on the show.
She said that she just wouldn't be on for a while because she was like going to take care of her grandma or something.
But now it sounds like mage just like isn't on the show anymore and she isn't coming back.
I'm sorry.
I just miss mage and her weird dreams and her drawings and stuff.
So yeah, what's the deal?
Sorry for being a fake fan by.
Okay.
How angry should I be at this person for not knowing?
Only mildly?
Yeah, mildly.
I don't can't remember which episode we would have said it, but I know we've said it at some point.
Yeah.
I'm just saying if you miss mage's work, mage is on Twitter posting her work.
That's true.
Get on Twitter.
Yeah, if you miss her drawings, YouTube is not, this podcast is not really the best place for them.
I think she's gone.
I think she's officially out.
I don't know.
Am I wrong?
I have no clue.
I genuinely don't know.
The door is always open.
She doesn't want to do podcast stuff anymore.
Yeah, the door is always open.
Of course.
Yeah.
That's her prerogative and that's fine.
Yep.
Who cares?
Next one is called Homestuck Preservation Follow Up.
Three, two, one, go.
All right.
Follow up on that whole Homestuck Preservation thing I sent a million years ago.
I finished Homestuck months ago.
I love it to death.
Act six is terrible.
Yep.
Yeah, that's true.
Tom's actually a lifesaver because he mentioned the whole Flashpoint project thing where,
which is actually preserving flash animations.
Somebody decided to take this and apply it to some weird version of Chromium.
And so there's an offline archive you can download.
Now, in order to get the one that I have, you have to email a bot.
It's at gimme homestuck at ZohoMail.com.
And you have to ask for an offline archive download.
And because he doesn't own any of the rights.
And then he'll send it to you and it loads the entirety of Homestuck and ProblemSleuth offline.
It's a little slow.
It's a little janky.
Sometimes the save feature fucks up.
But you can still use the map to sort of figure out stuff.
I don't know.
Thank you, Tom.
You put me on the right path.
Homestuck is preserved.
I do what I can.
That's awesome.
That's super great.
Yeah, I'm glad that it exists, that will continue to exist in some form.
That's kind of appropriate for Homestuck, I think, right?
That like you can only get it by emailing some bot.
I like that.
Gimme Homestuck.
Gimme Homestuck at ZohoMail.
Gimme Homestuck or Gimme Death.
Agreed.
Next one is called Exposed.
Three, two, one, go.
Continue as you were, gentlemen.
On our news site we posted an extremely ugly story about how Hippocrite here
actually turned out to be a transsexual.
Okay, would you care to elaborate on that?
It's all true.
The rumors, every and all rumors, even ones that don't make sense.
That's the truth.
Post up, none up, coin up, give us all the deeds.
My trainer code is 1-8-2-7-9-7-6-2-4-5-6-8 for my transgo game community video game.
What are the three numbers in the back and what did they just expire on?
Okay, so that's a little blast from the past as before it was trans.
That's mildly amusing.
What was that, like a million years ago?
Yeah.
At least.
Good times.
I mean, I could hear Nate, so it was like, wow, what?
So that must be ancient times before COVID, before Gib decided to go trans and spite God
and cursed us all with COVID.
It was a necessary sacrifice, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Worth it.
Tom, were you going to say something?
I just said, I was just going to say it was worth it as well, so.
Okay.
Yeah, well then we're all in agreement.
Good.
Next one is called a weeb with a counterpoint.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys, back during the election episode, some doofus came on the voicemails and was saying,
hey, if an anime is bad, and if dubs are bad, doesn't mean that the dubs of bad anime are good.
And.
Yes.
Generally rightfully, you guys said, no, of course, that doesn't make any,
that's bullshit, it's additive, it's not multiplicative.
Counterpoint, the ghost story stuff, which is good, despite being a bad anime.
Okay, but that's, no, that's not the same.
They're not dubbing the source material.
It's basically a bridge series, officially.
Yeah, that's not a bad dub, that's a deliberately silly dub, right?
Like it's trying to be funny.
It's all ad-libbed, most of it's ad-libbed, and none of it is representative of the source material at all.
I didn't know it was ad-libbed.
I haven't seen that much of it.
Is that the one where it's like the voice actors just didn't give a shit, and they said a lot of crazy things?
Yeah, there's a lot of like, really edgy humor in it, and it's pretty funny.
It was, I mean, it wasn't on like TV, right?
No, I don't believe so.
Yeah, it is basically just an abridged series.
What's the, there's like one particularly famous line from it, but I don't remember what it is.
Ghost, ghost stories, there's like the girl who's like really religious and always like makes Jesus
jokes, and then there's the girl who like falls in love with the bunny, and the bunny's like a
that's the voice of a deep, like a deep voice of a black man and stuff, and
there's a lot of weird shit in that dub.
I think there's a, I think there's like a pedo joke somewhere about the kid.
I think that's what I'm thinking of, but I don't remember what the joke is.
Yeah, that's, no, it's not the same.
This isn't, that's not a, that's not a bad dub.
That's just a weird, deliberately strange dub.
Uh, but good try, maybe next time.
Next one is called Cross, garlic and stuff.
Three, two, one, go.
So the garlic house diss track was pretty based.
I thought all of you guys did really great.
Talk about it, if you haven't already.
I don't know, is there anything fun, cool about production and shit?
Also super excited for the Brad Garling House lecture.
That's, that's it.
See you next week.
Good voicemail, solid voicemail.
Yeah, I guess we didn't talk about that at all.
Cause that, I had actually forgotten that that dropped this week.
Same.
Yeah, it was, uh, this process of that was nobody really knew what they were doing
at all at any point.
And, um, did we do any work on it before we were there?
Did we come up with the lyrics?
No.
I think, didn't, did did you like, they, they picked the beat, I think.
I think they had like picked the beat out before.
Yeah.
And yeah, we picked the beat out and I think I had like scribbled some things on a Google
doc and me and Munchie were working together too.
Cause we were like, we had figured out the, the like the chorus thing.
Like who, who was going in front of who and like we were left to our own devices to come
up with our own lyrics for our part.
And, um, yeah, I think I had done mine by the time we were there and some of us weren't.
I think Digi winged it.
Yeah.
And, and you hadn't written anything.
So we had to like help you write something.
Well, like no one, most people hadn't written anything.
Yeah.
Nate hadn't written anything either.
Like every, everyone else just like figured those out on the fly and I just suck and I
couldn't do it.
Right.
Confor was just so much shit going on at the same time.
Like even finding time to do that was like a pain in the ass.
And then like recording it wasn't all day affair.
It was just, it was so, it was so stressful.
We had to cram everything in.
We didn't even have time to do the final recording at Radcon.
So we all had to do our final parts individually and get them mixed after the fact.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, the reason it was like that of course was because we, there was a music video associated
with the thing.
I'm surprised that didn't drop and we just had the, did the audio upload.
Oh wait, are we not supposed to say that there's a video?
No, that was part of the Kickstarter.
It's like music video too for the, for the disc track.
The disc track is out.
There is a video.
Yeah, I was expecting the song to drop with the video.
I think it will come pretty soon.
He can't have forgotten.
No, no, no.
That the way it was, it was set up was the, the lecture comes out first, then the music video.
Oh, okay.
It's all linked up.
So the idea, so the song, the song was ready.
So Nate dropped the song and then the lecture will come out next and then the music video
after that.
Yeah.
Okay.
Very good.
Yeah.
God, it's, it, I think I've been kind of stressed.
I think it's been a source of like subconscious stress for me that like it's been so long since
Radcon 4 and like a lot of the content never came out.
I would not be stressed except for the fact that so much of it hinges on this joke that is like a
year old and like will it still be funny?
That doesn't bother me.
Honestly, that, I'm like, you know, that's in God's hands now.
Whereas things like getting the rest of the lectures out, that's, that's in, it's man.
We could, mankind can only rely on himself for that.
And I don't, I don't trust us.
I mean, I can't judge because I haven't gotten mine done either, but I'm going to.
Yeah.
I mean, I feel like that's an individual sort of thing.
If you've got one to do, then obviously you'd feel stressed about that.
But like, in terms of Radcon stuff, I guess I feel a little bad.
Yeah, the, I guess the lectures are not technically like stretches, rewards.
There's the, the OVA, which I still have to edit, but there's the OP, which is still being animated.
So they couldn't, I couldn't release it anyway.
There's, so that's Mike's use still.
Yeah.
I mean, that's, that was always going to take a while.
Then there's the, the dojin, which is the dojin, which we have not really even started.
It's because nobody wants to be the person to draw smut of ourselves.
Well, none of us is going to draw it.
We were going to commission someone.
We were kind of, yeah, we hadn't found anyone.
I think we just hadn't written anything yet.
I think, I think the holdup for me about that was I kind of thought that like,
it was going to tie in with the final chapter of Road to Radcon was another thing that needs to get done.
Yeah, it's all on Digi.
So there's, there's that.
And then I, I guess I thought that the dojin was going to tie into that somehow.
I thought it was.
Road to Radcon 5 at this rate.
Yeah.
Well, oh God.
Well, Road to Radcon Chapter 5 can also be the Road to Radcon 5 Chapter 1.
See, Bridges the Gap.
I see, I see.
Can we, can we get on Digi's ass about just finishing that?
Like, I don't, I want, like I have previously and they just, she just, she's doing strange things.
Stupid, stupid.
Road, road trips and drugs and strange new people.
And I don't get it.
And I guess it's fine.
It's just sort of like.
I'm not the only one who has no idea what's going on in Digi's life right now.
That makes me feel a little better.
I mean, it just seems like a bunch of stupid bullshit.
I mean, I don't, I don't.
And that's, that's all I know.
And that, I feel like that sums it up.
I'm just so fucking lost.
I don't know what the hell's going on anymore.
I wasn't sure if it just because I wasn't paying attention because I wasn't.
I just want to see the, the, the, the Brony lecture was great.
And that should come out.
It really was.
It really was good.
Yeah.
I mean, again, I can't judge because my lecture's not out.
Well, so.
I can judge.
You can, and Tom can.
You guys can.
Flex.
For sure.
We, you know, we really do need Road to Radcon 5 though.
And, and then the Dojin and then the, and I think that's like it, right?
That would.
Yeah.
After the, the Brad lecture and the music video, the OVA, the Dojin and the Digi's.
That's it.
Just like, just lots of stuff, you know.
I mean, Digi wrote the Road to Radcons.
She, she wrote them in like less than a day.
Yeah.
Like she just like, she just like blasted those chapters out like, like in no time.
So like, yeah, you know, uh, I feel like, uh, I don't know.
I feel like she could be gotten to sit down and do it.
We would just have to get her at like the, at a time when she was like.
Go to, go to digi.com and say, please Road to Radcon 5 in the comments.
Right.
Uh, and then yeah, we didn't, we, we, we, I think we tried at one point to decide like,
okay, who's going to write the story of the Dojin?
Who's going to decide what it is?
What is the story going to be?
Who's going to script it?
Uh, and we like never came to any conclusions about it.
It's like, how do you, like, and then they fuck like, I don't want to write that.
That's the dojin was not going to be like, uh, anti.
We, yeah.
It's going to be a little, a little itchy, you know.
Yeah.
Very good.
Wait.
Okay.
I'm brainstorming this.
The dojin should be, the dojin should be about how we all became girls for Road to,
for Radcon.
Like that should be the, it should be the, the gap.
Wait.
Oh yeah.
Did I just, did the girl, do, do people even know about the girl thing?
I don't think so.
Well, no, no, no, no, no, we have the calendars out.
Yeah.
The calendar, we have the behind the scene videos.
Is the calendar out?
Yeah.
It was shipped in the rewards.
Okay.
It was shipped in the reward.
Wait.
So was it shipped in the rewards with like no context as to like what?
Correct.
And only the backers know about it.
So only the backers know about any of that.
We spoiled that for the majority of people listening to this podcast.
I'm pretty sure in the original Kickstarter promotional video, that was part of the thing.
Like we're going to be anime girls.
You can get a calendar of us being anime girls.
No one's seen it.
Nobody knows, except for like the small glimpses in that one blog.
That's so god.
It's so stupid.
Remember when we were on the beach for an entire day dressed like that?
Recorded.
Yeah, it was great.
Yeah.
I was very attacked us.
A fucking dog.
I fucked that dog.
Piece of shit.
Well, it wasn't the dog, it was the owner who just wouldn't wrangle it.
Well, both.
Well, yeah, I mean both.
Like fuck the dog and fuck the owner for not fucking taking responsibility.
But whatever.
Okay, well, that's my pitch for, that's my pitch for the dojin.
Who wants to draw it?
Email us.
Don't actually, we'll email you.
We won't actually.
Fill in the comments if you will do work for free and then I'll be like,
Oh, that person does work for free.
No, no, no, we'll pay someone.
We'll pay someone, which means that if you're listening to this, you're not qualified.
Next, next voicemail.
Tom King's Mr. Miracle.
Three, two, one, wait, three, two, one, go.
I meant Tom King's run of Mr. Miracle.
It's on six issues long.
It's poetic.
It has great, it's beautiful.
And Big Bada, not a kuma, I don't come to comic books, but she is a beautiful little piece of
that.
She's tall, she's thin.
They draw her beautifully.
No, she just looks like any other woman.
It's good.
No, shut up.
Shut up about what's her name.
You're wrong.
You're wrong about that.
But if it's only six issues, that kind of makes me
think that maybe it would be worth reading.
Okay, I'll consider it.
I heard you think about this.
So, Tom King's.
Yeah, we got a voicemail last week about, I think it was the same guy.
That unmistakable, that unmistakable Hispanic drawl about Tom King's Mr. Miracle.
Is this Tom King's Mr. Miracle?
Because this is a character that's been drawn by other people.
Yeah, yeah, it's a run by Tom King.
Okay, this might be what it looks like then, because I just googled that.
Let's check it out.
I'll fucking check it out.
Next one is called Cowpoke Slim.
Three, two, one, go.
Howdy, y'all.
It's me, The Cow.
Mario.
I just wanted to call in to thank old Gib here for helping me round up them dusty old cows
in the dusty old Wild West.
Y'all was a big old help.
Is my trusty lasso that I loaned you holding up?
I might need her back soon, so make sure she's in good shape.
Well, it's time for me to go down to the old water and hole.
So, as they say in old me humland,
Sayonari, old canary.
I did that.
I must have been drunk.
Uh, uh, yep.
Something.
It's a new character.
Oh, it's the start of a new arc, a whole new arc.
Oh, it's going to be span months.
Oh, wait, I get it.
Connect to all the others.
The samurai was like, please give back scroll.
This guy is Cowpoke Slim.
Please give back lasso to Gib.
Oh, no, it begins again.
Gib, you lost Cowpoke Slim's prize lasso.
How is he going to wrangle his herds?
How's he going to wrangle his doggies?
How's he going to commit suicide?
But I misplaced it.
How's he going to commit suicide so Samurai Sama can resurrect him with the necronomicon?
How's the plot going to happen if something isn't going to happen?
How's the plot going to happen if you were introducing conflict?
You moron.
Next one is called bring back wonderbread guy.
Three, two, one, go.
Man, fuck these guys who shit on wonderbread guy.
He was the best.
The critics, they're all like, wonderbread guy.
He's a Nazi and he has weird conspiracy theory ideas.
Well, you shut the fuck up.
That's not the point.
And it doesn't even matter.
I agree that's not the point.
When he was telling his story about losing his virginity or whatever,
and you had to ask your questions repeatedly because he just,
he wouldn't answer them directly.
And his story was just so long and unnecessarily convoluted.
Does the funnest that I've heard is funnest for a long time?
It was funny.
I was literally laughing at loud and about his weird ideas.
Even though I disagree on them, I still find it funny to listen to.
Okay, bye.
No, I agree.
I think he was funny to have as a guest,
even though he's annoying as a person.
Lamal.
No, I want 100% on board with this.
Well, I'm bringing him back.
Well, no, not on that.
I wouldn't go that far.
That's the title of the voicemail.
On board with it.
Good voicemail.
Next one is called Keraskoet.
Satania, especially.
I don't know what that means.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Another comic book recommendation.
Anything by this French couple called Keraskoet.
They made these very dark stories with beautiful art.
Okay.
And it's a very fresh read and very good.
I appreciate these comic recommendations.
I've never heard of Keraskoet or Satania.
That's French.
French comics.
There's a huge comic scene in France.
Look at this.
Look at this one.
This is much better than Mr. Mama Luigi.
Mr. Mama Luigi.
Oh, that's interesting.
It does look pretty French.
Yes, it's like hell, just like France.
Just like France.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
Ah.
It's a great life drawing they do there.
Next voicemail is called Frendle Babin.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP.
Have you ever listened to Coast to Coast?
Specifically when George Nore is broadcasting.
You know, it's a show about the paranormal.
So a bunch of people who are way out there calling.
And George Nore, he's like a real hero.
He just like, he keeps them talking.
He keeps a narrative line.
And like, what I'm saying is I'm seeing a parallel
to how you guys have been recently.
So like, what do you call it?
Like, this is feedback and recommendation.
I don't know.
Just keep getting weird people on.
It's great.
Thank you.
Anyway, you have a wonderful 2021.
Peace out.
I sure hope we do.
I've never listened to Coast to Coast.
I've heard about it a little.
Thanks.
Thanks for watching.
A game theory.
Glad you like the guests.
Fuck you.
Coaster Coast is like a coast but made out of coasters.
Instead of sand.
Oh, a coaster coaster.
Oh, yeah.
Just fuck me in the ass.
Next one is called Gibb.
Where's the Lude Twitter account?
Three, two, one, go.
Gibb, where's the Lude Twitter account?
Wow.
There it is.
Straight to the point.
I can appreciate that.
I wish every voicemail were five seconds.
It's out there on the Twitter.
I feel like not, I don't want to promote it
just because it doesn't have a lot of good stuff on there yet.
It's just a lot of sketches and little bits here and there.
But it's called, let me find it just because she cares.
It's the PCP.
You can say whatever you want on this show.
That's true.
What's it called?
Big, at Big Girl Squish.
Big Girl Squish.
You can find out what I've drawn.
Find out all the secrets.
You can find out how to have sex.
Oh, no.
We don't show that on screen.
You can finally figure it out.
The secret knowledge.
Okay.
Next one is called Max Patrick Aylward-Nesbitt.
Three, two, one, go.
God, it's a minute 30.
Hello, pre-crastinators P and audience.
I've sent this voicemail over electronic mail to plead your wisdom on matters of
high importance and philosophy.
Furthermore, I wish to bring to the floor a motion on the discussion of the subject thusly.
Mr. Nesbitt, this is a library.
On the floor is to consider the limitations of what is heterosexual and what is otherwise.
Or gay.
It is it gay for a cisgendered man to be in sexual relations with a transgendered female person?
What about when it's a cisgendered woman?
All this theater in service of a fucking lame question.
How gay is it when a person looks on a transgendered person of the opposite gender?
Who cares?
Shut up.
No, stop it.
No, I'm done.
No, good try.
Whatever.
It's a very stupid take.
Who cares?
You should think about it a little bit.
Just think about it a little bit and just the obvious answers are the answers.
Just it doesn't matter.
Oh my god.
I'm annoyed.
I was actually I'm annoyed because I was a little excited because I was like, oh, he's
gonna like do a thing.
Oh, this guy is like a eccentric man.
This guy put a little effort into this into this into this voicemail.
A good, you know, he's gonna shoot a shot.
Well, it should have known better.
So good try.
Good try.
I know, I know.
The next one is called Santa came down my chimney.
So I came down Rudolph's throat.
Three, two, one, go.
I said I was sorry.
You said I thought we were cool.
Hey, guys, happy holidays from Cassidy.
So out of curiosity, I went back and had a bit of a gander.
This summer, I gimmick has been going on since August 15th.
And I think that Ben deserves like an eternity credit in the world for playing
along with it for these fucking four months.
Good on you.
Feels like yes, did you?
Because of you, I was able to confront my own issues with gender this year.
It's been a crazy butterfly effect from watching somebody with an unkempt beard
like mine giving a lecture on Maddox to looking in the mirror today.
And I just wanted to let you know that you helped change my life for the better this year.
Thank you.
But did you do next time?
I say one more.
Did you will never hear this voicemail, Lamal?
I'll personally see to it.
I'm never ready for a sincerity in these voicemails.
It always takes me a back.
I'm like, oh, God, cringe.
I know, right?
Just waiting for the other shoe to drop the whole time.
Just like, this can't be real, this can't be real.
In order to express even a moment's genuine sentiment,
you have to run a four month long character arc.
Ah, right, right, right.
That's the toll you got to pay.
Yeah, whatever.
Glad you're a fucking girl now or whatever you have fucking nerd.
Okay, next one is called Funny Joke.
Three, two, one, go.
PCP, more like HRT.
Okay, I thought I thought he was gonna go HIV, but that's fine too.
Tomato, tomato.
The huge
reps, I can't think of it.
I can't think of a PCP HRT turning that into words
that is not hormone replacement therapy.
That rhymes with PCP, procrastinators, whatever.
Shut up, shut up, move on.
Welcome to the next episode of this exciting episode
of the Hormone Replacement Therapy Project.
It's hypnosis.
You listen and we hypnotize you to make your butt look bigger.
You know, like a girl has a big butt, you know?
You know what I'm talking about.
Ellie is our cut this part.
No, no, no, no, refurb this part.
Okay, all right, shut the fuck up.
Next one is called GCCX on Cardfreck.
Three, two, one, go.
If y'all were anyone listening last week, thought,
hey, yeah, Game Center CX sounds cool.
I want to watch it and don't feel like torrenting.
You can always watch it on Twitch.
There's a 24 seven Twitch stream on twitch.tv slash cardfreck.
So if you want to watch an episode of Game Center CX
and don't particularly care what games being played,
you can just go watch it there anytime.
This is, of course, assuming Twitch doesn't just obliterate it
due to all the DMCA shit they've been doing.
But hey, for now, it's good.
Interesting. Game Center CX being the show that Tectonic Improv
did the retrospective on that got taken off YouTube for bullshit reasons.
I love modern internet.
It's so good.
I just love saying yes to cookie popups.
I still haven't gotten a single cookie,
just by clicking all those fucking things.
A 24 hour stream.
I think I feel like I really would like a Game Center CX
if it were in English, because that would mean that I could just
kind of have it on and sort of not pay that much attention to it.
Just kind of watch it passively.
But the fact that it's subtitles
mean that I would have to watch it actively and be reading,
and I just don't know if that's the experience I want to have with it.
It's funny you mentioned the subtitles thing,
because one of the really jarring things that's happened to me
in the last couple weeks, it started with playing Ghost of Tsushima,
because you can play it in English or Japanese with subtitles,
is I've decided that I hate subtitles.
I don't know why it took me so long to figure this out,
but I'm just so sick of having to read
while all those gorgeous animation happens,
and I'm ignoring the actual visuals of this visual medium,
and I'm really just like, I really need to just learn Japanese.
I'm so sick of missing all the good stuff that happens in anime,
because I'm too busy looking at the words
and not paying attention to the animation that people slaved over making.
This never used to bother me,
but now it's just like it's enraging.
Dubs are bad because they sound terrible,
and subs are bad because I can't watch anything anymore,
and I'm just like, no, the only answer is to become the ultimate weeb
and learn Japanese.
I have never once felt that feeling that you just described ever.
I feel like I've had that feeling.
I don't think I've ever thought to act on it.
It's just been like, damn, I didn't really pay attention
to what they were doing there because I was reading.
Damn, well, I can't be bothered to go back.
Drives me crazy.
Yeah, well, I don't think I've ever been like,
I didn't appreciate the gorgeous visuals because I was reading.
It's like, nah, I get the picture.
I understand the gist of what I saw without carefully examining it or whatever.
I don't want the gist.
I want to see the whole thing.
The point of, I don't know, in a film, if there's a really beautiful shot,
like, I don't need to be, I don't know, I can get the impression
that the shot is meant to give me even while my eye is kind of directed down at the subtitle.
It's just like, it's not even like a legitimate concern.
It's just one of those things that I just like realized was happening
and now I just have like this weird autistic fixation on it and it makes me really angry.
I just, it's the same with, I would probably re-watch
Monben a bunch more.
I've probably watched the whole series like twice, which is a lot for me because with subtitles.
If it were not subtitled, if it were in English and I didn't have to read for it.
Right, we'd be cool if you could just tab over and just continue to absorb that.
Yeah, I probably would have watched it like a dozen times.
That's how much I love it.
Yeah, I feel like similarly about...
Think of all the Japanese podcasts you could listen to.
Like a whole world would open up.
I think there might, I think there might be one or two Monben's that I have not,
that are like newly translated that I have not seen actually.
I should check on that.
They're like hard to find and keep track of because I think it's just like one guy somewhere
who is doing the subbing of them and like...
What a champion.
Yeah, I don't know why he does it.
Like I don't know, I don't know what he gets out of it, but I'm thankful for his work.
Pretty cool, yeah.
Well, shit, that's the last voicemail.
Thank God.
Yeah, we did it.
We made it to the end.
Made it to the top of the mountain.
Well, any final thoughts before we sign out till next time?
Wait, I have one thing, I do have one thing.
Because this episode, this episode will be coming out on Christmas, on Friday.
Oh, one mile.
So I'm going to post this in the chat.
It's time stamped.
Okay, the song, last year, the YouTuber called Tom, No Relation, sent in a voicemail
and we listened to it around Christmas time and it's been taken down.
You know the song I'm talking about?
I do not.
I don't really know.
Well, I mean, I want us to listen to it.
Oh, I remember this.
Should I count down?
The Hatsune Miku.
So, oh, I already pressed play.
Oh, right.
Yeah, I remember this.
Okay, well, I'm going to count down three, two, one, go.
I think it wouldn't be a PCP Christmas without listening to it again.
This is the only version of a song that exists anymore because it was removed from Tom's channel
for bullying and harassment of me.
No, I remember that.
I remember you saying that.
It's tragic and I tweeted at YouTube saying,
I like to be bullied.
Please let them bully me.
And they didn't answer.
This is a masterpiece.
It's so fucking good.
Oh, my God.
This is the whole song.
It's the whole song.
Oh, it just keeps going.
The extra level is just off the charts.
If you want to hear the song again now,
you have to hear it with Nate laughing in the background.
It doesn't have something to it to prepare.
It does.
Yes, yes.
I've killed Digi.
I've killed Nate.
I've killed Mage.
Killed Jesse.
You're the only two left.
Right.
I was just procrastinating on killing Ben Sane.
Soon it'll be me.
More, more, more, more.
I can't get enough.
All right, we're fading the hat.
Okay.
There it is.
Wait, Tom.
Okay.
Why was that?
There it is.
Shut up, procrastinators from the past.
I don't want to hear you.
Past, procrastinators.
The pro-pastinators.
Get them out of here.
Merry fucking Christmas, everyone.
Merry Christmas, Tom, other Tom.
Tom, who made the song.
Not this Tom, this guy.
That guy actually made something, you know?
Merry Christmas for everyone.
God bless us.
Everyone.
That's the one.
Good, good night, and God speed you, you black emperor.
Sweet dreams.
Good, see you next, see you in 20, fucking 21.
Before we wrap up, it's Christmas.
It's the season of giving.
So if you would like to give to us on this holiday,
patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
That's right.
And donate $5 a month where we can give gifts to you
in terms of multiple bonus episodes.
All of middling quality, some that are actually even
kind of good.
The latest one.
I don't know if it's uploaded yet.
It might not be, but soon.
You can hear me get fucking salty and just bitch about everyone.
So just like this episode and every other one.
Yeah, but even more.
No, it was like vicious.
Ben St. Unleashed.
That's the bonus episode.
Oh, God.
It was too hot.
It was too hot for YouTube.
So it's in secret YouTube.
Uh, that's the trick.
And send us a voicemail at speakpipe.com slash pzp voicemail.
If you think you can do better than these fucking hacks this week.
A low bar to clear.
You can do it.
I believe in you.
Anything else?
Are we done?
No.
Never.
Not Merry Christmas.
Very Christmas holiday.
Very, very Hanukkah everypony.
Good.
Happy Hearth Swarming Eve.
Ah, a unicorn power.
Dab, dab, dab.
Earth's power, I guess.