Hello everyone and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'd like to thank myself for being here.
Also Tom Oliver is here.
Yeah, and I'd like to thank myself for being better than everybody.
It's official.
I just leveled up last night and I'm officially higher level than all of you and it feels
great.
It feels good.
Well you are working on a Sunday which is a few deductions of, you know, that's bad.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
That is me and no, I did not know that with that I see I feel that this is the big difference maker
And this is the big meta thing that it is a huge
This is which because like and then the the the vessel there with that's where your choices don't matter
But that's because you're not that's that's exactly him
Because the vessel took you the player out of the equation by ripping out the soul aka hearts putting in the cage
So
The fact that that is there and the things that that imply I feel that's going to be what Delta rune is about like agency of players
Surely we'll know one day. I hope one day. I hope to know what I can't wait to play this one
I'm 40 and really finally get the answer to this question. Well, we'll get on PCP episode. What let me just let me just ask you guys this
Everybody does that make a big difference to you. Does that it make you well?
It gives me hope about makes it encourages me that there is more going on here
Yeah, I want to tell you and because Tom brought up the the YA thing
Cuz like a big part of the discussion we were having when we were playing this game is that I kept calling it like youth fiction that like
I was comparing it to like Harry Potter and like that level of very childish
Characterization and theming and I didn't mean this as an insult to Toby Fox's
Inspiration because I feel like this is a game that he probably wrote that dude's youngest fuck, right?
Like how old is 25 maybe now or something? I don't know. Yes. So so at yeah
2012 that he wrote this he's a he's a baby, you know and like this game feels like
someone who's
Trying to express his very personal experiences the fact that the the the big
Wham line the arc words of this game are quiet people piss me off
Is that what it is? Your choices don't matter is like the I mean
That line is repeated twice. It's repeated. Yeah, several times
It has said quiet people piss me off first by Susie and then by I think yeah and both at very important moments, you know big dramatic
pulls and
this is
This is clearly a game about
Otherness about being like an outcast Susie is this character is very angry about the fact not that she
That that people don't accept her for being who she is, you know that she she thinks everyone's already drawn their conclusions about her before
They meet her that like I think Toby was very inspired to make this game based on his experiences as a human
You know clearly this is a game
You fucking take one look at Toby Fox. Obviously. He's a quiet fucking nerdy motherfucker who's been bullied his whole life
So like this game means something to him. I'm sure never
but like but also I
Feel like when I looked at this game
I saw Toby trying to work through something like trying to work through his past and get this off of his chest finally
But he's doing it in a very
Basic and generic way and I don't even mean that as an insult like sure. Let's find it's it's well
Constructed. He's telling the story as well as any other youth novelist would it's as good as Harry Potter
I'm 27. I don't need to read fucking Harry Potter. All right. Let's get into that. This is what I care about most of all
Okay, what made Undertale one of my favorite games of all time. I played Ben turned me on to the demo. He just said it's great
Nate go play it. I said, okay, I play it. I'm fighting Toriel. I get the and I killer and I get a bad ending
I'm like, okay, I'm gonna try this again and not killer. See what happens. I spare Toriel this time
And Flowey tells me like lol, you think you can just like not killer. I remember what you did
I'm like, what what what are you talking about? I and you know and then like whatever I do a pacifist run
I see that everything changes. I do a genocide run and I see that
Oh my god this and it really it was the genocide run when the demo came out
That was the thing that made me think wow, this game is not afraid to go there. This is bold
This is creative. I've never seen this done in this way before
This could be and at that point I was truly excited and had no I did not think for a second
It was going to be as good as my expectations were and then it was better than them
Because it it did as much as you could do with that concept and I personally love the moment-to-moment
Like world exploration of undertale. I love all the flavor
I love the fact that there's an ultra mega secret boss. You can fight if you do a bunch of you know
Genocidal shit. It's so fun for me. I love that game
But the thing that made undertale so great was the degree of choice you have and like your own
Responsibility for your choices now
I current once I discovered that you can move the heart thing at the end after you know
Kara rips it out or what at Chris Bessel whatever that implies to me
Okay, Toby is smarter than me and he has things planned this man made undertale
I'm not going to under a smarter than you but at least yeah smart enough to appeal to you
I think okay playing this demo. Yeah, I feel like there is potential for this game to be better than undertale
There's just so much more going on that like if he if he did to this game what he did to undertale
It will be better, but it's just a matter of like we don't know that yet because it's a fucking demo
You know, see I completely agree and I think you're right and frankly. I'm more scared now that this game
I mean my my expectations were so high for undertale and it bet them
I don't like is it possible to do that twice in a row? Oh god. I don't know but more importantly than that
The the main conceit of the undertale demo
I understood and couldn't and was like this is the coolest thing I've ever seen
The conceit of this demo is that your choices don't matter and I know he'll subvert it in some way
But like what so I played through the game a second time doing it effectively a genocide run and I was disgusted
I had heard this and I tested to see I think I know what you're gonna say
Literally you have the ability to do a genocide run in
In undertale in the demo and the fact you could was amazing and incredible
I loved it you don't even have any of those kind of option like when what I when I played through the first time
I was like, oh man, I have to this is a creative thing Susie who's a member of my team
I have to prevent her from killing enemies to get the pacifist run by far the coolest thing by far
Absolutely the best thing about the game and then I played a quote-unquote genocide run and found I couldn't even kill people when I tried to and
Was like well that just completely invalidated all the effort I put in in my fucking pacifist run and I was
Like that was a terrible betrayal to me of
What I hoped the consequences of my actions to be Rob me of agency which is why it's extra weird
Yeah, that afterwards Toby puts out this statement
That's like I hope people don't play this game with the expectation that it'll be like undertale that might ruin your experience with it
Why didn't you fucking say so? I
It doesn't matter if it's a sequel to undertale or not the fact that the game itself sets this up
But it turns out it's just not an issue or it's like putting in QTE elements in a game that you can lose and you still win
That's what it is
Defense it worked and it did get me to play the game worried about like, you know stopping Susie from hurting people
Even though even though it turned out upon review that it was a trick and I did not actually have to worry about it at all
Can you quickly explain for the viewers?
Okay, me what happens when you try to do genocide run because I want to do that
I'll be happy to but I just did bug fixes for my game instead because I'm gay
I hear your brother. There was literally one difference doing a genocide run versus a pure 100% pacifist run and it is this
It is that at the end when all the characters when you're fighting the king at the end when you're like, oh, we can't kill this guy
What are we gonna do and then the enemies come and they like pick up the king and they take him away?
Like it you know friendship saves the day instead of that what you get is a scene at the end where
It's actually interesting
The what happens is instead of the king being carried away by enemies
What happens is Susie has over the course of the game has learned that pacify spell that Rawl say knows and
Casts that spell upon the king and he's really tired. So he gets pacified
That is the only difference. He learns it and doesn't just ask
I am 100% sure because I played it and that is what is stated by the characters. Yes
It's so for some reason the difference between these two is that I feel like she just remembered that Ralsei can cast it
So she asked him to cast it. Well, I have played the game and that is not what happened
So, I mean let me know how can you be 100% sure that you wait mage did you do this run?
I watched I watched
Dab dab dab dab. Yeah, that's what I thought. It's still it's still words Nate that I could read so, you know
Yeah, so you you're just saying that I'm wrong. I'll go check. I'll go fucking check right now
I'm just saying that we might be interpreting the same line in different ways, and I'm not sure which one is correct
I'm gonna prove it right now
Nate did this seem ambiguous to you at all. No, not at all
Changes there's actually two changes, but one is significantly smaller the second one. There's a secret boss
and
Yeah, and during the the pacifist route it turns into an armor, but it during the genocide run so to speak it turns into a
What then so the secret boss by the way is great and one of the best characters and
I just I want to say that you you you let you literally can't kill it like anything like you cannot kill anything
If you watch if you watch they do not die if you hurt them if you get them under zero HP
They like zip off screen like they're running away, right? But but can you what happens if you don't stop?
Susie from doing things just the same thing they just run away
They they get down to zero HP and and then they run away because that's what happens like mechanically that sucks
Okay, quickly. I just people are theorizing and I
Know what they're basing it off and it could be like completely wrong and I don't blame it
It's just an interesting theory
I just thought about is that darkers actually bleed and it could be because and the reason they run away is because
Toby Fox or whatever they're trying to hide the fact that they actually do bleed which is not common for monsters of
At least the lightings
What is that implying is that implying anything about?
Anything I
Don't know about it. It's just because at some point
Lancer Lancer. Yeah, Lancer brings up a bucket. It's like oh to mop up the blood that you're gonna
God, I can't wait for like a week now for Matt Pat to come in and explain all this for me
So I can understand it. Yeah, I did my due diligence. God damn it. I know everything there is to know
I just it's just I mean, I'm not saying it's true, but it's interesting theory
I mean, there might be a reason why you can I think it's pretty weak
I don't that seems pretty weak. It was a strange choice to have Kara literally break into the
Da-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba Fortnite dance at the end of the game. That was an odd
Animation so I want to jump into something a little bit here that like my biggest hope for a final version of this game is that I
Recently have been on this kick where I'm talking about how media can basically broke it be broken into two categories
stuff that is about
Exploring the self and stuff. That's about exploring society
like
Every story is either about a man trying to come to grips with understanding himself well man or woman, obviously, but you know
I say man broadly or trying to come to grips a society around them and like
Informulate different opinions and different perspectives into one thing and when you look back at Undertale even though it has
It's about a
It's about one individual and how they slot into society
It's like are you someone who's a protector or a sociopath like where do you fit in but with this game?
Because you have a party of three and who knows how many more in the final game could be our teammates could be more
More to explore with this party system
It feels like this is almost
Spiritually a sequel which is why it's kind of weird even that this was like thought of before Undertale supposedly
You know, I don't I can't say I know the chronology of thoughts and Toby Fox's mind
But nonetheless at this game feels spiritually like a sequel to Undertale
Just in that there's three people in your party and that
Literally core to the mechanics is how those three people interact that like you can warn enemies about when this girl's gonna attack and the entire
Demo as soon as I knew that I was just like when is that other guy
rat res
I'll say I'll say when is Ralsei going to get mad at Susie. Yes for attacking and Toby's way too good a game designer to
Not do something interesting with Ralsei as a party member at some point
Yeah, like I knew that scene was coming because I was like well your character is not gonna do it
But like the fact that she's doing this is a problem. It has to be wrong brought up at some point
Ralsei's gonna get upset at her
He's gonna accost her for this the way she's been acting and like that's a very basic childish kind of
You know
black and white way of looking at it like either you spare him or you or you don't but
Surely there's more depth to it and the game then steps into the gray area of like what if there's an enemy you have to kill
You you don't actually you can just spare the fucking
final boss
All the way, but like obviously that's the next step forward, but then it's like well if this is all explored in chapter one
Surely there's even more you can do with this. Yeah. Yeah, okay. Will this game ever get made?
Okay, okay, so what since choices don't matter and you're forced into a pacifist route in the chapter one so far
Yeah, so far. Yeah. Yeah. What if you're forced into a genocide route in chapter two
Potentially that'll be fucking crazy. I mean, yeah, that'd be interesting. That'd be interesting
It seems like you know, it's setting it up because you know of the whole ending thing
I honestly have a lot of faith in toby as a character designer
So, you know, frankly, I'm I'm happy to sit back and say
You know, maybe I can't imagine all the ways to do interesting things with these mechanics
But I feel like there is enough material here to work with
That he can definitely come up with something and that thing again with like the moving heart at the end
Which is the physical manifestation of the theme that like your control can be wrestled from your choices don't matter
It's a video game. Ah, the only way to win is not to play. Ah, you could definitely
You know pull up pull a spec ops the line sort of thing with that or something the way and uh
My position basically I've been wanting to say this but I kept forgetting
Just I don't think toby fox can
Disappoint me. I'm at this point
It's just like because the reason I like undertone and I like delta rune is because it has the toby fox flare
It has his sort of like a quirky humor and just the little
Sort of things without in like for instance when I got jailed in in delta room and I ate the moss and I put the shackles on
And I'll say commented on it. I found it so funny. It was like you're like you could eat the moss
Yeah, you can eat the moss and then so I didn't know yeah, and the susie says like oh, you didn't even leave any for me
There's so much love and I love his artistic voice
So that's that is a lot agreed a hundred percent
So because it was it's a toby fox game
I don't think he can disappoint me to the extent where I would be
Upset about it. Even if it's the game is not as great as undertale. It was or you know mage
That's that makes a lot of sense
I I guess it's just fair to state that like some people have different hopes and expectations for what you know
This game may or may not be in terms of like mechanical complexity. I mean, I sure have some high hopes about that
I think a lot of people will enjoy delta rune for same reasons why they might have enjoyed undertale
And that is I wouldn't say surface level because that's an inherently derogatory sort of like
Oh, you're just enjoying it on the surface level
But I just mean the art the visuals and the sort of dialogue that you hear from the players
I think a lot of people will enjoy it
You're solely based on those aesthetics and the voice of toby as you said
Yeah, and I personally had absolutely no issue with it being an alternate universe because I like seeing the characters that I love
Living their happy little lives in but they aren't the characters you love. They're different. That's true. I know
I mean, they're wearing their skin
Well, it's called. Well, it's called. I mean, I called it an alternate universe for a reason
It's you're not the exact same characters, but there's like they look the same
But it's a different universe where they didn't have to go through the whole
Nonstance that they had to go through
So I still think it's interesting to see characters who look exactly like other characters that you've read and you know
Got to bond with except now they're different and sly and sometimes well
Luckily, that's a very small portion of the game that you don't need to worry about that much because the rest of the game is different
Don't don't confuse me
I with with other people here. I'm not saying I'm not saying that this is a large complaint from me
I don't even think it's really a huge complaint. I am more so on the camp that I just think it's weird
I don't really get where it's coming from. It's not
Odd curiosity that's that's that's where my beginning and end of that comes from
um, I think oh
sorry, I thought I was fucking mouthful, but
Get that dick out of your mouth digi
Take the words out of my mouth. I love dick
uh
The thing about it for me and the reason I've been so emphatic about
Why I wish he would have said something is that I don't mind that it's the same characters because
I feel like I totally get that as somebody who um, like mage said earlier has
Has a stable of character. So I've tried to put in a lot of different stories because
I look at it as that
generally with artists
Your characters all represent a part of your psyche
Like most of the characters that you write are bound to represent something about yourself some way that you think like
I tend to look at a cast of characters
It's like if you are a prism through which a beam of light is being cast then
You know all the characters are the different colors that are refracted through that prism
um
So like and generally when you look at an artist's work you can often say like oh this character
It's just an xb for that character, you know to use tv tropes terminology
um
So rather than create like major saying rather than create a character who everyone's just going to say
Oh, this is just the sands of this game. Just use sands again. He's the best representation of that part of your mind and like
Undertale is already a universe that allows for so much that he could
Like portray these characters as best. Maybe he imagines them
um
So like that part of it. I feel like it wouldn't have even been a
A fraction of a question in anyone's mind had he just said from the start
It's an alternate universe guys
Undertale doesn't matter and like I guess nobody would have said a damn thing. I I mean
I'm slightly with Nate here. I mean pretty Nate with I'm pretty with Nate here
I didn't really think like I just assumed it was an alternate timeline and that it wouldn't really like I
I could instantly tell this isn't a sequel in the sense that this is
I don't I wasn't expecting it was a sequel
It's just that it's clearly an alternate timeline
But without knowing distinctly because toby fox says in his tweet longer
Like don't worry about your ending to undertale
Everybody in undertale is fine and that's that's not affected by actually they're they're exactly as dead or alive as you left them
Right, right exactly exactly
So so like uh, they're they're fine either living their lives are dead and buried like you left them, you know, that's that's that's fine
but
Because I understood that they were alternate universes. My question was this okay. How is this connected?
But if I had read that tweet before I'm like, oh, it's not connected
They're just the same and that that changes how you think about them. Now again, this is a tiny complaint
I don't know why we're focusing so much not about it, but like that's my position
That's because it's it's weirdly fascinating because it's just the fact that look it's not even that like playing this game
I thought it's not that I thought it was a sequel or a prequel
It's not that I thought it would have relevance to the actual story of undertale
It's that when you see these characters it makes you think that the game will be like
Undertale that it will like like like ben said we spent the whole game waiting for the other shoe to drop
And if he came out and said it's not like undertale, you wouldn't have been waiting for that
You wouldn't have been thinking. Oh, it has to have it has to be meta. It has to be crazy
I mean that heart moving thing at the end is kind of that shoe dropping
If it is, I mean that could very well be but like he even says
In the tweet longer like I don't think I'll ever be able to make you feel that way again
And I don't know how much of that is him being humble or literal like it's impossible to know before we get full day
I was waiting for I was waiting for a moment like when flowery suddenly flowery's face changes and suddenly he's attacking you
And you realize that like you've been tricked. I mean I was waiting for that like
The whole game
Or something the notion of whatever like lack of control whatever you your choice don't matter
Sounds to me just like a bad game
But I just believe that's why I think I think he must
Subvert it like that's not a theme like that's not a theme that is like
A game where your choices don't impact the ending like let's explore that like what no, that's dumb
Like that's that's one of those uh jokes on you
I was just pretending to be retarded
The reason why I'm so fascinated with this relation to undertale and the fact he uses themed characters
Is because even though I now know after reading the tweet longer the somewhat the quality the chronology
Of you know, it was delta and then came undertale and you know delta was first
It feels on the surface of it and I'm really I'm crazy for this as a sort of you know marketing corporate thing
You know I'm making a new game, but undertale is really popular
Let me put in the old characters. So it'll spread the word around like hey
Stay today. Hey Steve. Did you hear that sands is back sands is back
I say dropping all of my groceries to run home pretty good for that though. The fact that literally was planned this way
I understand. Okay. That's what like again. Why why would you start talking if I'm still in the middle of my point?
Why why would you do that? I'm sorry? It's just that waking up in the bed that the last game ended in is just like
You didn't have the same bed though. I'm not even talking about that
I'm saying that it just is interesting the fact that this came first even though on the surface
I would think that it was a marketing thing and now the fact now that that has taken away from me
I am just confused at the point of him doing it like this now that we that it's revealed like oh, yeah
Like he's really into this. He just really likes having the same characters there
I know what you're all saying like oh, it's fun to see characters in a different life
But I just don't resonate with that whatsoever. I think it's extremely confusing
I'm saying the same thing as you like there's no reason it had to be this confusing like
Literally if it had started in any other way
Then that undertale ends with you being tucked in by toriel and
Delta rune opens with you being woken up by toriel if it opened in any other way
It would have been a thousand times less confusing
Chris which is a new name
Not even the one it is fucking totally irrelevant to the fact that it's like you could do
Anything else you could do anything else you could start off in a forest you can start off in a city
You can start off anywhere other than a bed being woken up by the character who tucked you in at the end of the last game
And it wouldn't have been as confusing. I get it. I think that it's pretty minor like because again
Frisk has a canon name and chris also has a canon name and they're not the same name
The fact that it ends
Okay, maybe this is just a way that that my mind works
But like if you're gonna do
Parallelism if you're going to do a juxtapit like if you're gonna do the same fucking scene
That the last game ended on as the start of your game. You're making a statement there. Are these intentional?
Or is this just the way toby fox writes his undertale games?
No, it's intentional. He definitely wanted you to be confused by the start of this game
That's why he put out don't anybody talk about it for the first 24 hours guys
Nobody spoil anything even though it's irrelevant to the original game. There is nothing to spoil in this fucking thing
That was another point I wanted to make it's very weird that on the main site of delt ruin
It says this is an experience for people who have finished undertale yet undertale has no but rare
Relevance to this story whatsoever. Well, I mean there is the asriel reveal. That's that's not even a reveal
It
This game has literally no
Well, if you have no connection to undertale then the fact that we recognize the face of that character like wouldn't make sense
It wouldn't first okay first of all we don't because we've never seen that sprite before we can kind of infer that it's probably asriel
I think
What having what having okay?
If this is an experience for people who have finished undertale
Then I think that what that must mean is that like if you finished undertale
You will surely recognize that ralse is an anagram of asriel
And you will probably guess that he is asriel before the end of the game
And then when he takes off the mask you'd be like, oh, yep. Mm-hmm
Um, even though that makes no sense based on the other things that the other characters say you will
That will probably I mean, that's it. That's like the only real connection to undertale that I can see
Okay, I have and even that is confused and I and I feel like I can't even speak any further on it because I clearly
Missing information do you think do you think the point of all this stuff?
Because now now that nade has told me you can move the heart at the end at the end of the game
Is all of this meant for the player?
Right like like I mean, of course it is but what I mean to say is that
Everything that's happening like the reveal of taking off as like, oh, it looks like asriel
That's for you everything that happening in universe like it's not addressed, right?
And then at the end of the game it's like, oh, you're just the heart the character
You're playing as isn't you in this world the world's just happening
And you're along for the ride and that's why all these weird things that like we understand as a player
Like oh, that's the character from the other game
And like this is a situation that explains something from the other game kind of but how it's connected like all of that
Is like on a different level than all the actual events in the game itself
That's a good point. They're there. I mean we we don't have all the information
There's definitely he is stated this game is for people who've played undertale
The fact that we recognize all these characters and that is that is a separate thing from the people in the game that
I mean, I'm just saying that could be intentional and could build to something
Um, I'm I'm still waiting. I'm still waiting for that shooter drop. I am I mean when when when you told us about the heart thing
We were kind of mind-blown, but I feel like
That's the kind of detail only an undertale superfan would notice. That's me, right?
Like you got to be somebody who is expecting
More out of every single second of the game, which yeah, how much fun is that to find and be the one you discover these things?
It is it is fantastic those things exist. But it also makes me think about the fact that in
Normally in art
When somebody makes something that is so personal that nobody else can understand it unless they dig as deep as they can
That's called autism
Like when you when when when someone makes a
35-minute analysis of why a sonic game story is actually super deep. Yeah, like we call that autism
And we laugh at it and we say it's bad storytelling and like if you do it. Well, it's fine. It's not bad
Or it's not it's just it's not I'm not even calling it bad. It's just like a matter of
We didn't see this heart move moment and it's so easy to play this game and not notice that and like
That's at the end of three fucking hours
You know like for I don't know I tend to look at art in a more like I I tend to measure it more in like time for
dollars kind of way like
if
If every moment of my experience is great
I give it a 10 out of 10 if
One moment was amazing enough to make up for a bunch of
Parts I didn't care that much about. Yeah, it might be a more fair trade
I'm just looking at this game and I'm like is is the fact that you can move the heart at the end and that like
Oh, there's confirmation. There is more going on. Is that enough to offset the feelings?
I had of three and a half hours of going
Eh
Nothing really going on in this game
It doesn't it doesn't greatly improve my like experience of chapter one. It just makes me more hopeful that
Because I have tons of hope for like this is a full game
I think like I have no real reason to doubt that toby could make a great game
But when I watched this chapter one, nothing grabbed me nothing grabbed me the way that undertale did
I feel a little grabbed by this heart reveal
Um, like by the end of the by the end of chapter one my expectations were pretty low like I
felt like I felt like maybe toby was setting up for like
Okay
So all of this is just to say that these undertale characters are not the same and this will not be an undertale ask experience
This will be a new and like this will be a new like totally linear
Totally YA level, uh, you know story about like a mew and a mean bully like going into an alice in wonderland world together
And we will have episodic adventures where that happens and you will fucking like it
Um, and I was and I and I was a little crestfallen by this
I didn't feel that cynical about it because just the fact that susie
Could attack enemies and you had to stop her like
Yeah, that's something that felt so that felt like a mechanic that you could do so much with
that like to think that
That the game that this chapter didn't do that much with it and like we know what toby can do. So it's like
There's no way he wouldn't explore this to a more full extent. Yes
I kind of got the impression from chapter one to made as episode two
Hey, oh my god, welcome. Welcome to episode two waifus now that we've done episode one episode two waifus
my new waifu susie from delta room
minus rules card
I love him. Oh, you know, I I I it took me a while to figure out that that you whose name you were saying mage
Just because the way I know I had such a hard time spelling it. Who is it? I don't even know what you're talking about
It's the it's the traps or the uh, the puzzle master
Yeah
He's cool. He's cool. Also, is he gassed out? Is he literally gaster? No, he's not gaster. It looks kind of like gaster
I'm just saying it does look kind of like all right. I got a hot take. I got a hot undertale take laid on me
I love delta rune because other characters are nice and cool and it's really cute and stuff
Yeah undertale. Here's my hot take. I think undertale strengths were all way always the characters
And and the story and and the meta gimmicks and and and like the the the world bending stuff was like
It's nice, but I don't care if it's not in this new game. I care, you know
hippo, I'm really glad you brought that perspective up because
um
That's the biggest disconnect that I think there is between two different camps of undertale fans. We're like
For me, it's like all I care about is the meta stuff and the characters did very little for me
Whereas I feel like the vast majority of people who like undertale mostly like it for the characters and
Like the meta was kind of secondary to them like most people like the game because they think that dating papyrus was a great
Yeah, yeah, I mean that I don't really care about that particularly. I'm not gay guys
But um like the the way that toby writes is is funny and quirky and nice and cute
And I like it and the characters that he writes are the characters that the sort of
Sort of characters that I like
And and I like stories and stuff and I've been burned by steven universe not existing
And I've blown through adventure time and that's over and I'm sad because though that's a good show
But there's no shows there's no shows that exist that are good and deltarune is like, oh, this is not this is like well written
Like like, you know cliche story a little bit of a cliche story like like oh
it's a
Something or other somebody changes their tune and it's you know
But like it works and it's effective and I just don't get enough of it nowadays
I just don't get enough of just good stories that are just told. Well, I like it
I'm on I'm on board with this. That's that's kind of where I wanted to go
I can't tell the difference between nowadays and before days because I'm constantly watching old shit. So
Oh, well, I I completely growthy hippo and a lot of my enjoyment from undertale was also the characters
I would say it's more about a 50-50 split maybe a little bit more of the meta because I'm a homestuck boy
But I did quite enjoy the characters and all of the quirky dialogue scenes and stuff such as that
I would say the only difference here is I don't really resonate with the characters from deltarune
And I don't really think that's an issue per se. I just find them not as interesting as you know
Sands and empires and stuff like that. I don't know if I'm really going to say that's the reason why I don't like it
We got we got uh, we got susie who's literally just nelson months
She's yep. She's good. I like susie. Yeah better than nelson. Well nelson doesn't particularly fleshed out
I mean susie at least has an arc. Nate. Okay. I don't think you remember. I don't think you remember
Nelson has a lot of fleshing out throughout this the the many seasons
Then I think maybe you give nelson credit. You know what that's fair. Is that the fucking the
You know, what's funny is the only name in my mind was Seinfeld
and
uh
I know it's simpsons now that you've said the ha ha noise
I'm drunk as shit by the way. Okay, that's cool. All right. Did you just wake up is
No, dude. I've been up forever. Oh sleep means nothing sleep is a whole other world to me
It's like a whole other different universe. Okay. Um, you know, when I read the comedy scenes in undertale
My impression is like, huh, that was clever
I like them a lot. I really like the writing. Yeah, I love toby's writing toby's writing is great
Toby's characters are great. It's it's all very intelligent
It's all smart and funny and I look at it and I think that sure is smart and funny
The the I think the funniest moment in uh
Undertale was the part where you are in like the glowing
Place with like the glowing water
Yeah, and you walk up you go like to like a little side path and you find the little bird
And the little bird like oh, yeah flies you across the tiny little gap with like the heroic music playing
Yeah, that was great. That was really good. That was really funny
The dialogue jokes and stuff are like I I guess it's that like homestuck's comedy is I mean, uh,
Fucking undertale's comedy is homestuck. Same thing. Yeah, that's what I meant to say, but like
Distilled like yeah, it's homestuck. Homestuck is explosive and constant all over the place
Like it covers every base imaginable and it's so long and it goes in so many directions and undertale is like
Drawing a through line through that
Undertale is is more pop than boogie and homestuck is more boogie than pop or whatever
That's a perfect description. I was gonna use the word normie, but you got me in an even better terminologies. Thank you
Well, I just want to say
That I definitely I don't know. I agree with munchie. I care about both
I the thing is I absolutely love all the writing and jokes. I like
A lot of people get turned off by like tumblr enus of undertale doesn't happen to me. I love everything about it
I don't even think it's as tumblr as people think it is. I agree
There is there is a little bit of like like bait for certain types of people
I mean, I still think it's weird that undine and alphys are kind of like I don't get the connection
But like whatever. I don't care. It's fine. It's fine. I mean, okay
I feel like tumblr
Poisoned the well in this case because like I've been into lesbians and like gay shit
Since way before tumblr because I too have like have had
Gender identity issues long before that was popular to have
Before it was like a codified thing where it was like, hey support me on patreon because I'm not sure if I'm a boy or a girl
Like yeah, like I had those issues before that was the thing. So like I feel like
Undertale speaks
I don't feel like toby is doing it to cash in on a trend or like he only he only writes lesbians into a story
Because he reads tumblr guys like no, I think he he has a better appreciation than that
But it's kind of just in that world. I do wish that it was less like a
fucking
Virgin gay boys idea of it. Like I I want some hard fucking
You know, it's not that kind of story. That's that's really all there is to every story should be that kind of story
I'm trying to say
Hey, fine final point. This is really my final point on this on this whole thing. It's that
unequivocally in my in my humble opinion the demo from
Undertale was way better. I do think that's true
Don't think that's debatable in in every way except visually because deltarune has some incredible visuals the sprite work is off the charts
I absolutely my favorite sprite work is when the main character points in battle and there's little sparkles when he's commanding
It is gorgeous. It is gorgeous and I love the battle aesthetic is really nice
Yeah, it's great and I love that it's it's in world battle arenas. You don't final fancy teleport to another one
It's just it's chrono trigger rules
fantastic sublime
Is that true? I didn't pick up on that. Yeah. Yeah, you watching someone play the game. No, that might only be in some areas
It's only in some areas of very normal enemies. You just transport to a computer
Synthwave, but for bosses you go in
In the world. I hope it does more of that. Hope it does more of that stuff. Um, uh, but uh, uh,
Right, I just I want more meta stuff
I believe in toby my faith is restored and I just I need him to deliver some but I believe that he will that's
I think this could I mean I think that this game can be amazing. I don't know whether you probably talked about this
Well, but um
Sorry, there's a lot of lag happening. Um
The speaking of like faith restore and toby. I am just happy like regardless of like the quality of this this deltarune
I'm happy that I know what he's doing and then he's doing something me too
We were we were talking in the chat the other day and devoo say that we're all a bunch of assholes when this came out
But that's fine. Uh, we were just saying how man like what the fuck's toby up to can't wait for him to milk undertale forever
And never do anything and then this drops out of the fucking blue
Blowing me the fuck out my blowing my asshole wide open like a blooming onion from outback steakhouse
and I just want to say that
I have been deeply inspired by
Toby's commitment to his artistic vision with this shit and the fact that he's a one-man team
He's got temi on sprite work. He's been he's sucking japanese cock all day. He loves his japshit
With the translation and I don't know. He just seems really into it. Also. He's learning japanese. He's a hero
He's a hero this guy. Did you know about the fact that he interviewed zune?
What I had no fucking idea. He interviewed somebody linked it to us in uh, I am games
Yeah, he like met zune who was like who found out about undertale because people are like
This is like toho and they sent it to him and like he did an interview with him and like
Apparently he's like a huge fanboy of perfect cherry blossom
Yeah, yeah, those two together is such a perfect like those two fucking indie heroes basically
Yeah, I just maybe i'm exaggerating a little bit to call toby hero, but i'm reading his twit longer
He's definitely indy. Well, the only reason I say that when he was making undertale
He was definitely an underdog hero now. He's like he's successful, right? I'm sure he could ride
Indy hero. He is soon as fucking successful
I mean that's true
I'm just saying like like I was gonna say that like the fact that toby is like guys. I want to make this project
I have a vision. I don't know if it's even possible to make my vision
That is an inspiring thought and he's like i'm going to try
I'm gonna try to make a team to make it happen and i'm just like fuck. Yes
This is what I this man should be doing
This is what everybody should be doing. Yeah, if you can afford it, which he can thank god
More so than the game itself like that twit longer spoke to me a lot and like it made me
Even though I didn't it didn't make me love the game more, but it made me empathize with him more
as like when he said when he like the ball drops and he's like look
Like when I made the undertale demo was to prove to myself
I could do this game in a short amount of time
This demo took me years to make and like
He's straight up like some of it is because of the fact that it's aesthetically way more
It's got a lot. It's a lot more complex
And he had to set everything for the future in this if he ends up more
So he had to plan a lot. Yeah, but he also mentions like loss of enthusiasm in the project
Like at some point it's like hey, this is taking too fucking long. I'm he probably has had better ideas
He's probably just through sheer force of aging looked at this and said like I'm getting less and less interested as I go and like
He set a definitive amount of time of how long he's willing to work on a project
Seven years seven years is the maximum and he's like and consider three of those years are already up
You know, imagine seven years making a game and then you decide. Well, no, it's a bust. That's I'm calling it here
Yeah, someone's really done. I don't believe it
I mean Duke Nuke forever took 12 years to make
It started and stopped many times though. I mean for different companies and shit, but but like I just think of of tobi like
Like if he builds this team and he makes the game that will be great
If he doesn't I'll be equally excited that like it failed and he moved on to the next thing
Like it's kind of weird
When he was working like when I first found out that this was like Undertale 2
I was disappointed because I was like I would rather tobi be doing something else
Like this this man has shown us so much talent in undertale
Why would he chain himself to the same characters in the same world?
but then like
When he explained that it's not
Undertale 2 that he wrote this so long ago. I was like, okay, I get it. This guy isn't
He's not boundlessly creative. He's a man with a with a very specific something
He has to get off his chest. I feel more like you know, like it wasn't that undertale was
Born from him being somebody who's like, I'm gonna play with the meta of games and that's my career
It's more like he had something specific to say with these characters and they they represent something to him
to an extent that he would use them again, but
Like and then to hear him say like
Yeah, this idea in spite of being maybe less complex than the other idea
To like thematically is more complex in terms of design and therefore it will take longer and is harder to do
Yeah, it's it's uh, it's fascinating
I I just want to mention uh homestuck took seven years to be finished. So I think that's where he got that number from
Ha, maybe that is wait. Did it take only seven years? Yep
It felt like a lifetime
Act six was what four of those years wait, it took me it took me seven years just to read it
Wait, homestuck started in 20
2011 right no nine
Oh, okay, okay, that makes more sense. I was confused. I was like, what the fuck how could it have ended last year?
Hey, by the way, uh, just small point. I went and I read we were arguing about like the genocide ending how it ends
Uh, uh, me and mage and uh, I did look it up. I did look it up and what it says is uh, uh that
Like so susie does something the king falls asleep and then, uh, uh ralze walks over
They say that i'm surprised you remembered my pacify spell
So maybe she like told her to use it or something either way you got used maybe susie didn't literally learn it
Yeah, because it was it happened off-screen and we didn't see who used it and that's that's true. That's true. Yeah
Okay, so fair enough a small point, but I just yeah, yeah, yeah, it's good to have a resolution
Some sort of resolution. I'm sure they appreciate that
I mean, uh, yeah, I mean that pretty much sums it up for me guys. Uh, anybody have any other comments?
Hey, how about that how about that ending song with uh with the lady singing?
Oh, I hate it. It was it was reminding me that like a huge part of why I have so much respect for undertale and
Also deltardune is that the music is so fucking. Yeah, it was awesome
Like no matter what I could say about story mechanics, whatever it doesn't matter toby fox is an amazing fucking musician
That nobody can take that from him ever that battle thing
Nate
We were talking about two different things the smash thing. Oh, yeah, you smash the yeah, yeah
I was I was talking about the smash. I was talking about that. I wasn't talking about the the deltardune Indian song
That's what i'm saying like that. I didn't like the deltardune ending song. I don't like it. It's weird
Like fantasy. I want chip tunes. I want chip tunes toby. I don't want these fucking human voices in my goddamn undertale
Give me what I want. Give me what I want toby
It made sense to parallel to the original game because that was the like it had live guitars in the ending and everything
That's true. That's true. Yeah, he was doing a thing there. He just wanted that extra little punch
Oh, that's some kingdom hearts shit. I think he got um, I kind of love kingdom hearts
Speaking of kingdom hearts, that's the answer. Ralsei is just azrael's nobody
Yeah, Ralsei's azrael's nobody that's that's
Oh my god
Oh my god, light and dark light and dark
Just for fun. Uh, did you guys know so I I played everything I did everything, uh, you know pacifist and and aggressor whatever if you fight
Um, uh, the the secret boss the the devil which I love and is hilarious
Um, if you fight him and you defeat him with pacifism whatever something it doesn't matter
But when you defeat him with attacking and aggression
He tells you that the knight, you know, like the the boss that started the well and is like doing stuff
There's there's a mention of the knight is the one who's like doing shit
Actually in in that boss when you genocide fight this guy. He actually mentioned there's a queen who's coming back
So just so you know, there's a yas queen that the knight is actually acting on behalf of who seems like they're probably gonna be the real
Villain, so
Yep, yas queen. It's gonna be hillary. Can't wait. Can't wait seven years from now
Okay, you can't you can't die tom. You're not yet not until delta room
I heard actually I was on a thread and on v and someone's like, uh hate life want to die
No good video games, uh delta room comes out says it's going to be seven years till the game's like god damn it
I want it to die toby. Why won't you let me die?
Pretty good
All right. Well, I mean that's so wait is is this like a single topic episode or can we talk about smash direct?
Well, oh, let's we have only we have only talked about delta room, but we are not
Legally bound to it. If you want to talk about the smash direct. I say, let's do it. I'm shocked. It's shocked. Oh, right
I'm sitting was it to not have a new adventure mode. I understand that making the subsystem is
Substitutes a mysterious locker. I said it was the equivalent to make an entirely separate game
That was half of brawl development. I understand that it was a big idea, you know
And we're taking a lot of work to make all those fmv's
Uh, but
In male a's adventure mode was good enough male a's adventure mode was you were walking around in a world
You know first episode or sorry the first level
It's like you're playing a mario game and you can play a chic or you can play a zelder
You can play whoever and it was good enough. You just would go through these nintendo worlds
It was way shorter than brawls and it was could have been easily doable by the what?
900 billion people they have working on this fucking video game
So there is something though. I mean there literally is a kind of mode with world of light. Do you know that it's not that?
Well, I don't think we really know right now. Okay. Okay. I have seen no footage of a level in the sense of
Not a fight, but you know you were progressing from one side of the screen to the other and there are obstacles in the way
I have seen exactly zero of that in any of the trailers
And what it seems to be is that there's a giant world map and you interact with this world map
The world map is you know
Painted and it looks nice and there's all these different video game elements in it
However, you are merely playing a mini game walk around the map press some buttons on this over world
And then the actual gameplay is sometimes you will come across a person who you have to defeat in a
Combat scenario, so I have seen no evidence that it is like Maly's is just a sort of weird
Yeah, it's like a weird
Maybe almost mario party-esque like the fights of minigames and moving around on a board
I would describe it like that
Well, but the only thing is maybe there are still cool like there is at least that intro
Story thing where all the characters get blasted by light and I'd like to point out
Not every character was in that trailer. Does that imply that there's characters elsewhere who are not dead?
I mean like cloud wasn't in that where's cloud. I don't know
Yeah, the thing is there like a story that's gonna happen with him elsewhere. I don't know with the with the smash direct
There's there's like
Oh, I like smash. I I'm interested to see what's what's coming up
And then like the direct was just like a really terrible presentation like you can get annoyed about the presentation of that direct
And I did and I was yeah, well, what do you mean?
What I know about the game. Oh shit, right? What I what I know about the game is that there may be
Something resembling some sort of subspace emissary-esque thing with some amount of cutscenes
I don't know enough about it yet to actually like that
But that's all I wanted from a new smash game is a is a is cutscenes where the characters interact with each other
And and and they look at each other and it's like, uh, they're running
They're running that they're together
Samus and Pikachu you know stuff like that. It was so cool. We got a little of it at the beginning that cut that movie
We got we got that big. I mean, they've done so many promotional cutscenes that I
I really hope it's not all just for promotional reasons. That's what it was with the last game. So
You know
Where's gino guys? Where's gino? Why isn't he in the game cracks just sips monster energy drink?
Where's gino?
I'm about to say something more that will definitely make a few of you in the chat angry
And I'm definitely not saying that smash should not exist in the form that it has and there are a
Remiss any of the decisions that had led to this point
However, there is a small part of me that thinks
Some of the worst things about
Smash on a gameplay level is the fact that it's a crossover series
This is not to say that I don't cherish again the subspace emissary
Again to see these characters who you love interact in various different ways with people from other franchises
However, I will just say that as a
fighting game person as a person who enjoys the gameplay of smash
I I start talking and everyone starts booing in the audience who all hate super smash brothers. Yeah. Yeah, okay
I get I know I know it's not fighting games a part of the game
But someone who does I would say it's always very weird to me when people are like, yes
More players like more characters. Yes. We just need gino
But there's no one actually saying like hey, let's have like a new like, you know, let's have a new brawler type character
Let's have a new, uh, you know actually talking about their gameplay mechanics
I'm just talking about how it's a cool character that you like from other games
I'm so with you because like
Where do you fucking stock?
Where do you fucking stop the buck on that shit? Never you never stop it. That's the deal
There's like 45 fucking characters in smash. Like there are 74 characters confirmed 75
Fucking that's the most in any fighting game ever
Like you know, it'd be even better 75 75 would be even better with the plant. So, uh, you know beyond that like
Literally and you know what? It's great. Not only five is a new high
You could go on forever. Like there is no character. He can introduce that will satisfy me over the character
I wanted to be in like yeah, it's impossible for everybody. It's like
Fucking piranha plant really it's like
Well, what did you want asshole and then you get 35 different answers goku, you know, we gotta put them all in
Yeah, the Grinch
I've never been like interested in in the characters that come out
It's it's really just like it's the same with deltarune
Like I don't really like playing the game smash that much
I just remember the subspace adversary being a crossover and I love crossovers and I love characters and I love character interactions
I love those cutscenes for all those reasons because they they made
Like they made the idea of playing with these these, you know toys
3d digital toys
Like controlling them and having them like be real
Like that was the aspect of of smash that I always liked playing it
It's hard and I'm bad at it and I suck and I don't like it and
and you know, it's
Like all the characters in the world could be in it
I just
I don't care. I love I just quickly wanted to check the reason I'm being quiet is because I never played those games
Never gonna play those games completely not interested. That's why I'm fascinating. So
It's such a rare opinion
Yeah, I've literally never heard that opinion before I've heard even tom who
abjectly
Doesn't like smash, but I've never heard no interest and never played smash
Well, there I am here. I go. It is a nintendo thing to me the degree of which I just care about more characters realized
In the smash bros universe, you know, whatever. I want my gino guys, you know reuse cool incinero or whatever all these new
When will you accept that gino is a
Super fucking obscure character and I accept that
I also accept the fact that sakurai has specifically said that he'd like to put him in in the past
And he's also fairly popular in north american polls. So, you know, these are
What is sakurai's relevance
He's makes the game. Yeah, what makes which game super smash bros god did what
What?
That's the man. I thought sakurai was the final fantasy guy. No, that is. No, it's tatsuya. Nomura a.k.a.
Sakaguchi, I think it was sakaguchi. Sakaguchi, that's something. Okay. Well, that's the relevance. He is the man making the game
Go man, that's that's gonna. I'm sorry. Nate. That's gonna be a major. Go man. Now. Say I'm
It's spreading like like everyone fucking played like everyone with a super nintendo played mario rpg
Everybody fucking love. Look, I'm not true. What are you talking about?
Let's not pretend that gino is like someone that we that everyone is clamoring for across the world
I I get it. I have played mario rpg and not even made it far enough to see gino
I I bet I I mean, I wouldn't be surprised if more people alive today meaning millennials and no one else
Played mario rpg then played. I don't know
Castlevania one or two. What maybe that was playing today, right?
Uh, yeah, I don't know. That's a big oof for me there, ben, but uh, you think so you don't think so
I'm gonna look at the sales of each right now. Uh, I would like to point out as a smash boy
That smash bros was not originally smash bros
It was dragon king the fighting game
And it was a game made specifically just for the mechanics
Because it was iwata and sakura being like, hey man fighting games are all the exact same fighting games are the same
Let's make a new fighting game. That's different. And so they made smash and it's a beautiful game with beautiful mechanics
Where it's not just fighting, but you know health bar goes down
It's you know, you're racking up damage and hit them off the screen with the beautiful airtight controls
And it was incredible and they're like, hey, uh, no one's gonna like this game. How do we market it?
Uh, just fucking put mario in there, bro. Haha. Yes
Number one most successful game ever except for poke. I'm saying
I'm not saying that I hate smash or anything. I love smash. It's one of my favorite games
She's of all time
I love playing as kirby because I am kirby and i'm not upset like just want to make sure
Like guys don't vote me out of the office. I just think it would be cool if the smash genre wasn't relegated just do smash
And yeah, I know about rivals of aether. Yeah, okay. I know about rivals of aether. I know the other ones
But okay tbh who gives a shit fucking roll owned
Do you like that kirby is canonically confirmed to be the most powerful, uh, uh person in the game?
He's just like the only survivor from the no, he's just he's just the first
Yeah, I mean he was riding a war star. I guess I'm so on it. I'm about to slam myself here, dude
Because fucking apparently according to vg charts with the z dot com
Uh
Super mario rpg sold 2.14 million games and the highest selling castlevania symphony in the night is 1.27 million
That's fucking crazy castlevania seems so beloved and talked about
I certainly love it. All right. That well it is. I'm just uh
Mario rpg is talked about and beloved and and uh and not to mention it's part of the mario franchise
Which is just a huge advantage. I have not even seen one analysis video about super mario rpg. It's coming. There are best game ever
Super mario rpg legend of seven stars will be here one day. Wait for it. I did a g rpg on that. Oh, yeah
No, it will. Oh wait, that's right. That's right. Hippo did two g rpg on it
Well, that's I've seen so many about like mario and luigi and shit and mario is great. It's good
Uh, that yeah, uh, all right. I have a question. I have a I have a thought piece
Um
Would you prefer if you could only have one or the other would you prefer gino to be in smash?
Or for gino to come back for another game installment in the super mario rpg franchise
That involves weighing my my faith in nintendo as a development company to make another good j rpg
And I do not have that faith. So I mean look at cloud like. Oh my god guys
We're getting a final fantasy seven reboot. Uh, I would much rather just have them in smash and just like have the cloud
I remember and respect as opposed to the bastardization that we'll be in the remake. So, you know, that's pretty much how I
That's that's true. I'm just saying if that implies that like a direct sequel in the vein of mario rpg would come out
I would acquit like yeah. Yes. No, don't interrupt the perfect ending of mario rpg. It's perfect as it is
Well, nate. I mean like the mario games all take place in the same continuity
and like so like having a sequel to it would not ruin it any more than
I don't know fucking
Fucking any of the other ones. You know, they're all they're all mario games. There's there's what like 30 years of baggage now
Let's let's you already have a fucking mind's blowing. You heard those in numbers. I said before, right? Yeah, uh
What do you think is the best-selling mario rpg?
mario and luigi bowser's inside story. That's my guess
You are correct bowser
Bowser's inside story with 3.77 million
Jillian guys
Bowser's not sorry. It's a good fucking game. Literally stop hating for no reason
Saga being 2.1 and super mario. Okay. Well super paper mario for the we is the highest selling of the paper mario with 3.37
Actually, that might even top bowser. That's not unfortunate. That's a good game before look. It's good
But it's not as good as the other mario. I would say it's equal. It's just different
Okay, it should have said it should have stayed a spin-off. It shouldn't have decided the course of things
I'm gonna need a guide for mario and luigi and super paper mario because like everyone's opinions is vastly
Oh, oh, did you all get with the real shit? That's not fucking fake. Oh the only the only good mario luigi game is the first one
Yeah, all right. Yeah, correct. Yeah, accurate statement. Well, the first three are all great
The first three are all classic games
You should play the first three and then literally everything after that is a dumpster fire and terrible do not agree on that
The first and and similarly very similarly paper mario the first three are all great
Here's the difference between the paper mario games paper mario 64 is like a cozy experience when you play with the lights off
And you're in bed. It's a pretty slow experience
But it's kind of quirky in the same way that dealt to ruin. Oh callback is
paper mario 2
Paper mario 2 is sort of like a more action-packed version of paper mario 1
It's got which looks way better. It looks beautiful
There's a ton of interesting gameplay mechanics
And you play if you want to have a good video game experience and the worlds are also super interesting
Super paper mario is a great game as well with a bunch of it's not it's not an rpg in the same way that the other two are
It's like an action rpg where you move around the world
But it's got a really interesting aesthetic a great story and it just is a generally good spin-off video game that you should play as well
Paper mario super paper jam is a terrible game and it sucks. It makes absolutely no sense
Paper jam
Yeah, or what's it called sticker sticker star sticker stars the first one. I like paper jam paper jam is a thing
It's like mar it was a mar a paper mario 3 printer error. No, no, that's actually a thing. Uh, it's uh, mario and luigi paper jam
It's not paper jam
Wait, oh, do you guys know what is the best selling game with all time?
It's a bad game isn't it? Yeah mickey mouse steamboat will it's like a new game right? It's like it's like a new game
It's we we sports all right because there was one for we or something
8.2 million
We would like to know 82. I meant to say 82.6
82 okay. Hey going back to munchies point. I just want to say about about the smash thing
Uh, I am somebody who would sacrifice
Any degree of like balance or any of that fighting game bullshit just to get one new character
Because I don't give a shit about I just want characters. That's all I care about
Look, I'll I'll adapt man. Whatever. Whatever. It's fine. I don't care
The meta's gonna be what it's gonna be. Yeah, I'll just adapt. Why would they not add susie to smash?
Why?
Why this there was this the cryptic 24 hour thing and it was gonna coincide the smash
Oh, oh susie is gonna be in smash because delta rune's new and it's like a promotional thing. Oh, it's it's confirmed
I want it. I want it. What if he really he releases the delta rune chapter one and it's just a like side story
Explaining how sands found a poor magic portal that transported into smash
How is there nobody from golden sun?
That he's been confirmed as an assist trophy isaac tragically. He's uh, Nate. I mean, I know you like golden sun
But you are literally the only person I know who has ever played golden sun. I played golden sun one and two
Golden sun was my first video game at not literally but my first rpg is the first game I cared about
Okay, it's it's actually a fascinating story. Uh, because because here's the thing about golden sun
It is fairly well known and reasonably liked. Here's what I think the reason is why like I was a deeply beloved
I would say it's by by some that's true. Um, and it pulls all right in the polls
But like I think the reason why Isaac is not a care is not a playable character is because
Camelot the developer
It's it's because the series like they just like if they put Isaac in that alone
I think would catapult the series to get another game made and finish off the like the the sequel to dark dawn that I think they
Wanted I think camelot has given up. That's what I think and because they've given up
They don't want to put in the energy like if if we're gonna put a character in why put it in for like a dead series that
You know, we could do it for fucking piranha plant or you know, whatever it is. Oh, yeah, the new piranha plant game
I can't wait. I can't wait for the new piranha. I don't even that doesn't even sound weird
That doesn't even sound like a weird thing that would surprise me if it were true
Yeah, like these companies have to decide what they're gonna do
It's some kind of some kind of motion controlled thing where you like use the game pad to like tilt around and like stretch your
Fucking vine. Why would you ever expect?
Gino to make it in before chrono, I'll tell you why uh, oh before chrono you were saying, um
Well, one is literally mario character. I think that goes a long way
Yeah, but he was in one game. That's not that well technically speaking. He's been in two games
Oh, jesus christ has a little mario and luigi. He shows up. Yeah
But but okay, gino. Okay, gino has already been confirmed to be in
The new smash game as a little like player icon now
I'm not I don't know what that implies
But they obviously have the ability the legal right to use his likeness in the game to a degree
And I mean some people think that's a deconformation that like he isn't in but we saw like an image in the trailer
I don't think it implies that at all. I think uh, it things remain the same
He's likelihood as being a dlc is certainly possible
But I'm not even trying like I don't want to convince anyone that gino should be in the game
I just happened to think that he would you would you classify smash brothers as a religion?
Imagine a new mario rpg right imagine that in we we meet uh, we meet like gino, but not gino
As we know we meet the we meet the person
We meet like the person who is like an in-world superhero or something
Okay, like an in-world like captain quirk kind of character like, um
Who the who the doll was based off of and he's like a hero to the he's like a hero to the people and the hero to the children
But he's oh my god
You mean we meet the original gino who is not the same and he's more of like and he's more of like a corporate sellout
But then for whatever reason the star spirit has to come back to like continue
You know he has to repair the star road again
And he comes back takes over a doll again
And like the real gino ends up in league with whatever force broke the star road and the doll has like has to overcome
Okay, like original gino can't be a real person. Well, I guess it is mario. I was going to say puppets aren't alive, but
Wait what because gino could like canonically gino is a puppet
Like the mario is an inanimate
He's an inanimate puppet and the the the little toadette playing with him
Seems to think that he's some kind of superhero. Yeah, but that doesn't mean he's based on one
No, well, it doesn't mean that but he could be while we've been talking
I've been trying to like research the most popular characters in nintendo games from like the last
Uh 20 years
It's actually shocking how well represented like all the most popular characters even if the third party are in smash
To the extent that gino actually would be like one of the top five candidates probably those characters who would make sense
Um, what do you mean? How so how do you figure like just that most of the characters from like, okay?
I'm going by like game FAQs looking at like the most popular games that are looked at on there and
almost everything on nintendo consoles is represented like down to like bayonetta and
Shit, that's like not even first party
Um, but I do think it would make just as much sense for like golden sun or
Gino or something like that to be the next one
to come out there was something else
That I saw that would have also made sense
like, uh
It's it's really just a shame that rareware is like microsoft now because like banjo would obviously make sense
They should make a deal just make a deal dog like with cloud fucking figure it out pay the money
I don't know yeah like banjo or some resident evil characters like leon from re4 would make sense
Yeah, sure because re4 was a huge game cube game game before it became can we please get fucking
I forgot the name of the silent hill two main character. Can we get that guy, please?
Can we please get jill sandwich as a smash trophy?
We should we should we should get mara from shimakami tense eight
It really sucks that rare when with microsoft now they can't use donkey kong games because of donkey kong 64
Really sucks that they left donkey kong reds
Yeah, he's right. He's right. So you're implying that why don't they just use banjo and also but even more
I'm honestly shocked that like they have any
Square eighties characters and not so am I dude. I was blown the fuck away
I made a video about it like three years ago
Not having like if if you ask me like if they were going to do another square character after
After cloud like before gino. They will do chrono
I would have to disagree. But who knows maybe that you could be right. It could be right
I think one of the most popular characters of all time just because chrono trigger is so beloved
This this this is mara from shimakami tensey by the way. He was he was joking
Are there any shimakami tense it came on?
Oh, that's a dick monster. Oh the dick the dick chariot rider. Yeah
You're right. I do want him in there that would be that would be great. Which game is he from shimakami tensey
Just the first one. Yeah, just any game. I'm pretty sure he's in a bunch of them. He's in a bunch of them
Okay, beautiful. All right guys. This conversation is going down the tubes real fast. I feel it. I think we all feel it
Let's uh, look the only thing I have to say about the only thing I have to say about super smash brothers
Is that the latest the latest trailer that has like uh sonic running away and then reaching out to hold
The good grab pq and then they both get like teleported away
Uh, that's getting dangerly close to canonical sonatru and i'm uncomfortable about it
He's right. He's right
If only they had fused they could have had the power to escape, but they didn't do it in time
That trailer was that that that that that animation was great. I love seeing everybody try their best to survive and
Instantly die and can I just say okay? Here's the thing. I love most about uh smash bros and it also extends to like
Decidio final fantasy like games like that like that that's the zelda in
Smash bros the new smash bros is the character design of the one from a link between worlds
Which was like a tiny little like chibi sprite and it's been brought to life
So beautifully and to see that character design in these incredibly beautiful animations brings so much joy to my heart
And uh, and I wanted gino to be one of them. God damn it. He deserves respect
But now it's just gonna be a fucking dlc character. You know, I was like malo better
I'm zelda from uh smash bros, you know the new one. Okay. Yeah
All right, I was like malo better than gino. I know all right. We've been over it. We've been hey
I want malo and smash. Hey everybody since we spent this whole podcast talking about video games and therefore
Objectively the opening theme should be I just want to play video games for this episode
That would be true. What games have you guys been playing as of late?
Tokyo Zen and do ex plus nuclear throne in this war one at a fucking i'll go down the list mage
Mage you're first. What have you been playing? Tokyo Zen to do ex plus and also blade and soul
What in the fuck is tokyo zon to do ex plus?
It's uh, it's it's an jrpg
Excellent of what denomination what console what style of graphics?
Well, well, I'm playing it on pc
But I think it's available and originally was on ps4 or at least vita
Or at least the tokyo zon and do original one was I think was on vita
But then there's a PlayStation 4 and ex plus is the advanced version from what I hear
Is it good?
It's
I've seen this game on steam
Yeah, it was a sale
Yeah, it's it's fun. It took me a while to get the controls down with the mouse and keyboard
I actually sucked at it a lot with with with uh with the controllers
So I had to learn this definitely looks like a vita game like a vita port
Yeah, sadly, I didn't know that um, but I I only bought it because it was on sale on on steam
So and there we go and I'm having fun with it. It gives me
It gives me a little bit of bit of persona vibes. It's not as good, but I don't know. It's fun. It's fun enough
All right, we got to move through this fucking thing faster. Let's so let's let's get through these fucking games we're playing
Here's my list. I'm playing ease eight on switch a little bit. I'm playing hyper light drifter on switch a little bit
I've currently taken some time off a hollow night. I'm playing a little bit of devil may cry one
I'm playing a little bit of eventical the porn game from steam and I'm playing a little bit
How can you be playing a little bit of devil may cry one?
We we did a live stream of that last night where tom beat it in one three hours sitting
Okay, well, I've played I don't know maybe twice for like two hours settings. I'm not that good at it
So, you know, whatever take me a while last game. I'm playing believe it or not
Call of Duty black ops for a little bit every once in a while and it's fun as hell
That's it go tom gay
Uh, if you want to see what I've been playing recently go watch. I am games the most on brand stream on twitch
TV, that's right. The most on brand. That's a great. I like that. I love that. That gives me a
Oh, also, I forgot delta rune now. Good. What do you play?
Uh, I have been playing a lot of team fortress two and I've been getting getting into a big old like depression about it
About how I'm not good at the headshots and I keep missing my head shoots and I keep getting dominated by the entire other team
They're gangbanging me. They're getting me all in the shooting holes
Through my body. There's no body left. I'm dead and I keep coming back and I keep rage quitting every time I die
And I keep immediately opening tf2 after I rage quit and I just do it over and over again
I think to myself. What am I doing? Why am I doing? What am I? What am I trying to accomplish here?
Am I trying to get better or am I trying to what's going on here?
And then I go to youtube.com
Slash german 985 and I watch all of his old videos
Then I go to star underscore and I watch all of his old videos
And then I watch how it feels to play scout in tf2
And then I fucking I look at a million tf2 videos every day and I don't do anything
And I'm fucking sad and it sucks. It was the best game of all time
I love it when I can get a hail screw skill streak with my sniper rifle
Oh, I love tf2. Fuck you tf2. You shit
Idiot
Hey, but you know what the worst moment my entire life was was a few days ago
I wanted to
Show kathy some of my culture and so I turned on german is mad and she didn't get it
No, I know I know I was so fucking devastated. I couldn't believe that I that I thought it drops out
Yeah, that that that was investing time and the person who didn't understand the appeal of german is mad
What the fuck I've never seen german is mad german is mad is the only video on the planet worth watching
If you're watching another video, then you don't understand
German German and star videos are like the game grumps before game grumps, and they're still better than game grumps have ever been ever
sick
Bad, what are you playing well?
um plan uh
Me and munchie playing endless war. I'm pretty pretty tired today because and this is my chance to segue into what I actually care about
We had the uh, we had rfck con yesterday. It was great. We met up with some some top some top killers and top rowdies
My my achilles tendons are are raw and frayed to the point of nearly snapping
Because I was walking around in boots that were not the most comfortable
um
And we met uh, we met endless war in real life and that's what happened to the base of endless war
It was a great as a grand gay old time
Well, uh, we prayed we prayed for his mercy and we did not receive it. I gotta ask at the the pillow fight
Well, what was that room? Where were you? Was that a big old hotel? Oh, ben wasn't there?
That was like that was like an after party thing wait pillow fight. It was like an after party thing
I I because paradox rocks had flew in and he flew in like towards the end of rfck con
I wanted to spend more time with him because he is my literal adoptive son
We just went back to efrim's hotel room and me efrim a.j.
Shoop cough kazi and paradox rocks. All he just hung the fuck out ordered pizza and uh shot the shit
And uh, I beat the shit out of paradox rocks once. I don't think that that was recorded
It wasn't on my channel
Then paradox rocks beat the shit out of efrim and then I think efrim beat the shit out of someone else
But I forget hey, oh efrim beat the shit out of a television
Man, this is too fucking meta for me. I don't know what the fuck you're talking about. Munchy, what games have you been playing?
We're talking about a
Convent I'm sorry. I'm sorry that you don't understand literally everything that we're talking about
Yeah, that's well, that's it. I guess
Munchy, what a game are you fucking playing? I I don't play video games. I only play pokemon going in this war
Those are both video games
So you do there you go
Fucking asshole
Anyway, I got one gengar on gengar. I've been playing which also was rfck coming
I I for the six hours leading up for this podcast. I was playing tails of fantasia on the tails gets trolled
Digi, what happened? I don't know what that is code. You got to get it in the beginning of that
What happened to crosscode?
Getting it on the beginning of crosscode. It's not as valuable as making a video about tails
So that means you just wasted all that time playing crosscode, you know, it wasn't a waste because I had a great time
Why we're gonna we're gonna disappoint the iam games. We've been talking up that crosscode video
Nobody said that I quit crosscode just because I made him fucking decided to play tails of fantasia
Digi, it's gonna take it's gonna take us like 10 million if you're gonna do a bunch of tails videos
It's gonna take us what like longer than uh fucking delta rune will take the finish because there's so fucking many of them
Why are you playing tails of fantasia instead of tails of berseria with that very sexual main character velvet?
Who i'm very attracted to sexual I am planning to do a retrospective on the tails series on the iam games channel
Good luck, but you can find at youtube.com slash iamgames.fun
Yeah, go to iamgames.com for fun better yet. Damn. That's a good ass url that fucking url
How much does that cost you like what's that cost to do? It was it was relatively cheap. I believe
It was worth every penny
I should buy some I want to I want to pull like a jesse and just buy a bunch of urls
Anything even clothe like best man of all time best boy in the world, you know things, you know
I got a I got a deal. I got a hot deal on stcomics.com
So I technically own st comics with an x as well as st comics with a cs. Well done. I was well done
Cover all your base if we're speaking of urls go to apsadventures.site because by the time this comes out
There will be a new bail jpeg update video. Yeah
Is it done? Yeah, it probably won't be done. I don't know. Okay. You left us on a cliffhanger my dude
Yeah, it was fucked up what you did to your character
Now I remember why it was sounded familiar. Okay. Yeah, yes tails of symphony was my favorite game of all time
And I was 14 and I wrote a lot of pornography about the characters
What's uh, what's the name of the sexy ninja girl?
Sheena
Sheena yes, she was the biggest titty girl in the world. Well actually tifa was in my pornography
the lolly girl uh
And uh while sheena was asleep
inserted the hilt of us a short sword into her own pussy
And then put the sheath of said sword and now we're demonetized
In her sleep. Wow
That was one of one of eight chapters of which I got of which on fanfiction.net before they killed all pornographic fan fiction
I had 8 000 views which until the my little pony channel was the most views I ever caught on anything
I ever did on the internet. Do you ever see I've seen a couple of like 14
I've seen I saw one girl's twitter bio once that was like, uh, it was like 10 000 views on youtube
like, uh, something like 20 000, uh, like snapchat or twitter followers like
100 000 snapchat followers and then like 10 million views on porn hub and it was like an escalating
Legit that fucking tale of symphony of pornography that I wrote when I was 14 took me almost
10 no 10 minutes
Eight years to come in view count it took eight years of non-stop production of further internet content
What can you say it appeals to the largest demographic pornography? That's you know, yeah, and I guess tells everybody a fan's
Porn is for everybody. If you are a viewer and you would like to escape the frankly uncomfortable and confusing lifestyle
of listening to the pcp
And calling yourself a pcp fan like full stop in there then please go to
Uh, uh discord.gg slash lowercase
m t uppercase
s r x
lowercase
E k and join r c k
They're gonna remember that one or you could just find the link on our on the discord on the twitch page at twitch.tv slash rowdy
Frickers and hot goys probably easier to do that. Let's all be real discord is faggot zoomer shit
And you shouldn't be involved like if you're on the internet you are gay do not be on the internet
The internet is for straight faggots like if you're not
If you're not offline getting fucking pussy every day, you are doing your life wrong
Okay, like what did you call me? What did you call me at halloween? You call me like a like a zoomer like a zoomer pied piper
Damn that's so true and much is the lead zoomer. Yeah
He's the first one caught in my in my piccolo song
Damn, that's good. That's good shit. Yeah
I'm very proud. Um, I guess we're all kind of that. You know, I was just actually I got an interesting message from somebody
Um in my in my patron discord
I was like rounded up the you know the the people who haven't paid their taxes need to be killed
You know who unpatroned and one guy it was it was really fine. He's just like hey, dude
Just letting you know, uh, you know, just whatever don't want a patron anymore
um
And one of the things he said was that like like I've I've since outgrown the need for your message of like self betterment
And taken responsibility. So like I don't really need your perfect now
I get that every day like every time someone unpatriots me. That's what the message is. I mean, that's fine
But I was just like wow, that's actually kind of great. It's a little sad. But like they won't pay me
No, it's it's it's such a weird feeling. I see the temptation, but I think like that's dumb actually
I mean, maybe he's just lying and actually he just you know, doesn't know what
I feel like those people I feel like those people think that they forget about the fact that you
Remain older than them and that your message will evolve
Well, I mean like yeah, that's true continually need your guidance unless they are actually exceeding you unless you have
Unless they like they've taken like a huge
Attitudinal shift in their life or something. They no longer see they probably think they're a badass and they're gonna quickly realize
They're not maybe they are I believe this guy or at least that he believes it
It's just that like I mean I think about myself like nobody's that cool
I was nobody's that
If if somebody like I don't know is loving loves my content
But then like gets a great job like gets a girlfriend and is just like loving their life
Like I totally get why like you need to take responsibility or whatever. They're like I did that's good. You know got it covered fam
Sure, you know that just sounds like what I want people to do and and I've been thinking about how like
It's inevitable that at the very least people will probably age out or like just some people are gonna not care
About anime video, whatever and just go to other stuff. But then probably like new kids will cycle in
It's almost like you're a teacher in a classroom of a certain grade level
Whatever that may be and people cycle in and they cycle out is their life
Constantly realizing that you're aging because the kids keep getting younger and younger somehow while you only get older
Yeah
I don't know. It's just interesting
This sounds terrifying. Let's talk about something else. Okay, you know what we can go to those we can go to the voicemails anytime people
I want to quickly I want to quickly make a shout out. It's just
Not for myself not for myself. It's not not something that will benefit me in the long run
Is just so there's this anime that absolutely no one is talking about on the internet
It's just like it doesn't exist. I swear like three or four people and like it's called double dicker
So I just want to raise awareness about this anime because I give us the elevator pitch. Why is it good mage?
What's more like double dicker?
Yeah, why is it good mage sell us please have you guys seen tiger and bunny?
Yes, I have no I'm not certain but it seems like it's by the same people
He has that sort of aesthetic and style to it and like the characters are really fun
It is by sunrise who did this who did both but yeah
In fact, it is apparently tied into tiger and bunny. It is a
Oh, okay. I like it even more now
Okay, well, hopefully so much. Let us know
Press press m in the chat if you don't listen to mage and did that
Yeah, you don't have to like it
I just want people to be aware that it exists because no one's talking about it
I say I'm if you approve of mage press m and chat
Mage, I've got an idea. Why don't you make a literal anime analysis video on why it's so great to raise awareness?
Like I did with oh shit. They galco chant. I'm really not good at those things though. It's not hard enough
It's not hard. It's right. I I go search double deck your dug and krill and I see what it looks like
Is it a good mage? Do you like it?
I mean, it looks like ass, but if she says it's good, it might pass. I mean, it's a cg nightmare, so
I mean, I mean the tiger and bunny had also cg'd and so, you know
The city's state of wifillania
Two suns arise above the city and the people here live
Oh, yeah, it is in a city that is named literally this town is called lis valetta
Oh, which sounds like lithuania. No, I did not realize that
Oh
I see I see the fucking propaganda. Oh my god. There's government like
Mage has been hired by the government to push this propaganda
Is the main character a young a young girl dressed in complete purple with a baseball bat walking around the desolate streets
It is actually a young man described exactly that way
He does not have a bat. He does not have a bat
Is he actually purple?
The pieces are falling into place
His whole entire design is all purple, but like head to toe. Well, we know we know why mage is watching the show now
You're not entirely wrong
I got into it
I mean, I it was recommended to me by by biter and and he sold me because there was a main guy who was purple and he
Was cute. Oh, but bet his personality is so adorable. He's just so excited to be there. It's just how can you not love him?
That's always endearing. I like people who are excited to be anywhere
He's a bit of a dumbass, but I love him double decker. Check it out sponsored by mage and and state of lithuania
the state
Are we doing questions or what? It's it's time to go to questions. Yeah. Jesus christ. I forgot. I've been here forever
I feel like I'm dying slowly in my seat. All right. Here we go. It was 10 minutes for me. I'm drunk
I mean, it's been a boisterous last while. I've been enjoying it. Best day drinking of my life
All right, let's get to it people. Uh first first voicemail. Here we go. It's one spar checking in as you guys
All right, let's let's see what he's got for us today go
When I so as the time of this podcast release election season is officially over and with it a whole bunch of annoying videos about the importance of voting
Correct. Um, but right now I'm here looking up some information about the people running for my local offices
and uh, not only have I discovered
That uh, one of the candidates is the serial heckler who attended nba home games to berate the away teams to the point where he actually
Got banned from the local stadium
Um, but another candidate is a youtuber who makes candy and lunchables reviews
Yeah
A youtuber by the way whose catchphrase is just when you thought it was safe to get back into bed
So are there any
You guys
Uh, I just told us before but I can't remember
My chakras just got blitzed from that. Holy fuck
I would register to vote just to vote for lunchables guy
Wait, wait, wait, did you did you hold on on the stream yesterday or like two days?
You were literally making the case. There is no way you would ever vote under any circumstances ever
Okay, well, we found the one well tom guess what I didn't know there was someone
running on the platform of lunchables
I I still eat lunchables every fucking time I go to the
You thought it was safe to get back in bed. What does that mean?
What's gonna what's gonna happen lunchables guy?
Real quick question to decide whether you get to live or die. What is the best type of lunchables?
I just like the pizza ones with the goop on it. You know, I remember this
Any other answer you would be executed in my society. No, dude. Hammond cracker. You bet you're dead
dead in my society
I never even had a lunchable. Oh, that's sad. That's well. You're european. It's
Radcon four. We have to sit. We have to sit bow down with the pizza and the hams
Gotta make a decision lunchables reviews
We got to have a taste test. You got to pick his favorite. Oh, yeah, fine. Sure. I'll do that
I do recall having like things of in the similar vein of like it's food, right for children, right?
They're tiny little crackers and bits of cheese the thing is I never liked cheese so I would never eat
Well, okay
The lunchables that are good are the pepperoni pizza ones and it's because for me as a child
They were too expensive for my mom to buy them for me. But as an adult. They are like
Digi's over here in the lap of luxury with
Mountains of tiny pepperoni
They're like 250 they're like not even expensive. That's fine. You know, I relate did she I relate like back in the day
I couldn't get like cereal or like kinder egg surprise is too expensive. So now I'm just
As soon as I became an adult I was drowning in cereal
Best thing about being an adult. Yes
Did you have only I've only ever had the cheese pizza lunchables because when I was a child my mom was like the meat
And these are disgusting and you're not allowed to have
Because my mom she's wrong
Okay, well the thing about the lunchables pizzas is that the key to them is that they come with
It's three pizzas and you get nine pepperonis and the satisfaction of laying out your three pepperonis per pizza
And then like take like each pizza you can it's like perfectly proportioned to devour in three bites
So you have one bite per pepperoni. It is the most satisfying fucking meal in the world
You need to put like a video on the main channel if you analyze really do
Dude, I did I I made a uh, there's not on the main channel
But on after dark there's a video of me eating nine lunchables pizzas and I got the worst of a cake of my life
Do not eat more than one box of those. I know it's tempting because you're like, haha, I'm an adult
It's only five bucks. I can do whatever I want if you eat more than four lunchables pizzas. You will feel like shit
I'm just letting you know because all of it is just sugar every single element of it tastes like sugar
The the the end of that message was I think asking us like if there's any other like crazy election people in our areas that like have a
Kooky thing. Oh my god, that was a question. Don't you know about donald trump?
I mean, there's always a crazy guy. I remember like the last time in the in the
uk election for prime minister or whatever that there was a guy running
And he was like what I think he was wearing a giant elmo suit or something
And he was just elmer and nobody took it seriously
But he got votes because people hate politicians and it's funny to vote for that guy
Oh, okay. So there he was kind of like a goofing on the whole system. Yeah, there's there's there's usually a goofer or two
There's a guy with a giant boot on his head. I think I've seen an image. Oh, yeah, I've seen the guy
Are you having a vermin supreme?
Politicians, yeah, maybe got him
Right. Oh, Ben. What were you saying? I I know I've heard of vermin supreme
I have a I have a a delta rune
observation to make
To jump back. How did that happen? Did anyone know this is a this is a question slash observation
I want to know if anyone else feels the same way about this. I have a feeling I'll be the only one that thinks this
Uh, was anyone else annoyed by the dear girl having a crush on susan. Why do you hate lesbians so much?
Tell me explain it's not that I hate lesbians, Nate. Although I do but that's not the reason why I felt like it had no
It had no relevance to the game that was like it was just oh by the way he he
Ship them. Yeah, it was it was irrelevant, but I mean there's more chapters to come. So whatever maybe it will be
I know it's not because I want susie susie's mind and no one can have you know
My reaction my reaction to hearing that like to the learning that uh, what's her name?
The dear girl has a crush on susie is wow
This dear girl is a fucking idiot and probably a terrible person
Because susie is a freak and a monster who I don't who like bullies people
Shubs them into lockers and threatens to bite their face off
If you like someone if you like someone like that, you're probably
Okay, first of all, you're probably fucking stupid says ben
Ben first of all, I don't think anyone has actually seen susie bully someone because if you talk to everyone all she did
Throw a ball and then they hated her. It seems like everyone's scared of her
When she comes in the class they also say they no one actually seen her bully anyone
They're just scared of her because she's big wait. Do they wait. Do they say that do they say
There's an implication throughout the classroom that that that she
Tries to put on a front and then they can sort of see that she's not but they are still scared of her because they're just kids
I I think it's pretty evident that like regardless of whether she's done that or not like yet
She's a 14 year old to 16 year old girl. Of course if she's attracted to other girls
What would she more be more attracted to than the bad boy?
You know the the bad one the the bad apple the one who seems like a bad ass
I mean susie's like that sexy rebel kid from the breakfast club, you know, exactly. Yeah, uh, but she's obviously she likes her
But like she's mean and she's nasty. I think she acts terribly
I think if it weren't for the fact that undertale already did the lesbian thing
You'd be like this doesn't feel as forced as it does here
No, I don't think it feels forced. In fact, I think it feels totally natural
I think it feels like something that would definitely happen in real life
But it also makes me mad. Well, it makes me mad and I don't think it's fair and I thought I just think it's
I read girls and I was like Ben's such a Ben's a nice guy. Why won't you date him girls? Why?
It's just no, I no no no
I read that I read her being like oh
I have such a crush on Susie and I just put and I just put the game down and I'm like
I know I know of course you do but she's awful. She's awful
Ben do you think it's implied that it is healthy of her to have that
affection towards Susie
I don't think the I don't think the game really makes much judgment either way. It's implied to be innocent enough
Yeah, I mean, I think it's totally natural that she'd have that
Like I don't think Susie has displayed herself as like an abject sociopath. I think she's
She does she fucking she fucking shoves you into a locker and tells you she's gonna bite your face off
You know that not the kids in class
Also, I mean these people probably grew up in the town together. Don't you think it's possible
There was a time in in you know back in antiquity where Susie and this person were kids and they may be played together
And they she has some positive memories based on that so even if she's being a jerk now
Maybe there's a connection that's fan fiction. Hey, you just wrote fan fiction. Yeah, I got it consider it
The dear girl. She's like naive and innocent and and soft and kind
So she might admire the strengths that Susie has that she laughs true true
I just yeah, we're all writing some good fan fiction right now. It's just you know, okay
This is not this is not a story problem. This is not a the writing sucks problem
This is a this is a this is a the world is terrible problem where it makes
It makes sense and is totally fine and acceptable that someone that acts like Susie could have like, you know
The affection and admiration of strangers for it
People literally make fan pages for serial killers in real life. I don't that's true. Well, there you go. All right
I mean, I get your right Ben proving proving that but people like are attracted to weird shit and sometimes just strength and
Yeah, I don't you know, I want to I want to say on the basis of this conversation
Before I never talk about Delta Rune again. Yeah, Delta Rune is perfectly fine
I want to go on record as saying that anything negative I have to say about the game
There's nothing wrong with it. I'm just old
I don't I don't I have legitimate semi criticisms like this whole thing about how all my efforts to protect enemies from Susie
We're literally pointless. Let me let me take that back
It's not that there's nothing wrong with it potentially at all. Just that like it's it's overall good
I'm just I don't I don't care. Something being good doesn't impress me
Like I need things to be great for me to give a fuck because I've seen countless good things
Like I've seen hundreds of thousands of good things
So something being good is not impressive to me, but like I do think it's good. I'm not saying it's bad in any way
It's fine. I get that. I
I get the attitude that like sure it's good, but who cares
Because undertale for me is not impressive. I don't care about the good things
I don't care if Delta Rune does something totally different from undertale
It's just that undertale changed the game and awakened me a little bit more to like amazing things you can do
And like I just want something like that to happen in delhi. It doesn't matter. What can we move on?
Yeah, we should continue. We should continue. All right. Let's move on. Please. I want this to end
I I hear you. Okay. This one's from pcp fan
Unconditional love guy. That's yeah, okay. That's terrible real name. That's me. That's my
My cock is right here. I'm really happy to hear you guys on a Saturday morning at 3 a.m
I'm sorry. It was late. I just wanted to mention that there's now as many ptp episodes as there are
Is the greatest anime of all time dragon ball super?
I just wanted to know you could be any dragon ball character. Who would you be?
We got several messages about which dragon ball character we would like to be
I would be uh
Puar the shape-shifting cat. Oh, yeah, I would obviously be Goku because he's the best one
I was gonna say you'd be popo because you look like popo. I don't even know who that is. I've never watched Dragon Ball Z
Um
Munchy the very slightly minorities definitely like completely mr. Popo
It's not a race thing. It's the fact that he's a stocky boy with like big impressive girth and that's what munchy is
Why not boo? Why not Majin boo who's big and pink because he's too fat. He's too fat to be munchy
You're too fat to be munchy. Get the fuck out of here. I'd be sell because I'm into eugenics
So, you know, yeah
I'd be when I was a kid and we and dragon ball z was super popular and every kid was claiming
A person. I was android 18. So I guess for nostalgia's sake. I feel like ben's frieza ben just seems like
Cool, cool, I'll take it. I love it actually
I'm actually sincerely complimented that I was frieza and not I don't know that one pig. Oh, uh, whatever. Yeah
We're long
If I can I know I changed I changed my mind. I'm gonna be oh, I forgot his name
The the general blue
General blue. Oh, that's the blonde, right? The nazi guy. The funny the funny gay nazi is really cool
Magic mage by the way, I can totally see why you'd be android 18. That's the blonde one, right? Yeah
I'm reflecting on it and I get it. Normally. I would pick like some cute girl
I want to be right but like chi chi or something in dbc
There is no who thinks chi chi when they think cute
Like as a okay as a child she's an extremely sexualized little girl. So that sounds like something did you think though like
There's no
dbz girl who I really relate to
What about vedel vedel's pretty good as for the well, that's what I'm thinking is like
You can either be one of the girls or one of the like the guys who's with the girls and like ultimately if I had to pick
It's like well vedel is the cutest I'd be gohan so I could be with vedel
That doesn't feel that different from my actual life. No wait, who wants to be gohan?
Yeah, sure. He gets he's with vedel who's fine
That's the square. What okay the hottest girls are like android 18 and vedel probably
Yeah, that sounds about right. Oh, I don't we'll launch I guess from dragon balls
Launch is pretty good. Launch is good too. I mean the thing is that all I don't think the girls in dragon balls year that hot
Okay, what it comes down to is that the characters and dbz are all very basic
Like every guy is just like a male ideal and every girl is just like your ideal girlfriend
So it doesn't matter who you choose no matter what you get the perfect life like any dbz character you pick
You just live perfect. I don't really like a curatoriyama's girl
Or fucking tm. I like bulma. Bulma's looks nice. She's cute. Yeah, like everybody loves bulma. And if you
Bulma is pretty badly
Okay, who do you want to be do you want to be bulma so you can be a hot girl or vegeta so you could fuck a hot girl
It doesn't matter all the characters are the same. I just like bulma. She she stole my husband
I uh, I want
Oh, I want to I want to be android 17 because uh, uh, he's a not he's the closest thing to a machine man
That oh, yeah
He has unlimited energy and he's in super and he looks the same age
So maybe he's immortal. So I'm on is he the one with the red mohawk. No, that's no that's 16
Guys guys did pan ever grow up like because the last time I saw her was like she was in gt. Yeah
She wasn't gt. Yeah, jesse is telling us in the chat
You guys are looking at this all wrong the correct answer is krillin because he's the only one but the actual normal good life
It's true. I don't I don't like being krillin and getting to fuck android 18 is pretty fucking perfect
Um, like I mean, okay if I'm thinking of it in terms of like
Like when I think of it broadly, I just think that being krillin is no different from being gohan
Like if you're getting more specific krillin is krillin is like the best human in the entire series
Jesse's pointing out that nobody hates krillin
But I feel some people aren't too fond of gohan after what like he after gohan gave up like all his incredible power
Like I said, like I think we're thinking of this broadly
But if you're gonna get ultra specific like like I said all the girls are kind of the same all the guys are kind of the same
So it's really just like
If on a broad level like if you want to get specific
I just don't really think about tbc
And I don't know it well enough krillin or gohan the way that I respect someone like like goku or vege
Yeah, you know
It was like the least respectable guy at dbc for for in a way like he's he's a dead
He's fucking dead. Vegeta then. Vegeta. Vegeta is the best. Goku is awful. Goku is objectively a character
I don't like as I've grown older and uh, it makes me very upset
If anyone can explain to me what goku did to like not not that he deserves more power
But literally what technique did he use to acquire more power than vegeta who objectively tried the hardest genetic
genetic genetics
Which doesn't make sense. He just he just is strong and it's really gay and I hated it forever
Well, that's that's kind of what I love about dbc is that like the main character is like the least
Not okay. I won't say the least interesting character, but like among the central cast. He's like the least relatable
And uh, I think that's almost appropriate like if someone's going to be fucking god
Like the guy who solves every problem. You're not that fucking guy
No audience member is the guy
The moment in the kid boo saga when vegeta finally is he's like sitting there beaten and bloody on the ground like already
Basically dead but somehow came back and goku's like super saying three fighting majin boo
And he just has to come to terms with the fact that like yeah, you're better than me and it just always will be that way
Man that fucking hit me hard as a kid
Like like I think goku is there to remind us like we are not goku
That's why vegeta is the best character in dragon ball like not even a contest like the realist dude the best guy
Yeah, vegeta is the best character in in dragon ball z vegeta is the new main character when he you know comes in
But if you read dragon ball goku is interesting and I like I believe you I believe you
He's fun in dragon ball krillin krillin is the vegeta of dragon ball
Okay, this is my theory on why why goku sucks in dragon ball z because goku is the main character of a comedy series
And dragon ball z is not a comedy series
We'll share and also he never mentally grew up even like a little bit. He never kissed his wife. How did he have children?
Oh my god. I mean you don't have to kiss a woman to impregnate her. I'm just saying I'm just saying who says goku never kissed
Chee-Chee goku did in dragon ball super
There you go. Wait, what? Yeah, I don't wait. What? Yeah, he doesn't even know what a kiss is
But what about all that pornography? I read. All right guys, let's we've been a way too long in this question
Let's move on to the next one shall we? No, I'm fucking I'm fucking
Regardless of why their bed gives a fuck about dragon ball z he grew up with this show and to hear this is obviously
Fucking deeply disturbing
This is like wait, there's something wrong here
Something's rotten. I guess they're
Corrupting his character by you know
It is kind of ridiculous because he was like that in dragon ball like he's like chee-Chee like asked him to marry her
And he said yeah for that real reason and he never kissed his wife
What and it was implied that he he had no idea what he was getting himself into when he said he was married
Why didn't she say something like
How you know goku how you're supposed to talk to that. It's impossible. She couldn't just demand
Why would you marry it kiss her like what the fuck like she has her fucking
She's kind of got like
I don't know. It's a weird relationship where like sometimes she's in control and but most of the time she's totally not
What if she didn't while he was asleep? What if that was the only way it was safe because he's so strong
You know, yeah, maybe he doesn't remember kissing her
Do you guys ever read that it was like an article called like like how to fuck superman or like like something about like
It was a it was like a think piece about how lois lane has sex with superman
And it's about how like his sperm or so would be if his sperm is like proportionally strong as the rest of him
They would like shoot through her body and like rip her eggs to shreds literally happened in the movie hand cock
Have any of you seen it or heard about it? Yeah, I've watched it. I don't remember how it dealt with this
Yeah, will smith comes through the like roof of the trailer that they're fucking in
Like he has to pull out so that he doesn't fucking murder her with his god damn. I don't remember that
Yeah, there's a scene where they're fucking like and it cuts to the outside of the trailer
Like two holes appear in the roof as he comes through the roof of the she's got a double barreled cock. I guess
That's the only seat I've seen of that
All right, guys, let's move on
Let's keep going. Okay, ryan harper with a with a message. Here it is
Hello, I am the democratically elected representative of the detractors of the new pcp theme song
been sent to tell you guys that the whole issue with the theme song is that
It is more of a joke
than a theme the
Whole bit with the guy
doing a woman's voice
It's funny
But it's really force. Well, okay, it wouldn't be funny if it sounded natural
Okay, but because
Do any of us even disagree theme song like really and after hearing it
We all agree the new theme song is wrong, right? No, why did you vote for it? Oh my god, yeah
No, of course not did you we fucking voted for it and it won
Yeah, I mean I voted for it because it was funny until we realized that when you hear it over and over again
It's doesn't it's not it doesn't function this way. I mean, I
I like it like isn't it boring that every episode of adventure time opens them saying come along with me
Like we got it the first time guys. We don't need to hear it every time. Okay. Maybe you liked the second
Maybe you liked the runner-up. I get it. I liked the runner-up too. I also voted for it. I did not listen
It was the one that was just the word pcp in multiple ways
You know what? Yeah, what would be ideal channel trailer? I don't think opening themes are necessary for this show
Well, all right, we don't need to open this can of worms. I don't know. Let's talk about amongst ourselves the next meeting
We'll see what's did you won't be there to speak his opinion. Yeah, that's right. I don't even care. I'm just letting you know
What am I?
I don't care for the rock breakdown, but whatever. Yeah, the rock. Okay
I didn't remember that that was the thing like when I voted for this theme song
It was based on my vague memory of it from months prior. Oh, that sounds like your problem. Rock and roll
That's true. Uh, I I just will say what I've been saying the entire time
This has ever been even an idea is that we don't even need a new theme song. Why?
We always did money don't know don't know so about that. It's about that community engagement
Tom you're fucking insane. If you think that this is built more commuting engagement than I'm
Supposed to you're insane
The problem was that at first we were playing the wrong part of the song as the op but eventually we corrected that and we're playing a
Better part of it and it was no longer a problem in my eyes. So like I don't know what initially
I was a big complainer of us making the ed the op because of the fact
That it sounded wrong as an op but then like we used a different part of it
It was only five seconds long and it wasn't a problem anymore and like
It was like fixed before we made another op
I guess
This is what we
Let him finish this all right say it to go all I wanted to say is that we clearly fucked up
We should have referenced our good friend Jeff the master of what's in an op who could have helped us
Yeah, he's right. Okay. Love. Love you Jeff next message. Here we go. This is from uh mackeys back. I think all right go
Hey, Nate, you think you're so fucking cool with your electric skateboard. Well, listen to this
That's me doing a real grind
Yeah, you do that on your stupid heavy electrical piece of shit
What's that Tony hawk
Holy shit, was that bob burn quest was that bob's burgers calling in i'll take ten please
I want to see i want to see nat you show up to like a challenge
You show up to like meet this challenge and this guy. He's there wearing like, you know
Like a hemp parka or whatever the fucking zoomers wear or something
He's probably got a man bun, you know in peach fuzz or whatever
He's looking like a real cool skater guy and you show up on your like motorized electric skateboard
Wearing like, you know wrist pads and like a little a helmet and stuff and like a knapsack
With cheese sticks and pepperoni
The thing is I wish that was me because I fell again today and it hurt a lot again
Dude, um, I'm just saying also. I just want to say
It's it's really put in the fear of god into me and I'm getting more scared every time I ride because now I know
What I have to do and how bad it hurt when I fall made did you did you wear gloves this time?
Absolutely not mage abs. I have not learned my lesson yet. I'm cut listen. It's not so bad
It's I was just walking. I was just walking
After rfck con me and crack were walking to his car. I was just walking along the sidewalk
You know playing pokemon go
Just my foot missed the sidewalk and I just fell and ate shit
And I have like a big fucking as you as you put it a big fucking raspberry on my
On my on my right palm right now. We're like tore a bunch of the skin off the pavement
So I you don't you don't need an electric skateboard to risk pain and injuries as you're as you're getting around
Is risking pain and injuries
It's really the human condition. He's right. He's right. This is why we need to be robots
I could not have tell how legitimate that call was but like my mental image of a dude just like nonchalantly being like
Hey, Nate, you think you're so fucking cool. Yeah, like busting a sick grind and be like, yeah, fuck you dude
Like is that not the coolest image you could ever imagine? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's one of the best calls of all time
Mackie's back. Well way to go. I am thoroughly pwned
I'm thoroughly pwned by that
I'm gonna work on my grinding skills. Well, I'm not when I'm not terrified to get back on the board
Uh, okay next call. I fell on a skateboard when I was five and I never got back on so I feel you. It's scary. It hurts a lot
It's real bad. I need fucking elbow pads. I'm tearing my fucking body up. My dad is a big time skateboarder
He's got a bunch of dhs tapes of him fucking busting mad shit on a half pipe and he tried to get me in when I was a kid
Yeah, busting fat loads on that half pipe dude. Just busting him out there
And I like fell once and was like never fucking again. So that's why he fell once you said and then just stopped
Yeah, when I was like five. Oh, you did. Yeah. Okay. Okay. It's fucking hurts. It's serious. Um, yeah
All right. Yeah, here we go. Here we go. Next one. Uh, this is number six out of 10. Yes
I'm 17 years old calling in with a message. Let's see what he's got for us
Hey guys, so I was reading this book called how to win friends and influence people a book that
And uh, one of their principles is um, do not criticize other people
They say that just to not misconstrue what they mean criticism is futile because it puts a person on the defensive
And it usually makes them strive to justify themselves. You guys agree with that or you guys completely disagree. I agree
This is a great question. Okay. Okay. I like criticizing people when I don't care about like
You know coming to a some sort of agreement with them. I just want them to be annoyed because they made me annoyed
I'm sure that's usually, you know, that's just bad. Well, that means you're not trying to win friends or influence
Yeah, okay, don't you can criticize go you can you can criticize people but you should credit there's like
I don't know. You just have to do it the right way
You just have to do it in a way that shows that you don't like dislike them or think that they're dumb or that they suck
I like in like a like way like an inception way you want them to like kind of like think that it's their own idea
Right, you gotta ask questions instead of make statements. Yeah, if they're forced to answer badly themselves, it's more impactful
You want to criticize with like well, you don't just want to say oh, well this sucks
You want to be like, okay. Well, I really like the way you did this but this other thing over
I don't know if it really works with this like, you know, you want to like you want to give a little
Nate does this all the time every time we're on the pcp if Nate ever says, uh, I hear what you're saying
That means what you just said was retarded, but I'm not gonna say that that's me saying it in a diplomatic way
Well, okay, like I think that in most situations people are not looking for criticism like
Yeah, um, yeah, just just about 12 hours ago
I put out an album and there was this one guy who left a super long comment like criticizing every fucking song on it and
When I read through it, all I could think was this guy has no idea what my intentions were nor what I think
Of what I've released
Like his criticisms have nothing to do with my feelings on the songs or how I feel about him
But he phrased it in such a way like he was trying to be helpful and it's just like dude
Like you can't help me if you don't know what I'm trying to do
And when people are criticized the reason they go on the defensive is that
They have thought through this more than what they are saying
Like I think the average person
He turned on to us for criticizing
Sure
There is a huge difference between criticizing something
To the person's face and doing so elsewhere
And like this guy this guy who I'm talking about on my album literally said you're a critic
So I guess whatever and I was just like what does me being your critic have to do
With the fact that you're commenting on this because when I criticize things I don't leave them
On the guy who made its page like I I've never made a comment that
Reki Kawahara author of sort out online has read
If you know if someone if someone is looking for criticism, that's one thing in general
I would say okay. I I I do believe in not
Giving criticism to someone unless they specifically asked for it
Like I don't go out of my way to tell someone if I think they're fucking up
Because and I sometimes I feel selfish for that reason because I know that criticizing someone who is not looking for criticism will only
Honestly, it might benefit them to hear it if no one else has told them that they're fucking up
Yeah, but it can also make them hate you a lot. Yeah. Yeah. So that's a cost you have to pay
The reason I don't do it is for selfish reasons because I know that it will not it will usually not benefit them because most people will not
Hear it if they're not looking for it
And they will just hate me and I don't want people to hate me
So I just am like, well, I'm just gonna let this person figure it out on their own
I think because that makes sense because that's because that's how it always has to do
A person will not listen to your criticism unless they have already become mentally ready to receive it
I think one step further though, which maybe is too much
But I just think that like, okay, if I've got like my let's say like friends around me
I see them fucking up and I don't say anything
I personally worry that one day they'll be mad at me for allowing them and not like saying anything
You know what I might be too passive
On on that end like I have benefited greatly from people
Like criticizing me when I didn't want to hear like in the long run
I have looked back and been very grateful
Any specific or credits
No for criticizing me
Um on things and and there are other times when I'm like, I wait, I wish that someone had criticized me
There was one criticism I gave to you Ben recently
I could wait what there was one that I gave to you that I think will benefit you in the long run
You seem to sort of agree with that criticism of was it about uh
Being too like accepting of like
No, no, it was that you you just sing too much and it's not funny
That was the one have you noticed that I have stopped doing it?
I have noticed that I have noticed that so I think Ben singing is mostly hilarious
In small doses sure absolutely specifically if he is singing
Neutral milk hotel. I don't get the five six seven oh nine thing that he does all the time
That's that's an endless war thing. So there you go. Okay, whatever
Uh, it doesn't matter that speaking of stuff like that though
That's that's making me think like the reason why a lot of artists tend to be self deprecating and openly self deprecating
Is that they want to criticize themselves publicly as to like
Allow people to like agree
So that they you know, it's like nobody
It is it well
It's a shield and it's also an invitation because like if I say something of mine sucks
I want somebody I don't want people to say no no no no no no no no what I want people to do is like to
To take that as like
An opportunity to say yeah, I I you know because like people are generally very
You know guarded with their criticism. They don't want to make enemies with anyone. They don't want to make someone upset
So like how do you say please criticize me?
um
Like you I mean you say it like that but like a lot I don't think about it a lot and I think the reason people
like me self deprecate is is like uh like a
A sub uh, what am I thinking of a way to do that?
Subconscious way of doing that. Okay. I so this is
Okay, I think that people probably have the perception that we are all a bunch of like hyper critical
assholes right if anything and I don't necessarily feel that way I
I mean obviously you can do too much, but I respect I respect people
Well, you can be an asshole and criticize someone who doesn't want criticism and no good comes of it
And you just hurt feelings and nothing good happens and obviously that's bad
I respect people who are willing to criticize someone if they honestly believe see them fucking up
I don't think that I do. I think that I am too unwilling to open my mouth if I see someone fucking up
I'm too I'm too willing to be like
I'm just gonna let them deal with it because they're not gonna want to listen to what I have to say about this
Then I will tell you right here and now I will only criticize someone to their face if they ask for it
I'll criticize people all fucking day behind their back
And that could mean in the form of a long form youtube video viewed by seven million people
But like if it's to someone's face, I'm not gonna do it. They don't ask for it because like
I don't believe you can take it like I've criticized people and they haven't been able to take it
I've had people come to me asking for criticism and not be able to take it and like I don't have fucking patience for that
Like I need to have a certain level of trust in you that you actually are going to take this criticism seriously or else
I don't like it's even if I think it can help you
I don't trust you to take it the way I want you to and to like actually learn something from it
Like fuck you. You don't get my criticism. You don't get that help
Did you you do separate you separate people who don't take it well and people who just kindly disagree?
Yeah, but like I there there are people who I mean if you're gonna
If if let's say somebody comes to me asking for criticism
And then I tell them my criticism and then they disagree
And then maybe they they sway me or they don't if I feel like
I've offered my opinion and you just dismissed my opinion
Then I'm just gonna be like well. Why did you ask for my opinion if you were so sure of my of yourself?
Remember remember Dave did you remember Dave?
Uh, I assume you mean the german guy
The german the german writer he was a big part of why I developed like he was a guy who would constantly ask for criticism
And then argue against all of it
Perfect case study. Yeah, perfect. He's like the he's like the he's like he's like patient zero
For uh, he it's like he's like a cartoonish example of someone who would literally a good reason for why I have trust issues today
Might be this particular individual later. He moved on to I mean, I think most people have better sense than Dave
Um, but Dave would come to me and he would say hey ben. I wrote this like story
Or I drew this comic. He was mostly into writing like a novel at the time. I wrote this like chapter of a novel
What do you think and I would read it and be like, okay?
You know no offense
But your english is not fluid and then he would say well
I can't sell anything if I write it in german and then I would say well
Your english isn't good enough to sell in english. So no fucking nobody writes in german
Nobody reads books written in german. I mean to be honest
I didn't think that the humor was very good even if I ignored all the weird like like like esl like
Gaffes and goofs and whatever
But you know even aside might like the the first thing the first thing every time would be like
I'm sorry. I'm sorry if you don't you don't want to hear this but your english just isn't good enough
You do not read like a fluent english speaker like you shouldn't you need to you need to either write in german or improve your english
Like one or the other and he just wouldn't fucking listen
He would and then he would argue against me about why his english was actually right
Like why it wasn't as bad like why why it wasn't as bad as I was telling him
Yeah, even if it's not as bad it has to be if you want to be published
Yeah, yeah, at least get a proofreader. You know, it's not yeah like get get someone to literally
I would tell him that I would tell him you need an editor or a proofreader or something
And he'd be like no, I can't afford one and I'd be like well, sorry
We were supposed to be his proofreaders like he was coming to people
But then he would argue and he would argue against our proofreads. Right. It was really fucking ridiculous. Okay. Yeah
Okay, in those situations. Yeah, that's stupid. I was some people are just hopeless and their ego is too big to accept
You know, whatever criticism. I mean not even saying he's got a huge head
But like if he's not gonna take the the points then there's just useless. It's just useless
I don't I don't know. He was so set. He was like, no, I can't write in german. Why it's your fucking people read people read
Right people read in germany. This guy this guy sounds like somebody amazon bestseller
Like like like I would I would think that writing in german would be a huge advantage because that's a much more niche market
Right, I guess not everybody knows about marketing
So
What was what was he writing anyway? Was it like something anime related or something? It was like a
Furry weird fantasy. Oh, of course. He's a german furry all germans. Yeah
He was he was a furry. He was writing. It was like a sort of fantasy. What is it called when you're a furry, but it's all scales
Scaly scaly
We all know instantly
I was asking I was asking
Uh, this is all about birds. I I had hoped that there was a special word. We were talking about this on iam games, weren't we?
Oh, yeah, yeah, and apparently. Oh, no, variety fuckers. It's just avian. It's not variety fucker scop killers, wasn't it?
One of those two god, there's all of no, I think it was whatever. He was a scaleman. It's all a blur. What's the next fucking voicemail?
Yeah, please god the next voicemail
Uh, we've got we're not even at three hours. This is too long. We're all right. We're getting there. We've got we've got four left
This one is from uh, uh, hang on play. All right. This is from ring grompulation is is this one
Uh, let's let's see what he's got for us. Hey guys, I just wanted to ask what's on the short list for your like personal
cringe compulation
You know when you like think about like at random times like the shittiest thing
Or like me not even like like maybe like a minor thing that you did in middle school that you're just like
Where do I fucking begin?
I have one. I have one
Small man boy a non a non man. I have one. So what's that for you guys my blog?
Okay, that's okay. Okay. I I have one that I honestly feel so terrible and awkward and weird about to this day
and I and I feel like
it's it it's
I've like specifically avoided ever telling the story because it's uncomfortable for me in a way that does not feel fun
Sure. Okay. Um
Maybe don't tell it. Are you gonna tell us now?
I mean, I could I don't think I'd be happy to hear it
Objectively speaking. I don't think it's anything that anyone is going to crucify people probably will throw it in your face
And it doesn't matter if it's bad. It'll if it makes you uncomfortable then, you know, well, I don't know
I think I'm I feel like it's maybe a little overblown. All right. The point is we were we were we were in like
Fucking middle school. I was like probably in like fifth grade or something or maybe fourth grade whatever
and
I don't know why I did this. I don't know why I thought this was funny
but like we were doing like practice speeches for
uh,
fucking like student government like elections like we were
Sitting in the auditorium and we were like the the people who were running for student office were were practicing their speeches
and
one of the girls running was like a couple years older than me. I didn't know her and
she she gives a speech about treasurer and I like
And like this is this is not in front of like a big crowd or anything like that. It's just like and um
The she she gives a speech about running for treasurer or something and like I think she asked for questions
And I think and I decided it would be funny if I like raised my hand and asks like how does a guy get a date with you?
And as like a joke and I was like and like I think it really embarrassed her
And I felt terrible afterwards. I was like, what a weird. Yeah in hindsight like what what a weird
Thing to do like oh that's so mean too because it's like
Oh, she's trying to like do something here and you just hit her with that
You know, it's funny that you're upset like with yourself for that because I feel like the average douche bag does that every week
And I mean maybe yeah, that just shows that you're not such a bad guy
But it was very in hindsight. I realized I think I realized as soon as I said it was out of my mouth
When I saw the look on her face that I was like that this was like a very like demeaning thing to do and I had like
It's real
That's like the worst really where where like the you know the when you you say something and it wasn't even funny
And it wasn't even for a good joke like like the first time in your life where you
Something you say
Doesn't go the way you thought it would in your head and that's that realization of like oh wait
Like oh, oh no, I heard a real person's feelings. Yeah
God, I don't have a specific story like that
But I have had that feeling before of like just fucking up
Terribly in front of people
When I thought I wouldn't
I've got a I've got a small story about this that does haunt me to this day. This was the weirdest
Okay, this was the first time in my life. I attempted to make any kind of sexual advance on anyone
Uh, nice. It was it was nice. Okay. Well, whatever. I'll let you be the judge
Um, there was there was a girl in my class. I don't know what was going on
We were like out. I don't know like feel there. Whatever. We were just in school somewhere and uh, um
Like this girl was a well-known slut and I was like, oh, yeah, all right. This will be easy like yeah
Don't worry. I thought she was kind of cute. You know, I'm she likes to park in cars with boys. Exactly exactly
so
I forget what was going on, but this is how I communicated my sexual interest in her
um, okay, she like
We were I don't know what was going on, but like she like offered her hand. Oh god. This is this is
She there was something going on. She like held her hand. What was that? Where were you?
We were we were outside like doing something like the two of us
Um, was this like a school dance or something? It might have literally been a band camp actually
okay, um
And the way that I communicated my interest was she like held at her hand
Like I grabbed her hand. There was like she had like two fingers up
And I I made the like jacking off gesture on her fingers with my hand
This is what I did
What oh
And she just was like what and I was like that's that's like so forward
It was I know it was incredibly forward like okay. There was we were kind of friends. There had been jokes about sex
Uh, but like this was what I chose to do as my
Method you mean do you mean you guys I was probably sex before or no
Well, no, I mean, I was a virgin for many more years after this. She definitely was not
In fact this same girl, but you and her had joked about sex. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, you know as a group
That's less awkward. I guess if like the tone had been set to like make humorous
No, well the thing is it wasn't it wasn't like on that level. I made it real in a way that was not anticipated by anyone
I want to know how how old were you? I want to know how old were you?
I was pro I was between 16 and 18. I think somewhere in that oh too old too. Yeah way too old
It was it was too real and weird and uh, no no no no no
It's like when like it's like when the nerdy guy who nobody really likes you get paired up with in class to do something
Your girl in this example and he like starts coming on to you in some ways and you're like, oh christ, dude
What the fuck yeah, what is this when he like when he like when he like pulls out his katana
Like behind the school and like corners you with it and is like we're gonna you're gonna figure enough
We're gonna do sex stuff now and you're like, oh no not again. All right. That's it. What anybody else got when they want to share
I have a story that is something I regret
Okay. Oh, yeah
um, it was uh in school. I remember there was this one classmate that I was really
Really did not get along with him
Um, it was because he kept badgering me rather than like I badgered him
I don't know what his problem was with me, honestly
But he was he was bad to everyone
But I feel like he was picking on me the most but it was hilarious because he was the shortest guy in the class
And I was the short and I was the tallest person in class
So it was like a bit a bit of a hilarious duo now that I think about it
And he's such an odd yeah, and he was so I was walking with my friend
In the hallway and he was behind us with his friends and he was heckling me
I don't remember what he was saying, but he kept, you know
Agitating me. So what I did I just I I I formed the fist and I put all my strength in it
And and I turned around and I tried to punch him, but I ended up punching someone else
and I
And I felt so bad the guy ended up laughing at the guy that got punched
And I was like, I'm so sorry. I didn't mean it. I was gonna punch him and and
The guy ran away. I probably punched him really hard. I think he cried
He ran away and cried the violent violent violent violence has no no no don't off switch for for the lethal force
That was I think like one of the last punches I ever threw and now that I think about it
Just another story of her going too far
Just going going too far in this mad maxi and wasteland that is
Lithuania in the
What early 90s? I regret two things. I regret punching that four guy and I regret not punching the other guy after first
His defenses were down at that point. It was a prime opportunity
All right, anybody else anybody else
I don't know how to answer this question because I am a living cringe compilation
And I could think of a thousand stories at least as embarrassing. I can sum up jumping in I have one. Oh my god
Hit us up. Hit us up. I'm jumping in at like the last five minutes of the podcast
Because this conversation brought back a memory so traumatic and so cringy
That I've never told this story in my life. Okay, I vowed to never tell it
It's kept me up at night for like 20 years probably longer
It's
It's the worst thing I've ever done to another human being in my life and it haunts me to this day
I was like a little kid. I was like seven or eight years old
Just a little stupid little bastard baby shit
And I was at a carnival with my mom
And uh
They had the carnival games and there was a girl who was probably in her 20s or late teens
You know working at the carnival games with the balloons and you throw the thing at the bottles or whatever
And I went up to there with my mom
And
I don't know how it got brought. I think she had like a little kid with her or like a
She mentioned that she had a kid or something. I don't know somehow
It got revealed that this uh
This this lady working at the carnival game had a kid of her own and I was just like this
I was a little baby. I would never do this ever as an adult
Ever
But when I found out that she had a kid the first thing that came to my mind and I said it out loud to her
was
Wow a cheating carney and a bad mother
What?
I do not condone that I did this. This is the worst thing I've ever said to a human being
You said that when I was seven
I have two I have two questions. I have two questions one
What made her a cheating carney and two and two what made her a bad mother?
No, nothing. She didn't need to do anything to me. She did nothing to me. She didn't even cheat. She didn't even cheat or anything
I had no nothing against her whatsoever. I was just for race for class
I hadn't even like thrown the dart yet to confirm that she was cheating in any way
Oh guys
In my stupid like bastard baby shit right like eight-year-old brain
I just for some reason associated like carnies with like people don't like carnies because they cheat
You know like like how oh people don't like lawyers like it was one of those things
I assumed that it was like a stereotype and I just fucking like it just came to my brain
And I said that and the look on this woman's face. She was so
Yeah, did your mom hear you did your mom hear this? Oh, yeah, she heard me and like the woman was so livid
She said get the get out of here. You can't play this game. Get get away from me, which I don't blame her for at all
Yeah, I would have done that. I like if a kid had come up to me and done that
I probably would have left over the counter and kicked it in the face and gone to prison
So I don't blame this woman at all. She was like livid. She said go away you little brat and like
The like the worst part is
Like my mother because she loves me and she's my mom
Like my mother like stood stood there after I like ran away like a little fucking coward
My mom stood there and like defended me. Oh, yeah
That's a losing battle. That's a losing battle. Yeah, like oh, he didn't know what he was saying
He's just like no, I knew what I was saying
You like like she should she should not have defended me. She should have beat the fuck out of me
like in the public square
and um
I don't know since you guys were all debasing yourselves. Yeah, and revealing your darkest most shameful moments
I thought I'd reveal mine
My my story my shameful story is is is it is actually the most like painful memory that I have
The most it's it's yeah, that's that's the one thing that I remember is being like that one that you're ashamed of doing
Yeah, oh, yeah, okay. What the fuck that's the most shameful you've got
Yeah, I mean I hurt someone's feet. I hurt someone's feelings. All right. All right. You know what I'll share one
I'll just share the one that that's probably the strongest in my mind just to fucking
So when I was in fifth grade
It was valentine's day
And I was really I was really hoping to get some kind of love letter from several girls in my class
I had a crush on
However, I did
actually get a love letter
But I had no idea who it was from it just said like I like you or something
I saw this episode of king of the hill and it was your and it was bobby's grandma that actually said to you
That's fucking bizarre
No, I'm looking around class like which like hoping it's one of the girls
I have a crush on like who the fuck sent me this letter
Um, so I'm at gym class and at the very end of gym
A girl comes up to me who I've never seen before in my fucking life and it's like I've got a crush on you
And I having never spoken to a girl before
Just like freak out and don't say anything. I won't look at her in the eyes
I won't say anything to her and I just like get because like gym class is ending
So everybody's getting in lines to go back into the building
So I just kind of like rush into line and my my friend
Not particularly close, but you know, the only friend I had in my class was like behind me in line
and um, I guess this girl is like trying to speak to me, but I'm just like hard line ignoring her and pretending
I don't notice and like
She starts badgering this kid because I guess she can tell we're friends and I say to my friend like hey
Can you like I don't know what to do like can you tell this girl to stop bothering me, right?
And my friend looks at her and says
He hates you. Oh fuck
Oh god, I mean we've gone nuclear
He then tells me that he said this and I'm like ha ha and like she's
She's like crying and he's like laughing and so I laughed too
You had to pick a side you had to pick a side
And so it's so like it was gonna be a fucking queer into girls. So yeah
Exactly. I was staunchly anti-girl at this age. Yeah. Um a few a few like weeks or months later
We're doing like a class thing where um, this is a very bizarre project
Every one of my class had to pick like a famous person from the 1800s
And like we did this thing where we all we were all in the auditorium
And we just like had to stand still like a statue and if someone came up and like touched our hand
We had to give a speech as though we were like a living museum of that person
Okay
So I was George Washington carver and that girl came up and she kept like tapping me over and over again
And I like terrified just kept giving my rote speech of being George Washington carver like I literally was a
installation at a museum just like
Watching this girl like I I very
Clearly remember like her heart broken face like pressing my hand over and over again hoping I'll say something else
Don't treat me like a human being stop with the camera responses, please and and she didn't say a damn word
That was the last I ever saw
Do you like tugging at your sleeve like tearfully like please please please conrat and you're just like did you know that?
I invented peanut butter
Exactly what it was
And that's that's the first thing that comes to buy by that's a good one
That's really funny, but I have easily a dozen stories that embarrassing. I don't know why but I imagine that story
In the style I don't know why but I imagined while you were telling that story that it was like animated
Oh, it doesn't matter people have been talking over me this entire podcast. I don't care anymore. Yeah, sorry
Nobody will ever hear what I say they'll listen back. Uh, uh, uh, uh, Tom munchie. You want to tell stories or should we move on?
How can I top that?
I got nothing
Oh, I there was one time where I hit my brother over the head with a metal detector
And I felt bad about it. I hit victor with the face of the microwave door
That was pretty awesome. I threw a kettle at my sister's head as a child and I don't know what got into me over there
I wasn't a child. I was 21 when I hit victor with the microwave door
When we were fighting over who would get my friend's hamburger
That he offered to victor, but I felt entitled to it. So I
There are many stories about things I shouldn't have done
Sort of like digi but not in the sense that there are too many good ones
But just in the sense. I don't know what people will gravitate towards
There most of them are just like
Not embarrassing in the sense of like, ooh, who weren't you like a kooky child?
But like weren't you kooky like three or four years years ago and therefore aren't you just a terrible person?
Uh, I don't know. I mean I a lot of embarrassment just comes from like
Me saying things which would have been funny if I were on the internet and not terribly awkward
But like me trying to do edgy humor outside of like like an offline like
Just at a school and it coming up really weird and terrible and like
I don't know like I like I like I just would speak in some sort of like grotesque internet meme
And I would say something gross and then people would be like wow
What a gross asshole and then not talk to me anymore and I would think you know what maybe I should have seen this coming
Like why don't they get it when I when I when I say gamers rise up bottom text and strike the awkward penguin pose
Why don't they like get that? Yeah, what's I don't understand?
What have they never been on four champs?
There was well, there was one time where I was just talking to some girl and I was and I was joking about how one time
I saw like like like like there was this one image
I saw someone who like cooked their their period blood into bacon and ate it and she looked really upset
And I was like, oh, yeah, I guess you're not supposed to say that to people
How does one hook their period blood into bacon? Well, I put it on there. Yeah hook in why not why not?
You eat the placenta you cook the period blood. This is really gross
I'm imagining like a link cable from your pussy to the
Well digi they have those they have those rubber cups now that that that you just stick right up there and it goes into a cup
So you can pour it into anything you want you cook blood into you cook blood into like black pudding
Yeah, that's true. So like why not use it. I guess I did a couple months ago
I had a foe that had uh, it was like a blood foe. Oh god not a period
Like an foe like a blood like a blood. I have many blood foes
I have a new blood foe every day
Yeah, all right guys next fucking question. Shall we?
All right, I apologize to the carnival lady. I'm sorry
She hears you out there. So lying car a cheating car
All right, here we go. Uh, this is from suole as far as I can tell. All right go
Yo, okay, so munchie college. It's a bad idea. Everything you're saying sounds exactly like what I was
Maybe I'll make friends or something
No, like like everyone's saying about the financials and like I get it
But if you're saying like no, I've got it handled
I have to argue with you on a more important point
Which is the fact that the experience is not valuable you think it will be right now
But the amount of like real world knowledge that you will gain by actually being an adult and not being in some weird like daycare facility
For adults is so much greater if you actually just move somewhere and start your career
You're so lucky to be so young and have so many people actually care about what you're making on the internet right now
You could just bend st. Style
Start making shit and people would love it and you could be good
You think oh man, I'm gonna meet people. No, everyone in college is like a fucking super
Libtar'd like no, it's not gonna work. There are some good people you probably will make a friend
But here's the thing munchie. It's not a good idea
You can make plenty of friends just by being a normal human being being in a classroom in college
It's not like being in the classroom. I love this guy. He never stopped and no one talks to each other. It's a huge problem
No one gets along. It's listen high school is like the most. I mean college is the most
Fucking like denigrating experience ever will destroy you won't learn anything you can't learn from a book or by actually making things yourself
That's the most important thing just push yourself to keep practicing and you will become good
I I like honestly
I love the kind of that man's gym that guy's a fucking
So what I want to respond let munchie respond to two things first of all the
Two things that come in like every college discussion, which I don't understand
Are the speaking with absolute certainty about all colleges ever and the and the all bad
All colleges ever. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You can't you can't like going to college is a mistake all the time
I don't know about that. No
I feel confident
I'm worried about the liberal people in colleges nowadays
They're not that's not
You're gonna get off like some some some chick with a green side cut is gonna like is gonna come and like burn your house down
Okay, you guys have to remember that munchie is a libcock. So this is not a problem. Yeah. Yeah
Also, for me, I think the biggest concern I would question directly at me now
It's the yeah, I know, right? No, I'm just saying like because I was thinking about this after the conversation
You and I had about college munchie is that like
You were you were implying that you were like, oh, I'll come over to your house every weekend
And I'm like, how the fuck are you gonna have time for that if you're in college?
I like a serious college. I understand that that I should I misspoke and I'm and I said that like well
Well, not every weekend in the conversation, which you're referring to I misspoke every weekend is not realistic
Uh to go back to what the guy was saying
Okay, the second thing uh like aside from speaking as though, you know about every
Social like like group in every college ever aside from that
Also the just be a real person in quotes and you'll be just fine
I don't know like okay
If I were to just continue what I'm doing now what I would be doing what I'm doing right now
Aka never leaving the house and only talking to people online and doing my art slowly
So if that's that's what the equivalent would be
Going to college is being a real person all of you guys are wrong college is good being a youtuber is morally fucking
Reprehensible, I would give anything to have not dropped out of college
Wait, wait, it felt like the only two options here are be a youtuber or go to college
No, well, they're making it sound like oh drop out of college and be an artist
Here's an idea fuck faces stay in college and be an artist
And maybe don't ruin your entire life by dropping out and devoting everything to this fucking dead end of an artistic career
When I hear quote be a real person, I think get a cubicle job is what this guy is saying
Okay, okay, the thing that the thing that stands out to me most about what this guy's saying
Is the idea that there is nothing that you learn in college that you can't learn from a book
Or somewhere else like they don't have a monopoly on like secrets
Ben, of course, they don't have a monopoly on all knowledge
But like there are of an ensure you can learn some technical skill in books
But like what I've said a thousand times
I will have an instructor with me who is instructing me on a personal basis
He is helping me through things as well. I will be surrounded by constant artists. That might be great
That might be great or it might suck ass
Okay, obviously there is risk, but it is an educated decision
I'm making based on literally attending not a metaphorical college, but a college. I'm going to
Munchy, I'm not
Being a digi here and I'm not saying that college is a bad idea and you will regret it
You might not but I am saying that you you can't you can't tell me that you have it
It's an educated decision because you don't know
We you you look you will not know if it was a if it was regrettable and a mistake
You can talk to people who've been there and you know until after no, I'm not look you just won't know
Okay, it's just a fucking crapshoot. That's all I'm saying. It's a crapshoot. It's not a crapshoot. It's just always bad
Tell me one time. I've ever been wrong about anything
Oh
I didn't like the anime you recommended
Like like what shit wait made you didn't like angel of death
I I liked it at the beginning, but the further I got the worst. Well, I only saw the first two episodes
I can't you can't judge. Oh, I would I didn't see the whole show
I it seemed like your kind of thing based on how much I saw
I apologize that the show went to shit from your perspective. It's okay
I wasn't wrong at the time
Oh, I'll give you that much digi you're not there's nothing nothing is guaranteed
Of course and no matter how educated you think you are you could end up regretting it
Here's the thing you will you will end up in debt. You might end up okay with that
Maybe then of course that is true. I'm not saying I'm guaranteed to enjoy college
But again, I'm playing the odds and there's also no guarantee that I'll be able to make a living on the internet
With no sort of a hand and like foot in the industry whatsoever. There's no guarantee in that either
Okay, but but I'm just saying the idea solution to that is to just accept a large amount of debt and then pay that off
That's not all that I'm doing
You know, that's not all that as a man with debt
I can definitely say having debt is the worst part of my life and the biggest regret I have and the thing
I most wish I didn't have sure the idea that somebody on a fucking podcast
Can wave their hand over all of it and say that college is always a bad idea no matter who you are is insane
Well, only did you say that you're
Yeah, I know just like the idea that like say your father is saying if you don't go to college
You'll fail no matter what is also insane. Of course. Nice. Okay. Here's why here's why college didn't work for me
Because I I went to a community college. I didn't have the money or the grades or whatever to go to a real university
So I didn't really meet people or it didn't really take it seriously
And I went into college with an attitude of I don't need this I'm gonna be an artist
So why am I here? So I fucking I I floundered in it for three years and then dropped out
but
If you have the chance if you have the real opportunity
If you if you have to take if you have to like get yourself into debt to go to college
And you don't think it's for you then it's not for you
But if you have the opportunity to go to a real university then it is an experience that is valuable
You will probably make friends. You will probably learn something
You will probably get a good career out of it eventually
I just I've never known anybody who I respected who went to college
I went to college. You asshole
Tom you wait. Well, you did wait tom. Do you have a degree? Yeah, you do have a degree
Yeah, but you don't you you hate college. Okay. Let me replace that Ben is a degree
But I've never known anybody who went to college and didn't regret it that I respect
I don't entirely regret it. Well, I don't regret it. Well, hippo, you don't
You're from England. It's different
I I went to a social function a smash tournament at the school that I want to go to and it was a nice time
I didn't like make a new friend. I hope I hope to god
Guys, please we already had this argument before and I don't think we're bringing up anything new
You're not trying to tell me that you
That a smash tournament is an argument in favor of college. No, I'm not what no
Obviously, okay. Okay. Maybe if everyone would stop fucking speaking over me
So I can actually say what I'm trying to say and not just say one sentence of it
And then I have to stop munchy
I have to keep arguing because I have to keep increasing the time that I'm on this podcast so I can get paid for it
Now that I've jumped in
I'm not saying oh, I won't go to college because there's smash tournaments. That'll be cool. That's not at all
What I'm saying don't even like get that out of your mind immediately. That's I mean, yeah
I thought that that would be ridiculous. I just don't understand. Oh my god. Did you I can't believe you right now
After I just said that I want people to stop in or under me you come in saying something
Obviously, it's just hard because everything you say is obviously fucking retarded
Anything you have to say
At all munchy, please continue. I'm saying that I went
People are saying you you won't make friends the guy in the bush now saying you won't make friends
You just won't do it. But I went to a social function
I went to a social function and it was great. Sure. I don't have like oh like hit me up on discord
They are we're best friends now
But it was nice to hang out with people and it wasn't an air of like, oh, I don't know what I'm doing
I can't make friends here. I've been with the same sort of cultural
Like I've been to this school and I don't dislike the culture at all. It will be fun
I feel like anyone who says you won't make friends is just a weird person who wouldn't make friends anywhere
Yeah, like obviously that's wrong, but this whole friend argument is weird
It's like it sort of feels like we're arguing past the point because like yeah, you you you can make friends at college
But you can make friends
I feel like munching can easily make friends in any circumstance
He was in like there's no reason to go to dude everyone listening to this because I feel like most of the people who
Listen to the procrastinators are like in their late teens probably that's the demographic
They're probably you know weighing their options of whether to go to college if you can go
Fucking be young be young and be around other young people for the love of god
Do not be 29 years old and be a fucking youtuber and having a crisis. I want to go back to college
That's all I want in the world. I want to go back
Don't be a youtuber, but don't go to fucking college
Just get a regular fucking job like a normal human like 90 percent of the population who are fucking fine
You can go to college after the regular job and not have fucking death let people make their own choices about their own lives
If you've got the opportunity to go to college
Don't let people make choices about their own lives because don't make the wrong choices. Everyone lives their life fucking wrong
Hold on we are all people who have lived wrong and have the opportunity to tell people how to how to avoid the mistakes
We've made
I didn't make any mistakes. I made all the right decisions at every point
I came in like an agent of chaos
If you have the opportunity to go to school and you won't settle yourself with debt
Yeah, it's probably a great idea, but like it's the trade-off. Okay. It's the trade-off of a huge amount of debt
Oh
May or may not benefit you
Dang it. Oh, we're gonna get copyright claimed. We play that too long
No, it's from a video game. You can play video game music. Oh, okay. You might be right. You might be right about that
I I just want to say that I think it's really hilarious
that like
Munchy is constantly defending college from the standpoint of not having gone to an audience of everyone else who has gone to college
No, you're you're you're disparaging it from someone who never finished
I don't give a shit
Everyone I've ever told it's not just me. It's not like I haven't spoken to countless people who've been to college
It's not like I've haven't I don't have a huge
I am someone who's been to college and I don't even think it's bad. I'm not even against it
I'm skeptical, but I'm not like unilaterally saying the college is bad
Uh
Me hey munchy
Do you want to live the life of ben saint living with nine other dudes and making 400 dollars a month for the rest of your life?
Yeah, that's the lifestyle you want. Ben seems pretty fulfilled in his life. Well, then you'll be fine. Go to college
Wait a minute. Wait wait ben's life being like that isn't because he went to college. It's because he became an artist
When he was both are equally the problem. Yeah, okay, but he does have no I mean
No, becoming an artist was the right choice for me and I'm fucking happy with my life digi you asshole
I know you're happy with your life. I'm asking munchy if he would be happy with your digi
Here's the thing. I'm in front of a panel of people who have been to college
Who do I like the most out of this group who I like want to I'm sorry. I shouldn't say like that. It's a very mean thing to say
I
I mean, who do I respect?
Who do I respect? Like what kind of life do I want to lead? Oh hippo ben?
They both went to college and say it been in ben's case. Oh not like not a bad thing
You know there you gotta brood the prawns hippo was just yeah. Yeah, it was cool. It was good. Yeah. Well. I want to do that
Well, go ahead faggot. Well, I'm just letting you know that it's the worst decision you could ever make
Hey, man. Look, I used to visit my buddy who went to uh, michigan state, which is an actual college
Yeah, I used to visit him. I'd come there for st patty's day and it was beautiful
It was amazing
He would just walk around the college town going into everyone else's apartment
Having part every every every single house or apartment had a party in it with drinks and girls and fun and friendship
He was friends with the whole town go to college and you'll be just like that guy
Every time it's it's always good. I'm just saying that I'm now
I'm making the generalization
I'm going to college. It's like saying I'm gonna get an abortion on myself. It's like I hate my life
And I want to die like listen, but I I'm going to college. It's like saying I want to be castrated
If you go to college if you go to college, you can become an abortion guy
Professor and you can do that. You can be I just think it should be flexible
And if you don't you shouldn't feel like like if you like you need to fend like like if college
Isn't working you should be willing to
I'm not saying that I will
Like college is the best decision to me for definitively 100 percent. Of course there is risk and I understand
I'm sorry if I seem more to senses than usual. I'm just annoyed
But yeah, that's fine. I'm on team munch. I I believe in you boy. It's fine to be annoyed munchy
I understand why you're annoyed. I'm just annoyed every time anybody says the phrase. I'm going to college to me
Well, like every time I hear that phrase. I think oh great. Oh great. You're perpetuating everything I hate in the world
Great
Everything the same as it's been who fucking cares you have the opportunity to do anything else
But you're gonna do the same thing great. I wish the best for you
No, don't don't wish the best for me. Don't change stop. No more look
Can I can I make one here's how I win this conversation because conversations are about winning
So here's how I win it. They're not about understanding each other
No matter what you do in life, you're going to regret it. Whatever you do to your 20
You're gonna regret it when you're 30. So just do whatever you want, man
Everyone just do whatever you want. I win
Uh, yeah final point on this. I think this is a real actually big brain intelligent point
It's that I think that college
Is kind of the pleasures of childhood and then like working
This is not meant to be demeaning and then like whatever like getting a job
That allows you to get like the pleasures of adulthood
I think the pleasures of adulthood are better like having control of your life sooner and you know
Like what not going into debt being financially solvent
That's that's the main reason why I think that I mean and I would never say college isn't right for anyone including munchy
Uh, it's just you know, like well if you want to be a doctor, you got to go to college and a conversation
Uh, you know, but if you want to be a doctor, you're not a human being
Well, all right, fair enough fair enough. I want to be a doctor
I I I have um, I have like secret dreams of being a psychologist or a therapist. I
That's not a doctor
What are you talking about actually you need your doctor
I think about that a lot like I really want to go back to college and like major in psychology or something
So I can like do you actually have a doctor to be a psychologist
Well, you can be like a therapist without a literal doctor
I think or a sociologist you do not require a medical degree
You're you're not a medical doctor, but you do but you do you need you need your ph
You need your phd, which is a doctor. My buddy. My buddy's a psychologist. He uh, he went to a lot of school. It's crazy
Psychologists are cool. Psychiatrists. There's no one. I trust less in this world
Psychiatrists are actually like more
I mean, they're the one with the more exacting like medical degree. That's true
They're the people who I am thoroughly disgusted by
All right, let's move on to the next we got two questions left people here
Mr. Waffle guy is the one so here he goes with his question
All right, so on the halloween and student debt episode. We got a really good discussion about monkey's college plans
And what hippos got besides youtube
That's all fantastic. I loved it. But my brain mouth requires more
Feed it. It's greens. Give me the sustenance of the plans of the rest of the pcp methods
Anyone else on the episode? Where do you want to take yourself in the future?
Where do you see yourself and not only individually, but with the pcp? Or do you plan on doing?
Well, I've been tensed. I'm not going to college anymore and the and that that no one should go to college
So now I've officially abandoned that idea. So now I don't know those futures right open
I'm it looked like a career in homelessness. It's looking pretty good right now. You know just
I I I my career is going to be I'm going to become andrew hussey, but good
It's what I'm going to do. That sounds good. So you'll be toby fox then you'll be toby fox
Uh, yeah, but I'll have a different name called my name toby bison or you know
I don't have like a long term like step by step plan. I know that I'm gonna finish max surviving tbap and then
Uh, take a take a break takes like a social media break and go away for a while until vapors three is done
I just all I have is a list of projects. I don't have a life plan. All I have is a list of projects
I mean, that's and they go to tbap vapors three
Biscopades champion two and that's it. That's not that's almost admirable about more than anything
I think more than anything like life goal than you could have just having a list of projects. That's really nice
That's all I have. That's all I am is my list of products
All I am is my list of projects and the fucking bullshit standing between me and them. What a beautiful future
I feel that I feel that hardcore Ben
Well, my my current plan is next year to downsize my living situation because I overexerted myself moving into a place
That was too expensive. So I'm going to move into a less expensive place
Uh, try to reduce my cost of living while saving up so I can pay off the debt
I have to the government over taxes. Good plan. Eventually pay off the taxes
Um, once that's sorted out
Try to move my career in a way that I don't have to be so focused on having to do anything mainstream whatsoever
um
moving in a more artistic direction try to work with other people more because I'm
Increasingly less interested in what I can do by myself and more and what I can do with other people
um, so try to do that and then uh,
Maybe two or three years from now
Fuck off from all of it and go have a kid
Somewhere and two or three years in the mountains become a you want you want you want big digi
You want to talk about you might as well be saying i'm gonna abort myself. They'll have a fucking kid. I want to abort myself
Why would I hold on? What's the point of living at all?
What's the point of making a new life if I make a kid? Maybe he can do something he can make good
The point of life is the experience of living which you are giving up
You are giving up for some other person to have those experiences instead
Like consider this as a 27 year old nothing is fun to me anymore
However, having a kid I can experience fun again vicariously through that. Oh, you are a fucking idiot. What the fuck?
What's an idiot about that? What are you talking about? I think I think having a kid is not stupid
Everybody remember back when like christmas was fun and like you you you like enjoyed like doing things with people like
Stop chasing the pleasure of childhood and embrace the pleasure
They're about mastering your life and doing what you want and having a child can be one of them
What is more mastering your life than
Having well, I don't know what I'm arguing because it's fine to have a kid. Just I don't know
Man, yeah, I like I would like to see a new new lull arc of digi
Individually as human beings we have very little impact on the world
Continuing the legacy of humanity is far more important than anything we can do
That sounds like the most selfish reason to have a child imaginable. What is selfish about that?
What is selfish about wanting to continue the human fucking race like selfish would be being like
I'm gonna perfect myself and never continue humanity
Because I'm totally gonna have such a huge impact on the younger generation
Like like you don't need to continue humanity like it doesn't need continuing. It's gonna continue just fine
Oh, well, I mean, okay, somebody's gotta do it. Take responsibility and do it. You know
Fuck fuck it. No, man. Oh, fuck you. Let me tell you
I just want to be happy. That's my hope for the future. I just want to find something that brings me peace
I'm already happy
The point the point of life the point of life is the experience of it
And I don't I mean sorry if this is fucking selfish or whatever
But I don't want to give that up so that someone else can have what is giving up about how I don't understand
How having a kid is giving up anything you fucking being a parent is fucking boring
Kids are automatically more interesting than anyone your own age. No everyone my age
I already thoroughly understand. You're all the same as me. You're all fucking boring. All kids think the same shit
All kids think the same shit. They haven't had an original thought and they're shitty lives
They're worthless like 14 and like they understand a world you can't even conceive of because they've been fucking
Don't be just by then you're already and you fucking thought all their shit every listen kids are boring because by the time you have them
You have already thought every thought they'll ever have like a hundred times over. Maybe when they're like 30
Maybe when they're 30 if they're a super genius
Maybe they'll like seed your fucking mental capacity and teach you something
You're you're so fucking smart that your kid has to be a super genius to teach you anything
That's what you're saying then look at what what we do compared to what our parents experienced in their life and just
Just think about the radical difference and how they're able to kind of understand it through us
I'm just saying that has value. I don't want to understand things through people. I want if look, okay
Maybe maybe 20 years down the line. There will be a new cultural paradigm
I don't want to experience that cultural paradigm vicariously through a fucking, you know creature that I made
I want to fucking be involved in it. I want to be involved in it myself
I want to be I want to be relevant myself. Look ben. I completely agree which is why the smart man does both
That's what I say, uh by the way for the record. I think being a father is cool
I I think it's super cool. I mean if you do it well, you know, it's definitely the least cool thing
What are you?
All right guys
This is like a fucking it's always sunny episode. We're like they can't solve any problem without having a four hour argument
About nothing. That's pretty much true
This is absolutely true. All right, let's get to our final question. Shall we?
We're pretty split on all these
All right final message of the day. This is from it's from our boy crunchy crunches right again. No, I don't
Let's see what let's hear. What do you got this?
Wait, it didn't it didn't load properly. Hang on nightmare. This is this is gonna be good. I probably uh, let's see
It's already fucking dark at 440. What the fuck?
You survived my missile
But you will not be so lucky this time
Will you see I have a new mission and it puts all of your lives at risk
The pcp dating sim is real and it is coming. We have made good progress
We have already completed half the entire soundtrack in just one week
Costume designs have been finalized and all assets are well underway
The only thing we're missing is writers
If you are interested in writing steamy shit
Go to twitter.com at pcp dating and join the discord
Join the fun or else you will be eliminated
I have them snakes here with me
And if you don't go you will split into the first pieces and inject all of you with his them snakes
Venom and you will die
This is real loud
I just I just want to say that I'm very very disappointed that that cat is out of the bag about them
I really thought no one I thought I thought I could hide his existence forever. That that gave me a stroke. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah
a pcp dating I guess at pcp dating check it out
I guess I just want to say that that that that was like probably one of the funniest things on like the past like
50 pcps
Like not just on the strength of it, but the fact that I was experiencing such emotional turmoil and then and then almost if on like
Q narratively
The levity accusations hurled at me have devolved into hello
It's me the the embodiment of a cartoon villain
Um, that's incredible. Um, I couldn't plan it better myself and frankly it almost makes me forgive you for being a part of the pcp
Dane sim which is a fake project which isn't actually happening
It's actually happening in the in in the sense that people say that it's happening
Blast eye check it's just been people sitting on their thumbs and doing fucking nothing
So okay frank the the idea that the sound guys the soundtrack is half done and wow we make such progress
I mean come on that's
Let's you know what guys prove this wrong. I have heard nothing about this. Is this a thing I didn't fucking know
I'd share with like for it to be real right now
How did they make a soundtrack first without having anything written?
I don't know
All of well, I mean to didn't toby fox do the soundtrack before he made the actual you did god guys
There you go
Um, I've got it right here the the fucking link do they do they not even have artists though?
No, no, oh, you know who's doing the art for me
What kazzie?
No, she's not she said she she said she she said no she was she was okay, but she goes out I guess
Well, hang on this I see this twitter was made like seven days ago or something. This twitter is nothing more than calls for writers artists
Yeah, but it was made a few days ago. Wait, wait, wait. Why is the pcp dating sim location new los angeles city?
Whoa, yeah, wait
There's a discord link here though people
Uh, I'm I'm gonna check that shit out. Cool. They want you people help make visual novel writers
They want you get in there and their logo is like cleaner than our logo. It's kind of embarrassing
I really want that to exist mostly so that I can see how badly they write my dialogue
I'm very interested. Yeah. Yeah, I am. I am highly concerned, but also I can't curious
Okay, I can't wait to get flanderized to shit. There's no more. It's gonna be dope. Please release me. I bet half of my dialogue
This is just gonna be purple. That's that's definitely true. All right guys. We that's it. Are we are we're done?
We've made it to the end just gauntlet finally complete. Um patreon.com
Slash them procrastinators and not them snakes do never go there
Give us $5 for bonus episodes last one was the spooky stories halloween with art and animations by lethal or a mage
It was beautiful. It was glorious and everybody had a great time listening to it
Follow us at tpcrastinators for all your twitter updates
Check out at pcp dating on twitter and I guess go help these guys or something. That sounds fun, right?
Uh, and that's all I've got only do it if you're a person with drive and verve and the willingness to see a project through the end
That's I doubt that's any of you listening right now
Same but I do it and prove me wrong people. Uh, all right. That's it. Thanks for putting up with us yet again
This week for three and a half hours three and a half hours
We're yeah, we're getting out of here
Right now