Hello, everyone, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
With us we got me, everyone's favorite, Ben Saint, we got Gibbontake, we got Tom Oliver,
and we got our guest this week, who I am stoked to present to all our listeners, who I'm
sure you've all heard of Aria de Mezzo, the self-described transsexual anarchist satanist
running for Republican sheriff of Keen, New Hampshire. Did I get all that right?
Mostly except it's not Keen, New Hampshire, it's Cheshire County. Keen is just the largest
town in Cheshire County. Oh, okay, okay. So, right, even it's bigger than just Keen.
Your power would have extended even further. Yes, I have, I want to ask one question before
anything else. Are you named after the song from Final Fantasy 6? I am. Yes, I got it.
I did it. Okay, nice. Well, thanks for coming on. It's been a pleasure talking to you. I appreciate,
no, I'm sorry. I, yeah, so I, so I saw, I must have saw like a Twitter article or someone,
someone mentioned you and I followed it through to an article and I read about it. And I don't
know, just on a whim, I decided to look you up and I saw you on Twitter and I followed you. And
then like a couple weeks later, I think you followed me back and I was like, well, let's,
let's say hi. Let's say hello. Yeah, in general, I try to follow people back, especially if they're
like some sort of content creator. But you know, when this first started, I was getting just constant
notifications on Twitter. So I lost track of everything that I would have liked to have done.
But eventually I started catching up. You were, I saw you were followed by another guy I follow
called a bow of the fifth column. I'm not sure if you're, if you know him, but I saw that he was
following you. Okay, okay. I don't know him. I've talked with him on Twitter briefly. There was a
possibility that I was going to be on his show, but that fell through the cracks for us both. I
imagine he's actually a potential voter for me. Is he? Wait a minute. He lives here in Cheshire County.
What? Yeah, that's what he said. I thought he lived in like, I thought he lived in like Alabama or
somewhere down in the, in the Apple, Appalachia. Evidently not. That's wild. That's wild. Okay,
I had no idea. Um, I, I was, if I, if I were a Cheshire County voter, I think, I think I would be
happy to vote for someone running on a fuck the police platform. You know, we got, we got Ed
Markey here in Massachusetts running for Senate. He's fine. He's cool. He's not, he's not that cool.
So, um, I, I, uh, I endorse you. I think your platform sounds pretty good. I'm excited. I'm
excited to see you running. Uh, I find it a little inspiring. Uh, I find it, uh, I think it's great.
I think it's, um, this past year I've contemplated maybe in the future I might try running for some,
for some office somewhere. Uh, but I don't know. I don't know which one or anything.
Haven't thought that hard about it. Sure. I would recommend it. I would recommend everyone run for
some sort of political office, even if they don't intend to do the job. Like being the secretary
of deeds or the register of deeds or whatever this, someone wrote me in for a land management
position of water management. I don't remember exactly what it was, but it's like,
instead of doing that, they should have just run for that office. I mean,
they would have been able to do anything, but they would have run for and wanted office and
could have gotten their message, whatever their message is, actually out there to people.
It's when I, when I got the, um, the, the primary ballot earlier in the year, I looked and like
the people on there, there were, there was, there were so many of like these minor like
city council offices where people running unopposed or like, you know, two people,
maybe two people running against each other who I, I went and I looked them up to compare them
and they had like no online presence. They had like no, I had like, I, it was, they had like no
profiles whatsoever. Um, and it made it, yeah, it got me wondering like, what, what, what little,
what position could I, could I sneak my way into and just like, you know, start, start fomenting
from the inside out. I don't know. Well, if you pay attention to your state's registry about who
has filed for office and who hasn't, if you find any blank places for either, either political
party, just go ahead and file for that because I think my nomination proves that they will just
vote for you because you're on their ballot. I think, I think that's a good segue because
we're talking about this Twitter article, but like not everybody who's listening to this podcast
may have seen it. So I, would you like to like kind of set the stage and like explain what you,
what your game plan was just for anybody listening who doesn't know
why, why you're even on the podcast, you know, like we haven't, we haven't set the scene at all. So
I figure maybe that might be helpful for someone who's like, who is this person?
I forget that not, not everyone is as clued in as I am.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So the plan was to become sheriff, right? I ran as a libertarian candidate for sheriff
two years ago and this year the Republican didn't file. So I ran instead. The libertarians lost
major party ballot access here in New Hampshire because of the poor performance of our previous
governor candidate. And I expect we, we probably won't get it back this year. So I would have to
go around and collect signatures and all of that crap in the midst of, you know, COVID-19 where
most people won't even open their doors to speak with me, or I could just join one of these other
political parties that already exist and already can bypass all of those hoops. And the Democrat
party in Cheshire County is very strong, which is unusual for New Hampshire. There's almost no
Republican presence whatsoever. So I took the weakest one and that happened to the Republicans.
And the goal wasn't to troll Republicans in any capacity that just sort of happened when
they went online and started complaining about, you know, how did this happen?
You, you would have done it. You would have done the same thing if it was the Democrat slot that
was open. Sure. Sure. Yeah. Okay. I was a little confused about the whole Republican-Satanist
anarchist thing, but that clears it up. If I'm, if I'm not mistaken, you are, you are also,
you're a high priestess. Correct. Correct. Of the Church of Satanism. I feel like I read that
somewhere. Of the Reformed-Satanic Church, actually. The Reformed, the Reformed, can you,
I'm not sure what the, what the difference is between the Orthodox and the Reformed.
Well, the Church of Satan fought for 501c3 status so that they could be tax exempt like all churches.
And then they went on to proudly pay their taxes and they make it a point to always say,
hey, look, we're proudly paying our taxes. All other churches should. And I'm over here watching
the state drop bombs on weddings and doctors without borders hospitals. I was like, you are proudly
paying for that. I want nothing to do with that.
I see. Yeah. Okay. I understand. So, so you're a, I want to ask, so, so you ran in the past as a
libertarian. That would be, that was your party of choice before the, before losing a, I forget
losing a ballot status, right? Correct. And I, so I read that and I was surprised to see,
I don't know, what do you think? Tell me if you agree with this, but I, when I, when I hear about
libertarians, there's a, there's a strain of libertarian, especially like online, that is very,
it's pro gun, you know, a pro like anti taxes, but it's, it's like pro police. So,
like, you know, because police protect property. So I was a little surprised to see that, okay,
she is running, yeah, she, she runs on an anarchy, a fuck the police platform.
Do you have like a, do you have like a, do you consider yourself like a part of like a certain
ideological splinter group or faction with regards to that? Or what do you think about that?
Yeah, the label libertarian is kind of complicated and it can include a lot of different groups. Like,
if you take the most bastardized version as possible, you would have to include Rand Paul
as a libertarian, which he obviously isn't. There are a lot of socially conservative
libertarians who more aligned politically with the Republican party, but
consider themselves to be libertarians for whatever reason. There's also the left libertarians,
which is generally what I would count as despite being hardcore economically to the right.
What do you think about my man, Bernie Sanders?
I think he's probably a snake oil salesman.
Oh dear. Okay. You know what? It's, it's okay. I can take it. It doesn't hurt my feelings.
Well, I mean, he turned around and endorsed people that he adamantly opposes, right? It would be like
me going out and endorsing Donald Trump. Yeah, well, I mean, I wouldn't want to go that far,
but I know what you mean. He, yeah, I mean him and like, I mean, Noam Chomsky is another like,
is another like a lefty thinker or person who is like very much like lesser of two evils, like,
you know, vote Biden. It's, it's, it's an unpalatable position that, that makes me very upset,
but I understand where they're coming from when they do that.
For, for my part, I just turned in my ballot this morning.
The post office was closed. Thanks a lot, Christopher Columbus, but the, the town hall,
the town hall mailbox was open for early votes and I dropped mine off and I would have voted
Biden. I would have done it, but I thought about it and I said, what's the point of voting Biden
in Massachusetts? One of the blue estates in the union. So I thought, so I went, I went with a
pragmatic choice to do the most good with my vote and I voted green. Dab, dab. That was my,
that was the story of my morning. And I wish a happy, happy indigenous people's day to all of our
listeners. This will be coming out a week later. So it'll be too late, but the intention is there.
The intention is there. That's right. Um, yeah. Okay, that's all. Somebody else take over. Somebody
else say something. I've been rambling too long. Well, I mean, I gotta be honest, I haven't looked
up too much about you, Aria. No problem. I am very recently transgender. So I thought maybe
that could be something to talk about. How long have you been out as trans, I suppose?
Officially about three years, but the process really began five years ago. But you know,
it's a slow process. So yeah. So we had three and a half years, really.
Two, two, we've had two people. We've had two people in our little, in our little click
come out as trans in the last, in the last couple months.
Yeah, I really feel like it was accelerated by COVID and staying inside and being like
having nothing but your own thoughts is like, what if, what if, you know, my entire life was
wrong that I thought and it was all different. And a lot of people have been coming out as trans
that I know at least started with Digi. And then I was like, Oh, God. Oh, God, maybe me too. And
yes, it was me too. It was like six or seven months of just thinking about it. Recently, I've come out
and I'm on E already because I'm, I hate NHS sucks. Everybody can't get any of that stuff
legitimately. You have to buy it. Everybody is waiting for me to be the next one to come out
because I'm, because I'm already such a cucked soy boy. I don't know if it's going to happen,
but if it does, this will be stay tuned. This, this will, I'll announce it here if I'm going to do
that. Have you been thinking about it, Ben? I don't want to like push you into it, but like,
have I been, I, every, every time I see, every time I see someone speculate on that, I think about
how funny it is and a little annoying, but mostly funny. So yes, but not really.
I had a similar issue getting estradiol here in the United States, but it was because I lived in
the South where doctors, you know, are very conservative. There was no precedent for a
male to female trans person in North Mississippi. So I went online to a international drugmart.com
is what they were. And I ordered them there. It's not ideal because it would take six weeks for me
to get them. And if I happen to run out, there were always delays. Sometimes it would take,
you know, 10 weeks or whatever. And I would just have to go that period without any of them.
So it wasn't good, but I was ultimately able to take those empty packets to one of the doctors
in Mississippi that I had rapport with. And I was like, Hey, look, this is happening.
Here's a year's worth of estrogen that I've been taking. Will you just prescribe me this so I can
just go to the pharmacy to get it? And he agreed. That's good. But we don't have the NHS here. I
understand that does complicate things. Yeah. I mean, the NHS at the moment is like, it's, you know,
free healthcare, but like, so, so badly funded by the government that it's so it's like,
completely unable to facilitate basically anything. My brother's been like having
been waiting like almost all year to get like a diagnosis on this leg problem that has been
making him unable to walk. And it's like, I feel like the problem he has could have been like
getting worse over that period of time. Obviously COVID is like taking priority. But even before
that, it's just it's been known that transgender prescriptions take months and months to get you
even in touch with a therapist through the NHS before they can like tell you ask you questions
for months and months. And then they can say, Okay, we think that you're, we agree that you're
trans. And now we're going to say you can have the thing. And it usually you're on a waiting
list for then years to actually get the thing. It's like, it's, it's like terrible. It's quote
unquote free. It's like the worst sort of video game ever. I went to a, you know, it's paid away.
I went to a consultation recently for breast implants. And the surgeon there told me that
I would have to have a note from my therapist authorizing it. I don't even have a therapist.
I don't need or want a therapist. I have six grand in cash. I want you to do this for me.
Why is that so freaking difficult? Why are we putting all of these roadblocks in the way of
trans people transitioning? Since women don't have to have a note from their therapist.
That's absurd. That's super fucked up when you put it like that, like you have to be
you have to prove that you're insane enough to want this in order to God. That's kind of like
what it is though, isn't it? Yeah. The implication is absolutely that trans people are by default
mentally ill. I mean, I could, I could understand to a degree if you're going through like your
health insurance and I needed to clear with like your provider or something. But if you have cash
in hand, if there shouldn't be any issue, you should just be like, here's the money.
Like maybe, maybe if you're like, if you're like 13 or whatever, or like 16, but if you're an adult,
imagine being 30.
Like you would probably need some sort of written permission from an adult if you weren't quite
an adult yet. But like, if you have the money, you should just be able to get it.
I mean, especially over, you know, breast implants, those are easily removed if it turns
out that I don't want them. We're not talking, you know, sexual reassignment surgery here.
We're talking about just augmenting what is already here. Sure. And if I decide six months
from now, oh no, I wish I hadn't done this, they could easily undo it.
Yeah, that was one of my biggest like things thinking about it, like
taking estrogen is like, oh God, everything's going to change. What if I don't like what happens
in the future? But I looked into it and it's a lot of it is reversible except breast growth,
if that happens, it will happen to some extent. But then breast reduction surgery is easy.
It doesn't, you know, it's not too much of an issue to get it all back to how it was.
As long as I don't chop off my gonads, I'll be all right.
Exactly. I can do whatever I like. I am curious. I'm sorry, not not to derail,
not to derail or anything, but I did mean to ask about sheriff duties. If you become sheriff,
I read that you are going to have your sheriff's deputies police the regular police and pull them
over if they're like harassing people or like pulling people over. Are you still committed to
this position? Absolutely. That's so cool. Wait, no, no, no, it was better than that. You said
you want you'll have them do that or if they won't do it, they can just sit around in the
office and play video games. Yes, I respond to crimes where there are victims when those crimes
are reported. Yeah, sure. Or they can quit. Or they can quit. That's going to be the sheriff
department under my leadership. Will you quit your day job? Probably not, because I can't imagine
that the sheriff's department, as I envision it, will really require very much of my actual presence.
Do you get like, is it a salaried position, sheriff? I'm sure it is. Yeah, you're not sure?
I don't do it. I'm not doing it for the money. Sure, sure. But I mean,
that'd be funny if you became sheriff and then it just turns out like, I don't know,
now you pay you like six figures or something. I don't know what a sheriff makes, but that would
be pretty neat. Oh, the other thing, you've been getting, you've been posting on Twitter,
you've been getting hassled, right? Someone's been fucking with you and your campaign
right? Several people seem to have been. Yeah. Can you tell us about that? Well,
yes. So I have a sign in my yard that says, fuck them both 20. It's a presidential sign,
and someone keeps stealing that one up. I don't know if it's because they don't like that it
actually has the word fuck on it. Most of my signs for, you know, me running for sheriff,
they don't actually have the word fuck on them, but these do. And I'm not putting them up around
Cheshire County. I'm just putting it in my yard. But someone keeps taking it. It hasn't happened in
more than a week though. And I think it's because the last two people who did it found out very
quickly that I do in fact have security cameras and they are clearly there on YouTube stealing the
sign out of my yard. But more recently, I think it was Saturday night, someone in a gray Chevy
pickup truck went around Cheshire County pulling up almost every single one of my signs.
A woman saw this and reported it to the police. Presumably she also gave them the plate number
of the pickup truck. Police then contacted me asking me if I wished to file a report or do
anything about it. I thought about it and I ultimately declined. However, this is actual
property theft. There is an actual victim when it comes to property theft. And I will pursue it
if it happens again, because I lost $1,500 in signs that one night. And then I had to go back
out and put them back out there the next day. So I lost time. What do you think? A disgruntled
Republican? That would have been my first assumption, except one of my friends lives here
in Keen and he's got an apartment and he had one of my signs in his apartment window
that's on the ground floor. Someone actually ripped his screen out of his window. They stole my sign
and they replaced it with a Rivera for share of sign. Rivera is the incumbent Democratic candidate.
So it could be upset Republicans and it could be upset Democrats. Or it could be both. I think
if it's both, it's proof that I'm doing something right. But I can't identify.
They've put aside their differences. They've formed a truce. I mean, that doesn't even sound
like a joke. It sounds like, yeah, of course they would do that.
I'll upload the status quo, I suppose. Yeah. It's all the corporate wing at the end of the day.
This is really interesting because I read one article about this because I found,
I think it might have been you retweeting it or something, Ben. And at first, I thought it was
like a complaining article like from like a more of a right-wing slant, like, oh, there's this crazy
person trying to run for sheriff. But then I quickly realized that was not the case and it was way
cooler than that. But I thought I read at the end of the article that once you, you would like
withdraw your candidacy or something, but like now you're saying no, like you're going through this
and you have plans to change the way the sheriff's department works, which sounds sick. Do you have
any other interesting ideas besides like policing the police? What are your platforms? What are
you campaigning on right now in a general sense? Liberty, individualism, and the right of individuals
to do as they want as long as they don't hurt people. That's the wider philosophy that I'm
trying to get out there that I'm campaigning on. Good. Okay. I'm getting swayed. I'm getting.
Here in the United States, the police routinely violate that. And it's because of the mythology
of the state. You know, we don't call it kidnapping. We call it arresting. We don't call it,
you know, extortion. We call it fines. We call it tickets. But if you're a victim of having
been extorted for money or kidnapped, then in 99% of cases, made up statistic, by the way,
it's going to have been a police officer who did that crime to you. It's going to be a police
officer who extorted money from you, threatening violence if you didn't comply, or kidnapping
and threatening to kill you if you didn't, if you resisted the kidnapping. I oppose kidnapping.
I don't believe police should be out there kidnapping people for crimes where there are no victims.
The, they say, you know, when, when the punishment of a crime and like the punishment for lots of
crimes is like fees and fines and stuff. And it really bugs me that basically that means
that crime is just legal if you have enough money. Like if that's the punishment for crime,
you can, that's just saying, okay, if you have the money to burn, you can commit this crime.
But like, you know, someone who doesn't have money can't do it in the same way.
That's very true. But someone who has money would just get an attorney and a private defense,
a private attorney and the private attorney would just go in there and get the charges dropped
or get a not guilty. The entire system is like that. They don't care whether you're paying
in a private attorney or whether you're paying the state by pleading guilty because that's what
your public defender told you to do. They don't care. The entire legal system is set up so that
you're going to pay someone and it doesn't matter to the judge or to the DA or to anyone else who
you're paying because that defense attorney, he wants to one day be in the judge's spot. That
judge, he used to be a defense attorney. That defense attorney, he used to be a public defender.
They're just constantly rotating through and they don't care which one of them is actually
getting the money as long as you're paying one of them. And if you can't, I mean, like if you
can't pay anyone, then you can always just get sent into the private prison industrial complex.
There's money to be made there. Fuck money. If you don't have any money, we can monetize your
labor. Yeah, yeah, yeah. It can be... What is it? Meme on Twitter. I've been seeing this week.
It's that face Kamala Harris made at Mike Pence's sassy face. Like point of view, you're up for
parole, but the prison industrial complex industry is booming. Like no thanks. Actually, no, I don't
think so. USA. USA. USA. And of course, the police love to be out there arresting people for this
kind of nonsense and finding people because otherwise, you know, they can't pay their bills
and they can't justify their own employment. If police officers, if all of these police
departments out the United States only responded to crimes where there were actual victims,
instead of going out and responding to crimes like, okay, this guy is selling cigarettes or
this guy is smoking pot or whatever, they were only responding to victim crimes. We would
immediately see in the United States that we could cut 19 out of 20 police officers and we
could still accomplish that same amount of work. 100% agree. Yeah. And they don't want that. That's
why police unions are against ending the drug war. That's why police officers are against
ending the drug war because otherwise they can't justify their own employment.
It's the same with real war. You kind of want war to be happening so you can sell all those
bullets you're making. Yeah. That's why Lockheed Martin is so pro-war. They need customers or
victims. Yeah, I'm a big, you know, it's like you can invest in like other things like social
programs and like education and stuff, social welfare and that's whatever infrastructure you want
that like prevents crime or you can invest in, you know, the police which, you know, fight crime
or, you know, you know, persecute it or whatever. Well, that's what we're told, right? We're told
that they fight crime but police have no obligation whatsoever to protect. The U.S. Supreme Court has
upheld that. You had that school cop in Florida who ran and hid during a school shooting.
Yeah, I remember that. Yeah. And he had the Supreme Court ruled again that he had police
officers, no obligation to protect anyone. If they walk down the street and they see someone,
they're getting their head kicked in, they're not required to actually intervene.
That's so fucked up. I wish I wasn't required to like flip burgers when I worked at McDonald's.
Like you're supposed to do it but you don't have to. If it gets busy, you can just kind of go in
the back and like play video games for a while. You just run away because like it got too stressful
That's really messed up when you think about it. What's your position on victimless crimes?
Because if they're not the police's job, should it just be decriminalized or should there be
another kind of support layer in place to take care of those kind of things like drug issues
or anything else of that matter? Well, ideally, they would just be legalized. Of course, that's
not within the purview of a sheriff. But yes, sex work, drug work, all of these things,
they should be legal. We don't have people, we don't have Budweiser trucks getting blown up
as they deliver their fear to convenience stores because alcohol is legal.
We don't have sex trafficking in large numbers in these places that have decriminalized sex work
because it's legal. It's happening there above the board. People can check it, make sure everything
is legitimate. Even for like harder substances, anything that you would make the argument like
this is bad, like this is like a social ill like heroin or I don't fucking know, whatever.
The punitive model of policing and sentencing is really fucked up that you get sent to jail for
that. They're road pirates. Because it is a victimless crime. I mean, ideally, I think we would
have really easily available counseling services and rehabilitation services. But even in the
absence of that, it would at least be better if you didn't go to jail. Sure. I mean, it's weird
because we generally believe in bodily autonomy, but we have this whole drug war which kind of
spits in the face of that concept from like, it's very rude, which is really strange.
Yeah, I don't like it. I don't like it very much. It's not that great.
You should bring back gladiatorial combat arenas because the police, you know,
you could tell them, oh, you're supposed to like, you're not supposed to punish people,
but punishing people is fun with extreme violence. They want to do it. They want the itching to beat
the shit out of anyone they can see. That's probably why you're cops, yeah. So you just give
them a different job, make it a sport, make them kill each other. Give them, you know, hard, like
heavy metal objects. I thought you were okay. So instead of like, no, no, no, we can fund the police,
but like we fund them with like, we give them like Klingon, like Battle Place or whatever.
I thought you meant like, we bring back like a trial by combat, like in Game of Thrones or
whatever, like, you know, we don't need police. The DA will challenge you to single combat to send
you to the prison industrial complex or whatever. They have all this rage inside. They need to let
it out somewhere. So turn them on each other. Give them a faction name. They don't want a fair
fight. You know, they want they want to kick the shit out of somebody that has less power than them.
Blindfolded. Blindfolded. And they just like are told that they're fighting a child.
And they never have been, but they don't learn.
I mean, you're right. Police obviously do. They're predators. So they seek out the weakest
people to attack, just like all predators do. You know, lions out in the Savannah,
they don't go after the healthy gazelle. They go after the one that's already injured or the one
that's sick and can't run as fast. Same thing, cops do here. I mean, I mean, cop is already
statistically a fairly safe job. But you know, but everyone's like, oh, you can get shot. Oh,
if you're a police, you can get shot. You know, why are risks getting shot going after like a
dangerous criminal when you can just go after a nonviolent drug offender who's not even going to
do anything. Yeah. And whether or not required to do either fight back. Yeah. Yeah. Um, man, boy.
Yeah, fuck the police. We can all agree on that much.
General power dynamics and the police are in a great position to have a lot of authority and
power over the general population. I spend way too much time on Twitter, getting mad,
getting mad at people, quote unquote people, quote unquote journalists, just retweeting some
bullshit about about how like, you know, protesters are gonna are, you know, burning down, burning
down the entire West Coast or whatever. And we need to we need to deploy more secret police or
whatever into cities to, you know, to quash it. This is like, this is the thing that like makes me
matter. This is the thing that I'm like addicted to is seeing Tim Poole tweet some of that and
say, oh my God, oh, Biden's gonna, Biden's gonna come for your parents if he's elected and I'm
hooked on the rush, the rush of the fury. I don't think that's healthy. I don't think that's healthy.
Yeah. It's a victimless crime, though. So I can't stop you. You don't think so. You don't think,
you don't think that's that's a good way to be spending my time? You know, your life. I'm not
gonna tell you what to do. That's right. That's right. That's right. You better fucking not.
No, Ben, you have to be producing media for me to consume. How about I throw you down a fucking
well instead? Oh God. Well, you know, that actually relates back to your question about heroin and
particularly destructive substances like crocodile met crystal meth and all of that, you know, I
may not think it's a good idea for someone to do it. I may not think it's healthy, but that's their
call to make. Sure. Sure. Yeah. The education should be there and that's all. The education
should know what the risks are and then they can decide. The education, hopefully, and then for
when that fails, you know, ideally, you know. Well, we do have support groups like Alcohol Anonymous
and things like that. I mean, we would probably have those for other drugs. Sure.
And failing that like a like a snarky side eye, like, are you really gonna be looking at Twitter
comments? Oh, like bullying? Oh, yeah. Oh, like if someone like you just bully someone who's doing
heroin and like make them feel bad about it. You think that would work? I don't know whether it
would work. I'm not a fan of bullying. That's what the police do. And I don't want them doing it.
I, I agree. It's, that's what people say, like, ooh, we have to, we have to, we should, we should
fat shame more people. If we fat, yeah, that doesn't mean there would be there would be less fat
people. That's a really great line of thinking that has proven to work time and time again.
Yeah, there's no collateral damage involved in that at all.
Same, same. I mean, what is same thing with drugs? Same thing with
crime, generally. Same thing with anything we don't like.
Race. Don't ask me what I mean by that. Like a formula one. Yeah, like formula, like formula one.
That's right. That's correct.
Damn. Okay. Okay. So anyone play any good video games this week?
I really want to play Genshin Impact because I've heard good things about it, but recently I purchased
the Link's Awakening remake and I haven't even had the chance to sit down and play that yet.
It's been at least a month since I've played anything and that sucks.
I keep seeing video of Genshin Impact on my timeline and thinking like that looks pretty cool.
That looks pretty cool. I, okay, but I read that it's a gotcha game and I don't really know what
that means. I don't quite, I don't think I quite understand what Genshin Impact is.
As far as I understand a gotcha game is one where you, you do a whatever gameplay and then you
get points that you can spend to randomly collect more of a character or a thing
and you're, you know, it's a lot of work based on what you get and a lot of them have anime girls
and the rare ones are the best ones. It's loot boxes to unlock new characters and the idea is
you spend real money to get fake money in the game to spend on these boxes. There's a whole
Breath of the Wild clone built around it to incentivize the spending of said money.
But aside from that, I mean it's like a, it's like a open world like what MMO? Like a free to
play MMO? It looks, I think it's a Breath of the Wild clone because like the aesthetic of the game
is almost identical to the Zelda Breath of the Wild. So I'm assuming the mechanics are probably
pretty similar. But it's multiplayer right? Or am I crazy? I don't know. I haven't looked into it too
much because as soon as I heard it had gotcha mechanics I'm like oh I'm too emotionally weak
to resist those things. I refuse. I'm pretty good at resisting the siren song of paying for things.
So I am unless I like it. Like if I like something I'll, I'll, I'll lose all of my, my
reservations. I will like play a game free to play even though I'm not having a good time just
because I refuse to spend any money. I'll play it for like 200 hours and I'll be like nope I'm
able to play it for free. I'm gonna play it for free. I don't care. I just hate the business model.
I think it's shady and corrupt. I mean if you want to charge me for your game, fine.
Charge me for your game but don't, don't present it as free and then withhold massive amounts of
content until you get money from me. The business model is like it's not only
is it corrupt, like everyone is perpetuating it knows it is. There's a, there's a great,
I don't know, I say great with quotation marks, talk on that kind of monetary incentives on
YouTube called Let's Go Wailing and the guy opens up his talk saying like, now just because
this one, we can talk about the ethics of this at a later day and I'm like if that's how you open
up your talk you know you're about to like open the can of worms on some evil fucking shit and
he just goes on for like 40 minutes about like this is how you literally fuck everyone who's
playing your game over and trick them into spending money and I'm taking great pleasure in
and revealing how I've screwed over my customer base and it's just like wow wow you are scum please
die. I mean it's like some kind of the balancing act of like you know you got your free to play
game obviously though you want to monetize it so you got to put in you know loot boxes or
microtransactions or whatever you're going to do it and you got to balance it so that it looks
to the to the greatest extent possible like these are a non-essential part of the game
but that actually is as enticing as possible well you know yeah I mean and actually does
gate off as much as you can get away with right like the only reason people spend money in those
things is because they're enticing for some reason whether it be if it's like in fortnite the
cosmetics are um you know if you're a kid at school and you don't have the cool cosmetic you
don't have the cool dance you haven't downloaded all of the stuff then you get bullied for being
the shit kid the poor kid you can't spend the money on the game so for them it's like oh I gotta
do it otherwise I'm an outcast and it's not even like it's not like a social byproduct of playing
the game like that's inherent to the design from the get-go like in this wailing talk the guy talks
about you have to create a culture of consumption in your in-game economy you have to like if you
playing with your friends you have to build in that every time one of your friends buys something
you get a notification so you feel like you're missing out by not purchasing things and just
like all these little psychological tricks to like pray on like the herd mentality and the
fear of missing out like from people like you know in real life that are playing the game with you
to try and just manipulate you into spending money and this guy's just up on stage with a big
shit-eating grin like this isn't as great how he can just make money off of like stupid people
and I'm just like I hate this this is the most uncomfortable youtube video I've watched in a
long time. I've wondered like you know I mean people talk about whales and like there's I guess
there's two kinds of whales this either just people with too much money to spend or people who are like
who have like like an addictive personality yeah a compulsive personality that's like
and I wonder like to what extent to what extent does whale money come from you know one versus
the other because like I would think if it's largely just like a lot of people with too much
money to spend and then like a few people that are like you know psychologically vulnerable
I think I would think it was less bad like you know what I mean I have no data to save one
way or the other but I have a feeling that it would be more in line with you know people's
not like that they have a compulsive spending sort of personality but the games as a medium have
fine-tuned the act of making people want to spend money on all of these games so well that it
affects far more people than it used to. Well when you think about it like if you're like
if you're like 18 right now you've grown up and video games have just always had microtransactions
oh yeah what do you mean like this is just what video games are. That's so fucked up. My brother
was talking about this uh this he was he's had this Minecraft server that he's been making
and he's a programmer so he's had all these cool things in it but he hasn't bothered with like
paid services and and like buying ranks or buying levels or whatever you know every other
Minecraft server is like extremely pay to win if you jump into the server you can go to their
website and buy hundreds upon thousands of you know dollars or pounds worth of stuff for your
Minecraft account in that server and um he's had friends tell him that they want to pay for things
and when they jump into a new Minecraft server they if there's nothing to buy they feel like
it's a bad server like they just have outright said that they think it's a bad server if they
can't pay to win because they expect it so readily it's so prevalent. What do you what do you pay for
in Minecraft? Well the servers are like modded so that you know they have uh the admin creates
a world um and has stuff and maybe there's like skills like you can get a special ability to mine
really fast or something or you can pay for like a your own private plot of land to build your own
Minecraft house that nobody can grief or something like that stuff that you could get in game by just
playing or you could pay and just get it quicker and people like are legitimately interested and
happy to be able to pay for that because they know and have been and like through all these
triple A games that have sort of pushed the idea that games are boring and long and arduous and
terrible and not fun unless you pay so if they there's no microtransactions they they automatically
don't like what they're looking at they're like oh what I can't pay to skip the grind because they
can't imagine a game that doesn't feel bad to play. Civilization is in decline. It's the end.
We have to go back. We've roamed and fallen a day you know. This is this is this is the beginning
of the end. It sucks. Well that it does yeah blows blows pretty hard. I want to make a game that is
the best game ever but unless I put a microtransaction in I won't get any money because people think
it's lame and I mean you could just sell the game to people. Oh my god.
I'll put a whole price tag on it. Right. It's perfect. Yeah. Why didn't someone else think of
this. People are actually this is a new idea. This is a brand new is the future of gaming looks
actually looks worse because a lot of triple A developers publishers have learned that you know
they can still sell the game at sixty dollars but then include a ton of microtransactions and DLC
that should be part of the season pass that idiots are paying for anyway. I didn't buy Skyrim until
about yeah two years ago because I wasn't going to buy it until it was actually finished.
They just keep releasing Skyrim over and over again. I don't understand.
I don't understand how we as a culture have not become sick of Skyrim.
Yeah. Yeah. I've never played it on Elder Scrolls but you're still sick of it.
Morrowind is better. Why didn't they just stop?
They're making the sixth one. They could sell Skyrim like seven times.
Oh wait wasn't Bethesda recently bought by Microsoft. Microsoft bought Xenomax which
owns like all that including Bethesda. So they might actually make another one.
They already said they were working on six like two years ago. They're just going to take forever
because they're also working on Starfield and a bunch of other games and they're going to sell it.
They're going to sell it for money. Probably and then they'll fill it with microtransactions.
It's funny. It's funny. People are actually usually pretty okay with just buying a thing
if you can even believe that. People are generally willing to make a straightforward exchange
of currency for a user service. The road to this point though has been very,
very gradual. Like you said Rome didn't fall in the day. First it started with releasing games
half finished because oh we can just patch it later. Then they added DLC which then of course
they started cutting content from the game that was already on the disc so that they could resell
it to people as DLC. Then they kept adding DLC and season passes and then they created DLC that
didn't count for the season pass and then they just started adding microtransactions and now we
have all of these things and a typical game to get Skyrim completely if it had microtransactions
would cost tens of thousands of dollars. As it is, it's probably going to be a $250 game if
someone bought it as everything came out. $50 for the game, $50 for Dragonborn, $50 for Hearthfire.
It's insane. It's not as much a AAA thing but it's more of an indie thing but I guess
increasingly there's crossover between those two sectors now. Games that come out early access
but like charge full price and then never really reach a point of ever being done because everyone
already bought it in early access. So what did they care? They made their money. It's like the
Final Fantasy VII remake. I'm not ever going to touch it because Square Enix is promising like
six of these things and I didn't think it needed to be remade anyway and I don't trust the current
company to actually do the job. If they want to bring on the team that made the original and have
them remake it, sure, I'd probably play that but they promised they're going to have like six
different parts to it. I will be stunned if they ever get past the third part.
I mean the first part took like, I don't know how long they were working on it or how many times
they reworked how they were going to do it but the first one took years and years to come out,
right? Yeah. So how are they going to fucking do six parts? Six parts? It'll be like 20,
it'll be like 2045 by the time. Wait, I thought they were going to do three parts. I heard it was
like, so like, oh. Those are like Resident Evil. I think it was Revelations II that had the,
but any example of these games that, oh, we're going to release this in parts over the next,
you know, 10 years or whatever, none of them have fulfilled that promise. Yeah. I never trust
like something that comes out with chapter one. I'm like, okay, I don't care. Come back when there's
the full thing. Maybe I'll have a look at it. I don't want to be strung along for an indefinite
period of time to see maybe if they will develop the next part. You know, things happen. I can't
trust it until it's fully finished, which means I don't, I don't get into a seven part series.
Oh yeah. Namco cut their funding so they had to put four games worth of plot into the third one.
I didn't know they even made a third one. I remember they made the second one and it wasn't
as good as the first one. Yeah. And I think I gave up after that. Well, I have to get ready for work.
Oh yeah. I guess we've, I guess we've been going for an hour. All right. We, we can,
we can maybe move on to doing answering voicemails. And Aria, thanks so much for coming on and anyone,
any of our listeners in Cheshire County, New Hampshire, I would recommend,
I would endorse that they vote for you. Oh, thank you. Thanks for having me on.
Yeah. I'm, I really appreciate you coming on. Thanks so much.
Take it easy. Thanks to you. Thanks very much. Thank you. Very nice. Oh man. That was great.
That was cool. That's so cool. It was such a different vibe than normal PCP. Very different
vibes from normal PCP. I said, I said in the call before we started, I said, like, you know,
usually we have just like random clowns from YouTube on, you know, idiots like Cyber Shell and
whatever, Oblivionfall. People have no real consequence. Yeah. Yeah. They're not basically
not even real, you know. They're not sheriffs. So like, you know, I hope she, I hope she does it.
I hope she pulls it off. God damn it. I hope she becomes sheriff and then promotes our podcast.
Ooh. The official podcast. The official podcast of Cheshire County, New Hampshire.
Damn. Can't believe she'd do my boy Bernie dirty like that though.
That was fucked up. Right. We can all agree that was true. The truth hurts Ben. That was pretty
fucked up. No, no, no, no, no, no, it doesn't. No, it doesn't. No, it doesn't ever. He did endorse
Hillary. Yeah. And Joe. After the DNC fucked him and everything. Yeah. I mean, his choices were
really minimal, but like campaigning for Biden right now. Yeah. Harder than Biden is.
Actually cringe. Yes, actually cringe. Stop. No, Bernie. I mean, he's done good work in that he
is in, in brought the conversation more to the left. It is good. You know, I'm, I'm very sad
that Bernie is not the candidate. Nevertheless, it will be very good if Biden wins and Trump is
gone. You know, at this point, it's just like someone who's like too selfless and it starts to
like offend you. You know, you're just hurting yourself. You're not, you're not being kind.
You're being like self abusive. That's what Bernie is politically. He's a monster. He can't be
stopped. And you know what? Well, Bernie can't be stopped. Yeah, exactly. He can absolutely be
stopped. Well, you had stopped by the DNC twice. He can be stopped from succeeding, but he can't be
stopped from trying is what I'm saying. He will die in the political sphere, but he will never die
in our hearts. He's an old Jew from Brooklyn. He's going to live to be 130. So there. Sanders
2024. I'll fucking vote. I'll fucking vote. Sanders 2024. I don't give a shit.
All right. So the whole argument against him at that point, but you're so old.
No, which is already the point. I know the fucking fucking people, the same people,
the same people who are like, guys, don't, don't, don't laugh at Trump for getting COVID.
Like we need to pray. We need to pray that he makes a full recovery. We're the same people who
are like, oh, have Bernie Sanders got a heart attack. He's so fucking old. He's going to die.
What a loser. The same people. It's almost like people just care about their team winning.
Fucking libs involved at all. Fucking libs. I should have. We should have asked Aria what she
thinks about the fucking libs. We should have. Get her back in the car. Get her back in the car.
We should have. I should have asked her to like, hey, could you, could you for,
can you, can you give me a shout out and say fuck the libs? Yeah. Would you own the libs for me,
please? Oh, missed opportunities. God, if only we planned these podcasts and had a list of
statements prepared, we could have secured that. I, as I was, as I was walking home from the post
office today, I started thinking like, hmm, what should I, what should I ask? What should I ask
the future sheriff of Cheshire County, New Hampshire? Oh, I should ask about the
libertarians who support the police thing. Like, yeah, it's kind of interesting.
And I was interested to say about that. We can do, we can go to voicemails unless either of you
have anything else you wanted to bring up. Oh, no, no, I've zoomed out for one minute.
Disgusting. I was just looking at another chat. Sorry to say that again. Do you need me to repeat
my, I said we can go to voicemails unless either of you wanted to raise any other
issues of discussion this week on the procrastinator's podcast.
Nah. Nah, fuck it. All right, cool. Then here we go. First one up, we got the tar.
This is a topic episode, everybody. It was a topic episode. Are you happy? Are you,
we did it. It was a topic episode with a guest. It was. It's true. It's true. Vote, vote Aria.
Aria Stark.
I didn't realize the thing about the, hey, Eleazar, I hope that in the episode when I said,
when I asked that question about the song from Final Fantasy, I hoped you played the song. If you
didn't, you fucked up. It was only today. I was googling. I was like, you know, let me, let me
make some, do some last minute, get some articles up so I know that I don't make a fool of myself.
And I put her name into Google and this time it auto-corrected to the song, which is Aria
de Mezzo Caratato. And I was like, wait a minute. That's the song. That's, that's that one. That's
the opera song with cellis. You know, everyone's favorite. Yeah. She's going to sing that when she
gets the badge at her coronation. Would they pin the badge too? All right. First voicemail,
Tarbuck transom on ethics. Three, two, one, go. Hi, fast fucking craftsmen and indestructible
super god Tarbuck transom. And wow, Ben, I really like you, but I really do not like this plebeian
take about what it is or isn't utilitarianism. Oh my God. The thing that makes something utilitarian
isn't about the method of weighing things using absolutes or situational ethics or any of that.
It's about your priorities. All of the philosophies try to do as much good as they can. Only the work
of individual writers is about method. If you think that doing good just means making people happy,
then, and you say you shouldn't torture people because suffering is bad, then that's utilitarianism.
But if you say that you shouldn't torture people because the act of torture is wrong in itself,
that's deontology. Oh, he's right. If you do a problem and you decide to pull a lever and kill
one person and save three people because you're maximizing life and happiness, that's utilitarianism.
If you save three people because it would be morally guilty of you by your inaction,
then that's deontology, even though you made the exact same choice for nearly identical reasons.
You still tally things up with literally every decision that you make and you try to make the
most optimal decision available to you. Everybody does that. But if you consider your actions
to whatsoever, you will do this moral calculus. But why you weigh things one way or the other
is the real distinguishing factor of your ethical framework. Fuck's sake.
Okay, well, I've been demolished. It sounds like ethics and morals are stupid and they don't exist.
Like if you could make a decision for almost exactly the same reason
and you can qualify in two different ways,
um, maybe just don't qualify it in either way and it doesn't matter.
No, no, you've gone, you've gone too far.
They've gone too far now.
Words are stupid. Labels?
No, the point is, the point is that you're using a different, a different reasoning
to arrive at the conclusion and a different reasoning might give you the same conclusion
in this case, but it might give you a different conclusion in another case.
Oh, well, could you explain another case?
Sure. Like, if you say suffering is bad because, you know, if you're, if you're a,
a, a, a, a, oh God, what's the...
A dermatomologist.
If you're a utilitarian, you say suffering is bad because pain is bad, is morally bad and suffering
causes pain. Or if you're a deontologist because you think torture is bad, maybe you're, maybe
you're a Kantian, uh, fucking, uh, oh, what's the word, um, categorical imperativist and you're
like, well, if we tortured everybody, then everyone would just be getting tortured all the time and
that wouldn't be ethical. Uh, that would, that would lead to bad outcome. Like, you don't want
to be tortured.
I don't, this doesn't make any sense at all.
Yes, it fucking does. And then you, you come to another, okay, and then you apply the same
logic. You're like, oh, um, hmm, abortion. And then you're like, hmm, uh, then you're for
utilitarian. It's like, well, you know, a bundle of cells, you know, doesn't have any, any brain,
it doesn't feel pain. Therefore, it doesn't actually cause any suffering to abort a, a, a, a zygote
versus a deontologist or versus your a Kantian. And you're like, oh, well, categorically,
imperatively speaking, what if we just aborted everyone, then everyone would be aborted. And
we don't want that. So, you know, different, different lines of thinking lead to different
conclusions that are different, under different situations. There you go.
I really, I have no understanding of what you just said. Maybe I'm stupid. Maybe that's the thing.
I, I'm pretty sure I know how to come up with an opinion on abortion without knowing how or why
to label what my methodology of thinking. Okay. Yeah. Sure. Sure. Maybe you don't, maybe you
don't know what or if, you know, there's like some like ism label for the way you arrive at it. But
like, you still have like a reason, like a method of reasoning that maybe if someone asked like,
okay, well, why do you, why do you think abortion is okay? You could say, well, it's because I think
that this is bad and abortion causes this and therefore abortion is bad. Is there an ism for
changing my mind in every situation, depending on how I feel about it, and not having like a
structure that I use every time because I'm a human and I don't do that? Surely, surely you
must have some axiomatic principles that you fall back to in the case of like a difficult moral
quandary. Surely there must be some things that in general you think you can, you would consider
to be morally good or morally bad, and you might would apply those things in other, in other cases,
right? Maybe I just feel like I would change my mind even over the course of a discussion.
Like, I don't think I could like, like actually stick to any specific thing. Maybe somebody could
figure it out for me, but I don't know. Like, how do I think it differs? I don't know. I mean,
I think to have a consistent moral position, you really need to nail down what are your
axiomatic principles? My principles are liquid. They swish and slush. They go tight and tight out.
It depends on whether, it depends on the tide and on the moon position. On the moon?
Depends on the phase of the moon? Yeah, that'll do. Okay. We got another one from Tarbuck. It's
called the pro clownfish podcast. Three, two, one, ago. First mage left and then Digi came out as a girl.
Then Digi vanished and Gib came out as a girl. Now it's been a few weeks without Gib. So who's
the next clownfish to be a girl now that the previous one is gone? Place your bets now! I'm
gambling that she didn't come back for what will have been last week because I forgot to get this
mail in before you guys record this week. You idiot. Digi was on the bonus episode. Explain
what the clownfish? I don't know. Clownfish can change their gender. Wow. So can humans.
You got me. You got me. Fuck. Yeah, Digi was on the bonus episode. So if you want to hear about
what Digi says with her mouth, you can go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators and
subscribe for money to hear it. It's true. It's true. What was the question? Wait, was the question
who's coming out as trans? It's me because I'm a soy boy cuck. That's why. That's how it works.
What if mage comes out as trans and she comes back as a man?
I mean, well, I'm not going to say that I think it will happen, but I could imagine stranger
things happening, I guess. I don't know. Yeah, I could see it. Why not?
Yeah. Yeah, that's fucking everyone's trans.
A broke. Ben is the next trans because of what a communist antifa cuck he is. A woke mage
because she's a blackpilled migtail.
Mage finally wanted to be a proud boy in every sense.
I'm sorry. She got mad the last time I said that, but I'm joking, I promise.
The last time you called mage a blackpilled migtail, she got upset. I can't imagine why.
Yeah, I don't know. I don't understand it. It doesn't make any sense.
What would even be the context other than a clear joke like this?
I don't remember, to be honest, was like a year and a half ago.
Next one is called Margar, presumably it is from the man himself. Three, two, one, go.
Margar here, still in voice jail. I would like to escape the official death of Ben St. Samurai
master. Though he had started a Yakuza gang and was beginning to threaten me, I feel.
I don't know. I don't believe it.
His death sets a grisly precedent for now only unimportant goons and faceless inmates had been
killed. I think he probably threw down a smoke bomb or something.
Samurai was a plot important main character and his death has grim portents for my fate.
We'll see what happens, but I'm not feeling good about this.
I think he probably replaced himself with a log at the last second.
If I know that guy and I do.
Oh, like the ninjas from Naruto.
Substitution no jutsu.
Yeah, I would imagine so, yeah.
I never understood how that worked. They would need really long arms.
Uh, they use their fucking chakra to pull a log? Like the force?
Chakra's the answer to everything.
I've, now, now hold on a second. I can believe that you can use your chakra to
fucking create like nuclear holocaust level like whirlwind hurricane blasts.
But moving an entire log, I draw a line.
I mean, it's inconsistent with the way other techniques work.
It's just all I'm saying.
If you could move rocks around like that, why wouldn't you just throw rocks at them?
Nobody throws rocks.
I mean, there's probably someone with a rock throw no jutsu.
There's rock throw jutsus.
There definitely is.
Jutsus are just magic, so they can, yeah.
They had a lot of science mumbo jumbo put in there.
Yeah, like how the world, how the world of like Naruto's hair like shows like which,
which direction he needs to spin his chakra to do the most powerful Rasengan.
Yeah.
And the whole like learning about how to do the Rasengan was cool.
That's true. It was.
Unironically, it was based.
I mean, they added all that fucking filler.
They had all that fucking filler in Shippuden that made me quit.
I never finished it.
That I never watched.
I watched all of Naruto Kai.
They just cut out all the filler.
It was just like, here's a bunch of like 90 minute chunks
that are the equivalent to one volume of the manga.
And I just watched that.
It was great.
It was a great watch.
Did it include, include Shippuden?
Yeah.
It was all, it was the whole thing.
Just cut down.
They cut trimmed down the fat and it was just the good stuff.
That sounds pretty good, actually.
Peak way to watch.
Yeah.
Naruto, when it was good, was actually pretty good.
Yep.
Hot, hot take.
All right.
Next one is from, or is called, Antonio P.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello.
How do you cope with the absence of meaning in life?
I don't.
Uh, I don't need it.
Meaning in life, I guess.
Makes me sad all the time.
Like, if I'm not, like, I don't know.
Meaning as in like, oh, when I die, nothing will have changed.
Like, I don't know.
I don't care.
Meaning would be way more stressful because of that would mean
there's an objective goal everyone would have to move towards.
And then you could measure yourself against everyone else in the world
and how close they were going to that objective goal.
We kind of already do that.
But now there's no meaning.
You know.
I mean, yeah, you already do that subjectively.
But there's no, you can at least have the comfort that that's fake
and in your head and you're struggling with that internally
as opposed to it being an external truth.
You know what?
I'm going to change my answer.
It's actually not the lack of meaning that bothers me.
Yeah, the lack of meaning is fine.
Like, I can deal with that.
It doesn't matter.
I don't know.
What would it mean for there to be meaning in life anyway?
Like, who would even get to decide that?
Uh, that's like an opinion.
The great big dog in the sky.
Clifford the big red dog.
Um, uh, no.
I'm sad about all kinds of other existential problems,
but the lack of meaning is not one of it.
Uh, yeah.
It's weird when you break, when you break it down,
that's like, oh, what's the meaning of life?
It's like, well, who are you, who are you asking?
Who are you asking that question on?
That's an opinion.
Uh, okay.
Answered.
Meeting of life solved.
Next one is called,
Your words are like deadly that pierce my heart.
Frowny face.
Three, two, one, go.
Konnichiwa.
I knew it.
This is the log.
Use the log.
Sad boyo samurai.
Oh, he's upset.
Many people accuse samurai of racism.
They say in the discord, that the samurai voice is racist.
Samurai, cannot change the voice that the samurai
partner with them.
You bring a great dissonance to samurai warrior.
I'm with you.
You know what, I actually, I think that samurai
is great representation.
Yeah.
Thoughts?
How do they know what is racist?
Yeah.
We meet him in person.
Pretty insulting to assume that it's some white guy, you know?
Fuck you.
Sounds like.
I mean, even if he was white, like, it doesn't matter.
Really?
It's a silly thing.
We meet him and he's black, he's like, I don't know.
He's some kind of, some kind of just, you know,
just weird.
He's like Scottish or something.
I don't know.
He's an Italian.
I think he's Australian.
How would you even know that?
Because I saw him in a discord.
He's in your server then.
He exists.
Wait.
He's infiltrated your server.
I thought, I thought he said, I thought he said in a voicemail that that was not him in my discord.
Oh, well, I don't know.
Unless there was like a different one.
Unless he was white later.
And that is him.
Boy, what a fuck, what a quagmire.
We got, we got like ninja clones going around.
Yeah, yeah, he's multiplying.
He's like, he's like Clyde Cash.
You know, everybody, everybody is like claiming to be him.
You know, everybody's taking credit,
attributing their actions to a singular identity.
He's like, he's like Spartacus.
You know, everyone's like, oh yeah,
oh yeah, that's me.
The famous line from the movie Spartacus.
Oh yeah, that's me.
Next one is called Homestuck Preservation Problem.
Yeah, sounds like a cause for concern.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay, so I've got a problem.
I just recently started reading Homestuck for the first time.
And I, I realized that the way that Viz Media is preserving a lot of the flash
is by recording, like screen recording it,
and making it into YouTube videos.
And in theory, this sounds fine.
But the person who's playing the game sections
is just fucking mashing through all the dialogues.
So the fuck, you don't text play them yourself?
Or on screen for about a frame.
And I have to fucking pause it,
go back frame by frame just to read the text.
And also, I'm on Act 6, Act 3,
the game where you're running around is Jane.
And there are multiple moments
where you're supposed to click on a text bubble
and talk to Roxy and talk to Dirk.
But in the videos, they don't do it.
They just walk right the fuck past them.
Because what it does is it sends you a, it's a link.
If clicking on a little text bubble is a link
to a full text log on homestuck.com.
And they can't really, I guess, show that in a, in a video, which makes sense.
But it's just proof that the video
is not a proper way to preserve this shit.
The first time through, I was looking at it on my phone,
where, which doesn't have the option of using Flash.
And I just, I just had to skip all those fucking conversations.
Which is awful.
Like there needs to be another solution to preserve this shit.
It will be gone in December.
And Hussie clearly doesn't give a fuck
about preserving it properly.
Yeah, I, I've, I've heard, like, I, I mean,
it's the saddest thing ever because, you know, homestuck.
There's no easy Flash to HTML5, like converter.
How is this not something that exists?
I mean, maybe it does exist, but they just haven't done it
because there's like a billion pages of homestuck.
But they should still do it.
Yeah, but they're not all Flash.
Not all Flash.
They have had, for the longest time ever,
since they changed the website to homestuck.com
instead of MSP, Adventures, whatever.
It's, they've had like the, to experience this page of Flash
as it was intended, click this link
and it opens a little Flash thing so you can play it.
Or like, remember to unblock Flash from your browser
so you can play the game.
Otherwise, here's this video.
And the videos are terrible.
And Cascade, obviously, is like the worst hit by this
because of like the really cool thing of it.
Wait, wasn't Cascade a YouTube video anyway?
No. Do you not remember when you go to the site,
when you get to Cascade, it's a small Flash thing.
You click on it and as the Flash plays,
it slowly expands to cover the whole screen.
And it turns out the Flash file was the entire screen the whole time.
And it's like, whoa.
I think, I thought, what I remember is that it's a YouTube video
that is like big in the screen.
And when you play it, it starts out as like a small, what?
No, no, no, no, no.
It was part of the webpage the first time.
It was a Flash.
It was, it was trick you because you couldn't have known.
Maybe you're thinking about Collide, that was the later one.
Maybe I'm thinking of like, maybe it was a YouTube video
at some point because like the Flash version
was crashing Newgrounds or something.
They did make a YouTube video version of it,
which is the one that's the default now.
But like, no, you must have experienced it like the Flash one
because that was, the video has not existed for a long time.
But it was like, it was when Hussie was like learning
that he could use, you know, the webpage itself to tell the comic.
The whole thing prior to that was like in the banner at the top.
I know that it like expands.
I know that it does that.
I just remember it doing it as a YouTube video, which it kind of does.
The YouTube video does include that element sort of.
It's like, it's just such a sad situation
that it's not being preserved properly.
There is no way, even if the person was not fucking it up,
like it sounds that they are.
Like when they're playing the video to record,
or playing the game to record it for the video,
like watching someone play it on a video is just not like,
it's just not the same as just clicking through it yourself.
It's just not as engaging.
I can't imagine that it would ever be.
That one he's talking about with Jane.
The like missed one, right?
Where you kind of go from room to room
and you click the little yellow arrows.
Yeah, like it's a pseudo point and click adventure.
You have to solve a puzzle.
It's quite simple, but it just involves all like clicking through
and like quietly experiencing the planet.
And if somebody else is playing it,
you don't feel like you're doing anything.
It's so unfortunate.
It feels like almost that the books will eventually be
the preferred way to read Homestuck, which is terrible.
Ugh, God.
Hey, what about some problem sleuth?
Is Flash going to like fuck that up?
I don't think so because those are all gifts.
Those are just many, many gifts in that.
Yeah, you might be right.
You might be right.
I think that the conceit of Homestuck was like
how he had made a webcomic that it utilized gifts
in a really intense way and it was like,
well, what's the next thing?
Maybe I could do like an entire webcomic that's animated
and he made like the beta of Homestuck, page one,
where it was like smooth in Flash.
It was so fucking smooth.
Yeah.
And then he was like, no, that's not going to work.
And then he did it like mostly PNGs, gifts,
and occasionally a Flash.
Yeah.
So problem sleuth is fine.
Boy, I don't know.
Like I really hope they fucking, yeah,
are able to just convert it to something better
and not do it in a stupid shitty way.
Like it sounds like they're doing.
I mean, I don't, I haven't read Homestuck,
so I don't really care.
Tom.
I'm looking, I'm looking.
Tom, you got to read Homestuck.
It's already too late almost.
There's a, there's some like community project
called Flashpoint, Blue Maxima's Flashpoint.
I guess it's like an open source project
of people just trying to like port and convert
Flash games to something that can still be played
without Flash.
And looking at their list, there is a fair bit
of Homestuck content that has been converted and
saved essentially with this group of people
trying to bank as much as the Flash Internet
as possible before the inevitable destruction of it.
So.
Glad somebody's looking out.
It's, it's evolved into an international project
involving over a hundred contributors
encompassing both web games and animations
from numerous Internet plugins frameworks and standards.
So if you care about Homestuck more than me,
yell at these people to fix it on before it dies
because there's a discord you can join and all that good shit.
Imagine, imagine not reading Homestuck.
I, I live it every day and you know what, it's okay.
Cringe, cringe.
No, I wouldn't, I wouldn't wish that on my worst enemy.
Who incidentally is you?
Well, I'm glad, I'm glad you're looking out for me.
Because you haven't read Homestuck and for that reason alone.
That's fair enough.
Uh, next voicemail is from so spoke the moon on a late morning jog.
It's the same where I can.
No, maybe.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm looking up inside right now and the freaking moon is visible.
What the heck's going on, man?
Do you ever look at like the moon?
Think like what the heck?
Like what is going on?
It's just like an orb, man.
It's just like an orb that's so far away that we need to build like rockets to reach it.
Man, like what the heck's going on?
Where there's just like, we're living on an orb, man.
The earth is an orb and it's just floating.
Like what, where are we?
What the heck?
It's like how did the universe start, man?
Yes, big question.
God didn't like, what the, what the heck's going on?
What the, why, like holy, holy fuck, man.
It's just, oh my God.
Voice grail, voice grail, voice grail, voice grail.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll allow it.
So spoke the moon, so spoke the moon.
Congratulations, you just said it.
You said it so elegantly.
I couldn't have said it better myself.
We're on an orb, guys.
Where are we?
Like what's going on?
Dude, the next, the next time you get into an argument with a flat earth or just play this
and they'll be convinced.
I like, when I look up at the moon, I like to look at the sky whatever time of day it is
and think about, you know, maybe, like maybe it's like late and maybe I can see that like
the sun has gone down, but I can see like part of the sky is like a little lit up because
the sun set over that part of the horizon.
And I like to look at the moon and think about, hmm, where's the sun in comparison?
I think, okay, it's down that, that direction over the horizon, but like way further away.
And then think about like, oh yeah.
So, so that explains why like that the moon is lit up from that direction.
It's because the sun is over there and further away in that direction.
So yeah, the sun would be lighting it up more or less in that way.
And sometimes it makes intuitive sense.
And it's like, yeah, I can see why it's like how it's pointing that way.
And other times it like is weird because like the perspective is off because this
sound is like a billion fucking times further away.
And it like feels it's like hard to even, even like imagine the angles involved there.
But I like to think about that.
It's fun.
Yes, I like, I like looking straight up at the sky and then imagining that it's a
like a, like a dome.
And if you look up the firmament, like if you look up enough, like straight up, like lie down,
you can sort of feel it.
You can sort of feel that the horizon line is a circle that is encompassing you.
And the sky is a dome built on that circle.
You can feel the skybox.
Yeah, you can feel the skybox life.
That's what the, that's what the Bible says.
The Bible says, and this is my, this is one of my favorite parts.
It says that God made the firmament.
And it specifically means that he made a big blue dome and he set it over the earth.
And he sat it there like a solid object and it was the firmament.
That's one of my, that's one of my favorite words, uh, firmament, firmament.
It affirms my beliefs.
A friend of mine was going to make, he had, he had like some tentative plans to make a
rogue like one time and the game was going to be called firmament.
And the game was going to be about ascending like vertically, like level to level climbing
the mountain basically.
And I thought we brainstormed a little bit and I thought it would be cool if like the end of
the game was you reached like the highest Z level you could beat the fucking boss or whatever.
And then like you would try to ascend another level, but you would like,
you would like crack the screen, right?
Like you were breaking out of your computer screen because you had like come up.
You get it?
You get what I'm saying?
Cause like it's like you're looking down at like a flat grid and you go up, up, up,
up and then you hit the screen because you go too high.
Do you get it?
Yeah, break the glass ceiling.
Yeah, I get it.
Break, break the glass ceiling.
That's right.
Ah, good times.
Never happened.
Anyway, voice grill.
Yeah.
Next one is from Ray three, two, one, go.
These past few weeks have been horrible for me.
You know, back in September, I got COVID and so I was going to die.
And then later in October, I got shot on the shoulder and was rushed to the hospital.
Is this President Trump?
Luckily it wasn't anything serious, but I just wanted to say that I was listening to the episode
with Cybershell and that should really cheered me up while I was in the hospital.
I just want to thank you guys for still doing this stuff.
The podcast has been something that's been helping me keep on going and
now letting this dress get to me.
So I just want to say thank you again and keep being cool.
How the fuck did this guy get shot?
He got COVID and then got shot in the shoulder.
And our podcast was what helped him.
That's incredible.
Oh my God.
He got shot and he was like in the hospital with COVID and the doctor comes in.
He's like, nah, fuck this.
Oh God.
Well, like a doctor is like, I got to, you know, I'm going to end you like peacefully,
like right now, but he is a really terrible shot.
He's like, well, you know, he tries to like roll to avoid the shot,
but it goes through the shoulder.
Damn, imagine, God, imagine getting shot like fuck.
That shit must hurt real bad.
Are you saying the doctor shot him and he rolled out of the way like Dark Souls,
but his eye frames ended a little too early.
Yes.
He rolled straight out of the hospital bed, knocking everything over around him.
He had the chlorinthine ring or whatever.
So he just like cartwheeled like right up.
And you know, this is a real person that really got shot.
And here we are just being abrasive as fuck about it.
I know, God.
Hope you're doing good.
You know, I read all this scary shit about COVID and like, I know it seems like
a lot of cases are pretty mild and like don't get that bad.
But like, then I'll read about one that's like, oh, yeah, did you know that in some cases,
COVID gets in your brain and permanently deletes your sense of smell and taste?
Like that happens to some people and they have to do like physical therapy to like
relearn how to like smell and taste things afterwards.
That's the thing that's happened to some people.
Dude, that's super fucked up.
Yeah, yeah, it's better than death.
It's yeah.
Well, yeah, I would say so, in my opinion, based on the axiomatic principles that I hold.
But anyway, yeah, neutral.
Hope you're doing good with the COVID and the bullet wounds.
Yeah, Jesus Christ.
So fucking it's so fucking cool.
I don't know if I'd cool, but
cool that you are alive and able to make a voice.
I wonder if he got I wonder if he got shot by police because he was out
because he was out fighting for civil rights.
That's my that's my head cannon.
Okay, okay.
Cool.
Okay, next up is Bob's story one.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay, so this is a story about 10 years old and
I hope that Pippo and Tom are also there.
And I know at least Ben knows enough about Christian to know the horror of this story.
But I hope you guys can also appreciate this.
So 10 years ago, I'm working and I'm working this girl I work with
had like really big tits and I was super into that.
Nice.
And like big booby mommy milk or kind of shit.
Yeah.
But like she was also a horse girl.
So she was super fucking weird.
A horse girl.
But into horses maybe.
We started hanging out and I introduced her to Christian's bullshit.
Now that's not what you should have done Christian.
That was a peak bullshit.
That's not how to do it.
So like one night we're hanging out at her house and got to her house.
It's reading the old wiki.
Just like I guess she's into it.
This is not how you get laid.
All of his bullshit.
I don't know what's working so far.
And I want to say this was like I think that was like doing liquid Chris's bullshit.
So like the heights.
Like yeah peak the peak bullshit.
Yeah.
Yep.
Um but yeah.
Hold on.
I'm going to hear another voicemail.
Okay.
This is awesome.
All right.
Oh god the suspense is killing me.
We're going to have to do part two.
Here's Bob's story two.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
So part two of the story.
But like we were reading about Chris on the wiki for a couple of hours.
And this was like liquid Chris time.
So peak Christian bullshit.
But for some reason she wants to try and fuck with Chris.
So we take a bunch of pictures of her and she's naked.
Emailed them to him.
Texted them to him.
How the fuck?
Got no response.
Fuck Chris.
If you're listening Chris, fuck.
This poor girl all she wanted to do was fuck with you.
She sent you so many pictures of those tits.
Well yeah.
You did not get a fuck.
Yeah.
How dare Chris make her do that.
But uh.
What the fuck is this?
I'm very confused.
Yeah.
What's the point?
Yeah I don't think you're being a bunch.
That night she got really turned on by Chris Chan.
What?
And like I said she was a horse girl so I knew she was weird.
But it's been like 10 years and I've never been able to properly explain this to anyone
on how fucking weird it was.
I don't know if you've done it today.
I mean no.
I feel like yes.
Super weird.
So uh yeah.
Wait.
So the story was there was a girl at work or whatever that he managed to get
into Chris Chan and she thought it would be funny to send Chris pictures of her tits
and she got it really into it.
To.
I mean.
And he this guy finger banged her he says.
That's what he said.
So like a good job and then what that is that it.
That's the end of the story.
I feel like I could have been told in 30 seconds.
Yeah.
Definitely.
But like what was the horror.
Did something happen after that.
Did she.
No.
There's no horror.
He mentioned there was something it would be horrible at the beginning.
What's weird to me is that.
Like okay.
First of all strange.
I mean I guess stranger things have happened.
But it's it's curious to me that you meet this girl at work.
Introduce her to Chris Chan and yet she's still willing to come over to your house.
I'm like all right.
You're right.
He was at her house or something.
Oh he was at her house.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well either way it doesn't matter.
But okay let's accept that.
And then okay you're there you're reading you're reading the quickie together you know.
Sure why not this is a mutual interest you have I guess fine and so you're doing that and then she's like.
Hey wouldn't it be funny if like I fucked with Chris by like taking a bunch of nudes of myself.
I mean what I wonder is like okay well like were you was you there when she took the nudes
like did you take them for her or did she just like hey hey you wait here I'm going to
like go in the bathroom and take a bunch of nudes of myself and then I'll send them to Chris.
But like you can't see them.
Like they're not for you they're for Chris.
You know like were you like involved with it or was this like a thing that she was doing separately.
He was involved with it.
That was my sense too.
Which it's it kind of almost seems like maybe this was like sort of an excuse that she was using.
She was like I want to like get naked or whatever.
I want to like make this scenario sexual.
Perhaps perhaps using this this Chris Chan pretense will be a good excuse for me to move
the scenario in that direction so that this fucking beta cock that I have over my house
will just finally fucking nut up and finger bang me god what is it going to take.
I think if I was here that's what I would have been thinking.
Thoughts prayers.
Uh just prayers.
Just prayers.
Definitely prayers.
Satanic prayers.
I I mean the the follow-up question for me is what happened.
Like why did you just finger banger the one time.
Did did she did you did she move.
Did she quit.
How come where did this where did it go from here.
Was she just like yeah I think we shouldn't do this anymore.
Don't ever come to my house again.
I think I think there was a part that I almost missed where it was like fuck you Chris.
She sent all she wanted to do is fuck with you and you didn't care about all the tits she sent.
Maybe that's weird like that's that's weird.
That like yeah that he seems annoyed at Chris about it.
Yeah so maybe maybe to him maybe this this was like a one time thing.
Maybe maybe she just like you know decided that it was okay to get finger bang because
like she was already naked from taking these new yeah maybe she was more in it for the Chris Chan
fucking and like because he didn't go anywhere she lost interest and was like I never mind.
And like if Chris had responded this relationship could have blossomed.
What a strange way to start anything.
Yeah yeah thought provoking.
I like it good story Bob appreciate it.
Next one based Ben boy.
Three two one go these last episodes you know what these last two fucking episodes
they've been pretty good.
Let's keep it up.
Thank you thank you very much.
I hope you all enjoy the episodes and subscribe to our patreon.
Should we let's let's let's plug the bonus episode.
No no no we can do that at the end.
We can do that at the end.
We don't have to talk.
This is a good time.
This is what yeah right you're right this is a good great time to talk about the yesterday
right the episode that we recorded with Digi was we did it.
We did the first of its kind.
The first of its kind the thing that we've been talking about doing we did.
Oh wait what's the word retrospective.
Directors commentary on the riff tracks yeah yeah directors commentary riff tracks
voiceover commentary whatever on on the first episode where we all we we we we
you gotta play both at the same time so you can have the full commentary experience.
We counted in don't worry it's easy.
Yeah it's easy.
Yes we did the commentary check it out check it out at the patreon link in the description.
If you want to if you want to to have a little blast to the past and go back to five
fucking years to 2015 and revisit the good old days with us.
Where they maybe maybe they were kind of shit actually though.
You'll have to pay five dollars and find out for yourself.
True.
Next one juicy high lights.
Here we go three two one go.
Yo shoutouts to the fucking PCP highlights channel.
Y'all got to chill that shit bro.
He's right.
Elisar is working hard he's right some of those juicy highlights out there.
He's right true I don't check it myself enough but yes that is a thing that has been going on
for a while now there are plenty of highlights of the PCP all the good bits without all you know
the whole podcast thing that sucks just the funny bits.
I see I see it on Twitter I'll see that like I don't know I assume it's Nate who's posting them.
I have no clue who is that who is posting the clips onto Twitter but somebody is and I'll see
them there and yeah we've got the the highlights channel that's just like little like you know
highlight snippets if you just want to listen to some fucking some goofy shit that we said
one time or another subscribe damn it.
Next one oh the next one is called cross music recommendation for Gibb.
Oh okay three two one go.
As a genderfluid individual I've been super into the gib gone fem arc so I wanted to
recommend her a song that I resonate with a lot on this topic and I know you did that whole thing
where you ask for music recommendations to listen to while working on stuff so it all
kind of fits together.
The song is Boys Will Be Bugs by the artist Cave Town and I think you'd really like it as
well as a lot of his other music.
Anyway hope you had a nice vacation and here's a less than five second clip of the song so you
won't get copyright claimed.
Oh that sounds nice.
Yeah Boys Will Be Bugs.
That's pretty cool.
All right I'll listen to it.
Ha ha well as a cis male I might go and colonize it by listening to it myself.
Like an ant colony?
Like Christopher Columbus.
Oh the ant.
How festive.
Yeah yeah fuck yeah.
Uh, okay based next vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo vo
movements, but the samurai is still at large. Be careful.
The thing about the samurai is that like even before he had the necronomicon,
he had no shortage of ways to either to fake his own death or survive his death
or like undo his death or whatever. Like death is like with the least of his concerns.
So, you know, thanks for looking out, Margar, but you know,
you got to get up pretty early in the morning, something something when you're in the voice
when you're in the voice jail and it's time for you to make some more goddamn license plates
for two cents an hour. Baby, next up, yellow chairs, three, two, one, go.
Konnichiwa. This is Eddie Murphy.
Haha, not really. This is Samurai-sama, but how do you do it for a moment? Top cake.
Anyway, Samurai, not a hero to torment Beno-san this week,
but Restore Short, Shinobi Pinnis, coming soon to Butter Hall near you, Beno-san.
Samurai-sama, make a big announcement. Reaver of Abosensu.
Out of priority material and Blue Road last week. I mean, honest.
So until next time, I mean until whatever time. Sayonara.
Did you catch that?
No. I think it was a little too Japanese for me.
It was a little too, yeah, a little too Japanese.
I'm a little too white to understand that.
I think he said something about like taking a break from pre-written material?
Is that what he said? Is that what he said? Should we listen again?
Listen, you know what? I'm sure it's fine. Listeners, don't go back and listen to it again and know what he said for sure.
Don't make certain of anything. Just leave your life on the edge.
Next up, the priest touched my poopy. Haha. 3, 2, 1, go.
Konnichiwa. Reaver of Abosensu. Over.
Reaver of Abosensu. Fakayu. Benno-sa. Return to scroll.
Until next time. Sayonara.
Okay, so that was his leave of absence.
I see, I see. Damn. If only I'd known. If only I'd made sure to understand his wording precisely.
I could have avoided all this embarrassment.
Okay, next one is called cringe. 3, 2, 1, go.
That last voicemail. Pretty cringe, bro.
Tell me about it.
People are getting meta with the order of voicemails.
I agree. Imagine still wanting to recover the scrolls after all this time, you know?
It's like Samurai would clearly have done the yellow chairs and then as fast as possible done the next one.
So as to ensure that he was played twice in a row for the maximum comedic effect.
Now this person is like saying that last whatever it was voicemail was cringe.
It's cool. It's nice to see people are experimenting.
This is an experimental podcast. This is an avant-garde podcast.
This is the only podcast you need anymore from now on.
Next up. Entitlement. 3, 2, 1, go.
I like the new format and I'm perfectly fine with digenate and munching while leaving and wanting to move on.
I get it, people move on. But isn't that kind of only fair that they make some kind of official statement about leaving?
Because when it exists in this weird limbo state of them just staying and not going anywhere.
Well, it's kind of like equivalating or just selling a false truth and you're kind of acting entitled.
I mean, you're really not acting any different than Donald Trump saying he was going to do something about COVID but didn't.
Sorry, but if you refuse to cut them off and make it clear, you guys are the entitled ones, not us.
We pay for it. We pay. Do it.
I'm so fucking mad. I'm so fucking mad.
At the beginning of the podcast we never said like this show will always involve ex-members.
It's always been whoever's around. So that logic doesn't work.
Okay, I don't want to spend too much time on this because it's really stupid.
I thought this was a joke. Is this serious? Are we taking this seriously?
I don't know. Am I being an idiot? Am I being an idiot to take this seriously?
I don't know. I just don't think comparing us to Donald Trump would ever be a serious comparison.
That part is a little funny. That part's clearly a joke, yes.
The thing about, shouldn't you make a definitive statement? We did.
We talked about it in no-
I thought that was part of the joke.
Oh God, I'm too stupid for this.
No, maybe I'm stupid. Maybe you're the smart one and I'm being stupid.
I don't know.
People criticize me for not being able to recognize a joke and these voicemails a lot of the time.
I feel like maybe I am inclined to take them too seriously.
Good one, Mr. Entitlement, sir. You really pulled one over on me.
Okay, next one is called Ben Words Good.
Yeah, three, two, one, go.
So back when Nate was talking about shower speed runs for the first time,
Ben asked the question, what is this strange and esoteric ritual?
And that phrase is something that I have not been able to get out of my head.
It's etched into my memory forever.
It's because it feels like something about it feels so like perfectly,
like it perfectly captures the idea it's trying to convey in tone and meaning.
And like, Ben does this shit all the time or are you just like,
for random, just out of the blue for totally regular ideas,
we'll just suddenly find incredibly elegant ways to say them that are like,
wow, dude, those words were so cool, dude.
That was epic.
Fuck yeah, bro.
Keep using cool words, Ben.
I value clarity.
I think that a simple word is better when it conveys meaning
as well as a complicated or obscure one.
But yeah, I like to get a little fancy with my vocabulary sometimes
because yeah, it can impart a certain tone that I enjoy speaking with
at the right for comedic effect or just for interests.
Yeah, I mean, sometimes it's just nice to use words that are just not used as often
so that you sound like you're saying something that not everyone else says all the time.
Does this trend I've noticed over the past few years where people say super?
Oh, I'm super excited and I notice it now and I don't like it.
You think it's become cliche?
I think it has.
I think it's become super cliche.
Maybe, maybe I've noticed super kind of making a comeback a little bit.
Maybe.
Listen, don't just follow the crowd.
You gotta crack open a dictionary, find some words of your own that nobody else uses
and just use them as often as possible.
Squeeze them in even when they're not appropriate.
Use exemplary instead of good.
There is a really subtle joy of being really specific with your vocabularies.
Yes, it's really cool to learn.
The words have very complicated meaning in just one word.
One word can mean so much and we invented it for that reason and we don't use them.
For me, my new word is canard.
I'm gonna say canard every chance I get until I get bored of it
and no one can stop me.
So, you know, I think that this whole, the whole scheme of like stealing all of Aria's signs off of yards
sounds like a liberal canard to me.
That's what I think that probably is.
For instance, use it in a sentence, there I just did.
What does it mean, sir?
Thanks for the urban dictionary in real life.
I said on the stream that I thought it meant like a deliberately spread lie.
I think it's actually a little less specific than that.
It means here, I can answer this.
I can answer this once and for all, a canard is an unfounded rumor or story,
or second definition, a small wing like projection attached to an aircraft forward of the main wing
to provide extra stability or control, sometimes replacing the tail.
The more you know.
Think about it.
Learn a lot today.
I think that second definition is a canard.
I couldn't have said it better myself, could not have said it better myself.
Oh, etymology, etymology time from mid 19th century from the old French caner,
which means to quack into the modern French canard literally duck like the bird or also hoax.
Maybe it's because like a wooden duck uses like a decoy.
Maybe that's the connection there.
The reason why just the word for duck also means a hoax.
Is that why quack doctors use quack as the word?
Fuck.
Fuck, I don't know.
Let's find out.
This is on the rabbit hole.
This is real dictionary.
We're going we're going down the rabbit hole free dictionary dot com quack doctor.
Yeah, untrained person pretending to be a physician, a charlatan.
Oh, this is good.
A definition to a charlatan semicolon a mount a bank.
You definitely don't want to get called a mount a bank.
And then verb it quacked quacking quacks to act as a medical quack or a charlatan.
What is the what is the etymology?
What is the etymology here?
I don't I don't please.
Okay, middle middle English quack of imitative of imitative origin.
So, so it's different from the duck thing.
I guess that quack.
Maybe they thought that, like, the sound of a duck quacking was a duck, like, trying to, like, imitate.
No, what the fuck.
Trying to make.
That's going.
They go.
Maybe maybe the middle English quack.
Maybe quack is not related to quacking.
Maybe it's etymologically similar dissimilar.
Like, like a new bonus episode dictionary reading, like a niggardly, you know, no, no relation.
Nothing.
What does that come from that comes from?
What's the the that is from in a in a stingy or meager manner.
And that yeah, just comes from an old English word.
Niggard, which is like a person who is like greedy and and stingy.
So, you know, there you go.
What does that word come from?
What sort of person from middle from middle English, late, late middle English.
Oh, alteration of earlier.
Negan probably of Scandinavian origin.
Okay.
So there you go.
A stingy or ungenerous person.
No more, you know.
Yeah, I want everyone to go out and say that word.
Whoops.
Next up.
Next up is not a joke.
Three, two, one, go.
You know, every time like hypocrites or Digi bro, or whoever starts talking about like gender, I just kind of skip ahead five minutes.
And anybody else do that.
Yeah, me for sure.
Incredible.
Whatever.
Just kidding.
No, I'm just kidding.
I mean, if it's a topic you're not interested in, it doesn't matter.
I don't know why he's asking us.
We can't skip ahead.
Yeah.
I feel like this is a dress to the audience and people can sound off in the comments.
Oh, sure.
It's the same way like if somebody starts talking about Final Fantasy 7, I'm like, oh, I don't know.
Yeah, you know, that's fair.
Yeah, my version of skipping ahead is like, go doom scroll through Twitter for a while.
Okay, next one is called Praying for a Digi and Hippo.
Three, two, one, go.
Our Father, who art in heaven, hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done, on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread and forgive us our trespasses, as we forgive those who trespass against us.
Lead us not into temptation, but deliver us from evil. Amen.
Hail Mary, full of grace, but what Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women, and blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners.
What, did you have to pray in middle school?
Oh, yeah, I went to church until I was 17.
I believe in God, the Father Almighty, the Creator.
I mean, I went to church when I was a kid.
I never said a hail Mary.
My mom was like super religious, so we would go to church every Sunday.
We'd have to do a rosary all the way there and all the way back.
Really?
Yeah, it was a nightmare.
Were you Catholic?
Yep, hardcore.
I mean, I didn't buy into it, but I was forced at gunpoint to do the dance.
This definitely reminds me of that one or two times I've been to church, where I talk over the guy speaking with my friends.
The resurrection of the body and life everlasting, amen.
That was for you, Gib.
That was all legit. That was all real.
Do you feel better? Do you feel touched by the Lord?
Do you feel more manly?
Nah.
Damn, fuck.
Satan wins again.
I don't know what he was praying about. He was just saying God.
Damn.
I think we're being a little unfair.
Maybe these were prayers for a good, solid, strong transition.
Everything goes great.
We don't know what this is talking about.
You're right.
I mean, who's more supportive of trans people than the Catholic Church?
You know, the Pope is a crypto leftist after all.
Right, right.
Oh wait, I was going to say, I went to a Protestant church.
We didn't say Hail Mary, but we said the Lord's Prayer and I don't know.
It's one of those other ones.
I get the flashbacks from the first half of it.
I recognize the first part.
My first school had a church attached to it, like an old English church.
So we would go in there every Friday to do a prayer thing.
I was like, whatever.
Wait, are you at school?
Yeah.
We had every morning that was an assembly before we would go to lessons.
Four days out of the week, we would have it in the school hall.
And then on Friday, we would have it in the church because it was right there.
Did you go like a private religious school or something?
No, no.
It was called...
Your school was called...
Yeah.
I don't know what it meant.
It was just like a school that was right next to a church.
I think it may have been like a religious school at one point.
It was just a school that had access to a church.
It was like, let's use this.
We used the church for the nativity.
It was really actually epic.
I really like churches.
You did the nativity?
It was like a school play thing?
Yeah.
That's the thing you do at Christmas time.
The year six would do the nativity.
That's not secular.
It was a church.
Of course, it wasn't secular.
You stupid fuck.
No, but it was a school, though.
I'm talking this was at school, though.
Yeah, I mean, I don't know.
I'm just surprised that in the course of your regular schooling things,
like your state, your public state school,
you would do religious observances.
That's fine.
That's surprising.
I never did that shit.
I don't know.
I don't know how it normally works.
I mean, a lot of schools didn't have churches attached to them.
It was literally like two seconds walk outside the front building.
It doesn't surprise me that you would use the church or do things in this old church,
but that you would have school prayer time is like, hmm.
Well, it's not really prayer time.
It was just like there were hymns and a prayer was said when we were in the church,
because it's just a thing.
Yeah, prayer time.
Yeah, it sounds exactly like prayer.
That's what I said.
I don't know.
Like the thing with it is that it was strangely like, you know,
like it wasn't like said to be true in a way.
Like you were left to think whatever you felt.
And yeah, it was, I don't know.
Like when I learned about how America was,
I was like confused that people actually believed all that stuff.
I thought it was just stories because that's how I was taught it.
It was taught as like parables and stuff like, oh yeah, cool.
I never once thought that it was actually true and I would go to hell.
None of that happened.
But like, I mean, you must have known some people who were sincere believers growing up, right?
No, I knew a Hindu person in a Sikh.
And you didn't know any Muslims?
Maybe there were a few Christians that I don't know that they were like devout,
like followers of anything in particular.
Most people were atheists.
Okay, like Christmas, like observing Christmas,
when like what Christmas is was being explained to you.
Did nobody say like, yeah, you know, people believe in like the,
you know, the salvation of man through the blood of Christ or whatever.
I mean, I probably just assumed that it was all part of the festivities
and it wasn't like a serious thing because it, you know, it's like,
oh yeah, when you're in the church, you say all these things,
say your hymns and prayers.
And that's just, you know, that's the fun of the thing.
And you know, I didn't like saying the prayers all the time,
just sort of mumble it.
Yeah.
It's like in the same way that like you, I don't know,
you wear green on St. Patrick's Day, like whatever.
Yeah, like it's not like a sincere religious belief.
Even though I'm sure a lot of people like parents and stuff,
they were religious, they did all that stuff,
but they didn't like, the conversation never really came up.
I think everyone was just coexisting, which is cool.
Sure.
Okay.
That's weird.
That's weird was kind of interesting.
Thanks for the, thanks for the tidbits.
Haha.
Now I know where you went to school.
Uh-oh.
I'm going to get you.
Oh, wait, wait.
Elisar, Elisar, scrub that from the record, the name of the school.
Wait, really?
I don't know.
What if they like, you know, send a nuke to it with my name on it?
Hahaha.
Ah, based, based, based, based.
Next up is a MBF.
Uh, three, two, one, go.
Mon.
Uh, bark.
Fart.
I think that's classic.
That's a triple threat.
Hahaha.
That does conjure a funny image.
It's sweet.
It's a triple threat.
Like you, like you finish the, the, the coitus.
You're nuts.
Finish the coin.
Hahaha.
She enjoys it.
At the same time a dog barks and you fart.
It's the perfect triple.
Hmm.
Ah, God, I, God, I wish that were me.
I want what they have.
Uh, next up, communist cowboy.
Three, two, one, go.
Yeah.
Musical interlude.
It's been a while.
Welcome to the top fourth wall.
Hahaha.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey there.
Sorry, I didn't see you walk up.
It's me, your old pal, communist cowboy.
Hey.
The elite want to keep you poor and enslaved under their
corporate crack system.
They've rigged the social structure, placed the masses in a
state of stagnant subsistence while a mass near a fathomble
levels of wealth.
Instead of uplifting their workers and citizens together,
they'd line their pockets past necessity in a shallow
attempt to make themselves feel something in those hollow
hearts layers.
Remember, fought for labor rats, unionization, and
healthcare for all.
And finally, never forget, from each corner of their
ability to each according to their need.
Thanks for coming.
Play the guitar again.
Communist cowboy out.
Yeah.
Woo, I love you communist cowboy.
What a majestic creature.
Yeah.
I imagined the engineer from Team Fortress 2 was talking to us.
He's a big communist, that guy.
Next up.
Spoopy stories one.
I wonder if this will be spoopier than the story of how
you finger banged a girl who got turned on from sending
nudes to Christian.
That's the scariest thing I've ever heard in my life.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, thanks.
So it's October and spoopy season has officially begun.
And I was wondering if any of you have any scary, weird or
cold stories from any place you've ever lived at.
I'll give you three examples where you can think of stuff and
I'm going to tell these stories from least to most spoopy.
So I live in an apartment complex and there's a room in the
third floor where every tenant that has lived there has
ended up killing themselves.
I've only lived here for three years and the complex isn't
very old.
I think it's been around, it was built sometime around 2014
and only four tenants or so have lived there.
So yeah, that's pretty weird.
And now I'm going to give you a bit of context for the next
story.
I grew up in Mexican and American border cities.
So there's going to be elements of like people crossing the
border to and fro.
In the late 80s, my high school was infamous because there was
this white, rich, all American kid like a senior in high
school that was dating a younger Latino girl.
And the kid breaks up with her.
But the problem is that like the girl's mom was over the moon
and that her daughter was dating this kid because he was like
a top 10 of his class.
He was athletic, like his family's rich, more respected in
the community.
And she goes to see a fortune teller to see if she can
hex the kid.
The fortune teller says no, but then she could arrange to
kill him.
What?
Okay.
All right.
Spoopy stories too.
I feel like these spoopy stories need like the sound of a
crackling fire in the background.
They do.
Eleazar.
No, no, no.
He has to do it.
Sort us out.
Okay, or don't.
I don't care.
Spoopy stories too.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
So the girl's mom agrees and two hitmen from Mexico crossed
the border to kill a high school kid just because he wanted to
enjoy some college pussy.
This last story takes place in Mexico again during the late
early 90s.
That's the end.
My Mexican hometown was known for a cult called narcosatnicos
or Satanist drug lords.
This cult was led by a Cuban guy that was a drug dealer that
fancied himself as sort of witch doctor and soothsayer.
And the cult believed in Santera, Paloma Llombe, which is
some African Cuban spiritualist shit and plastic shit like
human sacrifice stuff.
To facilitate the killings, the cult leader recruits a gorgeous
girl who makes who he makes second in command, by the way,
that lived like three blocks down from my house.
Incidentally, we both lived near a cemetery and she was
supposedly this tough and blonde girl that could easily be
mistaken as American.
They kill a bunch of people, but they get busted because
during spring break, kids from all over the neighboring
U.S. state would come to drink illegally at my hometown,
both at the beach and at the red light district.
The girl seduced some American dude from up north, got him
drunk at a nightclub and took him to a ranch, all while in the
company of cult members.
A chop of his body removed his brain and threw it in a cauldron.
Because the cult leader was a sadistic fuck that killed
random people, competing drug lords and small animals.
They targeted this kid because he was said to be a doctor and
the cult leader wanted a smart prank for his rituals.
The guy finally reports him missing and I think the U.S.
governmental figures press the Mexican government to
solve the case.
So yeah, that's my hometown.
How about yours?
I feel like your spooky storytelling skills need some
more drama to them.
Yeah, those weren't spooky as much as like...
Like police reports, sort of.
Yeah.
I mean, it's scary to imagine that those things happened.
There's an art to making a story scary, you know?
You got to have a bit of an ambiance, a little bit of
atmosphere.
The spookiest part was the weight between one and two because
there was some tension there.
And I thought that the second story was going to continue,
but it ended almost immediately as that voicemail started.
That one was like...
It's like, oh yeah, the fortune teller says that,
no, I can't hex him, but I can arrange to kill him.
And I'm like, what?
Twist.
And then I start the next one and it's just like,
so yeah, she got some guys to go kill him.
It's like, oh.
Tension deflated.
So did he die?
I assume he died then, I guess.
I think his question was, do we have any hometown scary stories
of that nature?
I don't know.
Set the bar pretty high.
Well, not literally of that nature, but like scary stories
related to where you live.
There were some ghost stories in my hometown.
Oh, there was one of...
I don't even remember.
It's like some kind of like ghost of like a lumberjack or
something or some like woodsman who like you'll see on the
highway or something.
I don't know.
Like that's about it.
I don't even know.
I don't even know the details.
I was never quite clear on them.
It's like, yeah, there's a scary woodsman ghost who is on the
road.
Don't get killed.
Yeah, I don't remember anything about it.
There's Jack the Ripper.
He's in London.
That's close by.
I think I talked about how the time that when I got to college
as a freshman, there was like a ghost tour of the
campus because the campus was supposed to be haunted and we
went up to this like room and like the great hall or whatever.
And there was like a camera flash and I thought I saw some ghosts
in the window and I was like, hey, Mr. Ghost Tour, I saw some
ghosts in the window and he was like, what are they?
And I was like, well, it looked like an old man and a young
boy and the old man was wearing a poncho.
And he's like, no, those aren't the ghosts.
And I'm like, oh darn.
Okay.
Those are some other ghosts.
No, it's a woman ghost that lives here.
Those are tourist ghosts.
Yeah.
They're just passing through.
Don't worry about them.
That would actually be pretty scary to hear someone say that.
It's like, oh, the ghosts are so commonplace and we just have
ones like that just passing through.
There's a fucking hot spot of fucking paranormal activity.
Frankly, there's just too many ghosts to even keep track of.
I wouldn't bother.
You know, you'll get haunted one of these days and you won't even
know who it is.
Don't just accept your fate.
Next one is called.
Oh, this is going to be so sick.
Mig Tao owns minorities, BTFO.
It's going to be pretty good.
Three, two, one, go.
Isn't it ironic how there's this vocal minority of commenters
who are asking for better days and think this podcast has gone
downhill and is dying because their favorite member won't
show up on the show.
Oh, boo fucking who?
What are you doing complaining about it here?
You know they're all doing their own shit, right?
Meijia has a Twitter.
She's streaming.
Nate streams twice per week.
Did you still doing stuff?
And Jesse always posts at the end of the month.
What the fuck are you guys doing here, bitchin'?
Get out of here.
Agreed.
Have we talked about, did we mention Meijia's new puppet?
Oh, yeah.
I haven't seen it in action yet.
She made a 2D one, which looked good,
but I think the rigging was a little glitchy.
But she made another one, a 3D one,
which I tuned into her stream yesterday and it looks great.
It looks great in motion.
I'm very impressed.
I need to ask her about that then.
I asked her about it and she told me the program she used and stuff.
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Oh God, Jesus fucking Christ!
Oh, did you pull a hamstring?
No, I just, no, I dropped my, I was clipping,
I was idly clipping my cuticle with some nail clippers
and I dropped it directly onto my testicle and it hurt.
So, I mean, I'm wearing shorts, but like, I don't know.
The weight, oh, ah, oh God.
All right.
What a strange situation.
Only on the Procrastinators podcast,
you get quality entertainment like this.
No, it's normal.
It's normal.
Next one is called the RQ,
and this is our last one of the day.
So three, two, one, go.
So like, Radcon 3, like, what?
Two, three years, like, without the Radcon,
there's no point in the existing, you know?
Point in what existing?
Radcon.
Oh, is it the Radcon question?
Right?
Is that what it's about?
I think he's saying that like,
I think, is he saying that like,
if there's no Radcon, there's no point in the PCP existing?
Uh...
I mean, the PCP preceded the idea of Radcon,
and we decided to meet up because the podcast was like,
oh, we want to meet up in person because the podcast is nice,
but it would be better if we were together.
Um, I mean, what do you guys,
what are your guys' thoughts about Radcon 5?
Uh, it needs to happen.
My thoughts about Radcon 5 is that, um,
I would like it to happen,
but it's, I have no idea.
Like, how or where or when due to COVID and other things.
Yeah.
Mostly COVID.
I mean, yeah, for one thing, COVID.
For two, uh, I mean,
not even really worth thinking about until all the content from Radcon 4
has been put out there.
Indeed.
It's still working.
We're still working on it.
Yeah.
Yeah, true.
Um, I gotta get,
I actually gotta buckle down and get mine done.
Yeah.
So for those two reasons,
I haven't really been thinking about it.
I mean, I do think we're probably going to do it at some point.
Right?
Yeah, definitely.
Yeah.
It would be, I would, I would think so.
I don't, I'm not like, I haven't just, yeah,
I wouldn't count out a Radcon 5 eventually.
I don't know when.
It really depends when America gets its head out of its ass.
Maybe sometime next year would be cool if,
if we could make that happen.
I don't know.
That's not, you know,
the real question is who would want to turn up.
Would everyone want to come back?
Or at least Nate and Digi?
I don't know.
Um, I would,
you know,
I mean,
Nate and Digi are,
Nate,
I don't think Nate is like permanently gone or anything.
Nate has,
Nate has not,
Nate has like deliberately not committed to like,
I am leaving the podcast or anything.
He has not done that.
So I would imagine that, yeah,
he would probably be at a Radcon.
Digi, I'm sure,
I'm sure Digi would come to a Radcon.
I mean, Jesse fucking showed up to the last one
and Jesse's not on the fucking podcast anymore.
Yeah.
Radcons are an event.
They are.
And they're always a good time.
And I'm sure Radcon 5 will be just as great as the other ones.
Yeah.
All we need to do is to not promise to make a fucking anime OVA next time.
You know what?
Hold on.
I, I mean,
why do you say that?
Oh, well,
actually I specifically the animated OP for it and all of the other stretch goals
that we didn't really think about adding right at the last minute
that have hung over our heads in an annoying way.
It's a lot of time,
a lot of labor that we don't,
that we're not directly responsible for.
So it's kind of out of our control,
whether it gets done and stuff like that.
I don't know.
Like I know it's been a while,
but like do you feel that I don't feel like,
I don't feel like the OVA has been like a weight hanging over my head.
I feel like it's been something that we have like committed resources to getting done
and that is getting done in the background.
You know,
my, my hesitation is not even so much the fact that the task is so massive and scope
and like requires all the stuff to be done.
I think it's that all of the,
a lot of the content,
including this stuff for Radcom was kind of centered around the bit of Brad
and that joke is dead and old.
And so like it just feels,
the longer this goes on,
the more it's like nobody cares.
I don't even care anymore.
You know,
it's, it's dead.
It's a dead meme.
And it's just going to come out like two years from now and everyone's going to be like,
Oh, right.
I remember that.
I mean, I hope, I mean, I hope it won't be that long.
Okay.
To a certain extent, to a certain extent, I agree with you.
I don't think, I mean, in a way,
I think that's funny in and of itself.
Yeah, that's not my issue.
It's, it's really just like if we're going to do a Kickstarter with rewards and stuff.
Merch is doable.
This is, this is known.
It just takes time and not creativity necessarily.
You just need,
we just need the logo.
We need the resources.
Merch works.
Videos is like,
I don't know,
depending on like the,
the amount of effort put into them,
they take time to film.
The, the lectures are great.
Obviously we would do more of those,
but they take so much energy out of everyone and so much time to get ready and then record.
Like Redcon 4.
Redcon 4 was not long enough of a time to fit all of those things in,
even though it technically was,
it felt like nothing happened because we were constantly doing things.
Do you mean, you mean,
yeah, you know, yeah.
Constantly recording and constantly getting ready for lectures
and constantly doing things for the OVA.
And I was like,
I didn't really have a time to like even think when it was over.
Yeah.
I mean, I think,
I think,
I mean,
I have seen how the OVA is coming.
And I think it looks good.
And yeah, I know it's been a while and it's,
it's a bit of a shame how long it's taken,
but I think that when it comes out,
it will still be pretty cool.
And I don't feel like I am prepared to like regret having done it or anything.
Oh no.
No, I'm really just thinking forward,
Redcon 5,
I'm not going to say I'm going to,
I'm prepared to do something that I have no idea of being able to do.
Yeah.
I'm not going to try and stretch it just because of like a,
the last five minutes of a hype stream,
where we push the Kickstarter way over all of the stretch goals
and add so many things.
It's like, that's,
I don't want that to happen again.
Yeah.
No.
You make a solid argument.
You make a solid case.
I guess, I guess I agree.
Yeah.
I'm not trying to be a downer about it.
It was, it was cool that that all got funded
and we will eventually make it as just a,
I can understand the frustrations of people who are waiting
and thinking, God, it's been a while.
And I'm like, yeah, it has, it has.
It has, but it was always going to.
Uh, uh, uh, you know what, it's going to be funny.
In hindsight, we'll look back and be like,
sure is weird that all these things got made.
Yes.
And on, and on this very strange time table,
but that's what it was.
And I think that,
I think that when it's all said and done,
in the current state of it,
like mostly being like unfinished,
a lot of like the bigger stuff,
I think that it feels bad and sucks to think about,
but I think that once it is all done
and we can look back on the whole thing
and like talk about it as an, as a whole,
it'll be funny.
Yeah.
I mean, it's already funny how this like happened
just before COVID.
Like that's already a funny aspect to it.
Like we did a little stupid shit.
It's true.
It makes better in a certain way.
I am planning to buckle down soon
and get my fucking lecture out.
That's a thing I should really do
sooner rather than later.
And I'm almost ready.
I'm almost ready to do it, boys.
I don't know.
Any final thoughts before we wrap up?
I'm good.
Yeah.
No, you're...
This was an episode.
Bad.
It was an episode.
It's true.
This did occur.
It did.
All right.
Well, if you want to send us a voicemail,
send it to speakpike.com
slash PCP voicemail.
And if you want to hear the commentary,
director's commentary on episode one best game ever,
hear us wax poetic and contemplate.
Wow.
What were we thinking as we go over that?
That's me, Tom, Hippo, Digi.
$5 at patreon.com slash the procrastinators
get you access to that and all of our bonus episodes
of which there are like 40 now or going on 40,
something like that.
It's a damn good value.
Good bang for your buck.
It's hella value.
Hella value.
Follow us on Twitter at TPcrestinators.
Go buy all of our stupid funny shirts.
We have so many.
Right.
I have COVID shirt for those of you have.
Sure.
Every day of the week.
Keep people guessing around you, you know.
What is our store?
Whatever.
Link in the description.
We got the group piss.
We got all of the epic things.
The group piss.
The classic.
Those were good.
We are the reason people are dying shirt.
I'm just being cool.
You know, there are memes.
A bunch of fresh looks.
Guys, I gotta say I want to eat some activated charcoal
black ice cream.
Oh, be careful.
Be careful of activated charcoal.
I saw that activated charcoal can flush chemicals
out of your body, including estrogen.
If you're an HRT, right?
Yeah, I heard that.
I saw that same thing.
Someone on Twitter was like,
guys, watch out.
They don't warn you about this.
It's like, fuck.
I want it.
I just want it because it looks cool.
Just get Oreo cr- biscuits and crumble them.
No, those are brown.
Not black enough.
Get squid ink.
Squid ink the fuck out of that.
Squid ink ice cream might be pretty good.
Okay, I would think about that.
Okay, anyway, that was my final thoughts.
I think that's it.
Are we done?
Have we finished the episode?
I guess we're good.
Yeah, we're good.
We're super good.
We're fucking, we're the fucking best.
We're killing it here.
We're killing it here on the pro-Crossinators podcast
of Vote Arya Demetso for a sheriff
of Chester County, New Hampshire.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Be that.
Bye.