Hello and welcome to episode 4 of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Happy to have you back with us again this week, and we are here once again to talk about something.
My name is Guy, the best guy ever, and I'm here with my panel of esteemed internet personalities.
Digi, who are you?
I'm Digibro. I wear sunglasses at night.
Jesse Wood, who are you?
I'm Endless Jess. There's a horse in my house.
Hippocrit.
I'm Hippocrit, and I make videos. No, I don't.
You do sometimes. I've seen them at Ben.
Ben?
Patreon.com slash Ben Saint.
SaintComics.com.
Yes.
I'm really hungover.
He makes comics. Well, good man.
Okay, now, moving on.
Today, we are talking about a topic that's near and dear to my heart.
So, what we're discussing this week is when you're in the bathroom and you're taking a piss,
it is completely appropriate to pull your pants down all the way exposing your ass to ease the stream of urine from your dick.
Well, I just sit down.
That's what we're going into.
Whoa, does that happen?
That's wrong.
But I wanted to talk about that.
Okay, we'll save that for next week.
What we're actually talking about this week is too deep for you.
The concept of things being too deep for you, what it means, how it relates to art appreciation, how it relates to pretentiousness, all that shit.
And so, to start us off, I'm going to do what's becoming a tradition and read the Know Your Meme definition off it.
Oh, wait, no, no.
The Urban Dictionary definition.
Oh, fuck.
I didn't have that one open.
Three deep five me dogs.
That's right.
Okay.
So this is a timely topic because I think that everything is too deep for me.
Interesting.
Okay.
So, we really need to figure this out.
This is a big problem.
This is actually something that comes up with me a lot, but we'll talk about this later.
Okay, so here.
If you got the green on you before listening to this podcast, you should get two dank 420 you.
Yes.
No, I'm saying.
I do know what you're saying, dog.
Okay.
All right.
Urban Dictionary definition of too deep for you.
Okay.
When someone or something's artistic value goes beyond a person's perception, leaving that person lost and confused.
And then on the flip side, this may be used to sound like a total douche-tard because you think you're better than everyone else, often used by hipsters.
I mean, it's been a long time since I've heard douche-tard.
Yeah, me too.
When you say something is too deep for you, you don't actually mean that it's too deep.
You're saying it ironically to say that the thing thinks that it's deep.
Well, that is the ironic usage of the term.
It's a dismissive thing.
Yeah.
I've seen it in both ways, though.
Usually in lobby that fans of something.
Unfortunately, there's like half and half between people who are mocking the work by saying it's too deep for you and people who are mocking people who don't understand it by saying it's too deep for you.
But either way, I don't think it's usually that they actually think the work is too deep.
Right.
Okay.
You know, even taking a step back from that, let's talk about what it even means to be too deep for someone.
What is depth of art and what is the correct versus wrong way to perceive something?
Like Eva, right?
Eva is the big anime thing people always bring up is being too deep for you.
Eva.
Yeah.
Evan Gellion.
What the fuck is Eva?
I don't know.
I guess I called Eva so far.
I get shit constantly for saying Evan Gellion, but I haven't heard Eva yet.
Evan Gellion, the correct way to pronounce it.
In Ebon...
Ebon Gellion.
Oh, no one fucking says that shit.
That's gook shit.
Alright, let's...
In Fully Coolie, Meltos says that his dad wrote a whole book on the deep mysteries of Eva.
And that is one of the best dubs of all time.
And I trust their judgment.
There's also a dub for the actual show in which they also say Evan Gellion.
They say Eva, they say Evan Gellion throughout the whole series.
But in the movie, they say Eva for some reason.
And then in the rebuilds, they go back to Eva.
Uh, I don't know.
Anyway, the point is...
I just explained it to you, you dumb shit.
Gibbs Wright, who cares?
The point is, why is that show called Too Deep for You?
It's got a lot of symbolism, right?
And we can talk about what Anno himself says about the show.
But it's got all this symbolism.
It's got all this weird imagery where it's that thing where you really have no idea what's going on.
It's the episode where Shinji gets trapped in that two-dimensional angel or whatever.
And has this whole big crisis of what the fuck's going on.
Nobody even knows.
And, you know, how do you properly appreciate something like that?
Is it an issue of...
I think the reason things like Eva are considered too deep is because some people see it and it's weird.
But they say that they get it, whether they do or not is irrelevant.
The fact that they say they understand it.
And then a lot of other people say, I didn't get it.
This thing's too deep.
You know, it just starts that sort of conversation.
If it was just weird and nobody got it, nobody would say it's too deep.
They just say it was weird, I think.
That's true.
And Anno's been on record as saying all the Christian symbology he just put in there because he thought it looked cool.
So all that stuff, people...
I feel like a lot of people roll that into their understanding of the work and what it means.
I don't think the symbolism is what gives Eva depth.
I think it has played a depth.
People drop that fucking quote out to try and dismiss Eva as not deep.
Because, oh, Anno said that the religious community doesn't mean anything, so it's not deep.
But that's not even the fucking point of what makes it deep in the first place.
And everyone who says that it's not deep, I will take every goddamn one of you.
I'll remove your fucking skin from your bones.
I will put your skin on my dick like a condom and rape your mother.
I couldn't agree with you more.
Fuckers.
Because, you know, whereas Eva is a show that sometimes, I guess, suffers, maybe is not the right word,
but gets a slightly worse rap because it has something like that Christian symbolism
that ultimately doesn't really mean as much as you might think it would by watching it,
that there's something on the other side, like High School of the Dead,
that I think is a fantastic story and has fantastic character developments.
It gets shit on for the opposite reason, because it just shoves tits in your face the whole time.
But I would argue that that only makes the show stronger for what it was going for
and in no way detracts from the depth of the narrative and the characterization.
I think what comes down to is that the depth of the piece of media or art in question
is irrelevant compared to the fact that people are shallow.
And people like to say that they understand things sometimes
when they themselves are kind of concocting this meaning in their own heads.
Well, I think all meaning is, like, partially concocted in your own heads.
Oh, totally.
Like, there's no objective, like, deepness to anything.
It's just what you can take out of it.
Yeah.
I want to cut to the heart here of, like, why this whole concept bothers me.
This too deep for you, right?
Because on the one hand, I do think that a work can legitimately be too deep for you.
I don't think that that makes you wrong or makes the work wrong.
It just means that it's too deep for you to comprehend.
Could you?
Yeah, yeah.
Or even maybe deep isn't the right word.
Maybe it's just that it's too specific for you to understand.
Like, if I were to write a story that was full of references to my own life
that don't make sense to anyone else, and then I posted it up and no one understood it,
then, like, it would be too deep for you.
But that depth has no meaning to you, so it doesn't matter for you that it's too deep for you.
Right, and I feel like that's a lot of what comes up in, like, deep stories.
Because, like, ultimately, things that are deep, I feel like a lot of the time
what people are saying when they call it deep is, like, everything has the same underlying,
human experience, right, is ultimately at the root of pretty much every story ever told.
And it's the way that that's masked or the way that that's communicated.
That's where the complexity and, I guess, the depth comes in.
You can watch the asterisk war sucks part four.
Winning depths about that concept.
But yeah, but what bothers me about this so much with the too deep for you thing
where people are, like, derisive of stuff for acting deep or whatever,
I'm gonna pause at a question.
If Evangelion isn't deep, or whatever other show you think isn't deep
or is pretending to be deep or is pretentious, if that show's not deep, what show is deep?
That's a good question.
Can we ask this? What is actually deep?
Can we each go around and say something that we think is deep?
I think that doesn't be a good exercise.
I think Ava is extremely deep.
Like, I think if we're talking about the complexity of the narrative,
the amount of, like, different things that everything means in the show,
like where, like, the number of meanings that each moment or action has
or that each character has, I think it goes about as deep as any anime has ever gone, for sure.
And also as deep as, like, most literature.
Like, what books are everyone reading that are so fucking deep,
unless it's fucking Ulysses, that Ava is just too deep for you, dog?
Right, right.
Like, what is it? Where's this deep media that's supposedly out there?
You know, I wish I had concocted a list of, like, things that popular media
or, like, the popular culture says is deep, just to go into it.
It's not there, though.
Because public perception is what, yeah, right, it's all, it's all a fugazi.
I mean, I think, go on, Hippo.
Well, I was gonna say, a lot of the time, like, things that are considered deep
are often also considered pretentious.
Right, right.
So if you've got a list of, like, the most pretentious stuff
made by a dumbass, then you'd get all the deep shit.
If something is deep, but you don't understand the depth, then you have two choices.
You can admit that you are not smart enough or knowledgeable enough or whatever
to grasp the depth, or you can deny that it's depth, that the thing is deep,
and say that it's just fake deep, and call it, oh, it's just pretending, it's pretentious.
And say that's the root of it, podcast solved.
Yeah.
Well, on the other hand, though, I don't think that I don't believe in pretentiousness in media.
Of course, of course.
Like, because this argument does come up a lot where people say, like, how can a show be pretentious?
And I'm like, well, I do think that you can approach something with the mindset of,
I'm gonna make this as deep as possible, and then, like, go out of your way to load it
with as much symbolism and as much shit as you want.
And I don't know if I'd say that it absolutely isn't deep, but it's pretending to be, you know?
But I feel like you can kind of know it when you see it.
When you see something that's really putting on airs.
Well, I think we know it when we see it.
Because we're smart.
Everyone else is wrong all the time.
That's true.
Wait, Ben, I'm with you on this.
I think Bioshock Infinite is a good example of being pretentious like that.
Because it's got all these, like, like Matthew Matosis lays out.
I'm pretty much just gonna be paraphrasing him.
But, like, it presents all these things about racism and whatever, and time travel and whatever.
But it doesn't say anything about them.
It just, like, puts them out there and, like, uses them as elements in the story.
And everyone said, oh, advanced storytelling or whatever.
Like, something like, even something I watched just two days ago, I forget what,
erased this new anime this season, I think it does more interesting things with time travel already.
In that it really does...
I think the race is pretentious as fuck.
But we can talk about that on tomorrow's podcast.
Yeah, we'll do that tomorrow.
But, like, the way it's using it, whether you think it's succeeded or not,
to me it seems like it's using it as a conduit to tell the story
and has real ramifications on the characters.
And it's going to explore the way that they're reacting to it
and, like, exploring the choices they made in their life.
And, you know, that's the vehicle to do that with.
And I think it's effective, but, you know, that's to be...
I think that Bioshock Infinite is a pretty good thing to bring up
because it's very easy for us to say that we've seen these themes done better elsewhere
and this is not as deep as it's pretending to be or presenting itself as.
But I know people who are, like, more casual gamers who played Bioshock Infinite.
And when you first go to the city of Bioshock Infinite,
when the game starts and you see the city laid out before you
and it's all beautiful and amazing,
that alone is deep and that alone gives the game its artistic merit, regardless of...
I don't know.
Can art...
I wouldn't say it's deep.
I would say it's impressive visuals are not deep in and of itself.
Even though I might not be impressed with the narrative of Bioshock Infinite,
to the many people, I'm sure, who are impressed by it,
who am I to say that they are not valid.
That's a great point because I have heard so many times people I've talked to
say that they absolutely love Bioshock Infinite.
And I, myself, liked it.
And the more I thought about it, the more I liked it less and less.
I think a lot of it has to do with the fact that I had read Homestuck beforehand.
And because I understood everything,
I wasn't nearly as blown away by the things in the story
and could focus more on the things that really didn't impress me.
Well, let me talk about a thing that's funny about media.
If someone just drew a picture of that city,
there was no game, there was no anything, there was just a picture someone drew,
and it was as good as how the city looks in the game,
you'd probably be like, that's an 8 out of 10 drawing, that's great.
But then in the context of the game, you end up liking it less
because of the other things that are related to it.
But I do agree with Jesse that I think that that image of that city alone,
just walking out and seeing it does speak to the human experience,
because there's a reason, there's a mental reason
that has to do with where you are in society and everything,
that you would see that city and think that about it.
That it would take your breath away means that it captures some kind of
very deep-seated human emotion.
But when you then walk through that city,
and it's just one long hallway until you get to a scripted sequence,
then it becomes a different thing.
Where even though as great as the art design is,
and as much as that by itself would be a 10 out of 10,
then to walk down what is a badly designed game,
and then to come at it from the perspective of someone who cares about game design,
then you're like, okay, well this is a 1 out of 10 game now.
And then you put the 10 out of 10 together,
and you get this 5 that suddenly you're really sour towards.
But I do think that, I think pretentiousness in cases like this
is really in the eye of the beholder, because we can't really say,
A, we can't say what the creator wanted out of it,
like maybe in their minds, rather the people who made the game,
they weren't making something that special,
it was just a game they worked on out of their huge illustrious career.
They had a bunch of cool ideas that they threw together,
it didn't necessarily come together perfectly,
but they got all the ideas they wanted to share out there.
But see, what makes it pretentious to me are the attempts to do one thing,
and like the putting on airs that you've achieved that goal,
and then when you have failed in many other ways.
Like for example, why the fuck is the mom like a ghost?
Because she's dead in this world and alive in another.
Isn't that true of literally everyone in the multiverse?
And like, why can Elizabeth only do these tiny little summoning things
in these certain places when she has literally infinite control over the universe?
I forgot about ghost mom, that's horrible.
What you're talking about Nate is just plot holes.
No, I think they're more than plot holes,
I think these are specific misunderstandings of the mechanics of their own games.
Those things necessarily imply if something's not deep though.
Right, those are failures.
It shows me there's a misunderstanding of what they're trying to communicate,
and that severely hampers my enjoyment.
I don't think it becomes pretentious until it's literally saying this is deep,
and then that if there was a guy, if fucking Ken Levine or whoever came on,
that's who made it, right?
If Ken Levine came on screen afterwards and was like,
did you enjoy my masterpiece, you know?
But I'm saying it feels wrong because he says it's a masterpiece
and yet I see all these issues with it.
But he doesn't say it's a masterpiece.
If it was a 10 out of 10 perfect, if it was great,
well okay, if he doesn't say it's a masterpiece,
I'm judging it by playing the game, and the game feels,
I mean that's what pretentiousness is.
It feels like it's better than it is.
I don't think by playing the game you can only know how the game turned out,
but you can't know what their mindset was making it.
I'm not judging them, I'm judging the piece of art,
and the piece of art feels pretentious.
But how can you say that pretentious without knowing the mindset behind it?
Pretentious is, I'm saying pretentious is now an emotion that you feel.
It's not a property that the game has or that the developer has,
it's something that you feel the game is.
I think it's similar to good or bad game.
Like yes, you have to interpret it and decide how it makes you feel,
whether it's pretentious or not,
but I do think there are some standards that pretty much most people can agree on.
I don't agree. I don't agree.
I don't think that whether something is pretentious or not can come.
I think when you say something's pretentious,
you're saying something about the work and about the person that made it.
Yeah, I think that's why the word pretentious itself is dangerous,
because it's literally saying that it's pretending,
it's implying action on their part.
I don't understand, you guys really don't think that the work by itself
implies that you think it has to involve the creator directly?
I don't think you can say...
I don't know, maybe you can imagine some scenario.
I'm not saying that it's necessarily untrue that the work thinks
or that the creators think that it's better than it is,
but I don't think that you can make that assumption about it.
I think it could just as easily have been
that they had a lot of good ideas and a lot of bad ideas
and putting them next to each other made it look like they thought it was amazing.
It's kind of like if I made a video where I make some incredible point
at one point in the video and then at some other point,
I make a terrible point that kind of shits on the other one,
and it sounds like I'm trying to make myself sound really smart,
but I don't know what I'm talking about,
when it could just as easily be true that I just threw out all the ideas I had
and I knew some were good, I knew some were bad,
and I just threw them all out there.
To me, it seems like if you had something like, let's say,
like Romeo and Juliet, to me, is pretentious only in a certain sense,
that it acts like at the end.
There's a big monologue about how the star-crossed lovers,
there's nothing that could have been done,
and yet the events of the story are these really hammy,
like, oh, he woke up, killed himself, oh, she woke up, killed herself.
It's anime coincidences are what drive the plot of Romeo and Juliet
in the latter portion.
Well, yeah, that's why they were star-crossed,
because fate conspired to cause their downfall.
Okay, but I don't believe in fate, so I guess that story just doesn't appeal to me.
But when you see something like that,
if someone tells a big romantic story,
and let's just say at the end they do a thing like,
oh, and love, this was the greatest,
they do a big, small-ending, celebrating itself.
I was about to bring up interest-seller.
Interstellar is a great example.
I haven't actually seen it, but I know it has all these weird messages about love.
It does.
An interstellar would be a great pick for talking about this, though,
but I don't think interstellar is pretentious.
I would use the word misguided.
The script is bad, it has a lot of plot holes,
it doesn't make a lot of sense,
it has some amazing scenes in it,
it has some amazing cinematography,
but the parts where they talk about love being the defining force of the galaxy,
I don't think the movie is pretending that it knows more than it does.
I just think it's incorrect.
I think there's a difference between being pretentious and just being wrong.
No, that's true, it doesn't necessarily make it pretentious, that's true,
but I'm just saying sometimes I think you can tell.
The word pretentious is just overused.
That's certainly true.
Let me propose an example of something that I think maybe actually is pretentious.
Okay, cool.
When I was younger, I listened to Dream Theater,
and they had an album called Metropolis Part 2, and I really liked it,
and I still think it's kind of good in some ways.
However, it always irked me about it,
because in the story of the album,
the guy discovers that he is a reincarnation of this person who was murdered
and her murder was never solved, and he's got to go and fucking solve her murder.
So you're saying he's a trans woman?
He used to be a woman, I was a man, okay.
And one of the songs in it is him sort of like opining and reflecting on the fact
that now that he knows that he is a reincarnated person,
he knows that death isn't the end, and he doesn't have to fear death anymore.
Okay.
And that's cool.
However, it's just a fucking fantasy construct in the story that happens.
I, the viewer, I haven't actually learned anything.
The story of the album has not actually showed me anything about the nature of life and death,
so it feels really cheap when this character can say,
oh, now I don't have to worry about death.
I can say, yeah, good for you, but you're living in the world of this album,
in this fantasy story, what about me?
I don't get it.
And you know, that reminds me so much.
I think if I'm presenting that, I think that...
I really need to piggyback on your story, Ben,
because, you know, that, again, I think that you could just as easily say that the story is just bad and misguided,
not necessarily that it's pretentious, however...
It seems like it thinks it's saying something about life and death,
but it hasn't actually said anything about it.
Let me tell you a little anecdote about Dream Theater.
I was listening to them back when I was like 15 or so,
pretty much just the album Train of Thought, which came right after Metropolis Part 2,
but I read an interview in a magazine called Revolver with them.
It was just like a one-page thing, and the interviewer asked them something to the effect of,
why do you guys think you're not more popular than you are or something like that?
One of the members literally said...
He said, there's bands like...
He named these by name.
He said there's bands like Mastodon, Tool, and the Mars Volta,
who are kind of like us, but not as good, and they're more popular.
So it's kind of like people like stuff that's less good
and people don't like us because we're too good.
He cracked the code.
For the record, for me at the time, my three favorite bands were Mastodon, Tool, and the Mars Volta.
I just read this like, wow, this is what pretentious actually means.
How does this feel, Digi, to not like things that are good, to only like the bad things?
You've become Anthony Fantano in the past.
It's like that episode of a regular show where they become so smart that no one could understand them.
It's like dream readers like that, that they become so good that nobody likes them.
I feel like, well, that's the thing though, right?
Because what too deep for you is...
Yeah, that's exactly what this is talking about.
Right, what too deep for you is when you make something that's just too much
and people can't quite wrap their head around it.
But I think that when it becomes pretentious is when the creator is saying,
oh, you're just idiots.
You don't get it because you're not smart enough.
It's like, well, we don't get it because we're not you
or we don't necessarily have the same life experiences required to understand it.
If any creator puts in stuff like that that no one could understand because it's from their life
and expects the audience to get that from just a viewing, that's pretentious, no doubt about it.
Well, that's basically Horst You Finale.
True, but I think, well, I guess we aren't really the right judges,
but we could tell what was going on, probably because we know you so well by this point.
I don't know if anyone else was...
I have no idea what the general audience, what it was like for an average audience member to watch Horst You Finale.
No fucking idea. It was probably brutal.
I am a very big fan of Horst You Finale and I am not unwilling to call it pretentious.
Well, I've seen a lot of people take a lot of things out of it.
In terms of positive feedback, some people have taken stuff out of it that I didn't necessarily intend,
but that I'm okay with them taking out of it.
And some people have come closer than others to...
I'm not going to say that you don't get it because everybody gets it to a degree, I think.
I don't call it pretentious.
I feel like there's parts of it that I don't get.
Not so much about the finale, but the Horst You Saga in general.
I think there are parts of it that I don't quite see the way that you...
For a long time, I've kind of dreaded people asking me to articulate it or explain it
because I feel like if...
I don't think that's your job anyway.
Yeah, it's not my job for one thing.
And if artists knew how to communicate verbally, we wouldn't be artists in the first place.
Thank you. That's a good point.
Man, that's something that I've been trying to make the point of.
That's what I talked about in my Hideyakeyano video.
Yeah, exactly. Hideyakeyano is what I always think about when I have worked on that.
Have I ever told you guys that I always wanted to communicate how much I love Gern Langen
and I really think that this video was my best possible way of making those points?
That's kind of a big part of why we all do what we do.
Right. I mean, that's how I kind of justify what I do
because there's a lot of times where I feel like this author surely understands the work himself
and could explain it except that he already did try to explain it.
Yeah, with the work itself. The work is the explanation.
I think the problem with everyone trying to seek answers from Hideyakeyano about what Eva means
is that I don't think he could do any better of a job than he did in the show.
He made the show to express these ideas.
I don't think he's necessarily capable of expressing them a different way.
That reminds me.
I can do it a different way because I don't make Evangelion.
That's not what I do. I look at other people's work.
I interpret it for myself and try to help other people to understand my interpretation
and maybe find some grounds for their own, but I couldn't make Eva
and I don't think Anno could make my Eva videos.
Probably true.
I don't think he could necessarily explain why the shot compositions are all so good
or why the character arcs are so good.
I agree. I used to read about great works of art of whatever form.
He did this. He uses this technique. He does that thing.
I was like, wow, you've got to know all these techniques to be a great artist,
but that's not true.
In a lot of cases, those techniques just come about naturally
from following your artistic inclinations and just doing what feels right.
I'm going to almost reverse-engineer it with my videos
because I haven't studied any of this from school.
I watch a lot of shows and then I go, huh, well, the way that shot was animated
made it have a lot of impact.
In the case of animation, I feel like they've probably kept going to school for it
and they understand it.
Hideaki Anno never opened up a textbook and read a chapter on how to compose
some fucking iconic scene or whatever.
Or some technique about structuring an episode in such and such way,
the one where it cuts away from the battle and then you see the aftermath.
No one taught him that.
They don't teach that stuff.
My brother Victor is in film school and he's watched all of every frame of paintings videos
and he's like, why isn't this taught in school?
Because we don't learn any of this.
We should be learning.
My point is that that's not the kind of thing you can teach.
That's the kind of thing that has to be generated creatively.
That's true.
But what do they teach?
What is the focus on in such things?
I haven't taken the classes.
This is a 4x 720 camera lens and it goes on.
They teach you more like how to get into the industry.
Do you need four years of that?
You've got to remember that most of the people making movies are making shitty movies.
That's true.
All of them have been through college.
All of them have taken the classes, but most of them are still garbage.
It's almost like there's something more important than that.
Weird.
It's almost like creative spark is what matters the most and understanding having inspiration
and being able to translate it into a medium that people can appreciate.
Do you say something?
I was going to say, if we're talking about the communication abilities,
it's pretty obvious from my own podcasting prowess that I'm not very good at speaking
to communicate my ideas.
If it comes out at all, it's from the weird videos that I make and the comedy videos.
Which we all love.
I don't think I'd ever be able to get anything across through speaking and writing as much
as I would through my stupid jokes.
By the way, guys, Hippo is currently freezing his ass off in his retarded ass apartment that
has no heat right now.
He's a real trooper for being here with us.
Are you going to give me a round of applause?
You do sound like you're in Russia right now.
Yeah, you sound really cold.
You deserve credit for doing it anyway.
Okay, I don't think that was important, but thanks.
I want to say that this topic reminds me of one that Mr. B-Tongue video where he talks about art in other words.
I don't remember that one.
There are no other words.
If you try to explain a work of art, you're reducing it.
What Digi was saying, the art itself is the explanation.
Which also reminds me of a quote.
I'm probably going to butcher it, but it's something like, writing about music is like dancing about architecture.
Yeah, that's a good one.
There are no other words.
What's great about that, the funny thing is you brought that quote up.
I've often heard that people use that quote to say, like, don't write about music.
And people rebel against that.
People hate that term.
People hate that phrase, rather, because they see it as like,
oh, you're trying to, because my initial response when I heard that was,
well, I'd love to see a fucking dance about architecture.
I was just going to say that.
Like, I don't disagree with what he's saying.
I just think that it's not necessarily an indictment of the practice I think.
Right, right.
You know, I want to ask you guys, what?
Dancing about architecture.
I love the idea.
Fucking awesome.
I imagine it would be done to an Autecher song, and they have like,
you know, the guy who created Gundam, Yoshiyuki Tomino,
his daughter does like interpretive dance and teaches it.
And if you watch the most recent Gundam show,
Recon Gesta NG, the most recent one that he directed,
which is fucking insanity, the whole show,
there's like all the eye catches are like the characters dancing,
like doing interpretive dance,
and his daughter actually choreographed them.
Hey, that's pretty tight.
It's pretty cool.
That was a random fact.
I want to ask you guys now, did you change topic?
I like that.
No, that's cool.
Although Gundam Reco G Reco is perfect for this,
because that is the most too deep for you.
Really?
No one understands it, literally no one,
because there's so much random weird symbolism that makes no sense,
and like random moments of just insanity that no one gets to show.
And Tomino himself like later admitted that he completely failed.
He was like, yeah, he was like, I don't know why I thought this would work,
or why I thought this was a good idea.
Something like this, is it in fact a case that it was in fact not too deep for you,
was simply bad?
I think it was, I think it was both.
The show's not necessarily like all bad,
but like it's very clear that Tomino,
that all of the things in the show meant something to him.
It's just that what that meaning is,
is not something that most people can grasp.
You know what it really is at that point?
It's at that point you have to like struggle with something like that,
I mean how willing are you to do the research,
to like do whatever is required to figure out what everything means,
versus just watch it and then move on with your life.
And like I get it on some level because I have seen a lot of Tomino's stuff,
and all of it, there's like a general theme of his work is chaos.
Like he presents war and the scenarios of war as this chaotic, insane thing.
Like when you watch, like there's a movie called Gundam F91,
which is like pretty standalone in the continuity,
and like the first 30 minutes of it are just like trying to show you how chaotic war is,
and it completely like works and makes sense,
because it's really well produced,
and clearly there were people who knew what they were doing working on it.
You know it has like cool ideas,
but then like he'll do the same thing in another show,
but it doesn't, you don't get that it's about chaos,
it just is chaos, so you don't know what it's about.
Yeah, you know the thing is, I feel like the term is probably applied most
by the people who like take the time least to understand whatever it is they're talking about,
and like they're obviously not qualified to make such a judgment,
and yet that's kind of what sticks with things,
like you're saying with this war shit.
A lot of people are downright anti-intellectual about art.
That's right.
People hate when you say that art is deep.
They're like oh it's all just supposed to be fun,
games are just fun, games are only allowed to be fun.
Maybe we should talk about, they don't need depth.
We should probably talk about the stigma there.
Why is it people are so uncomfortable with things being outside of their grasp?
Is it just they're offended by the idea that they aren't on, you know,
able to appreciate it?
Is that just offend them, and they have this reaction?
I think it's intellectual cowardice.
Personally a lot of things I find are too deep for me,
but I enjoy trying to figure them out anyway,
so I think the reason a lot of people might hate the idea of things being intellectual
is because generally very intellectual people are snobbish.
Yeah, yeah.
There's some sort of like I'm better than you,
sort of trying to fight against that.
A deep work of art makes you work to understand it,
so it's asking more of the viewer,
and it's also kind of, well it means that you can either work harder to understand it,
or you can just like be, I don't know, smarter or whatever you want to call it.
So it's like if you're not smart enough to appreciate it, it's kind of an insult?
Yeah, people are saying like, oh are you saying I'm dumb?
I think the best resistance I would have against that,
and I would just say, I'm not telling you you have to care.
There's a sort of mentality in pop media where people think that everyone has to like everything,
and everything has to be for everyone,
and it shouldn't be.
I would like it much more if things were not made for everyone.
Like look at the AAA gaming scene, it caters to like the mass majority,
and as a result games are worse, they're more homogenous.
It's not as interesting.
I mean it's a thing, it's a matter of, I think that there's,
I like using the terms broad and niche,
where a broad piece of entertainment is made to appeal to as many people as possible,
but it will only appeal to them on a very shallow level.
Whereas when you make something niche that appeals to just like five people,
but to those people it like means everything in the world.
Yeah, once more valuable you have to ask.
Right, so I mean I appreciate why broad media exists,
and it can be a great way to get people into media in general,
and help them to develop like the lexicon of whatever media they're looking at.
If you go out to see a film, because everyone's talking about it, it appeals to everyone,
and then you learn how to appreciate film,
then you can go deeper and find the stuff that just appeals to you.
But like, I think people shame niche media for not being for them,
and it's like, not everything has to be about you dude,
like everyone can like their own shit.
Most of my favorite things are things that are not very widely appreciated,
but they mean a lot to me.
Yeah, yeah.
And I'm not saying anyone's stupid for not liking stuff I like.
I think that most people are just evil.
I would use the word lazy, I think in this case.
Evil, stupid, and lazy.
Is there a difference between evil and lazy?
You know?
I don't know.
Well I think any of those three things, evil, stupid, and lazy,
can become each other by being to a great enough degree.
That's true, that's certainly true.
Yeah, let me interject the second.
I think that a lot of people, when they say that something's deep,
I mean, we're talking about depth,
and I think when we say that, we mean that a thing is thematically rich
and complex and robust.
I think what a lot of people think that the word means
is that it tackles a like very significant theme,
like some like heavy theme, like I don't know, God or whatever.
I don't know if people would assume that.
No, I think you're right, because there's a lot of people who,
a lot of the people who get mad at me for liking stuff like K-On,
people will say it's just shallow, it's not deep,
and K-On has a lot of depth of characterization
and a lot of depth of showing you the human experience.
It tells you something about what people are and what we care about,
but yeah, I think most people, when they think depth,
are definitely thinking it should teach us something about world religion
or psychology or child beating.
That's part of the misunderstanding of Eva.
People think that it's deep because of all the Christian whatever,
and then when they find out that stuff is not really that meaningful,
they say, oh, well, it wasn't deep after all,
but really that's not where the depth is.
The depth into Shiji's character and the way he grows and the whole,
yeah, all that shit, yeah.
That's interesting.
And also I think if a thing tries to tackle some,
I don't know, quote unquote deep philosophical topic,
like the nature of reality or something,
like say, I don't know, kind of like...
Charlie Kaufman shit or...
Yeah, or something like that.
And they, and it fails.
Then I think that that's more, that's worse in a way,
and it looks worse than trying to tackle something more humble,
like, you know, high school girls' relationships like K-On does.
And so I think it's more prone to people seeing it,
being unimpressed with like what's being said,
and being like, it's pretending to be deep, but it's not.
Basically people are focusing on the wrong thing
when they're checking for the too deep for you stat.
Like people aren't going to call K-On,
even if K-On was a shit show,
people wouldn't call it too deep for you, ironically.
They wouldn't say it was pretentious
because they didn't think that it was trying to be deep,
because in their mind, deep means like, you know,
heady philosophical or whatever.
It's not deep if a child doesn't get beaten.
Right. If K-On, for example, like put in a thing
that was like, this is the definitive analysis
of high school girl relationships,
and then failed, like that would make it pretentious,
that would make it, you know,
if it did something like, if it makes some great claim about truth
and then fails, that's what I see.
Well, okay, let me, I want to move on to another topic here, guys.
So I want to ask, what do you do
when you encounter something that is too deep for you,
what that process is like for you?
I think I probably know. Never happens.
Never happens. Of course it never happens.
I watched Eraserhead not too long ago.
Too cultured.
And my first thought upon seeing was like,
okay, this is super pretentious.
I mean, I just don't get it, but everyone loves it,
so I'll give the benefit of that out
and try to figure out what's going on here.
And the cool, I mean, that is completely off the wall.
There's these ridiculous things happening all the time.
But when you step back and you look at it
and you think about, I mean, I had to look all this shit up.
I didn't figure it out. But everything that's happening
really does make sense.
And it's perfectly parsable once you know
like the symbolism and you are able to understand
what's going on.
I also, I watched Eraserhead a couple years ago
on YouTube.
Yeah, it was the kind of thing where like,
I enjoyed the overall experience
and I got like vaguely what it was about.
Like, obviously it's about
dealing with relationships and childbirth.
Like, it's about this awkward guy,
he hooks up with this girl
and everything's super fucking weird and awkward.
And like, you can easily look at it
and say like, well, it's all just,
this is just normal shit, but it's weird.
And it's like, yeah, but the point is that
it's how you're perceiving it.
That's what art is, it's taking something
and explaining it in a different way.
He's explaining his anxiety by way of
constant fucking metal noises
in the background and like,
weird architecture and shit.
And by having the baby
be a literal monster.
And it's like, if you look at it, you go like,
what does this mean? And it's like, it probably means
that babies are fucking monsters,
you know, it probably means that the idea of
childbirth sickens and disturbs this man
and the way he still is, and he still
kind of likes it, like he's got those warm
feelings for it sometimes. Oh, it's good stuff.
It's good stuff, I like it. And that's what, I mean,
that's exactly what the director has said
that he was going through at the time. He was
paranoid about having a kid, you know,
and that movie reflected his paranoia.
It all makes perfect sense if you just look into
it a little bit. And so for that reason, like,
one person's definitely going to call that too deep
for you, but I think a more
informed person
would say no, it's, I get it.
I'd like us each to tell
a story about this, so Hippo, I want to hear you
tell a, well, you can say what you were going to say
first, but. Well, I was just going to say
there's, I think there's like a difference between
getting
like a piece of media and understanding
the depths, because
I, when I come across something
that I, turns out is too deep
for me, like Ava, I didn't understand
it a lot, but I still enjoyed it, and I
got it, but I couldn't ever tell anybody
I couldn't, like
if somebody else did. Yeah, I couldn't
explain. I didn't know what
I'd liked about it, but I knew that I, you know, I
got it, kind of.
And that's how it usually is
with, like,
like, say Gurren Lagann had
lots more, like, in
the subtext than I would ever
have thought about. Dude, nobody gets
Gurren Lagann the first time they see it, nobody.
And, and it's like, I really
liked it, I really liked it,
but, like, you explaining it in your video
made it, like, extra cool.
Yeah, I, and that's what I was hoping
to do, to just lay it on the line for people.
So, yeah, so when, like, something's
too deep, it, as long as it's
got other elements to it, then
it's great.
I think that experience you're describing happens
a lot, both with Ava and, especially
with the show Serial Experiments Lane,
which is an anime series that, like,
most people say that they have to watch it
four times before they, like, before it, like,
clicks with them. I've seen it twice enough, no idea
what's going on. It was funny, though, because, like,
you're halfway there. All right. It was one
of those things for me, because I watched it
for the first, like, all the way through for the first time
when I was 14, and, like,
everyone had said that it takes them four tries
and they don't get it, and then I watched it, and I felt
like I got it, like, I was like, okay, I get the
point, I get what they're going for here, you know,
but, like, a lot of the specifics didn't
make sense to me, and then it was only,
like, you know, like, five years
later I watched it again, and I was like,
I didn't get this before,
like, I thought I did, but I clearly
didn't, because I get it now,
and what I feel now is totally
different from what I felt then, you know,
and eventually I made a series of videos
about it, but, like,
yeah, you know, I think
that effort, that willingness
that you talked about, Hippo,
I made a video about this called Art Is All
About Pressing Your Buttons, about, like,
why I will nit-pick
a show that I don't like so hard,
but with a show I do like,
I'll ignore so many of its flaws,
and it's because, like,
well, there's, like, a give and take between you
and the art, right, like,
a show that I can't stand is Ergo Proxy,
which is an anime series that's really,
it's super too deep
for you, you know, I've
literally called it Pretentious in the past,
that it was the only anime I was willing to call Pretentious,
because it does, it's, like,
way up its own ass with, like, symbolism
and rhetoric and stuff that doesn't
really seem like it means much in the context
of the show, it just seems like it's there
for the sake of having depth, you know, having
deep shit, but, like, you know,
I've had people tell me that
Ergo Proxy, that there are meanings to it,
there's all this stuff that I didn't get,
and it's, like, on the one hand,
I don't disbelieve
those people, but I don't
want to find out, like,
I hate the show, I don't want
to sit there and watch it again until I get it,
you know, like, I'm willing to accept
that maybe there is actual depth there
or that it makes sense if you think about it,
but, like, I don't want
to, whereas other shows, like,
it's kind of like, you know, a show
that needs, like, a balance of shallowness
and depth for it to be really good.
I don't think it has to have shallowness, I just
think it has to press your buttons right, you know?
Well, yeah, like, did you
say, like, he has to have some surface appeal?
That's true.
Did you not hold, like, his audience
hostage and say, like, you have to get this,
and in the same respect, he doesn't, you know,
you shouldn't say did you have to get everything, too.
Yeah, like, Ergo Proxy,
a lot of people like the show because
it has, like, a really good atmosphere,
has beautiful artwork, you know,
like, interesting characters and stuff, so, like...
And the best ending theme song in all of anime, baby!
Yeah, it's got a...
Paranoid Android, dude. Yeah, Paranoid Android by
I keep...
For both song and band,
I was thinking OK Computer, which is the name
of the album, but, like,
yeah, Ergo Proxy has a lot of things
that will draw certain people in,
and they certainly drew me in, but then there was
so much that I didn't like that in the end
I didn't care about it, whereas there are shows
that, like, that I think have
very little surface appeal,
but I still like them,
like, a 12 ounce mouse, like,
which is just ugliest sin
and weird
and slow and
doesn't make any sense, but it does have,
like, a super deep metanarrative
behind it, like, if you watch the whole
show, you'll... I never saw that.
If you watch the whole show, you'll quickly grasp
that there's, like, a whole plot behind it,
like, it is actually a narrative show.
It just doesn't make a lot of sense, and it was
unfinished, so, like, a lot of the answers
have never come out. Oh, no, the, like, 12 ounce mouse
doesn't have a surface appeal, because I
liked it immediately.
Okay, but not everybody really. I would say
it has some surface appeal in that it has,
like, great voice acting, like,
phenomenal voice acting, and it's funny
and weird, you know, but, like,
I don't expect anyone
to look at that show
and immediately be like, oh, yeah, I totally
want to find the hidden depth in fucking
12 ounce mouse, like, most people are going to look at it
and go, what is that, you know? I kind of think
you might be driven to do that by,
just by how, like,
uncommonly terrible its presentation is.
I think maybe the terribleness of
the presentation is part of the surface appeal.
Well, sure, but that's kind of also a thing with,
I don't know, like, what's that one, perfect
hair forever? It kind of reminds me of that,
and I don't think there's a lot of depth and
perfect hair forever. No. I think it really is
just the surface stuff. Not quite the same.
No, I'm just saying that that can be a form
of appeal, is lack
of appeal, if you know what I'm saying.
Yeah, I agree
and I think that would be why some people
might get into perfect, I mean, like, even
without depth, like, sometimes people like
shit just because it's so ugly
and out there, you know? Sure.
But, like, I would pause it,
that, like, if I were to
make, like, some just shitty,
like, let's say, I've tried to make
Jesse Wood's horse shoe saga, but I had
none of the talent.
Like, I'm just a weird, kind of ugly
basement dweller
who doesn't know how to film, whose audio is garbage.
Like, not garbage in a way
that's, like, endearing, but garbage
in a way that's too harsh for you to listen to.
I don't know which parts of that were about me
and which parts were about a guy with no talent.
No, I'm saying, I'm saying
this is a, this is an alternate universe
version of you who has none of the things
that you have going for you. Like, you know
how to, you know how to make a great set,
you have amazing charisma and camera
presence, you know how to write a fucking
type script. One piece of paper with a crayon word
scrawled on it, taped to his bookshelf.
Ten out of ten. It's awesome.
It is awesome, I know, I totally agree.
Everything, everything feels right
in a Jesse Wood video, you know, like
the audio is not necessarily perfect
but it works and the
video quality is not necessarily perfect
but it works. He doesn't have to be fucking
MKBHD for his videos to make sense,
you know, but like,
if I was making the same kind of story
and it was every bit
as deep to me
as the horseshoe saga, but
the writing was like,
do any of you guys watch that
what's his name, Roger Vanderweed guy, that
Davoo is like a fan of? No.
Where his, his writing
is like completely incomprehensible, even though
like, the points he's making are
great and make sense, but you have to
parse this unbelievably difficult
right, in fact he's a, he's basically
who I'm talking about now that I think about it
because his videos are like, weird,
terrible, the audio is way too harsh,
you can't understand what he's saying, the videos
are like, ugly, weird flash animations
of Sonic characters,
he's talking about bullshit
and insanity, yeah, that guy.
The guy who does like Sonic Analyze
with the two, with the two cartoon guys
talking, oh it's so hideous, I hate it.
Yeah, and like, the presentation of them is
so bad that I legit, I can't
get into it, but like, Davoo
like, has gotten into it
and he's even said, he was like, if I found him today
with the standards I have now for like, presentation
there's no way I'd get into it,
but like, because I already am
into it and I know like, what's going on
in the narrative, then it's
you know, he appreciates it
and like, if someone tried
to do the horseshoe saga with
even less skills than Roger van der Weed
then like, no one would
watch it, you know, no one would
appreciate it, but that doesn't mean it's not
deep or that it's not good.
Not to criticize Jesse's presentation
but I think that probably is
at least some portion of that is why
it hasn't reached as big an audience
as you know, we all wish that it would.
I think at a certain point
my continuity
became too much
for your average person.
Yeah, that's certainly true.
Like a lot of the horseshoe reviews
if you were
just going into them as single reviews
would be fucking
horrible to watch.
Well, I mean, the things would be confusing
so some things certainly would be.
You know, when you launched Serialized
Victor, my brother
was like, he was confused
because he thought Man Child Incorporated
when you put out the video that was announcing
that Man Child Incorporated was now a thing
he thought that was the endless jest channel
and that you just changed it again.
So he was like, he literally
got mad after the first Serialized
and he was like, I don't see
the point of it, he was like, who is this for?
And I said, well, it's for like
the Pony fans who've gone on and I was like
it's a new series without the continuity
and he said, but Corona was right
there in the first episode
so this doesn't make any sense.
And I was like, well, I guess and then I
explained to him that, well, it's not
it's not Endless Jest, it's the Pony channel
that's transformed and so it's part
of the same narrative in a way.
They really are all interrelated though.
That's like the best, I love that.
You can hear me in the background.
No more continuity vows so many times
I know you have. You can't let go.
I don't think you should let it go though.
I don't think the problem with your show is
well, let's separate, you know,
as a piece of art, I do not want
Jesse to ever stop doing what he's doing
but like for his own sake, it probably
would be best. Well, I don't think it's
my immediate thought when I started
Endless Jest was, okay,
new beginning, it's new rules, I'm gonna
all the stuff that I did, I'm gonna
do it differently, no continuity,
no reviews and now
it's like six months later and
now I'm just like, you know what,
actually a lot of that stuff is pretty cool.
I gotta take
the stuff that I like about me
discard the stuff that I don't like about me
but still keep the cool stuff.
You know some of the things you like about yourself
aren't necessarily marketable
and I think that's true of all of us.
I think we need a fucking sitcom about
Cold Corona. I would love
a Cold Corona sitcom, that would be great.
Man, I have such plans
in store for Cold Corona guys.
I'm excited.
The serialized saga is going to places
that no one could anticipate.
That sounds amazing.
I think to get back to the whole
art being about pressing your buttons
shit like that. Here's the thing
about Jesse's content.
Even a show like 12 oz mouse
which has no obvious appeal, right?
The reason people got into
that show is that it was on television.
It was literally
in a block where people were going
to watch anyways.
So even if a hundred thousand people
saw it and 99% of them
didn't understand it at all,
1,000 people are still there who are
totally going to love it and get invested
in the story and understand it in the long run.
I think the problem with trying to do this
on YouTube is that there's no real
platform by which
it's one thing
if I make a video saying
hey you should all watch Jesse because
he's basically just like me, then
people who are looking for something just like me
will go watch Jesse and they won't get it.
But like
there's no like TV channel
that is full of things that are kind
of like Jesse that he can be
broadcasted on and then people find out about it.
What he needs really is just
a foot in the door. All he needs is there
to be one video that was
attractive enough and got big enough
that people get curious about it
and then they are along for the ride.
The Batz video has over a million
views now. 2 million
2 million worthless views
that haven't translated to anything.
The video was blocked for
monetization within the first day.
I've seen no revenue from it
and nobody subscribed because
you should have contested that
you'd have at least 2 grand by now.
You think that the people who like this,
my little pony review would want to see more like it
because there's plenty more like it.
And the worst part is that if I took down the Batz review
and reposted it, it wouldn't get views anymore.
No, it's in the
YouTube feed cycle somehow.
It's due to the initial momentum
from when it was released.
But anyways,
I forget it. No, go on, go on.
I think we're running low on
stuff. Yeah, not to just talk
about myself,
which would be the most pretentious and too deep.
That'll be next week's topic, yeah.
Oh god, we could go on
for fucking hours.
I'm surprised. I could go on for this topic
for quite a bit longer.
I was talking like
fucking a while ago
when I first mentioned Horseshoe Finale
and how for a long time I wasn't sure
how I could articulate it to people
if anyone asked me. Right.
But I finally figured out, I finally got
the sentence in my head
that I can give to people now
if they ever ask me what it's about.
The simplest way that I can explain it
is that it's a retelling of a Christmas Carol.
I see. That's pretty good.
What's a retelling of a Christmas Carol?
Horseshoe Finale, or the Horseshoe Saga.
It's a story about a guy
who turns into this
fucking big bastard
but then he's confronted with his past
and his decisions and where he is now
and he has to come out of it.
And that's the main thing.
I really don't understand the Horseshoe Saga, do I?
I think you did fine in the Horseshoe
Finale, explaining it as
a wrestling narrative. I agree.
I think that, again, like the art
is the explanation, but
I was saying that I was struggling for a long time
to come up with a sentence that I can throw at people.
You know what's an element? Yeah.
What did I call it in my video, the Top 10?
Like, just the biggest come ever?
Well, that's just going to be my
go-to to throw at people
if anyone asked me.
The world's largest end zone dance after
the world's largest end zone dance
after the series of touchdowns that was
the Horseshoe Saga. That's right.
It's a disgustingly well-made MLP reviews, blah, blah, blah.
Does anybody else
want to bring up an example
of something that was too deep for them
experience before we wrap
things up? Because I know, did you mention that before?
You got a bunch of those. I forgot
if you had one or not.
Oh, did you? Yeah, if you want to do one?
Well, I could, but I want to hear Jesse first, because we didn't get to him.
That's true. Hippo did one, I think.
There's one creator
who I specifically view
as a pretentious
fucking knob-sucker,
and I hate all of his work.
Hey, hey.
Don't say that about Max Landis. He's a good man.
He's the
director, Lars van Trier.
Oh, yes.
I hate him. Somehow I should have known.
I've seen all of his movies.
Wow. When he releases a new movie,
I make a point to see it just so I can
hate it.
Or just so that I can see how much
I hate it.
Fun fact, I only ever
saw the first five minutes of Antichrist.
My friends were watching it on Netflix,
and I looked at it and I went, this is fucking pretentious
and I left the room.
Okay, he makes like
he makes exploitation movies.
That's what they are.
But rather than just
say like a Quentin Tarantino
would say, I make exploitation
movies. Isn't it great?
He's got to fucking put it in black and white
piano music. He's got to make it three hours
long and try to convince people
that it's like the most mind-blowing
complex thing ever
and people fall for it. This is the
greatest director of all time. He's amazing
and it's just fucking schlock.
It's just William Defoe's penis getting
stabbed to the screw. It's just fucking
Mary Jane
laying in a bathtub naked
being depressed for four
fucking hours.
Oh my god, I hate him. His movies
are so fucking
droll and boring. No, no, no.
Droll means interesting. Droll means cool.
Droll does not mean cool.
Droll means funny. We had this fight before
me and Ben had a huge fight about it once.
Turns out I was right. Well, I guess, I guess
droll is too deep for me.
Loveiest droll.
Yeah.
Life is droll. That's what, what's her name?
Kill La Kill always says.
Kill La Kill is a thing
that people, I think
seem as like not deep.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's legitimately too deep for most
of the people who watch it. I walked away from Kill La Kill
after seeing it, feeling like I had seen
something that was very complex
and had a lot to say.
And then I go online and everyone's like
not surprisingly
but still
disappointingly. There's a chart,
dude. This made me so mad because
there's this chart that's like an intro to
anime, intro to recommendations
and the guy clearly
knows his stuff in terms of what shows are good.
It's a great recommendation chart
but there's a part where it's in action shows
and it's like, I think it goes to
Girl in the Gone or something that it's like, do you want this?
But with no depth, then it goes to Kill La Kill.
Get out of here.
Really? Dude, Kill La Kill
and again, legit.
Too deep for everyone who watches it.
I know that the stuff that's in it
is there on purpose because
I've heard the creators talk about it
and I know their work and I know that they
fucking know shit, you know.
It's going back to people
thinking that depth
is equated to seriousness
or like big world
things. That's really weird to me.
Sorry, Ben. Go ahead.
I was just going to say that's really weird that people
think that about Kill La Kill because when I watched it
I felt like it was really being
shoved in my face that
this is a subversion of typical
anime nudity.
That's not even what I took out of the most
impressive to me.
I think people
probably write it off because of the
nakedness and whatever and just the
balls to the wall action and the scantily
it's so clearly saying
something about that stuff.
When Episode 3
rolled around and it was like Episode 3
is literally just stating a message about
the fact that she's trying to
use nudity as power and the
empowerment of being naked without shame
like it's literally a conversation about
that and then like you know there's
been a lot of debate over whether the way
the show handles that is meaningful or not
or if it's really, and like yeah that debate's
fine but then when people like
and that is deep but there's like a lot
more throughout the show you know and I
appreciate not getting it because
when I watched the show my impression
was I feel like there's something here
I'm not getting and me and Nate did a podcast
where me and Nate both said
like there's definitely something here
we're not getting because we were both confused
and I did no further research so at this
point I still am happy to admit I do
not fucking kill a kill. Whereas I
then like you know read some
shit that other people were saying about it
and then went to this panel where this guy like broke
it all down in like extensive detail and I'm like
holy shit like yeah this all
makes perfect sense and it
all totally is intentional
and it's definitely super
deep you know like this is some of the most
interesting stuff that's happened in a TV
series ever should remove yourselves
from the mindset that something
that's fun or sillier
you know can't also be complex
like another example
is Space Dandy
yeah I fucking
Space Dandy is an amazingly deep
show all of Watanabe's show Cowboy Bebop
you could say that about it's
the fucking it's and everyone would say Bebop
is deep and that's the thing though that's
why everyone would say Bebop is deep because
Bebop has moments where
the camera is so slowly and he looks
at his eyes the one's different colors because
it sees the future the other sees the past holy shit
they eat the bell peppers
without the beef it's bell peppers and beef without
the beef it's a deep
poverty it sinks in you know when Fe and
the other girls leave and the eggs are in their bowl and they start
eating those eggs instead of just their own
hey that's my analysis I did that one
that's a great scene
holy shit I love that scene so much but
yeah
but yeah like Space Dandy is
doing a lot of the same things just with
different characters who aren't obviously
like relatable
and with a layer of more silliness and stuff
which in no way detracts from the messages
underneath at all it just yeah
and I would also say that it's a matter of
like Space Dandy starts on the wrong
foot the first episode kind of sucks
and the first episode of Cowboy Bebop is fucking amazing
so people start up Cowboy Bebop
and they go this is gonna be
the most mind-blowing shit I ever see
in my life and they're proven right and
people start Space Dandy and they go this just
seems stupid and then you know seeing
the trailers for Space Dandy
and being really excited like wow this is
a it's gonna be like a fun like a
sci-fi throwback and like a flash
Gordon thing or a Star Trek
I watched the first episode and I just
didn't care to watch anymore for like
months huh yeah until I finally
picked it back up and then cool shit
started happening I mean I probably would
have if not for the fact that
it was a Watanabe show then I might
not have watched all of it that was my
whole reason to be interested and I still
haven't watched it but I really need to
but it definitely has
depth as it goes along and I actually
think that more people who watch all of
Space Dandy appreciate its depth
possibly because so many fewer people
have watched all of Space Dandy compared to
Kill La Kill but like I think
it is that I don't even understand
they seem both equally hyped to me
well we're all over Space Dandy's dick
when it was coming out a space
a throwback before it was out
yeah Space Dandy was very throwbacky
it was very old school I heard about
Kill La Kill has tits everywhere
that's the main reason that it's so
popular is that it has fucking tits everywhere
that's a lame reason it should be ashamed
well they don't they don't shove in your
face like a promo art I guess main characters
and like everyone in the
show like I think I think with Kill La
Kill it was a mixture of like
being a good show and also
being a show where there's tits
everywhere because everyone likes
shows where there's tits everywhere but no one wants
to admit it and if the shows are
usually bad so like
you know like a school a show like
high school DxD is really popular
because it's just
good enough that people can handle it
but then everyone's apologizes
for it nobody wants to admit it
don't they know the literal best thing
about that show is all the tits they shove
in your face and especially how the main
character is completely unashamed
he just does not give a fuck and it is
he's my favorite main character I've seen in 10 years
he's amazing he's my hero
I think there's a lot of people who do apologize
for their Kill La Kill affection
and I see a lot of apologies for it
but I think there's also
a lot more people who can
watch it and not feel that they have to
like they can say
well it's really good and of course
they'll explain it as
oh it's just good you can
turn your brain off sometimes
it's gonna offend me more than language like that
you know what it reminds me of
MLP people are just like
what even is this
there's nothing good to it
it's my little point there's no way it could be good
they just write it off because of this superficial
layer and do absolutely no research
to find out whether or not that's even close to true
or even worse they do research
and come across the fandom
and that makes it even more
I think
I've said this before
with ponies we used to say
anytime we criticize the show
people would always say it's a kids show
and then we'd say why are you watching it
if it's just a kids show
that's not good why are you watching it
because you shouldn't be
if that's the case
that's a good one
so my extension
of that to Too Deep For You
is if people say like
well sometimes you can just turn your brain off
and enjoy something and I would say
oh my god
if you just ignore
the bad parts
and only talk about the good parts
everything is a 10 out of 10
guys it's okay
you can watch anything it's all amazing
he nailed it
if you can
if criticizing
something is so wrong
or if all
art is just supposed to be fun
and it's not supposed to be deep
there's a difference just watch everything
it shouldn't matter anymore
just go for it
and depth can come in so many different forms
that it could just be
even if the only reason you watch a show
is that the character designs are good
the fact that the character designs are good
is kind of deep because
why are they good
what makes them good to you
why does your brain interpret them that way
and complexity and artistic
depth can come accidentally too
it's been a while
he literally
just wanted people
punching each other and going on adventures
but he ended up making this
all-encompassing
this saga of this character's entire life
and his children
and it's beautiful
depth can totally be accidental
and I think
that it probably should be
if you set out to make something deep
you're probably not making the thing you're trying to make
you're probably going to fail
I think you can
I don't think depth has to be
incidental so much as that
you can have an idea
and know it's deep and make it
obviously Undertale
Toby Fox knew it was deep
there's no way he thought it was just
some shallow
I just made this thing
that comments on the nature of the medium
and has everything to do with everything
people would think it was deep
he knew it had
qualities but didn't know
wasn't prepared to say
I don't think that he set out
I think what Ben is really trying to say is
I don't think you should set out to make something deep
but if the idea you have is deep
then whatever
run with it
he surely knew it was deep
but I don't think his goal was make a deep game
I agree with that
well
does anybody want to give any more examples
to wrap it up to did Ben
do you want to give an example of a thing
no
wait what about that comic I read recently
that was really great
the vapors
I don't know
is that something that I can support on Patreon
as a matter of fact
it is Jesse
just go to patreon.com
throw a couple of bucks the creators way
he's a real deep guy
I don't know about you guys but I'm going to go do that
before this video ends
I got to run
not walk to that Patreon page
I love
to get back to the topic at hand
I run into stuff all the time
that is like too deep for me
and
it's always like that
battle of like on the one hand
I really in fact I would say
all video games are too deep for me
all of them
all video games
because
you know what all of them
most of the games I beat
in the last 15 years
were like
6 hour action games
games like Devil May Cry
or fucking vanquish
or platinum games and stuff like that
but I always just played through them on normal mode
in 6 hours
and then never again
and like
what do you do with those
I know that there's way more depth to those games
if you replay them and get to the highest
because most of those games like
are made really with the highest difficulty in mind
if you play something like
Metal Gear Rising Revengeance
or Metal Gear Solid 3
or any of the Metal Gear Solid games
but like 3 most especially
the level of complexity
and depth of high level play
is so much different from low level play
that's basically another game
about what you can be forced to do
by the difficulty increasing
and how it makes you be creative and explore the game more
and I think that
most mainstream
critics of games engage
about 50% of the depth
of the game
maybe close to the 75%
depending on the game
that's the thing though
I think the reason that a game like Bioshock Infinite
gets so much critical praise
is that you don't have to play it again
you appreciate the depth
you do not have to play Bioshock Infinite twice
at all
I played it on the highest difficulty
because it's so fucking easy
and the combat is so terrible
that I played it on the highest difficulty
and fucking had a breeze with it
and there was nothing else that I felt like I was missing
there's little recursive hints
like maybe you'll get a little more out of the story
if you play it a second time
but I don't think it's anywhere near the level
of Metal Gear Solid 3
I think the systems of the game to play it on the highest difficulty
compared to normal mode
and that's why reviews are often times
not really very great ways to judge
the content of a game
that's why you need someone like Super Bunnyhop
who will beat that motherfucker up
he will smash the pussy of that shit until it no longer works
to tell you how it works
it's interesting though
that you bring that up
that a game could be reviewed well
because it is shallow enough
to be easily died
to the reviewing circle
is what they're going to advocate for
it plays well in the format that reviewers play
which is usually
at like a hotel somewhere
because they've been invited to a review event
or a fucking corporate event where they're surrounded by staffers
telling them how to play the game
and I love Bunnyhop
especially because and I was saying this
about the Fallout 4 review
and we had a little debate about this
maybe even in the best game ever podcast
where I was saying how like
this game is not that good
right now
the depth of this game will really be
explored once people start modding it
and turning it into something different
and then we'll suddenly have
probably a much better game on our hands
and I wish more reviewers
would write like that
would write like
this review is based on
I played this many hours of the game
this is how like all those fucking phantom pain reviews
that gave the game a 10 out of 10
and it's like did you really make it
did you really play the fucking
like what 90 hours it takes
to beat this fucker
because I don't think you did
I think you probably made it to the first ending
and went okay it was 10 out of 10
I didn't get bored with it because I only played it
for fucking three days and I didn't realize how much
like you know
bullshit there is but then again
if you do go beyond the impossible like Bunnyhop did
beat it to 100% completion
and found all kinds of unique things
that even people who played it
to the end you know who people like you guys
were just like oh fuck this game
it sucks you know like
he found all kinds of other shit
to like about it and came out with the sort of
you know and I'm not saying like reviewers
shouldn't review games on that level of
engagement because I think most people play games
on that level of engagement
games are too deep for most people
most people won't go all the way through
most people never see Ash Lake in Dark Souls
in the same way we need
different games for different people
we kind of need different reviewers for different people
and that's why George Weidman is so valuable
not only is he he's a real
real modern journalist
he does it the way that
that technology allows it to be done now
much better than
going to one of these fucking events and like
playing it for 10 hours or whatever
and like he plays it in the way that I play
games personally in fact he goes beyond what I need
but the thoroughness
is so welcome and so rich
I would love it if every reviewer
like if where they have all those stats
on like game stuff or whatever
game spot where they have like the little like
notations on the side or if it said like
how many hours I spent
playing it how many
you know like how many times I beat it
what difficulty I beat it on because you know
those are so important
super relevant and I love Yahtzee
who I respect him so much because
he does that in all of his review he'll tell you
like I only play games on medium
I expect them to be that I only play them
for a week because I have to do a show
you know like if I return to a game I'll probably
talk about it on a different show not my review
show he's admitted when he played
Final Fantasy 13 he was like this game's not for me
I played 10 hours and I'm fucking sick of it
I'm too busy
half of his review was about how he was opening up the
mana bar and therefore he couldn't
find time to play the game you know because
he didn't care about it like that says something
about it yeah like that's and
and like for me those reviews are
perfect because that's how I play most games
you know and I go okay Yahtzee I'm
I'm with you I also don't want to spend
30 hours waiting for this game to get good
you know but it doesn't get good after 30
hours let's be clear but yeah
but like you know
for other people there are and
and you know I think I think those reviews
are out there they're just very decentralized
right right game stop is not or game
spot or whatever it's not the ones making
those reviews if you go to like rpgamer
or something you'll find the guy who writes
that review you know I think I think it's
just a matter of like people should go out
and find the reviews that actually reflect
the way they play games right right
this is we've gotten off top we're completely
my point is that video games are too deep
for me because I never beat them to that level
of completion right
okay that's covers everybody we've all
told the story that this was
excellent discussion this was everything
I hoped it would be about the subject
anybody have any any other last thoughts
they want to put in
my dick
I think we all were thinking
that yeah the only one who said I mean
let's let's be at the end of the day what's the thing
that's too deep for anyone my dick
way too fucking deep
all right my dick runs deep
so deep put her ass to sleep
cutting off that blood flow in all the right
ways all right guys
I guess that's it thanks for watching everybody
and follow me
on Twitter at it's also ugly
stcomics.com
you know it's like we've got it's like you
just look at the fucking description
we've linked everything it's like we've got a
spam bot in the conversation in all
the best ways
all right thanks
for watching everybody we'll be back next week
with another one leave your comments in the description
leave any suggestions you got for next week
everybody say bye
bye