I won't bless that guy that son of a bitch.
Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's Ben Saint and Gibbontake.
I just attacked Ben with a red hot poker.
Yeah, yeah, you know how it is
Do you have something you wanted to start with well, I was gonna ask you about phantom's revenge cuz I was sure yeah phantom's revenge is out
You played it I did played it you played it and I watched you stream it and it was
So fun watching you figure it out in real time
I
Had a I re I rewatched most of the stream cuz I just liked it that much. Oh
Wow, yeah, I know it was great
Well, I'm glad to have been the perfect
Gamer for that one the perfect gamer you I think you you told me that you
Eventually you didn't beat it on stream, but you said it took you like three more tries
Which meant that you took like six tries total
Like so seven. Yeah, some of my bad
I think that's less than most people, but you really took your time with it like you really like
Took a while for each run and you were like unpacking after every move and like really like carefully choosing
Your next decision
It was because I had played the demo and that was like
The point of the demo is that you have to find out the one
Way to beat it. Yeah
And so every single thing you do is like that could end the run if you don't know what you're doing
Yeah, if you don't think about what you're doing. Yeah, I came into the the game with the right mindset
Yeah, I have I don't know. I might have told you this
I've definitely told some people on Twitter this but um, you know the demo was like really hard to the point that you basically
Couldn't win unless you did exactly the right
Moves every time every turn
The the the game as the final game is not quite like that. It's still pretty hard
You got to know what you're doing. You can't fuck around, but there is some leeway in there
You can you can make a few suboptimal decisions, but if you play it optimally 100%
there is a
Wind condition in there. There's something you can do in there that is as hard as the demo was
Which is to say there's only one way to do it
Specifically that is getting to the end without letting Virginia take any damage
You can you can keep Virginia completely safe through the whole thing if you do everything 100%
Correct and not yeah
Yeah
Well, well one one person actually did it like sauce pirate
seemingly by accident or maybe maybe just a
They just
Figured it out and just have just happened to do it the right way or something
But yeah, they they they did it that way and I was like wow. I almost and I kind of didn't expect anyone to do it like that
I
Feel like once you know
How long the game is yeah, and like what is expected of you to win?
Yeah
Because I think one of the playthroughs
I don't know whether this was on stream or off stream, but I did like optimal plays. I kept Virginia alive
I got to the end and I'm like, okay. I
have a
ton of slime
That is not useful
Because the amount of damage I will take and the amount of attacks I need to perform. Yeah, do not like deplete it
That much and I can't use it to level up because all my poisons are gone. So that that number is
Like excess slime I can use elsewhere earlier in the run. You mean after the after the big room
Yeah, after the big room or at some point near the end where it's like yeah
calculating the amount of
Slime I need and I had excess so I knew yeah that I could use that excess earlier in the run to save on like
oh
No, I think it was like I realized that I could afford to level up earlier and
Then that excess slime will be used up by my attacks
Right, and then it was like it was those sorts of realizations that were fun, right? Yeah. Yeah seeing you
Seeing you like figure something out like oh wait a minute like oh if I oh
I actually have to dab like if I dab it actually saves slime because then Virginia does the attacks
And I don't have to spend it just like kind of kind of seeing you
Like go from room to room and then in in a particular room
There were there were a couple of times when I was like
This is exactly what I wanted the player to feel like I wanted like I wanted them to get here and die in this specific way
And realize oh I can't do that what I have to do is this instead, and then I won't die there
The
There are
Yeah, so when I when I I added them the anoint command for leveling your weapon up
and and
Weapon marriage I added them in like a later update kind of just as like a
Joke basically like I added them thinking that they wouldn't even like do anything
But it turns out it created like a completely separate way that you can win
Like I didn't even intend for this to be it to be the case, but it turns out you actually
Well, I made the game thinking you would have to level up to win
But with anoint in the game you actually don't have to level up anymore
You can level up just only by anointing and without level you or you can win with only anointing and not leveling up
I didn't even mean for that to be the case, but it turns out it is and that's okay
I'm not sure which is like easier. I think it's just like whichever one you kind of
figure out first
Ends up being the way to do it, but they both work
I just think that's pretty funny because I think I didn't mean for it to be useful, but it is
That's like a lot of games
Yeah, they don't they don't have like a one win condition
They have like a bunch of systems that can interact in so many possible
Permutations the game designer couldn't possibly like account for every possible way
Yeah, I thought because leveling up gives you boost your damage more than
than
Anointing I thought that anointing would not boost it enough to meaningfully make a difference, but it turns out it did
So
Yeah, I am I've been watching my itch
analytics and
I
Was pleased to see that the game got a little boost the other day from being featured on Equestria daily
Yeah, a
Lot of people saw that and we're like I can't believe Equestria daily is still
Still posting I can't believe that sethisto
Yeah, I don't know much about what he knows
Okay, it's such an odd thing to put this like Justin does it
I don't know if he does like OC things a lot. Maybe he does. I mean
Well, you remember how it was back in the day, right? I
Mean back in the day if you made anything pony related
You would get like I feel like it had to at least be like relating to the show
Like your thing is almost entirely your own OC and a bunch of slime and
It's like it's barely anything to do with my little pony. That's true. You know on the one hand
You're totally right on the other hand. I really feel like I
Like I just said that back in the day they would host like
anything pony
It's got how much it's got it's got to be drier
Like the wells got to have run even drier these days, right? Like the brony fandom has reduced significantly
There's got to be less to go around. I feel like they'd be hungrier than ever
um, I suppose so but I mean
You're right though. They weren't gonna do it. I'm sure I added sethisto on Twitter just to see if I could maybe entice him and
Nothing happened right away
And then oblivion fall told me that he like emailed sethisto and like asked
Are he say I don't I don't know if he I don't know if he
Just like recommended it like hey look at this game or if he said like hey so that hey sethisto
Please you know you and I we go back, you know, we're we're best friends, uh, please as a personal favorite
I know it's embarrassing. I know Ben Saint is like a is like a weird freak and nobody would
Nor is ordinary circumstances want to be associated with please please let me call you know
I you know, I gave you my kidney that one time you were you know dying of alcohol poisoning
And you needed a new a new some new organs like please just I'm trying to call it in that favor now
Please just feature Ben Saint stupid little slime game on your pony website. Thank you and good night. I
Don't know which of those two things happened
I mean, I feel like Seth has always been consistently pretty cool. I
So like I'm sure I'm sure once it's been brought to his attention. He'd read it out like the blurb
I mean, wow, this is pretty funny. I mean, I look up ponies like I think I can see him just being like, oh cool
I don't really know any what he's like at all. So maybe you're right. I just I got no idea
I would think of you. Yeah, there was a blurb on the site that
Seemed it's see, I don't know. I guess he wrote it
So and it seemed like pretty genuinely appreciative of it. So yeah, maybe he saw it was like, uh, lol, what is this?
Which should be cool
Yeah, I'm joking about the the other option
I'm joking with the liver, but if Clayson wasn't clear, I don't think that that actually I don't think that that actually happened
Although I can't prove that it didn't
Um
Yes, and then um, I yeah, uh, oh, yeah side cyber shell played the game and posted his results
And I asked him if you wanted to come on this episode. He said he couldn't make it this week, but it will have him on
Someday one of these days soon and I'll ask him. I don't know to tell me that the game is good
And then he will
Uh, any oh, yeah, anyway, check it check out check out my analytics. Let's look at these analytics in the general
There they are. What flag is that? I think it's uh, is it bisexual?
Let's say it looks like one of those four different purples. It's like super bisexual. There's even more shades
You know what? This is this is four four distinct shades of purple instead of three
It's bisexual, but it it it specifically excludes the possibility of being like equally
Attracted to to men or women. It's like yeah
You can be you can be bi and you could be into one and the other, but you can't ever be perfectly
Perfectly in the middle. You always got to lean one side or another
I'm taking the stand and I'm fine with the L's and the B's and the G's and the T's
But the B's that are like I mean I'm kind of in the middle like nah those specifically those ones
I don't put their liars. They're just lying. They got to have a preference. That's what this flag means. I
sected more like by
Fercated by
No, um
The word I was looking for was defenestrated, but that's not that's not right. He forested
D-flowered
So what what's the yeah use the um, that's a big jump
Yeah, that was that was the day after the equestria daily feature
Uh, as you can see, so it actually had as you can see it got yeah, it actually did it got it got like um
Because it's not just on the website. It was also on the equestria daily
Instagram
And I saw the instagram got like a hundred or two hundred likes on the on the phantoms revenge post
That was pretty funny
But okay, what's interesting to me here is these colors, right?
Because there's four of these colors and these mean something um
They are these are these represent the sources that of the traffic
uh that
Okay, so
On the left see there's like the the purple on the top and then like a middle purple in the middle and then pink on the bottom
The the the top purple is on the far left not the not the blue we'll get to that later
On the left the purple is from twitter
And then the middle purple is from my website stcomics.com
And then the bottom pink is from itch.io
I think what that means is people just discovering it organically on the website scrolling. Yeah. Yeah, which is good
Like that's what I want the most of
Uh, because I think what that means is people who had never seen
You know my stuff before just finding it on the site like oh, what is this?
um
And then see yeah on the the day it gets the big spike that big up blue blue is from equestria daily.com
but you know encouragingly
uh the uh
Yeah, the pink bar the people discovering it on itch got got a boost too somehow. I don't know
um
Maybe that means people were going to the website and typing it in the search bar and finding it that way
It could be that or it could be like increased traffic
boosts the algorithm of itch and so it gets shown
It's like oh, this is a hot new thing. There's loads of people looking at it and then more people would find it via itch
I can't do anything
Yeah, maybe I I hope so and then uh that last day that's
Uh, that's today. So like, you know, it's still 10 a.m. So I'm hoping
I'm hoping that you know by the end of today it gets maybe it's has as many or maybe even more than uh yesterday
um, I don't know
but uh, yeah, so
You know people are are finding it through the website, which is good because you know, I would I hoped that the game would appeal not mere
I hoped that the game would appeal for its gameplay and for its puzzle elements to you know, just people that like
in video games, uh
and not necessarily just to people who uh
Have read the comic although, you know, obviously it's got the story in there that is directly tied into the comic and all that
Uh, so it's nice to see some people. Uh, just just find in it. That's very encouraging
Yeah, yeah
What else? What else? It's been good job. Nice game. Thanks. I'm proud of the game
I think it came out really good
uh, I want
more people to play it. I think I have
200 and something downloads now and I don't know like what
You know like in in terms of youtube numbers like that's terrible like 200 views of a video is like well
Get out of here. I don't know
like
That's gotta be better on itch. I don't know. That's probably I feel like that's probably a lot for just some game that someone posts on itch
I don't know if that's like if I should feel good about that number or bad about that number
Well, I don't have access to
uh pumpkin alley
like
Not not that i'm not that it's a contest or anything
No, no, no, no, I'm trying to see like if there's like a trend
What I have hippo not tries not to die from skeletons on
It's the analytics on that one. How do I find this?
Uh, if you go to your dashboard
Oh, shit, this doesn't go all the way back. No, it goes back to november 2021, but this was uploaded before that
It must be somewhere
Hmm
I so I um, yeah
I released a patch like two days or after release. I released a patch because there were some uh
There were a couple of little minor things that I had missed
and uh
I I had to I deleted the original file
And I uploaded a new file version 1.1
That's what you can download on the site now and I made a little development log
A patch notes page that explains like what all the changes are. It's all really minor stuff
um
But I but uh because it deleted the original file
It deleted the the record of like how many downloads that file had and I was like, oh, no
Now i'm gonna lose my analytics data
About you know, how many downloads the game has but no
It remembers how many downloads the page has had separately from how many downloads that particular file has had
So I did not lose that
Information so I know that it's 200 and
200 and like and 230 I think I pulled up. Um
Uh hippo tries not to die from skeletons when it came out
Or after I made a video about it. It got like 200 views. That was the spike
Mm-hmm, and then way later in like 2019 you got 50 views somehow. I don't know why
Was it like was it like uh, was it like
When oblivion fall made that uh made that uh
Uh the the cuphead animation, uh, I don't know could be
I feel like that was earlier, but it maybe is that then from that point, uh
Yeah, I don't I don't know. I haven't looked at the um dashboard analytic stuff that much
Phantom's revenge
To where I'm sitting at. Oh, no. Oh it passed 207 250
2174 views 277 downloads
It's not enough. It's not enough
When I hit a thousand downloads
When I hit a thousand downloads, uh
Where can I shill it?
Harder
Maybe I should like email some
Could I email some gaming games journalists about it? Maybe I don't know
Uh, yeah, I don't know about that. I don't know how that works
I don't know. I you know, I tried I sent a couple emails about endless war to some like games journals once
Uh, it nothing ever happened
uh
I mean
I could try it again now that I have a game with graphics
These fucking hacks need their need the baby needs their bottle. I guess game journals need their graphics
On their video games
I guess
Anyway, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, two 250 241
Views of that game hippo tries not to die
30 28 downloads
On on the peak and then there's a bunch of other ones. How do I find like the just just just on like one day?
Yeah, that was the the the peak is the same like 200 something views
The 28 downloads of that shitty little like who cares thing
But you're talking that's that was the day like the day it got the most
Traffic is what you're saying. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah
Uh, um, hmm. Well, if you go to yeah, if you go to dashboard
Oh, wait, I'll download counts 548 people downloaded hippo tries not to die
Hmm. That's my target. That's my glass ceiling. I got a breakthrough
Uh
Yeah, it's an it's a new creator dashboard
Did I did I talk did I mention the ukraine bundle? I think I did last episode
I think yeah, we did
The the games on there are so fucking ridiculous
You get the you get minute you get Celeste
You get the kingdom 2
You get there's like there's like a bunch of like
Games like everybody should play
On there. Yeah
I when I noticed was super hot, which is when I wanted to play but I couldn't be bothered to pay for it
Hmm. Do you have do you have a vr rig?
Uh, my brother does
Oh, oh bob. Oh my god. Yeah, baba is you and a short hiker on there
Already had those but that is nice. I did already have a short hike. I did not have the baba is you
So I might I might play that actually I already had I actually already had
Celeste and minute and a short hike, but like
Any one of those games is worth the ten dollars for the bundle. So I got the baba is you so I might play the baba as you know
I think one of the baba is you I think one of the baba is you guys worked on noida
I feel like I remember that factoid somewhere. I
Can't don't quote me on that
um
Anyway, this week has felt really long because
The the day that I put the game out
Felt like it it felt like an entire week went by
It's like watching. I don't know just watching like the numbers go up and like hearing people like, you know
Responding to people on twitter being like, oh, I can't beat it games too hard
It's it seems like it seems like people can beat it in
The number of tries varies from like, you know, half a dozen to maybe like up to like 20
But it seems like it takes people around like four to six hours or so
Of you know, try and shit and figuring it out
To to to figure it out. Yeah, how long was my stream like three hours your stream was about three hours. Yeah
Yeah, it took me like
Maybe two hours after that off stream
Mm-hmm
Steel viper said it took them like four or five hours
That seems that seems to be about where it's settling
which is uh
I don't know that might be
Maybe it's long. Maybe it's long, but uh, whatever
I hope that um
I hope that uh, it's gratifying when when you when if people can stick with it
And you know have that realization. Uh-huh. I found out what I need
I figured I would need to do and then execute on it and get to the end
I hope people will be like
Yeah, it was worth it. It was it was worth my my energy
My precious my precious spirit energy my precious time on this earth was uh
spent well enough
uh
If unless you have anything else, I don't know. Do you is there anything else to say about that at the moment?
Um, I don't know. I mean I I liked it. I enjoyed uh the figuring out of stuff
Yeah, it's very polished and cool looking
Thank you
and the
the story
And the the face the face of I guess we can't I don't really want to spoil like exactly what happens
I know you everyone knows that it's his phantom's revenge and nightstar is involved
Nice. I mean nightstar is on the um her little her little gift and the thing is on is on the store page. So uh, yeah
Yeah, so there's no reason to like spoil what happens, but I really like that one face
That one face. Yeah, I yeah, that's good. It's a good face
uh the
I have been um, I have been retweeting people that uh
At me or hashtag phantom's revenge with the screenshots of their you know win
Uh, I have not
I won't I don't retweet ones that include the entire screen because the entire screen shows
Spoilers, so if you want me to retweet you just uh, just crop that out. Just show your stats. Oh, yeah the um
You know what I want to mention the
The patch I did here's here's what I did in the
The the v version 1.1 patch notes
Uh, oh, yeah, this is funny
Did you know that the the the damage that the son that the squirt gun soniches did it was just wrong
They simply did not do the amount of damage that it said they were doing
I yeah, I think I saw somebody talk about that somewhere
Uh, and I it was so I I had no idea that it was incorrect. I just assumed that what I was looking at
Was truth. It's uh, the insect was a lie. I don't think it would have made that much difference
Really in in terms of like
Although I do remember that on the stream at one point you said like
Oh, I it's it seems important that the squirt gun damage deals more damage than attacking
Costs slime and it turns out that that's not true. I mean, yeah, yeah the the okay
So what what happened was I I figured it out. Um
These squirt guns were meant to do 960 damage
And it calculates the damage they should do as 960, but then to actually deal the damage
It because you know when you're taking the damage your your slime number like
You know it it actively like rolls down, you know, it doesn't just change number
So it deals a fraction of that damage every frame the animation is playing
And it turns out that the animation was only 20 frames and I thought it was 25 frames
So it only dealt four fifths of the intended damage. So it dealt 768 instead of 960
Uh, but you know the game was all balanced around the amount of damage they were actually doing
So I just changed it to be 768 to preserve the balance. So now it's now at version 1.1
It actually says 768
It feels like a really strange way to
To calculate the damage something takes
You think so like for for every frame of animation like if you ever wanted to change an animation
Everything would be shifted
right
Um
Yes
Yes, if I if I changed the if I changed how long
Okay, well, here's what happens. Here's what happens the the sonichu squirts a bullet, right?
It creates a bullet object the bullet object moves to
Uh, the player or the the the hero being targeted
Uh, then when it reaches their location
The bullet destroys itself and creates a new object
That is called hit splash and it's a little has a little like splash like to show like water splashing off of them
and then that hit splash animation depending on whether the bullet was shot by a
Uh, a squirt gun sonichu or a super soaker sonichu
It it has a lifetime value that is set to either
A long value or a short value and then it counts down that value until zero and then it destroys itself
And so that lifetime value determines how many frames
the object lasts
And so for the super sonichu it only the lifetime value it was set at at 20
And so it it exists for 20 frames
And then it dies. So yeah, if I were to change how long that
Uh lasted it would change the amount of damage that was that was being dealt
uh
actually the the number is like
The number of damage is actually based on
Phantoms starting slime level. So if I changed phantom starting slime level all the sonichus and all of both types
Would suddenly deal a different amount of damage because they calculate a value based on his starting level
And then they take that number and then they do the thing of like, okay
They divide it about by the number of frames and then they do a fraction of it every frame
That's I mean, that's how I achieved the uh the effect of like his his uh,
You know his slime count like, you know rolling down as he takes damage
I probably there probably was a another way to do it
It seems overly complicated and relies on like multiple different things aligning perfectly
Uh, it might it might be
To tell you the truth. There's another thing
I mean, there's probably a lot of things like that. Um
The screen shake like when
Okay, like when phantom takes damage, there's a screen shake effect
uh
Let me tell you what doesn't happen in that in when the screen shakes the game does not
render an image of itself
And then shake the image what actually happens is
uh
Is that the game goes through a list of every object that exists in the game
Selects those objects that I decided these things shake during the screen shake effect
And then takes those actual objects and moves them
around according to
a continually varying
Uh variable well first it records their initial position
And then it takes it creates a shake object that randomly
Varies through a shake variable and then it takes every object that is considered shakeable
And then it shakes them around and moves them around their starting position
And then it like ends and then it returns them to their starting location
And then it destroys itself and then the shake is over
uh, so
Very stupid and inefficient and bad way to do that
Uh, but that's what I do
I mean, it's funny because like you play the game and it just it nothing feels wrong
It's just sort of like yeah, it's a screen shaker. It's this is a jumping thing. It doesn't feel wrong
But under under the hood it's totally wrong and it's totally fucked up and bizarre and like
you know
Somebody I for I forget who it was
Someone on the endless war dev team at some point
Like someone was looking at the the endless war code and someone DMed me to be like ben
I'm looking at the code you wrote for endless war
And it is so bad
To the point that I am convinced that it has memetic qualities
Like that's what they that's what they say
What were they referring to I don't exactly know
They I they just thought that my code was so bad and so like counterintuitive that it was like
A joke it was like I'd written it as a joke
That's what they said anyway, I don't know there. I'm sure they I'm sure it wasn't that I'm sure it was fine
um
the
But it doesn't matter if the the end result is good
It just depends on how long how much extra time you may have taken to make something happen
Yeah with a convoluted way like that. Yeah, uh
Yeah, there's probably a bunch of stuff in there that I did the hard way because I just didn't know there was an easy way to do it
Uh, but you know that's learning
Uh folks
I mean
That's video games and you know and you know what like what's like what's the alternative?
Like that I feel like maybe there's some people that might hear that and be frustrated like ah ben
Like why didn't you just like learn game design first? Like why didn't you like study?
I don't know computer science first or something and I'm like well
That would it take like
Yeah, it made the game take longer that I didn't know
The right way to do these things
But how much longer than that would it have taken for me to like become educated beforehand?
Before I could have I would have even started
Making the game. You know what I mean?
Actually, it's funny. I actually feel like
You're
You're like higher education your physics degree and your your knowledge of mathematics you already have
Probably made you think of these more convoluted ways of doing it than if you were like a real dumb dumb
Hmm
What do you mean your brain is so a bit like like my brain's so big that I it's like that episode of
Mordecai and rigby regular show where they become so smart that the nobody can understand them anymore
That's like my code
It's like if I were trying to do something I'd be like, um, I don't know one plus one
How do I figure this out? And I would look at tutorials and being like all this
I wouldn't think to do it so convolutedly
Well, I wouldn't even know how to think about that. You know, you know what?
Something like screen shake. I probably could have just googled like
screen shake effect in game maker and just seen how people
How other people figure theirs out because like there are there are there are there are things in game maker that I don't even understand like
apparently like the game
it renders
all these sprites
onto a
Quote unquote screen, right? There is a thing in the game called a screen
Which you you can basically just quote unquote shake, right?
So I probably could have just googled it and I would have found that out and it probably would have made my life easier
I just didn't think
I just thought like okay the game is the game is drawing these pixels
I have to make the pixels move
somehow well
The the the the sprites are tied to objects. Well, I guess I got to make the objects move or I got to make the objects draw their sprites
Just just the most the most intuitive way that I thought to do it was well
I got to make the objects move
I got to make the objects move to make the screen shake
Turns out game maker kind of has a built-in thing that sort of means that you don't have to do that
I I guess I was like
I did oh, I I did use a tutorial like the first thing that I did the first the very first thing that I did when I started making the game
was I looked up tutorials for how to build a like a
jrpg battle menu
and I followed tutorials from
A guy I think he was called game maker rob was the youtube channel
He had just a tutorial series about it
And I just walked through with him making a thing
It took me like three days. I think of following his tutorials to get a menu going
Which seems like I remember at the time being like oh, this has taken me so long. I just want to be done with it
Now in hindsight, it's like wow three days
Little that I know this shit would take me like 13 months
Uh
Oh, well, uh, but um
Yeah, so I I followed that tutorial and uh, it was kind of annoying
And he you know, he was building like a rpg magic menu. So it has stuff in there
He's got magic. There's a magic option
There's spells. They don't do anything but there is like
So yeah, so in the phantom's revenge code there is like, you know
No, uh annotated out code for like
A man a magic option in the uh, you know in the battle menu and whatever
Uh, that was like the foundation that I built everything else on and then every time I wanted to add a new command
I'd be like, okay. Well, let's take a command that I already have
Like duplicate it and then like whichever one is closest to what I'm envisioning duplicate it and then just you know
Make make such changes as are required to turn it into the new command that I wanted to be
um
yeah
I
I don't know I
I'm I'm I'm actually like
I know I know that it was not
I know that I didn't do everything in the most efficient way possible
But how was I but like how am I supposed to know?
What what am I supposed to do about the fact that I don't know?
What am I supposed to do about the fact that I don't know the optimal way to do everything because right?
If I wanted if I wanted to be like, oh, well, let me first. I'll learn everything about game design
I'll learn everything about programming before I start making my game and then I'll know the optimal way to do everything
And then I'll you know, and then I'll do everything as efficiently as possible. Well, sure
But then I'll how I'll never I'll never start making the game, right?
I'll just you'll get caught in that thing with like, oh, I'm I'm not ready. I'm not ready to work on this thing
I have to um that that is true. That is a potential trap. I have to prepare for it. I have to like no
I'm not ready. I have to I have to study more before I can start it. I'm not good enough
you know
I'm never worried about not being good enough
Um, because I'll never be good enough. So whatever
Yeah, that's that's the best way you could ever look at anything
It is I'll never be good enough. I'll never be good. I'll never be good enough. So you to fuck it
I know that I'll it'll suck whenever I end up doing it. So might as well suck now
Why wait suck now die later
true
uh speaking of sucking and dying and video games
Uh, I've been playing Hades this week after after the game came out
I was like, I want to play a video game
I I started playing Hades famously the reason I started playing Noita was because
Someone recommended me and my old roommate Lorenz recommended me Hades
And I went to download it and then as it was downloading I saw steam recommending me Noida
And I went and I looked at the demo for that or the the the trailer and I was like, what the fuck is this?
And I downloaded Noida and then I played that for a year and then I never played Hades Lamal
Well, but I'm playing Hades now and it's really good
It's really fucking good. Do you?
Do you know about it? I I do know about it. It's the company that made um
bastion
Yes, and uh and and transistor
Yeah, they they have that
distinct
Isometric sort of style. Yeah camera angle thing
I submit isometric camera angle and uh like strummy like folk guitar
I don't know what you'd call it
Like a sort of like uh, I don't know what you would call that style of guitar, but there's a very specific
It maybe I don't know. Um, but there's a very
particular sort of strummy guitar soundtrack they have and sometimes
Sometimes that soundtrack the Hades sounds like that and I'm like, oh, yeah, this is a super giant game
I didn't play bastion and I didn't play transistor
and I also didn't play um
Do you know about their weird like fantasy basketball game?
No, uh, it's not it's um, hold on, uh, you play basketball in an isometric perspective
It's not actually basketball. It's a
But it's like a it's like a sort of it's like a fantasy sport game
That is sort of like basketball because it involves moving a ball to a goal
um
That's all sports. Yeah, pretty much, uh, pie. It's called pyre
It's a it's about um
I watched a video about super giant games one time and that guy said that like he pyre was his favorite
It's it was not successful
Uh, it's like their worst performing game ever
Uh, because a lot of people didn't get it, but this guy really liked it
because it's like, um
It's not like in universe. It's about like a band of nomads that have been exiled from some
country, but like they're part of this like weird spiritual, uh culture and they have to do these like
Rituals and like the the the the game it's not the game is like the ritual. They're doing this like
Ritual, but it's like a competitive ritual to see like who can I don't know
Make the sacrifice first or whatever
I don't it's very weird
Yeah, pyre is their other game people don't know that one as much people don't talk about it as much as bastion and transistor
Uh, but anyway
Yeah, I haven't played any of those games
I uh, I haven't played them in either. There's something about the
camera angle that that perspective that I I
I don't like for some reason
Yeah, I know I I kind of know what you mean. There's something about it
I don't I don't know. Yeah, like it's it's objectively a good way to
Depict what they're doing for for the gameplay
You can see a lot of the the the place and you can dodge around if it was in first person
It would be maybe disorienting if it was side-scrolling then there wouldn't be a lot of depth
And uh, if it was completely top-down, I mean, it would be the same I guess
That's just something about it. There's just like unappealing visually not like because of art style
It's just that that view. I don't like it. I get it. It reminds me of like shitty gba games
For some reason that I didn't enjoy like like there was this fucking spiral game that was on Game Boy Advance
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know what you're talking about like season of ice and fire or something
It feels yeah, it felt it felt cheap a little bit
Honestly, yeah, like that. I know the exactly the spire you're talking about. I've played it. It was like a cheap knockoff
I feel yeah
It's not fair, but yeah, I also feel like something about that it kind of looks cheap
Like I never I was not impressed by what I saw of bastion
And transistor. I mean they looked fine
I'm like I got it, but I was not enticed to play them
but people told me that Hades is uh, like a
You know a rogue a rogue light
With like really like fun combat deez nuts. Hey, hey deez nuts. And so
Yeah, I was like, okay, that sounds like my kind of game. So I gave it a try and yep. It's my kind of game
Uh, it's I really appreciate
Do you know the story?
I really appreciate it. I I assume from what I've seen that it's Hades son
And he's like, I don't go fuck and Hades like um, you do have to go fuck and then he fights all the gods
Some something like that. Uh, you don't fight the gods the gods are the gods give you boons because they want to help you escape
Uh, but it's really good because um the conceit of the game
This is this is what we call ludo narrative. Uh, whatever the opposite
I've had the same thing the other day. I couldn't think of ludo narrative assonance
Synergy, whatever. Yeah, uh
When you uh, because the story of the game
The story of the protagonist and the story of the player are the same
Because you know, he too he keeps going out and trying to escape and dying and getting reborn in the pool of sticks or whatever
And he's got to try again
He you know for him it's a pardon the expression, you know
This sycophie and task of you know, just going and trying over and over and over again
And for you and that's what you the player are doing as well
You're trying over and over and over again making it a little bit further each time
Uh, very good. Very good. Uh, they really were like
Hey, why don't we make the why don't we make the story fit the gameplay and then they did
Uh, I really appreciate that
The best ludo narrative synergy is when you die in the game you die for real
You you can either yeah, there's you could either make it so that you know, the character never really dies
He just gets reborn over and over, you know, that's one way but that's for cowards. Yeah, the better way is
You die in the game
The game the game shoots you with a VR headset with a gun attached and when you die the gun goes off
Uh
Really heightens the uh
It heightens the drama
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm
That would be a black mirror episode of some sort of cheesy like
Post like future scary future scary story where it's like
Everyone was playing vr, but they didn't know there was a fucking little bomb inside and if they died in the game
The bomb would go off in the future and they couldn't take that vr helmet off for no reason
Can you believe that in the degenerate future? You know
Humanity has humanity has regressed so much. We're so we're so like dopamine star that like people are even
People are playing vr games
They they can't even get off on regular vr games anymore
Now they have to play vr games with a little bomb in the headset
That will go off and make them die if they lose. It's the only way they can feel anything anymore
Uh, it's the future
I mean it sure that'll be invented by some crazy person and then they'll stream it and everyone will be saying no
I mean at that it's like, you know, I mean people die doing uh
Doing uh, what do you call it? Uh, auto erotic?
Auto auto erotic asphyxiation
Uh, so, you know, that's like, oh, you know the little the danger is what makes it is what makes it good. So
Uh, same, you know say but for but for gameplay instead of orgasms
uh
Good good video game
Uh, I think I I I I my first my first win my first win was with the rail
Uh, the the rail gun that's uh, that's how I got my first
win although
The story the story continues even after you quote-unquote win like
Just uh winning is not enough. You have to you have to do more beyond that. So I'm still
I've been playing it for like three or four days now. Uh, it's really good
Uh, that's like other than watching my analytics. That's like all I've been doing
Uh, I deserve it. I deserve a break
Yes, yeah video game I video games are good for you actually
Uh, I was gonna say this this segue earlier when you're talking about a patch, but the there will be
Uh, I'm not sure when but definitely like within the next few days as of recording a patch for pumpkin alley
Oh
Did you already do a patch that like changed the uh the falling thing?
No, no, we that was the patch I was talking about we were making and um,
It's not out yet because we there was a there was a complication with some people on some computers
max
Couldn't open the photo album from the menu and some people in different countries had like
Uh, the the the tutorial signs like not work with the text
It's there's a there's a bit of like
Fixing of a very specific little bugs
Um, but we it's very close to being
Done, uh, there's also
A new lizard
In this new no fucking way
There's a new lizard. Oh, and um
There's a bunch of changes to like the speed of characters and a bit of jumping tweaks and
It's a lot of little things. So it's not like it's not gonna be like
We're not gonna continue making patches over and over again
This is just gonna be this one time because there was a bunch of like kind of important bugs
And we thought we may as well like tidy up some stuff
While we were doing it and then this is this is the this is the pumpkin patch. We're calling it
Huh, and then that's great
and then later
We'll be the next patch will be the
Fucking finished game or however we we want to to do that
We might have an alpha for like kickstarter back as if we make a a
A kickstarter for to to fund it
You mean we're looking into that at the moment, but yeah the alpha
Uh, what are you gonna do for the for the alpha version?
What do you mean?
You you said you're gonna do a patch and then you're gonna do one more update and that's gonna be the alpha version
No, the no no no the the patch. This is just for the demo. We're talking about the hotfix for the demo
Yeah, and then when we make the full game
Oh, right
That's the next time you'll see any of new stuff. Okay. Okay. Okay. Um, yeah, it makes sense
Uh, so
So if you have played the demo already, there is reason for you to play the new one because of the new lizard
Uh, yeah, I wanted to yeah, I watched I watched keyblade spirit
stream the
Herself playing the demo and she found lizards that I had not even heard of before
I didn't know about the white lizard. That's exciting
Yeah, so I still have not found
The red one and the white one and I think maybe one other one or maybe it was just those two
And then I guess there's another one now that I'll have to hunt down
Uh
Pretty pretty cool. I like those
I call them surprise lizards because they make the little they make what sounds to me like the little alert noise from
Metal gear solid
There's something like that
Oh
I was gonna mention, uh, yeah for the the phantom's revenge patch the patch notes. Here's here's what I did
Uh
Yeah, so the squirt gun damage, uh, I didn't change the damage that they actually dealt. I just changed the number
Well, well, I fixed the code so that
It's it it intentionally deals the 768 and then I changed the number. So it actually says like, okay, this is how much it actually deals
um, there was a mistake in the
Virginia's sprite not in her normal sprite, but when she was sad in the chambers where she's sad
Uh, her tail had like a visual error in it where like
The impression of her like wings sort of like was taking like a chunk out of her tail
It was kind of hard to see but if you watched it, you could you could see it. It looked a little yeah, I mentioned that
Yeah, that's right. You did. Um, yeah. Yeah, I forgot it was you
Uh, uh, so I fixed that that's fixed. Um, I I made it so that the end screen displays
the end screen used to display your, uh
What was it your your time to beat your slime coin your
Uh, your virginia's status your horn status
Uh, probably maybe one I forget. Anyway added it now displays your final level and your final, uh, weapon skill or your weapon mastery level
because um
You know, it's there's since there's different routes, right since you can take a leveling route or uh
Or an anointing route. I thought it would be good to show like, okay. What's your final level?
What's your final
Anoint status so you can be like, oh, that's how you want. Okay, because those are those are relevant. Those are worth
knowing about
Um, and then oh, I changed it. You said this as well
You thought it was a mistake that uh, the final boss when you when you exclamation point data on the final boss
It shows her max hp, but it doesn't show
Her it doesn't update when you damage her. Yeah, that was not a mistake. I was just lazy
Uh, but I fixed that so now now it displays
Her her current hp as a fraction of her
Total hp so it says like, you know 2000 20 000 out of you know, 3000 32
um
The inner lad spoilers that number
Uh, don't worry about it
Uh the um
The inner lab music before I had forgotten to fix the inner lab music to loop
So if you if you played it long enough
The inner this is when you get past the the spoiler battle
Uh, and you get into the inner area
Before it just it would fade out and then start again. I changed it so that it loops now
Uh
And then I added to to the to the marriage animation
I added a little thing where the word skill up pops up twice
Uh, when phantom when phantom kisses uh platinum
His little heart comes little green heart comes out and then it goes bling and then it turns into a little double skill up
Because I thought oh, yeah
Because I thought there was a pretty significant chance that people wouldn't realize that marriage actually increases your weapon skill
So I added that to be just to make it crystal clear like this this is increasing your weapon skill
I thought it was it was just like a funny like cutscene. No, no, it's uh, it's it
It's too it. Well, yeah in endless war getting married
Uh boosts your weapon skill by two but means that you can't switch your weapon at will
Uh, so I mean phantom only has the one weapon so he doesn't need to switch
But uh, yeah, it it boosts your weapon skill. You can I think you can anoint
I think you can anoint
Four times before it stops increase you can keep anointing
But it just doesn't increase your weapon skill any further after a while
And then I think beyond you can then you can marry and I think that will boost your
That will boost your skill
Too higher than that
You can if you anoint twice
You can that's when you can get married
And then you could if you wanted to anoint up to four times before it stops being helpful
And then at whatever point you get married
Boost your weapon skill to above whatever you were at when you marry. So you could
Get as high as low as weapon mastery eight if you anoint four times
And then marry I think I think
Does that increase the slime it takes to attack or is that just your level? No, uh weapon mastery
Does not increase the cost to attack only leveling increases the cost to attack
The that's that's and that's that's the truth
Uh, so it doesn't it doesn't really matter whether you
Leveling it matters when you do it anointing it does not and marriage it does not matter when you do it
It doesn't it doesn't cost you more to do it earlier
Uh, and then oh, yeah, the last thing was I had a patron a patron's name was just in there twice for some reason
So I just took that out. So now it's only in there once
And those are all the patch notes
It took me like it just took me like a couple hours to do all these things was really easy
Uh, but now the game is perfect
Damn
Oh, oh, oh wait one more thing one more thing I have to say about this is it was really funny
So the way that you finish the comic is by beating the game
And then when you beat the game you get the link to the end of the comic, right?
Yes, well, I made two different versions of the ending where
Uh one where phantom has his horn and the other where he does not
Uh, you know, because I was like, well, what if you if you beat the game with your horn, you know
You want to you would want phantom to have his horn in the final scene? Yeah. Yeah
Well, it turns out you can never get the horn ending. It is impossible to finish the game
And get the the link to the horned version
Really? Yes, because I I didn't
the the
If you if you play the game optimally
You can you can keep virginia from taking a hit
uh, if you
You you can't you can't prevent phantom from
Well, no, you you can't prevent phantom from
Taking from losing his from losing his horn in the same way. I'm not gonna say I won't spoil why but the point is it doesn't work
Uh, uh, you you you can okay. You can win with the horn, but you
You get the bad ending so you don't get the oh, yeah, so you don't get the link
So yeah, you the only way to win
Uh with the horn means that the game doesn't let you doesn't give you the link to the final page
So that no one will ever see yeah
It's there. I guess you you would have to um
You have to heck the game you would have to well you would have to guess the url
You would if you got the the actual ending you could maybe try like changing the url
And maybe you could find the horn version if you really wanted to does that mean one of them is like more canon than the other
In my I already considered the horn the hornless version to be more canon
Because I was like well, I mean nobody's gonna
I I had I had forgotten I had actually forgotten
Uh, I had I was thinking for a minute that if you played it perfectly you ended with your horn intact and
Virginia unharmed that is that is wrong. You you can't do that
But you don't you just don't have enough slime
uh
So I was thinking
Yeah, you can do it, but like no one's gonna do it on their first
Playthrough and it makes more
You know and you know people are gonna lose their horn on their first win
You know of course and honestly it makes a little bit it's a little bit more thematic if like you know if phantom has taken
damage by the end of his
quest for for revenge
It's also like a cool cutscene like if this was part of the comic
Yeah, that would happen that would just be like a cool thing to happen
Yeah, so even even so the the hornless ending was more canon in my head
Although I thought if you get the hornless version that's canon too. You deserve it
Uh, but turns out no
It's not because it's impossible
I just uh, it's a different timeline thought that was thought that was pretty funny
uh, you can um
The bad the the actual bad ending though is not canon as endless war will let you know if you try to continue on
after getting it
Someone in my patron discord was like
Oh, the link's not working the link's not working and I
Smugly I was like, hey, you know what you did you deserve this
But it turned out no just like their their internet browser was just like not responding
So I was like, oh no
Oops, you know what you did. You know you didn't get uh google fiber. You didn't you didn't update chrome
new monster
Yeah
uh
LeMau
Whoo, so yeah, it's the the weakest felt really long
Uh, yeah, it hasn't it felt like a long time ago that the game came out
Your game came out it really did
Like I I released it that day and then like by the time it was like the end of the day
I was going to bed. I was like, it's only been one day
The game's only been out for one day. It felt like an entire week had gone by
was it uh, was it
Was it lenin that said uh, there are
There are decades where nothing happens and there are weeks where decades happen or something like that or stallin
one of those guys
One of my heroes
It sounds like yeah, this sort of thing. Yeah that a smart person would say
True
So a capitalist would never have said that they would never have figured that out dogs
um
Yeah, I guess uh, that's that's uh
That's what's been going on with phantoms or revenge
I'm glad the game's done, but now I don't know what to do with myself. So I've just been playing hades
and that's well
I mean, you did say you were gonna like work on biscuit page is the next thing. Oh, sure. Yeah
There's always like a list of of like projects to get round to it's just that
You've spent so long
Building up momentum and like
For this one project now that you've stopped you take a break and then it's like
Um, well now I've got to do another thing. Oh, no, you're you're at a standstill
You've got to like build up the momentum momentum again for a different thing
Actually, I lied what I have I have spent some time
Doing stuff related to the book
Uh, like I've been all right
I've been I've been in touch with printers like getting quotes from different printers and like finding out like who's gonna give me the best price
Uh, and I've been like setting up, uh, you know
The the image files that I will eventually use for the uh
it turns like a
I kind of put that aside for a bit because I need to deter I need to determine which printer I'm going with
First so that I know what dimensions to use and then I can do the like, you know
Set up set up the pages to be the correct, uh
Uh, yeah dimensions and whatever I it's looking like mix-im is going to be the the cheapest option
Cheap cheapest and has like the most um the most uh like options. I think
I just wish they'd send me the goddamn sample pack
I just still haven't they won't no they won't do it. Uh, oh, oh they said um
Um
Yeah, they did I did I tell you this already? They said uh
They initially told me that they wouldn't do it because there was a software issue
Like their website was just like not working and I asked them like
Well, can you just send it to me?
And they replied and basically they were just like no
I just won't they were they were like, uh, hold on. What did they say? They said something stupid
Um, we hate people from Boston
Okay, they they said unfortunately due to the global paper shortage
We are not offering sample packs at this time to anyone. So I guess they just aren't doing sample packs at all
Oh
So that's unfortunate. It is unfortunate and it makes me wonder like wait
Am I like getting am I getting like a bad price to print right now like is printing right now bad
Because paper shortage
I don't I haven't heard of a paper shortage. I would imagine something something covet would have done something somewhere
I don't I don't know maybe
That that's what they said unfortunately due to the global paper shortage
um
Maybe I mean it's just it's just like
I just need to know like I would like to see like the difference between like 80 pound paper and 100 pound paper
I could probably get that somewhere else
If I'm not the only people that could give me something like that
um
But anyway mixem seems to offer the
I'll probably have to just bite the bullet and spend like 60 dollars or 70 dollars ordering like a test copy
Yeah
Uh, but I don't they seem to be I
I contacted another local printer in boston. This one was called alpha graphics and they too
They were quoting me like like 30 or like 25 30 dollars a copy
Like what is like what is the point of view?
What what are you doing?
I don't know. I I don't know if it's their fault. Maybe it's the global paper shortage or whatever
But it's just it's just an unacceptable price point like I'm aghast like I'm aghast that they would show me that
And like not be shamed of themselves. I don't know. Oh, I'm looking it up
Paper prices have gone up a little more than 25 percent since january 2021
and
And because and because they're up 25 they can't offer sample packs anymore
25 well, there's
I mean there's more to it like they say the paper mills reduce their workforce during the turmoil of 2020
Many mills transitioned into making boxes for example for amazon versus making paper for direct mail pieces
I guess since paper
They have the power to make boxes and there's more demand for those. I don't know
Okay types and paper grades would discontinued. They don't elaborate on why
Okay, there's probably lots to learn about that. That's weird. But are but are you telling me?
right, but are you telling me
that
No, they can't no due to the paper shortage. They can't send a paper sample pack
But they can
just
print
A thousand copies of my book if I want them to
Well, yeah, because you're paying for it
Okay, but
Okay, but 25 isn't that much and I need and I want the fucking sample
I don't know man. I just
Seems stupid. They say they say 25 since january 2021. It probably has gone up
Uh like since 2020
I'm just looking at a blog about it
I uh, maybe
I just
Well, and that makes me nervous because like gosh like what if I'm
What if I'm paying like what if it's going to be like too costly to get my book made now? What if
I don't know. I mean I I would have been caught in like the heightened paper thing as well
It was still it was I mean it was still like within what I thought it would be
Yeah, although I did I did like order. I did look into it start looking into it in the middle of 2020
I think what if when the hell did I do the lord ghosts?
I don't uh
The paper was already expensive I guess is the point
The I wonder I mean that makes me nervous like geez like
If I wait till next year to do the book will that like
Increase will that like lower the costs?
I don't I don't want to wait until next year
But like I don't know
If if it would make the production cost like 50 lower or something I might consider it
But it probably I mean it probably wouldn't be that dramatic a difference, but like
It would be really sad if like just across the board like paper becomes more expensive because so much is
digitized
That you don't need paper so much and then like making comics is way more difficult
Physically it would be difficult. I mean it would be sad just just because it would be a sad thing
But it would also be sad for me in particular just because
you know
selling selling books selling the books has been like
a pretty it's been pretty good in terms of like return on investment like it's always been
moderately successful so that would be like
kind of a kind of a
bummer for that for me
I don't know
I was anticipating
I mean the vapors to Kickstarter did pretty well
I was anticipating that slime and punishment might do even bigger numbers
Which would be very exciting
uh
But
I don't know
Everything is bad
Like I looked at I looked at kablam again
You know kablam is where I printed vapors and it it didn't seem like the prices there were like significantly different than they were in the past
So, you know what? I think they're just making it up. I think much like covid itself the uh
The paper shortage is probably a hoax
You know what I mean? Yeah, I mean paper does grow on trees. It literally does trees everywhere
What are we even fucking talking about? You know, this is bullshit. It's it's all it's all
liberal media something something
um
Oh man, wait
This is totally off topic, but speaking of the liberal media, uh, do you see that the may is having her kid?
Uh, why would that be liberal media? Why would you tell me about this? Because the kill stream because the kill stream hates the
The kill stream is bravely standing against the tyranny and the scourge of the liberal why would you
Think that I would ever want to know about any of that
I don't know because I you like to keep abreast of the of the current state
of the world
That's not the world
It is
It's it's it's the most important thing we could be talking about right now
Well, I hope the baby is okay. I hope yeah
Yeah in the long term in the short term and the long term really
Really hoping really hoping things don't work out the way they probably will work out for that kid
Uh
Yeah, um
Good luck
child
Good luck child good luck child
What can I what else can I say?
um
Uh, yeah, I think I think she's like given birth like like did like this week or something like like one minute ago
I think I heard that like her water broke or something like her water. Why did you hear about people?
People were talking about it in my in my discord server somebody somebody said somebody said that like
Her water was breaking and she said like uh, Ethan. No, no, no, we don't have to go to the hospital
Just now finish your stream finish your stream or whatever
Uh, that's what I heard. I don't I don't know um
But uh, yeah supposedly I don't know so that's bad and I don't like it. Um
But uh, you know
Easy come easy go
Whatever that means
What does that mean in this context? I have no idea. Don't worry about it. Um
Damn, well, that's all what else. I don't know. Uh, I don't have any I don't have any notes this week
Speaking just briefly on the lord of ghosts at Kickstarter reward stuff
I have labels now, but I have been holding off using them because I found this company
Called a black box a black box dot cool
Apparently they are a Kickstarter backer
Like reward assist program. Yeah, you tell them what you need to send
And uh, where you live and you know, you're a Kickstarter link, please and then they'll give you a quote for
Handling all of the shipping to all over the place
And I'm like that sounds so helpful. I would love to do that
This service sounds like I'm its demographic
It sure does so they're gonna send me a quote
tomorrow at the latest
Um on monday and I'll I'll if the quote is like reasonable
I'll be using them
if not, then I'll be I'll be printing out labels on label paper and
and
Going insane for a few weeks, but either way, uh, I have all the pieces
You know, so it's it's not gonna take too much longer
Let me know how that goes because I mean if they're if they're a good service and their price
Point is reasonable. I mean, that's the kind of thing I might make use of in the future
Yeah
they they say they they um
A lot of kick starters are like for creative things. They they work with like board game people like uh, oh, yeah
People who make board games on Kickstarter and it's like difficult to send stuff around
Oh, yeah, and so they they made that service because they understand that artists are not smart
And then they don't know how to do it. That's right. That's true
um, I um
Damn
Wish I uh
I wish
Making I wish that making the book were not hard
I actually have a I have a lot to do
For you would you would think that like formatting the pages of a book would just be like, uh, open up like a
Open up like a photoshop document. Uh, you know make a square center it. Uh done
Uh, not not really there's like
I kind of I kind of got to go through like I'll have like a standard layout
And then but then like I kind of got to go through every individual page and like like because because they're not all quite
Some of them are like four most of them are four images. Some of them will be three or two
I kind of got to like customize each one or most of them or a lot of them to a certain extent
And then I have to write I have to write the index section
I'm actually gonna I don't even know what it's it's going to be
I don't know how long it's going to be but I feel like there's going to be a lot to say
In the index section. It's going to be a lot of words
It's going to probably increase these page count
significantly
It's probably use like a moderately small font just to avoid it being like a big like additional print cost
Uh, but anyway, there's a lot a lot to do with that
I think the the reason the the author notes in the homestuck books and the problem sleuth books are at the bottom
Is to save on
like an index
Yeah, because because the the like the page is the same like shape as the panels in homestuck
but like
There's no very rarely. Do they actually fill the entire page with one of the panels?
They'll have like
Because they have all text underneath them
They have like terezi do
The do the thing and then it's like they have the text with the image above it
And they have like maybe three panels per page with their texts
And if there's a pestilog that takes up and it's like
With that there's a lot of space to have author notes at the bottom without like
Compromising too much on like
Showing the pages in full. That's true
That's true actually and you know, I you know, I pulled out my problem sleuth
Uh book to like look at the layout
And yeah, I did notice that a lot of it is there is a lot of blank space
At the bottom of of many pages
Like the the images are all they're definitely there's like set towards the top and there's blank space at the bottom four
You know, it's potentially there could be text there and then at the very bottom. There's the
There's the running commentary
I I don't know. I kind of like the idea of like a dedicated index section though. I think I just
It
Yeah, damn it. Okay. Now I'm in a conundrum because on the one hand
um, yeah, my the four images like like the
The the the the the aspect ratio of the images
Most most even landscape oriented book layouts
They're not long enough. They generally they do will have some wasted vertical space. It's almost unavoidable
uh
So then I'm I'm I'm left with the choice of either I waste that space
or I
I could do a running commentary page by page and then that space would be used
Or you know, if I do if I do in the back of the book, there might be some some waste which is unfortunate
so
so like, um, you've got
You've got the four
For most tweets. There's four images the same size. Yeah
Uh
And like putting all four of those like with their sides touching
In a grid on one page would be too
Like would make the pages too wide or uh, no, well, here. Well, here's like a
I was working on it the other day. Here's what I was kind of
Um, hold on. I gotta I gotta post a
Here's what I was kind of like mocking up
Like, uh
this is
This is this is including like a bleed
So, I mean, this isn't even you know what this isn't even that bad actually like yeah, there's a little bit of space at the bottom
But it's not even it's not even that bad
You know what I was like futzing with it the other day and thinking like oh, there's extra space. Oh, I hate this wasted space
But like this is fine
Is is the white like the bleed area? No
Oh, sorry. No the white on the outside is like ignore it
That's just the photoshop file you're working in. Yeah, no the the black the black is the page
Or here, um, let me uh
here
there
Yeah, yeah
The corner ignore the red in the corner. That's irrelevant
Uh, so they would be
Some yeah, this something like for text if you got something to say or no, no, no, I think I think this is
I don't shit is this post because I because I got the template from mixam
No, wait, uh, this is uh
I'm not sure if this includes the bleed or not whatever this is whatever something something like this, you know
So, yeah, there there would be there. Okay, there would be some space for a commentary at the bottom
There might be a few
There might be a few cases where
I would want to write like a substantial amount that maybe I would want more than just the bottom
Uh margin for I guess in those cases I could make a little asterisk and have a little like
index section at the back
but on the other hand, I kind of just like the idea of having it of it being a
Uh an infinite jest style back of the book index section. I just kind of think that's funny
Yeah, I mean, whatever you feel like. Yeah
I I remembered that I was at one point thinking of making like a bell jpebook
And I started like laying out
some pages
Yeah, just sort of like this sort of thing. I like that
Would it be would it be square pages?
Yeah, the square pages would be pretty square. Yeah. Um, just because
Actually, I don't know why I think it was just because the problem sleuth books were square and I liked that
The problem sleuth books, they're not they're not quite square. They're like, um, they're like a little bit less
They're like a little bit more than square. They're like eight by eight and a half or so. I measured I measured mine
Uh because uh, you know
I was I was looking at this at this stuff
Uh, okay
I've got my
I still don't know whether I would want to make a bell jpebook
It's it's like a fun idea of a project
but it's still like bell jpe is
maybe not like
The thing people would really want
I don't know
How many how many would it be a lot of pages?
I think it would be a lot of pages. Oh, how don't I think I may like
I got up to
page
What's this page 35 of the book would be where tiki is introduced
I didn't I didn't finish doing that one. Let me page 34
I think it would be like maybe a hundred two hundred pages
um
200 yeah
Slime and well, I slime and punishment is gonna be like a hundred and
180 or something a hundred and seventy hundred and eighty and that that's not including the index
Hey, see I can't remember whether I'm that number is referring to like the number of panels I have
um
Because obviously I can fit multiple panels on a single page. Yeah, and uh, some panels are less important than others
If they're like like just sort of moving from one point to another. I like I like this like alternating a left and right
Thing you got going on here
Yeah, I think it's pretty good. It's pretty good
I feel like it would be a cool project once I don't have um
I don't know more pressing projects
Happening. Hmm. Yeah
I could have like give and take dot say and you can buy the bell j-book. I wouldn't I probably wouldn't do a kickstarter for it
Uh, or would I I don't know in a in a in a in a bit that I'm gonna rip off from the lord of ghosts kickstarter
What the hell did it it's not showing it whatever this this image. I just posted is uh, it's it shows the the bleed
It shows it with the bleed and like uh, it's kind of it's kind of narrow on the edges
I I really don't like how it's like coming coming coming close to the edge
But it's got like a more substantial margin at the top. I don't like that
There's more space on the right because this is like a left page. So, you know, there's more space in the middle towards the spine
Um, it'd be reversed for a right hand page
Ah, there's just a lot
There's a lot of lot to fuck with there's a lot to fuck with in terms of uh, so
What are you what are you copying from from lord of ghosts? Oh, right? Um, I'm gonna do a when I kickstart that I'll do a, uh
stretch goal zine
and the zine will be, uh
Nuts the beginning. Do you know what that is?
I
Yes, the like timeline conversions or like it's split whether or not you have the salted cashews or the unsalted
The salted almonds are the unsalted cashews. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, uh, or well
Uh, I mean, there is the there is the the secret brazil nut ending, but uh, we shouldn't talk about that
So, yeah, I'll do that as like a little uh
choose your own adventure, uh
probably like staple bound, uh
Zine it'll be like 13 pages
Uh, no, no, I'll probably be a little longer than that
Maybe like 20 something because it's all all these multiple versions. Uh
How many pages is the red man zine by the way?
That's about a hundred pages. It's a that's big for a zine
That is big for it's got like a flat like it's perfect bound. It's not like stapled
Oh, that's a lot more. That's not even a zine. That's not even a zine. You can't call a zine if it's perfect bound. That's a book
Uh, uh-oh
I got caught
That's a book my friends
Dang it. Now people will know I made a book
Fuck you fool. Um, I'm very disappointed. I want my money back
Uh, okay, thanks, but you won't get your red man. Oh wait. Oh
Oh, well, well, no, never mind then. No, actually
No, I want I want well, I want the money back
But I want to still have the thing that I paid for
Can we can we arrange something like that perhaps?
Uh, sure, I'll send it to you and then you complain and then I'll capitulate instantly. Okay. Okay. Good. I receive red man comic
You receive no money from me
Uh
We can make this work. I think
Um, you I receive red man comic you receive less than what we agreed upon
Hmm. Hmm. You you drive a hard bargain there
Uh, yeah
So let's uh, let's see
What uh, what else what else? Um, like I said, I have no notes this week. Um
I did nothing of note besides release the game and play Hades
uh
Well, you deserve it. Thanks
Anything I've been doing is um
Is waiting for
Well, at first I found out about like the
The the black box company and now I'm just been I've just been waiting for them to get back to me with the quote
Oh
So I've been playing uh animal crossing
Pocket camp. I think I talked about that before you mentioned it. Yeah
That's been fun. I have animals
I got Marshall. I got Raymond. Oh my god. Uh
The best ones
Yeah, I found all the best ones
Um, I think there's that new one new ish one
Uh, what's his name?
Bunny boy like turquoise
Femboy bunny that was like ha ha. It's so feminine for a boy bunny
I don't remember that one
It's a new one new with the
Switch game. I think
But that's a possible. I can I can find that one and and add it to my my campsite
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Good. Good
And uh, yeah, it's just that's just a fun game
Uh, is it you said it's different from
New horizons
Yeah, I mean there's a lot there's obviously less you can do on a mobile device
But like I haven't played the animal crossings. I've just seen people play it
seems to be just
Good like you go around and you shake trees to get at things you catch bugs you catch fish
You give those things to the animals as little gift bags and they're like wow, thanks
And then they give you crafting resources
With which you make furniture
To furnish your campsite. Mm-hmm. And then if you have the right furniture animals
Who like that furniture can be invited to be at your camp. Very nice
Very nice
Uh
And and like that that loop has not gotten tiring or tedious yet
This is uh surprisingly
And it's just it's a good one. It's a good mobile game. I like that. I like that they did that the
The the Hades loop has not gotten tedious for me
Although I was very
I was really mad. I was really mad. Let me tell you
When I realized
I had thought that diamonds I had thought I figured out that oh diamonds are just for like
They're just for like extra shit. They're just for like, you know, bullshit cosmetic stuff
So I bought a song. I bought like a soundtrack song for one diamond
And then a day later
I realized like, oh my god, I've earned all the diamonds I can like get easily
And I'm one diamond short
of unlocking arabus gates
And I fucking wasted my fucking diamond on a stupid soundtrack
I'm fucking gonna kill everyone. Yeah, you can yeah, you can buy like in-game music that plays at the music stand in the
Like courtyard or whatever
Right
And you get diamonds you get diamonds by slaying the lernian bone hydra, which is the boss of the second area
Well, you get a you get them in a couple ways, but the easiest way to get them is by slaying the hydra
With each weapon you get a one diamond for doing it with that weapon and you get one for doing it at different heat levels
which is uh
Sort of a difficulty setting you can like turn up for yourself if you want more rewards
So I had completed I had gotten all the diamonds that I could get that way
And then I was like, ah, fuck
I'm short of a an upgrade that would add like a new like sort of type of room to the dungeon
Uh, I ended up getting I had to like trade some shit
I had to like gather up some other crap and trade one for a diamond
And then I got the extra one and I got the I unlocked the room
But I was mad for a minute. I was like, oh, I wish I hadn't spent that diamond on that song
Oh, well
Uh, you got tricked. I I
It was bad conveyance. It was bad conveyance
They didn't they didn't signpost clearly enough that this thing that I had to slay the hydra to obtain was valuable and I should care about it
Uh
There was okay, we I just thought of one more thing one more thing. Um, I was talking
to Nate
about
Radcon funds
and I
I think I'm I'm I'm I think I'm taking over. I think I'm taking over a
PCP
Like accounting duties from him. He is handing them off to me soon
and also
Uh, we were talking about
The expenses that I have incurred while doing stuff like getting road to radcon done
And doing the dojin
And other such things and we went over the expenses
And uh, I think I'm gonna get paid. I'm gonna get that money that I spent
This is money that I already spent that I spent my own money that was PCP money
So I'm just getting reimbursed for that
and then
we talked again about the uh, the brad garlinghouse diss track music video
and the ova
And we once again and we once again Nate said
I'm gonna say I'm just gonna say it. I'm just gonna say it Nate said to me. Okay, Ben
I I'm gonna set a deadline for myself. I will have the
uh
Music video done
He said next friday
So that will be the friday after this episode
Or that will be a week from the day this episode comes out
So the day the episode after this comes out
Nate said he would and he told me he would have the brad garlinghouse diss track music video
These are his words. These are his words
Uh, all right, and now and now okay. I can't guarantee he didn't say that it would be published
He said it would be done
So he might
It might be the case that he has he hasn't finished then and then maybe we publish it like the next day or something
Um, so if it's not posted when this comes out, it's not quite time to
Call him out on shenanigans, but uh soon
Soon thereafter shortly thereafter
uh
I asked him
Do you do you care if like we talk if talk a little bit about like money funds?
um, I mean sure is
part of the
The thing I was concerned. I because I I had not seen like the money
Like he's just sort of kept it in escrow or whatever for this whole time
Uh, and I was concerned like
damn, what if we like spent it all and um
Like like what if it's what if it's all been spent and it's gone and we're not getting
And there's not going to be any money to pay us out by the time it's it's done. Turns out no
That's not the case
Nate said that like even after everything there's like
$15,000 just there just sitting
To be to be dispersed as soon as as soon as he is done
Well as soon as he's done with those videos and uh, and I get uh
Kaiju to finish the damn the damn dojin
Yes, Kaiju. It's not Kaiju's fault Kaiju said he would work on it as soon as he has time, but he has been
He has been busy with uh, his editing work for totally not mark, which he told me was going to be the case so
It's uh, it's uh, I I accepted that
Because I don't know he he said
He said I should consider finding someone else if I want it done sooner
And I was like, okay, I'll think about it
But other than like I genuinely don't know who else I would ask because I I really feel like his style is a pretty good fit for
uh eds stuff because I want to use what ed got done and uh
So like
That's good
And like I don't I don't know any other I have like I don't know I have not found any other artists who would be like
Oh, yeah, I could get that guy to do it and that would look fine
Like I just have I don't like maybe there's someone out there, but I don't I don't
I don't know I don't haven't seen him
I
Anyway, those are the I mean those are the things that have to get done before we get that money
We'll get like a few thousand bucks a piece. It'll be pretty sick
Yeah, and then finally
um
And finally the curse of radcon 4 will be lifted finally. Yeah, yeah the curse
God
It's been
So long that I can't even remember
Yeah
what like
If I have been reimbursed for anything or or not
Well, Nate has it all gotta go Nate has it all in records
Apparently he told me I had thought that I had been reimbursed for like my uh, not my travel expenses
But like my expenses while there like, you know food food and stuff
Uh, apparently I was not like
He he told me like now I have it I have it down here on the
Spreadsheet that like now you you listed like 400 dollars worth of expenses that have not been reimbursed. I'm like, yes
Fuck yeah
I'd have to really go back and
check
Wait, well if you if you already told him if you already reported him then like well, that's the thing
I don't I don't even remember if I reported
Everything well if you didn't I I feel like I I feel like I I like put
like
uh receipts
Somewhere, uh, yeah, I did I was meeting I kept all my receipts from the trip and then I posted screenshots of them
for him in the all business
uh
channel
And that's and I just did that and like that's that's all I had
Yeah, I guess the main thing I would want is like my plane ticket because I was part of the the Kickstarter
Yes, the pay for travel probably. Yeah, probably that 400 includes my plane tickets
And probably yours as well need to be paid out
along with everything else
Oh, yeah, that would have been big for you
because of a international flight and all
Yeah, did you not did you know over though? Did you not get uh?
Did you not get that covered?
Um, I don't remember it's been so many years
It's been two years multiple years
Or
wait
I mean red con 2 would have been it would have been around this time of year right like late march
I think on 2 or sorry red con 4
It would it would have now. Yeah, it was it was march. It was pre. It was just on the cusp of covid
So we're probably scary. No, so we're probably in like
Yeah, this this we were like right around the second anniversary or something like that. Oh
Yeah, it's so weird. How weird is it?
Like what watching the uh the red con 2 documentary and being like red con 1 and 2 were like four months apart
So bizarre
Yeah, well
Yeah, well things change. Yeah, well, that's life. That's life. I don't want to say about it. Yeah, I mean sure
Uh
I don't know that's all I got
That's all I got this week. Um
Oh, have you been reading one piece?
No
You're gonna get caught up. It's very good fame famously. I do not read one piece
Uh, I should watch it. I read it
I yeah, you know, you know what, uh, there's a there's a lot of things that I have been putting off doing and being like
Nah, I'll do it after the game's done. Well
Now the game's done. So maybe reading one piece
Should be one of those things that I do
Uh
Yeah, I should get caught up
I know I've been saying that and saying that and saying that but I really mean it this time
I really mean it. I'm downloading
Uh
Voice mails by the way, I don't know if we're gonna do them right yet, but I feel like we're getting
Closer to that time
I mean at the moment
Like all the things that are going on in my life that are major
I've already mentioned. Mm-hmm
And I'm mostly just sort of like enjoying the fact that it's getting a bit warmer. Yeah, and uh
Oh, there's there's a bumblebee every so often in that nice sunlight. That's good. Yeah, I went to the
I went to the post office the other day
I had like legitimately not been out of my house and like probably more than a week
Like I had not stepped outside
And I was shocked to see that. Oh, it's uh, it's warm now
That's weird
That's pretty cool. I guess
But I feel I have gone um
I have gone with the kids these days are calling goblin mode
I feel like they calling it that. Yeah, I feel like a monster
I feel like a devil who doesn't belong in society anymore. I feel like a wretched little
little uh
Little hand-wringing thing scurrying about I don't want anyone to see me
Uh, that's that's like you're like those little little bugs in in uh
Oh, no, not little little bugs the little scrabbly guys in blood boron you kill them you get little blood. Oh, it's the little tight night. Uh
Tight night equivalents. Dark souls tight night scarabs or whatever they're called. Yeah. Yeah
Exactly. Yes, exactly like that. Exactly. Um
You have great like powerful loot
It feels and everyone's trying to try and gonna try and squash you for it
Feels bad. I feel like I look terrible
Uh, I don't know what to do about it
Uh, just look good. Duh. Yeah easy. Yeah, you know what?
You're inspiring an inspired an inspiring message of hope
Uh for today's youth. Just get good. I Ie me
Yeah
You know what?
Never thought about it like that
And I never will
But anyway, the point was it was very warm out. It was like all of a sudden it was 70 degrees and I'm like, well
Damn, I guess, uh
I guess my excuse for uh
I'm running out of excuses to never leave my house. Uh
COVID's like
Nobody nobody cares about COVID anymore
Uh, it's not it's not even winter now. It's warm. So like fuck
I gotta go to a local park and pet a dog. Jesus christ. Don't don't
Don't fucking say such things
Uh
Do you have like a local park near
A local park
I mean there
There there is one that I there's one kind of I know there is one kind of near a sort of uh
Street crossing like square nearby
Uh, but it's sort of off the road and I have not actually gone to it
Long story short, there are parks. I just have not I have not really seen any of them
I guess I moved in
I don't I don't go to parks. Do you go to parks?
Yeah, I love going to parks
I I would never think I would never think to go to a park
It's just sort of um, you know, you go outside, but you're far away as far away as possible from traffic sounds
and
You know sometimes there's nice grass sometimes there's a lake to look at I don't look at like ducks and stuff
I don't know if there are any parks
Around where I live that are big enough that you would be like away from traffic sounds
Yeah, I mean, I guess it depends if if you're in like a big city or
Or a place where the parks are small
like
even just
Surrounding yourself with tall things that are not like made of concrete and instead are made of wood and they're trees
I mean, I go to the I go to the Boston Commons sometimes
Uh for various reasons. That's that's a park. It's not huge, but it's it's probably it's the biggest park
around I think
It's probably a bigger is that the place with
Uh
Wait, was that the place?
I think I went there. I think you probably did and we probably and we probably played pokemon go. Yeah, I think you did
Go there and and and another time
I think you and
Munchy did like a
Like a with rfck con or something with signs. Yes. Yes the slime. I remember watching a stream
Walking around a big green area slime war slime slime war now slime war now
Uh, yeah, that was in the common
Uh, it was also it was also the place where I went to uh, so you see andrew yang
Give us a beat when he was running for president
Uh
It was where we went for the when it was cold for that time you were here. Yeah, so you yeah, that's the common
I go there once in a while
um
Just for various uh reasons
I gotta go
Um, I actually after this is over. I gotta go to the
I've been meaning to go back to medford. I moved so my old
PO box is in medford
Which is kind of annoying to get to it was probably like 45 minutes to get there. I gotta go by bus
And I gotta I gotta check my po box because I'm sure that some packages have probably been returned to sender and are sitting in
My po box and need to get them
Uh
And uh, but I don't want to uh, it's annoying
So but I I'll probably do that today actually because I gotta go out to summerville for some other shit
um
I guess it's the first day of spring. It's march 20th
It's also my sister's birthday. So I should call her the sister who famously said you're a dog. You're a dog and I'm sick of it
Uh, it's her birthday today. I should give her a call after this
Hmm. Anyway, I'm just rambling now. What am I talking about?
Uh, nothing nothing nothing
Shall we go to voicemail? Yeah, let's go to voicemail
Oh
Oh, man, I made I made two ingredient cookies yesterday
Shit was so cash
The way two what cookies I talked about these two ingredient cookies the ones that are made
Of bananas and oats
Oh, okay. Yeah, I mentioned these. Yeah. Yeah, I'm gonna experiment next next batch. I make I'm gonna experiment with uh
adding
Because it's like they're actually I'm actually disappointed. They're actually kind of high calorie
Like a batch of like eight cookies
I mean moderately large cookies, but still eight cookies like a thousand calories
And that's a lot
Um, so I'm gonna experiment with sub substituting
This might be the worst thing ever. I'm gonna try and substitute some of the oats with psyllium powder
Which is pure fiber
Is so it's not psyllium. So it's non caloric. I don't know. It might be horrible. It might be just disgusting
Uh, but it might be fine and great and then it would be
It'd be very silly
Yeah, um
Do you want me here? I'll I'll post uh
Oh, yeah, sorry
Uh, are you gonna post them? Yeah, sorry. I'm getting them. Uh, this one is called
Sorry, I've got a lot of uh, fucking folders open at the moment. This one is called this is for this one is for Gib and not Ben
Okay, so the both of us will be listening. Um, three two one go
Hey Gib, uh, you said
previously
that
On your money spenders podcast you have gone over
details on
development of pumpkin alley
um, some yeah
Very vague details without
spoiling it
Uh, how much detail did you go into into the process?
a lot a little
no
Biden find out
Biden find out. I mean Biden will find out. Oh, he's he fucked around now. He's gonna find out
uh
I feel like there's there's not like
A wealth of information about like the process of making the game
I can't remember exactly what I say
but like
I wasn't like documenting it like very rigorously and I wasn't programming it either so like
How the game works
Is like secondhand information that I get from like watching charlie struggle with something
And I'm like we workshop like possible solutions to problems and
and stuff like that
um when it comes to like
What I was doing for the game
I was doing animation, but I don't know how to like talk about the process of doing animation for a 3d thing
I don't know. I can't remember
Oh
That reminds me I I forgot to uh
I forgot to record that uh that I said I was going to do a patreon podcast and I haven't done it yet
I'll do I'll do it this week and hopefully have that out before this episode comes out
I meant to have it out by the time the last episode went out, but I didn't uh
oops
Uh, whoops whoops. Yes, exactly
Uh
Okay, next one
Yes, put got a fucking pop-up
antivirus pop-up. Okay. The next one is called um
Dating advice 3 2 1 go. Okay. You wanted to give dating advice. My girlfriend wants to stick a chopstick up my ass. Should I let her? Yeah
Where's the other chopstick going?
It's gotta go somewhere
Ow, how are you gonna pick things up with chopsticks?
Is she gonna put one in her eyes and then you combine your powers to pick up the food that?
God
Stop no
Disgusting. I'm just I'm just thinking. I'm just there. Just read the practicality. Oh
Good, I'm glad somebody's thinking about the
the consequences
I don't want to talk about this anymore. It's terrible
Uh, next voicemail is called, uh, texas anti trans stuff as of march 13th
3 2 1 go. I'm a little late so I'm responding to you talking about this two weeks ago
Hopefully I'm not just repeating information someone else said but I want to clarify what's going on in texas with the anti trans stuff
The first thing is that it's not new legislation. There's no new bill here
Essentially texas attorney general ken paxson out of the blue released a statement saying gender affirming health care constitutes child abuse
And then greg abbott the governor turned around and was like, yeah, that's definitely true
And i'm gonna issue a directive right now to send cps to investigate families of trans children and threaten to tear them apart
Also, this has the effect that psychologists and shit are required to report trans children to the state
So a lot of clinics just immediately close their doors to adolescents outright
This has been happening families are terrified cps workers were diverted from real cases of child abuse
No checks and balances no need for anything to be passed by other lawmakers just abbott abusing his position to terrorize his citizens
Yeah, I know you don't have to tell me that it's bad
And the first hearing for that was on friday march 11th
state's defense was utterly pathetic and the judge sustained an injunction to prevent the investigations from continuing
Until the next hearing in july ken paxson the attorney general then submitted an appeal the very same day and said that he's not
Going to let the investigation stop. I don't know if he has any way of doing that, but I am kind of fucking terrified at the thought
I'll leave more voicemails if there's more updates before the next show is recorded. This voicemail was left on sunday the 13th
I did hear about I did hear about like a court ruling that the okay. I didn't realize it was not new legislation
I did hear about a court ruling it unconstitutional
uh
So that's good. Hmm, but like it was blocked
by the attorney general
And that and like currently like the judge's ruling was blocked
Is that what I'm trying to think if that was what they said just then
Because like does that mean that in texas like families are still being terrorized by this
new
thing not new thing but like
I am
stuff
Bad thing sucks. I'm unsure. I think it it mean it seems like
What it means is that it's under like uh judicial contention
Like there's it sounds sounds like okay, there is there was a judge ruling against it
but like
Other forces are attempting to combat the ruling
so so until there's a like a a
um
A consensus on that issue
Whatever is happening can continue to happen. I don't I don't exactly know what's happening. I guess I guess uh
uh clinic clinics being closed
Uh because of like the potential legal uh consequences is happening. Uh
Psychologists being forced to out trans children. Yeah, well, it's um
Yeah, I don't I mean I don't know if like
uh, they've
Uh probably it has happens a few times. I don't know. I don't know if it's like a widespread thing
But like I guess it might
From what I've seen it is like definitely a scary thing. I don't know if I've seen
Like specific examples of things happening, but like the precedent is like scary enough. The precedent is pretty scary
I'm
I don't know. I mean I could be wrong, but I
Feel like it like it hasn't there hasn't been like I don't know
there hasn't been like a uh, you know, like
A trans crystal knocked in texas yet, you know, hopefully there won't be
Hopefully like the judge will will stop it before that happens
Ah
2022 is a good it's a good time
Texas be crazy. It's crazy texans
um, that's it
The next one is called Nate bestman and terrible translations
There it is. Uh, yep there three two one go
Okay, so I just rewatched the one piece lecture even though it is the second worst lecture with the first one
Of course being the final fancy one
And one of my big takeaways
Was that then
You really got to tell your stupid brother to stop reading terrible fan translations
Because best guy mr. Nate bestman commits one of the cardinal sins of terrible translation
Where he says something to the tune of
When delfut users get seawater on them they turn into a hammer
now
The reason this is so bad is because the phrase kanazuchi in japanese which literally means hammer
Uh figuratively is often used in japanese as a phrase to mean somebody who can't swim
yeah, so
In a lot of like terrible fan translations, which I assume are just translated with like you will translate
They don't they they just translate that word as hammer. They just go like oh, you're such a hammer
Even though in english that does make any sense
um
But a japanese person would understand it because it just means a person who can't swim. That's what it means. Yeah other pet peeves
A best guy says things like shichibukai
Or tenryubito or kairoseki even though these are just normal japanese words that could be easily translated
They're not like titles or something. These are just words. It sucks. It's terrible. Fuck you. Okay. I I like shibukai
I think it's fun to say it like that. I
Instead of I understand this I understand warlords. I understand this caller's point
Okay, I feel okay. I mean
I'm gonna I'm gonna
I'm gonna extend you
The goodwill to assume caller that you don't think that nate thinks that like literally they turn into hammers
Right like you know that he doesn't mean that so like
Nate knows that he's talking about a colloquialism for not being able to swim a japanese colloquialism a japanese colloquialism
You don't like
That he spent okay. I think you don't like that nate says
That maybe you think that nate presents it almost like a sort of one-piece ism that you turn into a hammer
Is what happens to you when you?
Get water on you as opposed to the reality which is that it is just a common
Japanese phrase maybe it would have been better to not even bother translating it literally and just
Say, you know
You you you become dead weight you become dead weight or something else like an english I feel like similar what phrase
I feel like I just don't agree with this guy
Or maybe you sink like a stone you sink like a stone would maybe be a better translation
That like because I I don't know I grew up reading
translated anime and manga
And I you know, they don't always translate every word. They don't always
A localize every term. Yeah, and so I feel like that's
just sort of the fun
Like flavor of like yeah, I don't know it doesn't have to be one way or the other
I don't mind people who like insist on
Not saying the japanese words or
Or what but like yeah, well what you got to get on my case for saying shibukai or like akatsuki
Like I like saying that I think I think there's some charm
I think there's some charm to a sort of inept translation where you read like oh
He he becomes a hammer and then there's a little asterisk and then you read at the bottom
That's like this is this is a this is a colloquial expression for
Being unable to swim. I mean it feels like it's like self-evident anyway
Like he becomes a hammer in water. It's like well, I know what would happen if a hammer was in water. It would sink
I think
I think I think it's fun
It is also fun and I appreciate I could I appreciate the value of like yeah a localization that
It would probably be a more natural reading experience to an english author
You know or to an english reader if you don't have that and if you just instead of
instead of just saying
He becomes a hammer and then having an asterisk and instead of just
Being you use you use an english phrase like oh if you type water gets on you you'll sink like a stone
You know you'll use like a an english equivalent of like a colloquial phrase
I I think that's you know, it's fun to think about that and that's probably like that's probably a better
You know a better way like a more professional and like cleaner and smoother doesn't take you out of the
Story sort of way to do it
Uh, I guess too, okay
And I understand the argument that like to a japanese speaker
Maybe you would read the word tenryubito
Not as like a
You know a proper noun not as like a name
But just as a phrase the way an english person would read. Oh the celestial dragons
Oh the seven the seven warlords of the sea, you know, you wouldn't think it
Yeah, but I I I kind of like the japanese names. I like shichibukai and tenryubito
I like saying them. Yeah, I understand. I but although I get I get why it's like that's not how it's intended
It's it's not intended to be read as like a word spoken in a different language
So I feel like you know, I'm gonna be a fence sitting centrist and I'm gonna say I see both sides of these
Uh
Yeah, I like saying loro no zoro like what's the enemy?
Oh, did you know that in japanese the r letter is the the r
That's where yeah japanese
it's a it's a fun thing for a teenager to like try and figure out how to say
true not from the right culture to do that that's right that's what I did I
I tried I learned some I got a book on tape learn Japanese from the library when
I was a kid and I learned a little bit of phrasing here and there it was fun
anyway anyway this guy this this caller you got a point but I think you're being
a little too I think you're being a little too serious about it no it's
supposed to be straw hat it just means I mean I mean I mean I guess you yeah you
would make the same I mean I mean I mean actually I mean I guess that makes it
right because they're not they're not calling him some fancy title moogie
wada they're calling they're just calling oh it's interesting it's
straw hat loofy it's more it's colloquial I and I can I can agree and accept that
you are I would to come across as a nerd if I went around saying moogie wada all
the time but I just kind of like it it's over it's like that would be like if in
if in the original they call him like they literally call me oh stood all
had to do theater like there is like they say it like that like it's a it's a
name you know but they didn't anyway next one is oh god this one's gonna suck
this this is voicemail is gonna suck shit it's bad but I'm gonna play it anyway
how to get your podcasts on Spotify Apple podcasts etc. 3 2 1 go apologies if
the Spotify situation has been cleared up already if so feel free to skip this
I'm gonna lose my mind but as somebody with a podcast themselves
it's 12 podcast called tales gets podcast please check it out okay I might be a
modicum of help so the way you upload to platforms such as Apple music or Apple
podcasts and Spotify is that you have to submit an RSS feed this is this is
torture this is torture and so how you updates all the podcasts on like spot
etc. is just by uploading a new podcast to your RSS feeds then it
automatically gets put on all the different platforms okay so really all
you need to do is get your hands on that RSS feed yeah and just uploads the
episodes that aren't in there to it I assume Tom set up the RSS feed and I
don't know how you did it because there's many ways of doing it some you can
make it yourself or you can use like a service to make it so you upload through
that this is literally the worst track down Tom and like steal the RSS feed
like right out of so this is like missing the start uploading this is like how
did you talk for a minute 30 and convey zero information like I know we still
need to get a hold of Tom thanks for thanks like thanks for nothing like I'm
literally angry I'm literally angry at you from for making this like what is
wrong with you why did you think I needed to hear this yes the point is yes
Tom controls the RSS feed yes I know yes Tom is in charge yes oh I just I just
got to get Tom to do it I know that's what I've been saying this week has been
I've gotten a bunch more messages I don't I've got a bunch more messages from
people asking me Ben can you please no I know I asked already but can you please
put them on the podcast apps and like how many fucking times do I have to tell
you I don't have the power Tom's in charge of it Tom has the RSS feed how
many fucking times do you have to hear that's not my fucking problem why are
people still asking me about it how why don't they ask Tom like what could I do
to make it clearer that somebody else is in fucking charge of it I don't get it
who don't ask me again you fucks okay that's it cuz Tom doesn't answer me I
have it's Tom just don't just Tom just ignores me when I ask him about it and
that's and that's the truth that's that's just where we're at with that so now
you know like it's if I I just I just won't I just won't answer anymore I
just won't answer anymore anyone adding me about it cuz like I don't respect it
okay anything else no okay hmm what I don't know I see I see Tom tweeting about
playing Elden Ring yeah like like surely you'd be able to just reply and say oh
yes sorry I'll get around to it like at least that I know what he's doing yeah
no I haven't no he obviously and myself okay okay okay I haven't I haven't dm
him but I've added him you know what you know you know what you know what you know
what okay you know what maybe I'm being maybe I'm being a little bit of bitch
right now because I have not actually do you know what I'm gonna do it right now
I'm gonna do it right now I haven't done it before say hey dm Tom all right and
and and I rescind all my previous anger and if it doesn't get fixed after this
then I will unresend it I had assumed you already dm'd him and he just hadn't
responded that's why I thought no I just added him in the pcp discord which I'm
like he would have seen it obviously like like he maybe not I don't see why
not there we go okay all right message sent I just don't I just don't get it I
just don't get why people keep asking me about it when like I've said like it's
not me I guess I guess I guess just you know for the sake of cosmic justice like
I hope I hope people have been asking Tom too because like there's there's
literally no reason why like I'm the guy like I've said over and over that like
I'm not the guy so it's just it's a little annoying I guess but anyway okay I
sent I sent a dm there I dm'd and now now I have done the extent of
everything I could possibly do about it anyway I fucking hate you voicemailer
fuck you and fuck your podcast next next one is called Nate soundboard there
it is 3 2 1 go dude remember when Nate debuted as soundboard just to leave the
podcast like three episodes later was that all about kind of cringe I don't
know man I don't know like you it's cringe because you wanted to see more of
the sound yeah did you want more soundboard or do you think he just
shouldn't have bothered debuting it what's what's your what's your solution to
this to this cringe conundrum you've presented us with here you already had
it for a stream that in me I think it was just sort of like I figured out how
to make it play during a podcast yeah maybe yeah maybe I don't know I don't
know okay next one is something there it is it is called then you skip one did
I do six seconds oh right sorry yeah that was Ben Saints weekly reminder three
two one go welcome to Ben Saints weekly reminder to go to the library yeah
have you done it yet no not yet I'll do it yeah I'll go to the library I've been
playing Hades I just released the game a few days ago I guess it's been like four
or five days it's been playing video games and setting up book pages I'll go
to the library I'll go to the library one of these days but thanks for the
reminder next one is called Ben's Saint character inconsistencies to come on
writers three two one go when the character of Ben Saints reacted to the
reveal of the new Pokemons he uttered this phrase I haven't played a good
Pokemon game since white two however in his own Pokemon son Nuzlocke he said
this I love this game so no wonder this character is so controversial he is so
inconsistent the writers don't even know what to do with this character I mean
come on man get some consistency into the Ben Saint character now I I remember
like I I had a pretty okay time playing Sun I felt more positively about Sun
while I was playing it than I do in hindsight in hindsight I think it was
pretty underwhelming and I think a lot of the changes they made were bad and I
don't think it's a good direction for the series and I'm not very happy with
it at the time I thought it was okay even so even still I don't think I would
have sighed and said I love this game it just doesn't sound like something I
would say I don't believe you I think you're lying it sounds like the sort of
thing you would say sarcastically maybe something terrible happened yeah yeah
that sounds yeah it sounds about right okay next one is called rip capitalism
three two one go you made it I know we calling a nighter good bye bye thanks see
yeah thanks for letting us know that Nikolai died
that's a shame but at least we have closure closure on that arc okay next
one is called biscuits or cookies three two one go good day you old skippers
you're a newfound man some old newfound landers still called cookies
they call it biscuits there's not a high-class thing that dirty old newfound
landers are calling it that dirty old what man does you think he's saying
nuca landers like from fallout like nuca cola here in nuca I think he's saying
nuca landers I think there might be a fallout I think that's a fallout
location it's what I think but I don't know I have not played that one okay
whatever good next one is called what is it called bests every normie
three two one go the best and blessed ben saint returns to bless us with content once again
wrote to radcon amazing that's revenge incredible when will he ever make a bad work of art never
ah it's so cool when will he ever make a bad work of art just breathe directly into the microphone
buddy it's good it sounds good when you do it thanks for liking my shit
okay next next one I guess
uh uh uh uh that was here we go 25 is called uh motto three two one go
you know ben follows my motto for all of its worth if you're good at something never do for free
also give makes really funny puns and I love the occasions when they happen
I love that gal thank you the joker thanks the joker wow I can't believe the joker's a fan
uh yeah specifically the uh oh what's his name
dark knight and joker heath ledger heath ledger heath ledger yeah specifically that joker um
oh no oh no this is just like um oh but this is just like we have a problematic fan who did
terrorism this is just like when when like lauren southern fans like committed all those mass shootings
it's like oh we got a disavow we got a disavow all the actions of the time that was a really good
movie yeah it was a really good movie yeah the terrorism was kind of cool the joker did all that
terrorism but that but you know they made a great movie yeah yeah so it's all it all balances out
okay yeah true yeah true uh oh wait I okay I skipped one whatever uh the one 26 is called
I have okay well there's a oh there's an image file attached here let's uh let me get the link
oh it's a it's a phantom's revenge end screen there it is don't
elias are blur out the blur out the image blur out the uh the spoilery part with the image yeah
just show the text that parts you can't we catch no spoilers no spoilers here um okay anyway three
two one go so I just started listening to this podcast around the end of 2021 so I don't have
any nostalgia of what it used to be oh wow but I catch up by randomly listening to previous episodes
that intrigued me now and this wasn't too long ago but I was just on the orangutan flange episode
and it's really funny to hear a hopeful ben saying he won't add anything unnecessary to phantom's
revenge or and also releasing the cwc one or two lecture with it and also just truck
sink tricksy on actually riding rhodo rathcon chapter five the congrats on the public really
extended a lot of good here's my minimalist run where I actually beat it I didn't actually
didn't actually take me 10 minutes because I closed the tab after a break and then I proceeded
to drop in at the last 10 minutes of gib stream uh no I did take you 10 minutes um because that's
the time for the run I you're not the first person to say this and I feel like people don't
get that like the time is not the time you spent playing the whole game it's the time you spent
in the run it's always like that so no it definitely did take you 10 minutes uh don't
worry about it that's pretty fast though no one I haven't seen anyone try to speed run it
uh yeah I haven't seen anyone try to speed run pumpkin alley either
when the hot fix comes out I will explicitly ask for people to do that because
that there's there's a lot of like because it's a 3d game uh there's lots of like potential for
like time saving and and like skips I want to see what people can figure out I I did not add
anything unnecessary to phantom's revenge everything that ended up in there was 100
crucial for the experience um on a slime coin on a no you know no that not text texturally it's
texturally necessary it had the if it changes the it changes the uh the way you feel about it
uh yeah I guess uh no I'm just kidding obviously obviously you're right yeah slime coin is totally
slime coin is totally pointless floor reflections pretty much a waste of time they look nice but
they could have gotten away with they were nice I could have gotten away with adam and honestly
I probably should have but oh well whatever uh you know but not nothing unnecessary uh the um
um what else did he say uh about uh oh I was I think on a I think on a um on a
patreon podcast I will probably go into like stuff that I sort of thought about adding to
the game there was a bunch there's a whole I have a whole list of things that I was considering like
I would like to maybe add this to the game but then I was like no just just you have to stop
you see it has it has to stop somewhere there there were a few features that I was like
really considering uh uh I yeah also like before I really like got a lot of the game like nailed
down like when it was just a battle system with like nothing in it there was I was there was a
lot of like I was considering like a different sorts of like enemies and stuff I was I had like
different ideas about what it could have been uh I don't know there's a lot of things that could
have been but it is what it is and that's a tautology anyway the next one is there's no voicemail
there's just a link to a tweet from doid gazer oh yes yeah this is really good actually doid gazer
is um I haven't seen this I saw this on um yeah on twitter this is actually really good
the pcp iceberg okay or maybe it's or make you crew no it's the void it's like the it's supposed
to be like the void gazer is like Trixie the golden witch iceberg I think is what it's supposed to be
oh is it I think so well I feel like this is pcp stuff because like even at the top star fleet
weird utilitarianism has nothing to do with Trixie at all yeah yeah you're right
uh ask pcp I'm just could we use that hashtag I guess we did yeah for I for the um for when
we were doing questions instead of like voicemails yeah we did rebel pixels neuro typing that's all
this is all normal stuff yeah make survive tbap mining at night sigh wonderbred ripple xrp
group piss slash shit what's your favorite anime yeah one one one one uh riddle my ass
batman wears the podcast I'm gonna wait and I'm gonna go down until I find something I don't
even remember I actually I don't remember what's your favorite anime that was a question we got
like annoyingly like frequently because like people thought it was digipros anime podcast yeah well
and so there would be like again come up with better questions and that was like a thing we would
we would rag on I guess uh uh monkey kick uh what's that time Ben been recorded through speakers
what what does that mean you remember that uh I mean I know my mic used to be pretty bad
I don't remember Ben recorded do they mean that like do they mean like you were recorded
via someone else's speakers of your voice uh like so that's what it sounds like yeah I'm not sure
either uh let's keep going pizza jumps maddox synchronicities Ben and Jackie's college fun
that's that's a good one that now they now there's a piece of like lost media right there yeah
maddox maddox synchronicities is that's not do they just mean like like oh there was a breakup
and somebody's got to be the dick and somebody's got to be the maddox I think that is what they
like is that yeah yeah it doesn't really line up that's not really like a high profile thing
yeah like it's yeah it that's just like a hey is in some ways this one thing that happened was
resembled another thing in certain aspects like crazy um
has he groomed munchie now that now that one I'm familiar with give rights for doctor
Jesse okay I think I think this point when you get to the beluga whale that's when you just go from
like well I guess Tom is a vegetarian is is not true but like that we used to say that you know
we used to say Tom was a communist too uh that used that used to be a thing Thomas in one of the
the rumbles yeah yeah that was a way from way back give rights for dr who what is that in reference
to uh it's because you're just that I do writing stuff uh because you were a show you're a show
writer you do that I get do you do because you're writing stuff for a secret for a secret
project and still yeah so it's dr who because you're British oh well what else what else would
it be yeah um davoo is why davoo wasn't a red con three I don't remember that why wasn't davoo a red
con three I think she just didn't want to come I think it's as simple as that
or wait had she left by then the right con three no maybe um maybe a little are you sure I I you
know I don't remember I know I know at some point she hmm I feel like she was like the first person
to be like hey guys I've I'm officially like I'm like I'm actually leaving like I'm I'm officially
out and that might I feel like I feel like she was on a like a I need to reduce my presence on the
internet because I'm a game developer now people are gonna find my tweets like that was the thing
she was going on stupid and so she wanted to appear on podcast less and I maybe that was part of
like red con three not coming do you uh yeah I think you you know I don't really exactly remember
like if there was any particular reason or if there it was just like she was just like yeah
yeah um you know she deleted her she deleted her discord recently did you know about that
like she started discord no she had she put out like two videos started a discord and then deleted
it and said like oh this was like a youtuber discord yeah like like a like a davoo cord
to go along with like I remember it's it's very strange I remember she said she put out
she messaged me to say some shit about uh uh Trixie or whatever and then she said she said and
said she was considering like getting more back into like being online then she made a discord
and was like I want to be more online then like I want to be in like a community whatever
then she big mistake big big mistake and then she put out that uh five will goes west video uh
and then I think she did one more video after that I'm not sure like more like maybe like a week
ago or two weeks ago um which I missed at the time but it's there and then like a week ago she was
like yeah guys I've decided that uh this was like I was trying I was testing it out uh doing
community uh being online uh don't want to do it uh I'm deleting the discord by uh maybe I'll
like I'll keep making videos but no more community uh it's just stupid I don't know this is dumb um
yeah um anyway so in the in the lowest category then there's devu as a symbiote
does that is that like the the devu collective that joke
problem is something different you know it's probably
I mean none of these are none of these are real at this point these are all no but like I'm trying
because like I feel like the devu collective was a very well known joke in comparison to that some
of these other things I don't think yeah that's what makes me think it's not that I think it's
saying like devu is not a real human devu is actually like a like a creature that like like
you know maybe latched on to like a Trixie or something that was like a a parasite growing
in Trixie's body or something not a not a human I vaguely remember mage as a tulper I don't remember
in what context was she on an episode where we were talking about tulpers I don't think these
last ones are even like based in anything fiance blood ritual gamer saver and his xkgp
sounds pretty legit though I mean we don't we don't know how old he is
I guess not I guess not like exactly no
it's true then it's just true if we don't know so it's true yes so it's true if we don't
the fact if we don't know everything then like anything anything could be true
as far as as far as I'm concerned sorry I'm putting my bathrobe on because it's getting
chilly in here yeah okay uh so yeah this is uh this is great I love this it's pretty good
yeah it's really good a lot of a lot of a lot of funny jokes and references to things and uh
oh hi I gozaimasu I forgot you know what I still have the list here I forgot to put Kyle and
funny man and doid gaze are on the voice grail but I have them written down here I'm gonna put
them I'm gonna do it after we're done recording they're going on the list they're going on they're
getting in there they're making they're making the grade actually you might as well do it next I need
to pee you know what I fucking will a few moments later I'm back they're in they made it they're in
the document it's official hooray uh okay let's keep let's get a move on because we have like too
many fucking voicemails this week um next one is called oh shit I lost my place next one is called
Aston Villa three two one go what are your thoughts on the trash taste the podcast
thoughts on what trash taste uh I know oh that's no that's the one with um the anime guys uh
gigik and uh yeah I don't know I don't know I never watched yeah still never yeah whatever
I don't even know who they are they talk about anime I think apparently they don't talk that much
about anime it's more about like life in japan because they all they live in japan um uh yeah
you ever go wake up and you say oh hi oh gozaimasu next one is next one is a youtube video
it's a it's just a link to uh yeah this this one I posted here
Sierra I know games from Sierra oh this Ken Ken Williams Ken and Roberta Williams the other
these guys like were the Sierra developers or whatever it's a it's a interview with the
Sierra developers okay it's a 40 minute video I'm scrolling through looking at
what games they're talking about I don't think I know these particular ones why would you send
this as a voicemail maybe you thought it was interesting well they were wrong well they were
fucking wrong um next voicemail is called Ben why did you teach in Poland for are you're of Polish
bilu three two one go what the fuck yes uh well I just wanted a job and I wanted to leave the
country I wanted to travel and there was a I don't even remember how I think I was looking on craigslist
I think I think it might have just been a coincidence I was looking for like positions
teaching physics and there just happened to be one in Poland and I was like I'm Polish
I have a Polish name I bet I can get in if I apply there and I was right and that's that's why
that's why I did that uh next one is called oh it's just it's just another youtube link
uh god here we go at least we can skip them super metal what okay you have these these youtube
links are from wait the first one was from metal jesus rocks this one is from super metal dave 64
somebody likes metal metal gaming big metroid prime 4 update wow who cares okay the next one
favorite gen 9 starter uh okay I I forget his name but definitely the alligator
um oh the ones that have just been released yeah just been shown yeah uh I don't know
the the they all suck maybe foe foe foe coco yeah foe coco is my favorite of these three
uh like I I did like the cat initially but then everybody was like ha ha weed cat now I don't
like it uh weed cat's fine probably I would say foe coco best sprigatito second quacksley third
but uh is a non entity they're all pretty all right I think I like foe coco the best uh
that's it that's my answer um okay next one
shit sorry I lost my place I'm stupid I'm stupid uh oh god it's a long one
okay this one is called the best non pcp lectures and the problem with most lectures
there's no way this needs to be a minute 30 three two one go all right the best non pcp lectures
are the tectonic improv linkara one as well as the wip university christian reformation one
imo I haven't heard of that one uh there are some decent ones like for example the ash vampire
bionicle one no as well as vampires a piece of shit and his life studios russell grair one
the problem with most lectures though and the vast majority of lectures are
similar wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait did this did this idiot just recommend the void
gazers russell grair lecture the topics like aren't good for lectures is that what just happened
conducive to the lecture I wasn't listening like it's good final fantasy and this guy's serious this
guy thinks that the that the ash vampire bionicle lecture and the void gazers russell grair lecture
I watched like five minutes of that russell grair one and it was like incoherent and I didn't know
what he was talking about okay whatever there's like loads of them this guy this where this no
I'm done I've had enough now we know now we know whatever lectures you got to choose the right subject
matter uh it's got to be something yes oh my god it's the same fucking thing it's the same
fucking thing he says oh it's better to just watch the thing you need something that you need
that you need a lecturer to explain it to you on I know I'm gonna feel I'm gonna feel really bad
if this is like a new viewer who like hasn't like heard us say this exact thing like a thousand times
but well guess what buddy we've said this a thousand times ah I'm mad I'm mad at the voicemail
today um next one is called lectures part oh god he didn't make a sequel one did he next one is
called lectures part two aka why Nate is cringe don't copy him uh no we're skipping it no I
won't listen to it wow we're actually skipping it I'm not listening to that one um I've heard I've
heard all I need to hear next one is called uh it's a youtube video okay it's from this is from
what the fuck was this video lol at gmail.com okay this is the this is the lady latest yig studio video
entitled we have elden ring at home with the thumbnail called it says elfin ring I watched
like the first uh like minute of this it's performing about as well as all yig studio videos do
uh the I think the gist of it is my my computer instead of playing the elden ring I'm playing
elfin ring I'm playing it's not actually called elfin ring oh it's called like something ring
uh whatever ring a ding ding I don't know it's just it's like it's just a video I see like hey I
didn't play elden ring I played this other old rpg instead uh at least that's that's the video
I don't know that's pretty soon by the way I will be playing elden ring on stream
oh once the lord of ghost things get get shipped off you said you would be able to play you said
you wouldn't play it until lord of ghosts I gotta admit I have felt like I've been missing out on
something by not playing elden ring everyone seems to just be having such a great time playing elden
ring yeah it's it's just like universally like that's a good one so I'm like I'm sure I'm gonna
have fun with it and I and I I would enjoy the process of streaming it and having everyone in chat
be a veteran of the game and being like no no no no no you gotta do this you gotta do that and I'd
be like huh what then I die that would be fun I want that to happen that does sound fun um okay the
next one is called do not listen sent by accident sorry about that and uh chresothor on discord
sent me a message saying hey don't play that message I think it is just like silence like it's
just like I think it we literally just like butt dialed us or something so we'll skip that one
that's fine no problem uh next voicemail is called no tom no watch I wonder uh wait shit uh oh god
I'm so I'm struggling with all my windows because my second screen is broken today or like it's not
working and I don't know why so I'm struggling to organize everything on my screen there no
tom no watch okay three two one go I'm starting to decide with the guy who says no tom no watch
because uh where the fuck is Tom I don't know fuck you okay next voicemail is called uh he's
tumbling down he's he's playing he's playing elden ring and hanging out with saberspark that's where
he is uh uh apparently he moved to virginia he said he's he's yeah I mean this I just heard
the second hand he was saying for ever and ever that he was moving to Ohio and then apparently he
just moved to virginia I guess well gotta move somewhere gotta move you gotta move somewhere
I guess um okay whatever next one is a message for voicemailers everywhere three two one go
everyone or all of the voicemailers we gotta stop sending messages yeah gotta stop saying voicemails
for one week because every episode is way too fucking long so uh I'll stop it for one week
and then we can see you back on next week guys okay there are a lot of people who would be mad that
you said the episodes are way too long people love that some people are like super long episodes
five hour episodes please yeah I get it I watched that I watched the entire uh
it's it saves somebody it saves somebody having to like click on another video
yeah why would you want to let it play just let it play I get it I genuinely get it next one is
called phantoms revenge three two one go so then his fans revenge you're taking revenge on tripsy
if not you should update the game to be that because that would be an even and more people will play
and fuck you fuck you you didn't play you didn't play the game if you didn't play the game you
don't know it is I can't tell this is a joke I mean I think he's just saying like ha ha revenge
is tricksy okay yeah you're right now and now I'm imagining like the same game but like the
sprites are replaced with phantom horn is just been saying it'd be terrible and and um the sonichus are
uh yigtralite so whatever you could call them I mean did didgy brony is in is in the game
now that is true oh like like didgy brony too it's it's uh it's
you I think you started to pick up on it you started to pick up and I don't know if you
uh picked up everything but there is um there is sort of a like sort of undiscussed
like story happening in the game with the son I mean uh some of them okay I'll just say
her name her name her name would be didgy bro her name her son even though she's a son of
her name would not be didgy bro sonichu it would just be didgy bro
and that's uh that's uh that's that's consistent that's consistent with all the other uh names in
the game the I wonder what that means uh you you got to that chamber and you were like huh does that
mean does that mean that some of these sonichus were ponies and I was like hey hey you saw some
other stuff before that you didn't notice but uh it was there so it was there all along
so like pony sonichus turned from ponies I mean I guess nightstar well I shouldn't say anything
about that but I mean well nightstar okay well nightstar is a sonichu right in the same way that
chris chan is a sonichu yeah they they just are for some reason I now that I think about it I have
no idea aside from like generating soldiers for a war which I guess is happening I have no idea what
that like thing the the facility is doing in ponyville in everfree forests specifically
I will say if you've seen in my second lecture in sonichu one or two when I'm talking about
which which issue is it issue 13 or issue 12 the one that's just like a big text dump of like
fucked up shit happening there's the part where there is the part in that issue where um sonichu's
blood like chris chan's blood gets like splattered over like I think it gets like it gets disseminated
through the water supply or it gets like like a wave of it or something something happens
chris chan's blood gets on all the nazis that are invading quickville and they all turn into
sonichu's uh and that's just canon that's just on then the sonichu race is filled with nazis
I think all those nazis died no no they no they go a lot of them die discord gives them a lot of
them heart attacks a lot of the remaining ones go back to germany and disband the rite
that's that's just canon that's just the text that's just the text um there's a
I feel like I need to reread sonichu but I don't want to let me let me let me think there are a
couple of sonichu's in phantom's revenge uh what are they blue yon blue yonder is one uh strawberry
shortcake I think I think that no not strawberry shortcake its name is like uh strawberry something
um strawberry cream I think it might be called strawberry cream and there's another one called
uh roaming service and there might be one or two others too but the a few of the sonichu's have some
like descriptions that might stand out a little bit uh I don't want to say I don't want to I've
said too much already uh anyway next voicemail is called uh prince isolation
wait sorry I skipped one the next voicemail is called prince isolation
mimiori three two one go
last episode you were talking about uh the twitter artist mimiori and her among us girl
comic yeah and I just wanted to mention real quick in case people don't know uh that she also makes
a web comic that's original serenity called serendipity which is about like an overworked
depressed magical girl and uh it's great and everyone should check it out yeah I did fan art
of it because it made me cry uh okay uh bye that sounds nice uh not the crying part uh I have um
made you cry huh I have not read like much of it but I've seen it and I know the art is really good
yes serenity and yeah serendipity uh it looks really good I didn't mention it just because
I didn't want to go down a whole thing about like who is this uh artist but uh I mean yeah they do
more work on their web comic than on among us girl but among us girl is the thing that like
recently went kind of viral so I thought I'd mention that is like a thing people might have seen
but yeah she does a web comic too um looks good I like her art a lot anyway next next one is um
Ben's weekly reminder play deltarune chapter two okay I will say give we should actually stream
this week we really should right um well you want to stream deltarune chapter two well no I was
thinking minecraft oh okay because maren want maren maren sent that voicemail about how there's new
stuff in the yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah so let's let's do that like maybe Wednesday okay it's it's
been like it's been like two months or something um okay next one is called I'm not looking forward
to it it's called tonsil stones there it is three two one go Ben on your tonsil stone thing topic
whatever I've had these things as a kid for these little pieces of food gets stuck in the back of
my throat like the back of my tongue and they just get picked out once in a while great great
fucking voicemail um it's not it's not just it's not food it's not food getting stuck in the back
of your throat it's like particles it's bits like wedged in like the crevices of the tonsil like the
I mean I guess the tonsil is at the back of your throat but it's like inside the
tonsil it's not just like there okay whatever I've never had one before and I'm not sure if
that's what it was but I it kind of looked like one so I don't know I hope I don't have them all
the time that would be terrible uh like I said it didn't it didn't like smell or anything so like
whatever uh next one is called the it is gross though what do you guys think of the controversial
new mario kart I don't know I haven't seen it uh mario kart and crash and burn that's what I see I
would I don't care about mario kart uh next one is called ben's penis reduction three two one go
I had assumed too much been saint I'll draw the penis smaller next time uh are you talking about
that drawing of the penis shadow the penis shadow who was it overshadowing uh sonichu or
nightstar or something oh right yeah please please do not misrepresent me please draw the penis small
um next one okay now next one is called eqd enm uh right there
I posted it twice okay three two one go I mean I was gonna play phantom revenge
but then I saw them three little colored individuals I just don't like to tell the
kid you know what I mean do you know what he's referring to I there is the comment on on the
equestria daily yeah to explain to if referring to the sonichu characters as the three colored
individuals he he said I don't like the way this looks and you know what I mean and someone
this was a comment on the post and someone said do you mean the blood like on the sword
and he said no I mean the three little colored individuals yeah he's talking about the three
little colored sonichu's but like you said colored individuals
it's a classic a classic brony struggle moment right there okay next one is an image this isn't
funny and it makes american lefties look oh it's the vosh oh by the way I I was the only one with
the right vosh take last week by the way I'm the only one who's right everyone else is dumb
uh vosh I'm I fucking I've been so mad but the vosh people are just disgusting they're sick
they're they're like they're like as bad as smaller people honestly this they're pathetic I hate them
um uh I'm this this this isn't funny and it makes american lefties look bad but wait isn't that
true about any tweet this enlightened it turns out the twitter sucks literally literally any tweet
makes american lefties look bad sad it's sad but true it is true this is me becoming the cop killer
this is me this is the first time I discovered slime this is after nuts nuts the beginning
this is when I traveled to nlaka calm and found the slam there I went
it looks great looks awesome uh I love the wings okay uh next one is called vaguely British man
is miffed again there it is three two one go hello does me again vaguely a British man
uh and I'm back here because yet again bed saves has done something bad
he has promised uh voice grail people such as Kyle funny man I did it and uh do it gave
us that they would get into the voicemail documents two times but he has not written them
in the document and this this is getting me missed if I'm being honest here I'm being real
missed right now okay um okay that's it end end of voicemail yep I did it gotcha sucker thanks
for the voicemail uh die uh next one is called vroom vroom sorry vroom vroom three two one go
okay cool uh next one is called uh buffalo from phantomfucksatfrontier.singles three two one go
howdy partner it's me buffalo bill now I reckon it mighty presumptuous for me to claim
bearing in mind 10 hour motion picture dissertations having graced the fridge at frontiers youtube as
yet but I do clear you gotta made a darn tootin video game right on part darn tootin
wow thanks uh whatever your name was did he say his name but buffalo bill thanks buffalo bill
I'm glad you felt the game was darned too
okay thanks bye uh next one is called Jebediah Preckingsons long awaited return at pcp.rlm.com
three two one go
hello this is me Jebediah Preckingsons just wanted to drop in and just say
my penis got very hard when phantom drowned that bitch nightstar spoilers thank you
you're welcome spoilers uh we can leave that in unbleep because like it's hard to even understand
what you're saying uh uh that was uh nice to hear from Jebediah nice to hear from Jebediah
glad you enjoyed the ending of uh of phantom's revenge hey you beat the game you got the ending
that's pretty good uh drawing the ending I didn't like it I found it very uncomfortable
to draw that scene but uh Gabe you told me that it was fine well I it's without getting
too specific yeah it's like it's uh it's like somewhat gory yeah a little bit it's not like
like actually unsettling at least for me in terms of like visuals obviously what's happening is
maybe a bit like it's not it's not about yeah it's not about uh it's not about like the I guess
you could I guess you could call it gore a little bit it's not like yeah yeah it's sort of that is
just a yeah uh it's just like uh it's like what it says about phantom horn is that what makes you
unsettled it's sort no not really no it was just like uh it's not that it says like oh it's that it's
bad it's like oh oh I don't know it's not that it's just that it's like a it's it's literally just like
if I was phantom in this situation this would feel terrible and and like that's it so I'm just like
I'm just feeling it I'm just feeling it drawing it when I feel it feeling it when I draw it and
when I look at it that's it uh yeah that's because I'm that's I'm what you call I'm what you call an
artist give oh really what's that try it sometime why don't you um next voicemail is called uh did I
upload it already yes I did st comics dot com slash patreon dot com slash ben saint dot com three two one go
to the round of phony veal there was a stranger one fine day it's the song
heart I spoke to folks around him didn't have too much to say oh my god
Jesus she was wanted and a killer his slime level ten and four and his slime court verified
cal count number one and 19 more one and 19 more Jesus was this guy trying his best
early in the morning when he rode into the town yeah I mean yeah exactly what he said
haha what sounds like this is canon no one dare to ask his business no one dare to make a slip
the stranger there among them had a big artist if they can't I can't believe it I can't believe it
no hold the stranger lived a pony who would the stranger come to me and she watched the stranger
marching down the cobble pony this is this is great in her bunker on the yaskers she came
I'll kill you I'll fucking kill you fuck it up the slimy stranger was marching towards his day
marching towards his day
base that I like I like that being the canon voice of red man in that sequence
yeah that's what makes it funny this was uh I don't know LA is our post the somebody's got to
do it like a pcp animated event I did there's this there's a four panel sequence of red man
in the red man in the classic red man comic poses he's singing that song that was uh that was really
something okay next wait a minute okay okay the next one all right now I'm unsure because the next
one is called please don't play the previous one too late it's too late okay I assume that the other
one was the all right maybe this is the one that um maybe this is the one that uh crezathore meant
not to play and I told him I wouldn't play it but like that was good I already played it and like
it's kind I mean I have mixed feelings about it no no I love it I love it okay I think it's fine
yeah it's fine don't worry about it um next one is called uh uh god I lost my place next one is called
david hater come collector um oh wait I haven't posted yet David hater come collector there it is
okay three two one go so you wanted better voicemails to riff on here you go give then
possibly cheesy as a comic artist to a comic artist which platforms would you recommend for
upload they're all terrible also how much your sites cost you and how hard to maintain their
framework is um they're all all platforms are bad they're all terrible if there's one they're like
I don't know I guess line webtoon is okay it's probably the one most people use I don't know
yeah webtoons all right the I don't feel like they're necessarily good for all types of comic
you have to be like the right kind to get big noticed on there um yeah when it comes to my
website it's like a wordpress thing and I pay for the domain and since it's not like dot com it's
just dot site it's like cheaper if I got it through hover which is you may have heard of that it's
like a like a domain registering thing yeah it's quite easy to use my website I got through I think
it's called digital ocean uh I pay like 10 I pay like $10 a month just to keep my like domain active
uh which is like whatever um I pay like eight pounds a year on give and take dot site
wait do I pay $10 a month $10 a month seems like a lot but I guess I don't know
hmm I know for my other website um it's like 11 pounds for a dotco.uk for a site that I made
for uni that I don't use for anything I think maybe I just decided that I just wanted that dot com
really bad do with the coom it does it does seem high now that I think about it
I mean dot com I don't know the the legality thing I assume that like you're not allowed to sell
things if it's not a dot com like you can't set you can't have a website if it's not dot com
because it's commercial but I don't know whether that's actually enforced or whether that's true
there's no way that that's like enforced I'll I'll have to look into that because like I was
thinking like maybe I should make give and take dot com or something as well I just think it's more
expensive I don't know I just think it's yeah I mean I don't think it really matters uh it honestly
I probably should have just gone for dot st comics dot dot slime all right well I mean that would be
sick um there's lots of things you could do it's just like um I guess the cool ones are really
expensive and the ones that everybody knows to type in are the most expensive like dot com
or like dot gov if you're like no those are those are very expensive um all right next one is
what's that squeaking noise in the last episode uh answer I don't know I don't know what you're
referring to yeah I don't know was there a squeaking noise I don't remember one uh next one is uh
come collector two sons of liberty three two one go speaking of metal gear did you play
who is best but raid nor snake I played the first one and I didn't finish it and that's it I played
the first one for a few minutes by the first one I mean solid solid yeah metal go solid yeah
I didn't get very far and I was kind of confused and it was too hard I think I got to like the
like the second elevator sequence I did I never beat it I got like pretty far I knew it and I
never beat it I have like the short game I didn't yeah it's I had never played the whole thing
but I it wouldn't be that difficult to just go through it I think with games like that that
and like Resident Evil the fact that there are like oh um uh you can't there's like things that you
can't get back or like rations and stuff healing things or saving points or stuff it's all like um
what's the word finite you run out yeah that scares me too much fun fungible uh so so like
when it comes to that I don't know the full length of the game I get scared and I get too
afraid to use healing things and that means I die a lot and then it's too hard I because I feel
like I need to save those healing things because the game might what if I get to write the end of
the game and then I can't win because I didn't have any like healing things like uh like stacked up
and so that's why I don't play games you definitely you definitely shouldn't use those items that the
developers put in the game to like let you beat it you should definitely avoid those at all costs
it's like it's a holdover for me and the time that you shouldn't use them the most is when you
need them like that's when you that's when you know like no this is a trap this is a trap they've
laid for me it's just a holdover from like when I was younger and I didn't know like the extent
to which games could exist I thought like the possibilities were so far reaching and like
anything could happen that I need to be super prepared for every eventuality because one time
I got a game over and I didn't like it like you obviously you want your heroes and your JRPG like
after they beat the final boss you want them to like end the game with lots of stuff in their
inventory lots of like grenades and like vaccines and stuff like you know they're gonna need to like
sell that later you know to get their life started afterwards to get their retirement fund
exactly exactly yeah I could throw this grenade and deal some extra damage but like you know that's
gonna be like the starter capital to like you know start my bakery after I settle down start a family
later camp why would I like oh this this rocket launcher only has three shots if I use one that's
a third of my ammunition gun who knows if I'll get another ammunition box further in I better
use my pistol instead save save on the rockets and then fight this boss for 200 hours that's right
that's that's thinking now you're thinking uh what was the question what was the topic
it was your favorite metal gear oh um I don't know I I haven't played much of them um I have like
the HD collection that includes two three and uh snake eater I think and I also have
metal gear four I think three is snake eater three yeah three snake eater yeah no wait no yeah three
there's another one there's like a PSP one that's on in the collection oh um uh peace walker
peace walker yeah um one of those uh those are all possible my brothers play those
um they've beaten I think they've beaten like all of them actually I've sort of watched some
some bits of like metal gear solid four I was like oh that's the one where the they have the thing in it
that's the way I'm worried is our old man I don't know much about them I should play them
because I have them why not uh I just I just have the sense in my head that like metal gear is
like the hardest game ever made and you have to be a genius to be able to beat such a video game
why why would you why would you because when I was because I was when I was younger I had
trouble with metal gear solid one I was like okay well I guess I'll never beat this one
and that just that opinion carried through to everything else well I can't play metal gear
solid two uh before beating metal gear solid one and metal gear solid one's impossible so
they're probably all impossible I'm I'm a little baby child and metal gear solid is a video game for
grown-up big boys and I'm and I'm not a grown-up big boy yeah I mean I look at something like crash
bandicoot and I'm like well that's I'm supposed to be able to play that that's a kid's game it's
called goofy it's stupid yeah yeah yeah to play metal gear solid it's like it's like technical
you gotta like you gotta know how to like use a rocket launcher and like you gotta be able to
use your camera to look at things and be smart and I'm like yeah I don't want to do that I want to
go jump jump spin you know I don't know I don't know how radar works what am I uh what am I an
engineer what am I a science guy no no thanks just leave me with my with my with my mascot
platformers with my scrimblow bimblows please yeah scrimblow blimblows only scrimblow bimblows only
you should add that as a you should add that as a race in endless war
scrimblow bimblows just its own its own race of thing you can be except I think it would be too
popular uh okay next voicemail did I post it already yes roof girl comic three two one go
so last pcp episode somebody recommended a comic called roof girl and so he searched it up and it
is actually really fucking hilarious I would highly recommend it I couldn't find it something that
like give and take created like seven years ago and told nobody about uh because it's
really her style of humor and even has like one of the main characters is like a hippo character
so oh like what is this a secret give and take pilot um it's so good and the roof girl is really
charming character design it's a superhero who can only stay on roofs so um she has some tough times
but you know she gets over those tough times and saves the day sometimes it's great check it out
okay it is it is a comic there is uh the first page wait I can't I I clicked on a link and it's
broken uh that I found an almighty roof go okay I found a different thing called roof girl uh yeah
it's it I mean it's spelled the all migty the all migty roof girl uh okay that actually looks
pretty funny I might uh I might check that out later oh that does look yeah it does look like
I drew it a little bit yeah I see I see what I mean yeah huh well how about that how about that
shit um okay next one is called nostalgia critic episode 300 uh
there nostalgia critic episode 300 three two one go so I've been playing this game called
phantom's revenge it's about this cool pony guy with a canon of cold phantom one you'll also
have pet slime droid cold wargene you cool shit love games and slime the main enemy are those
pokemon hedgehog freaks called sonage oh god who could possibly create such a terrific monsters
wait what the fuck she dies in one hit I can't actually use her against most of the enemies
wait attacking cause he'll wait leveling up increases oh it's dug what the fuck oh you didn't
get that yeah oh okay I get it pretty bad it's really bad oh god he lost it well it's my turn I
guess now I'll review slime it's linkara I yeah you would think there's like a wealth of nostalgia
critic voice to to feed into an AI maybe you need to put it all in camps and then it will work
maybe okay next shouty okay next one is called uh red man's ballad three two one go
to the town of ponderville there wrote a stranger one fine day partly spoke to fox around him
didn't have too much to say oh it's true he was wanted and a killer his slime level 10 and four
and his slime hork verified kill count numbered one and 19 more great thanks uh next little
trump reads a bedtime story next one is called crypto three two one go
fuck crypto uh commercials and youtube seems like there's a lot more nowadays
on regardless what video it is even if I say stop seeing this and just keep on coming up
I literally never look up crypto once before my life they they pump a lot of money into marketing
because that's the entirety of the business model is to make people think yeah it's being
it's being pushed it's being pushed it's being pushed onto your feed uh okay the next voicemail
was just a link but uh I just posted the link there and it's broken it doesn't work so sorry oh
hang on there's two forward slashes in there if I do that now two forward slashes
oh I see I see it.com is that a website what is a website what is I see it
meme website I guess
welcome to I'll see it I'll see it visual media network where people can view viral
videos photos memes and upload your viral things also one of the best fun networks
in the world and how it belt girls how is this their logo how does this read as ah see it
uh yeah what that's just heart eyes well I'm looking at these memes these are terrible
what is this fucking website okay um okay whatever uh bizarre bizarre uh next voicemail
is called it's a youtube link uh from how do you feel about this situation at gmail.com
quantum tv review tech usa quantum tv tries to poorly explain away his bigoted hateful posts uh
answer I don't know I don't know how I feel about that who's quantum tv I don't know who who's that
I have no idea I'm not watching the video well okay 20 what don't put youtube video if you got
one us to watch a youtube video later it better be five seconds in the voicemail yeah um next
next voicemail is mage of light three two one go the thing about vosh is that he kept saying that
he's okay with people criticizing the misogyny but whenever someone criticizes the misogyny he keeps
saying that this is sitting ground to jk rallying yeah like well are you okay with being criticized
also like I know this is like it bullshit but if a lot of people have told you that what you did
was wrong and that they don't feel right about it maybe you should just like hear them instead of
being antagonistic towards them like what happened with contra was so fucking stupid and it's
literally like how about just saying hey sorry that's it that was all the thing but he is such
a baby yeah like fucking apologize dude that's it yeah I really think there's no I really think
there's no basis for him to just double down like the thing to do is be like like it's like it's
bad that it's bad that I said that and that like jk used it to like make me look bad and make all
of us look bad and it was embarrassing you like it's not it's not the wrong thing to do is be like
no it was good actually uh yeah I mean I watched his video explaining it and he doesn't he he he
doubled down he doesn't agree that like um it's good for jk rolling but he does agree that it was
misogynistic okay so I'm like okay well whatever so that's bad right yeah like we're all agreed that
that's bad then like yeah the that part of it okay um he thinks he still has an argument I guess it's
like there's an argument there I can't remember exactly what he said um hey it's just such a who
cares like drama fest at the moment I don't like it well it's like man getting all heated about it
all all I can say is like man I got I got some uh just just for like mention for mentioning it on
Twitter I got some I got some bros I got some bros showing up in my dm or not in my replies
and oh my god they're so annoying like yeah like like angry vosh people are like
they're not they're not quite as bad as smaller people but they're they're on the same level
because they'll show up they'll show up and like you can just I can just smell it I can just smell
it through them they think they're gonna show up and they're gonna own me with fax and logic that's
really what they're here to do they show up and they start asking questions they show up and they
just and they start asking questions that are obviously meant for me to answer them in a way
that will like lay a trap that they can catch me in like I that's obviously what they think they're
gonna do to me uh and it's just it's just infuriating I hate them um and uh yeah uh so next one is okay
we got another one from mage of light three two one go also before I forget I mean it's kind of
ironic that man is so angry at vosh because he constantly is doing the ironic misogyny thing or
maybe not ironic who knows I don't think that's true man you're you're so fucking hypocritical
when when was the last time I did that you just name name name an instance that I did that
I don't know what they're saying you're doing ironic misogyny I don't know even if I did I mean
the difference would be well I didn't I didn't get JK Rowling retweeting me saying something like that
and saying like this is this is what men do to me all the time and like I'll never back down from
this sort of bullying right the point is JK Rowling didn't like make it a make it a you know a a a
point in the culture war that's that's the difference even if you're right which I'm not sure if you're
right about that anyway next one is called you know fuck you fuck you it's not hypocritical
it's not hypocritical because it's it's a different situation like a like a like you can you can be
upset that the the the state of affairs is that JK Rowling uh screenshoted something
um the not necessarily like like vosh didn't know that would happen it's I don't think it's
probably a bad thing because he's such a public figure to have done in the first place but then
it's like I don't think vosh is a bad person for being like ha ha women bad like as a joke
like I don't think that makes him a bad person what I do think kind of is is pushing him into
like oh he's sort of just like a bad guy now territory is that when people say
well you know that you know it's bad that misogyny is bad he he doubles down and goes no
it's it's good and here's why no that's what that's what I saw his video that's like uh uh
you know like like the moral necessity of being misogynistic to JK Rowling or whatever
like I didn't watch the video no of course I didn't watch the videos I just saw what
there I just saw what they're called and I saw what he's saying on twitter right I mean that's
entirely the problem is that his is uh he milked he decided to milk the the discourse with a really
inflammatory thumbnail and title of course like the content of the video is obviously a lot less
well not obviously apparently but like it was a lot less actually inflammatory he acknowledges
the misogyny you know it's yeah and it's just like there's more nuance but like nobody who's angry at
vosh would like go to the efforts to like listen to what he's has to say and I don't think I should
have and it's like I'm not gonna I'm not gonna listen to his three hour stream because then it's
a 20 minute clip but if I don't want to listen even that's too much uh I don't want I'm not
gonna turn into one of these vosh people they're terrible uh the message the message that it's
putting out okay it's it's it's a little bit bullshit it's a little bit bullshit for for you to
like okay you title you title your video something that clearly implies one thing and then in the
video maybe you you put in there a little secret thing you put in there like oh well actually
I don't know I don't actually think what it's not it's not it's not my fault it's not my fault
that the message I take from that is that you think the thing you titled your video because
you were deliberately deceptive about it uh so yeah I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure that when he has
20 minutes to like talk about it I'm sure it comes across as much more nuanced than the title of the
video but I don't feel like uh I've made an error or anything by taking away from that the message
that is like he's doubling down on misogyny it's yeah it's it's it's a fair like assessment I guess
all right it's just um and I absolutely will not seed ground and I absolutely will not seed
ground and given to the bullying of the vosh freaks who just want to be like did you watch the stream
did you watch the stream here I'll link you a video watch this video yeah I won't like it's
I think it's what was annoying me about it most is like you know people are misunderstanding things
from both sides and like information is getting like not fully understood and people are like
living their lives and this is just sort of a blip and it's like you know twitter like
what is your opinion on this thing and like nobody is should be expected to go on an expedition
before they can give their opinion yeah um but I wish they either did that or just didn't give
the opinion if they don't know what is happening exactly I feel like it's it's too normal it's
too normal to be expected to say your piece on something before you understand it and that's
why a lot of shit happens and it's completely unimportant yeah well uh I guess I understand
what you're saying but uh I don't know I just really I just really don't like I just really
don't like the messaging that's coming out from like the vosh camp I really don't like I really
don't like it at all it's it's stupid yeah um anyway fuck you mage of light I'm not a hypocrite
uh I won't uh just let you uh say that shit to me it's not true uh next one is uh insubstantial
update to Texas anti trans oh great I can't wait to have this I can't wait to receive an
insubstantial update on the situation uh three two one go so earlier in the week I left a voicemail
about uh the anti trans stuff going on in Texas and the update is we don't really know what's
going on they're still appealing stuff that's that's what I said Texas DFS was asked if they're
still doing the investigations into families of trans kids and they gave like a non-answer so
who knows in funnier news ken paxton tweeted an obvious cancel bait tweet about how Rachel
Levine is a man and then uh the twitter made an exception to not delete his tweet but just flag
it as offensive because he's a public official but they he still went on and made another tweet
decrying big tech censorship about it anyway and is tweeting more like obvious cancel bait and it's
really hilariously transparent what he's doing is Rachel Levine that swimmer who I've been seeing
on twitter lately for the one who won a thing I don't know there's like a very tall trans woman
swimmer who like Charlie Kirk or someone was like tweeting about you know oh drag out the
trans women in women's sports thing the only time we care the only time we care about women's sports
is when we can use it as a wedge issue yeah against the people we don't like okay uh
so yeah I guess we don't know whether they're doing as I thought the bad stuff as I thought
well I hope they don't do the bad stuff I hope uh I was I was I remember seeing that like there was
a judge you know ruling an unconstitutional and I remember I remember being relieved like okay
I'm glad this isn't just just going unchallenged I heard Joe Biden say something about it as well
I feel like oh yeah Biden was pro Biden's auntie but the Biden administration is like this is bad
so that's pretty yeah but like are you gonna do anything about it Joe you know that's fair
what are you gonna do huh where are your thoughts and prayers thoughts and prayers from the from
the Biden administration uh they said um they released a press oh it was like um
the like the national sorry I don't remember exactly what agency but some national agency
released a press uh release that was like you know our you know the the national agency you know
offers like uh you know support you know you know in spite of like you know the like state uh
like if if any family feels they've been discriminated against on the basis of like
you know race sex a sexual orientation gender identity you know our agency you know we can
you file a complaint with us and we will you know help with that or something so it's good
it's good this is cool I guess uh anyway it's a developing situation um next one is called
tournament arcs three two one go
in episode 300 you talked about how lazy tournament arcs are and I can't agree more I can't believe
that Ben zane fruit one into the champion you're wrong you're wrong there's not an there's not a
tournament arc in the champion that just takes merely a tournament there is merely a tournament
but like story is not really about that uh story is not really anything because it's just like the
intro chapter like a tournament arc is a very specific sort of you have all of these characters
in a a story that involves a lot of special types of magic fighting powers and stuff you
put them up against people and to see who wins and it's just a long uh series of fights but like
the context for the fights is like a competition whereas usually it's like we're trying to do
something and save the world or stop someone bad I that's why it would be lazy is because it's like
what if we just got rid of the story from this battle manga and just had battles instead
yeah but that's not I mean you know I mean a good it's not it's not a bad good tournament arc
you know has a story going on it's yeah sure sure but like like the laziest way to do it is for
whatever story is going on to be put on hold while we punch each other for a bit right it's been
done badly before yeah uh um I'll get man I'll get I'll get back to the champion when I know
what it is that I want to say with it and also when I get over the feeling that in my gut
that I am too ashamed and embarrassed of myself to say anything ever uh one day
what do you mean like like the the the moral of the champion yeah you don't want to actually come
out and say anything about it it's not that it's that I it's that I don't it's that I don't really
know what the uh the real champion was the friends we made along the way I feel I feel like I could
ending I feel like I could say something I could I could have a message in there there's a kind
there's a couple different ones I could have and like I just I would just have to settle on like
here's what I want the message to be and here's exactly how I'm going to go about saying it and
I don't know exactly what that is yet uh so it's going to be it's going to be an allegory it's going
to be capitalism is bad for capitalism it's going to be an allegory for youtubeing and and
and and uh Sophia is a youtuber she's burnt out that's what she doesn't like making her youtube
videos that get slay queen and everyone loves them it's about being an only fans uh sex worker and
how uh it's it's a real job actually it's real work it's an allegory and then all the people
say I want to be just like you and it's like yeah it sucks exactly everybody everybody wants to be
an only fans girl or guy uh anyway okay we're almost done by the way you've got like two more
okay I think yeah yeah the next one is an image oh the procrastinators podcast is a show where a
bunch of content creators pick a topic and talk about it so no one cares anymore and we take
viewer questions on twitter where is this yeah what is this from is this like on the youtube page
I don't know what the lines are no the the youtube channel description just says like under construction
is this from the website is it um let's check I'm just thinking like what what has these like
like very faint gray lines behind on the white background uh backdrop I don't know
what is our is our podcast the is our website the pro crap yeah the procrastinators podcast
dot com uh is there an about section it's a true mystery I don't know this is inside the animus
an assassins creed yeah I have no idea where where this I have no idea where this copy comes from
um all right whatever it'll be it'll be a mystery forever um okay and then fittingly our last
voicemail of the day is called wait yeah it's called a one last message three two one go
hello comrades nicole here calling my god vulgar heaven he yeah he's giving me a chance to send
you one last message the nicole I would like to say he loves you very much and you'd like to
say goodbye nicole I go back to vulgar heaven where you can drink vulgar forever yeah goodbye
comrades it was good knowing you see you nicole uh why you gotta give him a why you gotta give him
a heartfelt send off like that oh gee I'll miss him I didn't know I didn't know how much I'd miss him
till he was gone nicole even just in the in the duration of this this uh episode yeah I've gone
from ambivalence he's gone tragedy he had a family did he yeah his brother his brother
let us know he was dead oh right yes uh all right well that's a lot I didn't see this
his brother it was his brother that's the end of the voicemails which is probably just about the
end of the podcast yeah uh go check out the pumpkin alley the new hot-fixed version see if you can
find all the lizards including the new one will that be out by the time this is out um it yeah
okay pretty pretty pretty sure it will be um the only thing we're waiting on is like feedback to see
whether something works on a mac version and if it does then we just set it live because it's already
uploaded hey what did you make a pumpkin alien what did what did you make pumpkin alien uh unity
in unity okay uh you know I was talking to crack and like I I want to get phantom's revenge going on
I wanted to run an html so I can put it on new grounds and I probably want to like maybe convert
to a bunch of platforms and I just I was thinking maybe I could maybe pay someone like on five or
something to do that because I don't want to do it um and I and crack said he would look at it and he
might be able to just do it and he told me that like oh actually he can't because um he uses linux
and like game maker studio just doesn't run on linux like even in in wine like it just doesn't
run you can you can make a game project for linux but you can't run the program that there's no
version of the program that runs on linux which seems insane uh linux is so odd it feels like it
only has drawbacks I mean I don't really uh the people that like it really like it but I don't know
why exactly from what I from what I gather is like it's a version of windows or whatever
that has stripped away unnecessary background um processes uh that like slow down the machine
and that don't literally need to be there um and so you as a user can customize the experience of
your computing experience you know your computing experience is perfectly customizable
and there's no like a windows update is forcing you to do something and it won't let you not do it
like well linux does not have that and that's like I think is the appeal is the total control over
your computing uh time yeah but I'm like it's like it's like the opposite direction to apple where
there's so much less control than you have over windows where you can you can see all the program
files and stuff and yeah in a mac that's possible but it's like it's harder like it there's just
super easy like consumer friendly apple product windows for like everyone this just is useful
and then linux for the nerds is what I understand indeed yeah it's for computer it's for people that
like know the enthusiasts and look that with a computer which I don't really know on that level
what I'm doing yeah uh so anyway uh I do I do really want to get it running on html and uh
and put it on new grounds at some point uh I just uh I just want to do it just want to do it it might
be mm-hmm I had I had started converting I had started converting it but it was
turning out to be a little bit of work and I gave up I'm like I just can I just pay someone
like 50 bucks to do this for me uh yeah I wonder if you could put 3d games on uh new grounds uh
I mean and I don't see why not like in theory it would have to be uh it would browse a version
rather than just a game file that you can run and executable it'd have to literally work in
browser so probably not I mean I I made um like the champion game runs in browser that one runs
html it's not a downloadable executable downloadable yeah but it's like a two-dimensional game and it's
not like a million things going yeah yeah but like there's nothing um there's nothing about
it's like you know 2d-ness I don't I don't see why a 3d game wouldn't work in html um well I know
3d games that do work in html I just I guess I just don't know enough I feel like the pumpkin alley
demo has a little too much to process for like the browser to handle it hmm I don't know how it
works though I maybe it just defaults to the computer handling it instead of the browser but
then how's it be on the browser wow I don't run away from snakes did work in browser but it took
a really long time to load and that's a much smaller game right yeah um I got no idea but uh
but I just really want I just really want fandoms revenge on newgrounds I want on every
platform I think I'm definitely gonna try and put it on steam at some point just because
I might I might change the music I might have to change the music because I stole the music from
front mission gun hazard you know how it goes what are you gonna do they're gonna make music for it
I I was talking to Nate about it the other day actually when we were talking about finance stuff
he seemed to think that the thing to do was just to commission like sound to like music which
yeah I could do that it seems like so unnecessary but like I guess if it makes the difference and it
makes it's so like it's so like bankrupt it's like creatively bankrupt like hey hey musician could you
like make me a song that like basically sounds exactly like this other song like it's it's different
but like just make it sound like this other song okay okay bye uh like how like how sad you know
um but that's all like like I but I you know like uh the game is it has like events in it that are
very specifically timed to like the timing of the music like I really I sort of made the scene
sort of around the music that is in them sometimes so there's really no way around it if I if I wanted
new music in there so I don't know I guess so yeah I could do that or I could just upload it with
the music intact and like just be like Square Enix will never notice because it's like from an old
game that nobody cares about and like that's true I don't know I don't know what I'll do about that
but I know that I want it on there just just to say yeah it's on steam Lamal
okay uh what do you think are we done I think we're done I think we're done yeah okay uh
patreon.com slash the procrastinators um I think we got some bonus episodes that have not been
posted yet that need posting uh like uh like behind the scenes bonus episode compilation things yeah I
think ellie is our made some and we just haven't posted them um so we should get on that uh okay
patreon um like comment subscribe uh play fantasy revenge uh check out the pumpkin alley uh patch
oh tom just got back to me oh my god oh jeez okay oh my god is this gonna this is gonna be the tom
fix the thing moment oh god he he replied to me with like a big thing I think he's telling me how to
do it uh uh he said he'll okay he he says he'll take a look he also explained to me how to do it
all right I might okay so maybe this issue will be solved soon okay happy ending maybe I still hate
you voicemailers all of you um okay goodbye it's the end of the episode the end it's the cliffhanger ending