Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am the best guy ever, which is a temporal designation, cause cool things used to happen, but I've always been the best.
Oh, I longed for those days when I was the best, which is also now. Also, Hippocrit is here.
I forgot how it went. The bad leg, that's why you're sitting there, I kicked your leg out.
Fuck you. You ruined it, Davoo. You ruined everything by fucking up your audio.
It's a good intro and it's gone now. It's gone forever.
Jesse's here, Endless Jess.
I am the mighty toer, a hinga-dinga-derigan. I love the Swedish meatballs.
Tommy Oliver. What's up, dude?
I got to recover my formula to defeat the Jews. It was there and now it's gone.
Oh god, without context, it just sounds like you're an anti-Semite.
Oh no. I mean, he is.
And our mutual mortal enemy, Davoo. Thank you for joining us.
So we're all feeling very nostalgic today. That was the topic of the episode.
We recorded an intro, you guys. It was a glorious intro, but it died. It was deleted.
It's in the sands of history at the sands of time now.
The thing that's quite apt is that it wasn't even that good, but we all love it because it was in the past and it's gone forever.
Oh my god. That's so apropos. That's absolutely true. It was total shit.
Garbage. It was garbage.
But I love it. It's my intro.
Yes. Many shit intros, but that one was ours.
But anyway, let's just, we're going to talk about nostalgia. What's the fucking deal with it?
And luckily, we have the world's foremost expert on nostalgia, Hippocrite, here with us to tell us everything we need to know.
The nostalgia critic's here?
Oh no. God, please.
He critiqued my video. That's what he did. That's all he's known for.
Wow. That epic review of one video made by Hippocrite.
Hippo, what is nostalgia? What is it?
It is. I love for a simpler time, usually an earlier time.
I mean, it's probably an earlier because you can't have nostalgia for the future.
But the point is, it's a time before, and you really wish you could go back.
And things from that time are sort of, they make you feel good just by reminding you of that time.
And that's generally, I think, what it is.
Hey, you know, I looked up the definition on Urban Dictionary, and the description is boring, but there's something interesting here.
So the top definition of nostalgia on Urban Dictionary just says,
And also, the condition of being homesick, homesickness, and there's no examples.
So this is one they didn't really give a shit about.
But underneath it, it just says photos and videos, and there's just one picture there, and it is a PlayStation 1.
And I'm like, yeah, dude, yeah, that is so fucking apt.
You know what, speaking of PlayStation 1, the thing that always gets me, that like hits that nostalgia bone,
is when you actually plug in the PlayStation 1 and press power, and you get that BOOM!
Yeah!
That's the best.
I don't get why consoles don't do that shit anymore.
When did they give up?
Like, did they give up after Gamecube, which was the best one?
Like, I just thought, okay, we're done now.
I don't know, that PS1 sound was like the coolest sound of all time.
And then it started the game, and then it had like a sequel like Little China.
Yeah, there were two of them on the PS1.
I'm so fucking ready!
And then the game was never as good as that sound.
And like, even like when you would play like PS1 games on like the PS3 when it was backwards compatible,
it would have the second one, it would have the second one of like the logo, but it didn't have the BOOM!
It didn't have that part.
Well, you know what? I've been playing like PS1 games on PS3 for so long.
I forgot that that was the first blang.
Yeah, it was the first blang!
You know, when I think of that sound, I always inevitably follow it up in my mind with, there's that
And then after the PlayStation 1 thing resolves, I just hear that
The Final Fantasy IX intro is what comes to my mind immediately.
That was the first PS1 game that I got super invested in, so yeah, I'm exactly the same.
Hey, you know, Final Fantasy VII would have taken it, but there is no like song that plays when you get to the title screen of Final Fantasy VII.
That's why it's the worst game.
I still have my original PlayStation, and I just like, not even plugging it in, just clicking the open the latch button,
and it goes kching with the spring sound.
And you love that shit.
And like the fucking Game Boy transitioning to the DS was the same problem where the Game Boy Advance was
Dwaaaang.
Yeah, yeah.
Then the DS was just dun-nun-nun-nun-nun.
Yeah, it was pretty shit.
What the fuck?
It was definitely less cool.
It was like way less cool.
What was interesting was that the Game Boy Advance, like visual that a Component had more like visual complexity than the DS one.
The DS one just kind of faded in, but like the Game Boy was like, look, we could do 3D-esque things now.
Isn't this cool?
I wonder why they stopped doing that.
I know why.
I'll tell you why.
It's fucking big government.
That's what this problem is.
Big government coming in here.
Fucking crippling our beautiful game intros.
You know what's funny is that I was actually questioning it myself, and I was actually thinking of a not ironic answer
that was kind of similar along the same lines.
Oh yeah?
If you want to hear my logic, but that's not really the topic of today, so.
I was thinking it's my aesthetic sensibilities have changed.
Well, I think it might be more to do with the fact that they're also making like huge menus
for consoles instead of just like, you know.
Yeah.
Honestly, I was honestly like unironically thinking it may have something to do with the Sherman Antitrust Act.
Wow.
What do they do?
What's your, what's the connection there?
Well, because I was thinking about Microsoft, right?
Because like Windows 95 had all this personality.
You know, its intro was like Brian Eno.
How'd it go?
No, no, no, that's the fucking Game Boy one.
You know, dude, fuck, I can't even do it.
It's such a complex melody.
I can't even enunciate it.
It's pretty, I know the one.
In the 2000s, they just kind of gave up on that shit.
And I'm like, hmm, what changed about Microsoft in that time period?
Oh, well that would have been when Bill Gates was kicked out of the leading role,
and that's when the government cracked down on their supposed monopolies,
and they had to rearrange a bunch of shit.
So maybe the government said, don't have personality.
Don't lead people to think you have personality.
And then like all the other tech companies followed from Microsoft's example.
So yeah.
All I want to say to that taboo is correlation does not necessarily imply causation.
Well, it's the best theory I can come up with.
Well, I mean, Apple still has that chime that they've had since like the early 90s.
Well, they haven't like done anything with it for like 10 years, though.
Yeah, but they're a bunch of fucking millennial scum, Apple.
I wasn't trying to defend it.
I wasn't trying to defend it, but they haven't fucking...
The sound is boring.
I haven't fucking...
I haven't really liked Crash Bandicoot 3.
They still use the same goddamn phones and the same design.
You know, you jump around, you spin.
Who, Apple?
That's so cool.
You want to talk about nostalgia.
You know, first level of Crash Bandicoot 3, you get the wizard,
you hit him with your attack.
That's good.
My...
When we...
When we bought a PlayStation 1, I remember this day so well.
Now, this is a day I'm very nostalgic for.
We had had like a Super Nintendo and like a Game Boy and a couple little...
And an original Nintendo for a few years.
But we went, we...
Me and my brother pooled our money, bought ourselves a PlayStation 1.
My dad, out of the kindness of his heart, bought us a dedicated TV to use with it.
Whoa.
And the two games we brought home, this old-ass tube TV that's still in my house and works to this day,
and we bought ourselves Crash Bandicoot 1 and Final Fantasy 7,
were the two games that we brought home that day.
That is a solid story.
It was a magical...
It was a magical day.
I'll never forget it.
Writing in the car home with my family that I loved, that was great.
You know, what...
That reminds me of like a feeling I've had that I've missed,
is like the idea of just having a console and having just a couple games on it,
and just switching between them, because like you don't have real money.
Like you got...
Oh yeah, if I'm tired of playing Crash, then let's go for a fucking epic Final Fantasy sort of.
It forces you to like explore every nuance of what made the games good.
As opposed to now, you've got 20,000 Steam games, so you play them each for like two minutes,
and you don't really get the worst.
Yeah, what I was thinking is, because I've long felt that I don't have like nostalgic feelings,
but like lately I'm thinking something I definitely have nostalgic feelings for is video games,
but not video games in general, but like specific moments or aspects of very specific video games.
Because like I've been playing through Earthbound for the first time,
and there's so many moments where I'm like, oh sweet, that's cool.
That was like a fun little charming moment.
And then I think, man, if I had been playing this when I was nine,
which wouldn't have been possible, it wasn't localized.
If I'd been playing this like ten years ago.
Are you talking about Earthbound or Mother 3 or something?
No, Earthbound, yeah, yeah, Mother 2.
And like every single one of those moments would have been like amazing to me at the time,
because it would have taken me like so much longer to figure out, you know?
That's true, that's true.
That was a key of like having a lot of nostalgia for so many moments for Mario and Luigi Superstar Sack.
It was because I hadn't played any RPGs before, so I had no idea how to play them,
and I didn't know like where to look up to like get hints.
So like I would get stuck on certain moments for weeks,
just pouring over all the little details of everything,
and not having any other entertainment to go to.
So yeah, it was really like being stuck in this like void with nothing but you and this one thing,
and this one little problem you have to figure out.
And you spend so much time on it, you really get attached to it.
But now, now that I have gaming skills, they all just kind of come and go so quickly
that they don't leave as much impact.
I've got to cut in and just remind the people out there that yes,
I too have nostalgia for Mario and Luigi Superstar Saga.
That does not mean it is not also just objectively the greatest game ever made.
It is a really good game.
There is no amount of nostalgia will color the fact that it is the best game ever made,
and fuck you if you disagree.
Yeah, it's a really good game.
As Nate said earlier, like I'm an expert on nostalgia,
because only I think because I made a video called why nostalgia is a good thing.
I can't actually remember what I said, but I think what the point was,
was there's a difference between a nostalgic enjoyment of something
and an actual enjoyment in a way.
I think, actually, forget it.
I can't remember whether that was my point,
and I don't know whether I even agree with that video.
Well, we should all go watch that video again.
Everyone go to Hippocrates, like the first video on the channel.
Well, do go to Hippocrates.
No, do it. You have no choice. Go watch it.
But I was going to expand a little bit on what Jesse was saying before
about how I definitely agree that just the changing dynamics of the game's market,
having flooded, just flooded games like Duck Game and things like that
that are built to be like sort of like popcorn games,
like consumable party games that you don't really necessarily have to spend a lot of time with.
They're designed to be like let's played once, and that's right.
Like that's like their whole source of revenue,
is people watch goofy let's plays and buy them and never play them,
because they're garbage games.
I got way more out of Duck Game than I get out of most online multiplayer games.
I don't know about you.
Duck Game is pretty fun, but I don't really have any of the popcorn games out there
that are made just to be less played, like I Am Bread or something.
Like nobody actually cares about that game, but it was made for like one week.
I don't have to speak for...
Definitely that kind of game for sure.
Right. I can only speak for myself here, but I much...
I mean, okay, this is literally just me, and I don't know how many people this applies to,
but I way prefer like playing games alone, a single one-player experience,
getting absorbed in it.
I have been playing this last week or two near Automata,
and I near as a great series because it gives you the thing that I crave most out of a video game,
like it incentivizes you with in-game rewards to basically 100% it.
And that is the best thing that every game gives you, that a game could give me.
It encourages me to explore the breadth and the width of the content of the game,
both in terms of story, in terms of mechanics,
it forces you to figure out how to do stuff the optimal way.
It gets you to be invested in all the characters,
and found out all the little side stories that have been planted there.
So like, you know, this was something that was kind of forced on us.
Doesn't IM's breadth also force you to explore the breadth of the game?
Oh!
Well, it was just...
Back in the day, we were kind of...
Back in the day, you didn't really have to force players,
at least when we were kids at the very least,
you didn't have to give strong incentives for people to explore all of games,
because you would just do that because you had five games.
Of course, you're going to play them a thousand times and figure it out.
But in the current market, I really think it definitely pays,
and gives your game the kind of longevity and the good long runtime
to give, to structure it in such a way to encourage fully exploring it.
There's a number of times where I'll decide I'm going to just play a video game
and not do anything else for a day,
and not accomplish something by being able to focus that much.
And I'm like, wow, this is kind of sad that attention span is so scattershot
and tiny now because of social media and shit,
that I legitimately feel accomplished by playing a video game consistently.
Yeah, something that was not hard.
Like 100%ing a game, or like beating a game,
now like to me, just turning on a game and sitting down and playing it for 10 minutes
feels like something I worked for.
It feels like an accomplishment.
It's like a huge library of games that I haven't touched.
And it's weird because we're talking about nostalgia
and how we used to be way more invested in games back in the day.
And I think so much of it is just that, like we were saying,
because we don't have a lot of money and you only had a few options.
Because it's not even, I don't think so much that games are designed differently now.
I think it's just because I have disposable income.
Because I have like, right now I have 15 PS4 games,
50 PS3 games, and 70-something PS2 games
and I've played like maybe 10% of each of those.
And like, those are the games that like, they have depth.
They weren't designed for like, let's plays.
Like most of them predated let's plays.
But I just play them for like 10 minutes and I'm like,
oh, we're both the next one.
Or I just don't touch them at all and they just sort of shelf them.
It's impossible to not be nostalgic like just for video games as a whole as you get older
because you have no fucking time to play them anymore.
It feels like you have to force yourself to relax.
And like you said, they still make games that have a lot of depth,
that like reward a lot of investment.
I've had the last Guardian since November.
I haven't played it yet.
I have Breath of the Wild.
I haven't beaten it yet.
I'm only like a little bit into the game.
What do I do every time I turn on the fucking PS4?
I just play Binding of Isaac for an hour.
That's all I can fucking do every day.
It's the same game.
It's the same fucking thing every time.
It's just running around in room shooting shit.
But it's the only fucking thing I can invest in anymore
because fucking putting my brain into a Zelda game for 40 hours
seems more taxing to me than playing 40 different hour-long runs of the stupid Isaac game.
Yeah, I feel like a little bit of reason.
I hate you Binding of Isaac.
I hate you Florian.
You'll never be in Binding of Isaac.
Florian really.
It's all your fault.
I feel like a lot of the reason I do like a video game review show
is so that I can play games because there's a reason to do it.
Like Let's Plays, they take a lot of time,
which is why I turn to streaming now for like,
oh yeah, I want to play an old game,
but I can't be bothered because I got stuff to do.
And the games I'm like reviewing,
they're also games I have to play and I enjoy doing,
you know, recording them and playing them for stuff.
But the streaming is like, that's like, yeah,
I could sit down and play a game for a few hours
and it can be fun and it won't even be feeling like I'm an idiot.
And it's great.
You know what this kind of reminds me of?
It's just, I know I've said it before,
but even something like this podcast basically exists for the reason,
at least to me, for forcing us to be able to talk to each other
and do something together.
Like that's why I like to do it in order to get this game out of it.
I cannot motivate myself to do anything ever
if it is not feeding into some grand design goal
that will pay off in five years.
I think that is probably the big fucking mental change
that has happened with social media and stuff.
I feel like now that nothing I do or say has any sort of legitimacy
unless it's projected onto some social network so strangers can see it,
and it's really weird,
because I've just been doing a bunch of work for myself
the last couple of weeks in the beginning.
I was really jonesing on it,
and now I just feel like desperate for validation of what I've done.
It's just like a disgusting degeneracy of the mind,
being conditioned by like,
you have to have the clicks, you have to have the likes,
you have to have the views,
and it's just like, I can't just do shit anymore.
I think it's why I don't play video games or anything anymore,
because I have to stream it or I have to make a video about it,
or what's the fucking point?
Well, for me, I don't need attention.
I don't need people looking at it in the meantime.
It just has to be feeding towards something,
which I've been using game design as the excuse.
I'm like, well, I want to make a game with this, this, that, that,
and this mechanics in it.
But I want to make sure I've played all the important games
that have these mechanics in them,
so that I know I'm doing it right.
So I just wrote out a giant fucking list of all the games
I've been wanting to play my whole life,
and I'm like, I have to play them now.
So Earthbound was first on the list pretty much.
So for me, I'm having a great time.
I found the perfect excuse that's just an endless well
of perfectly, mentally, and emotional justification
to play all the stuff I've always wanted to play.
Well, that's good.
But it is sort of a similar motivation to what Tom was saying.
It is towards an end goal.
Well, I think, I don't know whether all of that
is necessarily like a downward sort of thing.
It used to be better when we were kids
and we would just do something for no reason.
I think it was where I didn't like it as much
as when I was a kid, because I felt like, even as a kid,
I was just sitting around trying to come up
with some sort of grand design for my life,
and I couldn't come up with anything at the time.
Well, yeah, I mean, what I'm saying is like nostalgia
is not necessarily inherently better than the current.
I think sometimes you look at the past
and you're sort of like rose-tinted goggles
or whatever you say.
Oh, I have no rose-tinted goggles for anything.
I think everything in my life is better now
than it was when I was younger.
Well, yeah.
Yeah, but things like this, like streaming,
I actually legitimately enjoy it a lot,
and I don't think it's too bad that I feel the need
to play a game on a live streaming platform
instead of by myself.
It's just fun.
It's like somebody's talking with me in the room,
like, yeah, I got friends over, kind of.
And it's kind of a replacement for, like,
because I don't actually have friends in real life.
Well, but...
Yeah, those are gay anyway.
It's...
You know, it's...
I don't know.
I think things are good.
War has changed, dude. War has changed.
The way that we conduct ourselves
is social media has changed the game forever,
and I don't know if we'll ever go back to the way it was.
I mean, there's a lot of...
Nier Automata is an oddly appropriate game
to have just played, because there's all this stuff
about how, like, all the robots,
and it's fucking robots doing shit,
like, they're all networked,
and they all kind of relate to each other
in different ways than a human-talking,
you know, person-to-person does,
and, like, you're able to...
You're able to kind of use your consciousness
through different bodies.
It's this whole complex thing,
but all I'm getting at is that
the way that we relate to each other
by having this electronic network of communication
as opposed to just verbal,
or, like, fucking smoke signals or whatever,
it's way different,
and it's only getting more different
and more different than, like, humanity was
at its inception,
and these are real fundamental changes
to us biologically in the way that we live in this world.
I think the way I see it is, like,
is that, like, you know,
hanging out with people in real life
with no fucking cameras anywhere, no recording.
That's still good.
You know, that's the classic.
It's been around forever.
You can still enjoy it,
but, you know,
talking to people,
having an extended Twitter rave about something
is also fun.
It's a new thing.
You know, one does not have to permanently
kick out the other,
and, you know,
sitting around playing a video game for 10 hours
is also a thing that you could do with your time.
I don't walk away from any one of these activities
feeling more or less satisfied than the others.
It's like, if I just play the video game for 10 hours,
I have this feeling in my mind of, like,
oh, God, I didn't do anything,
but play a video game for 10 hours.
But, like, if I just hang out with, like, friends all day,
I'll end it with the same feeling of,
wow, I didn't do anything,
but hang out with friends all day.
Like, it doesn't matter.
After I hang out with friends,
I feel like ending it too, my man.
I know what you mean.
It's just, like, there's just, there's just nothing.
In my opinion, there's nothing,
there's no one thing you can do with your time
that feels like the definitively perfect thing
to do with your time.
Everything you do is shutting...
Everything you do is closing the door
on everything else you could be doing with your time, you know?
So everything is a huge trade-off.
Everything lacks something.
So just don't worry about it.
It's my philosophy.
I've, uh...
Hmm.
I've heard the...
I don't know if I agree with that,
but I can respect it.
Hmm?
Because, like, I don't know.
I guess in my opinion,
I guess at the top of that up now.
That's the end of the PCP podcast.
It's over.
At last.
I don't know if I agree with that,
but I can respect it.
No more shows.
No more episodes.
All right.
We're done.
Well, I mean, I guess, I guess because me,
I just, like, my...
I just...
Working is always, like, the number one thing,
and if I'm not working on something,
like, if I'm not working on, like, an animation
or a drawing or a writing or something like that,
something productive,
like, there's always this creeping feeling in the back of my mind
that, like, you should be doing that.
So I'll play video...
Like, I used to play video games for hours and hours
and hours and hours.
Like, I wouldn't do homework in high school.
I would, like, lie and say,
I have no homework.
Like, for, like, two months now.
I just play video games,
like, until I have to go to bed.
Oh, well...
Oh, yeah.
Don't misinterpret.
There are lots and lots of things
I don't feel very happy doing.
I basically listed off three of the only ones.
Let's see.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Saying really interesting stuff on Twitter,
like, making a really interesting narrative
on social media that will always be great
to go back to.
I guess on Twitter,
it's hard to go back to it.
What the fuck ever.
Playing with good friends
who are interesting to talk to.
Playing an actually good video game
that isn't, like, just, you know,
fucking one of those fucking, like,
roguelike games.
Those fucking meme games, dude.
Those fucking meme games.
Yeah, one of those roguelike games, like,
I was getting kind of depressed
playing Nuclear Throne too much back in the day.
I was like, okay, I need to cut this out.
It's the same shit every time, you know.
And also working on a project.
Nuclear Throne, is that called
Donald Trump simulator?
Oh, ho, ho.
Oh, ho.
Oh, shit.
Oh, man, I am so nostalgic
for Donald Trump jokes.
Remember back in the day
when we used to,
when everyone used to make fun
of Donald Trump.
What happened to that?
Bring it back, I say.
Oh, yeah, bring it back, please.
We need more.
Not enough making fun of Donald Trump
on the internet.
You know, ever since I'm with her one,
ever since Pokémon Go to the polls won,
it's been, you know, just boring.
You know, we've just been Pokémon
going to the polls every day since,
And no one's been taking time to stop smell the roses and make fun of Donald Trump
Did you guys know that his skin is orange like Cheeto dust?
What what tell me more?
Also, I have it on I don't believe you. I have it on good authority
His hands
Well are small big oh
Oh
Wait, but how does this affect his dick size? What's the relationship here? I mean well
That's the real heart of the matter
I think I think the issue is that his hands are smaller than like a regular man's hands should be so maybe also
His penis is smaller than a regular man's penis should be which see that's why he's not my president
That's why I should have my election. That's why we all Pokemon went to the polls. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm feels good
It feels good to be a an active member of the
Socialist liberal agenda trying to you know anarchist for life. It's uh, it feels good
I don't know how true this is
I'd like you all to comment on whether you think it's true, but I've heard that
Millennials and 90 kid 90s kids or whatever they feel more nostalgic for their youth than previous generations
Because I've got a reason for that because the okay, go ahead things have like
technology and stuff has just
Accelerated during that time to the point where you you grow up playing with toys and then you're an adult and you've gone through
So many consoles and video games and things and now it's just so weird like
We're like mm-hmm because like our generation like
Guys my age like 25 to 30 or whatever like we are the very last
Generation that will ever have existed without the internet
Yeah, and I can remember a time in my life when like the internet entered my life and changed everything forever
And I remember what it was like before that line wire Dave line wire
That's why I feel like I feel this like weird like disconnect with people who are even like like four or five years younger than me
Because they they grew up they have this there's this culture and this language of like everything's fucking ironic
Everyone is like taking pride in being an autistic or like a shitty person and it's just a tag irony is a purely destructive force
It's it's weird like I
Like the this feeling that like that like people get for like generations 20 years their junior of like all these these young kids
Nowadays, they don't know shit. They're all fucking weird and psychotic
I feel that way about people five years younger than me because there's like a huge fucking divide
In and it's like a whole new way of thinking. Oh god. I just hate them. I hate young people
That's it. I'm with you and I agree with you on all that the technological
The rapid technological advancement, I mean you had definitely has created a a cultural tag the young all sex and nothing else
There is the the real phenomenon that the Millennials are the first generation in like I possibly ever
I think that actually has a worse economic
Foothold than the generation that came before them. We're over the tipping point with our generation
Well, that was hopefully it doesn't stay that way, but that's where it is
That was a point that I made a while ago
I don't remember where but I was just like I wonder if the reason the Millennials are so nostalgic for the 90s and shit
It's because we're the first generation that has nothing really to look forward to it's because when we were kids
We didn't have to worry about you know all kinds of bull. I mean that was I'm like the case for people who were born in the 30s
Like hold on. There was that whole 10-year period where the economy was total shit. So I'm sure it was the same thing for that
I don't know what that is
Well
Say to say it's the only time it's like an exaggeration
I think we're we're the first generation to really have some perspective on how doomed we are as a species because we're the first
Generation to like have the knowledge available to us that like in 20 years the fucking one world
Government is going to be raising all of our children the internet. Yeah, it's something
I think that is really fucking with our generation because it's fucking with me and I hate it because it's something that I never
Stressed to it when I was a little kid and it was it only started when the internet happened is this really like
broad world-wide perspective of how mediocre I am
Hmm because because like like back in the day before the internet you could do stuff
Like you know like when you sat down and play Pokemon with your friends or whatever
You're like, oh man
I'm like one of the best people at Pokemon or it's like I think there's 10 people I knew who played Pokemon now like I want to
Like make videos and do drawings and shit
I have access to the internet and I can see people in like fucking Taiwan who are like 10 years old who are gonna be better than
I'll ever be in my entire life and it's completely changed this perspective of like how good you are at things
What the like the bell curve of talent is and also like it set expectations
That like the the exceptions to the rule have risen to the top in this interconnected world and become the new norm
So it feels like that's the standard. I feel like I feel like some of that a lot of that came through from TV
Anyway, like TV and magazines
Cuz like with TV like the celebrities were at a distance, but now like Pewdiepie is just a dude in his fucking room
Well, like I get that I get that like the um, you know that that there's like a worldwide perspective of how mediocre you are
Like you said, I don't think you're mediocre by the way, but that's what you said
Um, I like I feel the opposite like for me the problem is that I have this worldwide perspective on how mediocre the world is and how
I'm just
Everyone is psychotic and like everyone is evil
It's it's that's that's my nightmare and it's awakened like I wake up to every morning
It's kind of similar to I was just having an existential crisis about this other day
And I mean I always know this on an intellectual level
But it really hit me as I was again playing near and which deals a lot with like the role of humanity and the end of civilization
All that shit like no matter what I do in my life
None of it will matter at all because even if humanity lives a billion years the universe will end and nothing will
Absolutely no traces will be left no matter what I do
I'm I'm fucking banking on the idea that we're gonna have like a billion years. We can hop dimensions. We can hop dimensions
Theoretically, yeah, yeah, that's what I'm talking about. That's what I'm that's what I'm banking on is that I mean like
Okay, our civilization was able to figure out how to break our gravity and then land on our moon within like 12,000 years of civilization
And only like a hundred thousand years of our species with a billion years
We can figure out dimensions. No biggie. You know, it's not fucking you know
I'll give it to you that my my more pressing concern is that will destroy ourselves. That is my main concern
Honestly when it comes to stuff like that
I think of what the human race will be that the language will have morphed if I were to travel to the future
English would be like no longer English
People would have you know change, you know
Strange or if they live on other planets, they'll be really yeah stuff if there's lower gravity or whatever
And it'll be it'll be so alien to me that it may as well not even be the human race and at that point
I don't really care, you know, that was another thing I was thinking about where I I have this thing where I really care about
Humanity survival and I like I root for humanity to go out and colonize space and then I just thought to myself
Why am I really so dedicated to team humanity?
Why is it not okay for like a superior alien race to just yeah, like that's my go with it
You know, that's my hope is that somewhere out there?
There's a there's a better race than us because if we're the best the universe has to offer the universe is fucked
Yeah, I want to I want to be on Picard's team where Picard's like
Humanity has so much potential we can evolve so we can we can you know learn from our mistakes
We can improve ourselves and I'm just like I'm out looking here at humanity day after day and I'm just not seeing it
It's pretty obvious that Hobbits were better than
Regression when I look at humanity, I think people are getting worse as time goes on
We could just be a slump. It could just be a slump. Yeah, I mean you never know
Well, I guess it's interesting that we're talking about this whole like humanity thing because that's never been something like I can I can
Understand your enthusiasm and your investment on like a logical level, but I just don't care like I guess I'm just too much of an
Individualist where I'm just like I don't like I want of course
I think it's cool like conceptually we have humanity to succeed and do all this crazy shit and become Starfleet
But like I'm not invested in that struggle because I'm gonna be dead in like 30 to 40 years
That's and it doesn't have anything to do with me like even if we succeed in a billion years
I'm not gonna be here to even comprehend it like you know
I'm with you on all that but to make things even more depressing
What is even the point of Starfleet to just spread humanity like a fucking cancer over the other planets and galaxies?
Like what's the point? What are we serving we really have a separate podcast for about futurism and the idea of what should really do?
We should I actually was gonna suggest this a couple days ago, and then I fell asleep interesting
Cuz I actually suggested it in a let's play that me digi and Ben and monkey Jones recorded last night
I actually
Well, let's not out yet is it? Oh, well, we're totally off topic right now
The only thing I can really say about nostalgia is basically just to bloat that like I've secured
I've been privileged enough both like emotionally and financially that like I've just succeeded at life
And like everything is better for me now
So like basically the only way I could imagine just talking about this is just for someone to name something that
So you should hypothetically be nostalgic for from the past that I'm totally not and just go down the list dude
What about what about back in school when you drew the little s
Anything
The way I see nostalgia is that I mean I
Especially hate it whenever anyone says it or implies. Oh my god. You didn't do or know this thing. You didn't have a childhood
That's yeah, who didn't have a childhood. He didn't make the s's
You're doing a funny old joke here, but I really hate that I really really hate that anybody who in who pushes their
Does anybody mean that seriously this and has anybody ever met that legitimately
They need to be punched in the face. No, no, no people people all were all the time. I mean, who does it?
Well, I mean do people who were born in labor wrong generation
I'm not I'm not I'm not even denying that you're I'm not even saying you're wrong
I've just never encountered anyone seriously meaning that
No, you mean but like I've gotten over it since then so yeah another thing is better about my life now is not caring about things
I was going somewhere but I figure I'll just come up with the other thing I was gonna say is that right now
I'm on my laptop and
That's because I'm away with my family at a like a weekend sort of holiday thing in the countryside
And it's really nice and it's stuff and it's just reminding me of like family holidays
Because we haven't been on a lot of those mom and dad have been going on holidays by themselves
For the past few years because like I don't know it's just sort of like it's weird
Just keep going on family holidays every year, and but now we're doing it again. It's like yeah
I'm not nostalgic for family holidays the last couple ones of my family had were like really boring and hard
That's like I just want to I just want to work on my dang videos. Yeah
It's not just the family holidays thing
But it's just like reminding me of all the stuff that you don't do or I did before like technology
And I'm thinking of like yeah, I used to really like
Stuff and places and things and and frogs and castles and and wind and trees and I like all that that's good
Fresh air is nice. Yeah, I sure wish I had more of it
one thing that I'm I don't know if I'm just I guess it's nostalgic but
When I you know I was living in Massachusetts my whole life my dad at a boat and we'd go out in it
And I never really like enjoyed going out in it because it took like all day and I would actually you know
I never looked forward to it, but once I was out there usually had a great time
But I would I used to really really enjoy going down to the marina where his boat was and just standing there feeling the sea breeze
And the first thing I noticed when I moved out to the Midwest and I'm in Ohio is
How much I fucking missed the ocean and just standing on the shore feeling the smelling the salt feeling the breeze feeling the fucking sun
That's where I want to be. I want to be there all the time
I think it's important to remember that the real world is pretty good if you're just yes. Oh, yeah, I love the real world, too
Yeah, fucking I I'd be going on walks all I'm gonna go on walks all the dang time as soon as my ankles finish healing
That's a good. That's a good thing
if I could live on like a
What's the word like a beach house
Right next to the fucking ocean where I could go swimming if I want and be able to come inside go into a little studio and like record
Podcasts and videos and edit shit. Oh
That'd be and then at night I could leave the windows open feel the cool ocean breeze and smell the sea
Oh, that would be the perfect life. That's what I want for me one day and have a big fat slut in my bed
Big just a real hambeast a big monster. Yeah, just smother me to death every night. That's what I want. That's what I want
That's my dream beautiful
And I guess you'd call it nostalgic. Yeah, that's like a nostalgic fantasy
Fago and a car full of fat chicks. That's the American dream
That's right
It's funny you mentioned the ocean because I did something rather similar like remembering how much I liked the ocean cuz um
I you meet me my family used to go to the beach all the time because we're in Massachusetts as well
So we go to go to the cave
We go to like Brockport like beach and stuff like that because I was really close by and go to horse neck
You ever go to horse neck beach? I never went to horse neck beach. Okay, just one. I missed out on that one
but um back when I was a kid
The more I got into video games the less I wanted to go to the beach because like video games beach didn't mix
So I was like fuck that I just want to play video games
And I remember like as I got older I really disliked the beach
but then my friend came over and
She lives in Missouri, so she'd never seen the beach ever in her life
This was like last like like last year never never gone to the beach and she's like I want to go see the beach
I might have fucking beaches gay who cares, but I guess you've never been there
So I guess we should probably go and we go and she just like freaks out and like holy shit and just like and like and like
It's it's it's cold. It's like it's in the winter. It's water's freezing
She's still like fucking runs into the water and just like
Experiences it. I'm just standing there and like it's the first time I've been on the beach and probably like seven or eight years
And like like the same kind of things like the smell of the salt and like just being there and feeling the breeze like it triggered like this like
Like yeah, you just look down you just look down there and you just think to self. What a fag
Exactly
It was you kind of remember what you liked and to see someone else kind of like
Experiencing the joy you used to have there was really really interesting. That's anything. I don't know. I appreciate it all over again
That's really interesting because I'm also from Missouri
And I also saw the beach for the first time like six months ago when I moved in with Digi and I went there and I was like, yep
I don't know why I'm able to be such an asshole being
Contrarian about every single thing people are talking about today. It's just for some reason
Deville you've created life and turn us all into wrestling. Well, that's all you're the mortal
That's where the arch nemesis of the PCB are villain from within. Yeah, you know, it's fine. We expect it
It's I mean, I was there when you first discovered sand and that was quite weird
Yeah, to see someone discover sand like big amounts of sand on under your feet
That was a sand box and it was like a different kind of sand. I was like, oh different texture
Yeah, I was pretty interested in the sand the beach part, which I guess I guess a beach is half sand half ocean
So I guess I was half interested in the ocean now
It's cool
I like when you go out on to like a playground and
And there's like the tarmac and there's like little girls there and they're like not being watched by their parents
And you can just like
Go to the playground and you sit and it's like a summer day and the playground's been all like heated up
That's all right guys secretary just walked in. She's being a goddamn bother
Well, shut up secretary. I'm telling a story
I'm telling a story about how I like it when you go sit on a tarmac and you got your hands and you put it on the ground
Yeah, that's hot, but then it's okay after a while. It's like, yeah, I know the exact feeling
And it's like there's no one around because it's sort of the end of the day
And then parents are taking their kids and you're like still there
Because you know, you're a little bit older and you're allowed to stay out a little longer
And it's like, yeah, I'm I really enjoy the playground and now I can't go there anymore because it's gay and I'm a pedophile I guess
So this meme of of raping children is bad go away
When will that me man, you know, I'm ready for it to swing the pendulum to swing the other way for a while
Sex with the child's
Whoa
Like yeah, that's right. That's you you got some
Every every day I run the risk a little bit more of them discovering all these things and me getting
I'm getting a little bit of heat for it, but not so far so good
So feels feels good and you know what I kind of want it so that I'll be fired and be forced to be a YouTube's man
So, you know kind of a
Playgrounds did anybody like
Using the monkey bar that said no one tell them no one tell them
Did anybody use the monkey bars? I was like a monkey bars champion. I can yeah, I was fucking outlawed those shits
I don't know in America
Because you know, it's it's lobbyists with their conflicting goals
It's like you got the you got the bureaucrats office and waiting to meet in
Damn big
There's the there's the very concerned mother gonna talk about obesity with children
But then there's a very concerned mother talking about the children who get hurt whenever they go out and be active and burn calories
And I guess just last decade the fucking burn calories getting hurt mom was just more upset than the other one
So that's how things yeah
What about right when you when you're a little kid and you fall over and you scrape your knee and it's like ow and there's blood and
Then you come home, and then it's like a day later or half a day later. There's like a scab. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah picking that that's scab
That's a nostalgic. I don't get scabs anymore. You know what you're powerful
You were talking about being nostalgic for like monkey bars and stuff, you know that reminded me
When I was a kid in elementary school, we used to have monkey bars
Monkey bars
That guy's weaseled his way into my fucking brain
He's changed my perception of monkeys forever
But uh, you know we used to have monkey bars
We used to have like a real playground at a certain point like they renovated the playground and like they tore everything down
And like made new stuff and the new stuff was like
It was like all wooden it was like there was like a big like monster made out of tires
And there was like you know everything was like made out of like tires and rubber and wood and stuff and at the time
You were like oh wow this new playground is even cooler, but looking back on it. That was just garbage
They just built the playground out of old tires and shit. Oh, yeah, my whole life has been we were playing on garbage
You know what I'm I am
Nostalgic for actual good playgrounds
I will say because that is something that has definitely declined in my lifetime like because of safety concerns
Mm-hmm all playgrounds. They get renovated and become boring and shitty like gay grounds
Okay, you know what the problem is here. The problem is people are our two hyper
Individualized they're not folks enough on community and I mean this sincerely cuz everything go in a communists back again
One mom sees her child a trip and get a splinter on the wooden playground
She decides this is this needs to stop this can never happen to her child or you know
I get maybe any other child ever again
So they tear that motherfucker down and they build like a stainless steel
Monstrosity in its place
Vaccine and you know what it's amazing that how like one out of every
100,000 kids will die from a vaccine and that mom is super good remember vaccines guys. That was great
I miss all right. I love autism. I'm all about autism
But anyway Jesse, what are you saying? That sounds like the opposite of what you're saying is it sounds like if you're saying
No one else can have the playground because they might get hurt like Mike did that sounds like putting the
community before individual rights
Well, it's like okay. The everyone loves the playground is what is the is the fictional thing?
I'm constructing my brain everyone loves this playground one child gets hurt in a way that any child could get hurt at any time
And they decide that the playground is like a threat and should be
Personal responsibility just like I didn't take good enough care of my kid
So I'm gonna blame it on the state and their shitty playground or people need to accept if my child fucking
Accidentally hung himself by his fucking shoelaces on the playground. That does not necessarily mean the playground is dangerous
Humanities need to find a someone to blame in every situation
Someone needs to take the fall when my child accidentally strangled himself when my way child accidentally
Was masturbating and choking himself and he died that's on the monkey
Accidentally choked himself masturbating on the monkey bars and was reborn as
And that's the canon origin
See but that's what I'm talking about like
People need to people need to see that like okay just because this thing happened doesn't mean even if it was legitimately the things
Faults if it does more good than bad. It's still worth having even if there is a threat
Just I don't know make people aware of it. I don't know this this always drives me crazy people think like that
Something similar to playgrounds is a big old play places with with the climbing frames that you just yeah
They're still around I'm sure but they they seem to be
they aren't they're like they were like a
supposedly like a
Not a biohazard, but it's like they were they weren't sanitary so they got rid of them. Yeah, well all of them
Pretty much at least in America. They're pretty mean. I'm talking about like play places for McDonald's
Yeah, you can't go to like
Well, I've never been to a McDonald's. I had one of those but oh yeah into a couple places that were specifically
Like like like a warehouse where you could just set your kid loose. Yeah, like um well play places
I know they don't build any more of those but like here well in the Midwest where I used to be
I still saw plenty of those. They just never tore them down, right?
Yeah, I think there's one particular the one that used to be my hometown where they did tear it down
And they replaced it with this thing
It was like that was like
Still was kind of a play place in that it was literally just one tunnel that led to one slide and that was so and that was it
I was so fucking pissed and most of it most of it most of it was video games
And I'm like yep. This is this is what's wrong with the world, you know, this is
This is what's wrong with you. This is what's wrong with talking about okay
Finish your fun. This is what's wrong with fucking parental guidance where it's like everyone's like man
Why are all the Millennials us sitting around in their houses?
I mean, maybe it's because Millennials were told if you fucking go out of the house where we can't see you you will
Trip and fall and break your nose and then get abducted and molested
And so all you can do is is play in this like three by three, you know back there are there are dramatically less
Crimes committed in America including like kidnappings and you know pedophilia charges now
Then there were in like the 50s and yet now we have far more regulation than ever on all this shit
So like what what what the fuck? Oh, I think it might have been
I mean, I think the regulation might have helped a bit because since there were no key there were less kids out
Right exactly like maybe it was just died out. They just walked around until I mean
I advocate that we need to sacrifice some children to the pedophiles in order to save them in order to avoid large pedophiles
You know
Pedophile dance like like you've tied the pedophiles
Great pedophiles we sacrifice days to you the giant pedophile king comes out of the mountains
Yeah, I think video games are good enough. I can I can be in my room all the time
I don't fucking do it speaking of fucking nostalgia
I just had a had an acid flashback to in a McDonald's play place
There was this like I can't really remember what it was, but there was like this weird
Game slash like animated cartoon thing that played barbaran by the fucking beach boys
And there was like a story of like a guy trying to like woo this nurse girl
I think and he couldn't get her
But then he was about to die because he was doing some stunt to impress her and then she saved him
Then they were like happily ever after in love. Oh my god
That's are you sure that was it's been it's been in my brain for like 20 years
It was a it was like part of some interactive McDonald's play place thing, man
I just trip. I just I'm nostalgia for recess recess was fucking cool
ban it
It's it's it's ableist recess is ableist the the kids who are in wheelchairs can't play dodgeball
so I have I have a lot of nostalgia for
Play we called it play time
Because we go out and play and there's like
There was a whole game. I don't know. I don't know whether
There's probably not a game that was like anyone ever plays, but we had like and we had like a
Lines on on the on the playground for like football and basketball or whatever
Yeah, and sometimes there would be like a couple squares and we put we would play this game called to square with like up to four players
Where you get a ball and somebody just spikes it or like or hits it like as if it was
Volleyball, but not like an actual volleyball hit
They just hit it however they like and the other person just has to get the ball onto the other square and have it bounce once
It's like a combination tennis, but without a net and we call that we called that four square
Yeah, that's the exact same game, and I was the fucking champion. I'll fight anyone in four square
Well, yeah, we had four squares. It was divided to four instead of two
I guess I will fight anyone at a four square at any time. I'm a fucking planet and
When we went I wasn't at school because not you know people weren't always playing it
I wasn't really the sort of person to grab a ball and get people around to play to square
So I would just get like a ball with my brother at home
Just randomly and we would go on to the driveway and we would play there
And it would that would be I would just do that for hours
I'll that would be the the funnest thing ever just to play to square on the driveway with a ball
Fuck video games over my video games. I don't even like them. They're not even cool. What do we talk about?
You know, okay, I'm with it
We talked all about a bunch of nostalgia shit, but let me let me ask you guys
I wanted to this we've touched on this a few times already
But like so and it gives video was kind of about this so is nostalgia
Actually a good justified thing and or is it just a shitty thing that as an adult you have
Is there any value I haven't answered this weird demonization of nostalgia is just like a weird contrarian cynical internet culture thing
And I think it needs to die. I
Think I say in my video that people generally think nostalgia goggles are
Like something to be ashamed of or avoided and it's like who cares. It's it's something you like it makes you happy
So what are the well as long as your arguments are sound? Yeah, that's for me
Nostalgia that nostalgia that I feel for specific video games is
Like lately like can be a reason to go back and play the video game
But nostalgia like is like a fuel source that does get burnt out by going back to the game, right?
Like I've I've gone black back and played Superstar saga out of nostalgia like probably two or three
Well a bunch of times and eventually it's like I've played the game so many times, you know, it's a linear RPG
It's a single-player RPG. There's not that much replay value 13 times
Is enough time just that's what people I think people accuse you of like nostalgia goggles when they're trying to like
Shit on something you like or like, you know, they say you just think it's good because of nostalgia
But that's not true like like Final Fantasy 7 for example, they'll be like, oh that game is not even good
You like it because you're nostalgic for like no, I'm not I play it like every year
I've played it like a billion times. Maybe the first time I went back and played it there was nostalgia
I have no fucking nostalgia for that game anymore whatsoever. It's just a good game that I like
Yeah, yeah
There are definitely things
That are not good that I have nostalgia for and that makes me think that they're good
But as an adult as an adult a
I try to figure out whether it's nostalgia or not and if it is nostalgia
I will still let myself enjoy it, but I won't tell anybody that it's good
I will just tell them that I'm nostalgic for it and that will sort of make sure that they don't
Hate it like but sex, you know, you always look back on but sex and you have this nostalgia for it like yeah
Yeah, totally cool. I want to do that again. They do it again, and you're like, oh wait. Yeah
Oh, yeah, this is a butthole where poop comes out of this isn't good at all. Why do I have nostalgia for this?
You always go back to the but
95 shit that I'm nostalgic for and if I see it again
I'm gonna be like whoa
I remember that and then like in the course of like 20 seconds the amount that I care because of the nostalgia is gonna wear
Off into nothing. It's like it's you know, it's it doesn't last that long the nostalgia trip
Is there anything wrong with that? No, there's nothing wrong with that. I'm just saying that's how it is for me and
There's a very simple test. I think I feel like there are some people who like just because their lives went to shit
Like they really depend on the nostalgic memories to get by like I feel like people like movie Bob kind of come off that way to me
Sometimes we're like he's just so endlessly obsessed with Super Mario Bros. 3 and I'm like, you know
There's not that much of Super Mario Bros 3, but it's just because you know, I mean he's fat
So he needs this, you know, that's true. He is very happiness. He came. I'm sure he has
Yeah, exactly. I feel like I feel like it's because there are definitely certain people out there who have like like too much
Fixation or like like like like um people liked the nostalgia critic who Doug Walker started that series because he was 25 and
Going through a nostalgic phase. That's what he said
But it ended up becoming a this arch platform that he then made into his job
And so he's had to continue like like like dwelling on that nostalgic phase for like ten fucking years now
And so I think when people see that they sort of get this perception that there are these people who just drown in nostalgia endlessly
And I think it's probably the case for some people
But it's mostly just because it makes for a good YouTube show in the mid in the late 2000s
And so they get this they get this perception that like oh, you know when they see Jesse
They're like, oh, he's still talking about Final Fantasy 7. It's because he's just like that, you know
I think that's where the misconception comes from for some people
If you can defend I mean whatever point you make ever if you ever if you're accused of fucking nostalgia
Just like if you can defend your point intelligently, that's it there. There is there's no case
Like what nostalgia just means like you remember something fondly from your childhood like even if it's fucking shit
Like like I watched and loved as a kid the dub of Monster Rancher and I watch it now
And it's fucking the worst shit of all time. Yeah, but you know what?
I still remember that fondly because I like that is
Something there's you don't need like to put together some like
So here in like five-page essay arguing why you like it
I think that if someone did you bro if someone is saying that what you like is not good
Then the burden of proof is on them
If you're saying that something is bad and people shouldn't like it then you're the one who should have to fucking state your case
Intelligently and if you can't then fuck you get the fuck out of here
My hope
YouTube channel is based on the idea that I want to figure out whether my nostalgia is there is valid or not
Because I want to figure out whether the game is good despite the fact that I really like it
That sounds like my all-time favorite youtuber cat Icarus. It's time to find out which games need to be salvaged or slaughtered
He's got the two guns
He's got he's got the salvage gun and he's got the slaughtered gun. You ever see that? Oh god
My final fantasy 7 I think is Frogger
He's back the the Frogger remake from the late 90s that I played the shit out of as a kid and like the only real difference is that as an
Adult I'm I can understand why it's so good like it really is um, but not good
It's not good in the way that most people would agree with it just so happens to like do almost everything
I want a video game to be I have a that reminds me of a
of a
Story with a point about nostalgia or something probably it's probably vaguely related to this topic
I don't I don't fucking know but I don't know maybe I've even told the story before I don't fucking know
But when I was a kid it was like like Easter or like 1998 or some shit Easter or 1998 one or the other it couldn't have been
Those two things contradict each other
But you know, I really wanted my mom was gonna get me like a present
And I really wanted the legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time for the n64. That was the the hot new
Game the the hot new mobile app as we call games today for all you
Yep, so I really wanted Ocarina of Time and I'm like, okay
Give me can you please give me this game mom and she she comes back from the store and she goes
Well, I thought at the store instead of getting you just one sixty dollar game
Oh, I'll get you. Oh, no two thirty dollar games
So it's even better
It's two games and your mom is part of the reason that those red box
Those red box ripoff movies like Atlantic Rim exists, right? And and uh, well like what an indictment
The story yet the two games that she got me instead of Ocarina of Time
Get out of my drawers. What are you doing?
The secretary get around here. She's going through my pajamas. She's putting on my clothes
She's fucking digging through my fucking my stuff. She's stealing my toys and my games
She's playing with my money toaster on the table. She's pocketing all my fucking loose dollar bills. What are you doing?
No
Gasol women
Now she's she's got her pants off now, I don't know what she wants
Well, I don't know about you, but I'm offended. This is
I'm still telling the story, but I'm looking at a pussy right now and I want to touch it
I'm still telling the story. Nobody interrupt me
Okay, go
Get out of my PJs
Oh
Man we're off the rails now
They all have holes in the crotch if you want to wear my pants you have to deal with
You're not gonna find a pair in there. That's magically intact
It would take it would take magic to find pants, which don't have a hole in the crotch
It would take you know what I'm packing. You know the power
It does the pants
I'm gonna touch your bus if you if you don't stop getting naked. He's just putting out all my pants
None of my pants are safe. He's just switching between pairs of pajamas
We're never gonna know
I really want to know these two games
Was it shinobi 2 and 3
Was it earthworm Jim
Okay, now she's in my bed. Hopefully she's fucking satisfied for now. She's dead
Even though a woman has never been satisfied when in your bed previously, but maybe this would be the exception
Nate stop projecting
Never okay
So so she gets me these two games I'm still tongue story. This was all part of the story everything that
That part happens every time I tell the story
Important chapter in the tail
There's like a flash forward to like when I'm 27 and there's a secretary in my room
It's a narrative device. It's like that Ferris Bueller story. I mean not Ferris Bueller fucking Princess Bride
It's like a story being told from the future. Yeah, it's the framing device of like right, right
So the two games she got me instead of Ocarina of Time we're bust a move to and
Frogger on ps1 and so what ps1? I love bus to move. I love bus to move
Yeah, so like I was like really disappointed like what is this shit was the other one bust a move in Frogger
Bust a Frogger whoa
You were just talking about Frogger and how great it is and now you're acting like you don't know what it is
You're your audio your audio cut it a weird way. That's all
God damn it
So let's just clarify bust to move to and frog. Yes the frogger. Okay. That's got you
Got you. I was audio literally edited your fucking audio connection literally edited you into saying bust a frogger on my end
That's true. It literally did
Bust a frog. Well, we all know that if you bust a frogger every day, that's his source of power
So I was disappointed there's the point of the story
I was like all these games are probably not good and not even good and not even good
I wanted the other game, but you know, I played them and it turned out they were pretty good
I had a lot of fun them and I'm still very nostalgic for those two games to this day
And that is the point of the story and that's how it goes into the topic at hand which is nostalgia and I'm sorry
I even told the story. I'm sorry. I even try to say everything
If we ever do a let's play it should be fucking frogger for ps1
That's I agree sure
Because I came I want to do bust a move to
Yeah, let's do a bust a move to play because my mom loved bust a move and got me
It's like the only video game ever that my mom got me into well the only video game ever
Yeah, it's the one it's the one video game
I have heard of it. What does it you do? Do you bust a move?
But no, you know, it's the game where you bubbles and it's like bubble-bobble
It's the same like little mascot characters from bubble-bobble if you ever heard of that shit those little cute little dinosaur guys and
And you fucking and it's like a puzzle game
There's bubbles you and you got to match the colors you shoot them out of a little cannon and you match three of them
And you can get combos and fucking you
Fuck up. It's sort of like Tetris only you combine colors
Yeah, and you know what?
You reminded me of how
Mad I was I didn't get my money's worth with the Nintendo Wii because neither of my parents enjoyed it at all
Unlike what the commercials said like that for me was the biggest betrayal of Nintendo
Just because my parents are too fucking old even for the Wii like my dad top 10 anime betrayals
Yeah parents did not enjoy my dad said like there's just no video game that I can relax to and that's
The only reason he consumes art is to relax
My dad's remember the Nintendo Wii
Yeah, that's what they actually used to call it. It's like you're in
The Mario Galaxy was a fun game
I actually do have nostalgia your referencing old AVG in episodes that are from the future from the past
Well, yeah, I'm nostalgic old man nostalgic for that episode. I'm also nostalgic about the Wii and also
Specifically playing golf with my dad on the Wii golf. That was cool. He really liked that. That's cool
The angry video game nerd was like was a guy like nostalgic about old games and now most of us are really nostalgic
About the early angry video game nerd episodes. I know right? He still does. Yeah, it's still great
But you know, but particularly the old old episodes. There's just something there's just a timeless quality to them
Of course
It is I kind of ironic that the nostalgic critic hasn't ever made anything that's good
Disagree, I think he's made some okay. What I mean is a not nostalgic for any particular episode
He's not as rewatchable. You know what I'll give you I'll give him one thing
I really liked of his was I mean, okay, his reviews are all the same
He just talks about shit that happened. But yeah, when he reviewed
He's an integral part of what got me into the room so much
Yeah, I watch his review of the room and so it's always been part of the room experience for me
And I'll watch that to this day and laugh
It's a good one. See I'm nostalgic for one thing that he's made. There you go. There you go, Doug. You're welcome
I'm nostalgic for kikassia and all those things. Oh, yeah, kikassia was fun
But I mean like it wasn't I don't know what that is
Well, I'm the first big that guy with the glasses used to do I mean big old crossover movies, which
Progressively got more and more elaborate and stupider
It was always like me the only good part about the about any of them was Spoonie because he was the only person on the website
Who was funny and like had any kind of charisma
And eventually they like fired him from the site and so then there was no reason to ever go to the site again
We see my problem is that like I just fundamentally hate 90% of the people on that website at any given time, right?
So like when the third one happened and Todd in the shadows showed up. I'm like, oh sweet finally. There's like, okay, Doug
Nostalgia chick. I like her and fucking Todd in the shadows. That's like three guys. Fuck. Do you guys all like Todd in the shadows?
He's writing is terrible. He's boring as fuck. I don't like anything about you, Nate. I hate him
He's not a good boy, but I don't know why these guys like you and did you talking about how much you like Todd in the shadows
And you get people like like Phyllis and people like other they're all just fat white guys, you know
And it's just like oh, they're all the same fucking born
That the thing I liked though. Are you saying that you like him because he's not white? Is that your reasoning here?
The thing the thing I I am I liked about the fact that so many of them were annoying and stupid is that I could imagine myself
You know as a young
Loser kid like becoming an internet reviewer and joining the site just so that I could be there and do it better than they could
Yeah, unfortunately, I got disillusioned to the whole thing by the time I'm actually making yeah now
You're doing the AVGN style in my opinion kind of sort of better than the AVGN does
In my opinion if hypocrite reviews becomes like 50 episodes long
Then I think I would if it becomes a hundred episodes along then I would like it then more than the first hundred episodes of AVGN
Slightly but still hmm just my opinion man
Get in Gib. I am right now
Well, I'm not right now
Well, okay, I feel like we've gone pretty deep into that. How about we shifted to questions? Is that is that cool?
Let's go. I just want to say that revenge of Shinobi on PS
I mean on PS on Sega Genesis was the fucking coolest and I'm nostalgic for that first level
Because it's really hard but it's really cool and we didn't talk about 16-bit games because you're all fucking young and I hate all of you
Yeah, yeah, I'm with you there. We didn't talk about anything important. We just talked about a bunch of we need to do
You know that thankfully we should just do like another nostalgia podcast in like a couple weeks
And then we can be nostalgic for this podcast and then also talk about the actual nostalgic stuff that we all neglected this time
I think I think I might be even though we spent
I think I might be one of the only
Procrastinators that didn't grow up on 16 bit at all. I didn't even know what an SNES was for like you didn't grow up on SNES
Well, no, I I the only reason I know about what an SNES is is because the ABG and talked about it
I primarily grew up on PC and I just didn't play any good games. I had like only three good games for my childhood
It's so easy to not be nostalgic because like all the games I played were shit
Haha, hey, you have nostalgia for your trampoline. No, I only got a trampoline when I was like 14
That's a number of years
Not long enough to be nostalgic because like mainly the memory I have is spending my childhood wishing I had a trampoline
Okay, well, do you think okay? That's interesting
Do you think when you die you will have more internalized the feeling of wishing you had a trampoline or actually having had a trampoline?
What's more to the being of Davoo honestly the main the main feeling that sticks out to me is like everyone liking that video more than I do and
Like me being so mathful that how much people like that video and let me in like well, okay nice
Totally surprises me for all it was just a nice. It was just a nice wholesome like yeah, this is why trampolines are good
I'm like yeah, it is I get it though
It's got no other pretenses of them to be night a nice little funny video about trampolines. That's true. That's true
It's not like a guys. Here's my epic Zelda breath of the wild review. It's new. It's a video
loves video games
Let's what what last thing before we go to questions. I just remembered this anyone else
Nostalgic, I know you are I know the answers. Yes, there is some porn out there that I am super nostalgic for like
Anyone remember Heather I have I deep throat calm. Come on
Everyone that she's the deep throat Queen everyone loves Heather Brooke. She's a champion
It was like the first porn I was ever introduced to by outside friends
I am change the game nostalgic for like a few early
Bang bros things
Did you ever watch Bruno be I remember Bruno be that is I was just like a
Never I've never to this day watched or read Naruto, but whenever I see the character designs
I think about a lot of my early masturbation. That's for sure
Shout out to shout out to acid head does some shout out to porn
masturbation I get nostalgic for Naruto
Also in Bible black also the one of the first hence I ever saw also the best that there are I can fire emblem fan art
The first the first inclination I ever had the people could draw
Characters from things in sexual ways
No, I remember fan art right flourina specifically. She had her panties show in I was like what you can see that
Oh, no
Christian sensibilities, no
All right, well there you go
Yes, so let's let's go to questions. Here we go. It's do it. Okay. We got a bunch here
Here is okay. Here's a question. That's that's I think is interesting
Is there any okay, right at an untitled ab
Abrogda, it's like an untitled abridger, but it's weird Tony this this guy tweets the procrastiners all the time
He says is there anything is there anything good about politics favorite political leader? Yes of any definition slash
All it takes are cool until it's like
300 million people right
Like when you watch like maybe like some TV show that involves politics and it's like it's like okay
Okay, the fucking chairman election art from the end of hunter hunter
It's like it's like politics, but only like 300 people are involved and it's got a lot of it's a clash of really interesting
personalities with a lot of really interesting shit and like when you see those tiny countries of like three million people
There's still a lot of personality that comes through
But you know how like the more
Participants you get in something the more it averages out like the more that you flip a coin the more it becomes 50 50
Like the problem with America is it so many fucking people that the only people who can end up becoming nominees are like these weird fucking
Bullshit blends of different opinions that make no fucking sense and it becomes utterly depressing
So the problem with America is it's too big and that's why our politics are so annoying now
It is it is possible that in our in our internet age that we're in now like human beings are in maybe maybe human beings are
Like what's the word? I'm looking for lethally tribal
And that as we're more and more exposed to the other people that actually share the country with us
We're finding out like holy shit. I share the country with these people fuck that and it's it's gonna cause more dissent
There's too many people and the people are too uneducated and that's the problem
Politics forms is nothing but a mental cancer and once it's in people's brains it invariably turns them into worse human beings
I don't disagree. I just want to say lethally tribal Aurora mage
Lethal lava land from Super Mario 64
Yes, I I want to actually defend politics for a second and
Cuz you're gay
All I have to say is remember Ross you from
Fucking girl
What Ross you represents is is well, I would I would normally say like a what's the word a
God, what's the fucking word for someone who like Bush benevolent a benevolent despot is the word?
I was looking for which is a term for like a
Dictator who like has the legitimately has the best interests of the people in mind
But Ross you wasn't even a dictator or like a despot or anything. He was just elected
Doing it, but so like if you I'm doing it everybody's possible. What do you do it on my secretary's pants? That'll fucking show her
Both agree that the only way to defend politics is better than my pants. Yeah
They're all elastic and I think I think it's because political intrigue is interesting politics is dry and boring
No, no, no, but see the the okay, but the thing about Ross you is Ross you as a hero
Spends Ross you was a politician who spent like 50 fucking years just toiling and toiling and toiling to make sure that you know
All the spiral races work together and shit
And we see exactly none of the hard work that actually went into making sure everything went smoothly
So that everyone didn't kill each other and like just like in real life. We're bored
We're endlessly bored by by the nitty-gritty of what it takes to actually run a society properly
And so in the anime they fucking skip that and they just tell us it was really hard
But it went well, but what it it's in real life
You have to actually like live the life of a guy spending a thousand years
I see most politics is interesting, but most politicians are boring because like they
Like what it takes to make a politician you have to like yeah, I sure have a static
before the
Yeah, I just wanted to talk about how cool Ross you is
That's I that's the answer. He's he's a hero guys. He's a hero next question. Okay next question. Um, okay, what?
Oh, what's his face at?
kick
Can kink kuck kink kuck right kink kuck asks what is the best fast food?
Restaurants five guys also why a restaurant so shit. They're all terrible guys. They all don't deserve to exist. I
Agree, I mean you say five guys five guys like tastes like an actual burger that was made at home basically
What counts as fast food if it doesn't carry house cuss count as fast food
That's like sit down. That's like a sit-down place. Yeah, I usually order that in or take away. It's like
Reasonably quick. I'll say it counts. Yeah, whatever. I'm gonna say Domino's pan pizza because I'm getting that as soon as this podcast is over
I would have already ordered my store is currently unavailable for online ordering and I'm kind of wait
I got it online ordering right now. I got it fish and chips the the English classic fish and chips
Wait, that is chips. Is that a restaurant? It's fries. It's no, it's just a food
It's battered fish with with fried chips and it's it's fast and it's food and I like it and efficient chips is efficient
Yes. Oh
Nice nice. I by the way, I got a fish in my shoulder. I
Hate I hate fast food. I think it's a cancer on the world and
What one time I was watching some show on the food network that was like it was like chopped
it was like a competition between cooks and
There was one cook there like the others, you know, they try to make tasty food
There was one there whose whose main emphasis is to make healthy food that people will feel good and improve their lives when they eat
She got voted out in the first round because she didn't load enough salt and oil and bullshit into her food and tried to actually care about
The people who she was serving to whereas the other people only gave a shit about what instantly was the most
Instant gratification eating it and I think that really speaks to humanity at large
We treat food like it's something to make us feel good and not fuel cells that we need to power
I'm absolutely a hundred percent on board with you. I think I think taste buds are the worst thing and they should be genetically
Added out of
I think the worst thing that we that we have in our bodies is the butthole
Because we
I would here's the fucking tier list for fast food, right?
It's like okay
There's Burger King which tastes terrible makes you feel terrible makes you want to go on a killing spree
Then there's stuff like McDonald's and Wendy's which has like this like half second
Mmm, tasty when you put it in your mouth, but you just feel gross during and after it feels unsatisfying
I don't know if I put McDonald's above Burger King
I definitely I put Burger King way below all the others. It doesn't even taste good
But anyway, so then you have stuff like five guys, which is like it tastes great
And then I feel great as long as I haven't been eating just this right as long as it's in the occasional
The exception to the rule when I eat something giant and greasy and ketchup now to boo
Oh, man, this is a very typical argument to have here. You're advocating for like that. Oh, I'm a I'm a I'm a free American
I can eat whatever I want
But the fact of the matter is fast food is garbage and no one should eat it at any time in their life
I don't want people to have the freedom to eat it. It's not much worse for you
Good for your soul SpongeBob SpongeBob's dead because I murdered him so
Is your tear list based on the amount of tears you cry when you absolutely freaking Lutely, yeah, yeah
Here's a here's a question that's never been addressed before at sis white scum 69
What is your favorite mud in video games?
What's going on with mud
Do we have any experts here who can answer this question actually wait, um, isn't there a mud track in Mario Kart?
DS yeah, warrior. I believe warrior. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well, you included the warrior one in the list hippo
But there's another one. That's like chocolatey. It's like a chocolate mountain in Mario Kart. Oh, yeah
That's the isn't that the 64 well
DS one, but I guess I guess it's
Yeah, that's why I didn't put it in I remember a great mud level
There was this game. Uh, there's this game called conquer on the n64 where you run up this whole mountain made out of mud
And then you you know you go inside the mud mountain and you fight like a giant mud man and the mud man throws toilet paper at you
For some reason I never understood why he was throwing toilet paper. His name was the great mighty mud
Yeah, it was a good wholesome game for a young developing boy like myself
It made me the man I am today wholesome and full of values
And that's why you have so much mud in your pants at any given moment
Wait a minute
It was crap
That explains why I'm the crappy pants man
My cannon origin at last
I am actually curious if anybody knows of any other games that have cool mud in them because I couldn't really
I really thought about it when I watched your video and I'm not sure I'm trying
I feel like there's is some game that I played that has mud in it that I just didn't remember like getting on the character and thought
It was gross, but I cannot for the life of me or call what it was
Is there a mud in the Lion King for Super NES?
This is my favorite thing about you Tom that you are the one remaining like Sega warrior champion against Nintendo
Decades later. It's you do my life. You don't understand
Tells the full tale. I tried to buy I bought a Super Nintendo like years later, and I was so offended that it was in my house
I just sold it to my friend. I'm like, I don't want it anymore. Oh, I hate it
Man, man, you know, we should have a PCP about
Arguing and fighting for the sake of it being fun because like when I was like 13
I was all console worry, but like totally as a meme like I was my god, dude. Yes
I was on GameSpot forums all the time lemmings and cows and sheep. Yeah, man
I was like it was like when the Wii was coming out
I was all like, oh dude like this is the future of gaming and like all that online multiplayer shit is just going in the wrong
Direction and like I thought it was fucking funny and then like years later or recently or soon afterwards you get people like guys
What's up with the console war stop being such petty assholes? I'm like you killjoy dumbass. You don't know what this is
Let's let's do it
I want a fucking episode of us talking about fights and how people do it all wrong like people take stuff seriously when it shouldn't be and
People stick to have not serious. I should be because like because like so much fighting on the internet is like someone like see something on Twitter
And they go that's gay then they type like ergue
You're a big asshole head, but then smarmy YouTube people are like look at all these people being so worked up about it
You know like they think that that guy's like all worked up
But he's he just typed a bunch of exclamation marks in his tweet because he thought it was funny, you know
That's it's it's hard to tell when people are serious and a lot of people are just assumed to be serious all the time
That's tough. Yeah, we should educate the people on that. That's a good idea
Um, here's a shit. There was one more that was decent
Filling time filling time get through a sea of not good questions
It was it was here god damn it
Hurry up. I want to get my pizza. I found it. I found it. Okay. Here's our last question
No, you mate
We got to get out at no you mate asks how okay, this one might get real so
How satisfied yeah, how satisfied is each one of you with their work right now? Oh my
I think my work is the best it's been in a while at least in terms of productivity, so I'm pretty good agreed
Uh, all of my work is garbage. It's retarded
Uh weird meta content that appeals to absolutely nobody and has no point and the only good stuff
I make is stuff that I just write and that that never sees the light of day that no one ever gets to see
um my satisfaction with my current output would be um
Like a light eight which is editing digi's videos, right? That's pretty good. My satisfaction with like my workflow
is like
All is like a strong nine and my satisfaction with where I think my work is going like the direction that my output is going
I would say is also like a 9.75. So I'm pretty sad
Fuck you people being happy
Yeah, that's the meme that needs to die if i'm not happy nobody yeah me and tom are going to start our own podcast called the
Everyone's do happy
Tom feel like also we love old video games
Jesse and tom should do like a jessie and tom cast me as a way for me, okay?
Feel free the reason we're not happy jess is we played too much shinobi and killed all of our joys
It's a new weekly podcast on this channel the airing of grievances with tom and jess
Every week after the pcp. We just shit on everyone for real
I I'm also uh, I I I hate how I'm actually I you know, here's a here's a confession
I'm like learning now how to make fast videos. I don't know how to make fast videos
I'm trying to figure it out. Dude. It's really hard. We're all perfect do it like that forever
Those are good. Those are good. It's I'm kind of used to giving myself space to take as long as I want
Can't do it can't do it anymore. It's because you don't like fast food. You go to take inspiration
Oh, I gotta go to burger king first. Yeah, I gotta gotta go back to eating at burger king
But pita
You brought it back you brought the forgotten meme back
Thank god, uh, I love it. I love it double batman really appreciated that one. I'm sure
Uh, okay, that's it enough for questions. Uh, thanks for asking everybody make sure you send us more at tp
Crassinators when we fucking record them set about through throughout the week. Uh, whatever. Fuck you and remember everybody
Whatever you do. Don't trade pants with the crappy pants man. That's the moral of this week
That's right. All right. Thanks for listening everybody. We'll see you next time
Working right now, I'm supposed to be working
What the hell is wrong with me