Welcome to another Pro Crastinators Podcast, Ben Saint. And who else is here?
There's me, Gibbontake, and we've got Tom Oliver.
Henshinagogo, baby. Wow.
And we've got our buddy, our lord and savior, our master of disaster drawing.
Kaiju Koon.
You used to be called Nexus Mania, some people might know you as Nexus Mania.
The artist formerly known as Nexus Mania.
No, no. I don't know who that is.
Okay, deal.
It's me, yeah. I made it. I'm here.
You made it.
What do you do, Kaiju Koon?
What's your fucking deal?
What's my fucking deal?
What's your fucking problem?
I draw cartoons.
Okay.
What a degenerate.
I guess that explains it.
I do art. I'm actually opening commissions today.
I do comics. I work as a video editor and I breathe.
You're very prolific.
I'm not sure about that last one.
Not for long. By the end of this podcast, that last one might not be true anymore.
Oh, no.
You're very prolific. You feel like you draw pretty fast.
You put out a lot of pieces.
It's cool. It's pretty good.
You've done a lot of PCP related fan art, which would be very embarrassing,
if not for the fact that you've drawn so much that you've drawn plenty of other stuff too.
Much more other stuff, so it's not weird.
It's not weird or anything.
Imagine as my whole deal was just a PCP fan artist.
Imagine how your deal was just on PCP.
That'd be pretty kind of based, though, actually.
You would have gotten on this show a lot faster if that were the case.
Yeah.
So you've really shot yourself in the foot.
So here it's January 10th, 2021.
What's going on?
What's on everyone's docket for this week?
Well, Ben, you said to me that you wanted to talk about the Mr. Boop ending.
Oh, that's right.
Because last week you hadn't read it.
I hadn't read it.
So you've read it now.
I have read it.
Well, what did you think about?
Wait, Nexus and Tom, have you read Mr. Boop?
Tom, you have.
No, Kaiju.
What?
I'm sorry.
Don't use the dead name, Ben.
I apologize.
Have either of you read Mr. Boop?
Who's read Mr. Boop?
I have not read Mr. Boop.
I don't even know what it is.
I remember mentioning it to you, Tom, what it was, and it was like the concept is a guy
is drawing a comic where he is in the comic and his wife is Betty Boop and she's hot
and she loves him.
Oh, yeah.
And it's like.
That did sound like the greatest thing ever.
It is like an absurdist sort of comic.
It goes into a lot of interesting places.
And some of the lines are just, some of the comics are like so stupid that they can't,
like they're genius.
Yeah.
The early ones are really, have just a really iconic, like really funny bits like, I don't
know, I want you to, I want you to take this gun.
Oh no, no, what is it?
Like, are you the, is this the divorce attorney?
We don't usually call it that, but yes.
I want you to take this gun and if I ever try to divorce my wife, Betty Boop, I want you
to shoot me through the head.
Amazing.
It's, it's so, so what did you think of the ending, Gib?
I, I thought it was okay.
I mean.
Yeah.
There was something about it.
I agree.
It was already.
Spoilers, spoilers, spoilers, spoilers.
Big spoilers.
They get a divorce?
No, no, no.
I mean, lots of things happen, but the ending is a video with Neon Genesis.
What's the, comes to Sir Todd?
Where have you say it?
What, one of those songs?
Yeah, you said it right.
Why are you, why are you pretending that you don't know how to say it?
I thought you had a funny accent.
You're supposed to say it with an accent.
I don't know.
Has that music playing the classic like Ava music and the, in the comic, in the comic,
there's like, it's just a mishmash of like, well-known characters from other media, like
Peter Griffin from Family Guy.
I want to reiterate.
I really want to say, if you have not read Betty Boop, I really don't want to spoil it
for anyone.
You mean Mr. Boop.
Mr. Boop.
What did I say?
Betty Boop.
You said Betty Boop.
If you have not read Mr. Boop, I really think you'd be better off reading it instead of
getting spoiled here, and it won't take you very long to read.
Damn.
I would like to read it, but I'm in the show.
What should I do?
Should I kill myself?
You should, you should kill yourself.
Just, just honestly, honestly, if you want to like mute, if you want to mute your fucking
headphones.
Let's go, let's go on another chat.
Let's talk about Garo.
I can, I can at you guys when we're done, if you, if you want.
I don't know.
I'm willing to accommodate you on this, but I want to talk about it.
If, how much do you want to talk about it though, in spoiler territory?
You know what, we don't have, we don't really have to spoil it that much.
I just want to say about the ending, that like, okay, yeah, it is, it is a big, it is
a big Ava reference.
And uh, I didn't, I'm not telling, I'm not, I'm not answering that question.
And like, it's kind of funny.
It's not like, it's not, it doesn't blow me away or anything.
It's just like, yeah, okay, ha, ha, they ended it with a big Ava reference.
Like the conceit of the ending is fine and it works and it makes sense and it's all right.
Uh, uh, and it's like, okay, and, and, and I'm, and I'm happy that it does have like
a satisfying ending that makes sense.
It doesn't suck like the ending of Homestuck, but it's not like, it's, it doesn't really
end with a bang either.
It just kind of is like, okay.
We told the story, we draw it to a satisfying conclusion.
Yeah.
What it feels like to me is like a boomer that is, is, is like trying to be hip and
they've learned about like over 9000, but they're using it a little bit too late.
That's what it feels like.
Really?
That's, that's harsher than I would be.
Well, not in a, like a horrible way.
Like I agree with you.
It's like, that was a pretty good ending, but like, I don't know.
I feel like the Ava sort of thing, maybe he's played out, but I don't know why I think
that.
I feel like he could, like, I, the, the ending being a video, the ending being in video format
is fine and it works.
I think that I, this, oh God, we're, it's, it's back to the classic thing of like I
don't like pastiche and I think that references are lame.
I think this reference was like not super great and didn't add like a ton to it and
it probably could have been something else.
Yeah.
Honestly, the fact that the ending is just a giant Ava reference is kind of like, well,
but Betty, Mr. Boop is, is great on its own.
Like it's sort of like, oh, it ends with, I know that's isn't the case, but it almost
feels as though the entire comic was just leading up to a big Ava reference and like,
but I don't think that's not, okay, that's why I think it doesn't work.
Like I don't actually think that.
That's just kind of how it feels when the entire like climax is an Ava reference.
It's like, eh, did it really deserve that?
Is it, does it merit that level?
I don't know.
Yeah.
I'm being, I'm being a little more critical than I think.
Well, it's only, it's only because the comic up to that point was so good that it's like,
yeah, the ending doesn't feel bad.
It just feels like, like, okay, sure, I wasn't expecting that, but I, whatever.
I think it's kind of a safe ending.
You could kind of see where the ending was going.
It's pretty quirky though.
You could, it was pretty easy to see how it was going to end, like while you were reading
Act 4, like it was like, it wasn't really subtle about where it was going.
So you know, but you know what, it came, it had its run, it ended, and that's all the
ending really needed to do and it did it.
So, you know, thumbs up, 10 out of 10.
Yeah.
Glowing review of Mr. Boop, Reed, it'll take you like an hour at most, maybe.
Oh, maybe, yeah, not very long.
Nice.
It's like, what is it, maybe like 200, 200 strips, maybe not even that many.
Yeah, 200, four panel strips or something like that.
Yeah.
Yeah, comics.
Nothing, nothing can top Dr. Sonic the Hedgehog though.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Okay, I want, I do want to update everyone on something of much greater importance than
that.
I just want to let everyone know where I'm at mentally and where I'm at mentally is
that I have been watching Bitcoin just go off a fucking cliff.
Morning.
It's so bad.
No, it was like, it was doing pretty decent and then it was doing like, okay, it's just
kind of hanging on and then just today obliterated.
So literally, just today I literally watched like all my games just go up in flames.
You fool.
No, you fool.
You fuck.
I hate you.
I fucking hate you.
How dare you?
How dare you fucking criticize me?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, it's not for the, what is the Teddy Roosevelt thing about the doer of deeds?
I'm the doer of deeds.
You're over here on the sidelines going, you could have done better.
You could have invested here.
It's because it's true there.
You could have made more money.
You could have made more money, you know, you're the fucking nerd.
No, you're the fucking bitch.
I'm calling you a fool for doing anything at all.
I'm technically haven't lost money.
So there's that.
Like last time I checked you were saying like, oh, I've made like technically like a thousand
dollars.
Yes.
Two, if I had sold two days ago, I would have been, I would have turned like a thousand
dollar profit today.
I'm up like a hundred dollars, but you know, it is what it is.
Easy come, easy go.
Am I right gamers?
That's, that's just, it's way too stressful for me.
Yeah, I need, yeah, this has been my week.
This has been my week just, you know, watching fucking queue people storm the capital and
watching Bitcoin just bounce around, uh, sad, sad times for Ben saying it.
Yeah, I guess did we, the last PCP episode that it hadn't happened yet.
Do we want to talk about the insurrection at all?
It's sort of like a bigger thing that happened.
We should probably, I mean, probably, yeah, you could say something about it.
You could say that.
Oh, you know, that was, that was a pretty big gamer moment.
Not gonna lie.
That was a pro real, a major, major gamer moment in American history right there.
I was like watching it live, like before we started streaming on the, before we started
streaming on Shekels for Hekels Gib, I, like I had like someone's video feed from the thing
opened and I was like watching them live as they were like, as the first as they were
like, you know, like rushing the police barricades and then like storming up the steps and then
like pounding on the big iron door at the front of the Capitol building.
Like I was watching all that happen live and I was like, oh, this is neat.
This is interesting.
Yeah.
The time it was just sort of like, wow, huh, strange, like I'd never heard of something
like that happening.
Yeah.
Man, these guys really want a PS5, like really bad.
They had all of them.
They could have forced Sony to make more.
That's what they were.
Nancy Pelosi was scalping all the PS5s and they had to go get them.
I want to play Steven Jones.
All these, all these fucking private military contracts.
She's like in there with like hundreds of boxes like we have to pay back the deficit
somehow.
All these like all the, all these fucking like petite bourgeois, like fucking like jet ski
dealership owners and like glazier contractor standing outside just like we're, you know,
it's for the man who's got everything.
What's the only thing they don't have is a PS5 and they know, they know where the supply
is.
It feels kind of stupid to talk about because I'm like, I know I'm not like on the level
of a political commentator and then all I can really say is like, Dan, that's fucked
like that's stupid.
Why would I bring it up?
Why did I do that?
But I don't know.
It like started happening and it's like, oh, that's pretty stupid.
And then I went to bed and then I woke up and it was still going on like, oh, that's pretty
stupid.
And then I just went about my day.
You know what?
I'm, I'm happy at the time I was looking at it and I was like, oh wow, this is just happening
and like nobody's doing anything about it.
It seemed for a minute there that just like nobody was going to do anything about it.
But now it's like a big fucking deal.
And that's, and I'm glad, I'm glad they got in trouble with the, with the authorities.
I'm glad I see like a few people like with their mugshots, like they're being the people
like that guy who had the, the podium, he was like, haha, I got the podium.
Like he's in jail or at least is convicted of something.
Yeah.
We know what it is.
I hope he made the same face for his mugshot that have been a good meme.
No, it's the opposite.
It's like the opposite.
It's a smile on optimism, optimism gun.
I thought storm in the capital and stealing shit would not lead to this, but I unfortunately
who?
Yeah.
Um, oh God, I'm, I'm sorry, I'm just distracted this Bitcoin is still, it's gone even lower
while you've been talking and I'm upset.
You want to know how to instantly make Bitcoin go, go to the moon, sell it, look at your
keyboard, hit alt, then press F4 and all of a sudden all your problems will be over.
Go to make Bitcoin, to make all the Bitcoin problems, go to into your hard drive and delete
system 32 and then, and then just live your life and just live normally from then on.
Oh, it's plummeting.
Oh no.
I'm upset.
It has, it has to stop.
It has to stop sometime, right?
Like this can't continue.
Like this, this, uh, uh, uh, someone call, call the police, call the police and, and
put a stop to this.
No, Ben, you need to stop.
You got to buy low.
Oh, that was your mistake.
You didn't buy low.
I was, I was supposed to buy low and sell high.
Oh, easy to get those mixed up, but you know.
Okay.
Well, I mean, wait, if you had it wrong way around, surely it plummeting would be a good
thing in your mind.
It has, it has officially crossed the point, it has just crossed the threshold wherein
I have just started to lose money.
That's good.
That means you can buy.
As opposed to having, having turned to profit.
Now's the time to buy.
So to go back up and you'll make money.
Hmm.
Don't give him ideas.
He's actually considering it.
No.
It's okay.
That's, that's a great point.
That's a great point.
Oh, it's good.
It's going to happen again.
So the cycle never ends.
Okay.
The real demon souls is this.
You have to understand we're on, this is a new year.
We're on the cusp of, of, of, you know, boring, old, trite, been there forever.
Socialist Ben St is finally going to die.
Capitalist Ben St is being born before our eyes.
It's going to be an amazing year.
Hmm.
You know, no, no, no, no, no.
So is, is fat, is fat been like the beginning of the arc?
Yeah.
You have to be a fat cat capitalist.
Right.
He has the fat part down.
Yeah.
Now he's going to get the cat part down.
When, when's catburn coming?
Hmm.
Sooner than any of us would like.
Yeah.
But about that.
I really should probably stop looking at it.
I'm, I'm, I'm okay.
I'm, I'm actually going to just not look at it for a little bit.
Cause I think that the thing that was getting me most is not like what happened and the
you know, of like how it occurred and all that.
It's the people responding on Twitter and, and places where I keep seeing really, really
discouraging, depressing arguments from people who just don't understand anything that's
happening in front of their eyes, defending it, thinking that it's Antifa that did it,
even though it clearly isn't just, it's, it's, it's, it just adds to all of this like annoying,
like nobody, nobody gets it anymore.
Okay.
I've seen, I've seen the people claiming that it was Antifa, but it doesn't really seem
like anyone buys it.
It, it, it doesn't really seem like that is a narrative that is going to like stick and
people.
Sure.
It just, I don't know.
It's, it's, it's not even just like the, the outrageous stuff is the um, I don't know,
the implicit like, like, I don't really care about this.
And I would rather point out how BLM was like, that more buildings were burned in that one.
Like, like the implication being that, I don't know, this was good at all.
Yeah.
This wasn't, this wasn't actually bad at all.
Or, or if it was bad, it was less bad than that other thing that those other guys did.
And it's just, yeah.
That's all right.
I've been a bit like recently.
Yeah.
Good.
Let the rage consume you.
Get radicalized.
But I'm not, but I'm not good at yelling and throwing Molotovs.
I'm not good at that.
Um, it's okay.
You can throw Molotovs inside.
You just got to throw Molotovs in Animal Crossing.
That's going to make YouTube videos talking about these things.
That's, that's how you do it.
That's the secret.
Hello.
Welcome to YouTube.
You're already here.
And here's my opinion on the things that are happening.
That's real activism right there.
Yeah.
Fuck.
It's never enough.
It's never enough to do the bare minimum.
I sure wish it was enough to do the bare minimum and even less than that.
In fact.
Hmm.
Well, all of that stuff is fun.
But all I did this week was buy PlayStation one games.
And you know what?
That was time and money well spent in my book.
Yeah.
True.
It's going to be pretty sick.
I got vagrant story.
Oh, resident evil two.
I got dino crisis.
I got mega man legends one and two.
Uh, did you know that they had like a first party like dual flight stick for PS one?
I got that and it works with descent, which is one of my favorite games.
So you can like fly around in a ship.
Oh, it's going to be great.
The capitals getting in like fucked up, but I'm going to be playing descent with a flight stick.
It's all good.
Wow.
Life is good.
It's great.
It's going to be a great time.
It's for sure.
Hell yeah.
Well, yeah, games are pretty good.
Yeah, I miss the PS one.
Dude, PS one.
I do.
I never had a PS one as a kid.
This is all new to me.
I've never played any of those games before.
I've never had a PS two.
I haven't played any single PS two game besides Metal Gear.
I've said it before and I'll say it again, but it's all been downhill since the Super Nintendo.
Wow.
Imagine.
Don't laugh.
I'm not joking.
Don't laugh at me.
No, I'm laughing.
I'm laughing.
I'm serious.
That was a good joke.
You might be serious, but...
You're still wrong.
All right.
I can buy the idea that it's all downhill since the Super Nintendo, because I never had one.
It may be even better than the PlayStation one and two, but the PlayStation one and two
are still incredible and so fucking good.
It didn't dip down to the depths that we currently live in, at least with AAA development.
It wasn't like Bitcoin today or anything.
Shattering the glass floor, just dragging me down into the poor house.
It wasn't anything like that, is what you're saying.
Do they have glass floors in those analogies?
Well, I mean, you understand what I mean.
I know.
It's a volatile market.
Everything has to be made of glass.
Glass walls.
Everything's made of glass.
Yeah.
When it goes up, it shatters the glass ceiling.
When it goes down, it shatters the glass floor.
When it stays the same, it's exploding all of the glass walls around it.
It's the same.
Just smashing left and right with glass shots flying everywhere.
Always shattering.
Always remember to wear your goggles, otherwise you get permanent blindness.
Bad advice to throw stones in your glass house.
It's all one interconnected metaphor.
Those who use Bitcoin shouldn't, because you'll get glass in your eye.
She is right.
Okay, no more looking at Bitcoin.
Close the tap.
I do kind of like cryptocurrency conceptually as the torrent of currency, because you can't
block torrents.
It's just like a function of computers.
You can block the sites, but the torrent files is a way to share things that you can't...
It's the capacity for email.
There's not a company that can own the torrent and then stop people being able to get things.
In that way, it can't be fucked with as a currency Bitcoin, like real currency.
That's what they say.
That's why they say you got to hodl it.
There's something happening.
People were trying to make money.
I know it's like right-wing media, people, pundits, and Trump, and everything getting
banned off of all these things.
People are saying, oh, that's bad.
It's bad for free speech.
I'm like, it's good that he and they are gone.
Free speech was already...
It's not good that they have such control and such a interconnected communication that
they can't even do that.
I just agree with what they've done this time.
Yeah, absolutely.
It is bad that they have the power to ban anyone they want, and that they've basically privatized
our town square, basically, is what someone on Twitter says.
I just wish they were honest about it.
Because Twitter finally pulls the plug on Trump.
And then just like with Alex Jones, everyone in the media is like, oh, well, now all of
a sudden, yeah, it's R against R terms of service too.
It's like, all right, you were just waiting for someone to fire the first shot.
You just wanted to get rid of something you didn't like.
I would have much more respect.
You're just like, you know what?
We kind of just fucking hate this guy, so now he's gone.
Just be honest with me, please.
You're not fooling anybody.
Just be honest.
Just be like, orange man was bad, and we didn't like it anymore.
Just say that, please.
It's like, yeah, they shouldn't be able to do this kind of thing to anyone.
I would prefer it if it were publicly owned and like a public asset and common property
that everyone could use equally.
But if it is a private company and they are going to bring the hammer down as they see fit,
then yeah, I would prefer it if it came down on people that I think are worse.
Yeah, I mean, I've watched this Valsh.
I keep saying his name's stupid.
It's Valsh.
Valsh.
It's Valsh Stream like yesterday where he was talking about this, and there's like people
who translate thinking that Donald Trump being banned is good with I support these giant corporations
when the two things happening are different.
It's bad that the corporations can do this on such a completely, like all over the place,
like they have all over the internet.
Like if they wanted to silence you, they could from as many possible things, including like credit cards,
like Mastercard and Visa or whatever, stopping people being able to pay you if they really wanted to,
which is why Bitcoin is cool.
But like, it's bad that that can happen.
But it's good when a bad person is blocked from a social media application for doing bad things,
which is a different question.
It is a different question.
So I've seen a lot of people saying it's hypocritical to think those two things at the same time,
and it really isn't.
No.
I just wanted to say it on my platform, the Procrastinators podcast.
I guess my only concern with banning Trump and all this shit is that you've basically just,
this entire narrative with Q is basically just like you're giving them all the ammo they need to like quintuple down
on everything they think.
I know what you mean, but like, you can't just let them have their way just because, oh, it'll upset them if we stop them.
Yeah.
Well, I'm not even saying that.
It's just that you've just, you're just going to, I guess like the problem is that these,
everything that's happening right now, and it seems like it's inevitability that it's just going to result in like a complete fracture of society.
And there's just going to be two alternate spheres of reality going on at the same time, you know, because like they've,
they already had this big movement on Parler.
Now Parler is being shut down by everything.
So like all these people are going to go somewhere else.
And then there's just going to be two narratives going on where both sides believe they're right and the other side's wrong.
And it's just like, okay, well, we're getting, we're just inevitably leading to a point where like society breaks down.
Because it's like, okay, there's just two different versions of literally, because like my dad is like a conservative and believes everything.
He believes that the Antifa were there, like all that shit.
And it's just like, okay, well, like there's nothing, it's just, what are you going to do?
Well, that's the thing.
Like there's no convincing people.
This, yeah, in the case of it not convincing people, it already hasn't like, I think the, like it's true that has been going this way for a while.
And that banning Trump is not going to, you know, make anything any better on that front necessarily.
Maybe some extremely casual, right-leaning people would be like, oh, he's not on Twitter anymore.
I guess I'll forget about it.
I don't know how many people like that there are, but that's the only difference.
The thing is just like, his Twitter was still there the whole time and it was continually getting worse.
People were still getting in the bubbles despite having, you know, all this.
I think it's just sort of, it's wrongheaded to think that banning them, like it is too little too late.
But like banning them doesn't necessarily, it doesn't do much, but that doesn't mean that having them is a good thing either.
Well, it just gets them out of your way, I guess.
And like maybe that's like not the grace thing because like every time Trump says something stupid on Twitter,
like we could see it and be like, wow, that's fucking retarded and like know that there was that dumb shit.
Now it's just going to be on some site.
None of us go on.
And so the next stupid thing that happens, none of us are going to know about.
And who knows how it's going to spiral out of control when there's not like people like calling out the bullshit as it happens.
So I don't know.
I'm not, I'm not sold on it.
I guess I'm just like, I've seen, like it's been out in the pub, out in the open for so long anyway.
Like they were planning this, this insurrection thing on, on Facebook openly.
And it's like, nothing ever gets done about it, despite us knowing about it ahead of time.
So like, what does it matter?
If we, if we agree that like the kind of rhetoric that like Trump's rhetoric is like, is like dangerous,
is like the equivalent of like yelling fire in a crowded theater, right?
If, if we agree on that, then I don't buy that like, oh, banning it will just drive it underground or it confessed her in secret.
It's better to have it out in the open.
I don't think that's true.
I think it's, it's worse if it's more public.
It's more emboldening to people who agree with it.
So that's my thinking on that.
But I'm confused.
I'm a little confused about like, okay, I, if Twitter wants to ban Trump, you know, that's, they can do that, I suppose.
And what's the, like, what's the reason why, like, all these other accounts are getting suddenly deactivated?
Is it just because it's like-
I think it's just a knock-on effect.
I think everyone was just waiting for someone to fire the first shot.
The same thing with Alex Jones, you know?
It's like-
What do you mean, like, do you mean like, the different right-leaning people?
You mean to say that Twitter, that Twitter was waiting for Trump's presidency to end to like defund, to like, or not defund,
to like ban people, like, the quartering and like, stone toss and stuff?
Like, I don't, that doesn't make any sense.
I just think this is, this is like, this is, this is the, um, this is the incident that like, was the straw that broke the camel's back.
And they're finally just like, trying to wipe everything out.
And just like, you know what, I don't, we don't want this shit anymore.
And they're getting rid of it.
And I don't know-
I guess-
I think what it is.
Once the dam's been broken, it's easier to just keep the fucking momentum going.
It's not so much a political thing.
I don't know, I feel like-
From the perspective of these companies, I don't think it's like, we've wanted to get rid of Donald Trump for a while because we're politically against him.
And now is the perfect time.
I think it's more that this incident has made right-leaning things, like, obviously bad to the point that they're going to lose money.
And it's all about money.
So like-
I guess, I guess it wasn't all those like, mass shootings that have happened before.
It's like, let on by exactly the same stuff.
Well, hasn't-
I think this is just, this is more like, in the minds of the average person, this is more clearly like a Trump and a right-leaning thing.
Conservatives did this to the Capitol building to try and overturn democratically elected, whatever.
So it's like, wow, that's so blatant.
There's no way that that isn't going to look bad if we keep it up.
I guess they must have had some sort of like, they were in the discord call, like just like this one.
And they were saying these things like, hmm, I just want more money, so I'm just going to get rid of them all.
Like the optics were just too bad, you're saying.
It's like, it's suddenly became apparent that like, okay, keeping these people around is now too much of a liability.
Yeah, I think it's more about money than it is about individuals at the top caring about Trump.
I mean, it's never really been about that.
It's always been about money.
I mean, that implies that implies then that they were keeping like track of like who is like spouting conservative, like like like ultra like nationalist rhetoric.
But they had a list of like, okay, there's Trump and like here, here's a here's a list of people who are like in that camp and we can ban them if we decide they need to go and now they've decided they need to go.
Yeah, that means that they've been like keeping tabs on it.
That's the scary.
I don't like that.
Yeah, I agree.
It is scary.
Big tech is really scary.
That's that's one thing.
You know, you got to hand it to them.
You got to hand it to these fascist psychopaths when they're right, they're right.
And big tech is scary.
That's that much I can agree with.
I mean, I do agree that like giving like having this consolidation of all this power with these like handful of companies is fucking terrible.
It just really sucks that any time you try and make an alternative to it, you're naturally just going to attract the worst possible actors because they're the ones who have to use it.
And so those spaces are ruined and nobody is going to want to use them because you're surrounded by fucking psychopaths.
And so the monopoly continues because no one wants to go hang out with Nazis.
Yeah, because it's the it's the people that got it's the people that got banned from the mainstream platform.
It's like bit shoots a great fucking concept.
It's a peer to peer YouTube alternative.
That's great.
Too bad everybody on there is like fucking terrible.
And it's like, I want to talk about my little pony down there.
I'm talking to fucking fly.
I guess maybe it will.
It's been cheap.
There's apparently a bunch of Nazis who are into ponies now.
So I don't fucking know.
So so I've heard.
Yeah.
Bitcoin.
Bitcoin update.
It's bounce back.
Close the tab.
It's up.
It's up from the profit line.
It's a little bit up from the profit line.
I'm in the green, baby.
Eleazar, I want you to edit in a chart of the Bitcoin live going up and down.
Yeah, live.
I should be screen recording right now.
Honestly, maybe next episode I will.
If you haven't gone broke by then.
Pretty fuck.
Yeah, true.
If I'm not in the poor house.
Hey.
Our guest.
When am I getting more bunny wave?
Let's talk about something that's not gay.
When's more bunny wave?
My favorite web comic.
So hey, that's what's going on with the world, huh?
I've been like living like a hermit.
I just stopped watching social media.
I stopped talking to people.
I stopped everything.
No.
My entire life is just work.
Nothing else.
Just work and consume books, comics and movies and stuff like that.
What a fucking God on ironic.
Then what do you post about?
He posts the work that he does instead of looking at Bitcoin all day.
Yeah.
Oh, Pasha.
Pishposh.
It's right now.
Why work?
Why work when you can just invest in Bitcoin and accrue capital gains, you nerds?
Gross.
The fucking Bragg chat channel in my Patreon Discord server is lit up constantly with
Kydric and posting new things all the time that make me feel like, man, I should probably
work harder and then I don't because I suck.
I feel bad.
That's basically every post there is mine.
Yeah.
You've taken it over and I just want to let you know I have no problem with that.
I feel a little bit of a little pang of guilt every time you post and it makes me get like
3% closer to actually doing something.
So keep going.
In like two months, I might have actually created something like one piece of artwork.
Well, the thing is, I've been working in a lot of comics and just not posting anything
about it.
And right now, I'm redrawing some bunny chapters.
Redrawing?
Yeah.
You're doing a remaster?
Why?
I'm redrawing the entire chapter two and I'm going to redraw some panels from chapter
three.
Doing like the Blu-ray touch-up version?
No, it's more like that.
It's like, you know, I have another character that is called Wolf.
Yes.
So this character is now part of the bunnyverse and there's another character in the bunnyverse
that looks exactly the same.
So I'm changing all his panels and making him look different.
Like, I gave him like a new complete look.
Also, chapter two, it looks terrible, so I ended up like changing the whole pages.
So I'm about to be done with the redrawing.
If you think it looks terrible, if you say it looks terrible, then...
Yeah, it looks shit.
I will just have to take your word for it.
Super shit.
Yeah, I hate it so much.
I can't even sleep just thinking about it that chapter two was published.
Can we like post the original version versus the redrawn version of one of these?
Can we get those edited in and sound off in the comments?
Well, you can actually find those posts on a website which is called patreon.com.
Where you can see the comparison between the old ones and the new ones.
Which is quite the difference.
Gotcha.
Very good.
I'm also working on more original comics with a friend of the show, I believe.
Which is called Doon Koon.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's writing a really cool story right now.
He already wrote an entire story for me to one shot.
And it's going to be pretty fun to draw.
I intend to draw that this year.
Is she Doon Koon's a she now?
Oh, really?
See, that's what I'm telling you.
I'm so disconnected from the entire world.
I don't know anything.
Tragic.
See, this is why.
This is why you got to say plugged in and jacked in like me at all times.
No.
So you never say, you never get canceled for something like that.
Yeah, actually, I'm un-canceling.
But if you're unplugged, like Kaiju Koon is you don't have to worry about being canceled
because you're not even on to be canceled in the first place.
You're just in your own shit.
Unplugging from social media is just the first step on the, you know,
engaging in IRL is just the first step towards becoming a Nazi.
That's the IRL to fascist pipeline.
It starts there.
It starts with not posting and getting off Twitter.
That's how they get you.
It starts with you stop like not like live tweeting your Bitcoin reactions on Twitter every five minutes.
Because of idle hands of the devil's workshop.
And if I hadn't been live tweeting my Bitcoin gains and losses,
I would have been in the Capitol building, storming it, knocking down the doors.
You chain down.
Getting that PS5.
If I hadn't invested in Bitcoin, I would have a PS5 now.
Oh, well, that sounds like a good trade to me.
I guess I'm problematic after all.
Big problem.
Fuck.
I used to make comics once upon a time.
Wow.
Making comics.
Can't imagine it.
Right now I'm doing my mysterious construction.
My special project, my secret week.
And that is taking my attention away from comics because it's not a comic.
That's the one special knowledge nugget that you have now that is not a comic that is my secret special thing.
Everybody has secret projects.
My secret project is...
Secret project is the best way to live.
Because that way people say, so what is it?
It's like a secret and you don't have to say anything.
Yeah.
Nobody's asking me like, when is it going to be done?
Because nobody expects anything.
Nobody knows what it is.
Because I haven't told anyone.
I've only, I've alluded vaguely to something and nobody knows what timeframe to expect it in.
Ben, is it a...
Is it a nuclear bomb, Ben?
Is it a super weapon?
Perhaps.
It's just a big...
Metal gear.
The kid.
The day comes and I'm just like, it's Bitcoin.
It was just Bitcoin all along.
I was just accumulating one Bitcoin.
Mass unfollow of Ben's.
And I roll out the giant Bitcoin from behind the door and I'm like, there it is.
And then I pose for it with a photo op.
Ben makes the PC pending review.
Yes, I've been developing my own crypto.
What if it was, what if it was a custom cryptocurrency?
What if I was making slime coin real and that was what it was?
You did, you made them real.
I have one right now.
Right.
But when I say real, I mean publicly traded on the blockchain.
They're already real, but how do we get them on the blockchain?
On 3D print them.
You 3D scan them.
Put them in the scanner.
Kaiju-kun posted.
What?
It's an image.
It's page.
Why would he do that?
Why would he post?
I don't know.
What we're talking about pages.
You just posted cringe.
Kaiju, you're really good at drawing and that's all I have to say.
That's some damn good composition right there.
That's the word I was looking for.
Damn good composition.
We were talking about bunny and the page took a while to export because there's a lot of shit in there.
My God.
That's one of the redrawn pages.
Do you work at like super high resolution?
Yeah.
What resolution?
I mean, it's not that high.
1200 DPI.
That's 600.
600 is pretty high.
That's a lot of pixels.
600 is like bare minimum for print, I think.
That's a good print resolution.
That's the thing.
I'm trying to do two books of bunny.
Are you doing digital toning now?
Because this doesn't look like...
You're not still cutting tones, right?
Yeah, I'm doing everything digitally now.
Alright, thank God.
The man was manually cutting out fucking tone dots and shit for the pages before,
which I can't even believe anyone born after 1990 even knows that's an option.
Incredible.
It took me a while to figure out.
I thought, like, there's no way you could cut it and then stick it down,
and then it would look good.
There would always be a little bit...
Because I used scissors before.
I used little knives, scalpels to cut things out.
It never looked good.
There's always wrong shape.
How'd you guys get that magical power of just making good shit?
I re-opened...
I remade my YouTube channel and I uploaded a video I made way, way back in the time
where I tried like...
I blocked this one piece Hiroda DVD that comes with the man himself drawing.
And there's a lot of exercises.
So in the video, I follow all the steps and all the exercises trying to do drawing.
And you can see me there just cutting those screen tones with the knife and all that stuff.
I can't believe you would cut screen tones with an actual knife.
That's so bizarre.
That's the way you do it.
That's how you get good, Ben.
The results speak for themselves.
No, shut up.
I had a book of how to draw a mango when I was a kid.
And it was like, yeah, you can buy these screen tones, you can cut them with a knife.
And I was like, what the fuck am I looking at?
I mean, I've never seen such a thing in an art store.
Maybe I just wasn't looking in the right places.
It just seemed so esoteric.
I remember just missing that out of hand, being like, that's a lot of work that I'm not going to do.
They're really hard to find and they're also incredibly expensive.
Yeah, exactly.
No idea how expensive they could be.
Jesus.
You know why?
Because manga artists actually earn a lot of money.
What?
Yeah.
Impossible.
The good ones, the top ones, the 1%.
Not me, Ben.
Okay.
The bougie.
Yeah, not you.
We need to redistribute Oat as well, because what I'm hearing right now.
That's right.
I'm going to get his ass.
All this time, One Piece was Oat as well from making One Piece.
That's it.
The real, I guess the, well guys, the manga's over.
I guess the real One Piece was all the money I made along the way.
Oh, that's why Roger reacted that way.
Yeah.
He saw the end and it was just like a, what's that?
What's that?
What is it called when you look into a mirror infinitely?
The recursion.
Recursion?
Like he's watching himself as like, oh, One Piece is One Piece.
Oh, lol.
He starts reading, he gets to the bit where he laughs and he laughs again.
What if, what if they, what if they get to Raftel and they find it and it's all just a bunch of books and it's all just One Piece, the manga and it's meta.
The real One Piece is literally the manga series One Piece from the real world universe.
Oh, that just draws himself in like photo realistic style.
Yes, he photo bashes himself into this fucking.
No, it would be like the fake straw hats from Shibaldi.
Shibaldi.
Yeah, sure.
We got to bring those guys back.
Underrated.
Fan favorites.
Well, that would be the worst possible thing to ever happen in manga history, in my opinion.
That's why it's going to happen.
Yeah.
Okay.
I really, I really admire your, your skill level next.
Kaiju.
Excuse you.
Excuse me.
I haven't said it out loud a lot.
But yeah, it's, it's impressive.
I was, I was looking back at my own like Clarissa thing and I'm like, sucks, sucks so bad.
Even though it was like, it was good in the time that I made it, like it like time wise.
But I'm looking at it and I'm like, oh fuck.
It was really fun.
It was, I liked the comic.
I should finish it.
I feel like, I feel like remaking it would be like a, at least right now with my skill level
basically exactly the same would be like an exercise in futility.
I'll just finish it and then put it out and I'll be like, whatever.
Oh, all redrawing is an exercise in futility.
Sorry.
This page looks pretty good.
Well, it's a character design.
You could have just thrown a different page that good.
Yeah, but like, look at that composition.
I'm kind of about it.
Yeah, I kind of, I'm just, I've been learning a lot of manga, manga and comic composition.
That's why I've been reading a lot of shit these weeks.
And that actually helps a lot with motivation stuff.
If it's, I mean, if it's to change, if it's because you need to like change what a character looks like to make the story make sense.
I think that makes sense is perfectly, perfectly reasonable.
Now he looks like an actual character.
Yeah, he looks like, he looks like the kid from the, the world ends with you.
The white hair kid.
You ever play that?
Oh yeah.
That guy.
Yeah.
Now he has to redraw it again, Ben.
Thanks a lot.
Wait, what?
Huh?
What?
What happened?
What did I do?
You compared him to a character that exists.
So now he's got a scrap.
Yeah.
You kill.
You kill myself, Steve, Ben.
I can't draw anymore.
Oh, no, Mike.
Why is that a thing that happens?
A character, he's got, he's got like a sort of similar hairstyle and he's wearing a common type of shirt.
Well, it's, it's goes in the trash.
It's a rip off.
Might as well just be fucking copyright infringement.
You know, it's all over.
I guess to be fair.
I don't know why I've never run into that issue.
To be fair, that's a cool uniform.
So it's not like a regular shirt.
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
It has to be that shirt.
That's, so you're saying it has to be copyright infringement.
You had no choice.
Yeah.
I was a retired officer.
Was no other way.
Your honor.
See the trick, the trick is to like have character designs that are so lame and like lacking
of information.
Nobody else would have ever made them before.
Whatever I've made right.
Nobody would have had a character like red man.
It's the first of his kind.
It's literally true.
He's just red.
But it's so good.
So fucking flawless.
Oh man.
Like people who get their art stolen and put on t-shirts like by a bot on Twitter.
I see sometimes like, it's like bots that look at Twitter artists, download the thing
and then they like cut off the name, like the signature or whatever.
And then they post it on a t-shirt and then they link it in the thing.
It's like, hey, buy it on a shirt and it's like stealing money and all that.
Nobody would ever do that for my stuff.
It's a foolproof plan.
Yeah, but what you need to do is you need to start going to every like regular store
like Target and Marshall's and JCPenney and just start copyright claiming every red t-shirt.
Just be like, that's my original character.
You can't sell a red t-shirt.
That's copyright.
I have a patent on that.
Tom Scott in jail.
Exactly.
I want, I want, I want you guys to, I want to, I want to show you.
Okay.
I've been, I've been teasing this.
I've been teasing this for a while, but I want you to actually see what I've been experiencing over here.
I am going to mark, I'm going to mark the, the, the, the profit line here.
And I'm going to, and I'm going to show you what has transpired in the course of this episode.
Just, just so you have a little context into, into what I'm going through.
Oh, it was bouncing back.
It did bounce back.
But as you see, that's that the peak, the big peak over on the left there, that was two days ago.
And then it's just been kind of, and then today has been the, look how fucking low it did.
That's okay.
I'm, I'm okay.
No more Bitcoin talk.
We got to put, we got to put, take, take your Bitcoin and just put it on the shelf.
Just put it on the shelf, leave it for a rainy day.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm, I'm, I feel like I'm, I feel like I'm crossing a line into being legitimately.
Yes.
So to speak.
Okay.
Anyway, and Eleazar, delete everything I said on this episode.
Delete everything before this point on the episode.
So yeah, delete, give from this episode.
Thanks.
Okay.
No, no.
Double buy.
Like copy, copy, paste.
Now it's just me and Kai Jakun.
We can probably talk about guns.
Snap, snap my fingers.
What I've been waiting for.
Give snaps her fingers and I dissolve.
No, no, no.
Take, take my audio and then like make a new track.
And then copy, paste my audio and then offset it by like half a second.
And then there'll be like two of me.
Now the episode is un-listenable.
This is just multiplying.
No, but like slightly different pitch.
That could be, like, and like, and like they're all different sizes.
There's like a, there's like, there's like, give number two is like a little higher pitch
and she's like smaller.
And then give number three is like a lower pitch and she's just bigger.
And they're just like a sort of cluster.
New bonus episode harmonies.
We have to have our voices harmonizing with other tracks of ourselves the entire time.
What was that called?
Auto tune.
We all have auto tune on.
Everybody has to download the IMT paying app from 2008 and we all have to speak into
that for the entire episode.
Speaking of bonus episode.
Eleazar said that there is now almost an hour's worth of a bonus content of secret
unreleased blooper content, so to speak.
Should we, should we make that?
Do we think?
The cutting room floor stuff?
Yeah.
Eleazar said they've got, he's got 50 minutes.
And I said an hour, but I feel like 50 minutes is pretty good.
Yeah, yeah.
We could get the bits from this maybe.
There might be some bits.
Okay.
All right.
I'll tell Eleazar that yeah, it's time.
It's time to pull the trigger.
It's time to go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators to get that sweet, sweet cutting room floor
pieces, a bonus clip show secret content unreleased behind the scenes.
All the content that was not good enough for their normal episodes that we released for
free.
You can now pay to listen to.
What a value proposition.
Can you imagine?
It's secret.
It's never before seen or heard words out of our mouths, bad ones.
It's like when you, it's like when you are a wild animal and you have to shit, you go
shit somewhere that no one can see.
Well, now you, the listener can go and see that secret place that we put our shit in
so we wouldn't have to smell it.
This pitch is getting even worse.
This is what we have on offer.
I changed my mind.
Ben, go back to looking at Bitcoin.
Clearly having your full attention is not working out for the episode.
Okay.
I apologize.
38173 38181 38176.
Shut up.
Okay.
I want to say that are you, do you have something to say to Kaijuku?
What?
No.
I thought you were going to say something.
I thought you were saying something too.
So the last few months of last year, I was like, it was like very bad.
And I was not doing anything at all of the time of the days of the weeks of the months.
I was felt like shit.
And that is all gone.
And I'm suddenly extremely busy.
The exact opposite problem.
I'm getting so many little things going on that I have to keep track of.
What?
What the fuck is going on?
I don't understand.
Well, it's like, well, the writing work came back.
So now I'm doing writing stuff while my secret project is happening.
Okay.
And because I'm doing stuff now, I'm more like get up and go attitude about getting things
done.
Therefore, like every day I'm getting something done.
Kind of a Goku get them attitude.
I did my taxes the other day.
I cleaned the bath because it needs cleaning.
Like things that I have on my calendar.
I'm like, okay, I got to do this this day.
But my fucking sleep schedule is still like the worst it has ever been.
So I'm waking up at like 4pm and I have a full day of like no time.
So yeah.
That's like hyperbolic time chamber for like getting your shit done.
If you can get all your stuff done in like half of a day.
That's like when you take the weighted clothes off.
When you get up early, all of a sudden you just become a productivity God.
So maybe this is like training.
Maybe, but it's it feels like being stupid and I should just figure out how to.
You'll be like when you're fighting Gar, you just wake up at 8am, you drop those weights
and everybody just flips shit as like the entire stadium fractures in half.
That'll be all.
That was good shit.
You might say he who carries the sharpest blades always hungers lasts.
Wouldn't you agree?
You agree?
Oh, yeah, I remember that.
For context after last was it last episode of the one before that after the after that episode
we we were in the call like doing our audio stuff and I think and I mentioned this Twitter account that I follow called
chock and smirk or at beanie Tuesday and you two were like looking at the tweets
and you posted that one posted in the chat the one of the like every every every.
Every guilty gear character versus every tech and character.
Right.
Yeah.
Jimmy was like Jimmy.
Jimmy from second.
Get ready for a knuckle sandwich.
Oh, it's a classic.
Show it on screen.
Yeah.
Pause the video and enjoy it.
Just soak up every last glorious deep.
Finding it well.
No, keep keep keep talking.
Keep keep going and entertain the people.
Shit.
No, I can't do it.
It's too hard.
It's dude.
Guys, guys, we've done this like 200 and almost 250 times.
It's still really hard guys hard to beg to a podcast.
Talking difficult.
I don't understand.
I don't understand what a podcast even is.
What is a podcast?
That's a good.
From the word from iPod cast iron shackles and you shackle yourself to the iPod and the iPod
looks into your eye and puts peas from its pod into your eye and you talk about that.
And that was the first podcast.
Oh, that sounds way more wholesome than I was expecting.
God God invented the first podcast.
God had the first podcast in the Garden of Eden.
Adam and Eve listened to it.
No, no, no.
What happened is the garden garden of Eden.
The God was like, you have your entire this entire garden, but do not touch the tree of Apple podcast.
As soon as you do that, you will have the knowledge of good and evil.
It would be cast out for my kingdom.
No.
And the snake comes up and puts the earbuds and ears and Eve's ears like you need to listen to this political podcast.
And it was all downhill from there.
I'm saying that was that was the first podcast ever was was when God said, hey, don't eat that Apple Bros.
And that was it.
And it was and then history history ever since has just been a long procession of podcasts.
Remember that time?
Remember when like Abraham Lincoln gave the speech after the Battle of Gettysburg?
That was a great podcast.
Yeah.
Great podcast of history.
Martin Luther King's I Have a Dream podcast was a classic.
Indeed.
Lamal.
I like the simple the simple little podcast that you have with your friends on the school ground.
Every day just talk like podcasting to them.
And then you have that podcast with your teacher.
Yeah.
You had the student teacher podcast every like twice a twice a semester when they would discuss your
progress.
That's why they call that's why they call groups of school kids pods because they're all just getting
together, talking to each other, casting, if you will, casting their ideas around.
That's that's a Canadian thing.
By the way, I'm pretty sure in like Canadian public schools, kids are like grouped into
pods.
And I know.
And I know this and I know this only because in that.
Remember that show My Life Me?
No.
We've talked about My Life Me.
I have gone on tanges about my life.
Okay.
Ben.
I will have to show you.
Yeah.
Shut up.
No, you do.
You do.
I promise.
Okay.
You just screenshot of My Life Me.
Oh, it's so fucking cool.
It's so fucking epic.
It's this this Canadian like pseudo anime.
It's it's like a it's like one of those flash animated cartoons, but it's like an early one.
It's like really.
Oh, I can tell it's an early one.
Yeah.
It's fucking how to draw mangas.
They read the same books I did.
But but like the whole like these kids in the show, they're not like friends.
They're pod mates because in school they're all like they've all been like arbitrarily
sorted into this pod and they just have to like do all their assignments together, even
though like they don't even like each other that much.
That one on the left is pretty crazy with his straight jacket and putting his foot on
the hands instead of this hand.
That's yeah.
What is happening?
Oh god.
That's so weird.
This image is overselling his wackiness.
Well, that's unfortunate.
He's he's he's not like other humans.
He's not actually he's not actually a menace to society.
He's he's just kind of a normal goofy dude.
He doesn't I would personally I would unshackle him given the choice.
He's kind of unhinged though.
No, he's good.
He's wholesome.
He's a good boy.
The goth ones hot though.
Yeah.
Like I'm big 12 true.
Cartoons don't have ages even when they canonically do.
Twitter might disagree.
Anime characters don't look like they're any particular age.
They they're a mere suggestion of a person.
That's all art, Ben.
Yeah, I'm I'm not touching.
Okay, that's true.
I guess that I guess that it's merely a suggestion of reality.
What if it looked like this and you were watching it or reading it?
Yes, accurate, accurate and true and good and based and and democratically
elected Joe Biden 2020.
2020 is over and so is Joe.
I've still got I've still got hashtag Lisa Simpson 2020 in my tag in my
in my Twitter handle and I think I'm going to leave it there for the
foreseeable future.
The dream still lives, you know, the dream still lives.
I mean, Biden hasn't been inaugurated.
A lot can happen.
A lot can happen between now and then.
It's it's always it's always 2020 somewhere.
You know, that's true.
God willing.
There's a little there's a little 2020 in all of us.
You can take the you can take the the the boy out of the out of 2020,
but you can't take the 2020 out of the boy.
It's like they always say hindsight is 2020.
They did they say that now it's true.
That joke.
My whole life.
I've waited for that joke and then it came and everyone made it and I was
like, oh wait, this isn't funny.
I think it was funny enough for one more go.
Now that now that I've exhausted it though, no one can do it.
Future side is 2030.
Oh, shit.
Just an arbitrary increase on the number.
Do you imagine having like a hundred, a hundred eyesight?
That would be pretty good.
Doesn't it get worse as the numbers get bigger though?
Or am I totally making that up?
Wait, what does what does they refer to then?
If you have one one eyesight, do you see things for how they truly are?
That's that's God.
You see you see all the atoms individually.
That's that's what Superman sees, you know.
I don't know.
I don't know what the numbers mean.
And I don't know what my I don't know what my eyesight is and I don't know
what my prescription is.
No, I'm fucked up and that's fucking punk.
I'm so fucked up.
I say looking down at my hands, but my I'm holding my glasses in it, you know,
that fucking graphic that Jim Sterling made that now that's punk thing.
Have you guys watched Jim Sterling at all?
Yeah, yeah.
I'd watch him sometimes, but I don't know.
I don't know the image you're talking about.
Like ever since like the whole cyber punk thing blew up, like he got somebody to
do this like really cheesy, but hilarious looking.
Now that's punk graphic and every time someone says punk now, that's all I think
about because it's perfect.
Well, I haven't I binged some sterling like a month ago, but I haven't really
touched it.
I don't like I don't like keep up with them.
I'll just like, yeah, go back and watch his catalog once in a while.
It's kind of what I do as well.
If there's a big video game, I always go to see what's he got to say about this
one?
Yeah.
No, you got to go to you got to go to angry Joe.
He's he's the game reviewer for the everyman.
For the for the for the white working class for the aggrieved white working
class.
Shout out to my boy skill up.
He's he's he's the guy.
Aside.
Aside from like angry Joe being kind of stupid a lot of the time, his game
reviews are all right.
I kind of like them.
Like I have like no opinion about him whatsoever.
Joe is like he he's not.
I feel like he doesn't really try and be like a critic.
He's just like, I'm a dude who plays video games.
And this is what I think like his stuff is like kind of it is like it's
like unironically in every man kind of approach like, you know, you watch a
lot of critics are just like, this is like a professionally researched
like in depth, like talking about the industry as I know it.
Joe's just like, game fucking sucks.
Or it's fucking rules or it's fucking dope.
It's the actual it's the only he's the only actual reviewer in the
world.
No one else actually reviews things.
They always like they're like stuck with the reviews.
Everyone else tried to elevate it to like analysis and commentary and critique
and all that shit and video essays.
Joe is just like, I'm going to get a cheap five dollar costume.
Do an opening skit.
No, those games.
Good.
The skits are so bad.
They are bad.
It's really I go to angry Joe.
The skits.
I go to angry Joe when I just want to know like, what is this?
This big thing I've heard so much about.
Is it good?
We're angry Joe would usually say if it is or not.
Did they don't fuck it up?
Well, I mean, like, what did he have on the last of us two?
I can't remember.
Like he had like his issues with the story stuff.
And I know that is a bit like blown out of proportion because of the leaks that
happened.
And people, you know, there's a whole big thing with that.
The game itself, I've heard from many different sources that is actually
quite good.
And I don't know.
Like he has his emotional issues with certain things.
But like generally speaking, if you just want to know what is in a game and
he'll tell you.
It's not the best guy.
I just like I find him like the first time I watched him, I was like, this is
stupid, but I guess it's all right.
And I feel I feel obliged to defend him a little bit, even though that doesn't
really need any defending at all.
In fact, I hate him.
Fuck him.
Yeah.
Agreed.
Much, much better.
I'm glad you came around the only reasonable conclusion.
I'm glad we've cleared that up.
A character development tick for give and take now hates angry Joe fucking
stupid idiot.
That's that's Gibbs whole character now is that she hates angry Joe.
Yeah, it seems to throw the rest out in the garbage.
I'm on a epic quest to dislike every YouTube or ever.
One other project is just hating on it.
But they're also likeable.
No, it's that's what they want you to think.
They're also charismatic and unproblematic.
They would never do anything bad because they made me laugh that one time.
They made me laugh and they made me pee my pants and shit myself laughing.
And I just enjoy that moment in my memories.
No, no, I liked it when they groomed me.
They would never groom me in like a in like a bad a bad way.
They groomed me in a bad way.
They groomed me like apes groom each other like a communal grooming.
They washed me.
They washed my feet.
They anointed me with sacred oils.
All right.
They sent me on my way.
What?
All the YouTubers.
I went I went I went to YouTube headquarters and all the YouTubers were there.
Quinn reviews was there and Matthew Matosis was there and PewDiePie was there.
And, you know, it's so on in that order and they all were just like stripped stripped down.
We're going to we're going to oil you up.
But it was in like a but in like a sacred sort of way.
And then they did it.
And I was like, thanks.
He just walked out of the building.
And nothing bad happened.
So don't tell me.
So don't you tell me that my favorite that my favorite Internet content creators are,
are, are, you know, flawed.
Shout out.
Okay.
That's it.
That's the bit.
Bits over.
No more.
I don't know where the bit ends and starts.
This whole podcast is a bit podcast is a bad bit.
Godzilla versus Kong coming out in a few months.
Will it suck?
Yes or yes?
I'm worried about the movie.
I mean, I'm not worried about the movie.
I just want the two guys beat the living shit out of each other.
They're going to make Kong.
They're going to make Kong win.
The guy who's making directing the movie is a big Kong family.
They're going to make the monkey beat Godzilla.
I'm going to make me really mad.
Yeah.
I'm really curious about if they're going to give Kong electricity powers.
Dude, that would be sick.
Like the original one.
That would be unironically based.
That will be super funny.
They have like a toy coming out where they give Kong his big giant axe.
He has an axe.
If he has an axe in the movie, that'd be so fucking sick.
Unironically.
Maybe I'd switch to Team Kong.
He has an axe.
It just beats the shit out of Godzilla with a giant fucking monkey axe.
Godzilla has a tree.
Don't you remember that scene when he grabs a tree?
And that's really funny.
King Kong is a primate.
He's got opposable thumbs.
He can make tools.
So he could definitely make an axe or a gun.
Dude, yeah.
Kong with guns?
All right.
Now we're talking.
All he would have to do is find a giant 3D printer and then he could just 3D print himself
a giant gun.
He doesn't even have to know how to make one.
He just needs the schematics.
And then he can storm the capital to get on the PS5.
He makes a giant 3D printer out of mountains.
He makes a 3D printer out of a volcano into a mold, like the magma coming out there.
King Kong has had enough of these pedophile elites and they're adrenochrome harvesting
and he is going to Washington D.C. to make his voice heard and do something about it.
It's a people's revolution.
Yeah, but when they say like four people died, Kong was all four of those people.
Did you see, wait, I have to mention this because I didn't see this.
Like I saw like one tweet about this and that was it.
And I feel like people aren't talking about it.
Did you see the clip of that woman who's like, they pushed me down and maced me.
We're storming the capital.
It's a revolution.
Do you know what I'm going to say about it?
I have seen that clip edited in a funny way, but I don't know what the original was.
Okay.
Well, I saw a tweet pointing out that if you look, it kind of looks like when she's like
rubbing her face in her hand with it has the towel on it that she's wiping her face with.
She seems to be holding an onion and is like rubbing her face with an onion to like fake that she's been maced and like
make herself cry and make her like eyes, eyes inflamed.
Yeah.
So weird.
I saw that.
There's a couple of frames in it.
You could see she's like, she's rubbing on her face and then she puts it down.
And there's like this white round thing that she's holding and it looks exactly like the resolution is not amazing,
but it really looks like an onion.
And yeah, some people are saying I was just a little blown away.
It's so weird that someone would do that.
Yeah.
Some people were saying in the comments that like for some reason there's like a myth that like an onion can help with tear gas like
like rubbing with an onion will help like not like tear gas.
I don't know if that's real or not because like that's never a problem I've ever had to consider.
I mean, obviously it doesn't work.
I don't know if that's like a common misconception or not, or if that was just something people on Twitter were saying.
That's really weird.
That's something special is like tear gas.
If it was, you know, if it was something like that.
Okay, okay.
I could, I could see that, but like one thing I don't buy that this woman would have brought an onion like in preparation for
she got tear gas because these people were not expecting to be with police resistance.
Because it was impromptu, right?
Why would you bring an onion to a Trump rally?
I mean, I don't know if it was impromptu.
They were not expecting to meet with police resistance.
They were not expecting to get maced and shot.
There were definitely people who came to that thing with equipment and like were prepared to do certain things.
There's that image of that one guy had those like a ziplock ties to like handcuff people with.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, true.
I got, I said I got maced.
I didn't really get maced, but I did breathe some tear gas one time.
Just like, just like, I was just on the periphery of the cloud.
I got like the barest little whiff of it at one time.
That was enough for you.
You went home.
I went, I wanted more, but they were like, the cops are just like, leave us alone.
Stop asking us to gas you.
I need the cloud, please.
I need it to weed.
The cloud?
Oh, the cloud.
The cloud, the clouds for cloud.
That's, that's the new, the new nonprofit events.
That was, that was when I went to the, the, the counter protest for the straight pride parade last year.
Oh man.
The one that Milo was at and they had one float.
They had one Trump float and Milo was on it just waving and it was, it was pretty sad.
Honestly.
Wait, straight pride.
He's not even straight.
Is he?
No.
That doesn't make any sense.
But he's just, you know, he's just, but he's, he's there to be a provocateur because,
because he knows, because he knows that this is going to trigger the libs.
And you know what?
It did.
So good for him.
He did it.
The system works.
Mmm.
Good times.
Oh, those are the days.
Oh, those are the days of going outside.
Oh yeah.
That's right.
Imagine, I forgot.
I forgot all about the before times.
I am.
No, keep them.
Keep them in your heart.
I'm like, keep them in your heart.
So lost.
Should I reconnect myself with the world to understand what you guys mostly talk about?
No.
Here, I'm going to save this.
All right.
Here's something that you don't need context or world understand.
I found, and I found, I mean, someone showed me the greatest, the greatest shitpost of
our time.
It's called flex air five.
Everyone needs to watch flex air five.
I tweeted it.
If the link will be in the description.
It says this is like video and available.
Get a VPN.
Find a way to watch.
Another upload.
Wait a minute.
It's the most incredible shitpost I've ever seen in my life.
It's like a full 3D animation, like kit bash shitpost.
I can't even describe it.
It's multimedia art of the highest caliber.
It's amazing.
It's like a sequel.
It's like this is a whole series.
There is.
There is a series.
There's four others before this.
I did see this or maybe I didn't see this one, but I saw something like this, like, or
maybe just a clip of it somewhere.
I saw Saver Swag did a stream and he like showed this and I was just happened to catch it.
And that was like a week ago.
I can't stop thinking about this video.
It like changed my life.
It's so good.
It's just the funniest, like the amount of effort that went into this for nothing is just
incredible because like,
Well, it's not for nothing.
I guess saying nothing is a bit like hyperbolic, but just like, it's just a meme.
It's a meme.
It's a meme compilation taken to like a like an unexpected extreme, which makes it a whole
other layer of joke.
Yeah.
I think I've seen bits of this.
Yeah, this is really.
There's there's a lot going on in this.
This is amazing.
And every time I watch it, I notice something new.
Like the last time I watched it, I realized, oh, the like speedometer in Shrek's car is
an RTX 3080 graphics card with like little dials put on it.
Like, why would you do that?
I don't know.
Okay.
It's incredible.
Hmm.
What's the, I don't know.
Is there like a story behind?
I don't know.
There is it.
Well, it's just a series of meme videos.
This guy's done.
This is the fifth one.
He's been doing them for like a year and change and fucking know.
Dude, it's so good.
Everything about this is my favorite thing.
Yeah, it's incredible.
It's so powerful.
I mean, I want to ask why, but I have one question.
It's too good.
Hmm.
Look at the Ricardo Milo's.
It's just, it's just so the drop is the most powerful moment in cinematic history.
Yeah.
It's like a base drop.
Wait, I might have skipped past it.
It's not like one minute 40 or something like that.
I think it's the guy in the bus tub with the.
Yeah.
When the bathtub.
I'm on that part.
Yeah.
It's like 214.
214 is when the base drop hits and it's just.
Oh boy.
It's good.
Oh, oh, there he goes.
Okay.
What's that cat's name?
Is that I've seen that cat.
I don't remember where.
It's not bongo cat.
Is it?
It's the one, it's the one just from that GIF where it's just kind of like.
Yeah.
It's bongo cat.
Okay.
You played the bongos and then people made it do other things.
I don't think I saw this one.
I think I must have seen like an earlier one.
You know, the most impressive part about this is the cutting out of every frame of all of
these videos of these things.
Right.
And the way they.
The anime as well.
There's like subtle little tweens on like, on like the live action characters that they're
not doing to make them kind of look like they're doing things like when Ricardo Dards dodges
the bullets, like the way there's like the, the.
Is that the guy in the bandana, Ricardo?
Yeah.
The way, the way that like he moves to kind of look like there's like some momentum to
like him dodging bullets.
I just saw that dance.
It's so like you go all the way to the end.
Like there's the anime girl is just standing there in the final shot, but he like adds
a subtle like breathing animation with like a tween that didn't need to be there, but
it is.
There's just, it's masterful.
It's like actual art.
I'm floored.
I'm stunned.
It's, it's, I can't stop thinking about this video and how powerful it is.
This guy must.
I don't know.
I don't know what software he uses, but.
Everything uses every.
Lots of things.
Wow.
I just think it's so dense.
Every frame has so much going on.
It's true.
Damn it.
God damn it.
If it ain't the truth.
Yeah, that was incredible.
Why is Carl dressed like Megumin?
I don't understand, but he's just there.
And I don't, it's a mystery, but someone made a full 3D model of Carl dressed as Megumin.
And then it's happening.
It's in this.
I'm like, all right.
I, nah, I could have made that.
Oh, okay.
I could have made that, but better.
I mean, that's fair.
No, no, no.
I was commenting more on the fact that it even exists in the first place, not to the skill in which it was created.
No, I was actually, I was actually going to make this exact video, but I decided like, nah, that'd be stupid.
Nah, I could do better.
Well, jokes on you.
It's got over three and a half million views, buddy.
So, nah, those are shit views.
Pretty sure he's made more money with those views than you have on your crypto.
Those views.
Oh, you fucking.
That's on today of all days.
That's hitting below the belt.
You never, you never insult a man's crypto.
I would have been checked on my fucking Ethereum's doing.
Well, I have a feeling that it probably has gone up for a while and just had a pretty big dip today and then recovered.
So I've had it for like almost two years and I've never looked at it once.
I know that it's there.
Wait, really?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, okay.
I'm going to take a look.
You've had it for two years.
I think so.
About that.
This is all I care about.
All I care about anymore is cryptocurrency.
As soon as the opportunity to talk about cryptocurrency comes up, I'm like, I'm like, I'm there.
We made it.
Okay.
So let's say if you bought it in like 20, if you bought it in like 20.
Like the middle of 2018, something like that.
Middle of 2018?
Yeah, something like that.
So you bought it like at the peak.
I didn't buy it.
I was gifted it from MDOT.
He just was giving out Ethereum.
Wait, how many Ethereum did he give you?
Oh, I don't fucking remember.
Not a lot.
It was like, at the time, I think it was like 50 to 70 bucks worth of Ethereum.
I mean, if it was early 2018, then it has probably worth about the same.
If it was like late 2018, then it's like quintupled in value.
Yeah.
Well, I have no idea.
Ben is turning into Brent Garlinghouse.
Yeah.
No, it's not true.
The fan theory that Brent Garlinghouse was Ben from the future in an alternate timeline
makes more and more sense in every passing day.
No, no, it's not true.
It can't be true.
We had the time traveling technology from Homestuck where you can talk to people in the past on
your computer.
You send an email to Nate Bestman with the virus on it.
I sent it.
That's how Brent Garlinghouse was created, actually, from the time paradox.
He just spawned out of the e-fair to complete the loop.
Did you see that post that I put in the Discord about like Brent Garlinghouse posting all these
like, let me address the current allegations.
I don't know what it is.
I guess Ripple is in trouble.
I guess XRP is in trouble for something.
Ripple XRP is so...
I mean, nobody talks about it.
So I feel like it's not like a big enough thing.
It doesn't seem like a big...
It doesn't seem like a big thing at all.
And yet I'm sure it's worth like billions of dollars.
Like for some reason, I don't know.
I don't know what it does or what the point of it is.
Well, you had all those viruses going around to take over people's YouTube channels.
Not that I don't know whether he was necessarily behind that, but like whatever.
There's something shady going on with him.
Oh, oh.
Whoa.
Oh no, XRP.
Dude, XRP like cratered today.
Oh my God, XRP went to like...
No, zero joke.
Yes, in the space of today, the value of XRP went from over 35 cents, almost 40, to like less than three.
So like one tenth of its value in one day.
I'm not kidding.
I don't understand these things.
Holy fuck.
Like this, wait.
What the fuck?
This can't be true.
This would mean...
No.
The fact that the golden promise of a digital border-free currency
has been reduced to just being a speculative trading asset is really depressing
and shows how humanity will never progress forward.
We'll never have starfleet at this rate.
No, I'm wrong.
It didn't go to...
Sorry, I was misreading.
It went from like 35 to like 30.
So it's like, it's gone down.
That is so much more boring and uninteresting.
I'm sorry.
I know.
I thought I was seeing the death of Ripple, but...
I thought our diss track actually did something.
And now I just feel like we're just never part in the wind.
Yeah.
It's true.
We're never going to be a threat.
About the...
What were you saying about the currency?
I mean, everybody who has Bitcoin is like...
I'm in it for the long haul.
The point of Bitcoin is not to speculate on the point of Bitcoin.
That's all anybody does.
Let's not even kid ourselves.
Not the people on R slash Bitcoin.
They're all just there like, I'm holding until the day I die.
Bitcoin is the wave of the future.
Bitcoin is going to...
In a free market, the most stable currency always wins,
and Bitcoin is the most stable currency or whatever.
That's not even slightly true.
Well, I mean...
Well, it's the most...
In that you don't...
It doesn't have any operating costs associated with it,
is what they mean.
Well...
Not that it's value.
It's not stable.
But as a store of value, it has no...
Entropy associated with it.
Like a thief couldn't break in and steal the Bitcoin?
No.
To transfer it doesn't cost anything,
and to hold it doesn't cost anything,
whereas other things do.
It's free as in freedom.
You literally have to pay money just to store gold,
or to transport gold, right?
That's the way in which the value is not stable.
Yes, I never really think about that,
but it is tied up somewhat in physical stuff.
Yeah, and that's what they say about Bitcoin,
is like, this is the way of the future,
because it doesn't have any of that,
and that means it's guaranteed to win out in the long run,
and any Bitcoin that you own now
is going to pay for the rest of your life
in 10 years from now or whatever.
That's what they say anyway.
But who knows?
Never know.
Nothing is certain in this life.
COVID-2 is right around the corner, actually.
COVID-2 is actually transmitted through Bitcoin,
so sorry.
You're fucked.
Good job, Ben.
Fuck it up again.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
And yet, you did it anyways.
Well, what do you think about voicemails?
I think they suck,
but I think we should listen to them.
You know, I agree on both cats.
Sure. Obviously, you're right.
Okay. Nexus?
Cut that out.
Kaiju.
Yes.
Anything, do you have any last words?
Any last words before we fucking execute you
and go to voicemails?
Any objections?
Am I not allowed to listen to voicemails?
Oh, dang.
No, that's not what I mean.
I mean, do you want to bring up anything
before we do that?
Oh, like a topic or something?
Nah.
Sure.
I have no life.
Okay.
Nah.
Alright.
I just draw every fucking day.
Patreon.patreon.com.
Yes.
Eleazar.
I want you to go back in time
to when the episode started
and just put like a flurry
and just put like a whole flurry of like Nexus art.
Just have it.
When Nexus introduces...
Who?
Kaiju.
When Kaiju introduces...
And I'm going to kick your ass.
Just have all the...
I'm sorry.
I'm so...
God, I'm so stupid.
God, I can't do anything right.
Fuck.
You know what?
At least your software.
Kaiju should...
You know what Kaiju should be on?
Should have my spot on the podcast.
Kaiju should be the new Benz Saint.
Clip that.
We're going to need that for level.
God, I should...
I should...
I should resign.
And Kaiju must take up my position.
Can...
Wait, wait.
Can I take your patrons too?
No.
Aw, fuck.
No, sorry.
You work for me now.
You're the face of BenzSaint.com.
Okay.
The first...
First voicemail is from...
How do you say it?
Ctole?
I think that's how you say...
Ctole, yeah.
Yeah, actually...
God, I feel like login to all of this and everything.
Who was...
Oblivionfall sent me this audio file and was like,
yeah, Ctole recorded this as a voicemail,
but the quality wasn't good enough.
So they re-recorded it in, like, high quality, high fidelity.
And this is that high fidelity version.
Wait, is this not on Speakpipe then?
No, it...
Well, Kaiju can't listen on Speakpipe.
Oh, right, right.
So we have to do it in the Discord.
I posted it in the general room.
Okay.
It says Protesta.
All right.
Pro...
P-R-O-T-E-S-T-A.
Three, two, one, play it.
We've made it.
We've made it into the Capitol building.
Yes.
We're going to take back...
We're going to take back this country.
Go, go.
We're not going to stand for this photo squad.
In Arizona.
Get her.
Whoa.
Aris.
How does it feel to be a part of history?
You know, I've never thought hearing a woo echo around the halls of the Capitol building
would be so...
The Arizona Capitol building.
Why Arizona?
Huh?
Well, I mean, that was also being attacked.
Those who control the Arizona I.S.T. production control the world.
All right.
They were storming cap...
They were storming capitals all over the dang place.
I forgot.
I forgot because the DC one is just so dang iconic.
Congratulations.
Where we go when we go all?
It's funny.
Someone pointed out in the last episode that I made a...
That I said where we go when we go all.
I made a Q reference and it was like, ooh, that timing.
Ooh, right before.
It's almost like I knew.
It's almost like I hid inside her information.
It's almost like I was the Antifa instigator on the inside the whole time.
Right, right, right.
But it's not that.
All it took is one.
One thing's seen and then they riled up beyond compare.
It was literally just me like retweeting people saying like, socialism's good actually.
Bernie should have won the primary and it just made the right wing so angry that they stormed
the capitol building and that's what did it.
And you know what?
No regrets.
Okay.
Fuck.
Where did I put that freaking...
Where did I put those freaking voicemails?
This one is called...
This one is called rat.
Three, two, one, play.
Fuck you, Ben Sainte.
You are a rat.
A rat and I hate you.
Hey, Gib.
Hey.
Cool.
Yeah.
That was a quality voicemail.
Honestly, honestly, I support the idea of people literally just giving us a call in a voicemail
just to like say hi.
Just do it.
Just fuck it up.
You know, just fuck it up.
Who cares?
Here we go.
Next one is called...
Let me see.
The next one is called a video game gem you've probably never heard of.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, guys.
Don't mind me.
I'm just playing this underground game.
You probably haven't heard of it before.
It's called Pokemon Heart, Gold, and Soul Silver.
Okay.
Yeah.
Pretty not well known.
Underrated.
Now listen to me ramble for a minute.
As I list all the mechanics that everyone lists when they talk about this obviously popular
game.
Yeah.
That's definitely worth your time.
I wonder if I'm trying to make a point about something.
That was actually bad.
It was so bad.
You ever heard of Radiohead?
You ever heard of The Beatles?
Yeah.
It's pretty underground.
This sucks.
Anyway.
Honestly.
Black lives matter.
Gay rights.
Yeah.
You know.
Cool.
This is becoming like an arc.
Kaiju, I can't believe you're so bigoted that he would say black lives matter and you
would laugh.
Like this is no laughing matter.
This is a story by surprise.
Civil rights are no laughing matter and you need to, and you need to, and you need to,
you need to own your privilege.
All right.
You need to check your privilege at the door.
And you are fucking canceled.
Oh my God.
No.
What if I did?
Can I kill myself?
Can you, I will allow you to kill yourself.
Yes.
Thank you.
Okay.
Spooker yourself to retain your honor.
Um, yeah.
I like that.
Like, like I agree that that hardcore Soul Silver voicemail was pretty like, hey guys, this
is an underrated game.
Lol.
Like the most fucking popular game in the whole series.
Uh, uh, I like that.
Like this person was so mad about it that they had to do it like even two weeks out.
They still had to make a voicemail just to say fuck back.
The second week they were like, I just, I just got to let it go.
But then it's week two.
They were like, ah, I have to do it.
They're still mad about it.
Like I just have to get this off my chest or else it'll never, it'll never go away.
Uh, based.
Okay.
The next one is called, um, okay.
The next one is called skip if Tom isn't on.
So there it is.
Skip it.
Three, two, one, go.
Tom, what 3D engines are you thinking about doing low poly pixel crunched games?
It's incredibly easy to do in Unity.
There's a bunch of resources, free packages for cell shaders and pixel perfect cameras.
Plus Unity now has its own blueprint node based programming tool that you could use.
Blueprint programming would be a slight workflow change from construct, I think, but it's all
about programming logic in the end.
Check out a short hike for an example of a low poly pixel game built in Unity.
Yeah.
I know there's like a pre built shader that does like the low poly thing in Unity, but
Unity sucks.
Every time I try and use Unity, it's just like a bloated garbage.
Like I did like a tutorial on Unity where it's like, Hey, here's a baby intro to using
Unity.
I'm like, okay.
And you download Unity, it's like 15 gigs and all this fucking bullshit and it has to
install like visual studio and like rape your computer with all.
Oh, I can't say that infects your computer with all this fucking shit.
Right.
Okay.
And then it's like, here's, here's how to like drag a model into a scene.
And this is how the editor works.
I'm like, okay.
You finished the tutorial.
Would you like to pay $50 to add assets to your game you just made?
I'm like, I didn't do shit.
Fuck you.
Yes, please.
It's just like so gross and bloated and crappy.
I'm probably going to use Godot.
There's a, there's a low poly shader for Godot as well.
And it's like literally like 70 megabytes of space and launches instantly and doesn't
sell you anything and is completely free and doesn't have a splash screen.
You have to pay $500 a year to get rid of.
Do you know, do you know a short hike?
I'm aware of a short hike.
The game that I always think of when I think of like visual programming in unity is the
last tree.
It was made by one guy who had a film background and he used, not not that one.
It's really cool.
He just, he's, he did like everything was models from the asset store that he modified.
And he did the whole thing in using what's it called not, it wasn't both, which is what
I'm assuming he was referring to with the visual scripting.
He did it with playmaker, which is like an even simpler version, but not as extensible.
So that's pretty cool.
And that like that game sold like gangbusters.
You made a ton of money off of that.
So it's definitely doable, but I want to suffer.
So I have to use a niche tool that doesn't feel bloated because those are things I care
about apparently.
Hell yeah.
Wow.
Plus, plus pythons easier to learn than C sharp.
This, I mean, this doesn't look anything like, this doesn't look anything like a short
one.
Yeah.
It's, it's a different aesthetic.
Right on.
Okay.
Sick.
Next one is from God.
I tapped, I tapped over.
What was I thinking?
Next one is from all pronouns are gender neutral in China.
Wait, there it is.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
Go.
We can fix that.
Be like me.
Eat a bunch of mushrooms and embrace Xi Jinping thought.
America's failing.
China's limiting poverty.
Planning trees.
It's the future defect.
America has nothing for you.
Move to China.
Teach English.
It's the best.
Is I Jen Guilos?
Okay.
Why are they?
I mean, if China, if China is ascendant and is going to win, why do we even need?
Yeah, what are they?
No, that's not what I'm saying.
I'm saying they don't need us to go there and speak English.
We need to start teaching each other, each other, Chinese.
I took Chinese in college.
It was actually pretty cool.
Did you?
Yeah.
I didn't know that.
It was, I found it easier to learn than like other languages like Spanish and German,
which I took before because it's, you don't have any.
There's no like reference to English.
Like when you look, when I look at like German or Spanish or something like that,
my brain thinks of it in English terms.
So when you look at Chinese, it doesn't, there's no frame of reference to English.
So you just kind of engage it on its own terms.
And I found it easier to learn for that reason.
America is failing.
China may well cannibalize us.
I don't think that's a good thing.
I don't think China is good.
If China like fucking, okay, if that happens and like,
if China like becomes the new dominant superpower,
that means the one would replace the dollar as the, as like the world's reserve currency,
which means all of our debt would like immediately like fuck us over.
And we'd like fall into a massive recession.
We'd all be fucked.
Let's not do that.
Wait, if the dollar became worthless,
then wouldn't that just mean that like our debt was worthless?
No, because we would still owe, we would still owe that money.
To other, because we, from what I understand,
like we owe debt not in like American dollars,
but like we owe a certain value that like is like converted.
Like we owe X amount of dollars to like China or other countries,
but like as our currency of changes in value, that number would change.
Oh, you mean the national debt?
Yeah.
We would be fine.
Like me and you, we could just like, oh,
I guess I just won't eat my slice of bread today and I'll pay off my student loans
because we're all billionaires now because the currency is worthless.
That would be pretty based, but that,
that high would wear off pretty fucking quick.
I don't understand anything.
Me neither.
I probably, everything I said was probably wrong.
I can't wait for the voicemail next week when someone's like,
hi, I'm like a fucking PhD in economics.
Actually, the yuan is a notoriously inelastic currency
and the United States dollar is robust and this that in the way is
and what you just said never happened.
I make podcasts on the internet.
I admit that I'm stupid.
Okay, I'm talking out of my ass.
Imagine having technical knowledge in a subject
and thinking that anyone gives a shit to hear what you have to say.
No, listen to us.
Listen to us.
The podcast guys.
The sad fact is more people will listen to us than the person with the knowledge.
And for that, I'm sorry.
Just, just like in Bitcoin, you got it on the ground floor.
We established that base and now,
and now it's just smooth sailing to the end of time
because the currency of the future is posts
and the ultimate form of posting is podcasting.
The future currency is PS5s.
Oof.
Oh, no.
Why was I trading in Bitcoin when I should have been storming the capital?
Next one is called this is a really good idea.
Three, two, one, go.
It did you.
I just had this really good idea.
Nice.
Okay.
Why would you think Digi would be on though?
Seems like you got to manage your expectations there.
You got to send the voicemails to content if you want to talk to Digi.
Unfortunately, Digi will never know what a great idea you had.
Unlike the rest of us.
Next one is called Apple's missing headphone.
Jack.
Three, two, oh God.
Oh God, it's a minute 20.
Christ.
Three, two, one.
No, wait, hold on.
Before we even listen to this voicemail, I just got to say,
listeners, voicemailers, if you think that you have a minute's worth
of things to say that are worth listening to, you're wrong.
I promise you, you do not.
You are not worth listening to for an entire minute.
Don't send long voicemails.
We hate them.
Anyway, let's listen, shall we?
Three, two, one, go.
Time and worms.
Applejack.
Worms and beetles and dirt and so on, death and hell and Satan.
Heaven is not real, but hell is.
Outer space, outer space, outer space, outer space, outer space.
Outer space is the place for me.
Burying me under an outer space tree.
Let me tell you a story about a skeleton.
The skeleton was lonely so he adopted a puppy.
The puppy is a metaphor for another skeleton.
The skeleton is also you.
Everything is bones.
When your heart stops and your poop shoot loosens,
corrosion begins.
Bones become dust and meat becomes a nursery for maggots.
To the maggots in the corpse, the corpse is the universe.
To the worms in your casket, the casket is the cosmos.
Heaven, can we be so sure about our reality?
This message has been brought to you by Burger King.
I love Burger King.
I love skeletons and Burger King and Lucifer.
I'm so excited to meet Lucifer in hell.
Well, Ben, it's been a minute.
What do you have to say?
I was wrong.
I can't wait to adopt a skeleton.
This is my British voice.
Feed me bangers and mash.
You wanker.
I'm deeply terrified of death.
I think about death too much.
Feed me death.
Feed me death, you wanker.
I can't wait to meet Justin Bieber in Burger King.
I was wrong about everything.
No, to be fair, none of our listeners said any of that.
That was Applejack, which is a guest appearance and a totally different concept entirely.
True.
Also, that was scripted.
That was scripted.
If Applejack, if it had been one of the listeners, though,
that would have been a voice grail for them.
Unfortunately, Applejack gets the voice grail instead.
Can we put Applejack in the voice grail?
I think Applejack.
I think we can.
Okay.
Applejack is right in the voice grail.
I'm finding that Applejack and the rest of the main six
weren't already in the voice grail by default.
Okay.
Okay, though.
Was that a reference to something?
I feel like it was.
The thing about time and worms and soil and death and Satan,
I know I've heard that somewhere before.
That's a Jesse thing.
Okay.
I think.
He might have copied it from somewhere else.
I feel like, yeah, it was maybe in one of the...
Like a horseshoe finale.
Yeah.
God.
But it was maybe somewhere else too.
It was taken from somewhere.
Time and worms and time and worms and death and soil and Satan.
Yeah.
Because that whole thing was not like from a horseshoe finale.
No.
So the rest of it was something else.
Okay.
Anyway, whatever.
Either way, voice grail.
Applejack.
It's so nice to have some horse representation in the voice
grail.
It's a red letter day.
Next one is called...
Where is it?
Here we go.
Next one is called...
She mentioned you...
She's mentioned you like six times.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben, you should fuck Asterios Coconos' girlfriend.
Okay.
Repeat.
Ben.
Deal.
You should fuck Asterios Coconos' girlfriend.
Yeah.
Or at least go on their show.
Okay.
You mean Serrancha.
This is called...
She's mentioned you like six times.
I mean, like I've met her in person.
I met her at BronyCon.
And like we've talked before.
So when you say she's mentioned me, I would like to know where specifically you mean.
But like that sounds true.
And I'm supposed to be on...
I've been...
Like I've been supposed to be on an episode of...
What is it?
They do...
They do like a Kris Chan.
They do like a Kris Teri podcast.
I think it's just called Kris Teri.
And I'm supposed to be on it.
And I've been supposed to be on it for like a year.
But it hasn't happened yet.
But like I'm sure it will at some point.
So...
So there you go.
Thanks for the tip.
Cool.
Okay, next lol.
You guys still there?
I'm still here.
I'm here.
I'm doing something funny.
No.
Watching Flexio5 again.
Well then why am I not laughing?
You'll laugh eventually.
In voicemail though.
In voicemail.
Okay.
Next one is called...
I miss Cluster Punk Kitchen.
This is from fuckmyassholeatpcp.net.
So it's gonna be...
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
After your pizza is carded, you can go...
Then take your pizza and put it down for a pizza.
After you do that...
I wanna make sure I cat out of it.
Pache, I'm going to fucking kill you
if you ever show your face around here again.
Get the pizza now.
That actually like...
That actually gave me like weird vibes
and I had to like look around my room.
That actually like spooked me.
I'm a little embarrassed to admit but it's true.
But it's true and I'm all about that emotional honesty.
It's all about the pizza.
It's all about communication.
It's all about letting your partner know how you're feeling
and your feelings are valid.
Fuck.
Okay, next one is called...
Unauthorize made tapes number one, M-A-Y-D-E.
Unauthorize made tapes number one.
Three, two, one, go.
Gar fields come can be used as an alternative fuel
If you consider my asshole a vehicle
I'm a voice grail.
Voice grail, voice grail, voice grail for...
Yeah, I'm not.
Okay, two for...
Wait, wait, there's two more.
There's two more.
There's Unauthorize made tapes number two.
Here we go.
three two one go I am terrified to have sex with anybody because the last time
that I showed my wiener to someone they love
fucking barbershop like what is that they beat us to the punch with the IMT
pain bonus episode it's happening right now they did you know they really did
fuck wow this could have been us they identify they identified the market
they identified the market niche before we got to it then here it is unauthorized
made tapes number three three two one go bad things to say when you night whoopsie
do here comes to the goo it's slime time have some bro a shot of goo from me to
you gonna split the good it makes me think of like a daft punk song that
want that it's like daft punk only good you imagine a steady beat on that like
that's good that's actually I want to listen to more well I guess I assume
this person's name is made so made voice grail voice grail forever good thank
you there was a desperately needed bit of levity in these trying times thank you
for it on this on this on this trying podcast in the in the dower wasteland
that is the procrastinators podcast episode 245 next one is called kingdom
kingdom hearts explained in 30 seconds wait there it is kingdom are explained in
30 seconds three two one go okay guys I have solved kingdom hearts so we've
take the heart of sore I get it now yeah yeah that's the pizza one was better
pizza yeah pizza one was better yeah I don't even know if it's the same person
whoever sent this one this is the sort of thing that will have megalovania you
can't really see it there's only for mile away only room for one there's only
room there's only room for one only room for one voicemail that's why the first
voicemail every episode is always the best it's all downhill from there here we
go next one is called time to commit sue kid or sue said I don't know what that
means three two one go all right time to commit suicide goodbye everybody
what is with this this week with these voice I don't know that was a really
cathartic sounding gunshot though yeah that's not some good game feel I don't
really understand the plot of that one I don't really know what it was I just
listen to the committed suicide the and then he the production valley though yeah
yeah it was like the Michael Bay voicemail you know I was going on but the
production value is really good yeah and then like a minigun started firing it like
any good piece of art it's open to interpretation I mean you can you can
commit suicide and figure out yourself maybe that's something that happens maybe
that's maybe it's a piece of art that's acting as asking a question as opposed to
providing an answer yeah no it's not it's it asks a question and my answer is
voice jail I kid I kid next one is called Ben heads when Nate returns okay
three two one go
I don't like these they upset me those there's some weird vibes going on
yeah okay I'm glad I'm not the only one that could have been like seven seconds
and been funny but 23 seconds was was too long man I'm like shift I'm like
shifting in my seat like yeah yeah okay all right now it's good no no the next
one will be good I promise next one is called where is it here we go next one
is called more like pootex face of poo champ oh we didn't talk about no the
biggest the biggest story of the week was the downfall of gootex as pog champ
oh that's true well we can talk about it after this voice mail I will did you see
I actually watched the the Quentin reviews video about it it was what I
just didn't expect there to be a video about it already but yeah it's it's
surprising he's apparently he's been working on a gootex video for like
weeks and like just so happened that like this thing with pog champ just
happened now like by total coincidence which is like incredible timing if true
oh my god bitcoins go to the moon bitcoins going to the moon to the moon
386 34386 46386 50 it's like it's like more than halfway back up to where well
no that's not true well from today from today it's like almost halfway back up
it's gonna be okay it's gonna be guys we're gonna be fine we're gonna make it
we're gonna make it okay yes anyway more like pootex face of poo champ three
two one go so I really hate when people signal boost Nazis and I don't
understand how getting rid of pog champ from twitch is anything but that like
Pog has become the most ubiquitous thing on the internet for like the past year
or more I don't even I don't know for however long like everyone says Pog but
you know gootex the face of Pog is orders of magnitude smaller like yeah so
few people who use Pog actually know who he is or anything about him he doesn't
even look like the same person he may as well not be the face of Pog so when
twitch then says like oh we're gonna get rid of Pog champ because you know gootex
said some stuff that was like sympathetic towards the domestic terrorists at
the Capitol like I can understand the motivation there I can understand it but
all you've done is raise you signal boosted his like his message with the
sheer ubiquity of Pog by set doing this and now we're gonna have the whole thing
of like it kind of similar to Pepe where that was a dog whistle for as long as
people continued to say and believe it was a dog whistle and people you know
people on the all right did use it as a dog whistle and it's gonna be the same
thing with Pog champ now but if you look at twitch now Pepe is
ubiquitous again and no one cares no one says that it's racist like he's just
fine no one gives a shit and it's gonna be the same thing with Pog champ he's
just gonna come back in however many years so like why why what's the point
of all this what is the point of all this all you've done is signal boosted a
Nazi okay a couple couple point okay I understand I understand the point here
I don't think I agree uh one I mean Pepe is a cartoon and like not a real person
like Gutex is a real person who is like pro uh who is like pro maga insurrection
uh uh that's that's different from like the image of Pepe which was which was
co-opted by you know uh like the 4chan kekistan people but was not like there
was nothing inherently political about it like originally I think I feel like yeah I
feel like it's different um and the other thing is I I would I mean I I guess I can see what he's
saying that like had twitch not removed the Pog um people would not have felt the need to like
say what why Gutex who's that looks him up finds out I don't know whether that is like an argument
that people will then become like if anything people will be against the insurrection more
because Pog was deleted because of it because nobody would be happy that Pog is gone and if
it's Gutex's fault they'll hate Gutex I I don't know I don't feel like it's too much of like a
a platforming of him I think in a in a way that no I mean I think in the short term yeah
it has made some people be who who otherwise would have no idea be like wait the Pogchamp face
is gone wait why oh because a guy named Gutex said something oh this guy Gutex was the Pogchamp guy
okay well what did he say like what's I'm in the short term yeah I think that is you could maybe
call that platforming him but I mean I think in the long term it's probably better to not have him
be the face of this like thing that's very famous on twitch uh if you if if we're talking like okay
sure you you can you can call that platforming him if you want by drawing attention by taking this
action but like is it not platforming him to like make his face the face of this thing that
everyone knows I don't I don't I don't think that you can you don't like like yeah yes if
the argument I feel like that I feel like I feel like that's a big thing yeah I feel like him
keeping him as the Pogchamp guy is platforming him more I think so if the goal is to not platform him
I feel like this is the right move I guess I just I would agree that nobody who looks at the Pogchamp
face really gives a shit about finding out who it is at all yeah it's so much more like it's like
say like nobody really cares who drew the troll face initially then nobody's looking that up
yeah yeah I mean I don't know when it when it's a face of a real person though like an actual
I guess I'm gonna be a little bit of an actual human's face I think that Quentin Quentin said
something like basically we should just we should just keep using it in like a knot and like reclaim
it I think he did say like the same way like we should reclaim it like we reclaim Pepe
and we probably maybe maybe you're right maybe you're right that like the fact that it's his
face doesn't actually matter um I don't know I think for Twitch in specific to make him not
their Pogchamp face I think makes sense in broader terms in general maybe just continuing to use it
and like not giving a shit who the what the guy is like is fine and the thing to do I don't know
makes sense I agree with everyone maybe we're all right maybe we all win
I'm we're alt right haha okay uh next one is called um emphasis on the poo
three two one go although goo tax is the actual piece of shit here why am I why would I focus
on twitch I mean they just wanted to distance themselves and that's perfectly fucking fine
so you know what I was wrong I'm stupid okay cool after all that uh I you know what appreciate
I preach I'm not I'm not sure you were entirely wrong um but yeah okay I appreciate I appreciate
the willingness to self-reflect and consider and consider and for change possibly change
look at just use the the give and take Pog the brup because it's it's it's fun you're looking anyway
true and it was Pog before Pog
um I mean maybe maybe Pog needs to become more of like a diaspora like anything can be a Pog
you know like any anyone making that face is a Pog face yeah there's not it's not just
this is not just the one um oh my god if bitcoin hits 39 if bitcoin hits 39 again
I will I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna clap I'm literally I'm literally gonna clap I will do it
I will I will clap on on show don't think I won't do it uh next one is called um
innocent android three two one go I hate the procrastinators podcast I fucking hate it
I can't get through a single point without literally every single host constantly like
try and jump on me and cannibalize my point to the point where it's unrecognizable
uh oh I don't uh why are the voice mails cursed this week they are cursed
and I don't I don't mean I there's a glitch there's a ghost in the shell there's a glitch in the system
I'm I'm actually not sure what that one was saying that the we cannibalize their point what
I don't know what does that mean oh maybe it's like maybe it's like the the voice mail is being
said and we're talking over it while it's being said and then we miss it oh I don't know
I don't fucking know I wasn't paying it I just was maybe maybe we talked over maybe we talked
over voice mail sorry sorry it's our show we'll fucking talk over your fucking voicemail if you
want to um especially if they're fucking cursed and haunted demon voicemails like this week uh
this one is called oh wait why did I just download another one this one is called um thank you for
your service let me put it in the discord there you go thank you for your service three two one go
I share this point of the project as Martha's puppy around being seen has made a lot of great
points about these people storming a governing building to show that he's satisfaction instead of
looting their neighborhood zen setting fire to black owned business
uh insurance he also pointed out how these people were made with much less violence
than black lives matter protestants and that's why four of them are dead I I mean is he talking
about me thank you for sharing your opinions man you are very insightful when we're informed and not
just stuck in a social media free black bloop free black bloop is this guy serious I can't
remember when you're accusing Biden of fraud when he fucked over bunny me neither uh Gib you're very
brave to say normalize calling people morons when they support fucked up shit when the only chance
we ever get to do that was when more logic was here and you just stayed silent you guys are very
brave very stunning very talented smart funny young artists and I'm very lucky I did feel
bad about how I did cool more logic in here you guys political commentary kept going that's what you
guys should be dedicated in your time too this hey what was the first thing you said this is the
most cursed voicemail of all because it hurts my feelings what was the first point he had the first
point was that Ben oh hold on it was it was a bunch it was that I okay he said the thing about oh
people accused people accused uh uh the democrats of voter fraud when Bernie lost the primary
which not not to the same extent a lot of great points about
okay okay well he's he's okay his first one I completely disagree with he says that like oh
ben saint you've made a lot of great points against basically he's he's drawing a comparison between
these people storming the government building to to uh versus like blm like burn it's the stupid
like oh they've burnt down cities shit okay I thought I thought he was saying that but I wasn't
sure uh that's just completely stupid I've I if okay obviously this guy obviously this guy uh
follows our twitter's so if you've been following my twitter you've seen me retweet stuff that is
like I'm not against like riots and I'm not against like storming buildings I'm not against
direct action I just I think it's good when it's for good things like blm and fucking communism
and bad when it's for bad things like fucking QAnon okay that's the difference that's the
fucking difference it is really just as simple as that like the amount of buildings burned or like
businesses like like the whole conversation about blm not being a good thing because some
bad things happened in it like yes it's not good it's not good that someone's business was burned
down in in in the chaos but the movement to like get black um like uh rights rights like rights
rights on the same level right and and for and to like d d overreach and such like to make the police
less powerful and less like able to get away with fucking over black people like that's I've been
very mad no I've been very measured on twitter I have not called out I did I did refer to them as
terrorists one time but I was like sort of like half joking I have not been like oh these people are
you know this this kind of thing is unacceptable like we need to have a crackdown we need to crack
down on these people and send them all to jail I haven't been like that I've been like
the this isn't this is a this is bad because it's I mean I definitely think they should get
incarcerated for I mean in the same in kind of the same way in kind of the same way that like
yeah I think it's bad that I think it's bad that twitter can just ban anyone from the discourse
but it's not bad in particular that donald trump has been banned because like it's not like the rest
of us aren't subject to that in the same way I think like no it's it's not great that like um you
know the cops fucking shot that lady no I'm proud but it's but you know it's going to happen to
ever if it's happening to everyone else like if other people get if people are getting shot for
protesting well you know am I am I sad that it happened to you also not particularly that's my
fucking feelings on that and was the other thing the voter fraud thing about biden okay people were
talking about like the dominion machines and the Iowa caucus the Iowa caucus was a shit show
there's videos of like the the fucking Iowa caucus being like really weirdly managed and like the
rules to it are like esoteric and like deliberately hard to understand but there was not like a
conspiracy on the level on the like it wasn't to the same level as like this whole the whole like
stop the steal thing like it's really stupid it's just not even it's not even comparable
so fuck you but thanks for following me on twitter though I love you
you know the only thing that that is like an actual dig is like we didn't we didn't shut up
more logic enough during at the time I'll give him that I I at least told him that his story was
terrible you did I was I was a bit like god I didn't know this was gonna happen I wasn't prepared
but it's I don't know whatever criticism taken whatever he's he was funny he was funny for how
stupid he was I don't know what do you want um okay next one so
so does it like it's like what what what does what does this guy think like does this guy so
this guy doesn't like more logic he doesn't like more logic I don't know I think he's trying to like
catch us in like hypocrisy or something is this is it okay does this does this guy agree with us
but just don't think we take it we go far enough or does this guy disagree with us and is like
just using them or logic thing as like a weird gotcha I can't tell I I don't know like yeah
the thing with BLM if you have a problem uh whatever it's I don't yeah I'm done I'm over it
it's so simple that it's like million worth going over so much thanks for the thank you for the
voicemail I love you you're very we love you you're very special uh um the next one is called uh
what do you call a bad hot dog three two one go the worst
okay thanks for the voicemail thanks the voicemail dude shut up stupid next one next one is called
cross critical plays smash uh there it is three two one go
what why because it's a guy called critical's playing so I don't know why
critical is critical like a youtuber yeah youtuber yeah he's got a deep voice
okay he's pretty fine I think all right thanks thanks for the voicemail uh next one is called
stuff sucks this is the last one by the way three two one go
hello to summarize okay so every time every voicemail ever from a samurai I say
konnichiwa and you react somewhere the one no time samurai sama try to have fun with the reaction
no reaction you know react and ruin voicemail joke what the fuck what the fuck are you
return the samurai scroll I did it on purpose okay I don't have another joke this week so until
you next time sayonara
can we get it can we get a gong eliezer can you can you edit like a gong sound in as the samurai
makes his his honorable exit or like like one of those little drums in the
yo yeah yeah there's a name for it kabuki sound kabuki drum there there's that specific
yell though it's oh yeah have a name it has I just don't know what the name is because it's in
it's in um it's at the beginning of uh it's in uh uh the kamishibai of uh pastel defender heliotrope
the game if you've seen my if you've seen my lecture if you've seen my pastel defender heliotrope
lecture you've heard that scream when I play the game in the middle of it uh yes that's that's where
I know it from most vividly um well shit guys okay yeah all right now I can reveal my funny joke
ben I have bitcoin now no I I thought during the podcast I was like you know if it has crashed
maybe it's time to buy some wait really and I got a coin based account and I I put in two pounds
um and like there's a charge for of like 99 cents just like whatever oh my god so like
you're 50 down no but that's fine because because that one pound like basically like I added one
pound in and I've got one pound and three pennies it's gone up wait what what was the exchange rate
that you bought at um the exchange rate yeah what exchange rate did you buy at I don't know there
rates well what what what do what do you mean I mean when you I mean when you bought the coin
like like what was what was the coin what was the bitcoin to usd exchange rate that you purchased
your bitcoin at oh um it was something I was I was looking at the UK I'm sure it was something
no I need I need to know because now I have to keep track of whether your whether your two pounds
has grown or shrank um well it's grown what time did you buy it like like 15 20 minutes ago 50 oh that's
you should you should have bought it give you should have bought it at uh uh uh at at 3 27
p.m eastern standard time uh 20 minutes ago okay okay yeah yeah yeah there was a little jump
wait wait tell me give me the exact time give me the exact time I don't know the exact time hang on
give me the fucking I just want okay I just want to do the exact time so I can know exactly how
I'm looking I'm looking at the thing I'm looking at the thing yes yes okay good and I bought it at
uh 9 59 p.m GMT so you don't have to change that oh oh you actually you at yeah yeah yeah okay like
at 9 59 yeah at like at at uh at 10 o 3 at 10 o 3 it suddenly started jumping up and it went from
like 379 up to 3 80 up to 3 88 yeah so that was actually a pretty good investment has already gone
like one penny two penny three penny dude I got pennies more than I had before you've almost you've
almost you've made back like three percent of the 99 pence three fucking feed to buy in so you know
my my my strategy will be this I will come on the pcp I will listen to ben sainte scream about
what is happening in bitcoin and then I will look so I don't actually have to look myself and then
if it's a good time to sell I'll sell if it's a good time to buy I'll buy and then I'll continue
like that just like two pounds at a time well I'll do a bigger one next time I just did this for
the joke for the mean but like a few months all right well I hope so all right yeah buy buy and
now buy and now when the value is high no it's uh when it's I'm gonna wait for it to crash again
it'll never crash again this was the this was literally the last time it'll ever do I don't
know I just need to I just need to hear for like the ben sainte cry the ben sainte scream and then
probably okay now it's time to buy it did not it did not hit three oh wait no it did it did it
just barely hit three nine sometimes it does this thing that like actually concerns me quite a bit
where it like gets right to a milestone it gets right to like a like a something that ends with
a few zeros and then it like stops there and I don't know why that happens and always makes me like
concerned it was it was right at three thirty nine k for like two minutes and then it dipped like
down to like eight three eight eight okay enough enough of that um well shit guys this has been a
this has been a wild episode of the pro crassinators podcast patreon.com slash the pro crassinators
to hear like 50 bonus episodes of this and soon the new uh uh clip show behind the scenes
shit we didn't put in an episode cut cut content uh amalgamation uh coming soon um and other such
stuff what else uh speak speak pipe dot com slash pzp voicemail to send us a voicemail
please no cursed voicemails please no please don't scare us anymore thank you
uh anything else uh kaiju koon tell us where you can we can find all of your stuff oh yes do that
okay uh this is gonna air on friday i guess so by then you should have like five chapters of
bunny wave on my patreon while bunny wave is on patreon as for now for now i'm gonna i'm working
on a website and you can read them free there once it's done just not still on the world is it
patreon.com slash kaiju koon yes that's my patreon you can find me on twitter where i'm gonna start
posting updates and stuff please follow me on twitter and you can follow me
on twitter is kaiju what's your handle what's your twitter handle kaiju arts kaiju arts kaiju arts
yeah okay link link to all link to all this down in the description and if you like my my video work
you can follow me as editor san i usually shitpost there
face i feel like i feel like we had a missed opportunity okay we like a lot of shit we had
a lot of shit to talk about this week we didn't really talk as about like i don't know about all
the like pcp like pieces you've done over the years you've done a lot of like you've done a lot
that i feel like bear mentioning elias are have swarm the screen swarm the screen with like pcp uh uh
are the kaiju's done like i don't know the one that i remember the most most vividly is um the um
the radcon three arena like where we're all shooting the guns yeah that was that was really fun
yeah yeah yeah um pretty based pretty based um read bunny way just another on iran yeah read
bunny uh read read wolf and also read the manga i'm working on as well which is gonna be released
sometime around march it's gonna be fun based based just in time for the one-year
anniversary of us cope have a new car exactly uh all right that's it that's it we're done
we're out we've solved we've solved racism everybody and it's time about time and it's
time for us to end the podcast because we did it we won also also also thank you for having me
oh fuck oh well shit well she thanks for coming uh no anytime anytime appreciate it
appreciate you being here and uh thanks for all your fucking thanks for all the fucking your
fucking drawings uh i don't know thanks for what you do i i i i feel bad i i think you're really
good at art actually did i did i make that did i make that clear okay did i okay say it again
all right i wouldn't i wouldn't want to leave that on set okay cool all right that's the end
of the episode everybody and thanks for fucking around with us uh goodbye it's the end of the
episode thanks for being here goodbye bye everyone thank you see you next week