Goodbye, dry dumps, though I barely knew you at all, you had the grace to stay in me, while normal shits would fall, fall out of the asshole, still filled with that juicy moisture that the body craves, which you needlessly dump away.
Now it's January, my ship will fly like dust in the wind, it's my dried up sandy feces, must flow with the breeze.
And I would have liked to kept you, but you were just a cry, the moisture is all gone now, now the dry shit sand must fly.
Dry dump December, never forget.
I was going to announce my secret, secret announcement, but it's not quite, I'll be one day shy of when I'm ready to say what that is, so I can't quite say it yet.
So the day after this drops, check my Twitter, and I, well, probably then that day. I don't see why not. I'll be announcing what that is.
That's going to be very funny. But in the meantime, I'm Ben St, and this is Give and Take.
Hey, you know, speaking of secret projects, I said last time about mine that it would be done by the end of the year, I was pretty confident.
And the day after, immediately, things came to my attention that would push it back. So I was pretty optimistic.
Can I say, I told you so.
Sure, I don't mind that.
Yeah, woo! I want to know the details, but obviously I'm sure you can't go into detail.
I can say that it was optimistic of me to think that I would be able to work hard while Christmas was happening and even afterwards. I'm so exhausted.
Oh, is it?
And I'm like, I don't want to work.
It's not that there were more things that needed doing.
There are more things that need doing, but they're like intensive things that you can't just, you can't just like,
I will do a little bit here and there. You need to dedicate a day to it.
And it's like, it's the holidays. Let's chill out, for fuck's sake.
And, you know, Christmas holidays goes into New Year's Eve. That's also like a thing.
So I'm like, all right, next year, early next year.
Well, you know, when you get close to being finished with something, like the closer it gets to being done, the longer, the harder it takes.
The harder it is to like, what am I saying? The more like polish it takes? You know what I mean?
Yeah, I mean, the 80-20 rule.
Yeah, but the thing was, I already had been like, I knew that and I was thinking about it.
And I'm like, when last episode was recorded, I was like, we're really close.
And then it was like, actually, no, there's these other things that you didn't think about that need to be added.
And so the news changed the way of things.
Well, I would love to know which things, but I'll have to ask another time.
You'll have to go to patreon.com slash give and take. It'd be a money spender to get the Money Spender's podcast where I will drop the deets on that one.
See, the secret secret secret of the secret project is that there is no project and I'm just making people sign up to my Patreon so they can hear about it.
The secret project is a viral marketing campaign advertising something on the Patreon that doesn't exist.
That would be really funny, actually. Actually, if it were that. Not that I'm saying it isn't that, but if it were that, it would be really funny.
We can't rule anything out.
Yeah, okay. Well, you know what? That's okay.
I would have liked it. It would have been nice and neat and tidy.
To have it done by the end of the year.
Yeah, like whatever.
I mean, I missed my goal of having Phantom's Revenge out by exactly one year after I announced it on Twitter.
I missed that by like a week.
You did release the beta, though. That's out.
Did I mention? Yeah, last week I think I said I was gonna release the beta. Was that just this week that I released that?
I think so. It's only been out for a couple days. I haven't played it out.
Wow. Yeah. This past week has just felt like a lifetime is the thing.
Wow, okay. I can't believe that happened in the same week as everything else.
Yeah, I guess I did release that fucking thing.
I released the Phantom's Revenge beta on Patreon and it's good.
I expected it to have bugs. It did have some bugs. It had some small bugs. It had some typos.
It had a couple...it had one bug that I don't...is very upsetting because a few people have reported it.
And...okay, I mean, I have to sort of briefly explain what it is.
There's a bug that a few people have encountered that is like basically you get to the end of the game and instead of just letting you play the game normally,
it stops you from being able to use your attack command for some reason.
And then people that are like, and they try to use other commands and they use a different command that you're not supposed to be able to use
and the game like softlocks and like you just can't do anything, the menu just like dies.
And I...so basically it just means you can't beat the game.
And not everyone's gotten it, but several people have and I can't replicate it.
I don't know what those people did to make it happen. I can't make it happen, which means I can't find it and I don't know how to fix it, which is very upsetting.
You would need to gather more information about what computer they're running it on and things like that.
In case it's like a, I don't know, Mac or Windows thing.
I don't think...well, I think all those people are running it on Windows.
I don't think it's going to matter what computer they're running it on. I think it's got to be in the code of the game.
And I just...they must be doing something.
Like they must have...I don't know. I don't know what it is.
But it's a terrible bug that is...I can't let it stay in the game. This is one that needs fixing.
But I also can't find it and they can't give me any additional information about how they found it.
So I'm just like, uh, okay. I guess I gotta find it.
I think you should ask them to, like, record their gameplay.
And if it happens to them again, send that game so you can study what's happening.
Yeah, maybe.
That would be my only idea.
Well, I mean, they've explained to me pretty clearly what it looks like.
But like, they're...and they've asked them, like, okay, what are the conditions under which it happens?
And they've fully explained that to me too. So it's not...
So I'm just like, hmm, I don't know what else it could be, but it's got to be something.
Like maybe it's that they died and reset a certain number of times before doing it or something like that.
I mean, what's the code that causes the end of the game?
Well, the game? Okay.
Does the menu change a bit?
What I think is happening, what I think is happening is that against the final boss, you're not supposed to...
I think the final boss is basically...
Some sort of code is happening that is making the game think that the boss has been...
Not defeated, like the boss doesn't enter a defeated state, but the menu that generates lists of enemies that are targetable during an attack phase.
I think it is removing the boss...when the boss is attacked, it is removing it from the list.
And so when it comes time to do an attack, the menu sees there are no enemies to attack, and then it says, you know, you can't attack, no enemies to attack, right?
I think that's what is happening. I just don't know why it's happening, because when I've tried it myself, it doesn't happen.
So, you know, this is...
I was fixing bugs that people were reporting me, and it was all little minor stuff. It was all, haha, very silly, very funny.
This is the one that I'm like, shit. This one, I don't know how to fix it. I mean, I'm sure I'll get it eventually.
At the moment, I'm like...
I don't know how to fix it. It wasn't supposed to be hard. This was supposed to be easy.
When you go to try and replicate it, do you start from that stage, or do you start the whole game?
Yeah, I've been mostly starting it from that stage. I have to...
Yesterday, I was talking about it, and someone suggested instead of starting up the game at that stage, start from the beginning,
and not in the game maker demo run function, but in the external zip file.
You know, the external executable that I created that I made downloadable for people.
It might run differently, so I have to try it out in there.
But other people have gotten to the same point and not had the issue happen, so it's not guaranteed, apparently.
It is fucked, and all that is to say nobody has beaten the demo, or the beta.
People beat the alpha, and I made the beta to be a little less hard than the alpha, but nobody has beaten the beta.
And I'm sad to say I think it's probably because of this bug that just ruins the game.
But not entirely. It's not entirely because of that, but I think it's...
Maybe if that weren't the case, somebody would have beaten it by now, but nobody has.
So I'm a bit bummed about all that, but I'll figure it out.
I mean, other than that, the game is a masterpiece, obviously.
Looks great, runs great, tugs at the heartstrings, makes you cry, makes you laugh.
Memories still last a lifetime.
A satisfying conclusion to the arc of the character of Phantom Horn.
Yeah, so I got that to continue chugging away on this week.
Yeah, I can't believe that it was in the same week as Christmas, and as me getting COVID.
That's very funny.
How are you feeling, Ben?
Okay, pretty decent.
I felt really bad on Christmas Eve.
I felt really bad on Christmas.
I felt better the next day.
Today is the day after, the day after Christmas, and I feel...
Well, mostly okay, I think. It's a little hard to say.
I had a fever.
I was getting a fever in the early stages on the 23rd, 24th, and 25th.
A fever was coming and going.
I was getting up to about 100 or 101 degrees, and I felt fever, and I felt hot and cold.
I felt chills, felt sweaty, alternating between the two.
Very bad, very unpleasant.
And then that kind of went away.
Sometimes I feel a little bit of it.
Right now I'm feeling a little bit warm all of a sudden, first for no reason.
But I've been taking my temperature, and I haven't had any fever in a day or two.
And they say, according to CDC guidelines or whatever,
that you are probably, you might be non-contagious,
you might have kicked the infection as of three days after having a fever.
Even if a sore throat persists or other things persists,
if you haven't had a fever in a few days, you might be over it, you might not be contagious anymore.
But I guess that's good.
This morning I felt like I might be losing my sense of smell, but I wasn't sure.
And there were other factors at play.
The room was really dry, and my nose hurt because the air was dry.
And also I've been eating menthol, menthol Ricolas.
Maybe the menthol was interfering with my smell.
So I was frantically smelling things, and I could smell some things.
So I was like, okay, maybe it's fine.
But then other things, I was like, I feel like it used to be stronger.
I feel like I used to be able to smell it stronger.
I can't tell. I can't tell if I'm just imagining it.
Sounds like you sort of are still stuffed up, which is normal to not smell so good during a cold anyway.
Because of all the nose problem, the mucus and the stuff.
Yeah, but I don't think it's... I have a little bit of a nose thing.
I don't think it's that.
I wasn't stuffy this morning when I was smelling stuff.
Now I kind of am.
If you were dry, then you couldn't have made enough mucus to get stuffy.
But you also can't smell when you're dry.
You just got to drink a bunch of water, and hopefully it'll flush itself out and you can smell better.
The symptoms have been like...
It's just like a rotating list of things that just keep happening.
Like rotisserie chicken.
COVID is like a big rotisserie chicken, just going around and around and around.
Juicy and delicious, but you can't smell it.
The symptoms just keep changing.
Like sometimes I have a fever, sometimes I have a stuffy nose,
sometimes I'm coughing, sometimes I'm sneezing, sometimes I'm just fine.
Like I woke up on... This is a tragic story.
I tested... So I thought I might be sick.
So I tested myself on the night of the 23rd, and it was negative.
And I was like, great.
And then I woke up, but I felt sick.
So I woke up early the day of the 24th, before my mom was supposed to come get me.
No, my whole family was supposed to come get me for Christmas Eve.
And I was like, okay, I'm going to test again.
And I tested, and I was positive.
And it was like a little pink line appeared on the test strip.
Very faintly. I was like, shit, but it's positive.
So I had to call them and tell them, guys, Christmas is fucking canceled.
Like I got COVID.
Yeah.
That was very sad.
Quick note, by the way, a few people made fun of me and said,
the monkey's paw curled.
Multiple people made some comment to that effect.
Because last time on the episode, I said,
if I got COVID, at least I wouldn't have to do my stupid family Christmas Eve party.
Which is true. I meant it.
I meant it about my extended family aunts and uncles and cousins party.
I hate those. I don't care about that stuff.
I don't care about those people. I have nothing to say to them.
I did not mean it about my like, regular, like seeing my family for regular Christmas.
That I was very sad about. I had a very sad Christmas this year.
That sucks.
Yeah, it does. Yeah, it does. I was pretty bummed about it.
But anyway, anyway, so I tested positive.
So then the next day, Christmas, I woke up and I was like,
I don't feel anything at all. I don't feel like I have a fever.
I don't feel a headache. I don't feel runny nose. I don't feel anything.
I feel like, could I be over it?
So I went to, I went and I got another test and I took it.
And it was, the red line this time was like dark crimson.
It was like, no, you're way more positive now than you were before.
Oh, dear. A Christmas nightmare.
Yeah. Yeah. So, but I didn't feel worse.
Like I have continued to feel a little bit better.
I'm still not 100%, but I feel much better today than I did on Christmas.
I was like, like I can, like it was hard to like walk.
Like I was getting like, fatigue going upstairs and stuff.
Now I'm like, you know, I feel mostly normal, except for, except for a little bit.
But it's like 90% there.
So I'm hoping that I'm over it mostly or I'm going to be over it soon.
The, when you Google it, it says like, you, you, some, I found some sources that say,
oh yeah, when you're like, yeah, when you're like five or 10 days in a lot of people,
they start to feel better, but then like five or 10 days, bam, now it comes back and then they get long COVID
and then they're sick for like a month.
Like, oh, okay. Yeah, that's cool.
So for me, that would be in about three to in about three to five days,
that would be the 10 day mark for when I got sick.
So I guess we'll see by then if it comes roaring back.
I was a bit nervous. Hey, you there? Can you hear me?
I was a bit nervous. Okay, I hear you.
I was a bit nervous to record this podcast because having a conversation, having like a talk will be a test for the scariest symptom of COVID,
which is a brain fog, which is when you just can't think and remember stuff correctly.
And it happens for the same reason that you sometimes lose smell and taste,
which is why I was very scared this morning when I woke up and I thought maybe I can't smell stuff,
which is that according to some Google results, COVID just destroys your brain.
Just kills part of your brain, just shrinks it, no matter what, even in a mild case.
Just if you've had COVID, you have less brain than you had before.
So you're going to be hyper aware of how witty you're being this episode.
Yeah, I am. And every time I stutter and stammer, I think, I've got it.
I've lost my brain. I'm permanently stupider.
But, babe, you stutter and stammer all the time.
I know I do. I know I do. I know I do.
As Trixie made fun of, famously made fun of, in Who Are These Podcasts.
But little did she know, it would be my saving grace.
I could point you to go, ah, that's proof that I still have my brain, though.
It's very scary. It's very upsetting.
I could imagine, yeah.
Because it's your brain, so you don't know at any moment.
Yeah, I can't imagine.
I can't imagine a more upsetting symptom that you could tell me is a symptom of a disease that I just found out that I have.
It's like, try not to think about it.
Just try to relax.
Because I guess getting stressed out is not going to do anything.
But it's hard, I understand.
Not thinking about it.
Yeah, when I tell people that I'm worried that COVID will destroy part of my brain,
I usually feel like they just scoff at me.
Nobody seems to care or take that seriously, that that is a thing that you can read about on Google.
Is that it does that? There's nothing you can do about it.
I mean, I haven't heard that.
But I also don't know that many people who have gotten COVID either.
There's not that many reports about it, but there's a few.
I was furiously googling, looking for reasons to believe that this would not happen.
I couldn't find that much about it.
Obviously, there's not that much research into it yet.
But there's a few very disturbing ones.
And I don't know, there was one.
Were those people vaccinated, though, when they got that?
Was it the same strain that you read about?
Some of them were from before the vaccine was available.
Some of them were studying the brains of people who died of COVID,
which is like, okay, maybe that's kind of a self-selecting sample right there.
There was at least one.
No, there's at least one that specifically says,
even people that had a mild case still saw a brain loss.
And that was comparing cat scans or brain scans of people that had had them before they had COVID,
and they got scanned after, and they just compared it.
And it was like, yeah, across the board.
And I think that, and that one was the word, I think that one,
there's a line in it, and there's a video that goes along with the two,
and the nurse in the video repeats it.
And they say something that's a little bit of the effect of,
this could be a major health crisis in the future.
All these people, the effect on the brain was something similar to what you see in Alzheimer's,
or what you see in the aging process, right?
It just made the brain effectively older.
And it's like, oh, well, this could be a major health crisis in the future.
Maybe all these people will just be at increased risk for Alzheimer's later.
And it's like, oh, okay.
Maybe on the one hand, I want to say, well, that's pretty ridiculous.
A third of the population has had COVID.
Are you telling me that in the future, and that number is only going to go up,
it seems like probably everyone will eventually get COVID.
Are you telling me that due to the COVID pandemic, 20, 30 years from now,
in the future, everyone will just be at increased risk for Alzheimer's?
Are just way more people going to have Alzheimer's?
That's ridiculous.
But then also, what if they will, though?
What if that is just a thing that will happen because of this?
Was it just one nurse saying this in this one video?
Was there like anyone else saying it?
I remember the wording was a bit ambiguous,
because it wasn't clear if she was talking about these people as in these specific people
the study was about, or if she's talking about these people as in people who have had COVID.
Generally.
I would imagine they're talking about the specific case of the people who had a mild case,
the person who had a mild case, but still had brain change, brain shrink.
Here we go.
It's called, it's W.W.W.
The Scientific American, even mild cases of COVID may leave a mark on the brain.
This is the one.
Okay, this one, because like, right, the COVID,
COVID affects your, it makes you lose smell and taste sometimes.
And smell and memory are in like the same.
I think they're in the hippocampus.
I think that's right.
But they're in a related part of the brain and like,
I guess where a lot of the effect happens is there.
And so like, when it fucks up your smell,
it's doing similar damage to a place where it might fuck up your memory.
Could you link that?
Yeah, sure.
It's right here.
There's a video too, which,
it's not really like, it's not playing here.
One time I had this article open.
I had this very article that I'm about to link to you.
And I went to like pick up some, like my grocery delivery and I came back and,
and it had started playing a video.
I hadn't told it to play one.
Maybe it wasn't this one.
Maybe it was just a similar one, but it was another way.
It had auto started playing a video that I hadn't even aware.
And yeah, there was a nurse saying the same thing about like,
this could be a major health crisis going forward.
Oh, maybe it's this one, the CMAJ news,
which has like the same, the same title.
I'm getting like a dry throat from talking about it.
I think I might just be talking too much.
I'm going to take a sip of my, my black raspberry,
blackberry, clear splash sparkling water beverage from stop and shop.
Well, I'm lucky, I guess.
I haven't got COVID yet.
And I did manage to like the last minute get my booster that I've been told like,
well, I didn't even get my booster.
I put off getting it like a fucking idiot.
I mean, I did as well.
And I was like, I should, I should probably get it before like the Christmas Eve party,
but there's no way I'm going to get one in time.
Yeah.
But then miraculously, my phone popped up with a notification.
You can now get your booster sign up at the website.
I'm like, fuck.
Okay.
I was kind of waiting for them to do that because people had told me you can just sign
up, but I'm like, I guess I could have.
But like, there was one like a few miles away and it was on Christmas Eve morning.
So I'm like, fine, that's good.
I'll have the booster in the morning.
And then in the evening, there'll be people around.
And hopefully none of them have COVID.
Yeah.
I haven't actually tested since then, but I've, everyone in the family's felt fine.
Nobody who has been to the party has reported anything.
So that was, that's a lucky one.
And my arm hurt for a bit.
And that was it.
But it was a Moderna.
It was a Moderna booster.
I got, I got, I got Pfizer Pfizer Moderna.
That's my code.
That's my secret code.
You, you can't mix and match.
You're going to die.
If I'm a level in like a PS one game and you've got like four symbols to choose.
Yeah.
It's your, it's Pfizer Pfizer Moderna.
That's my level.
Pfizer Pfizer Moderna.
Yeah.
Cool.
Good.
Yeah.
I didn't, I, I didn't get my booster.
Obviously I regret that now.
I don't know if it would have made a difference because.
Omicron is apparently very good at not giving a fuck if you're vaccinated.
It was just very funny.
I mean, I heard that like, um, you got it at like Munchie.
Munchie's like a house party with a bunch of people.
Yeah.
And those people were boosted and a bunch of them got it.
Or at least some of them were boosted.
I heard the Munchie, oh, I had to like cancel a flight to go see his parents for Christmas
because of that.
Yeah.
They had a, they had Christmas plans and they had to.
Maybe even worse than, maybe even probably, you know, probably even worse than mine honestly
because they were going to travel to see their families.
I was just going to go.
Well, I mean, I was going to see like, you know, I mean, I've seen my parents not that
long ago, but like, you know, Nate and Michelle were in town and my sister and her boyfriend
were in town.
We were going to do a family.
You know, I didn't get to see them.
Who knows when I'll see him again, but oh well.
But yeah.
Munchie had a similar.
A similarly tragic, uh, cancellation.
Uh, you know, Cassie too.
Everyone over there at the Munchie house.
Everyone got sick.
They're all just sick.
Sucks.
And then I'm going to be flying in there soon.
Presuming that like I can, I probably will be able to.
So hopefully we'll have a herd immunity, I guess.
Bye then.
When are you?
Yeah.
When are you coming?
Like, like soon, right?
Like second week of January, I think.
Oh, so like three weeks from now or less.
Oh, wow.
Let me see.
Are they, let me see.
Are the COVID cases snot spiking as much?
Let me take a look.
No, they are spiking more than ever.
Okay.
That's terrible.
I'll just have to, I'll just have to.
Like look like weird and people will leave me alone, which I'm very good at.
I'm very talented in that area.
It might help.
To an, it might help to an extent.
I feel like it's kind of inevitable if I'm getting on a.
Plane and they're like, if it's with people on it.
That are next to me, I think it's kind of like.
If one person has it, there's no chance.
There's a high likelihood that I'm just going to have COVID in Boston.
It's, it's a bit out of your control.
Yeah.
Is it worth.
Hmm.
I don't know.
I think so.
I mean, I'm not afraid to die.
Well, I am.
Yeah.
The, the, I don't know.
It's.
Geez.
It's, I don't know.
I don't know.
You know, a, a Nate.
The whole, the, the, the, the, I think it was Nate in particular.
Nate in particular was pushing.
Nate wanted me to just like.
You know, Ben, I know you got COVID, but like, you know, you should come anyway.
Like we're all prepared to get COVID.
Like we don't care.
Well, not, not exactly.
He, you know, he was like, you know, you can wear a mask, you can social distance.
And I was like, on the one hand, that's nice of you.
I'm glad that you want me to be there.
And, and that's nice.
On the other hand.
Terrible idea.
Also, I feel.
Horrible.
I feel sick.
I want to go to sleep.
So for all these reasons and more, I will not take you up on your kind offer.
Yeah.
Lamal.
I feel like if there's like.
If there's a saying, oh, you probably shouldn't fly.
I would have to reconsider.
People start saying you probably shouldn't like if a government thing comes out says you're allowed to fly, but we advise against it.
I'm not sure.
I would probably go anyway.
I'm still allowed to.
It's, it's, it's like.
I don't know.
On the plane.
I think if you are like.
If you get like unlucky and you probably get seated next to someone who just happens to be contagious, I think you're probably just fucked.
But like.
Yes.
Who knows if that will have, you know, you could get it going to the airport.
You could get it in the airport to true.
Yeah.
First, the most likely scenario if you were to get it while traveling is if you just happen to be seated next to a contagious person, which you have no control over.
Yes.
Unless hopefully my favorite time in a plane is when it's not full.
And so you can just spread out and go to have a whole little area by yourself.
And I feel like just after Christmas, planes are going to be packed with people going home.
But a little bit after in January, I feel like maybe it'll be a little quieter.
It'll, it'll.
I'm prepared to get sick.
I am a little worried about what could happen afterwards.
I feel like, I feel like it's, since I'm also boosted, I feel like the worst that seems to be happening for most people who have the double vax and the boost.
The worst is like, oh, you have a fever.
Oh, you have a cold.
And there's no lasting effects.
And you're fine.
Yeah.
I mean, that's what happens to most people.
Some people.
I'm, I'm part of most people.
You are part of most people.
Congratulations.
Some people, some people develop long COVID.
Some people develop memory problems and permanent loss of sensation.
They're not most people.
And I, and I do think those, I think that the incidence of long COVID is, is, is reduced.
If you, if you are boosted, if you're vaccinated, I think that's the case.
The, the, the.
But, you know, Omicron just kind of doesn't give a fuck.
Omicron just doesn't really care about vaccines.
So who knows, man.
Uh, uh, uh, I don't know.
I don't know.
You know, I mean, if you, if you, if you get sick on your trip, I feel like it'll ruin
your trip.
You know what I mean?
Well, of course.
Yeah.
Okay.
I mean, the whole point is to see people.
If I have to hide in a room the whole time, what a waste.
Yeah.
What, what a waste.
It would be, it would be, it would be even worse.
It would be even worse than just not getting to go.
Frankly.
I don't know.
I would, I guess I, what I'm saying is frankly, I would consider, I would consider rescheduling.
I, I, I mean, I, I, I said, just, just the numbers, the numbers.
Numbers go up.
Look, look, look at this graph.
Um, I don't know.
I'll think about it, but it's been so long.
It has been so long.
I don't know.
I can't tell you what to do.
Um, and, uh, the, the, the, wait, I want to say, I want to, I want to gripe.
I want to gripe about fear some more.
I want to say that I'm scared.
Um, it's the thing about most people.
Most, most people don't complain about memory loss, brain fog, permanent loss of sensation.
Most people don't complain about those things.
But according to one or two Google results, citing scientific studies, uh, it might be,
I don't know, a lie awake at night.
Think of like, what if, okay, but like, what if those people just don't notice?
What if those people just did lose, you know, precious brain?
It's gone forever, but they just, you know, but it's not serious enough that like they notice it,
but like it is gone and it is affecting them just in a subtle way that like they, they're not picking up on.
They are stupider.
They have lost some cognition.
They just aren't, aren't noticing.
What if, what if, what if that's like most people?
What if that's me right now?
What, what, what then give?
What if that's true?
What if, tell me what if right now?
Tell me what if that happens.
If you want to find out for sure.
Okay.
You should, you should write on a piece of paper.
Like a, like a, the smartest thing you could think of.
And every day check it.
And if you can still understand it, then you're fine.
I think to myself, you know, Ben, you're pretty stupid already.
So it's fine.
But then I think, is that good?
If I'm, if I'm going to lose a little brain, do I want to be stupid?
If like, if I'm, if I'm already stupider, then does that mean I have less to lose?
And so the difference would be less.
There'd be less and overall difference.
Yeah, man.
I do.
What if, if I'm stupider, would I have less to lose?
Or do I want to be smarter?
So that I'm, I have more brain so that if it goes, so that if I lose more of, if I lose it, I'm left with more on the net.
You know, which, which one of these is better?
The smartest people are the dumbest people.
Say in the comments, say in the comments, say in the comments whether you would like to have less brains to lose or start with more and be left with, and lose more but be left with more.
Think about it.
Let me know what you think.
Look, if you're going to lose some brain power, lose more, lose all of it.
Get, get it gone.
Dude, be a man.
Do the big brain loss.
You're right.
Why go, why go halfway with anything?
Lose it all.
Lose yourself in the moment.
Lose yourself in the COVID.
You better never let it go.
I don't actually know the words to that song.
I can't, I can't riff it.
This opportunity comes many times every day.
This opportunity comes.
Oh, if I can time.
This opportunity comes when you're in public.
I don't know.
Don't wear a mask.
We'll know.
Just, just got to do it.
Just got to do it.
If you had one chance to lose all your brain cells with SARS-CoV-19, would you take, would you get it?
Would you catch it?
This is your moment to get COVID?
Once in a lifetime chance.
Dude, those bug chasers must be fucking thrilled at all this, all this COVID.
It's that meme of the guy on TikTok offering a trade, you know?
You, you receive SARS-CoV-19.
I receive you lose brain.
Yes.
What meme is this?
You know, it's a TikTok.
It's of a guy, I don't, I've never actually seen the video, but it's like a guy with long hair in like a suit.
Oh, it's a joke of the meme that like lose brain and then he's talking insane?
No, the meme is just, he's a guy in a suit and he's sort of, he's sort of got his hands together.
I know the meme, but like, I don't know what you were saying.
Um, I don't know.
Just because the, the joke of that meme is that you lose, you give something and you get something and that's funny for some reason.
So that, but it's COVID.
I receive COVID SARS-CoV-19.
You receive SARS-CoV-19.
We both have.
We both have both sick.
It's a good, it's such a fair trick.
My, my, I'm, I'm still, you know, I haven't, I haven't tested again.
I'm going to wait a few days and test again and it's possible that I might be negative or non-contagious soon, in which case I will count myself lucky.
But you know, there's, I think it's possible that I might, you know, you know, some people, some people develop complications.
And those start to show up, you know, soon.
So I'm still worried.
I'm still like, you know, I woke up this morning like, oh my God, I can't smell.
Oh my God.
I know the wake up.
I think I'm going to die feeling.
I've, I felt that before.
Yeah.
So the, I don't know.
I mean, optimistically, optimistically, I'm like mostly recovered and I'm going to test negative in a few days and nothing else will happen.
And I'll be like, okay, whatever.
Ha, ha, fine.
Well, if I lost some brain, I guess I wasn't using it anyway.
Lamal.
But, and then you go to fix the bug in Phantom Horn and Phantom Horn's revenge and like, oh wait, I needed those, those neurons.
Oh God, I needed those exact amount of neurons.
They're gone.
Just, just like with, just like with this conversation when I'm, when I've been, when I've been working on the bug fixes, I keep thinking like any, any time I like, okay, it's so, it's so stupid.
Any time I think like, oh, I lost my train of thought while I was working on this thing.
Oh, I got distracted.
Oh, I don't know how to, how to do this.
I'm like, there it is.
It's the brain fog.
It got me.
But then I'm like, I'm all, I'm always like this.
I'm, I was always just constantly just like, type of, type of, type of, get distracted, you know, just pay attention to something else for like 45 minutes.
And then like, what was I doing?
Like that's normal.
That's normal for me.
So, so I guess I've already had COVID.
I guess I've just been living the COVID life this whole time.
Yeah.
I am COVID.
Oh, best.
Funny.
Wait.
Okay.
I have a couple of Christmas gifts that I want to mention.
The funniest Christmas gift that I got was my dad re-gifted me that I have COVID shirt.
So I haven't.
Now you have COVID.
It's past from father to son.
Yeah.
Although I think, I think he got a false positive or, or he was asymptomatic or something because he like had no,
basically nothing happened.
He didn't report like any symptoms at all.
He said he felt fine the whole time.
So, you know, but I mean, that was before Omicron.
So maybe it was just, he got it, but it was like, he was vaccinated.
So it was like, didn't do anything.
So that was funny.
Nate gave me a George Washington's rules of civility and decent behavior in company and conversation.
Lol.
And this is a, this is a, okay, it's funny.
It's not, he didn't write this when he was like an adult.
He, when he was, when he was like 14, George Washington wrote down a bunch of rules of like how to be polite and make people like you.
Here, I'll read an excerpt.
I'll read an excerpt.
This is the 70, George Washington's 75th rule.
In the midst of discourse, ask not of what one treateth, but if you perceive any stop because of your coming, you may well entreat him gently to proceed.
If a person of quality comes in, comes in while you are conversing, it is handsome to repeat what was said before.
Okay.
So catch them up to speed.
Catch them up to speed.
Don't interrupt.
But only a person of quality.
These are, these are actually, yeah, some, these, a lot of these are actually pretty good.
Like, a lot of these are like, yeah, I, it would be rude to come into a room where someone is talking and be like, hey, what are you talking about?
But if they like stop to be like, no, no, continue.
Don't stop on my account.
Like that would, that is the polite thing to do.
That's, I think that's good advice.
That's true.
Here's another one.
When you see a crime punished, you may be inwardly pleased, but always show pity to the suffering offender.
Oh, here we go.
This is another one.
This is one I have, this is one I disagree, I have to disagree with.
Show not yourself glad of the misfortune of another, though he were your enemy.
I can't, I can't condone that one.
That's like, that's a classic anti-bensane line.
I think, it would, it to me, it would depend.
For me, it would depend.
Okay.
I mean, I mean,
What would it depend on?
It would depend on the manner of misfortune.
If it's, if it's a, if it's like a completely unearned misfortune, like if it's someone like gets like run over by a truck or like breaks their leg or like gets covered or something.
I might, I might be like, I might, even if I hate them, I might be like, oh, that's too, you know, I mean, but if it's like, oh, you know, they, they, they, they ruin their own such shit.
They brought it on themselves.
You know, they were an anti-vaxxer and they got COVID.
Then I'm like, fuck them.
You know, so that one's like, I sort of agree with it.
I just made myself laugh thinking of like, ah, but I'd, I'd, I'd enjoy hearing about misfortune of, of like super rich people like Elon Musk.
And then I imagined the headline, Elon Rusk run over by his own Tesla and the image was, it was a little absurd, but it's so true.
He was in, he was in his own exploding.
When it exploded tragically.
No, no, no.
He was outside of the Tesla and it ran him over and that's how he died.
Um, I have, I haven't, okay, here's, this one's cool.
I'm going to read one more of the 36th rule.
Get a load of this one.
Artificers and persons of low degree ought not to use many ceremonies to lords or others of high degree, but respect and highly honor them.
And those of high degree ought to treat them with affability and courtesy without arrogance.
Okay, I don't.
What's the ceremony bit part mean?
I don't know.
Okay.
By, by artificers and persons of low degree, does he mean like craftsmen and like blue collar people?
I, I would imagine like lower class.
Okay.
So they, they don't use ceremonies.
Treat them, treat lords with respect, but don't use many ceremonies as in like being like, oh, your, your highness, your grace.
Oh, it is my, it is my great esteem.
Oh, like, don't, don't bother talking to them.
Just get your work done.
I think, I think that's what it means.
Yeah.
Don't fucking waste my time with this shit.
I mean, if you're a person working, you don't want to have to like bow every time a lord enters the room while you're doing his wall.
You'd be like, you're doing the, doing the, we're going to break it down here through there.
Like a lovely little plaster.
You know what that one, that one sucks.
Let me, let me read another one.
Read, read no letters, books or papers in company.
But when there is a necessity for the doing of it, you must ask leave.
Come not near the books or writings of another so as to read them or give your opinion of them unasked.
Also not, also look not nigh when another is writing a letter.
Yeah.
Okay.
Pretty reasonable.
It's a work in progress.
Get out of here.
I'm trying to write.
I'm trying to, I'm trying to read.
Hey, hey, what you, hey, what are you writing there?
Hey, hey, George.
Hey, George, what are you writing there?
What are you, what are you writing there?
Ah, leave me alone.
Didn't you read my book?
I said, I said, leave me alone, kid.
I'm 14 and this is, this is upsetting to me.
I'm going to write that down in my book.
I'm 14 and I'm writing here.
I'm trying to write here.
All these dang, all these dang artificers as persons of low esteem always coming into my dang study and asking me,
asking me what I'm talking about and what I'm writing.
Leave me the fuck alone.
Quit using all these damn ceremonies at me.
You fucking, you fucking freaks.
The beauty degenerates.
It's George Washington, like English and he came over or born in America.
I have no idea who he is, but I know he's like early, early American boy.
He must have been born in England.
He couldn't, like there wasn't like no, no, no people lived in America.
No, I'm stupid.
He was born in America.
It's like the colonies had existed for, well, how long did the colonies exist?
Like more than a hundred years.
Well, how long did it take them to build the railroad?
Well, we built the railroad after the war for independence.
Right?
Okay.
Yeah, they had the wagons.
They went around, killed all the natives.
That was later.
Kind of.
Well, we never really stopped doing that.
Did America even really exist?
No, there's no, there's a real question.
Okay.
He was born in a log cabin in the middle of the sea.
No, I think he was from Virginia.
Right?
Born.
God, I'm looking at his Wikipedia page.
Yeah, he was born in Popes Creek, Virginia in British America.
Yeah, he was, he was born in the colonies.
So he was American.
Okay.
I didn't, I didn't know they called it British America, but it makes sense, I guess.
They call British Columbia.
Oh, well, this one, okay.
Okay, George, I could have told you this one.
Never express anything unbecoming, nor act against the rules moral before your inferiors.
No, don't, don't say anything, don't say anything bad or do anything bad when people
can see you.
When people of lower stature can see you and say, hey, that nobleman deserves a guillotine,
maybe.
I guess that implies that you can do things that are unbecoming and act against the rules
moral when you're around your buddies or your superiors, in fact.
So that's a classic, like, hoity-toity thing.
Yeah.
Be not immodest in urging your friends to discover a secret.
By discover, I think he means, like, reveal it.
Okay, this one seems weird.
In walking up and down in a house, only with one in company, if he be greater than yourself.
Wait, what?
In walking up and down in a house, only with one in company, if he be greater than yourself,
at the first, give him the right hand and stop not till he does, and be not the first that turns.
What?
Okay, there's more.
Wait, let me finish.
All right.
And when you do turn, let it be with your face towards him.
If he be a man of great quality, walk not with him cheek by jowl, but somewhat behind him,
but yet in such a manner that he may easily speak to you.
Okay.
This is just sort of like etiquette when walking with a person of greater status to not leave
him around or to, you know, to be in front of them.
Okay, let him stand on the right, don't stop before he stops, and don't turn before he turns.
Okay, so be a follower.
If someone is your superior, fucking like, yeah, okay, let them lead you.
Okay, well, whatever.
It's funny, because I feel like this is mostly common sense.
Some of it is, some of it.
Yeah, yeah.
Like you would learn this like living normally.
Shake not the head, feet, or legs.
Roll not the eyes.
Lift not one eyebrow higher than the other.
Rye not the mouth.
And Badoo, no man's face with your spittle by approaching to near him when you speak.
Yeah.
Yeah, true, Jor.
Badoo, I have Badoo your face with my spittle.
He's had, he's definitely had a few like annoying people come up to him.
Yeah, he was thinking of, there was someone specific he was thinking of when he wrote that.
Someone coming up who's being so rude, Badooing his face with spittle, raising his eyebrows
and rolling his eyes like, oh, what are you, what are you writing there, George?
Okay.
What are you, dumb?
Are you stupid?
Hey, what are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
What are you writing?
Okay.
Shake.
That before the Badooing with spittle, which is just great.
Shake, that first list of things, it's like things, it's like things you would do if
you're like being disapproving and like you think someone is an idiot.
It's, these are like a list of things that you would do to someone that you think sucks
and you hate them.
So it's like, yeah, don't do any of these things or people will think you hate them.
Like, you know, shaking your head at someone, rolling your eyes at someone, lifting one
eyebrow higher than, you know, cocking an eyebrow at someone, making a rye face with your mouth.
These are like, it's like, don't make a face at someone that looks like you think they're
moron.
This is really funny.
But the idea that he's like encountered these annoying people and 14 years old, he's like,
I'm going to set the record straight on how you're supposed to be.
Because I hate these people.
He didn't even like come up with these himself, actually.
Did he not?
Okay.
George Washington and the father of our country exhibited notable manners throughout his
life.
Diligence and social matters was common practice in decent society over the world during his
lifetime.
Unlike, unlike in the modern age, am I right?
Unlike these days, kids these days and society when we live in a society in 1984.
At the age of 14, George Washington wrote down 110 rules under the title, rules of civility
and decent behavior in company and conversation.
These rules were drawn from an English translation of a French book of maxims and were intended
to polish manners, keep alive the best affections of the heart, impress the obligation of moral
virtues, teach how to treat others and social relations, and above all, inculcate the practice
of a perfect self-control.
So these were 110 rules that he read in another book that he was like, yeah, these ones are
good.
Okay.
So he didn't even really.
Ooh, this is number, number one.
Rule number one, every action done in company ought to be with some sign of respect to those
who are present.
Okay.
Number two, when in company, put not your hands to any part of the body not usually discovered.
Meaning like, don't like stick your hands like in your clothes and like touch yourself
in like weird places.
Yeah.
Okay.
Don't.
Number three, I like this one.
Show nothing to your friend that may affright him.
Don't scare your friends.
Oh, spit not in the fire nor stoop low before it.
Neither put your hands to the flames to warm them nor set your feet upon the fire, especially
if there be meat before it.
Gib, Gib, you gotta give me one second.
Okay.
Gib, you gotta give me one second.
I spilled some shit.
I gotta clean up.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Oh, lol.
Sorry.
I'll be right, I'll be back.
You know what I'm saying?
Ben St.
The drink spiller.
The liquid loosener.
The, uh, the deuce spiller.
Table wetter.
A few moments later.
Okay.
Gib, you there?
Yeah.
Sorry.
Sorry about that.
What did you spill?
Oh, no, I know what you were drinking.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What was the second bottle that was on the ground that I had forgotten about?
Oh, piss.
So, I am, you know, I'm gonna have to, I'm gonna have to, like, use my Mr. Clean later
to prevent bugs.
All right.
Anyway, so that's enough of, uh, so that's enough of George Washington's rules of whatever.
Rules for life.
Yeah.
They're, they're George Washington's 110 rules for life.
Okay.
Well, the other funniest gifts.
So those, those were the, those were the, uh, two very funny gifts and then another one,
which I feel the need to show.
Uh, I'm saving, I'm getting it from, uh, another folder right now.
Okay.
Michelle, right?
Michelle made me this and this is so awesome.
I can't even, I can't even really, I don't, I don't really have the words to express how
great this, this is, uh, this is, um, a painting of a scene from, uh, T-Bap Phantom Reviews,
a hearth-swarming Eve.
Uh, she made it for me.
And I think Nate framed it.
I think Nate said, Nate, he put it in the frame.
Oh yeah, that's, there you are.
Yeah, it's the scene of, uh,
Wait, Michelle painted that.
She did.
Dang.
She painted it, uh, um, it's the scene, yeah, at the end of Phantom Reviews, it's Phantom's, uh, fantasy of himself on the, on the equestrian throne.
Uh, and he's got all the, uh, he's got, uh, he's got Luna and Celestia enslaved there.
He's wearing the crown of Princess, uh, what's Princess Platinum from the, the old, the ancient Princess of Unicornia.
He's got all, he's got the elements of harmony there.
He's got the crystal heart.
He's got Sor, uh, uh, uh, not Soran's horn.
Um, who was that evil pony, the shadow?
Sombra.
Yeah, umbra.
Yes.
Sombra's horn, yeah.
That, on the bottom left, I think that's the book from that one episode where Rarity finds the evil book that gives her evil green, like, greed magic.
That would, I thought that was Trixie that did that in that episode.
No, no, no, no, they, they, she and Spike find a book in a library.
And she goes green.
That was the episode I reviewed where the Gibbon rub face comes from.
Or, I don't actually remember what the episode was about.
No, you know, that, that might be, that might be like Star Swirl the bearded's journal or something.
It's a little hard to tell.
Like, I forget what that.
Is that cake standard in carbonite?
Yeah, it's cake, cake standard frozen in carbonite.
The ultimate prize.
Um, yeah, so I love this more than I can adequately express.
Damn.
Michelle always said she hates artists and yet here she is being.
And yet here she is.
What a, what a hypocrite.
And yet you participate in art.
Hmm.
You criticize artists and yet you painted a thoughtful Christmas present for me.
You bitch.
Yeah.
Hmm.
So that's delightful.
Um, and then this is crazy.
I'll tell one, one more like shocking gift that I received.
My, um, who does this?
My sister's boyfriend got me and Nate.
He just got us both playstations.
What?
Like, that's like, that's like $150 like on eBay.
Like an old PlayStation one.
Yeah.
Like a, like a PlayStation.
Like an old PS PS one.
Like nice.
Okay.
Okay, buddy.
All right.
You can play Final Fantasy seven.
And he also, and he also got me a greatest hits copy of Final Fantasy seven.
And, uh, wait, what was the other one?
Uh, Crash Bandicoot Warped, which I think is a racing.
No, that's the, that's the third Crash Bandicoot.
That's the, that's the best one.
Have you not played that?
Wait.
No.
Okay.
It looks like, it looks like he's riding motorcycles and shit in all of these.
That there is motorcycle levels.
And like flying plane.
No, I've only ever played the first one.
Oh, the third one's nice and polished and fun.
Oh, wow.
I didn't even know there was a third one.
Okay.
Speeding it.
The box art, I just noticed that the box art, it's him and, and the girl.
Wait, hold on.
I'll post the box art because it's pretty funny.
Um, uh, they're on motorcycles and shit.
And in the background, speeding enforced by Sheriff Neo Cortex.
I guess he's gone from being a mad scientist to a, a highway cop.
It's, it's just like the, like the bad face on every like billboard or thing.
It's like Neo Cortex is the bad guy everywhere.
He's not just a mad scientist on an island.
Hmm.
Uh, a cab includes Dr. Cortex.
I like that.
Like sort of like, like, like dejected looking dinosaur in the back.
I never noticed his expression.
He looks like I should be the Yoshi of this, but you have a motorbike instead.
And a tiger.
You got a motorcycle and a tiger and like, where does that, and where does that leave me?
Huh?
He's really sad.
He looks like, um, you know, the.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
It looks like that.
Um, so, so the pretty, I don't know, just like a pretty big flex of a gift to just get to
of.
Yeah.
He wants, he wants, uh, to get on the good side of your family.
I guess.
I guess so.
I mean, he already is.
Like he's come to like, well, he didn't come to last Christmas because it was canceled.
Lamal, but he's come to like a bunch of other family stuff.
He's pretty much already on the good side as he needs to be.
Uh, um, I don't know.
Crazy shit.
Um, we did a, um, yeah, we did a, um, we did a sort of a friend's mess, like, like a gift
exchange at Munchie house.
And of course the, the greatest gift of all that we exchanged was of course the Omicron
variant.
Um, but, um, uh, uh, uh, what did I get?
Oh yeah.
Munchie got me a, another cop killer shirt.
We got, we got a new, a new matching cop killer and ratty fucker shirts was my gift.
Um, there was also, um, for, for someone who, uh, I don't, we don't know, for someone who
I know locally, I got a, I got a copy of B here now, which is like some like 70s, like
missed, like Western mysticism yoga.
Shit.
And also a copy of, um, but the, but the spending limit was $20.
So I found this copy of B here now and I was like, this is weird.
This is cool.
And he loved it.
It was great.
Uh, it was a perfect, it was a perfect gift.
I'm a genius, but it would only, it only cost like $9.
So I had 11 left over.
So I had to get something else to fill out the, um, you know, the spending requirements.
So naturally I did the only reasonable thing and I threw in a secondary gift of a copy
of, um, the truths we hold, the Kamala Harris autobiography, which went, which went over
like gangbusters.
Everybody clapped and cheered and said, oh my God, it's the first woman to hold presidential
power while Joe Biden was anesthetized during a routine colonoscopy.
And I said, yes, queen.
Classic.
That's her, that's her claim of fame.
It's exactly how everyone reacts whenever Kamala's around future, future of the Democratic
Party.
Oh yeah.
Um, I didn't get much gifts actually this year.
I got, um, I got like a dress from, from my mom, which was nice.
And like, uh, like, like, like girl shit, like, like stuff for girls.
And I was like, that's cute.
That's fucked up.
It's a little, it's a little epic.
I tried it.
It looks weird on me because I'm not used to like wearing a dress like a normal day to
day thing, but it looked pretty good.
Do you not have dresses?
I have dresses, but like, I don't know.
Dress feels like a party thing.
Not like a wake up, like it's a formal, like it's a formal dress.
It's not a little fancy.
No, no, no.
It's just sort of, I mean, I have, when you get close at Christmas, or at least when I
get close at Christmas, I wear them on Christmas day and then a few days after just to see,
you know, how they feel.
And for the first time, I've been going like, like, I was about to say hardcore girl mode
and that's not the right phrasing.
Hardcore girl mode.
But like wearing a dress and leggings and stuff in front of family and it's no big deal.
So that's, that's a nice, that's a nice feeling.
Even my dad was just sort of like, yeah, it looks good.
So that's a, that's a nice thing.
Sweet.
But aside from that, yeah, I don't know.
I got dreams that PS4 game where you can like make video games and then play other people's
video games, like LittleBigPlanet.
I was going to say, is it like LittleBigPlanet?
I haven't seen that one.
It's by the same company, but like the, with the PS4, like the, the abilities to make things
are like so much greater.
You can basically make anything.
Oh.
Some people have made like recreations of Spyro games.
Peter Griffin goes to Bikini Bottom.
Yeah, you can do.
That's pretty exciting.
You can do all sorts of things and they have like very easy to make like platform things
like 3D platformers, lots of 3D platformers.
People just trying to recreate Spyro and Crash Bandicoot and stuff and Jack and Dexter.
Yeah.
Because it's not actually difficult to do that.
And I'm like, that's, that's neat.
And then there's like really cringe terrible things that people didn't try very hard on,
which is also funny.
I've been playing that and I think that was about it.
It wasn't really much of a, like a gift haul.
And isn't, hasn't been usually because I don't like ask, I don't know what to ask for.
Whatever.
Why, why is like this character, one that I see a bunch of images of when I search for
Dreams PS4?
What is that?
That's a fat person doing like a dab.
House of, House of Beavis?
Dreams PS4 House, House of Beavis.
Uh, there's a, there's a YouTube video.
Let's, let's find out, shall we?
Okay.
I think this might just be something that someone made.
But yeah.
Oh yeah.
Look at, look at like the amount of stuff you can do.
You can make a full like fucking 3D game in, in dream, in dreams.
Little big planet.
It was like side-scroller or if you fuck around, you can maybe make a top-down thing.
But in this, you can do fucking everything.
Could you make a top-down and a little big planet?
I don't even remember.
I only remember side-scrollers.
In Little Big Planet 2 and 3, they introduced like a, a, a motherboard, like computer chip
board thing, item that you can stick to a block.
And then you can give it like code, like rudimentary code, like and or gates and like line up everything.
And so you can make it so the gravity doesn't work on a thing.
And by pressing directions, you can go up, down, left, and right.
And that you can control the block and you can make yourself invisible.
So you create like a block that is your character.
And then you can top-down, you can make the level like that.
And it's why it's, it's, it's a real big hassle, but it was possible.
I never actually figured out how to make a top-down level in Little Big Planet.
I, I played a bunch of levels in Little Big Planet.
I never really, never really got into like making stuff with it.
Me either.
I made like a bunch of levels, but they were like very, like very much not a finished product.
I got very bored of things very quickly.
I had like a level that was just one thing, like a slide slams you somewhere.
Or like I made a car that goes, whew, and it's smashed into something.
And I was like, I don't, I don't want to build a level for this.
Fuck it.
Okay, I'm watching this video and it seems like this is just some art piece level.
Yeah, you can.
Where you run around like a weird sort of abstract like museum and look at weird stuff and hear
Bennett Foddy style, like audio clips of things.
Yeah, there's no like limits on what a dream is in dreams.
It doesn't have to be a game.
Sometimes it's a, it's just like a movie or short film or music.
Ah, walking simulators.
No.
Yeah.
But there's plenty of like, there's plenty of, there's plenty of fun and not bullshit.
True.
I did type in Vriska to see what there was and there was like a cutscene of, of Vriska
killing Tavros and I was like five seconds.
Well, this is pretty neat.
This is, this is just the little big planet thing was like, you could make games, but
it was all like tethered to this like sort of like toy set sort of aesthetic.
This just seems like they're just like, fuck it.
No, no rules.
Do whatever you want.
There is no, there is no unifying anything.
Yeah.
The, you know, the need for, the need for any such.
It's over.
We don't need it.
Let's do whatever you want.
There have been like a number of little games I looked at that were like legitimately could be
like indie games on steam.
Like with the level of polish, like, dang, you could, you could sell this, but it's on
dreams, so you can't sell it.
I don't know what the people do who make these.
Like the quality level, the quality ceiling is like, you could probably like recreate
a AAA game in dreams.
I, I can't help.
I'm noticing, you know, I don't know why, but in my, in my search for ps4 dreams, this
image was at like the very top of a bunch of my search results.
And I'm just, I, is this a real video game?
What's, what is this?
Occultic nine.
That's a funny box.
Uh, it sure is funny.
What is, I, I had, hmm.
Now not to body shame or anything, but something about this character.
I don't know.
This makes me think this isn't a real video game.
Occultic nine, anime boobs, boob physics, GIF.
Okay.
Is this like a, is it like a supporting game?
So this character is like, it's, it's a gigantic boob lady.
And that's her character trait physically.
Okay.
Is that what the game's about?
Is it like a, is it like an ecchi game?
That's, I'm a little, I'm a little bit curious.
Occultic nine, blah, blah, blah.
Is it Japanese light novel series?
Yeah.
Okay.
We just found the same result.
Yeah.
So this series, and it's a game of it.
Okay.
So it's, it's anime, which means it's hyper sexual sometimes.
Oh, it's by the creator of Stein's game.
That's more like Stein's pants.
You know what I'm saying?
I do.
Sadly, I sadly, I know all too well that to which you refer.
I just like, I'm sorry.
I can't, it's bold.
It's bold, bold to make that your fucking box art.
Like, I'm sure the game has a plot.
It looks like a, like persona or something.
It's about like occult investigators.
But the box art is just about a girl with huge tits.
Oh my God, that is just the box art.
I thought it was like a promotional image.
No, that's just the box art for the fucking game.
I'm looking at an article.
Well, I got my attention.
Is, are they going to like, in this article,
address the fact that the box art is what it is?
No.
They're just saying the game is launched.
Like, it's funny.
Like, in all the other art, you know, there's a bunch of characters
and one of them has huge tits and like, it's fine.
It's like, it's, you know, it's notable.
I notice it, but it's not like the main thing.
I think it's a main thing about her character.
I can't see anything.
I can't see anything else.
I can't see anything else on the screen.
That's a deep dive thing.
I'm going to look into why that is the way it is.
Cause I'm sure like,
Right.
For the creator.
For educational, for reasons, for academic reasons.
No, but for real.
That's such a weird thing to put on the box art.
Okay. I'm not crazy, right?
I saw that box art and I'm like, why is it like this?
This seems unusual.
This is, I don't know.
Well, my first thought was like, do they put like,
do they put like a, like Hentai
visual novels on the PS4 now?
Is it a visual novel?
I mean, the visual novel.
No.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know what kind of game it is.
Maybe it's a visual novel.
But I saw it, it looks like, you know,
it looks like a Hentai visual novel.
Like if I saw it on Steam, that's what I would assume it was.
It's funny.
Some images of this character do not emphasize the breasts.
She's just sort of like a detective.
Yeah.
And she's like.
This one.
This, this, this yellow one does not really emphasize it.
But the cover of the light novel doesn't emphasize it.
Yeah, she's just, she's got an arm in front of it.
You can't tell.
But I guess, damn, I guess they were like,
I guess they were like, we know what, we know what,
we know what sells.
Like we know what the.
We know what the most marketable aspect of this series is.
The, the Occultic Nine opening movie.
No emphasis on the breasts at all.
I go down to the comments.
First comment.
I'm a simple man.
I like the cover of the game.
Yeah.
That's why everyone's here.
They fucking got me.
That's why we're talking about it.
I've been tricked.
They're not even real boobs.
They're a fake.
This is a fake simulacrum of a human that this,
that this mangaka or whatever dreamt up to fucking fool me.
And.
They did the most interesting part about it is like.
It's not.
It's not obvious why like obviously sexualizing things.
Is like pretty normal in Japanese media.
But.
I feel like.
This crosses a threshold beyond which is that is like.
Except can never.
We can never.
Imagine seeing a character like this in like Pokemon or something.
Yeah.
You could, this would get, this would get censored.
This would get, um, this would, this is.
Yeah.
The, the, the, the.
The, the posing, the, the brazenness of the posing.
It's like, it's like remarkable.
It's, it's.
It's, it would be.
It's, it's remarkable enough that I see it and I think this has to be porn.
And then to find out like, no, it's not porn.
It's not porn.
It's actually just a completely, it's, it's just a completely normal.
You know, like video game.
Uh.
But.
Yeah.
That's why I want to.
It's actually, it's dirtier.
It's, it actually makes me feel dirtier.
Like if it was porn, I'd just be like, yeah, okay.
But there's like, no, like the fact, like it's not, it's not that.
I know you thought that, but it's actually not.
And I'm just like, well, then you, I, you have failed.
You have done.
I feel like it's, it's crass, it's crass of them to art, to, to, to, to.
Market it that way in a way that looks like porn.
And then you look at it and it's like, no, it's not.
It's like, well, I think that's on you.
I don't think I'm, I don't think I'm to blame here.
That what I want to know is whether like her character design is like
thematically relevant to her or the events of whatever is going on.
I want to look into it just to see if there's anything there because if there's
nothing, it's just like, it's a character that just happens to have a completely
incidental detail.
Here's, well, here's the thing.
I was wondering about this a while ago.
It must be remarked upon.
Sure.
Um, like a character would be like, oh my God, that lady has huge boobs.
Boob lady.
Wow.
Let's start a mystery team.
Absolutely.
Get my magnifying glass out, have a look around.
Let's do some, do some slew thing.
Yeah.
But like, I was thinking about this a while ago, like, I had that character
scraggity, aggity, the scarecrow.
Yeah.
She's got big boobies.
They're made of like straw.
Yeah.
And they're like, they don't have to be like that.
I just liked it.
Yeah.
And I'm like, I'm thinking the, like this is weird to me.
It's, I don't like find it offensive.
It's kind of funny.
Yeah.
And odd.
And I wonder if like, this shouldn't be something that people take issue with
like a character just having large breasts.
Well, I mean, with, okay.
But she, but she's not a real, but she's not a real person.
Right.
If she were a real person, obviously there would be nothing objectionable.
You know what I mean?
Objectionable.
I don't even mean it's objectionable.
There would be nothing to even remark upon, but this is a, this is a, this is a piece
of marketing.
It is remark able.
Yeah.
I've seen these, some of these gifts though, and they are like clearly supposed to be,
I don't know.
Titalating.
Sure.
If I post it there, will it be a gift?
Yes, it will.
Like that.
Like that's just, that's comical.
You know, looking, looking pretty good, looking, looking pretty good.
Listen, I, I get it.
I get the appeal.
Of course.
It's just, it's just amazing that like you're, you're, you're non, you're, you're totally
you're totally PG-13 detective, like occult detective, light novel game.
You dedicate like a third of the entire box art to the secondary character's boobs is
all.
Is it a secondary character?
I thought it was the main character.
I'm not actually sure.
I kind of thought that the main character was that kid in the yellow trench coat, but
this could be the main character.
I don't actually know.
Actually, it kind of looks like it's both.
It looks like it might be both the, this girl and the kid in the yellow coat.
She strikes me as like super ditzy because she's jumping around like, yeah, something,
something happened.
I'm so happy.
Bounce, bounce.
Doesn't even realize that her tits are bouncing.
And then all the guys, all the guys are like, oh my God, I can't believe she's jumping around
like that.
I mean, I would be like, I can't believe she's jumping around.
I can't believe she's jumping around like that.
That's what I would do.
Like if you actually had breasts that big, you would know what would happen if you did
that.
I think so.
And you would probably wear more modest clothing usually.
Unless you were trying to look attractive.
It's sort of, it's an odd character, like design and personality combo.
I mean, that's, I think that's, I think that's a pretty standard anime thing.
I guess.
The girl who doesn't seems completely oblivious to what her own boobs are doing.
And that's her personality.
That's the truth.
Yeah.
Girl who is just doesn't, that's the one thing that she's just not keyed into is like what
they're doing and where they are at any given time.
I just think of like, I like things to be thematically relevant.
And so I look at this and I'm like, surely there's something beyond like boobs on screen.
You look at these like, these tits better justify themselves in the story.
Or I'm going to be mad.
I mean, they could like, like an attractive character and there's like a young boy who
like, I don't know, sexual feelings because that's normal for a young boy and he sees them
as like, there's some, him growing up is part of the narrative.
I don't know.
Like some aspect of like a character being there, being the way they are.
That's funny.
That's something to do with the characters.
There's something funny about like your first go-to example of like, why would big boobs
be relative to a story is, well, what if like a little boy sees them and wants to get,
and he's horny for them and learns a lesson along the way.
Like that now that would be a story.
Well, it's, it's, I'm just spitballing, but like, in, in, like out of, out of like a,
like out of, I'm trying to think of the weighted phrase.
It's not like out of context, but like, were there no context existing?
There should be no difference between a character having any given attribute in a story.
They can have any attribute they you want that doesn't need to be used in a thematic
way to be necessary or allowed or valid or whatever.
Yeah.
And I would like it if it was fine for like characters to just have large breasts in
and the only place that doesn't seem to happen is in anime.
Where's the big booby rights?
But they only seem to be in anime for like titillation reasons.
Where's the big booby like not sexualized?
Well, it's like, it's because it's because if you're, if you're making a piece of media,
you know, you're, you're designing the character.
You know, these aren't, it's not, they're not a real, they're not, they're not a real person.
They're crafted by an author.
So it's not the same as just a person having a body like that in real life.
No, no, no.
I understand.
But like art can replicate life if you could put any body type into a piece of media.
And like if, if the say, you know how like representation is like skewed in the favor of
what the author knows about and is comfortable drawing or making.
So there's a lot of white people in Hollywood and have been for years.
So it's like, okay, representation.
You, you, you increase the pool of the types of people that can be in movies.
And that's good.
It just gets more people work and it's nice to see your own body type or sex or race or
whatever be represented in media that you consume.
So it should be the same for large breasts because people have them to have representation
in media, but it's always, I feel like it's always used for sexual like gratification.
I think, okay.
Crazy.
Here's my crazy, crazy take, crazy take.
Tell me if I'm insane.
I think that like you, you, you, the, the, the stereotypically attracted like, like the
classically beautiful woman, right?
I mean, I think like, like, like the Hollywood actress, the like a famous woman like that
who we might see on television or in movies.
They're, you know, they're, they look a certain way.
They have a certain build.
They have, they might have breasts.
They might even have somewhat big breasts, but they're not that big.
Like who's like the, like the biggest breasted famous woman might be like, I think Scarlett
Johansson's are kind of big, but they're not that big.
Like I actually kind of think genuinely there is sort of not that many women that have like
really large ones.
And I know that that's kind of just because they're sort of just uncommon in general.
I don't know.
I think maybe we could stand to have a few that have like abnormally large ones for lack
of a better word.
Why not?
You know?
So, so like those are not, those are not, those are not considered like Hollywood beautiful.
Those are considered like porn.
Those are considered like pornographic.
They're not considered like, um, like you should be in movies.
You should be a model.
Beautiful.
I think it is a little bad.
And I, and, and, you know, the fact that it would cater to my personal taste is doesn't
have anything to do with what I'm saying also.
It's even, even, even removed from that.
I think the point is still true.
What's the, what's the word when pigeonholed, right?
Yeah.
When you're pigeonholed into a role.
Women with large breasts can't be a Hollywood actress.
People.
You have to be the, the large breast woman.
Yeah.
If there is something like that.
People say, um, you know, um, you know, big, big boobs, like, ha, ha, they're, they, you,
you, you're, um, you're, I don't know.
What do they say about that?
Like, you know, they, they're like, I don't know.
They're like, they don't, they're the luckiest, I guess.
Or like they're like, like they don't, there was that one episode of, um, king of the hill
where Peggy gets like tricked into being like a foot fetish model.
And, um, she tries to explain what she's doing to Bobby by saying that like she's helping
like equal the playing field for women because like now it's not just like women with big
boobs and big butts that like men like now they like women with big feet too.
And, um, and Bobby's like, I don't get it.
How does this help the woman with big boobies?
And she, and Peggy says, believe me, Bobby, they don't need any help.
And it's like, you know, it's like a good thing.
It's not like, like, yeah, they don't need any help.
Like it's not a bad thing.
But I think, yeah, but you never, you know, there's a certain, I think there is a certain
size threshold that you don't really see anyone in like mainstream media going over
unless it's like a comedy character, right?
They'd be like a fan.
Unless it's a comedy character, unless it's a comedy character or if it's an anime where
Yeah, an anime is different, obviously.
It's, it's like, it's a way more common because you can draw them.
You don't have to find an actress.
I guess.
You know, having, having mulled this over and all that.
During this conversation, I started, I started representation.
We do.
That's where I'm getting.
Like at the, at the outset, I still think a cult nine is doing like the classic big boob,
but only because sex, sexual appeal and not because it's just happens to be a character.
No, this is, this is not, I would not call this representation.
No.
So in some sense, it's, it would be fine and cool.
In fact, if she just has breasts for no, like large breasts for no reason in the game,
but the way she's portrayed in the media is like a meta.
Like the reason is that like people who like big boob will click and will be interested
in the marketing.
You're saying that she has, if she just had big boob, but it was not like the point of
the character and it wasn't like.
If it wasn't so big on the buck side.
Right.
Like the fact that it was done as like a media, as like a marketing choice is unfortunate,
but it would you.
Yes.
Yeah.
I mean, it would be really funny to play the game and for her to have giant hits and
for no one to ever really comment about it.
That would be really funny.
And I would like that.
I mean, I would say it could be, it could be commented upon.
It could even become relevant in some way, but it's like.
But it doesn't have to be.
But if it was not the point.
Yeah.
Not being not the point of the character.
I don't know.
Maybe maybe I'm jumping to conclusions about this.
Maybe.
Maybe if we actually read the fucking light novel or whatever, maybe we would find that
that is the treatment that the character gets in the story.
It's just the marketing material.
Yeah.
It's just like fuck that.
Like, yeah, sure.
We got to sell this garbage.
Nice, good representation of all body types, please.
Sure.
All body types, all sexualities, all people.
Right.
I note like, what's his name?
Scott's roommate from Scott Pilgrim vs. The World, the movie.
Oh, not young Neil.
Fuck.
The other guy.
The guy with stubble.
Yeah.
I forgot his name.
But he's like a good example of gay representation.
Because him being gay is not like, I mean, he does have a few like jokes where he's like
floating with other guys.
But it's not like, I mean, it's based on a comic.
But like, usually or not usually, but it used to be in Hollywood, you have a gay character.
They're flamboyantly gay.
They talk about sex constantly.
Right.
I mean, how else would you know?
How else would you know their gay?
They're always talking about a guy's dick specifically.
And it's like, okay, that's not, that's that's stereotyped.
That's not representation.
And that's why the best gay representation of course is always be Albus Dumbledore,
who never mentions being gay in any way.
Almost, you might even think he wasn't.
You might even think that maybe he was never meant to be.
And it was just a complete afterthought that was like decided upon after the fact later.
But but it's not obviously that would be silly, but it's good.
But it's good representation because you would never know because he because he's a good,
he's one of the good ones and he doesn't talk about it.
Well, that really, that really activates my coronavirus.
That really gets my Omicron's going.
That really gets my Omicron's raging in my hippocampus.
Oh, there we go.
I can feel them.
Lost another lost another lost another the micro leader of gray matter there for sure.
No question.
All right.
What else?
What else are you talking about here?
Well, Christmas Christmas.
I mean, we kind of talked about gifts and stuff.
I didn't have a Christmas.
I was robbed of the holiday.
Yes.
Did you have a tree?
No, not in my you did decorate and all that.
Yeah.
When I went for Thanksgiving, we decorated me and my dad decorated the tree in their house.
So I did that.
You didn't get to see the fruits of your labor on the big day.
No, no, I didn't.
I had to fucking it was so so depressing.
They like those my family got came.
They drove by my house and like they dropped my you know, we met out in the parking lot
and they dropped my stuff off and they helped me carry it in.
They dropped my gifts off and I carried it into my house and I put it in my room.
And then on Christmas, like I called them in the evening and like I opened them up like on the phone.
I was like, ah, geez.
But it's OK.
It was fine.
Still got my sweet phantom horn painting so can't complain.
So got my PlayStation and my copy of Crash Bandicoot warped.
What more could a boy ask for?
If you're OK when I come over, we should play that.
We should do a let's play.
Oh, sure.
Of you.
Three.
Sure.
Yeah.
Why the heck not?
Yeah, I've played.
I think I think I've only played the first one.
I might have played the second one.
Maybe at some point.
I don't know.
Definitely never played this one though.
I will put it.
Yeah, I've got a I've got a PlayStation now.
So that's kind of that's that's pretty neat.
I think it came with all the cords and stuff needed to hook it up pretty pretty base.
Yeah, that was anyway, that was my Christmas.
There's nothing more to it than that.
I had our family trying to sleep.
Our family had the the the traditional Christmas Eve party where we get a bunch of our friends over.
And just drink about stuff, talk and drink.
And last Christmas, it was canceled because lockdowns and stuff.
This Christmas, we were allowed to but people were scared still.
So not that many people showed up.
And we had a bunch of food that we prepared and still there is so much food.
We couldn't eat at all.
But some people did appear and yeah, I was determined to get all fucked up a little wasted.
Because I have been tired and stressed out all month trying to get the secret project done.
Realizing that it wasn't feasible to get it done before the end of the year.
Trying to trying to like feel happy because the holidays are happening and not feeling happy maybe feel guilty about it.
And I was just I was just getting all like worked up over really nothing.
I should have been just relaxing.
I think you may have seen on my Twitter.
I said fuck Christmas it sucks.
I hate it and I'm sad and that was good because I felt like it's the holidays.
You owe it to other people to be happy and I wasn't feeling it and it was really stressing me out.
So saying fuck Christmas on Twitter allowed me to unwind a bit and then getting drunk was great.
And we played like I played a guitar.
I played like getting drunk is great getting drunk is great.
I played guitar and my dad was on drums and his friend played bass and we played some played some AC DC just fucking around.
That was good.
And that was it.
That was a good time and then I got hungover.
Sounds good.
Sounds like the kind of fun and low key time I probably would have had if I had gotten to go to my parents house and hang out with everybody.
But I didn't.
Sad.
I never get to see.
I like never get to see Nate and Michelle and my sister and her boyfriend.
So that's maybe I'll see them again in like spring or summer or something.
That's pretty cool I guess.
I'm sad about it.
Yeah.
I hate the Corona virus.
I don't like Omicron.
I guess that was Christmas.
What are you going to do for New Year's if you're feeling better?
Well, I don't know.
Since everybody fucking in the Munchie house is infected, maybe we'll maybe we'll do like if I if we feel better maybe we'll do like a New Year's thing over there.
I haven't really asked about.
We were we were going to do a New Year's thing, but then COVID happened.
But then it's like, well, if we all have COVID, like fuck it.
You know, assuming we all feel better together.
Like, you know, like I said, I'm feeling better and hopefully I will continue to feel better.
And if that's true, then I feel like I will be all right for that by New Year.
So maybe we'll do something for New Year's.
I don't know.
I'll have to see how everybody feels about it.
Oh, somebody.
Okay.
So despite the glitch, despite the glitch, the glitch that I have not fixed yet, the first the first person just beat the beta crow is crow is looking on discord.
Just beat the phantoms revenge beta.
Congrats.
First one.
Wow. Yeah.
Oh, they're talking.
They're talking about they're talking about how he did it.
Oh, they're talking shit.
Oh, he figured he figured out he figured out that okay, he figured out the method.
And I think that now that he's figured out the method other people will be like, oh, okay.
And they'll kind of figure out how to do it because I think a lot of people were not.
There's sort of a trick to it.
There's a there's a couple tricks to it, actually, and you once you know it, I think it's like, all right, I know what I have to do.
But before you think of it, it's it might it's like, you might just never think to do it.
And you might be just be like, what am I doing wrong?
Lots of people, a bunch of people were DMing me like, Ben, what am I doing wrong?
What am I doing wrong here?
And I refuse to refuse to give anyone any help.
But I'm surprised because I see maybe I'm forgetting wrong.
I see I feel like it was the same trick in the in the alpha.
I think the alpha had kind of the same trick to it.
So people should have remembered, right?
Like I think so, unless I'm stupid, but I was like certain that it was basically the same trick.
And yet people that beat the alpha seemed unable to beat the beta, maybe because the glitch stopped them.
I don't know.
I should check check on that.
What was it in like Wreck-It Ralph, the glitch they say going gamer?
What do they say?
When you when you go from one game to another.
Oh, is it?
Is it just called going glitch?
No, no, no, no, the glitch was like.
It was that guy.
No, it was the girl. She was the glitch.
No, was the wasn't the racer guy?
No, that was the bad man.
He was the one he was the original guy who went gamer and went into a different game.
And his fucking around caused the glitch.
That's caused of an LP to be a glitch.
Oh, yeah, I.
Yeah, I remember what you're talking about.
I don't remember shit.
I don't remember what it was called.
Is it just called like it's not called like going rogue or going.
It could be that it going indie would be a really funny word for it.
No, it wasn't that funny.
It was just sort of like I like going gamer.
That's funny.
So maybe a little glitch was going gamer and got into your game.
And it fucked it up with some people.
There's like a little cake standard going around like fucking up the game from the inside.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
Crow is looking has figured out everything.
Crow is Crow is looking has completely cracked it.
He has not.
Okay.
I'm looking at the at the log and the thing he he not only beat it.
There is a there is a secret objective you can achieve in the game in the beta.
If you play it absolutely perfectly if you play it completely 100% don't fuck up anything
do everything 100% as optimally as is possibly to do it.
There is an extra thing you can you can beat the game with and he has not done it.
But he has correct.
He has correctly identified the means of doing it.
I feel I feel like I'm giving away too much by even saying that but oh well.
I'm I'm impressed.
Okay.
So I guess that's progress not my it's not my progress on the game.
It's other people's progress on the game.
But I got to fix that glitch.
I got to fix that glitch and then I added them.
I added features like I added the ability to change the window size because apparently
on like a high res monitor it's very small.
My monitor is not that great.
So it seemed normal to me but like on cracks monitor it's like tiny.
So I added the ability to change the window size and stuff like that.
So I'll release I'll release the patched version with the bugs fixed and that added as beta version 0.02.
And then I'll alpha will come after I got I got to start drawing.
Fuck I got to start drawing comics again.
I got to start drawing slime and punishment to actually get that done.
Oh, I got to make an itch page.
So hard suddenly suddenly so many things.
Not suddenly I've known I'd have to do all this shit for a while.
It's just a it's not suddenly so many things.
It's just like always so many things and no matter how many things I do there's always a big list of things that need doing.
Ain't that the truth.
I am very excited.
I mentioned at the beginning but I'll say it again I'm super excited for New Year's when I can announce my other thing.
My other my other funny thing.
I'll announce on Twitter and then the next week I'll say it on here.
My secret secret thing is going to be it's going to be it's going to be a blast.
It's going to be a who everyone's going to have a good laugh about it.
And some people will probably give me some money for it.
So every everyone wins.
Very exciting.
Another thing I did.
I don't know if people know but I have an art website which is just sort of a collection of images from years of art that I've done.
It's called Gibb and Take Art and it's a Google site which I didn't know about a while years ago but then I found it.
It's just like Google documents Google spreadsheet.
You just make a website in like Google Drive.
And I did and it was really easy.
The only thing is that it's like it's got a dot site dot Google site.
It's sites dot Google dot com slash view slash Gibb and Take Art slash home.
I'll just post that link.
Go in the description and see the art I made.
I did one now for 2021.
I got a page.
It's art I made.
There's some not-safe-for-work stuff in there this time.
Oh wait I saw you posted this on.
Is this a new site?
This has been around for a few years.
I usually just talk about it on Twitter.
Oh wait I have seen this once or twice.
I feel pretty happy despite my not drawing quite as much this year.
I feel pretty happy about what I have to offer.
What I have done.
I'm pretty good at drawing.
The queen is pretty good.
Of queen saying Lamal based.
Yeah that's like a good.
The anatomy is really solid on that one.
Yeah I feel like I've gotten a lot better at just quickly doing an arm or a leg that just looks right.
Yeah.
I don't really need to think about it.
Yeah you have.
A lot of these.
A lot of these just have.
Pretty good anatomy.
Yeah these are.
Yeah this is.
Yeah.
Looking at all these.
You know I already knew this but looking over it again.
Yeah you've definitely improved in art this year for sure.
Thanks.
I only really drew.
No that's not true.
I drew doodles all through the beginning of the year.
And then the like the porn stuff.
It's never like nude but it is like large boob.
And that's that's something you can't you can't tell the children about.
As we saw from occultic nine.
If you have huge boob.
It's and you'll get.
You'll make people like us mad.
No we'll be on your side because we'll want.
Boobs to exist in media.
I should I should make.
Perhaps something that has like big as the main character.
But she's like overtly like a sexual being.
Because I've made her as the porn character I draw.
What if what if she was just having a normal day and she just happens to be really big.
She just happens to be fucked up.
Really hot in every way.
That would be super fun.
I would lose my fucking mind.
If that happens.
But yeah you can look you can look back in this website.
I've got art going back to 2012.
Where I had like a few pony things.
Compare 2021.
I'm gonna compare to 2020 just real quick.
2020.
I mean 2020 was Lord of Ghosts and Clarissa.
Which is insane still.
I can't get it.
I can't get my head around how much stuff I did that year.
I'm still I'm looking I'm looking I'm looking.
What the.
What is this.
I don't remember seeing this one.
Oh that that was part of like a.
Like a draw together with friends online website thing.
And I drew Aliyup and what's her face.
She's the character from Rayman Legends.
She's the.
Fuck why can't I remember her name.
But till it knows not but till.
Shit.
I gotta find out I gotta find out.
Oh god I never saw I never saw this image of endless expansion.
I never saw this one.
Yeah.
Endless expansion is like a dome because of course.
You know you know I saw this I actually I just happened to see.
I was looking on Twitter and I saw.
I was looking at an NSFW artists page their feed and they had recently retweeted.
An image it was like an iceberg image.
But it looked like this it was like a big ball with a nipple on top it was a big.
Spherical breasts with a nipple on top and it was like an iceberg.
And it was supposed it was like cut off not cut off but you know there was a line through it.
At the nipple and it was like the big huge breast ball was like.
The art you don't see and then like the nipple on top was like the art you do see.
Yes.
And it was like exactly like this.
Okay yeah so there you go.
I don't think I copied it this was this is 2020.
That was I don't know when that other thing was.
But the name is Barbara of that character Barbara the barbarian.
I think the construction I think your your construct your character construction and anatomy is like.
Markedly better in 2021.
You think.
I think so yeah I do.
It could be that I chose badly but I wouldn't say I haven't improved.
Maybe it was choice maybe it was partially just choice of subject.
No I would say definitely.
Like I need to try less hard to get better images done in 2021.
I think try 2020 was like when I when I just started to draw big in trip trip pants.
Yes that image of the trip pants you like be good.
What is this shirt was that just the shirt that that that emo girl that I posted was wearing.
Yeah some sort of a red dragon thing.
Can't wait to get my copy of the Lord of Ghosts comic book.
I got to get around to that.
Yeah I've been trying to relax but then I forgot to like stress.
I've been thinking I've been thinking I really want you know I have to draw a bunch of stuff for slime and punishment to finish up the comic for the game.
I really don't want to like draw it out too much.
I have I really am thinking about like how can I how can I like pretty quickly like move this shit along.
I had started to draw a few more pages one time during like 2020 before I had like not decided I'm not going to draw anymore before I make finish the game.
And then I and that was like it was discord sort of giving some like narration.
It was a bit of like discord narration about like and then and this and these were the the fallout of these events.
Right.
And then the last I have I've long I've long had some scenes in my mind of like how Phantom goes from New Los Angeles City to Equestria back to to go back to find Nightstar to seek his revenge.
So I have a couple of scenes of that that I have to draw that will hopefully I don't I don't think I need to spend too many panels on them.
Even though some of them are a little some of them are a little complicated but that you know the whole the whole ethos of slime and punishment is doing it really sloppy and not giving a fuck.
So we'll just do it like that and it'll be great.
And then there's a few scenes I will actually take me a bit of work because I want to draw I want you to pick some things happening to Phantom in Equestria before he gets to Nightstar.
And it's annoying because drawing Ponyville is like sucks like I hate drawing Ponyville like the houses in Ponyville are really annoying.
It's very detail heavy in a very specific way that I have to like like I can't like I can't ignore and I've never liked drawing Ponyville but I have to just just for a bit just for a few pieces bits and pieces here and there.
Oh well anyway I will hopefully get it done really fast and then I can worry about making a book and then I can worry about formatting a book and making a book out of it and that'll be fun perhaps.
Is this is this flower heads Canon color scheme.
Yeah he's he's got yellow pedals.
Oh okay.
Nifty.
That's about the only thing I really know about his character color scheme and the sort of dull gardeners green.
Yeah.
Cloak the sort of tarp color.
That's what all I thought of.
It's like yeah.
I like the idea of him having a very bright cute pastel color for for a head.
Despite despite his dour depressing angst.
Based based.
Well is there anything else or do you think it's voicemail time.
I guess not.
I guess the only other thing I've been thinking about is like how I like looking at people do lists of the top something or other games of the year.
But I didn't play any games this year that came out this year.
I just like the idea of me doing one of those.
But I don't know how.
So I guess I won't.
I like year roundups.
What did you play.
I also I played like Noida and like hardly anything else.
I played Minecraft.
I played Kenshi.
I played balloons tower defense.
Of course.
Wait what's Kenshi Kenshi.
I think I've talked about it before but it's like a post apocalyptic squad based micromanagement macro management RPG where you control people in like a post apocalyptic Japanese sort of wasteland.
Did you say you were playing it with your brothers.
No.
Oh that must have been something else that you said you were playing with your brothers at some point.
Okay.
Never mind.
I think I played Hollow Knight.
Oh yeah yeah I played games during the streams that I did for the Lord of Ghost kicks that I played Hollow Knight and I beat that on steel.
So that was fun.
Right.
I remember that.
I remember that and that was amazing.
So that was hype.
That was hype.
Gaming moments.
I guess I won a stream.
That was a heated gamer moment.
It was only heated in the tension.
I was not angry.
In fact I was glad because it all went swimmingly.
Yeah.
Yeah I want to get back into a bit of streaming.
I'm going to do like a New Year's Eve stream.
So actually if this episode is coming out on New Year's Eve I might be streaming or I might already have been streaming.
Because I like to stream as the New Year ticks over and then the stream is like I don't know what year I'm in.
Does it do that?
No it always goes into the next year like the first of next year I think.
Actually I don't remember but anyway.
I like doing those.
So I'll play some games.
I don't know.
You said I should probably wait for the final version of Phantom's Revenge before I play that.
Well.
I don't know.
It's not that big a deal.
I don't really mind.
What if I get the glitch?
What if I can't eat it?
It would be super embarrassing.
It would be a little embarrassing.
But it's fine.
I mean it's in beta.
And I mean I'm hoping to have that glitch fixed in the next day or two.
I need to hunt it like urgently.
It's like the most urgent thing I have to do actually.
So I will probably be doing that as soon as this podcast is over.
Or I should have done it yesterday.
So that's what I'm going to be doing.
Use the New Year's stream.
Come check that out.
I don't know why I'll be playing but it's always nice.
Oh right.
That'll be this evening, the day this podcast comes out.
Yes.
Right.
This evening in Britland time so earlier.
So it'll be 7 p.m. for me.
Right?
Around about there.
Around about.
I'll double check.
6 p.m. probably is midnight for me.
So it'll be like 5 p.m. or earlier that I'll be streaming.
And then I'll go over to next year.
Where it'll be like 8 p.m. for you.
That's about roughly.
Wait, did you say what you were going to play already?
I don't know yet.
Usually it's just like something.
Just any sort of game I feel like playing.
Last time I think we played 24 the game.
Which like with Jack Bauer.
And it was really, it was, it was all right.
But it was kind of jank.
Did you play it because of like the countdown aspect?
Oh, I didn't even think of that.
I think we just played it because we had it and it was new.
Yeah.
It was a new game that we had and it was funny.
Tectonic Improv did a Christmas, I think it was a Christmas, shit.
I think it was Christmas Eve.
Super Metroid speedrun.
I mean it wasn't, he's not like a, he's not like a pro speedrun or anything but you know.
I think he beat it in like an hour and a half.
Which is, you know, it's actually pretty good.
Actually now that I say it out loud, like, I don't know how long speedrunners beat it in,
but like it's way faster than I could beat it.
Cybershell also showed up to the chat and that during that stream, which was pretty fun.
That was pretty cool.
Yeah man, New Year's, New Year's stream.
Good, good shit.
Yeah, my stream is on Gibb and Take on Twitch.
Should be easy to find.
I'll check it out.
I'll be there.
I'll pop in.
I'll be around, I think.
Sick.
I don't know what I'm gonna be doing.
I don't know what I'm gonna be doing for New Year's.
It depends on whether and how sick I am by then.
Hopefully I'll be fully recovered.
You know, they say, what do they say?
The guidelines were a little confusing, but I think the...
It's like 10 days since either you first developed symptoms or you tested positive
and three days, no less than three days after you stopped having a fever or something.
But also if you test negative, that means you're fine.
If you test negative on the antigen test, that means you're not contagious.
So theoretically, even if you just started having symptoms yesterday,
but you got over, you felt better and then you tested negative,
you would theoretically be non-contagious.
So I don't know.
I have one test left.
The tests are kind of expensive.
There's like 25 bucks for a set of two tests, which is a bit shit, but oh well.
That's okay.
It's just helping me rack up more spend towards my sign-up bonus on my AmEx Blue business cash, baby.
So it's okay.
Anyway, my point is that that's what depends on what I do for New Year's.
Oh no, the brain fog.
Ah, the brain fog.
I'm getting confused.
All right, voicemails?
Yes.
Okay.
Let's see what we got here.
All right, the first voicemail is an image.
Let's take a look.
The Phantom Eve.
Oh, this is a roller coaster called The Phantom's Revenge,
which someone else has pointed out to me that there is a roller coaster called The Phantom's Revenge.
I see Nate there in the bank.
Nate just hunched over their little plastic garden chair.
Is that just a whole...
No, that must be someone else.
It must be someone else, and it's Nate's hood, yeah.
Why am I here twice, and one of me is like, oh, a soy face looked behind me, and the other one is like, no!
Well, am I happy about this?
Maybe one of them is the rowdy...
No, not the rowdy fucker, the cop killer, and the other one is Ben St.
Oh, yeah.
That's true.
Bearded Ben is always like, hell yeah, and clean shaven Ben is always like, no, why?
I shaved my beard again a while ago, but I've been growing it back, and it's starting to come back again, which is good.
It's kind of at the level where, if I trimmed my neck beard, it would almost be not a beard beard, but an actual feature of the face, and not just an accident.
So that's pretty cool.
Next one is a video.
A YouTube video.
Five real...
Jesus caught on camera and spotted in real life.
Oh.
It's crazy.
Hey, should we play it?
I'm playing it.
It's three minutes, okay.
Creatures.
Oh, I'm skipping around.
Cut on camera.
Number five.
This video is recorded from the Spain.
Oh my god, the Jesus winked.
Oh my god, the cloud looked like a face.
Wait, there's a guy like shitting in the woods, and they think it's Jesus, because it's got a white cloak.
I think this is a joke video?
I mean, it's called five real instead of four real.
Or maybe it actually means like five.
Is it called five real?
Viral, top five, fifth.
English does not seem to be this guy's native language, so I'm not sure if he would get the pun about four real, five real.
Five times real creepy crawler.
Creepy crawler?
Look at this.
It's so obvious.
The cloud is so obviously like CG.
This video is recorded from New Jersey in the USA.
Five times real creepy crawler.
Look, there she is.
Well, voicemailer, thanks for bringing my attention to all these times Jesus showed up.
I'm gonna change my wicked ways.
Okay, let me get the first actual voicemail here.
The number is nine three three nine six two.
Here we go.
This one is called hi guys.
And there it is.
All right, three, two, one, go.
I was listening to an old episode in which you guys talked about changing the show's name as part of the rebranding.
I assume you guys aren't actually considering that, but nonetheless I want to say that it would be a bad decision.
Most name changes are stupid, because often the thing itself hasn't fundamentally changed, like Facebook changing its name to Meadow or DG Bro turning into Yeeks Studio.
It's the same shit with a different name.
I'm not comparing the PCP to those things, but the same logic applies.
The PCP hasn't fundamentally changed.
It is still a group of friends talking about their interests.
There just happens to be three of them now.
The only thing a name change would accomplish is that former viewers who want to return to the show would fail to find the channel.
What do you think?
It's it's fair.
That's probably why we haven't voted.
I think I agree.
Yeah, I think it.
If I wanted to mount a counter argument, it would be I would say that like the change in who is on is fundamental enough that a rebrand was called for.
And that was why we were thinking about it in the first place.
But I think you're right.
I think I agree with you.
It hasn't fundamentally changed enough that it's like we need a new name.
Yeah.
So yeah, agree, agree.
Okay.
The next one is just a link to a Trixie tweet.
Oh, but I belong to which I even be able to see this.
Okay.
The tweet is the tweet has been deleted.
Unfortunately.
What was the tweet?
You should have left a voicemail saying it.
Yeah.
That's too bad.
I'm curious.
I'm curious now.
When was this voicemail six days ago?
Six days ago.
I'm a little bit.
I'm a little bit curious.
What was she tweeting six days ago that someone felt the need to post about to us.
Yeah.
So that it's the 27th.
So this would have been on the 21st or thereabouts.
She wasn't really tweeting much this month.
It's all just a bunch of like weird anime, anime art retweets.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I don't see anything and I feel like I'll never, I don't know.
If anyone knows what this was, feel free to let me know.
Yeah.
But yeah, the tweet's deleted, so I can't respond to it.
Sorry.
I'm on my mom voicemails.
Right.
So this one is called Happy Holidays PCP.
They're posting it right there.
There we go.
Happy Holidays PCP.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys, I know that this will only be played on the episode after Christmas, but was just
calling in to wish you all a Merry Christmas.
Hope you all had a good time with your loved ones, your families, and hope to see you in
the new year.
Hope none of you die of COVID.
Bye.
I wonder this guy didn't even know.
This guy didn't even know when he made this voicemail.
How appropriate.
Well, you know how my Christmas was, but thank you for the wishes.
I hope yours was good as well.
I hope everyone, I hope all our listeners had a Merry Christmas, especially the Jewish ones.
I hope they all converted before Christ returns.
It's coming.
Can you do a frame perfect, like a religion switch, and you'll be found.
Frame perfect, yeah.
Well, you know, actually when you, every Christmas, your religion data is stored in a variable
that is accessed.
So if you convert one year, all you have to do is celebrate Christmas once, and then the
Christian variable, the flag is turned on, and then all you have to do is you have to
execute a wrong warp when Christ returns.
Yeah, it's frame perfect, but with practice you can do it.
And then there was a good video.
There was a good video that I saw the other day from a channel that does nothing but post
videos about Final Fantasy 7.
I think they're called 4-8 Productions, Final Fantasy 7, wrong warp.
The video was about the Final Fantasy 7 wrong warp.
Yeah, it is, 4-8 Productions.
Final Fantasy 7's ultimate glitch, the wrong warp, and explain how in the PC port of the,
which is not even really a port, it was basically developed like almost as its own game.
They didn't just port the old game, they basically made them at the same time.
But yeah, for the PC version of Final Fantasy 7, there is a wrong warp that existed in the
game for like 20 years before anyone found it.
And it's a very interesting, like it was found in other versions.
There was a version of it that was found earlier that was not useful, but then like later developments
made it into something you could use to basically warp to the end of the game.
I love that shit.
I love fucking speedrunning bullshit videos.
4-8 Productions is a very funny channel.
It's not very big.
Well, it's 82k, which is, you know, respectable.
But it's a very humble little channel.
They don't do anything other than Final Fantasy 7.
Well, that's not true.
They're doing a Final Fantasy 9 Let's Play marathon.
But nobody watches that.
I don't know.
They're just a humble little channel that like two years ago they had some hit videos explaining
like, you know, speedrunning tech in the Final Fantasy 7 and other stuff like explaining
like fully going through like every material and like explaining like how they work stat-wise
and stuff like that.
And they were just like, well, we're just going to make videos about Final Fantasy 7.
Final Fantasy 7 are our gig now.
They made a Patreon and I'm just like happy for you guys.
They're not big enough that I have to be mad at their success.
Yeah.
So next voicemail is, oh, it's called Penny Packer.
It's another one.
Posting it.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys.
You know, after listening to your response to my voicemail last week and the week before
that about me misgendering and whatever, you know, I think you're right.
I think so.
I think you guys are right.
I think he's going to troll us.
I guess I was just being an asshole.
I was being a fuckface.
Yeah, it got me thinking a little bit and yeah.
15 seconds left.
Yeah.
You're right.
And I just want to sincerely apologize for it.
I guess I'll think twice before saying retarded shit.
See ya.
The twist there is that he says the R word, which is, I mean, I have quit saying it.
I have quit saying it myself pretty much.
It doesn't bother me that much, but yeah, it's not a good thing to say.
It doesn't bother me personally, but I don't say it, but I do tolerate it in others.
Other people say it and I don't scold them or anything.
So I can't really be offended that he said it because I let people get away with it.
I hope that was sincere.
I guess I can do nothing but accept this seemingly sincere apology.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, next voicemail is called Mr. Boop.
I wonder what it could be in regards to.
Three, two, one, go.
So I've had Mr. Boop open in a tab ever since you all talked about it that one time.
Really?
And I just found the time to read it.
It's not that long.
Read through the whole thing.
There we go.
And that was fucking stupid.
Tab for like a year.
I mean, that was completely retarded.
There was nothing funny, entertaining, or interesting about it.
Really?
Thanks for nothing.
Hmm, what do you think about that?
Do you think that maybe it's not as good like if you just binge read the whole thing?
I think certain funny moments are still funny.
Just like the panels of like, you read it and you're like, man, this guy is drawing Betty Boop as his wife.
And he's talking about how it's like the meta story that conjured in your head.
Is that of a cartoonist who is enacting his fantasies of having a woman who loves him unconditionally.
And that he gets to tell his friends about how hot his wife is all the time.
And they're like, yeah, and there's nothing else to the comic.
And then you get a sense of what the author is like.
That's where the meta comedy sort of elevates it.
And then it's just funny on that level.
And then it escalates.
I feel like if you don't like the first part, then you're...
It doesn't get any better than it starts.
Yeah, I think the funniest part is that meta of the author being like, this guy.
That brief moment where you're like, is this guy serious or is this a joke?
And you're having like a little bit of a...
I'm not sure for a second now.
Do you think the fact that this guy had heard us talk about it and already discussed like that?
And so like he knows like, you know, obviously it's all a bit.
Do you think that that kind of kills the comedy of it?
Perhaps.
I think that maybe there's something too.
Like if you don't know what it is, but you see it on Twitter and you look at it and you're like, what is this?
I kind of think that's the initial...
Maybe that initial intrigue adds something to the whole Mr. Boop experience that this guy was robbed of.
Maybe.
I feel though that like some of the like strips are really just funnily worded and can be enjoyed out of context of the entire thing.
Yeah, some of it is...
Some of it's gotta be funny, no matter what.
There were some fucking...
I'm Dr. Sonic the Hedgehog, no relation.
Come on.
Nothing funny in it, really?
I don't know.
I don't know, dude.
Okay.
Well, the next one...
Alright, there is a voicemail, but there's also a link to a fast upload, so I guess I'll just do both.
I don't know.
Here's the voicemail.
Three, two, one, go.
It's Keto.
Very nice.
It's very strained rhyme on revenge there, but it's okay.
The AI couldn't like do the extra work needed to make it fit.
Wait.
Okay, I'm stupid.
So, well, I won't play it again, but Eleazar used this one.
This is the same message, but without the shitty static, so use the better version.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, yeah.
But I understood it perfectly fine.
Very good.
Very droll.
Thank you.
Thank you for the poem.
I hope to have Phantom's Revenge, not just in the Christmas stockings of those at patreon.com.
But in the home of every hard-working American before too long.
Right on.
Next one is called X6.
Let me get it here.
Here we go.
X6.
Three, two, one, go.
He is not ejaculating, but he is coming nonetheless.
Okay.
I don't know what that means.
The last time someone was coming, someone was coming, maybe to get us or maybe just coming.
Oh, I see.
It's building.
It's a building narrative.
There's a building narrative here.
I forget.
Was the last one called X6 or maybe was the last one X5 and this is X6?
I don't know.
Man.
Nobody knows.
Maximum tension would be counting down to zero.
I guess when he gets here, we'll find out.
Yeah.
Okay.
Next one is...
It's a vocary.
I'll download the...
It's called...
I'm stupid.
It's called Song for January Sad from Dry Dump December at DustyDumps.com.
Three, two, one, go.
Fall out of the asshole
Still filled with that juicy moisture that the body craves
Which you needlessly dump away
Now it's January
My ship will fly like dust in the wind
Yes, my dried up sandy feces must flow with the breeze
And I would have liked to kept you, but you were just a cry
The moisture is all gone now
Now the dry should send us flying
Dry Dump December
Never forget
It's a very nice song.
Can we put that at the...
Can we make that the theme song for the episode?
I think that's a fitting intro for this episode.
Dry Dump December.
Yes, that's good.
This will be...
If you're listening to this, alright.
So the plan for New Year's is this episode of the PCP will be out on the 31st.
And then at midnight British time, Gib will be streaming.
And then the clock will turn over from Dry Dump December to regular dump January.
Regular ass January.
So regular ass January.
And so at the stroke of midnight, I think we should all be in Gibstream releasing our pent-up Dry Dump.
All is one.
Diarrhea January.
It kind of works a little bit.
I think it sounds good.
Dry Dump December.
Diarrhea January sounds like a one-piece character's name.
God.
God, I hope not.
He ate the poopy poopy fruit.
Oh no.
It wasn't a devil fruit, it was just poopy.
It was just poo.
He ate poo.
It made him sick.
He has permanent diarrhea now.
It was not...
Nothing magical is going on here.
Suddenly I'm really hungry.
Suddenly I really want to go and get a frickin' Egyptian frickin' shawarma wrap.
Since I'm not feeling too sick anymore, I might double mask up and go do that after this is done.
But anyway, for the moment, next voicemail is called...
Nope, not that one.
Next voicemail is called Voice Grail Reparations.
Here we go.
Two, one, go.
Hey, now that we're in the business of Voice Grail Reparations,
how about getting one to good ol' Cringis Mingus?
He definitely deserves it.
I made this song for him and everything.
I love that man.
Did we not do that?
Cringis for Voice Grail.
Now, please.
Yeah, I thought we already had.
I'm surprised we didn't, but I wouldn't be that surprised if we didn't.
But yeah, if he's not already in there...
Yeah, Cringis Mingus for Voice Grail.
No argument here.
Alright, next one is a text...
Is a pay spin.
The pay spin.
Text post.
Okay, I'll read it.
Suppose there's a guy called John.
John murdered my mother.
I despise him for having murdered my mother.
Someday, John changes his name to Michael.
He is really serious about his new name, oh god,
and gets mad every time someone calls him by his old name.
After learning that fact, I start calling him John
because I want to make it clear that I don't respect that person.
Is this a valid justification for my action?
Alright, I'm gonna say...
I think I know that this is an allegory for trans people.
I'm gonna say...
But you cannot equate somebody's change in their gender.
Well, here's what I think.
Oh no, they're just saying you don't like someone.
I'm gonna say...
It's gonna sound goofy.
I'm gonna say no, it's not justification,
but with the caveat of like,
okay, maybe you're not justified in not respecting their name change.
Like, who cares compared to the fact that this guy is a murderer, right?
Like, these two things are not comparable.
So, sure, yeah.
Okay, yeah, Mr...
I hate these fucking questions.
Like, okay, Mr. Fucking Genius, yeah, sure.
What would you not call a trans person their dead name
if I was holding a gun to a baby's head and I said you had to?
Well, no, I guess I would, sir.
You got me.
It's just sort of like the murderer thing.
Like, the dead naming is like...
It's a bigoted action, right?
Like, it's disrespecting someone,
but specifically because of their, like, status as a trans person.
I would say...
It's not about what they did, it's about who they are,
and you're trying to get at them like that,
but you are doing a bigotry by doing that.
I would say that you're not really just...
There are better ways to, like, I don't know.
Yeah, I would say you're not really...
I would say that regardless you're being a bigot,
but like, fuck the person who was a murderer as well,
so I don't...
Right.
I wouldn't, like, cancel you for doing that
because it's somebody who murdered your mother.
Yeah, I would...
But you are doing a bigotry.
That's unambiguous.
I mean, I would say you have a...
Yeah.
Um, so...
I would say you're not really justified in not respecting the name change.
It's just such a small thing that it doesn't matter.
But, like, you know...
If you're like, oh, oh...
What, Michael?
Oh, you mean John, the guy that killed my mom?
You know, okay, you say that,
and I, you know, debate lord that I am.
I come...
And I'm gonna...
I stroll in...
Oh, my God, it was the brain fog.
Um, I stroll in, and I sit down on a chair,
and I turn the chair backwards, and I say,
hey, so...
Hmm, are you saying that you don't respect anyone's name changes?
You know, John went through the legal processes,
like, you know, he changed his name in the courts,
you know, it's Lee, like, do you not respect anyone
to change their name?
And you're like, well...
No, it's just this guy killed my mother,
and I'm like, well, oh, okay.
Well, uh, so I guess that, you know, by extension then,
you know, because this guy killed your mother,
that means that you don't respect anyone's legal name change at all.
What's your criteria for a real name?
Does it have to be given by the parents?
What if the person's parents were dead?
What if they were adopted?
Do their adopted parents get to name them?
Would that what you call them
if they never met their real biological parents?
Da-da-da-da-da.
Okay.
Um, so yeah, I think it's true.
I think it's true you're not justified
in not respecting their name change.
Fuck you.
Uh...
Yeah, that's it.
It's just like, you know,
in a situation where a person changes their name,
it's not the same as someone changing their gender
and having a dead name, exactly.
What this question is?
I know, like, it, like,
they're...
The only reason they're asking the question
is because they want to
try and, like, logic
around
calling someone a dead name
because you don't like them
as being okay.
And I just think it will not be okay
because it's, like, inherently a bigoted action.
What this question boils down to is,
like, okay.
What if, okay, you say
I shouldn't do something
because it's, like,
it's not really, because it's not justified?
Well, okay.
Well, what if something made me
really, really mad and upset?
What if something really bad happened
and made me really upset
and made me really want to do the thing
that isn't really justified?
Wouldn't it be justified then
because of how mad and upset I am?
No.
Well, not, I mean, not, not really.
An obvious, an obvious thing
to say is, like, if it were a black person
and you said the n-word,
it's like, well, I'm really mad at them,
but yeah, that's still, like, a racist thing to do.
Well, yeah, but he killed my mother.
You can hate him.
You can be really mad.
I understand why you would say that, you know.
But it's, like,
the, the, the action
is still a racist act.
All right, all right.
There's no, I don't know,
I don't know what you want, I guess.
Do you want to just say bigoted things
and not get in trouble for it?
I think he, I think he's just trying
to get our goat, and I think he did
because we've spent this long on it.
Well, I mean, it's, it's an interesting
question to, like, try and figure out
I guess, you know what, I guess,
to poke and prod.
Like, I don't know what this guy,
maybe he has, like,
sincere intentions.
I'm just, I'm just so used to
getting this question
about Chris, in my fucking
YouTube comments about Chris.
I got another, I got another,
I got another shitty smug
comment about, like,
and I won't,
I don't even remember the whole thing,
but it was another one, it's like,
okay, obviously
none of us are against
trans people, but
but bro, obviously
we're not gonna respect Chris Chan's gender
because
of things.
And it's like
I get the same, I get the same
comment every fucking time
and it's always the same, and they all
think they've figured
something out. They're all, they're all, like,
they've all hit, like, the most
basic, like, grade
school realization.
They've had the most basic grade school thought
in their head and they think they're a fucking genius
and they think they've, like, cracked it
and, like, they have an undefeatable argument
that beats me. And they all
have the same attitude about it.
The main thing that, like,
differentiates, like, doing
a bigoted thing or a racist thing
or whatever
in, like, a, in a
potentially justifiable, like,
state of anger or, like,
revenge or whatever
it is.
The reason it's always not okay
is because
the bigotry hurts people
who are not involved. There's a
collateral damage
like, caused
or perpetuated
by the
the insistence of using
bigoted language
to hurt people
and you could just punch them in the face
and that's direct and personal
and that's different. Right. Sure.
And it's like punching someone in the face
because they're a murderer.
Why not simply exact vengeance?
It does not cause collateral damage.
Why not simply avenge them
yourself upon them and drink their blood
in victory?
Yeah, it's just, it's
it's lazy to go
for the bigot stuff.
And if you insist
on using the bigoted words, then
it's just sort of, like, weird.
Like, are you
you, I don't know
what you don't need to
use those words. You can just
gender them correctly and call them a piece of shit
and say
they should, you know, be locked up
forever. It's, it's not
difficult. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. All right.
I agree.
Next one
is
Nate's real nobody name
from a real Kingdom Hearts fan.
Thank God.
Finally got one. Finally.
Did you see, wait, before we play this
I retweeted a really good
tweet on the PCP account
the other day, or it was on Christmas
I think.
It was like, you know what, I'll just read
it because it's, it
cracked me up.
A piece going to the PCP
account.
Let me look at it. I'll read it verbatim.
It was
the X
in Xmas isn't meant to replace
Christ. X is the Greek letter
for, for key
pronounced key. Jesus
was a vessel with no darkness meant
to battle Vanitas a being of pure darkness
to create the key blade a weapon
of ultimate power to open the true Kingdom
Hearts.
Yes.
You know, like
it's a funny juxtaposition because
you think it's going to be about
real history, but then
there's
the Kingdom Hearts.
Woo, I love me a good juxtaposition
of concept.
Isn't that a bait and switch, not a juxtaposition?
Yeah, I guess it's both.
You would call it a bait and switch setup.
Yeah, it is. No, it is a bait and switch.
That's true, for sure.
Okay, but anyway, Nate's real
name. Three, two, one,
go.
Every single one of you
is stupid. Yes. Yeah.
Nate's nobody name is
Texan.
You're not the first one to say that,
but he's not from Texas. It's got the
N-A-T-E.
Yeah, it's a funny
name.
You're also stupid.
It would be funny if his name was
Texan, but that doesn't sound like a nobody name.
Yes, also he's not from Texas.
That's the joke up.
Although he does like to use the cowboy hat emoji.
God bless him.
So, I mean, that's gotta
mean something.
It's gotta.
Next one is unapology.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh my god, I'm sorry.
I called you all stupid, everybody.
I don't know what got into me.
I was like into the bit and
I don't know.
That's okay, dude.
I'm so stupid.
Yeah, you are so fucking stupid.
You're so fucking dumb that you would say that.
You fucking idiot.
Next one is called
I'm posting it.
It's called web comics.
Three, two, one,
go.
Alright, my last voicemail was too negative.
Mr. Boop, I thought it was gay.
Maybe you like it, whatever.
What I thought was cool was Scoob and Shag.
Have you ever heard of that one? No, really?
It's another web comic along the lines of
Tails Get Strolled and Mr. Boop.
Not really. Because you got Scooby,
Shag, Kermit, Mickey Mouse,
Yosemite Sam, Fred Flintstone.
All the characters.
And this one has like awesome action.
Okay, maybe you were looking for
the wrong stuff in Mr. Boop.
Scoob and Shag, check it out.
And I also read Clarissa Gunsmoke,
which was really fun and cool.
One's the next chapter.
I read...
I'm not...
I'm not caught up with it,
but I did read some Scoob and Shag.
I was caught up with it as of maybe
like two years ago or something.
So I've read a bunch of it.
And like, I think Scoob and Shag is...
It's good.
So I think a lot of people call it cringe.
A lot of people think it's lame.
And I think, and I understand why.
Because it's very like...
It seems basic.
It seems like a basic version of
Tails Get Strolled.
Yeah. Like normal, like normal
nerds can get into.
What does Scooby do when Shaggy
was so like showed in battle
mango anime?
Sort of. I mean...
I've heard people sing his praises as well.
But like...
That's the general gist.
Is that it's pop culture
characters
that go from
just a normal comic that you're just enjoying.
And then it becomes more serious.
And it's funny because
you wouldn't expect Shaggy to be serious
in a shounen battle mango.
But that's what it becomes. And it's like, that's the extent of it
as far as I understand.
Maybe it's more in depth than that.
I think it kind of starts as like a...
It's sort of like a regular
Scooby-Doo
fan comic. But it's
drawn kind of like weird.
The way Scooby is drawn
is weird.
And the fact that he draws
Scooby that way is sort of like
the running gag.
He always keeps drawing him
that weird way. Even as
Scooby becomes like the most
important character in the universe
and stuff. And all these
shounen battles.
Scoob and Shaggy is genuinely
good in a technical way.
The art is really good.
And a lot of the battle...
I think a lot of the battle...
There's a lot of shounen power stuff.
And some of it is kind of interesting.
I don't think any of it is as
like, whoa,
that's kind of unexpected
cool as the neutrals.
Yeah.
Some of it is good.
Some of it is pretty good, but I don't think
it's any of it is as good as the neutrals.
It's um...
But like if
I think if this guy
was like, read Scoob and Shag
and saw Mr. Boop, and it was
also incorporating other characters,
I would say that the scale
of Mr. Boop
is not the same thing. And maybe
he was like waiting for it to go
further than it did.
What's a little bit more...
It's not really about that, but...
Yeah.
What's a little...
What I think makes Scoob and Shag
a little lame in my opinion is that
it's not just like
Tiltgates Troll has all these characters
and sometimes they refer to
the cannons they exist in.
Like they do...
Bugs Bunny is canonically a loony tune
and he does...
He puts up signs for duck season
to trick Elmer Fudd and whatever.
But um...
That's totally not relevant
to what they're doing.
Scoob and Shag, the story of
Scoob and Shag is about
these cartoon characters are
from... It's basically like Space Jam
logic. Like these cartoon characters
are coming from the cartoon world and they
did like a...
There's some kind of weird plot about how they were
escaping their cartoon homeworld
to come to
the real world or something like that.
It takes itself a little more seriously
in a way that I think is
not funny.
Uh...
I still haven't read much of it
so maybe there's more to it.
Mr. Boop doesn't take itself seriously at all.
Mr. Boop is just fucking around.
It's like so stupid.
Mr. Boop takes itself maybe even less seriously
than Tails gets trolled because like
Tails gets trolled...
In Mr. Boop like do they even...
I guess they do probably...
Mickey Mouse does still belong to the Disney Corporation
and like...
You know...
The Homestuck
Trolls are...
They do sort of exist in their...
I would say it's pretty comparable.
Like the amount
of like this character's
backstory and like canon matters to the story
is pretty similar in like Mr. Boop
and in
Tails gets trolled.
In
Scoob and Shag it's bigger.
Um...
Sort of. Kind of.
Yeah.
I fell off Scoob and Shag and I kind of was like
yeah I kind of get it.
I think the best thing about Scoob and Shag is the art
actually because like a lot of it's really good.
Um...
Obviously that's not really true
of Tails gets trolled and
Mr. Boop.
But oh well.
Uh...
So that's based.
That's based. I want to see the end of Clarissa.
Uh...
2022 is going to be the year
of doing
a bunch of shit.
It's just going to be the year of continuing to do a bunch of shit
as much as I can.
So I will definitely
plan to finish Clarissa.
Um...
At least the story that's currently happening.
What's Scoob and Shag is
it's like the sort of the comedy of
Scoob and Shag is in that
like...
It's the comedy of the fact that it takes
itself 100% seriously.
Like the whole like melodrama.
Yeah.
It's...
Yeah I think maybe I'm being a little hard on it.
Um...
But like the whole melodrama of like these people are from like another dimension
and they came to a new universe
and like a lot of them lost their memories
and they're brainwashed and they're
rediscovering this like
ancient truth about their people and whatever.
It's like...
It's all delivered with 100%.
I think...
Which is...
The way to go in a very different way.
The way to go with a
thing like a premise like that is
is to go as extreme as you possibly
can into
what a cartoon character situation
would not be like. Where
characters are bloodily killed
and the neutrals. And in Tales of Gets
Trolled they go so fucking
intense with some of those scenes.
They do in Scoob and Shag too.
Sure.
I haven't seen enough to know.
But like that would...
That's what you would need is that it would need to be
it would need to be like as depressing as
Berserk to be like a peak.
Scoob and Shag is.
Of that joke.
That is basically what Scoob and Shag is.
So like there's definitely some...
It's definitely going for something and it's
achieving it. For sure.
Also I remember there's one shot of
um... This is a bit of a spoiler but
Bugs Bunny turns out to be like a big
villain.
And when he reveals his power. Cause basically
every cartoon character has like a
sort of like one...
It's sort of like a stand. They have like one
like power that is unique to them.
That they have. And Bugs Bunny
is like the ability to
I think it's like
he can like erase things from reality
and the way that he does it is he controls
like TV static.
Like he can generate like TV static
around himself that can like erase
stuff. And
it's awesome.
Like the the the the the panel
of him like
revealing the power and like all this static
is like exploding out of him. Like looks really cool.
And that's the that's the image
that stuck with me the most
uh from
Scoob and Shag.
Yeah so
very different reading experience
uh yeah
um
anyway
next one is
me failing oh god
me failing drugs. Was it
webcomics? No that was the one
we just listened to. Okay so I've been sort of
clicking on them on the website
half. Oh yeah. Clicking
in the discord half. I don't know which one
we should listen to. Yeah that was just
webcomics that we just listened to. The next one
is me failing dry dump December
uh three two
one go.
I'm not listening to this.
I'll listen.
Oh here grunting.
Grunting.
No that's dry.
I'm I'm I've muted it.
Grunting.
You didn't get me. Oh god
I think he's going to be bleeding after this.
It was very dry.
It did almost sound like sand so congratulations.
Man
you were so close. All you had to do was hold on
um another like well this
was two days ago so another like five days
you were so close. So close.
That little bit of moisture that
was left that would have made it into sand
you know you lost it and now you'll never get it back.
Tragic.
Stupidest joke ever.
Next
Next one is called
uh unedited clip
from the PCP
which I will just uh
it's revocorous so I will download
unedited clip
from the PCP
three two one go
oh my shit is not clean
my shit is not clean and it's a mess
and it it oh man
there was um my shit is
not clean again this was the thing
it was another problem I had this week
with um
with reflections
there was a
uh what was it what was it
uh shit there was something
with a character
brain fog in the game
that was
what was it doing
it was doing something
oh I remember it was like
it was um
I guess
so I'm meant to be so I'm meant to be
shamed right by this
uh yes
I don't
I don't get it like yeah
I didn't get to the point
in 40 seconds
I don't yeah I stammered a bit and I was trying
to remember something
I mean yeah if you're trying to remember something
it'll take a while
I was kind of awkward when I like
I don't say anything in between
but I don't really know what to say
a lot of the time
I was conveying information
in this clip like I conveyed that it was
something about a character
doing something
and then I was trying to like fill in the details
as I went so I don't know man
this one doesn't I don't know what we can really
learn from this
would it be better if I never stammered
never paused always knew
exactly what I was going to say well sure
of course of course
um next one
is a video
the seven seconds long
the eight seconds long
Anthony Fantenna reviews
the procrastinators
podcast
podcast is a skeleton of
what it once was I'm feeling
a light to decent for on this thing
yeah
okay so this is
an Anthony Fantenna voice
modulator
it's not a very good one
I like saying that. I don't know what they're called. Yeah, it's not a very good one. Yeah.
The Dr. Wolf and Applejack ones were much more convincing.
Maybe because those are cartoon characters, so I'm just like more easily more easily convinced by
them. That's not the fault of the cartoon character. Well, even well, I mean, he kind of is he has a
animated little character. Yeah, but like Anthony Fantano has way more footage of him talking
in a microphone on the internet than Dr. Wolf, I would think. Well, what a draw from it should be
smoother. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, I think it's a slap job for sure. Yeah, you're right. I think this
but it did you know what message received message received the melon thanks we're
thanks for slipping. So we got to, I don't know, do something about that, I guess. Next
one is called Nate heads. Putting it here in the chat. Okay, Nate heads three, two, one, go.
On episode 273, someone asked why best guy of his fans are called Nate heads and not something
that rhymes like Nate mates. Well, that's simple. It's because they're always sucking Nate's dick.
Because because they give a Nate head. No, I mean, Nate mate would also would also be like a sexual.
It would be. Well, that implies like they're equal partners in their sexual intercourse.
But that's not acceptable. That's not that's not that's simply not the case.
When I'm a fan of something, I give it head. That's that's how it works.
Anything? Yeah, if I'm a fan of Minecraft, I'm a mind head.
That's what giving head means, right? As you call yourself a head after it. Yeah.
I'm giving my head a silver platter.
What? I don't know.
A silver platter? Like if like, like decapitated myself.
Oh, I'd be giving it a head. But like, whatever, stupid.
No, I get it. No, I get it. Okay. It was a bit. It was a bit of a leap, but I got there.
Um, next, this is the last one with the last voicemail and my eyes and nose and throat are
feeling pretty dry. So hoping my hoping my not my hemoglobin, my Oh God, brain fog.
What's the word for the part of the brain? Sarah, not the cerebellum.
No, part the part of brain. I said it earlier.
Part of brain, smell, memory, hippocampus. I hope my hippocampus has survived this long.
I mean, I guess it's good that you've been doing dry dump December because you need
all that extra moisture, it seems like. More now more than ever. Now more than ever.
I can't afford to defecate. Next, this one is called a special guest calls in to respond
to Ben's football take three, two, one, go. Football sucks. It's a garbage sport for toilet people.
Boo. What was that for? Sorry. I feel like I've heard that video once.
Um, I don't remember. I may have heard that line before, but I definitely don't know what video
it was from. Fuck X. Did Jesse ever make a video that was just called fuck football?
No, I don't think so. Yeah. Oh, well, that's it. That's all the voicemails.
Yeah, that is it. All right, well, I should hopefully order some more groceries.
And then I might just try to, I don't know. I'm not I'm not sick enough anymore that I'm like
need to just like try to sleep all the time. What time does the PCB like come out in America?
Usually two PM is the normal time for two PM and Friday. So somebody watched it when it came,
when it comes out, they would have time to prepare for the end of the year and have a good
New Year's Eve. Yeah, I mean, we could always put it out earlier in the day if you wanted.
Uh, no one's like, you know, that's a usual time, but no one's like super married to it or anything.
Well, in the off, on the off chance that people are like not busy and had the time to listen to
the episode before the New Year, a happy New Year. Every listener. Right. Yes, happy New Year.
You know, by the time they're done, by the time they're done listening to it, though,
it will be three hours after that. So they may have, well, so it would be five PM.
Yes, that's time. Well, which would still be, which would still be time. Yeah.
Okay. Yeah, Merry Christmas for all the happy, happy holidays, everyone.
Don't get, oh, don't be like me. Don't get Omicron.
See you in the New Year. Yeah, it's the last, last one before 2022. 2020 was bad. 2021
was not the best, but maybe the trajectory will continue upwards. 2020.
The fact that 2021 had the vaccines is a relief because going into 2021, they didn't exist yet.
Yeah. All right, that's true. I'm feeling a bit down on 2021 lately because of, you know, the
current spike and how my Christmas went. But overall, it was definitely an improvement.
But that's what I'm saying. It's a big spike, but it's good that the vaccines are there to make
it not fatal for the vast majority of people who are getting it. Yeah, although, you know,
Omicron doesn't, I don't know, Omicron doesn't... Gank COVID is not fine, but like...
It does help. The death toll and like the need to be on ventilators are like minimized.
I'm not saying it's fine. I'm just saying the vaccine is not, is significantly less effective
against Omicron. So that's unfortunate. Maybe they'll come up with a reformulated boost that
will affect Omicron. It is effective. It is effective against it because people who have not been
vaccinated refuse to get it. But it's... Yeah. They're getting on ventilators. They're dying.
Those are the people who are anti-vaxxers are getting hit hardest with all this.
Well, sure. And it does. I guess it does, yeah. It is sad when people die, even if they
brought it on themselves by being foolish. Yeah.
Man, well, anyway, all I'm saying is here's to a good 2022. Let's keep the good times and the
vaccines rolling, baby. Let's stick them up. Let's fucking pump our veins full of whatever
Dr. Fauci wants us to. Let's get high on that 5G. Yeah. The year of 2022 will be the year that
my secret project comes out and Clarissa Gunn's vote will be finished and the Lord of Ghost stuff
will be sent out. And Lord of Ghost Chapter 3, the final one, I mean, the final act of Lord of
Ghost will also be finished. Aside from that, I don't know what I will be doing, but that'll
keep me occupied, I'm sure. That's pretty good. That's pretty good. It will be the year... I think
I can expect that I will do the Slime and Punishment book this year in 2022. That's good. It will be
the year that... It'll be the year when my secret secret project get to be revealed. I'll reveal it
soon. It will be happening, going out, available, which will be very funny and cool. I'm going to
say it will be the year when all of the Radcon 4 content is finally released. I feel very confident
about that. I suppose. It's not entirely up to us now. It's not. Bulls are in other courts at the
moment. That is true. Nevertheless, I feel confident about it. But anyway, all that's pretty good
stuff. That's not enough to fill me in. I don't know what I'm going to do this year. I have a few
things on my to-do list and I don't know what order I want to tackle them in, or maybe if I need to
change tactics, change gears, and maybe come up with some new things in the near future. But I
I don't know. We'll talk more about that in 2022, I guess. I think it's going to be...
Not to be cheesy or anything, but I think it's going to be a good year. I think I see big things
happening. I think I see changes on the horizon. I think it's going to be good. I'm excited.
We can only hope. Yeah. All right. Are we done? Yes. The end. All right. Well, love you all listeners.
See you next year. Peace out. Have a good one. Goodbye. Goodbye.