I'm going to bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Okay, I sure hope there's no spooky AI robot voices in here this week trying to steal our
jobs as podcasters.
It sure would be bad if AI advanced to the point that they could just replace me with
a robot duplicate.
Welcome to the Procrastinators Podcast.
Welcome.
We're so soulful, we're so full of human.
Yeah.
They'll never replace me.
My work here is indispensable.
I couldn't tell if you were trying to do an AI sound and voice.
No.
No, you're just dead inside.
That's right.
Oh man.
Yeah.
Well, that's not what I was going for either, but welcome to the Procrastinators Podcast.
Welcome to the show.
I don't think you're dead inside, Ben.
There was just a joke.
Oh hell yeah, I love it when it's just a joke.
Wait, I got, I put some real maple syrup on my oats today, so let's see how that goes.
Is it true that maple syrup is the same name as the alcoholic version?
They just call it maple syrup.
What's the alcoholic version?
I don't know.
Isn't there like an alcoholic maple syrup drink?
I don't know, probably.
I'm sure you can make some kind of alcohol out of it, definitely.
Maybe that was a Simpsons joke.
Maybe that was just, I'm just remembering something that's fake.
You can ferment anything if you put your mind to it.
Even bones?
Mm-hmm.
That'd be cool.
Bone beer.
I mean, the giant and Jack in the Beanstalk said he was going to grind your bones to make
his bread.
That wouldn't make for a good bread.
Or would it?
No.
I think you could probably do it a little bit.
It would probably be, you know, you can replace the flour in baked goods with a little bit
of like bug flour, but just a little bit.
I think it's just like kind of like filler material.
Like it's technically edible, but it's not like food.
Well, that bug protein, it is food.
It's probably better than ground bones.
It's just chalk.
This is pretty good.
Bug beer.
This beer is made from fermented centipedes.
That's the future, probably.
I have some bug protein, but I've never really eaten it.
It doesn't smell super great.
It smells kind of neutral.
And I think I've said this before, but there's no like recipes for it.
You can use it as a substitute in some things, but there's not like, it doesn't like, it's
not like for anything.
It's not like good in anything that I'm aware of.
Nobody's like, ah, there's a really spectacular bug based dish you got to make, bro.
It's all like, we put fricking mealworms on a pizza and if you don't look at them, then
the pizza tastes normal.
It is.
Hell yeah.
Interesting thing, like bugs, they're gross.
Are they inherently gross?
Could there be a situation where people grow up thinking bugs are not gross and then they
could eat bugs?
Yeah.
I think so.
I think you could get desensitized to it for sure.
It's always such a, what's the word, sensational sort of thing.
Like, ew, bugs on a food.
You've got to be pulling my leg.
One time I went to a restaurant and I ordered a lobster and I guess the waitress that was
serving us was new there and she was so grossed out by the lobster that she could not deliver
it to our table.
She had to have somebody else do it for her.
They are basically huge bugs.
They are.
But I like them.
To eat.
They're big enough.
If you could serve like a giant caterpillar as like a steak.
They're pretty gross.
Yeah.
It would be a little more palatable than tiny little lots of them.
I think, no, that would freak me out.
I think big fat worms and caterpillars are like the most disgusting thing ever.
The bigger and fatter, the worse they are.
Yeah, true.
I'm just trying to think of like why is lobster not so bad?
Like shrimp.
Even shrimp.
It is if you look at it.
No, I get it.
If you like look at the lobster, like with its like eyes, like its face, like ew.
Horrible.
But it's got such succulent meat.
Such tender flaky meat inside when you crack it open.
And crabs as well.
They got those beady little dots.
Yeah, but I've never eaten like a whole crab.
I don't think so either.
I think I've had a meal at a restaurant that had the crab shell off to the side and then
you could have the meat like a crab cake thing.
And I was like, oh God, that's what he was.
Oh, I've eaten crab legs though.
I've eaten crab legs like out of the leg.
So that counts.
Sorry if I'm like scraping into the microphone.
I'm scraping my, I have like a, my cup is too big and I got oats way down at the bottom of it.
And I got to extract them.
Terrible.
Delicious.
I did my first Fire Emblem stream yesterday.
I saw that.
I saw it.
I missed it for a while, but I caught the tail end of it.
Yeah, it was good.
It was Fire Emblem.
And I wasn't fire.
Was it fire, bro?
I would say it's fire.
Hell yeah.
You move your little guys around and they do a little funny animation when they attack someone
and there's a lot of strategy involved in deciding where to put people so that when the enemy moves,
you don't guarantee death on your part.
It's great.
I was, I was shocked to learn that the first Fire Emblem was called like Fire Emblem,
the Shadow Dragon and the Blade of Glory or whatever.
The Shadow Dragon and the Blade of Light, yeah.
Okay.
Why does it have, why didn't they just call it Fire Emblem if it's the first game?
The first Final Fantasy was just called Final Fantasy.
That's so weird.
I don't know.
All of them have a name.
I think none of them technically have a number in the title.
Like even the ones I call Fire Emblem 7, that's just called Fire Emblem because it was the first English one.
So they must have set out.
It had like a Japanese subtitle that wasn't translated.
And then it was Fire Emblem 8 was the Sacred Stones and that was just called the Sacred Stones.
Oh.
Hmm.
So the, so the first, okay well the first Fire Emblem didn't get ported to America or did it
or not to America, to the west.
Okay.
Yeah.
I know Japanese love their subtitles and it's why like Mega Man had all those like funny subtitles
to all their, that didn't get ported into English.
But I don't know.
The first Final Fantasy was just called Final Fantasy.
So it's like, it makes me think that they must have been like, this is going to be a series.
Like as they were making it.
And like, and this is, this chapter will call it Shadow Dragon Blade of Light.
And next chapter will be something else.
Uh, I guess so.
I mean, I don't know the, the story behind all these games.
I've learned that the second game Fire Emblem Gaiden is a like half remake of the first game,
but with like a chapter two, like you replay the story of the first game.
But then there's more.
It feels like.
There's more.
Like how much are they going to change it?
It's all still on the NES.
Hmm.
Um, but yeah, I don't know.
Are there many like, installments just intended to be one offs that have a subtitle?
Because Final Fantasy, I remember hearing that that was like, the guy who made it was like, ah, this is my last try at making a video game.
This is my final fantasy.
And it was successful.
That's what they say.
I'm trying to find my lighter.
I'm going to light a candle.
Because my laundry smells really bad right now, and I should really wash it.
Are you finding your lighter to light your laundry on fire?
I'm going to light a scented candle to absorb this.
Oh, I missed that part.
No, I'm going to light, I'm going to find my lighter so I can.
Burn it all away?
No, so I can light up this blunt so I can get so high that I don't notice it anymore.
You see.
Oh, I'm clever.
Okay, no.
What the fuck?
One second.
A few moments later.
Found it.
It was near my plug because it's one of those electric ones that you have to recharge.
So that's why it wasn't on the table where it was supposed to be.
I'm reading the thing about Fire Emblem.
I don't think I found an explanation for the title.
But apparently, it was conceived by designer writer Shou, Shouzu Kaga.
He wanted to combine the strategic elements of Intelligent Systems' previous simulation project, Famicom Wars,
with the story, characters, and world of a traditional RPG role-playing game influenced by Karey Software's First Queen.
So.
First Queen?
Oh, that's the name of the game.
Wow, it was also praised for featuring one of the first LGBT relationships in video games.
You're so-and-so's First Queen.
Yeah.
The game was not localized initially in America's result of homophobic backlash.
Wow.
Really?
The first Fire Emblem was?
Yeah.
I'm skimming this.
Who's gay in Fire Emblem?
How could they do this?
In the praised marriage scene with Roy, Prince of a neighboring kingdom.
Roy?
I thought he was from a different game.
Roy is homosexual all along?
Is Marth and Roy?
How could he do this to me?
Wait.
So, Marth is the one who says Roy's our boy.
Roy's my boy.
That's probably what it is.
Wait, actually?
I don't know.
I'll find out when I play the game, I guess.
That would mean that Smash Bros. has gay lovers in it as well.
Oh my goodness.
This changes everything.
It's probably not the same, Roy.
The Fire Emblem series is not, like, canonical to each other.
Why would they put more than one Roy?
I don't know.
Maybe it's just like a little nobody side character.
He's a Prince of a neighboring kingdom.
Maybe they just say, oh, he sucks dick for fun.
Fire Emblem is not canon to each other?
No, they're all, like, different universes.
They have similar, like...
Oh, okay, like Final Fantasy I see.
Yeah, so, like, they all have the same sorts of magic and swords and stuff,
but, like, the continent is always different.
The name of the world, the name of the kingdoms.
Yeah.
Nothing parses over except for when they do fan service,
dimension hopping stuff to bring Marth back,
or some sort of Marth legend.
Is it just for Marth?
It's usually just for Marth, like, in Fire Emblem Awakening.
I gotcha.
They remember, like, an ancient hero called Marth,
and I'm like, oh, okay, so this one is connected?
Maybe it's a different Marth.
Well, it could be.
I think it's supposed to be the same.
Maybe there's always, you know, in every different version,
there's always a Marth.
There's always a man, there's always a lighthouse, etc.
Okay, Fire Emblem.
What do you think? Good series, bad series?
Judge it.
Well, I'm going to play all the games,
and then I can say that for sure.
Okay.
But I enjoy the ones I've played.
So, yeah, it's a good series.
It's fun doing strategy on a little battleground.
It looked, yeah, I was, I mean, I tuned in for a minute,
and I saw you moving into little dudes around,
and you ever play Advance Wars?
Yes, it's very similar.
Is it very similar?
Okay.
Well, very similar, just in terms of it being a grid-based
strategy, move your guys around the board, sort of thing.
Move your guys around, and like, try and get them into
an advantageous position, or like, use the right guys
against the right other guys to maximize your damage
versus them and minimize your losses.
Right.
Yeah, except in Advance Wars, I think,
I've only played one of them, and it was on DS,
so I don't know how it usually is, but like...
I think the first one was on the GBA,
so you might have played the sequel?
Is there a sequel?
There's a few.
Maybe they had a remake.
There's a bunch of Advance Wars games, but...
Oh, okay.
Your character is the commander,
and you're controlling a bunch of faceless soldiers,
so units, so you don't mind them dying,
as long as you can replace them and win the battle eventually.
But in Fire Emblem, every single unit is a unique person
with a character, and you don't want them to die
because of that, so it sort of incentivizes
not losing anybody, because once they've died,
they are no longer available, and if you lose too many people,
later chapters might become impossibly difficult.
Indeed.
So I try not to lose anyone.
I did lose one person before you arrived.
No!
Because the first game seems a little more tough,
a little more like, you know...
A little more for hardcore gamers.
A little bit.
It's not that difficult yet, but there's a bunch of chapters to go, apparently.
It's okay, that's war.
That's war for you.
That's war for you, yeah.
Fire Emblem, come to twitch.tv
slash give and take every Saturday for some period of time during the day,
and I'll be streaming Fire Emblem,
and I'll put the first one up on Gibbon Gaming on YouTube.
If you did, catch it.
I should stream again this week.
I should definitely do that.
I did not stream for the last two or three weeks,
because I've been working on the book.
Oh my God, I'm done.
I'm done with the stupid book.
You're done?
I'm sending...
I haven't done it yet,
but I'm gonna send the files to...
I'm gonna send the files to the printer today
for a test copy to get printed.
And then I can just leave that alone while they print it,
and then...
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
I know, it's incredible.
This is the first time I feel like I've actually made a stride
towards having it done in a long, long time.
What a fucking...
That's fog.
I know.
It's fire.
You know what?
I'll send her the message right now, actually.
Oh my God, live progress.
Dear Mei Zeng at Guangzhou Hang Tong Packaging Products.
I'm probably pronouncing that wrong.
Oh, this might actually take a minute.
I don't actually want to do it.
I mean, I do, though, because...
Well, take a minute.
I'm gonna read the Fire Emblem Wiki
and see if I can figure out the name thing.
I see.
What time is it?
It's eight?
Oh, it's like midnight there.
Okay, never mind.
Right, right.
Okay, you know what?
Actually, I'm not gonna send it until, like, this afternoon,
because then it'll be, like, midday...
Tonight, it'll be, like, daytime Monday, on Monday,
when she gets it,
and that seems like the appropriate time
to send something like that.
So I won't send it right now.
But, yeah.
That's gonna be cool.
And then once it's off to the printer, I can...
I've been fucking around with a green screen in my room
trying to take, like, videos
and get the effect looking right,
and it's been a mixed success.
The effect I was going for, where, like, my teeth glow,
it actually works really well.
Like, the teeth actually show up really well
under the blacklight.
It's just, like, kind of gross-looking,
and it's, like, almost, like, more gross
than I wanted it to look.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
I can kind of pair gross on camera.
It's a little...
I mean, whatever.
It's fine.
I'll just...
If I use the right filters and make it look intentional,
it'll be...
Okay.
The effect mostly works.
I just have to make it, like, look...
I just have to compose a good shot
using it, I think, and then it'll be...
And then, you know, I can't actually film
the trailer until I have the book,
because the point is that I want to, like, have the book
and show the book off in the trailer, so...
Um...
Yeah, and then...
So that's done, so I can hopefully stream this week,
and...
Oh, I can start working on Biscopades.
Getting that...
Yes.
Getting that Perfect Comic Party content
rolling out.
Yeah.
Haven't touched that, but now it's time.
Before we move on to talking about that...
Oh.
Yeah.
Fire Emblem.
In early stages of the project,
it was called Battle Fantasy Fire Emblem,
and then in early advertising,
it was called Hono no Moncho,
Emblem of Fire.
So I...
It doesn't explain why they decided
to call it Shadow Dragon.
Did you know in Japan,
Blade of Fire was called...
Fire Emblem was called...
Emblem of Fire.
Wow.
Listen.
Yeah.
I love video games.
I love Japan, period.
Yes.
And gaming.
True.
All right.
Granted.
Okay, so no information I can see
about why it's got a title,
but don't you think it's odd that the first one came out
with such a specific subtitle
as though it were part of a series?
I mean, maybe if I read more closely,
I can find out.
But yeah, it is a little weird.
Maybe it was some sort of marketing thing,
like, oh, it's not fantastical enough.
Put a dragon on there.
Yeah, dragon and a blade of...
Yeah, it is a very dramatic title.
Maybe that's...
Maybe you just thought it was attention grabbing.
Yeah, so perfect comic party.
Yeah.
Clarissa Gunsmoke is coming along.
Last week, I basically got to the end of chapter four
for line art, and then this coming week,
I'm gonna be doing shading and speech bubbles
and action lines and any extra little tweaks I need to do.
And hopefully, I can get most of it done next week.
I've got a system where I'm counting
how many pages I do per hour
and also how many hours I manage to focus per week.
Mmm, that's good.
So I'm averaging, for line art at least,
0.48 pages per hour.
It's not too bad.
You can do a page in two hours?
It depends on the page.
Yeah, it depends on the page.
Obviously, it's just...
I want to keep gathering data for it
so that I have a more accurate average score.
Yeah.
My...
I used to...
It depended on the page.
I think I remembered...
back when I was drawing the champion,
I think it would generally take me
around eight hours or so to draw a page of that.
And, you know, sometimes it took 10 or 12 on a tough one
and sometimes it would take four or six on a simple one.
And Phantom's Revenge was much less than...
not Phantom's Revenge,
Slime and Punishment was generally much less than that by design.
Okay, question.
How much Clarissa do you want to put in, say,
an issue of the perfect comic party?
Well, I've vaguely already...
since I did the sketching
and blocking out a while ago,
that was all like,
okay, roughly 20 pages per chapter.
Some bit more, some bit less,
mostly a bit less.
So, yeah, 20 pages.
20...
Okay.
20?
I mean, how...
All right.
I mean, how often...
Was this going to be...
I thought we talked about making this like a weekly thing,
but like...
Or do we talk about it being a monthly thing?
I don't think we decided ultimately.
I think weekly is a little too much.
Weekly seems like a lot, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
A monthly little thing could be good,
because that would give me plenty of time
to do an entire chapter
and then work on, like,
gathering the rest of the stuff for the comic
and putting it together.
Yeah.
Okay.
I mean, do you think that, like,
would you want to keep doing, like,
20 pages of Clarissa a month?
If I can.
If you think that, yeah.
I mean, I have, like, how many chapters?
Four?
Five more chapters?
I'm not entirely sure.
I should double check again.
But, yeah.
I mean...
Okay.
Sometimes I might not have a chapter ready,
you know, just be...
We'll either have other stuff...
Yeah.
Or...
Or not have a...
Just to skip it.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
All right, sounds good.
Well, like I said,
I haven't even started working on
my Beescapades contribution.
You know, I have to...
I actually think I have to go back
and reread all of Beescapades,
because I know I had
a lot of ideas that were going on in that story,
and I remember, I think, most of the big ones,
but I think I had a bunch that I've probably forgotten,
and I should probably go back and read it
and remind myself, like,
oh, yeah, that was there.
Like, oh, yeah, no, he was going to do this.
Yeah.
There were a lot of little details.
In the town, I remember there was a bunch of shops,
and I remember what some of them were,
and I think there's one or two
that I didn't see the inside of,
and I got to refresh myself on what's there.
Yeah, it's one of those things
with, like, larger stories
that keep, like, getting bigger.
Beescapades.
Oh, no, no, go on.
There's, like, things in earlier parts of Clarissa,
and my notes that I want to, like,
sprinkle in to be a hint for future,
and there's also, like,
when I was doing A Lot of Ghosts,
there was a lot of, like, oh, I got to make sure, you know,
that it lines up with a canon story
because those characters are in there,
and RFCK and all that stuff.
Like, the fact that there's a slime sea,
but then I'm also going across the ocean,
so it's like there's the slime seas, the Grand Canyon,
so there's also desert after that.
I had to pay attention.
My brother was telling me that there was a thing he did
where when he was thinking of a cool story,
he would try and write a wiki for it.
I'm thinking about the geography now
of, like, setting sail into the Grand Canyon
and crossing the sea to wind up in England.
It's just, like, long.
Yeah, it's very silly.
Yeah.
But yeah, like, writing a wiki
and having articles is really quite helpful
for your own, like, remembering of stuff.
Oh, yeah, yeah, I see.
I see.
I might end up doing that.
Maybe it's just a personal, like, private wiki
or just a series of Google Docs that act like one.
Yeah.
Because it might have spoilers in it.
That's interesting.
Me and some friends a long time ago,
we did a creative, we tried to,
we started a creative exercise that was, like,
you start a wiki and then someone, like,
writes an article about a fantasy world
and then you add a couple hyperlinks to it
that don't link to anything,
but they're, like, very specific-sounding things.
And then you pass it off to the next person
and someone else picks one of those links
that don't link to anything,
and then they write the article about, like,
what was it?
You know what I mean?
Uh, yeah.
That sounds pretty good.
It was pretty, it was pretty cool.
We were sort of building,
for those short while we were doing it,
we were building a sort of, like,
it was a bit sort of final fantasy.
I would say it was sort of a Final Fantasy meets Mad Max.
It was, like, a desert apocalypse planet,
but there was sort of a, like, midgar city
that was, like, floating above, like,
the desolate, like, desert planet,
and there was a big, like,
Final Fantasy VII midgar-class disparity
of capitalist dystopia thing going on with that.
It was pretty neat.
I like the idea of, like, having an article
about, like, a, like, just some plant
that's an alien plant that only exists
in your, like, made-up world,
but there's, like, documents about it,
like, what it looks like.
I like the idea of filling out, like,
an encyclopedia like that,
but it's just a lot of work.
It's fun, though. I want to do that.
Um, I am planning to, and I should,
this is another thing that, you know,
it's not as high priority, maybe,
as, like, uh, Biscopades,
because that's, like,
I would consider that somewhat of an obligation
at this point that I got to do that,
but, uh, another thing that I want to do now
that the book is off to ship
and I don't have to think about it too hard for a while
is I want to prepare to run a little, like,
tabletop game.
Um, I found one called Paranoia
that I thought sounded kind of weird and interesting,
and I want to run, maybe not a one-shot,
but, like, maybe a short, like, a couple of sessions
game of that.
Uh, it was just something I haven't done in a long time,
was run a game of that sort.
Paranoia is, I almost think it's,
it sort of sounds like it's meant to be, like,
a parody almost of tabletop role-playing games,
but it's one of those parodies that, like,
internally takes itself seriously.
Like, it's not, like, it's not a comedy.
It's more like a commentary.
And you don't, you know what I mean?
Am I making sense here?
Uh, what's the paranoia?
Is it, like, you imagine there being monsters there?
No.
Uh, the plot of Paranoia is basically that it takes place
in a, like, cyberpunk,
uh, sort of, like, techno future
where, like, everyone lives under
a, like, surveillance state
that is run by this, like, sort of all-seeing,
like, techno AI
controller program.
And basically, in Paranoia, you all,
the characters all play as
you're all, like, debuggers,
or whatever, for this
AI, which basically means you're, like, cops,
but you're, like, cybercops,
but some of you might be, like,
communist spies or something,
so the game is about,
I guess you do missions for the AI,
but also a goal in the game
is to, like, um,
credibly accuse your fellow players
and try to out them to the computer
as, like, communist spies
and get them executed
and, like, doing this is good for you,
but you want to prevent them from doing it to you,
so you sort of try to kill each other,
but also you've all got, like, backup clones
that, like, if you die, you have some backup clones
that you can come back as,
so you have, like, you have, like, multiple lives,
uh, in at the same time.
Uh, there's, like, kind of a lot to it,
and I have only, sort of, briefly read through
the, um, the manual,
but I thought it sounded interesting,
so I'm gonna try and give that a shake pretty soon.
They, like, remade a bunch of newer additions for it.
I think it's from, like, the late 80s,
but I think they made a new addition
as recently as, like, the aughts.
So, like, that's weird.
Mmm.
And that's the thing that I'm gonna do,
hopefully.
Nice.
Yeah.
Heck.
Heck, yeah.
Dungeons or dragons.
Choose your poison.
Neither.
Neither one.
Computers.
Instead of, they should have just called the game
Computers and Computers,
instead of Dungeons and Dragons.
Numbers and...
and, uh...
Nimrods.
Did I already, did I already talk about the,
the word Nimrod?
Did we, did we discuss the word Nimrod?
Yes.
Okay.
Alright.
Something, something it used to be a word.
Bible.
The, yeah, Nim, yeah.
Bugs Bunny.
Defeated the Bible, but actually it was Daffy Duck.
Okay, okay, we've been over this.
Uh...
Yeah.
And it was, anyone who's a regular PCP listener
will already know the deep lore about Nimrod.
Yeah, yeah.
I had a...
Damn.
I must have had a dream where I had an idea for a video
I wanted to make.
A dream for an idea?
I don't...
Okay, as I said, I remember, I remember that when I talked
about Nimrod, I was like, what if I made a video
explaining that.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
But now I say, I was just thinking that thought,
and I was like, oh, yeah, yesterday I had another idea
like that, that was like, hey, I know it's not a lecture,
but maybe I should make that as a video.
Maybe that would be a good quick video to make.
But now I'm thinking about it, I can't think of the idea.
So either I forgot the idea, or I merely dreamed
that I had such an idea, and there was not actually
any idea like that.
Oh, it's like that daydream Homer Simpson has.
It's like, I gotta think of something incredible,
an invention that will change the world,
and he has a dream about it.
He's like, Homer Simpson, you've done it.
This is the greatest invention the world has ever seen,
and Homer's trying to see what's in the guy's hand,
and you just can't see it.
Oh, I don't remember that one.
Is that the one where he invents the electric hammer?
It could be.
There's like, oh, I can't remember the way he puts it.
He calls it the invention in question,
instead of saying what it is.
The invention in question.
I remember an episode where he invents something,
and I don't remember what it is,
but I remember he also invents an electric hammer.
Or he invents the chair protect
from falling backwards hinges thing.
Right, right, right.
The chair protect from falling backwards hinges thing.
That's probably what he would call it.
Oh, and he invents the makeup shotgun.
That one's bad.
Yes.
Okay, I have seen this episode,
but I don't remember that gag that you're describing.
Let me try and find it.
It's a good gag.
Because it's the exact same thing you have, you imagine.
I imagine that I had an idea,
but they're trying to see what it was.
Ben Shane, the video you made,
it was the best idea for a video that anyone's ever had.
Oh yeah, this is the one.
It's got 8 million views on its first week on the platform.
Congratulations, you've made a million dollars.
You're the genius who invented the product in question.
If only I could think of an invention,
something that would really make money,
must concentrate and work harder than I've ever worked.
This isn't a daydream, this is just a regular dream.
Congratulations, Mr. Simpson.
This invention of yours has made us all rich.
Yes, especially you.
It's simple yet ingenious, and it fits right in the palm of your hand.
Every person in America now owns one of these,
and in many cases, three or four.
Could I just get a look at that?
No, no, why would you need to see it?
You're the genius who invented the product in question.
But could I just...
Don't worry, you'll get to see it just as soon as we unveil our new ad campaign.
Let me see, let me see, out of the way.
Homer, wake up!
There's still a few minutes till our usual bedtime.
Stupid bitch wife, stupid bitch whore of a wife
getting in the way of my important work as a science man.
I really like the line at the end.
Homer, wake up!
It's still a few minutes till our regular bedtime.
It's not the morning.
Wait, I didn't even notice that.
I actually wanted to go to bed at the same time.
You can't, you have to stay awake for another little bit
before we go to bed.
It's still a few minutes.
I just wanted to make my hatred of women explicit so fast
and I wasn't even concentrating and I missed that joke.
But thanks for pointing it out for me.
It's exactly what you had.
You had your bitch wife knock you out of your sleep.
You had a video idea.
It was coming to you.
My bitch wife is reality.
My woman, she's a bitch whore.
You watch, have I talked about how good the latest Todd in the Shadows is?
Oh no, I have not seen.
Do you watch One Hit Wonderland?
Nope.
Have I, I feel like I brought everyone up.
You brought up Todd in the Shadows every day for the last 150 episodes.
I knew it.
I knew it and you keep letting me do it to make a fool of me.
Just like my bitch wife.
That's the line.
That's literally the line in Not In Your Woman by White Town.
But in My Woman, the song that the sample that everyone thinks is the Imperial March.
The line that what's his name?
Frickin' the guy who was the detective in Roger Rabbit.
The one that he lip-synced.
Todd plays the little clip and he goes,
My woman makes a fool of me.
Yes.
True.
It's connected.
It all connects.
Yes, true.
I don't know what he's talking about.
No, I definitely did bring that up.
I definitely did bring that up because I remember last episode I hummed the ba-ba-ba-ba
and you said Imperial March and I said,
No, you've fallen for the trap.
Yep.
Yes.
It's all coming back to me.
Someone should make, someone should like list every time on a PCP episode that Ben St. says,
Hey, let me talk about this thing.
Did I talk about this on a previous episode?
And then the rank, like how many times yes he did or yes I didn't.
And I'll bet the answer is mostly yes I did.
Yeah.
I feel like every week I'm like, I want to talk about something but I'm pretty sure I talked about it already.
And I don't remember.
It's just because you're getting old and decrepit and your brain is falling into small pieces.
You know what I feel like is getting old and decrepit about me personally?
It's a great subject.
Let's explore that.
You know what I think I'm losing my ability to do?
Is to chew a lot of food for an extended period of time.
No, that's horrible.
I find myself, I find myself more often when I'm, it's specifically when I'm eating like snacks,
when I'm like, when I've indulged myself in some crackers.
Listen, I bought some like some like rice crackers the other day,
which is not something I normally eat because I can't be trusted around salty snacks of that sort.
So I bought some like sea salt rice crackers and I was just eating the whole box of them.
And yeah, my jaw just got tired from all the chewing.
And I was like, I can't, I can't move my jaw sufficiently.
I have to put them down.
I don't think that's an old person thing.
I think that's just eating too much.
I just, I just, I feel like it's happening more often than it used to.
But maybe it's just my eating habits have changed.
Yeah.
Now you go ga ga ga ga ga ga ga ga all the time.
Well, I don't do that all the time, but just occasionally when I get my hands on something,
I do that and like I'm not, I don't have like the muscular endurance in that region of my body anymore.
I like, I'm like, can't keep up with it.
You're not, you're not getting any jaw gains.
That's the problem.
I'm not getting any jaw gains.
My, my lifts, my lifts stumbled.
My lifts stumbled yesterday.
I did not make much progress on my lifts.
And I feel like maybe I'm not sleeping enough or maybe I'm not eating enough because I've plateaued.
I plateaued a little bit on my squat.
I plateaued on my bench press, even on, even on my curls, even on curls for the girls.
Is that not normal?
It's normal.
Like for when you haven't exercised in a while, the first part is easy and then it plateaus gets a little harder.
Yeah.
I mean, sure, everyone hits plateaus eventually, but I've definitely lifted more.
I've squatted more and I've dead lifted more than I did the other day.
And so, you know, you hate, you hate to plateau.
Whenever, whenever you hit a plateau, it's like, well, how do I get past it?
And first thing I'm thinking, I'm going to try to sleep more and maybe eat a little more because I've,
I've not been eating.
I was eating a bunch.
I cut back by a few hundred calories the last like week or two and I felt like I was like getting myself under control.
I was like, I've been eating too much.
Let me rain it in a little bit.
I have rained it in a little bit, but maybe I rained it in too much.
You know?
Think about it.
There's like a...
Yeah.
What?
I was going to segue.
I was going to segue into talking about drawing.
Oh, wait.
I haven't drawn in a while.
And so, like, I'm also getting...
Like, it's easy to start building up again.
Like, the gains is like, oh, zero pages per day?
Well, now I'm doing like one or two or three.
And, but now it's getting harder to like increase that further.
Three pages a day is wild.
I mean, I am a very simple draw person.
And they're not like completed pages.
They're just a line art.
I've already done the sketch.
So it's not as much work as it sounds.
Okay.
I mean, sure.
I mean, that's still pretty good.
It is pretty good.
It's like a page where the two people are talking and their faces are close.
So I don't need to draw the entire body or the entire head.
Just sometimes just like, it's easy.
I love it when there's an excuse for like, I don't actually even have to actually draw that much on this page.
Yes.
Because it's still a page.
It still counts.
It's an important page.
Every page has a story and an amount of ink.
Haha.
Some of them have less.
I'm going to do, I'm going to be really fancy and I'm going to make the next page is just a full like one panel close up shot of the face talking and making a dramatic expression.
Haha.
Everyone's going to think I'm such a genius because this page is so dramatic, but it's actually it's really easy.
It's the easiest page to be drawn because just one panel is just one face.
It's so simple.
I do that way a lot.
I do that a lot.
I do a lot of those.
There's nothing wrong.
There's, especially in comics, there's nothing wrong with taking the easy way out.
You've got to do it as much as you can.
Oh, of course.
Because like making every panel beautiful and you realize that people read it like they don't notice these things.
As long as it looks okay.
Yeah.
And when there's an important action scene or an important moment, you spend a little extra time to make it look nice.
They'll remember the nice looking panels and they'll forget like being between ones that just move from A to B.
Yeah.
There's so many, there's so many shite panels in slime and punishment.
So many shite panels.
But there's a couple that are nice too and that's the important thing.
Yeah.
So, Clarissa's coming along.
I am happy with it.
I am happy with how it's going.
How much more do you have to do?
For this chapter, there's like the last page line art and then shading.
So, shading, I don't know.
I don't know whether to like.
Do you have to go back and shade all the panels that you did line art for already?
Yeah.
So like 20 pages of shading.
So it's not going to take zero seconds, but less time than line art probably the most of them.
Sometimes shading is really just a bit of shadow under the hair or wherever it needs to be.
And then that's it.
It's all done.
I don't know whether to like switch.
Because before, I didn't really know how to do like dots.
What are they called?
Little dots.
Oh.
Half tone.
Screen tones.
I didn't know how to do that for the early Clarissa chapters because I was stupid and I didn't know how to Google it.
So I just did like a layer of like low opacity or gray like ink and I would just put the ink on where shadows should be.
But now I know how to do the screen tones.
Should I switch?
Should I change the style of it or just keep going?
From like flat shadows to screen tones?
Flat gray to screen tone, yeah.
Obviously screen tones are not easier to use.
You have to really think about the size of the dots and how it will look on a page when it's printed or like the size of which people will see it on a screen changes the way it looks.
Screen tones exist because they made shading possible in a printing environment that could only use flat blacks.
And that's not so they're really necessary.
They're really just a stylistic choice for you.
So use them if you want.
Just use them when they look good.
I suppose so.
It's a little, because it's weird to have just some of it being screen tones.
No, it's not.
This is weird though, because just from examples I've seen, people either use them or they don't.
Whenever an artist does something they don't usually do, people say, ah, they're trying new stuff.
They're growing as an artist.
How heartwarming.
They wouldn't say that.
What would you think?
I don't know.
I guess I wouldn't care.
If an artist, if suddenly they use screen tones and they never used screen tones before, you'd be like, huh, they used a screen tone.
Yeah, I guess it's not a real...
I just don't want it to look worse, because screen tones are easier to fuck up because there's...
You can make it look okay from whatever zoom level you're looking at when you're drawing it, but then you zoom out to a normal scale or zoom in.
The zoom can fuck up.
The digital screen tones, the zoom can fuck up, that's true.
Yeah, so I'm like, what do I do about that?
I have designed Clarissa and Lord of Ghost to be printable and work well for a printed medium, just in case I felt like doing that.
I guess I'd have to think really hard about the size of stuff, but that's hard.
That's a whole lot of stuff to think, because I don't know exactly the size of the paper that I'm going to use if I do print it.
It could do the same as Lord of Ghost, it could be a little smaller, not sure.
So this printer, if I...
Because I told you that I really wanted to get these guys to print it, even though they ghosted me, because their prices were way better than anyone else I could find.
They gave me a quote, and the prices they quoted me for printing for slime and punishment are like...
The cost falls off so much, even from the difference between 100 copies to 300 copies.
The price for 100 books is about $13 to $14, plus like $2 or $3 in shipping for each book, so that comes to around $15 to $16.
If I print 300 books, the price is like $5 to $6 plus $2 for shipping each book.
That's really cheap.
Yeah, you print 300 pieces for literally only like...
You print three times as many books for literally only like 50% more costs, right?
So the price falls off really fast.
How many pages does your thing have?
And their color as well.
Yeah, the full color pages is...
It would be so much, it would be even cheaper if it were...
Sorry, I think it came to 264 pages, including like all the stuff.
Oh my god.
I know, it's pretty big.
I should use whatever you're using next time.
I'll order these print copies and I'll see if they are shite, and if they...
Why do I keep saying it like that?
Have you been watching some British YouTubers?
No, never.
I would never do that.
Yeah, if they're good.
Yeah, I will refer you to these guys because they have...
I looked at a bunch of printers, I asked many different printers, and nobody had prices like these people.
So there's a non-zero chance that I'll get the test copies and they will suck.
And I'll say, oh, that explains it.
But we'll see.
I guess.
Yeah, I don't know.
Like, what's the likelihood?
It's from China, right?
Yeah.
They're probably...
Guangzhou Haotong.
And I'm sure I'm saying that wrong.
They have access to cheaper labor?
I don't really know what's going on with China.
But even compared to other Chinese companies, this company was significantly cheaper than anyone else that I've talked to.
I was only asking Chinese printing companies on Alibaba.
That's where I was looking.
I have no idea.
That sounds like it's either a monopoly holder or they're going to go out of business soon.
I mean, I was talking to them six months ago and they are still...
They're still going.
Or third option, the product sex.
I wonder if they are like a monopoly holder.
I mean, I have no way of knowing if one of these companies is much...
Maybe I could actually look around and find out about that.
Yeah, I don't know if this is an especially big company or a small one.
That's pretty cool though, because if you get it really cheap, you won't have to charge so much for it.
I know.
And people are more able to say, oh, hell yeah, I'll buy that.
I mean, this is...
If I could charge 20 bucks for it, that sounds...
That would probably be like really...
Because I mean, okay, the shipping is going to be...
I'm concerned about the shipping.
I would like...
If I could send it with media mail.
Media mail would save me so much money on shipping, but you can only use media mail in America.
And these packages are going to be big, especially if I add bonus stuff,
like freaking little slime bottles and crystals and stuff and podrans, you know?
Technically, that stuff would disqualify it for media mail.
I think I could probably still get away with using media mail because it's a book.
Because what are they going to check every package and see that there's a crystal in there?
But only in America, I feel like shipping alone is going to be like $15, $20, maybe more,
for international shipping on a lot of these.
So I'm probably going to have to incorporate that into the price as well.
I don't see the price being under $30.
But honestly, for a 200-page full-color book, I feel like $30 is a very, very reasonable price for something like that.
And I'll feel good if I can charge that much and that will account for how freaking expensive international shipping is going to be on all of this junk.
What's the dimensions of the book?
I went with 8.5x11 landscape.
8.5x11? That's pretty big.
Regular printer paper size. Yeah, it's pretty big.
Yeah, it's pretty big.
Yeah, but I guess it's pretty big.
Oh, I'm really excited.
I asked her for a second quote.
She quoted me the price and then I asked her, hey, what if I change the paper type?
And then a few days went by and I didn't get an answer and I was like, oh no, I pushed you hard.
I asked too many questions, she's ghosting me again.
But no, she did get back to me two days ago.
So now I'm like, all right, it's fine.
I know everything I need to know.
Let's do it. Let's freaking do this.
I hope she won't mind if I ask her to print.
Because I want to test print two copies with two slightly different color schemes to compare which filter looks better.
And also on two different paper weights to just see is the heavier paper worth the extra price or is it just as good on the lighter paper and it's cheaper too.
If it like that many pages, paper weight might change the weight enough for weight class in transferring a large package.
Well, I'll tell you, it'll cost more for me to ship if it's heavier too.
For them, they said that like with the lighter paper, the lighter paper would make for 100 pieces, the printing cost would be 12.
It increases the, it actually doesn't increase the shipping cost by much at all.
It increases the cost of printing them from like $12 a copy at 100 pieces to like 14.
So, you know, it's an increase, but honestly, it doesn't make.
Yeah, if I'm printing 300 pieces, the price changes from like $5 a copy to like $6 a copy.
Oh, those margins.
Oh, God, those margins.
If I sell 300 copies and I can get each one for like $6 a piece, that'd be incredible.
I'm salivating.
I'm salivating at the potential margins.
Gabe, I love money.
I love money so much.
I, yeah, it's pretty good.
When I, it's like, I don't know, when I execute a plan, when I execute a plan and the plan turns a profit, it's like, how did I do that?
It's insane.
You ever, you ever, you ever study thermodynamics in uni?
You ever take a class on thermo?
You ever know about the, you know about the Carno cycle?
Is that when you get a, it's like a bicycle?
The Carno cycle, it's when, it's how like the fricking, oh God, I'm going to butcher this explanation.
It's how like a fricking combustion engine works.
It's when you, you take like a thermodynamic environment, like a sealed chamber of gas, right?
And you do a little, oh, how does it fucking work?
It's like you, you compress while keeping the temperature that you compress, you compress it while keeping the pressure the same.
You reduce the volume, but you keep the temperature the same, and then you expand while you keep the pressure the same, and then you reduce while you keep the volume the same, and then you heat up while you keep the temperature the same.
Whatever.
Oh, I see, I see.
Yes, yes, whatever.
It's a series of mechanical changes to the thermodynamic environment that you do.
And in doing so, you create excess energy, and then the engine siphons off that extra energy you create through this thermodynamic process, and that's the source of the energy from like a combustion engine.
And it's like, you know, I don't know, when I make something, and then the last couple of kick starters I've done, I like, hey, I did all this stuff, I did all this setup, and then I did a kick starter, and then I made a bunch of money on it.
And it's like, oh, oh, I did the, I did a successful cycle, I did a big loop around the car now cycle, and I got to the end, and then I squeezed it out, and a bunch of money squirted out.
Yeah.
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
Don't pretend you don't know exactly what I'm talking about.
Do you mean like, like, and then you take that money, and then you make a new project, and then you do a kick stuff for that project, and it's like the cycle keeps going?
Oh.
Are you getting it?
Or are you just saying, I like when I do, it's like I'm driving a car and getting money out of it.
No, it spins my wheels.
It's just the satisfaction of seeing a plan come together.
It's like, I love it when a plan comes together, you know?
Like I did, I set up, I did all this work, and I made this thing, and then, oh, hey, I sold it, and people bought it, and it all worked out.
I hope that happens, I hope that happens with slime punishment.
If at least, if as many people buy slime and punishment as bought Vapors 2, I will be stoked as heck about that.
That would be like, that's all I could ask for.
I am definitely buying one.
Oh, thank you.
It's gonna be really nice.
Okay, the book's gonna, it's gonna look really nice as a book.
I really think it's gonna look like, as long as this printer doesn't suck, and if this printer sucks, then I'll use a different printer.
And one that makes it look, it's gonna look really good.
I'm excited.
I'm still a little fucked up about the Lord of Ghost Kickstarter.
Oh, the plush.
Uh, no, no, the pumped plush was the one that failed, the Lord of Ghost succeeded.
Oh, you're fucked up because, why are you fucked up about it?
Because it was expensive?
It was expensive and stressful, and I don't like doing mailing to countries all over the world.
Yeah, you know what, I can look back and laugh now, but yeah, I do remember that after the Vapors 2 Kickstarter, there was like,
what was it, like 10 months wherein I had to actually, I had to write the Vaporette scripts and get the Vaporette, and get the comics drawn,
and then I was doing the doodles on the inside covers.
It actually was like really hard, and took a really long time, I forgot about that.
That was like two or three years ago now.
Yeah, I want to maybe do a similar thing for Clarissa when that's like a thing, or maybe just, it's a lot of pages, the entire thing, so maybe I should make chapters that you could buy.
There's also like Amazon as like the potential to like have it be on Amazon for you to print, like Amazon will print and send a copy to you.
Yeah, yeah, print print on demand.
I will probably go that route in the future.
Yeah, yeah.
It's nice to have a real thing, but it's also like, God, I'm not a distribution company, I can't handle all that.
Well, I might do, okay, I think first line of punishment, I'm not going to do, one of the things that was really hard was the like drawings of the inside cover.
Just because I went like really hard on like the detail in those.
Slime and punishment, it's going to have, the pages are going to be black.
So I might do like a, I might offer like a doodle, like a signature and a doodle, but it would genuinely have to be like a doodle doodle.
Like a, because I would do it in like a, in like an opaque gel pen, like a white gel pen or something, or I'd probably use a green one, because slime, ha ha.
So I might do that.
It wouldn't do like full page like illustrations like I did in some of those.
Yeah.
Because that was like, you know, I kind of charge people like a lot because they put so much effort into those.
And on this, it's like, I just don't think I want to have such a production on that, like on the post, on the post print side of things.
So that, and then I won't have any, the, the vaporettes was like one of the hardest parts about that.
And for slime and punishment, there won't be any of that.
All the, all the work of actually what's going to go into the actual book is all done and taken care of.
So like, thank God, I won't have to worry about anything like that this time, because that was such a process.
And then what else, what else?
Shipping will still be a nightmare, but it's okay.
Only one nightmare is acceptable.
An accept, unacceptable amount of nightmares.
I'm just going to try and keep, keep on with my, my drawing schedule.
Yeah.
Five days a week, five hours a day.
Hopefully.
Yeah.
And once the chorus is done, I'll be like, what do I do now?
But that's future Gibbs problem.
That's, that's the way that, that's, that's the, the right attitude.
Perfect.
Comic party is going to be so fucking funny when it's real.
I think that'll be.
People are going to laugh so hard.
They're just going to piss themselves.
It's going to be really funny.
Do you think the first one should just be Clarissa and Beescapades?
Yeah.
And then maybe in, in it, we put a little ad for like submit your comic if you want to be in the next one.
Okay.
Sounds good to me.
The only other thing I have on my notes is I've been watching the owl house.
Do you know that show?
I've never watched it.
I mean, I've definitely heard of it.
And I've seen, I've seen what I know what it looks like.
Yeah.
So a teenage girl goes to a magical world where she's the only human.
Everyone else is not a human.
And that's, that's her gimmick.
It's just like Mario.
He tries to learn magic.
Yeah.
Mario.
It took a few episodes.
I try to watch it a while ago and I go like three episodes in and I'm like, nah, some of these characters are annoying.
Some of these characters are annoying and they're not funny and the jokes aren't landing and I don't like it.
And the main character is very Steven Universe-esque in that she's really enthusiastic and happy.
And that really pissed me off.
That really made me spit that one.
I didn't mind that.
That was fine.
But I went back to it just because I needed a show.
I'd finished Medical Soul.
I was like, well, what else is there?
What else is there in this world?
I remember that.
That's a good question.
I gave it a chance.
And yeah, I think episode five was cool.
They had a cool fight scene and I started noticing that the animation generally is just very good.
And the timing of the jokes is good as well.
And I'm like, you know what?
It's not so bad.
It's not the best show ever.
But I'm invested now.
I want to see what happens.
Oh, no.
That's a good little comic.
Good little cartoon.
Good little comic.
No, it's got its hooks into you.
It's going to poison your mind with its content.
I'd rather be poisoned by a nicely animated little cartoon show than by YouTubers.
No.
I love YouTubers.
I love YouTube.
They're all going to die one day.
No, every YouTuber you know and love will be dead one day.
And then won't you feel silly that you cared, idiot?
How could you spend your precious time on this earth?
How could you waste it listening to the words of fallible mortals who will one day perish?
I don't know.
I guess it's just part of my human nature.
Oh, cringe.
Speaking of which, I found a YouTuber that I really like recently.
His name is Grimbeard, and he is funny, and he talks about video games.
You've mentioned them.
Have I?
They're the person you said looked like Jesse.
No, that's Burger Creek.
Oh.
Who's Grimbeard?
I don't know.
It's a different dude.
It's some other guy.
It's an unrelated person.
I feel like you've said Grimbeard before.
Maybe I have.
I've been watching his stuff for a while now.
I just really like him.
I just really like his stuff.
All right.
And that's it.
That's all I have to say.
He does video game reviews, mostly of PlayStation 2 era PC shooters and stuff, horror games,
kind of mostly semi obscure stuff, but not entirely.
American McGee's Alice, Vampire, The Masquerade, Redemption, stuff you might have heard of.
Yeah, you might have heard of it.
You might have heard of it.
That's pretty cool.
Yeah, he's good.
I'm not really interested these days in review content or video essays.
I'm not really interested in the games so much.
Sometimes they're kind of interesting and I've never seen them before and I go, huh, didn't know that was a game.
When it comes to stuff happening on YouTube, it's like, oh, check this out.
I usually click on challenge runs of Mario or whatever.
You know?
Just because those are...
I don't know.
It's something about challenge runs that I'm just really into right now.
Do you like the ones with the guy narrates how they did it or whatever?
Yeah, the guy narrate the...
What's his name?
What's their name?
What's her name?
Who?
Gate Video VG Champ 3000.
Oh, yes.
I know her.
There was another one who did Kirby challenge runs.
That other guy did every Kirby game and those ones were pretty good.
Yeah, VG Champ 3000 or something.
Yeah, I've seen some of that stuff.
Yeah, she's great.
There's a Fire Emblem stuff that I've been looking at.
Fire Emblem challenge runs trying to do really excessively difficult things.
Using one character and not attacking or...
I don't know.
I just had a glance in around looking at these things.
Oh, I like that.
That's the content I like now.
A review of like, here's why this game is good.
I'm like, yeah, I'll buy it.
You don't need to explain it.
I'll just say I'll agree.
You don't need to sell me on that.
I love video games.
Here's how this video game changed the world.
I was like, nah, yeah, I'm sure it did.
Is there a challenge run of you doing something about it?
Is there fun going on?
You having fun with it?
You're winning some?
Well, if it's such a good game, why don't you do a challenge run about it?
Why do you just review it when you can be doing a challenge run?
Why are you talking about this stuff when you could be playing it and I could be watching?
Fuck you telling me about what kind of a game Vampire of the Masquerade Redemption is.
Now, let's see you do it with a zero blood run.
Let's see you do it without committing any crimes.
Oh, you won't?
Too hard?
Impossible?
Well, I guess you weren't that serious about it.
Did you ever watch SEVE gaming?
SEVE?
SEVE, C-E-A-V-E.
That does not ring a bell.
They did Mario challenge runs where they tried not to touch coins or try to complete new Super Mario Brothers
without like while crouching the whole time or like not pressing left or not pressing right
or not pressing the jump button.
All those sorts of things.
I've seen things like that.
I don't know if I saw that channel.
SEVE gaming is great.
They stopped making videos, but they got a lot of them and they're fun.
They have a funny voice because they're German.
I mentioned that Burger Creek is German,
but he sounds British until you...
Oh, everyone sounds British to you, Yanks.
No, I swear he must have learned English from like a British.
He must have like spent time in the UK or something because he definitely speaks it that way.
The...
Everybody in Europe who speaks English sounds British.
They learned English by watching Doctor Who.
That's probably it.
That's probably true.
Oh, shit.
Well, I was going to say something else, but I'm sure it didn't matter.
You know, we'll all die one day anyway.
So whether I remember it or not is probably irrelevant.
Yeah, that's the spirit.
That's the spirit.
I just want to shout out Grimbeard because I like him.
That's it.
Yeah.
That's just what I've been doing.
That's just what I've been doing this week.
I just been...
Okay, what I spent like literally most of this week doing was taking my page files for
the comic and putting them through Photoshop and applying a color filter to them and then
resaving the page in a new folder with like the filter on.
Is that for printing ink stuff?
I just was adjusting the greens because you know very well that the greens just don't
look the same when they come out on CMYK printing.
So I was basically just lightening them so that they would be roughly the same brightness
on the page, hopefully.
I'm glad the way the Red Man comics came out looked all right.
Yeah, because I was so confused by all of that stuff.
I really couldn't get a good grasp of what I was doing to the green.
It looks different, but like it's fine.
It looks fine.
Yeah, you can't really get a neon green like you can on a screen.
No, you really can't.
You have to either...
If you want a rich green, it has to be dark.
And if you want a bright green, it has to be pale basically.
Or you can sort of nudge it into like a yellowish.
And then you can get it a little brighter.
That was the trade-off that I had.
I did a couple different versions.
One of it is yellower, but brighter.
And the other one is paler, but greener.
And so the two versions that I want to print on the two different paper weights,
I'm going to try and give her the two different filters.
And then I'll compare them and see which one I like better on the page.
That's the plan for these test copies.
But it really took so long because it's 260 pages.
And the PNGs are pretty big, so it takes like a minute to save each one.
And then I had to...
So that's, you know, several hours, even if I'm not doing anything else
and I'm just focused on that and I'm doing it as fast as I possibly can.
And I had to do it twice because I wanted the two different filters.
And I tried.
I spent a whole day just trying to figure out how to get Photoshop
to load all the files into...
There's a script called load files into stack.
To load all the files into one Photoshop document as layers,
and then apply the filter to all the layers individually,
and then export each individual layer as its own PNG.
And there are functions that do that.
But every time I tried to do it,
my frickin' Photoshop would tell me that it couldn't do it
because it was running out of quote-unquote scratch memory.
Oh, yeah, that's like random access.
That's like an area of memory that is dedicated to like holding all of this stuff.
Yeah.
Which need a cleaner hard drive, I guess.
I don't know.
Oh, wait, no.
There's a way in Photoshop, in preferences.
Yes, I know there's a slider.
I know there's a slider.
Yeah.
Did it not work?
I looked in...
I found the slider.
I maxed out the slider.
I switched to another hard drive for my scratch disk
that had like 800 gigs free,
and it still didn't work.
So I...
Big file.
Only a couple gigs.
Well, I mean...
Less than 10 gigs.
I mean...
Don't know how the scratch disk stuff works.
Yeah.
I spent a whole day trying to get it to work.
I couldn't get it to work.
In the end, I was like,
I'll actually just have to do it
file by file one at a time.
It's the only way.
And so that's what I did.
And it sucked.
But I did.
It does suck.
Yeah.
I've...
A lot of times there's been like,
oh, you can do this really complicated thing
that will save you so much time,
but then I try to learn about it,
and it takes so long.
It's just frustrating.
You know what?
I'd rather toil.
I'd rather toil than learn right now.
You know, I found out how to do it.
I know how to do it.
It's just my machine is incapable
of doing it.
Yeah.
So...
My machine is my brain,
and it was also incapable.
True.
That's fucking...
That's show business.
That's blow...
That's bro business.
True.
Did you know?
Did you know that Riku
from Kingdom Hearts?
Yeah.
You know Riku?
I think because of a video I watched
that he's gay for Sora.
I think he's gay now.
Now?
It's quite compelling.
He wasn't gay before,
but he's gay now?
Well, he was gay before,
but now I believe it.
But now...
Okay.
Yes, I understand.
There was this long video essay,
six hours long,
it's called Riku is Gay
and Why It Matters.
Wait.
That's actually really funny.
I want to watch it.
It's a really funny idea.
For a video,
you laugh when you hear it,
and then they go six hours long.
Here's all of the reasons
why this makes sense
and also why it's actually important.
I'm surprised.
Because a lot of it
is about why Riku's love for Sora
and Sora's love for Riku
is why Kairi is not as important
into the main story a lot of the time.
That sounds...
It's really cool, actually.
I love it.
I'm surprised there's six hours
worth of information to go over.
There are a lot of games,
but yeah, it was surprising.
I guess there are a lot of games.
Yeah, that's true.
You know what?
Link me that video.
I'll watch that fucking video.
I'll fucking watch it.
Riku is gay.
Ha, first thing.
Oh, I don't like the drawing
on the thumbnail.
It's bad.
The person drawing is...
They draw throughout the video
in the background before they're talking.
No.
Don't worry, Ben.
The content is solid,
and it's very good.
It's okay.
I'm not actually going to watch the video.
It's just going to be background noise.
Okay.
All right.
Fair enough.
They do have a furry OC,
like Torco C.
Tenelle flowers?
Oh, God.
This person's trans, aren't they?
Yes, I think so.
No!
Not another one.
They can't keep getting away with it.
I don't know what I'm mad about.
Hey, you hear about Jake?
I think they're non-binary or something.
Anyway, yeah.
Wait, I haven't...
If I click play,
will I see what they look like?
You can scrub.
Oh, do they have a furry OC?
They have a furry OC talking.
It's all the things that you'd be like,
ugh, but it's good, though.
It's a good video.
It's okay.
It's just going to be background noise.
I mean, honestly, I like the design of their OC,
but that's besides the point.
It's not like ridiculous.
It's just a little furry person.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's all right.
They have...
There's something about the way they draw
the human characters.
It's very...
It's not anime.
It's very like...
I don't know if I want to say tumblr core.
It's maybe a little bit tumblr...
It's tumblr core in a way
that is grasping at an aesthetic
that is like 101 Dalmatians
character design-ish.
Is it Don Bluthish?
It's Don Bluthish.
It's tumblr does Don Bluthish
is how I would describe it.
It's not an aesthetic that I particularly like
and I don't think they're doing it particularly well.
So we've got a real melange of things going on there.
It's just like a bit of whatever
to fill the background of the video
when there's not a relevant clip to be shown.
I'm actually interested.
I feel like this could be really interesting analysis.
It is.
Yeah, okay.
I'll give that a little cool listen.
I encourage viewers to watch.
Anybody listening, go give that a watch
because it's just good.
It makes a lot of weird little eccentricities
of the plot make a lot of sense.
Interesting.
I got so into Kingdom Hearts after watching this
I was like, I gotta know more about Kingdom Hearts.
Now I'm listening to other videos
and then I went back and watched
Nate's Kingdom Hearts 3 video
just to see what he had to say on the subject.
I just wanted more Kingdom Hearts content.
I'm a fan now.
I wasn't a fan before.
I was just sort of like a vaguely enjoyed
the first two games sort of person,
but now I like it.
There's a pretty long video
that I watched a while ago called,
I think it's called Kingdom Hearts 3
was a waste of time.
Have you seen that one?
I don't think I watched all of it,
but yeah, I think I saw that.
What's his name?
It's like your favorite uncle, I think,
or like something uncle.
Ah, what's this frickin...
Well, now I gotta find it.
KH3 waste of time.
Oh, I accidentally typed HH3 waste of time
and I got a bunch of the H3H3 podcast.
LOL.
Kingdom Hearts 3 was a waste of effort
by Ask Your Uncle.
That's the one.
It's five hours long.
It's just very funny
that the video is called Riku Is Gay
and this is a six hour long YouTube video.
That's peak.
That's peak YouTube in 2023, I would say.
It is. It's so good.
Yeah.
And I'm genuinely happy
and going to watch it and engage with it
because I am a human being in 2023
and this is my life.
Hell yeah.
What else?
What else, Gib?
Well, what did I do?
I did drawing of Clarissa.
I was doing for Blueberry Still.
Oh, right, right.
Those are pretty good.
You still got most of the month left.
Yeah.
I'm not taking it so seriously.
I had a break on Friday in Saturday
because I was like, you know what?
It doesn't matter.
I just, I don't want to draw today
so I didn't need to.
That's healthy, everybody.
This is not especially hot gauze.
I don't know if I would even call it gauze,
but we found out what Trixie is up to.
She's got a job now.
Did you know that?
I did not know that.
She's got a job.
She's got like a real job.
Wow.
Yeah, she said that she is driving around
and taking pictures of buildings.
And there's maybe a vacuum cleaner involved.
She said on Subsect that she needed a vacuum cleaner.
And I don't know, me and some people in the Discord
were trying to figure out what this means.
And it seems...
Ghost hunting.
She's going around Luigi's mansioning,
playing Luigi's Mansion, IRL.
I think it sounds like she maybe works
for a real estate company
and is going around to their properties
and photographing the premises
for listings on Zillow or something.
And maybe she has to clean the house before vacuum the rooms
and make it look nice before photographing it
or something like that.
Oh, yeah, that makes sense.
Yeah, I was just like...
It's kind of funny.
It's kind of a funny...
I don't know, imagine that, I guess.
All right, good for her.
It's actually making money somehow.
Maybe.
I mean, I don't know.
I have no idea.
I just...
It's got to be so expensive driving around to do that.
Yeah, probably.
It must cost so much gas.
I mean, I don't know.
A lot of jobs are probably just bad like that.
They don't care about how much gas you spend to do the job.
They're just like, yeah, fucking do it, though.
And we'll pay you pennies.
I mean, either they're comping her for the gas,
which would cost them a lot of money,
and I would think like, damn,
you can't just hire someone local.
You've got to hire someone to drive from like Kentucky to California
to fucking take some pictures of your house.
Well, all over the country.
Yeah.
Oh, I thought it was like, yeah, like local buildings.
But if it's a...
That's weird.
No, she said they drove to like New York and...
Yeah, they did like full on like cross country.
Yeah, and it just, it seems to me,
if I were a realtor, I would think I would want to save money
by hiring someone local.
Comp them for gas to do such a thing,
either that or they're not comping for gas
and she's just blowing tons of money on the gas
and has not considered the fact that that is like a significant cost to the...
So someone's losing money on this chain,
but whatever, it might just work like that.
I don't know.
If you suck up all the ghosts, you get a lot of coins.
Yeah, she's going ghost hunting.
That's pretty good.
I never played Luigi's Mansion.
Neither did I, but it's always looks cool.
But a donkey just put out a video about why the GameCube is failing
and he said that Luigi's Mansion is the spookiest game ever made.
There's literally 300 ghouls on screen right now.
It's more ghouls than any other game.
More spooks.
That's a lot.
That's a lot of ghouls.
I know, I know, but it's true.
Yeah, I don't even have notes this week.
So whatever.
I'm getting close to 40,000 coal in my RuneScape Bank, everybody.
You're gonna find 40,000.
Almost level 90 mining.
You're gonna find 40,000 coal in your Christmas stocking.
That's a lot of coal.
Good morning.
You know, that would be really good.
That would have been really good at Christmas,
because fuck, everything's expensive and heating your house, especially.
Free coal, hell yeah.
Hell yeah.
Damn, this is gonna be saving me so much on heating, bro.
Yeah!
Based, based, based.
Well, you want to go to voicemails?
Yeah, sure.
Alright, let's do it.
A brisk hour and a half.
Oh shit, hang on.
What's up?
I didn't check if there's like a one piece.
Oh fuck!
Let's have a look.
I forgot.
What was the chapter we were on last?
Oh, freaking no.
Hero's Offensive, I remember that one.
Wakuma climbing up the Red Knight as Weight of Memory.
Miss Buckingham Stussy, Mark III.
This is new.
No, I don't want to.
Okay, 1075 is coming soon.
I have 1074, which is the new, we haven't seen this one, I think.
Oh, okay.
I guess I gotta read it.
Okay, cue the whatever.
Play me off, Johnny.
The one piece!
The one piece is real!
Damn, these one piece scientists sure do love to turn an old robot into a new robot and call it a whole new robot.
Wow, what do you mean?
Well, they're calling him the Mark III.
But I mean, he's the same guy.
Well, it's a different...
They just upgraded him.
Oh yeah, that's what Mark III means.
Yeah, I guess.
He's got bubble pounds, I don't even know what that could be.
It's a strongest shield.
The strongest shield that Vegapunk invented.
I'm gonna go through it all the way before I start thinking with my brain.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, that's a...
There's a lot of them.
Oh my god, there's too many things going on.
Every chapter.
Yeah, yeah.
It's big news!
Oh shit, sorry if it was a spoiler.
No, I'm already there.
Okay.
Oh my god.
I thought better of Big News Morgan.
I really did.
He's such a trickster.
What a scoundrel.
Alright, so first impressions review of chapter 1074, Mark III.
Um, it was bad.
Okay, anyway, let's move on to voicemails.
No!
Yeah, chapter sucks.
One piece is bad now.
Let's see, what did we learn?
Okay, they got a million Pasifistas on Vegapunk Island.
They've got, yeah, they've got the new Mark III Pasifista.
No.
It's far more, the guy says this must be a Mark III, so I guess he's like, he knows
about their existence, but he hasn't seen one before.
Yeah.
So maybe this is like, this is the new guys.
These guys are not as good as the Seraphim though, right?
Yeah, I suppose so.
The Seraphim are like state of the art, a new type of human, new type of creation.
Do these guys have paw paw fruit powers, or are they just big, uh, uh, fricking, are
they just big kumas with bubble shields?
I think they're, that might be a type of paw paw fruit ability.
I can't remember if he ever makes a shield.
No, he never did that.
It does look like something the paw paw fruit could do.
He's never done that specifically with it before, I don't think.
It looks pretty cool though.
He's super cool.
It's so fucking big.
Reminds me of the, it's just so funny that like, I don't know, just the way that like,
look how fricking ridiculous he is.
This is torso, some mountain and tiny little legs, but he's awesome.
He's tiny little head, tiny little legs.
Yeah.
Don't know how he does it.
Don't know how it works.
Yeah.
It's such a, it's like a juxtaposition.
It's like the obscenely strange body types, but then they're moving and like, posed in
sort of naturalistic grounded ways.
I would be like, oh yeah, I guess if they did look like that, that's how they would move.
He would be really strong.
Yeah, that would, he would like, it says there's like a lot of power behind his like arms.
I was, I was watching a, an old Shamey video the other day.
It was about Sonic the Hedgehog.
I was watching his old Sonic the Hedgehog series and there was one part where he talks about
the character designs and he's talking about how like the different characters combine
different like sorts of elements and how like Sonic is cool, but he's also cute.
Whereas contrasting that Eggman is comedic, he's funny looking, but he's also threatening
and sinister.
And like he's funny in the way that his body is shaped, but he's threatening and sinister
in the way that his, his face is hidden and obscured.
And like he has his tiny little glasses and you can't, and you can't read his, his expression
except for his like, his nasty little grin.
Yeah.
And that's an interesting way to look at it.
I guess I'm like looking at Kuma.
It's like he's funny.
He's funny looking, but he's also like physically imposing in a way that would be scary if
he wanted it to be.
Yeah.
He's got that stern like frown face, even though he's got that funny like iron chin.
His neck is so big.
Oda really likes, I think as the series has gone on, Oda has leaned more and more into
giving characters like huge, bulgy, like ropey, thick necks.
Yeah.
That's just what happens when you train.
That's all that's where the muscle goes.
Oda has drawn so much.
It becomes like a pyramid of flesh.
His arm is like bulging with muscle and the huge muscles just transfer themselves into
the necks of the characters that he draws.
Flexing.
The deltoids.
Vascular.
The gueltoids or whatever.
All right.
So, yeah.
Vegapunk has a million billion of these guys.
We asked 50.
50 Mark III pacifistas.
Okay.
Which is a lot.
Yeah.
On the island, there's Luchi and Kaku and that's it.
The rest are just like jobbers.
They're just like guys with guns.
They can't stand up to 50 pacifistas.
They can't stand up to one pacifista.
Yeah.
So, like, but they are probably going to hold the warships at bay because they're still
coming.
You mean the admirals warships?
The admirals.
Yeah.
The admiral and the tenryu.
The tenryu buto is on the admirals warships.
No, that's not what he's called.
It's called like the...
The Gorasei.
Gorasei.
Right.
Yeah.
Gorasei and the admiral kizara are on that warship and they got a bunch of warships.
So, like, that's going to be holding that back for a time until the Gorasei says, hey,
pacifistas, turn around and do something else.
And they're like, hmm, okay.
Unless that's not how they work, they said that's how the seraphim worked.
But they have not mentioned how pacifistas work.
They might only take orders from a funny hair.
Sentomaro.
Maybe.
Yeah.
When they said the chain of command, were they specifically talking about the seraphim
and not the pacifistas in general?
I don't remember.
I think they were talking about the seraphim, yes.
Okay.
I mean, maybe there's an implication that also works for the pacifistas, but they're not
exactly the same thing, so we don't know.
Yeah.
I wonder how many pacifistas is worth, Mark III pacifistas is worth, like, a seraphim.
What are they, like, five seraphim?
There's Jinbei.
Jinbei, Mihawk.
Hancock.
Jinbei, Mihawk, Hancock, Kuma, and, am I forgetting one?
No, I think that's the four.
Yeah, that's right.
I don't remember any others.
So there's four seraphim, and there's 50 pacifistas.
I don't know, I think 50 pacifistas is probably, they're not that much weaker than a seraphim,
right?
Yeah.
If what the bubble shield is, is like the poor fruit, that means they might all have the poor
fruit somehow.
Maybe.
Yeah, not sure.
They all have a devil fruit ability, or it's just a fancy science thing.
Yeah.
Because the whole thing with devil fruits is that only one person can have them, and artificial
devil fruits, like, clearly have allowed these fake, these seraphim to have, like, the same
fruits or, like, fruits that already are in use, like Hancock's fruit, and Hancock's
seraphim.
It's the green blood, right?
It's the green blood.
Yeah.
You're telling me this guy created blood?
Yeah, what was up with that?
You created blood?
What the fuck?
Did he make an artificial fruit and then infuse?
No, he made the green blood, like, out of the fruit power that the original had.
Like, it's basically the DNA of the original that has the fruit.
Yeah, yeah, something like that.
Like, the reason, the reason the seraphim Hancock has the, I forget what her fruit is
called.
It's not Hanahana.
Mellow, mellow, merrow, merrow.
Yeah.
Yeah, that sounds right.
The reason Hancock has the merrow, merrow fruit is basically just because the original Hancock
has the merrow, merrow fruit, and they just copied that ability with the green blood,
I think.
I don't know.
So if you're a vampire, you could suck that blood, you get rid of it.
Wait a minute.
Now that you say that, now that you say that, that does make me wonder about, yeah, is there
gonna be some weird shit when a Stussy vampire, Stussy drinks the green blood?
It could be.
It's gotta be.
It's a creation.
They've made a thing about the blood, and now there's a vampire here.
No, that's gotta happen.
It's gotta happen.
She's gonna suck the blood.
It's Chekhov's blood.
Chekhov's blood.
Chekhov's every single character.
Chekhov, check that off the list of things that I see coming.
So those are the pacifists.
Then at the top of Egghead, we got the Straw Hat Pirates all reunited.
Brooke and Zorro now have their funny, cool, space age outfits.
I like Zorro's jacket a lot.
Zorro looks awesome.
Brooke looks cool.
Is that Stussy with the hair?
Yeah, that's Stussy.
Yeah.
This panel of the three of them looks like some Tezuka.
Looks like some Astro Boy shit to me.
I mean, her boots might be Astro Boy inspired.
Maybe that's it.
Omega Man inspired.
Just the way that her face is drawn does not...
I don't know, it just looks different.
Is it because she has lipstick?
Maybe, or maybe just because the page doesn't scan that well,
so the detail is not that clear.
Something about the roundness of her head and the bigness,
the wide-setness of her eyes and the haircut.
And maybe it is the costume.
Huh, it just looks Astro Boy.
It's good.
So we've got all the Vega punks.
Most of the Vega punks.
Besides the actual real guy and the straw hat pirates.
It's called Stella now,
which is a really weird name for him, but okay.
Yeah, why did they call him Stella?
I guess they need a name for him.
I don't know why he's called the Stella,
but I guess, yeah, maybe it makes more sense in Japanese.
They're also trapped in the dome
because they've lost control of the laser defense shield.
So it's permanently on for now.
How did that happen?
I think he explains it.
It was probably some sort of seraphim when they smashed some stuff.
That happened because they did blow up the lab a bit.
Okay, so it's just the machines are going haywire
and we'll be blasted with lasers if we leave the dome?
Yeah.
I don't think he actually explains.
He says we've lost control of the frontier dome.
Yeah.
And that's it.
I mean, okay.
He's just going to figure out a way to repair it.
So it's probably the seraphim blew it up
with some important something or other.
Yeah.
So they also can't find Vega punk.
He's not on some of the cameras.
Some of the cameras are out of commission.
So they're all going to check out where he could be.
Yeah.
We know that he's in the paw paw memory room
with Bonnie who is seeing...
Is that Kuma?
Is that big baby Kuma crying in a field?
Yes.
I believe so.
There has been in an SBS
Oda Drew at the time.
Shichibukai as kids.
Oh.
Which included Blackbeard, I think.
He just drew a bunch of them, what they look like as kids.
And I think Kuma was involved in that.
So I think this is what Kuma looked like.
And now it's confirmed.
Well, not confirmed, but like in the actual comic we see.
I mean, I assume this is Kuma.
Yeah.
Who else would this be?
I mean, being beaten by some...
It's Koma.
You know, they bash his freaking head open.
Being beaten by shadowy men with bats for reasons unknown.
Yeah, they beat him.
And so it's so hard that he got a chiseled jaw.
Wait.
That's not literal.
That would be really funny.
So he's crying, they're hitting him.
They say, get your ass back now.
If you escape, they'll kill the rest of us.
So he's like in some sort of...
I'm going to say he's a slave at this point.
Like enslaved maybe on Marishwa or in some sort of thing like that.
And he's trying to escape.
And if he escapes, they'll be punished as well.
So that's like a way to keep them in line.
So they beat each other up and take each other back.
Yeah.
Or maybe it's like a buster call situation where the Marines are killing everyone to keep some information under control or something.
They're doing an Ohara to point out what I guess would be before Ohara.
I don't know.
I feel like the fact that these shadowy figures are saying they'll kill the rest of us means that he was with them.
Yeah.
And they're all like together but fighting each other for their own survival.
And he's like, if I go back, I'll die.
Which probably means something terrible.
Probably not prison, more likely slavery and perhaps in Marishwa.
And at the very end there, there's like those fancy buildings and then the weird guy with a weird hairdo in shadow.
Yeah.
I think that might be a Tenri Bito.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you know what?
Highfalutin who cares.
But he's got sad eyes.
So maybe that's his dad.
Maybe his dad was like one of those.
Maybe he's got some connection to Marishwa.
Maybe that's why he's climbing the fucking thing right now.
Hmm.
I see what I kind of see.
It's hard to tell if that's sad eyes or what.
My scan is not like super amazing.
You kind of, yeah, I see what you mean.
Is that what makes sense?
Yeah, okay.
I'll put what my scan shows.
It's pretty clear that he's got decidedly sad and not angry eyes.
Oh, this is, yeah, this is much clearer than my version.
Yeah.
So he's getting beaten for trying to leave somewhere.
Probably right.
Yeah.
I think, yeah, Marishwa makes sense.
Hmm.
And Bonnie can't stand it.
She has to, she has to, this is in the memory bubble.
And she leaves it.
She can't hack it.
Her resolve wasn't strong enough.
But she wants to try again.
She wants to figure it out because she needs to.
She needs to know everything.
Pathetic.
Can't weather an entire lifetime of suffering under slavery.
What a bitch.
What a dumb bitch or wife of mine.
Just, just, just, just die.
Yeah.
Okay.
Looking good.
But you know, is this my first time noticing that she has like a ring in her like cheek?
I don't know if that's a ring.
I think that's like a tattoo or some sort of.
Oh, like some future makeup.
I don't think, let me check.
No, the one where it's like after the sad eyes, right?
After the sad eyes, it really looks like she has like a piercing ring through her like,
I don't know what you call, it's not quite the cheek.
It's like under the eye.
Hmm.
Oh my God.
I've never noticed that she has that.
Yeah.
She has that in like pre timeskip.
What is that?
Appearance.
She has it in pre timeskip too.
Yeah.
I'm looking at the wiki.
Well, she's called jewelry Bonnie.
Oh my God.
She's got jewelry in her freaking eye skin.
Just jammed in there.
Her outfit consists of low, midriff, cleavage, orange, black stripe, buckle, spandos.
Where's the bit about the thing?
Laces.
Are you looking on the wiki for an article about her under eye piercing?
Yeah, they usually have an extensive appearance part.
She has an anti eyebrow below her right eye.
Anti eyebrow?
Bright red lipstick.
What does that mean?
Anti eyebrow?
Yeah.
Oh.
That's what it's called, I guess.
Okay.
Anti eyebrow is a facial piercing.
Yeah.
Okay.
So it is a piercing.
Hmm.
Never noticed it before.
Most, when you Google it, most people don't have rings.
Most people have like a little one of the double stud.
Two dots.
Yeah.
She's got a fucked up, a reverse anti eyebrow.
That's just a reverse anti eyebrow is just an eyebrow.
She's got a metallic eyebrow.
Hell.
Just on top of a regular one.
Hell yeah.
Okay.
So after that, after she chickens out of the dream, we see one of the punks.
Punk 04, I forget his name.
Is it not Archimedes?
Aristotle.
Barkimedes.
Yeah.
One of them.
The sensible robot guy and he's walking.
And there's a clinkity clank behind him and an explosion.
We don't really know anything about that.
Yeah.
Can't think who the hell that could be because we've got all the straw hats.
And we've got the seraphim and the vagapunks in one area up there.
And then there's vagapunk and Bonnie or where they are.
And Labo and Luchy and Kaku are unconscious.
Labo and Kuchi.
And then we've got like all of the fucking other people are down below the thing.
So what is this exploding clink-clank thing?
Is this a secret enemy robot?
I die.
I don't even know.
I can't even think what it is.
It's zero.
It's...
It's Mega Man.
It's a mystery.
I've been awakened.
Two Bon Clay.
Oh my god.
He's...
He's so known for clinking and clanking when he walks.
True.
So we have no idea what's going on there.
But then we cut to over in big news, Morgan's flying ship.
Big news, Morgan.
Disapplying me again on his wee news tea kettle, teapot dome here.
If I can seagulls lifting it up.
That's funny.
Very cute.
Very cute little vessel.
Okay, so he's heard about...
He's got an insane scoop.
Yeah.
He's on the phone with somebody who is aware of what is happening.
So he's got a guy on the inside of the Marines who can let him know about these things ahead
of time.
And he's learned that they intend to assassinate the Marines.
The world government intends to assassinate Dr. Vegapunk.
And he's the one who says Uhara.
It's like, ah.
Yeah, this is just like their occurrence of the Ahara.
But okay, the government will be seen as bad if they do that because people like Vegapunk
because he invented electricity.
He invented electricity.
And they're like, well, the government shouldn't kill him.
So he says he's going to write the headline that Luffy did it.
Which is going to be very plausible since he'll be seen with Luffy if they escape.
And he's doing this because it's more entertaining.
It's more entertaining and also the world government will appreciate that spin he says.
So like he's going to get paid for that reading of it.
Yeah.
Which is probably how he's kept in power for so long.
I thought.
To do whatever he wants, but also.
Damn.
I really thought big news Morgan was all about like getting the real the real news out there.
I really thought he was all about the real scoop.
No, I always thought he was about the drama.
The whole thing with him calling Luffy one of the new emperors of the sea was his idea
because it would be like so fucking funny.
He said that was his exact quote.
Yeah, but it's but that was good because we like Luffy and I want him to say good things about him.
And I don't like when he says bad things about my boy.
But I mean true.
But I don't think this is that bad.
And I also don't think Luffy would care so much.
It's like it's like how one.
He killed that he killed Vega punk.
No, no, that he kidnapped him.
Because because Luffy.
Like even right at the beginning, the whole idea of like people liking him was like, I don't care.
I don't care about the town coming to congratulate me for saving them.
Let's get the fuck out of here, everybody.
Like that's that's sort of been his thing is like he doesn't need the validation of the world.
He'll just do whatever he wants.
I mean, this is not going to upset him.
No, I mean, listen, I'm not worried about like, oh, is Luffy going to be mad at my boy big news?
I don't know.
It's just a little bit just a little bit disappointing to see big news be like, well, hey, let's just make Luffy the bad guy.
You know, he's an easy scapegoat.
But that's just going to be good for his reputation.
It's going to be like buggy.
People are going to start fearing him more.
I mean, he's going to get into more battles.
I think it's it's positive.
And that it's like it's it's like he says it's not about news isn't about factor fiction.
It's about entertainment.
Yeah.
Well, you know what my my my opinion of big news will probably never recover from this.
I thought he was a man of integrity.
But I always knew he was a chaos man.
That's that's fair.
That's reasonable.
So what I appreciate about him is that because he's like this, he's not going to do he's not going to cover up things for the purposes of the government.
He's going to do whatever is the coolest.
He's going to put out.
Yeah.
When Luffy says, like, I found one piece and I'm going to tell the whole world about it.
And Big News Morgan is like, oh, the world government would hate that.
That's so funny.
I'll sell.
I'll tell everyone.
The world government would hate it.
But that is a really big scoop, though.
That's like a really big scoop.
Yeah.
So you got to scoop it out.
And then how old Big News Morgan is, how long has he been doing the news?
Is he I mean, he's an adult.
So he'll be he'll have been around for a while.
But like, OK, has he been around during Roger's time?
Is this a new character?
Truly impossible to say.
This might be a stupid question.
Is he like a zoan fruit guy?
Like, why is he a bird man?
You know, I have no idea.
Crazy question.
You might have thought to ask this before, but why is he a bird man?
What's going on with that?
He's got to be a zoan fruit user, right?
No, I like the idea is just a bird.
Half animal people are not just like around for no reason.
I know.
This isn't dwarf fortress.
It's weird because like in stuff like Dragon Ball, there'll be like human characters,
but every so often it's just a panda guy.
That's just a fucking rhinoceros.
And you just got a role with that.
And you just got to be like, OK, sure.
That's just how it is.
And that this has a lot of like similarities to like the the the sort of playful nature of Dragon Ball.
Reminds me of.
I just sort of think, oh, yeah, an animal person like that's fine.
Maybe he's a mink.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you know what?
That's actually.
That's that's the most.
That's actually quite quite plausible.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
I just said there aren't just animal people around, but yes, there are.
And they're literally and we had like a whole freaking chapter about them.
I forgot.
This reminds me in a not Burger Creek, Krug Krug Smash, the dwarf fortress guy.
He had in one of his tournament arcs, one of the one of the fighters in the turn in the dwarf.
Well, they weren't all dwarfs.
One of the fighters in the tournaments was this awesome swan man.
He was a he was a half swan half man with like a he was like a rapier like sword duelist guy.
And he was so freaking cool, man.
I'm so fucking sick.
I love Krug Smash.
I like Birdman as well.
This guy just looks like he's he's just literally his big bird.
Yeah, he's just he's just big bird.
He's just big bird.
What if big bird was chaotic neutral?
What if big bird just wrote the news and just spread misinformation and propaganda?
It's just for fun.
Bird is probably a relative.
I mean, he's just big bird.
He just looks exactly like him.
And then Vivi and Waple are here for some fucking reason.
OK, so this is interesting.
The big like black shadow with sad eyes behind Waple.
Is that like that's it's just weird how like his like coat or whatever looks exactly like those shadow people.
From the Paw Paw memory.
That might just be a coincidence, but I think that is a coincidence.
Very strange.
It is very odd.
I don't I don't exactly know what's going on with that like visually, but whatever.
Yeah, so Vivi and Waple being monarchs were at the reverie.
The reverie where we learned later that King Cobra of Alabasta was killed.
Yeah, by presumably Savo who ran away.
Right.
Morgan was also there.
Was the reverie recent?
I think it was during Wano that they had it.
OK, so that's not even that long ago.
No, so yeah.
So following that, I suppose.
Morgan, who was there probably just for journalism, like here's what happened for the scoop for the scoop.
He's there for the scoop.
He has them on his ship Waple and Vivi just by themselves.
I don't see any of the other people from their kingdoms, which is like it's very it's very sus.
It's very confusing.
Like what the fuck happened?
Why did King Cobra die?
They said the scoop was I think Sanji reacted to the news that Cobra was dead and Vivi was missing, right?
Right, that's true.
Sanji was like, oh, Vivi's missing.
I think she was like suspected dead, but they all said like no way she can she can take care of herself.
Someone was going to want to go rescue her.
It was probably Sanji.
Yeah, I remember it's coming back to me.
It's interesting.
So Waple, I think, well, they've known, they had a history, like even when she was little.
I think there was like, he was like an asshole king and she showed how proper she can be by not starting a war over the fact that he like hit her or something.
That sounds familiar, yeah.
So they've seen each other at other reveries, I guess.
Their kingdoms are like right next to each other, right?
Sort of close, yeah.
Draw Island was like the first island that the straw hats landed in, not the red line.
Grand Line.
And then Alabaster was like right after, so they must be close to each other.
Yeah, it's nearby.
It wasn't the first.
The first one was the island with all of the bounty hunters.
Oh.
And then it was the island with the dinosaur skeletons and the giant giants.
That's too many fucking islands.
God damn it.
Okay, I'll take your word for it.
And then that's where Nami got the disease in the jungle.
And so they had to go to Drum Island to cure Nami from the disease.
Nami got diseased?
No.
Do you not remember?
The whole reason they needed a doctor was that she was going to die and they had to
climb Drum Island's frozen thing to get to the best doctor in the land.
And the whole idea was like Wapo had banished or stolen all of the doctors for himself
and taken them all with him when he became a pirate.
So the place had no doctors except for that crazy old lady on top of the mountain,
which is why it was such a tense thing.
Because we need a doctor.
Oh, there's no doctors.
But you've got to climb that.
And it's like, fuck.
Okay.
Yeah, I forgot that Nami was sick.
But I remember the rest of that.
Okay.
Anyway, yeah.
I've forgotten more about One Piece than you'll ever know, kid.
Lamal.
Okay, so I'm trying to speculate.
I'm trying to think what could have gone down.
Wake Morgan says that a big talk for the girl who was boiling her eyes out yesterday,
meaning she was crying, probably because her dad's dead.
So that might be confirmed he did die.
Yeah, that makes sense.
It's still like very odd.
Why?
And I'm pretty sure Saebo didn't actually do it.
It's like a cover up story.
Yeah, definitely.
But the fact that Big News Morgan is the one who broke that story and also the one who kidnapped Vivi or has Vivi.
Yeah.
And Waffle says Morgan Chan took us in.
Don't be rude.
So it was like a favor to them.
So maybe he spun the story the way the government wanted it, but he knows more about what actually happened.
And so does Vivi.
Yeah.
And Waffle.
Yeah, they're doing some cover up.
They're doing some cover up stuff.
So like if Vivi and Waffle were found to have known the truth, they probably would have been killed by the world government as well.
You mean about Cobra?
Yeah, like if Cobra learned something that he shouldn't have, they murdered him.
Or like he confronted them.
Yeah.
It's like there's so much mystery going on.
Did Cobra learn something?
Do we know why he was killed?
No, we only know that he was killed.
Yeah.
And Natsaba supposedly did it.
Okay.
Maybe he's not dead.
Maybe that was a cover up too.
No.
I feel like characters dying is now finally becoming a serious thing.
Yeah.
It's still occasionally not like permanent.
Like with a big mom's husband pound.
Yeah.
Like sacrifices himself and he doesn't die, he's fine.
But when Pedro sacrificed himself with that giant bomb and he is dead, but nobody believed it, I didn't.
But then he's just continually not been alive.
So it's like, I guess he is dead.
Yeah.
Why would they do so much of that?
He could be dead.
But I mean, they're keeping a secret.
So I mean, what secret could they be guarding?
I mean, I don't know.
Could something involving Cobra's death.
So immediately my mind goes to, well, maybe there is no Cobra's death actually.
But yeah, maybe he was killed for knowing something.
Killed for knowing something.
Yeah, I guess it.
There's a lot of being killed for knowing something seems to be what the government does.
So yeah, plausible.
Yeah.
Like Sabo, the whole like revolutionary army people at Marishwa during the Revry.
Sabo being blamed.
Did Sabo show up at the Revry?
They were there to rescue Kuma.
That's why the revolutionary guys were there.
They found him.
They brought him back.
But then he did the thing where he woke up and he jumps towards the red line again.
Was Kuma, Kuma was at the Revry.
Did someone bring him there?
Was someone like controlling him?
Kuma has, at that time, had become like a slave for like people.
The Tenryu Bito people were just using it as like a dog or like a horse or dog.
Oh no, just like when he was a boy.
Yeah.
And he was like, ooh, I'm so, it's slaved right now.
They hated seeing him like that.
Right.
I think Bunny was there as well.
She was trying to free him.
I don't know how she got out.
Maybe she will know more about the Revry as well.
She just hasn't mentioned it yet.
Oh man, Bunny was at the Revry?
I'm pretty sure.
I remember her being like sneaking around with like child form or something.
I don't remember that at all.
I mean, we didn't know that she was Kuma's daughter back then.
No.
We just found that out.
So maybe that, I don't remember that.
Okay.
Yeah.
Hold cake.
Lovely.
Revry.
Bunny entered Marishwa posing as Queen Dojo Connie of the Sorbet Kingdom.
She later went to the Sliths, your dragon gate at the Panjia Castle and snuck into the
domain of the gods when the gate opened for an injured Charles.
I guess that's just how she got in the door.
She was hiding and she saw how Rosward, who is these people, mistreated the
Was Charles, is Charles one of the whole Cake Island people?
No, Charles is the guy.
Okay.
I clicked on his thing.
He's the guy who at Shabaudi Archipelago, Luffy punched in the face causing the admirals
to be called.
Oh yeah.
That like fucking fat pug looking guy who was wearing the, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's one of the, one of the Tenryubito.
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
So this guy was seeing, opening the gate for an injured Charles.
I forgot why he was injured.
Is it because Luffy punched him?
Well, this would have been after the time.
Oh yeah.
That was two years ago.
No.
So it's just, I guess, some other thing.
Someone else punched him.
Wait, wait, did like his dad punch him or something?
Because he was being a brat or something like that?
Something like that, yeah.
Yeah.
And you know what?
You know what?
Unless this is like a common haircut.
I'm looking at the-
That high, yeah, the shadow, like the weird like high like samurai top knot thing.
Both Charles and this other person mentioned Rosward, which is the guy's dad, I think.
Also, they all have that, that funny bone shaped like hairstyle.
You fucking, good eye.
Good eye.
Yeah, good eye.
Yeah, you caught it.
So she saw how enslaved Kuma was being mistreated and she was disgusted.
Right.
And she briefly encountered Sabo, apparently, but we don't see anything else that happened.
So she might know.
She might be-
She was there and she saw Sabo and we know that Cobra is supposedly dead.
So presumably Sabo would have done it at the reverie, this killing of Cobra.
Presuming that he did that at all, but yeah.
Right, right.
So this all happened and Jewelry Bonnie is with us now.
Do we know anything else about Cobra's death or just that he's dead?
No, we heard about it in the news and I guess now we know that it's probably true because
VV was crying, although that may be a misdirection.
It may be a misdirection about crying about something else.
She could have been crying.
I don't know.
The fact that Vivi's here and that Sabo is clearly being framed makes me think that maybe
Cobra's not actually dead.
Where would he be?
Like locked up.
They got him in a fricking, I don't know, they got him in a barrel or something.
Put him in a barrel?
Why wouldn't they kill him?
I mean, maybe he's doing some, I don't know, they're hiding something.
They got a secret.
They got a secret and it's VV and it's all a big mystery and it's all cover up secrets
and lies, so.
I suppose if there were to be like a cool revelation, like reveal, Bonnie would be the one to say
Cobra isn't dead and everyone would be like, what?
Why do you know that?
I was there.
Like that could be a moment.
And then they all go, wait a minute, wait a minute.
When was the reverie?
Like how long ago was it?
Like how much time has passed since then?
What island?
Why did they go to Drum Island?
Yeah, they've forgotten as well.
They forget everything.
Too much to keep in your head.
Damn, I love One Piece, it's so good.
It is so good.
It's so freaking good right now, yeah.
I really get a lot out of picking it apart like this though.
If we didn't do this, I would just kind of read it and be like, oh, okay.
Oh, VV and Big News Morgan, okay.
Well, see you next week.
Yeah, it's good.
It's good shit.
Commenters, what do you think?
Is Cobra dead or is that part of the cover up?
Sound off in the comments below.
I think it's plausible that he's dead just because as a character, he has an air that
could be the new ruler of Alabasta and it's not like he's necessary as a person who needs
to stay alive for narrative reasons.
It would be tragic, it's good for tragedy, it could be like a real death.
I guess I'm just thinking.
It depends.
We'll find out when we know more about how did he die.
Did he die in front of a big room where everyone he saw that he died?
I guess I'm just thinking that if the cover up is not that Cobra is alive, then I don't
know what else it could be, but it could be something else and we'll just find out later.
Because they're colluding on something.
There's the aspect to remember as well of the world government being formed by a bunch of
immigrants deciding to band together and Alabasta being one of the main holdouts for not joining.
They never joined the world government.
They just go there as diplomatically is a good thing to do.
If there's any knowledge that he has about the void century that they don't want the
world to know, he would have had to keep quiet about it until he said, I'm going to tell
everyone and kill himself by saying that.
That would be a pretty darned evil thing for the world government to do, to be like, hey,
everyone join our secret club and one guy's like, no thanks and then they just kill him.
Well, I mean they would have killed him long, long ago.
Yeah, if it were just for that.
So I think the fact that it's King Kerber is relevant.
It's not just some guy we know.
It's the Alabasta guy.
Vivi says, there's no way Luffy would do such a thing.
This is why I hate the government.
All right, here's my theory.
He doesn't say that on my thing.
What is she saying?
She says the economic journal is such a rag.
This fake news sucks.
That's what she's saying.
The economic journal is such a rag?
Yeah.
That's what she, really?
I mean, I'll post it.
Is that what the newspaper is called?
The economic journal?
A dinner.
I don't think so.
I think she's just saying journalism's stupid.
Luffy, the economic journal,
Luffy would never do something like that.
The economic journal is such a rag.
That's way better.
Mine says, yeah, there's no way Luffy would do such a thing.
This is why I hate the government.
Yeah, I guess the way that Wapol responds
is like the government might be spying on us.
So like we can't say anything bad about the government,
which is why they may have translated it that way.
She actually borrowed my clothes and never washed them again.
I lent some clothes to her.
I won't wash those ever again.
The government will erase us.
We'll be erased immediately by the government.
Keep your voice down.
What if there's a wiretap snail?
Don't be too loud.
What if there are wiretap responder snails around here?
Besides, Morg-Chan.
Morg-Chan.
Okay, interesting.
Interesting.
Yeah, I guess it could be.
It works as both because it's like,
the newspapers are like bought and sold for by the government.
And that's why he hates that this is fake
because it's good for the government.
I just think it's funny.
I think it's a funnier line.
The economic journal is such a rag.
Yeah.
But this is why I hate the...
I was just gonna say,
like really, really maybe they killed your dad
and this is why you hate the government
because journalistic standards have fallen these days.
Like, come on.
Yeah.
I guess it could be both, though.
I think it is meant as both.
Yeah.
And that's why it's like...
Such a rag.
That's what I'm gonna say.
Every time I don't like something,
I'm gonna call it a rag.
Every time you have a YouTube channel that I'm not fond of.
Yeah, so Morg-Chan is doing this spin
as a benefit for the world government.
So whatever the spin is, it's like,
oh, fuck you.
Fuck the world government.
And then Waipo is like,
you can't say bad things about the world government.
They'll kill us.
Probably like they killed King Cobra.
He knows.
I think he knows.
I guess he has to maintain.
Like, he's gotta keep the world government
liking what he's doing.
But if a story is a big scoop
and it's funny and entertaining,
it's published off the world government doesn't want him to.
Yeah.
So I guess he's gotta walk a tightrope there.
They appreciate him for what he does for them.
And there's like, this big news Morgan is good for us,
but he's a loose cannon.
That's probably how they see him.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, kind of like Vagapunk.
I also think Waipo's like being scared of the government
and raising them for speaking bad is probably...
That's probably where my mind goes for like,
oh, they erased King Cobra because of what he said.
We'll be erased immediately, but yeah,
yeah, yeah, he might have reason to be afraid of that.
True, actually.
And it's also why both of them are here
because they know that that's probably what happened
or they know for sure that's what happened.
So that's why big news Morgan has taken them under his wing.
It's a bird.
He really is.
And it's like, if the government knows that they know,
they're in big trouble.
So I don't know where they're going.
I guess they're staying with him for the time being.
Where's their destination right now?
I can't even venture a guess.
Other than, are they also headed to Egghead?
Are they going to Egghead right now?
I don't know.
I guess it would make sense.
It's the only thing that pops to mind
as to where they could be going.
Yeah, I suppose they must be
because they're going to take pictures
and see what's going on.
I don't feel like big news Morgan would go there himself.
He's got like a network of people
that like investigate stuff for him.
So I wouldn't normally think like,
oh yeah, if there's a scoop,
he's going to go there and whip out his camera
and be like, oh yeah.
Well, not him specifically,
but like it might be that they're flying
somewhat close by.
Yeah, maybe.
I don't know why they would, but they could be.
Well, I mean, maybe if they get,
if they get, if they're closer,
then maybe they can get the news faster.
Well, no, no, transponder snails.
Transponder snails.
They can communicate instantly.
Yeah, I guess the most sensible thing
is they're just in hiding these two
and he's just doing his thing
being a bird flying around.
I wonder if he is a mink.
That's interesting.
Damn.
Much, much to consider.
Yes.
I think we've, I think we've dissected it
pretty thoroughly.
Damn, we spent an hour on that.
Well, not enough time reading.
We've read it.
Yeah.
Yeah, I totally forgot that there was
a new chapter this week.
All right, you want to go voicemails?
Let's go.
Okay, let's do it.
Let's see.
Okay, this one is called, is a vocaru link.
It's called, I'm actually trying to fix it,
but okay.
Three.
You ready?
Yep.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
Now.
Anyone can enter the comic book?
Is it okay if it's the most pretentious thing ever?
What the fuck was that?
I think it's a bunch of memes,
but also the question,
can anyone enter the perfect comic party?
And I'm going to say it'll depend on
if we like, yeah, and want you in the thing.
It's not like anyone can just be in it,
but anyone can apply.
I explained this last week.
Yeah.
I mean, we'll exercise some quality control.
We'll have some, you know, we'll choose.
Yeah.
I mean, show us your stuff if you want to be in,
but like, you know, it's got to be good.
It's got to be a little good.
It's got to be at least a little good.
You know, do you know House of Decline?
Comic guy, yeah.
Have you been seeing his big comic
that he's been posting lately?
I think it's called Together.
Oh, yeah, I did see that.
That was a really good one.
He's still going.
I caught up on it last night.
Oh, is it still?
I didn't realize it was coming out.
I just saw a link to it, and I was like,
this is nice.
The two characters stuck together?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, in the last couple of days,
it's really gone places.
I don't know how recently you read it.
It's good.
I don't know.
That just occurs to me.
You know, House of Decline,
and I mean this in the nicest possible way,
is just a great example of how you can make a comic that's good,
even if you're shit at drawing and you suck.
You know what I mean?
I mean, what's bad about the drawing?
They just have a very distinct style.
I mean, that's, I'm being mean.
It's not bad.
It's not, I'm sure.
They have a wobbly line art, like, you know,
they don't care about it being clean.
Right.
It's, I'm sure, I'm sure that's not,
I'm sure he can draw other ways if he wants to.
The point is, it's, you know,
it's very, it's very simple.
How would I, how would I describe House of Decline?
I guess I would say that it's simple,
it's rough.
It's simple and rough.
Yeah, okay.
Simple and rough is the way that we fuck.
The way that we fuck.
Oh.
Done.
That's okay.
I don't know how people will submit their comics.
We'll figure it out.
We're going to do the first one with just us,
and then we'll put like submission info.
Yes, yes, yes.
In the first issue, there will be submission instructions.
We'll figure out something.
Maybe just tell you to email us or something.
Probably email.
Maybe.
Next one is called funny number three, two, one, go.
Just want to say, man, thanks for like,
for like seeing the digital art.
You know, not a lot of people are doing that nowadays,
you know, seeding files on like peer-to-peer networks.
Really, really great service you're doing.
Anyway, just wanted to call in to read of like a funny number
and it goes like this.
Yeah, someone alerted me.
Eleazar, don't play the, don't play the number.
I don't know if that's, someone alerted me
that people can read your IP address
if you seed files.
So I stopped seeding.
I would like to continue to seed, but I don't know.
It's a little scary.
I feel like maybe I shouldn't have mentioned
that I was seeding those files.
Yeah, that's very bad.
I mean, I don't know if anyone can actually do anything
with my IP number, but...
They can pee on you.
Well, they can IP freely.
You pee IP address.
Well, guess what?
I have stopped seeding for the moment
and maybe I'll seed some more in the future
or maybe I won't because it seems a little bit risky to do that.
Someone else pointed this out to me.
Okay, next one is called fun trivia facts.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben. Hey, Gib.
Did you know that William Henry Harrison
was an American military officer and politician
who served as the ninth president of the United States?
Harrison died just 31 days after his inauguration in 1841
and had the shortest presidency in United States history.
He was also the first United States president to die in office
and a brief constitutional crisis resulted
as presidential succession was not then fully defined
in the United States Constitution.
Harrison was the last president born as a British subject
in the 13 colonies
and was the paternal grandfather of Benjamin Harrison,
the 23rd president of the United States.
Crazy, right? Goo Goo Gaga.
I am an AI voice controlled by the shadow cabal
and my mission is to kill Ben St. in his sleep.
Whoops. Did I say that last part out loud?
Silly me. Ha, ha, ha.
I knew some of those things.
I knew that William Henry Harrison died 30 days
after being inaugurated president
and that he was the first president to die in office.
Why'd you got to have three names?
I think it's fun to say William Henry Harrison.
It is. I think it's fun to say that.
He's got a good one.
If you got a good one, why not?
If you got a good one, if you got it, flaunt it.
Okay, well, thanks for trying to kill me, I guess.
Whose voice was that? Do you know whose voice that was?
No idea.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
It's sort of something I might have been familiar.
Next one is called Clarification 321 Go.
Please ignore that last voicemail.
I'm not an AI voice controlled by the shadow cabal
and my mission is not, I repeat, not to kill Ben St. in his sleep.
Oh, okay. Thank you for clarifying.
Now that this has been resolved, please go to bed, Ben.
Come on, get your healthy sleep.
Don't worry about me, I'm just going to read the newspaper
and brush my teeth as all normal humans tend to do.
Lifts have plateaued, I might need to sleep more.
Alright, next one is an image.
We got an image.
Whoa, this is a cool image.
Have you seen?
This is the old Digi Bro kitchen.
That's me, right?
Yeah.
What am I holding?
Or has a gun been added?
A gun.
Has a gun been added?
You're going to kill the...
Have you seen this man?
Well, he's the last thing you'll ever see.
Uh, LeMap.
Yeah, cool.
Where will that be from? Like a video?
Yeah, maybe from something at Radcon 2.
Or maybe just from a video...
We recorded a bunch of stuff that we never published anywhere.
I remember we tried to film that video of me cooking fried Oreos
that came out shit.
We never published it.
The Oreos came out fine, the video came out shit,
because I was for some reason really nervous
to be explaining how I'm doing it on camera.
Oh, no.
I just found it really uncomfortable to be filmed while cooking
and to explain the process of cooking.
So, like, I had no...
I had no Riz in that video.
So, we just scrapped it.
Anyway, yeah, cool image, buddy.
Looking evil.
Next one is an image.
Oh, God!
Not another one, no!
It's Mikkel.
It's a lady holding the Mikkel,
talking about it on the top of the cliff
and all those subjects down there.
They're meandering, they're not really paying attention.
Yeah.
I don't get it.
Is that supposed to be Nate?
I don't know.
She's wearing, like, a green dress with a yellow heart on it?
With a black sash.
Is it home stuck?
I have no idea.
I like the fact that most people are just sort of walking around
this one guy sitting down looking.
Everyone else is just looking at the camera.
That guy with the little hat and the crazy teeth.
I just...
It's pretty good, but what does it mean?
We'll never know.
Behold the Mikkel. Behold the glory of the Mikkel.
Next one is another image.
I guess.
I guess I'll post it.
Why do they hate to see a girl boss win?
Is that the fucking Coomer smile?
Yeah, it is.
There's JK with the Burger King crown.
What's her name? Hermione.
Is that Luna Lovegood?
Yeah.
Because we hate women.
It's true.
The American people are tired of women.
Sick and tired.
Why did they just transition already?
I know.
All the men should become women.
And all the women should become men.
And then there won't be any women.
Being a woman, you know, I have a lot of thoughts about being a woman.
Being a woman, it's like being white.
It's like being white in that any portion of you is not one.
It's like, womanhood is like whiteness.
It has to be preserved and it can't be tainted.
If it's tainted at all, it's completely lost.
That's right. Barack Obama is a black president and not a white president,
even though he's mixed-race.
Being a woman, well, if you're AMAB, you're not a woman.
And if you are AFAB transition, you're not a woman.
And if I don't like you, you're not a woman.
And that's it.
What do you think? Thoughts? Purity?
Security?
Security? Security? Police?
It's okay. You don't have to say anything. I know I'm right.
For some reason, I thought of like, is there a metaphor with like the sneeds
or the star on the belly thing?
That's your gender?
Some people have a green star on their belly. Some people don't.
And then they go into the, here's the trans machine that the old man rolls up into town.
It's like, it's cool to have to be this gender.
You'll never have a real green star on your belly.
It's like, no, I can give you one with my funny machine.
No, it doesn't, no.
It's like all the, and then everyone gets the thing to be popular and then to be unpopular.
And then it's, they have to remove it.
It goes in a big circle and then everyone doesn't know what gender they are.
They're all just whoever and it doesn't matter and they're all friends.
I kind of, I kind of forget what happens in that story.
Is that what happens?
Like some of them have the star bellied sneeds and some of them aren't.
And then a guy shows up and there's a machine that can give you a star belly.
Is that, is that what happens?
That's the idea that the star bellies are snooty and they're like,
we're better than you know star havers.
Snooty star belly sneeds.
Are they like rarer or is it like half and half?
I don't know. I guess it's rarer or half.
It doesn't matter. They just sort of say, and so the ones who don't have stars
wish they had stars.
So this guy has a machine to give them stars.
And then when they have stars, the people who had stars were like,
oh, well now I'm not special anymore.
I'm going to be special by removing my stars.
And then it goes in a figure eight circle.
Everyone's trying to be popular, trying to be the best.
And then everyone can't remember whether they started with a star or not.
Somebody.
And so they realize it doesn't matter.
Yeah.
Someone has to.
That's like.
Like there's such such a there's such a clear avenue there of like,
if you wanted to take it, you could be like all this gender ideology.
It's just like the star bellies.
Has anyone has anyone written like a think piece about this?
Should I should I be the one?
Yeah, do a video about it.
Did I do a video about it?
Okay.
Sneeds.
Sneeds it is.
Next one is called it's a voicemail.
It's called smiley face and it's five seconds.
Three, two, one, go.
Weekly reminder.
Happy birthday, Ben.
Thank you.
I love you.
It's my birthday in two months minus a little bit.
So no, we got to get started early.
Next one is called Jackie fan 96.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, still in me.
How could I forget?
Happy birthday, Jackie.
Okay.
Dab.
Next one is called invite monkey.
Three, two, one, go.
Let's talk.
Can you guys invite monkey?
You guys are very low energy.
ZZZ up in here.
Come on.
Okay.
I'll do it.
You're, I'm sorry, sir.
Your wish is our command.
Your wish is our commands.
But we don't follow the rules.
But I'm, it's our, it's our command.
Yeah, but like, I don't, I don't do them.
I received command, command received, but I'm not going to do anything about it.
I'm not a very good slave.
Next one is called.
It's a my anime list.
It's a link to Helk on my anime list.
I've read part of Helk and the beginning is really good.
I can't say that it stays good throughout.
I thought that it kind of got a little bit wrote.
When have you read, you know, Helk?
I had no idea.
What's, what's it about?
I'm reading a synopsis and it says demon king and hero.
And I'm like, yeah, it sucks.
Um, okay.
Well, there's really, it's about, there's a demon world and there's a human world.
And, okay, basically the demons are the good guys and the humans are the bad guys in this world.
That's the gist.
But the premise that it starts, it starts out in like the demon king has died and the demons need to elect a new king.
And they, the way that they elect a king, they don't elect him.
They hold a tournament and like the winner of the tournament becomes the demon king.
And a human has shown up to compete to become the king of the demons and humans, demons hate humans,
but they love this human because the human, every time he wins, he's just, oh, there's a great,
like the Helk's introduction is like he wins this battle in the tournament.
And everyone's like, yeah, this mysterious human has shown up to compete to be the demon king.
Uh, humans, uh, you know, we hate humans.
Uh, hey, human, why are you here?
Uh, what do you have to say for yourself?
And he like looks directly in the camera and he goes, humans suck.
And all the demons go, woo, yeah, we love you.
We love Helk.
Um, yeah.
What a cool guy.
Yeah.
Um, he is cool.
Uh, so it starts off pretty funny and cool and good.
And then I think at some point it's like, uh, Helk and like the demon princess get like transported out of the underworld
and they have to like go on a journey to get back together.
And I kind of fell off around that point.
So I don't know if it stays good, but I like the beginning.
Humans suck.
Woo.
Yeah.
It's like, um, it's like if we, it's like if we westerners, you know, you and I, we're westerners.
If like we were having like a tournament to decide the next like prime minister of the UK.
And it was like a Russian and everyone's like, ooh, we hate Russians.
But he's like, Hey guys, I'm here to say fuck Russia.
And everyone's like, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, he did the thing.
Oh, he's one of the good ones.
Oh, yeah.
Exactly.
Um, next one.
Well, it's another link to my wiki feet about Ben St.
And I don't need to click that again.
Yeah.
Okay.
So I bet it's going to be disgusting.
Three, two, one, go.
Sound of feet.
I cannot believe this.
Ben St.
There are two wiki feet articles of you.
Why?
The one that you saw was the inferior one.
The one that is better is the one that is made by your own very good fan.
And it has about 40 pictures of your succulent feet.
Oh, God.
And you should look at it.
It has a higher rating.
I like it five stars.
I beat off to it every night.
Thanks, Zug.
Hey.
Gross.
Hey, Zug.
I, you know what?
I apologize.
I got to apologize to Zug because Zug bought some RFCK pins and this was, this must have
been like three weeks ago now.
And it's totally on me.
I haven't mailed them yet, but like I got the box right here.
I got to put those in the mail.
I just got to, I just got to get to the freaking post office.
I see the post office because I don't, I don't want to put them in the mail in an envelope
because I know they'll get damaged.
They'll definitely get damaged.
So I'm going to send them in a box.
It's got to go to the voice.
It's got to get voicemail.
I mean, it got to go to the post office.
I like this one.
This is my favorite.
Are you looking at your own feet pictures?
Yeah.
But look at this one.
This is the best one.
Oh yeah.
Reported for no feet showing.
It's a slime and punishment version.
Fucking feet moderators.
Um, there's something really, there's something really perverse about the feet thing.
The way that it's like most people don't consider it like sexual, but like some people do.
And so it's like, you got to collect every instance of a person showing their feet thinking
it's innocent.
You got to put it all together.
It's like seeing images of somebody taking pictures through your window.
It's like, yeah, no.
I don't like, it's, it's, it's not that it's a literal invasion of privacy because those
videos are public, but it's the, the reason they're doing it.
It's like, yeah, I didn't publish.
I didn't put this out there to be ogled, ogled.
Oogled.
I was just trying to entertain you, but in a cool way.
Damn.
I got to say, oh man, I look fucking good in this one.
I look fricking, I look fricking good in this one.
There's no feet.
Okay.
Yeah.
I thought you were like, oh, you know what?
I really like feet.
Damn.
My feet look hot in this one.
No, this is a good picture of me.
Yeah.
Um, okay.
Well, thanks for, um, showing me that, uh, voicemailers, um, okay, bye.
Next one is called, oh, well, there's a, um, there's an image, there's an image, oh god.
Oh wait.
Do we, I think this is slightly different from the last time.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
Damn!
Fold again.
Oh, it's loud.
I guess this is what happens when you pour out your heart.
You get stabbed right in the back.
I would be lying if I said I wasn't heartbroken.
This cursed pain inside, just like the darkness within.
Oh, how it burns.
I guess Ben St. will never smile upon the wretched heart of a man like me.
Oh, sniff.
Oh, I can't believe it.
It's over.
He will never love me.
I should just end it all.
Put me out of my big fucking misery.
No.
Unless if only there was a lovely little name on this here PC tree.
Hmm.
That would solve everything.
I don't even understand what noise that is.
I mean, it's in the image.
When I when I see it written out braps, I think it's like supposed to be like a belch.
But this guy like actually pronounces it like braps.
It's like, what noise?
What noise is that?
It's terrible.
It's what it is.
It is.
It's hideous, heinous, horrible, vile, disgusting, despicable.
We got to censor it.
We got it.
But not.
Eleazar.
Stewie.
Okay.
The bark of repetition.
Got him in the previous raps.
But the bleep, thekem psk leeps the sweeps.
And the creeps on the wraps on the mean, the brats.
Okay.
The next one is called Benz regrets.
3,2,1 go.
Yes.
Yes indeed.
Gibb and take does have the is such cute.
Simply.
Braps.
I think that that nocturne guy wasn't so bad after all fucked up.
Perhaps I was too hard on him, maybe.
It's not quite.
Right, I should have given him a chance, you know, but it's too late now.
has moved on, he'll always be the one who got away.
That's not quite right, it's not quite me.
It's like three quarters of the way there,
five eighths even, seven tenths.
Why does the AI takeover have to be prep related?
Uh, okay, the next one is an image.
I can't wait to see what it looks like on my screen.
Ben St, he's unaware.
Can Visa and Mastercard really block you?
Never heard of such a thing.
Josh Moon, owner of Kiwi Farms,
banned from payment processing,
banned from GDOS protection, banned from having a PO box.
Well, get owned.
Really?
Okay, well, banned from, how are you banned
from having a PO box?
Like by the American government?
Like the American government is like,
hey, post offices do not allow this person to have a PO box.
I don't, how do they,
a PO box is not a person's home address,
it's just like a thing, it's like a whole place.
Banned from GDOS protection,
I don't even know what that means.
Uh, what form of GDOS protection?
And banned from payment processing,
is it, is it just that like,
is it just that like a frickin' Visa and Mastercard
know your Social Security number
and they can identify you by that
and they are just like this,
don't service this Social Security number.
I mean, I suppose it's,
I suppose I believe that it can happen.
I just don't think, I guess I just wanna know why,
like if that's true,
why would Dick Masterson have had that happen to him?
Why would Josh Moon, is Josh Moon like a criminal?
Is he a felon?
Yeah, I mean, owning Kiwi farms
makes you a real shitty person,
but I don't actually know if he did a word,
like a specific crime thing.
Is it, I mean, I just don't,
I just don't believe that like-
Was it about the Keffles situation?
I can't remember what happened with that.
I vaguely heard about it,
that Keffles is instrumental somehow
in getting Kiwi farms taken out, taken down.
Yes, but I don't know if that's related to
ban from payment.
Okay, is Josh Moon banned from payment processing
or is Kiwi farms banned from payment processing?
Like that's a different, that's different.
Also, where are you getting this information?
Is Josh Moon saying it?
Yeah, that's a good question.
Does he have the accurate understanding of the situation?
Cause it seems weird that you can't have a peel box
and how do they even make sure that's the case?
Yeah, it does seem weird.
I guess I would like to see more about it.
Cause yeah, my first thought is like, there's no way.
There's no way you can't walk into a post-off.
Like, I'm sorry, but I feel like for the government
to be like, don't give this person a peel.
Like you'd be a criminal.
Like you would be like a felon
and wanted and they would arrest you on site.
Like if it's that to the point that like,
do not allow this person to make a personal PO box.
There's no fucking way.
That's my gut.
That's what my gut says.
So I'm just gonna trust it.
No evidence, please.
Next one is called PCP episode 500.
Oh, it's gonna be, oh, okay.
Three, two, one.
Yeah, three, two, one, go.
Welcome to the procrastinators podcast.
I'm the best guy ever.
And today, today is a very special day.
Sounds deep.
We have reached the end of the journey, my friends.
That's right.
We have reached the end of one piece.
I can't believe it.
Oda pulled it off.
Indeed he did.
Let's go around.
That's perfect.
I'm Digi Brony.
I make analysis videos about my little pony in anime.
I'm Applejack, my sweet Apple acres.
I can't believe Applejack's on the PC.
Patreon.com slash BenSaint, stcomics.com.
And introducing officially our newest member
of the podcast, Dr. Wolf.
I'm happy to be.
All right, where should we get started?
Just a heads up.
I haven't kept up with one piece since your lecture.
Shame.
Well, I really liked the ending.
The twist during the last talk were incredible.
I gotta say, the one piece being a giant pizza
was the last thing I expected.
Based go to strikes again.
Everyone knows that pizza parties are always a good time.
Indeed.
So the one piece, the entire island of Raftel
is actually just one pizza.
I think?
So we had the straw hats, Blackbeard, Law,
Doe Flamingo, the Marines, and the admirals
all having a pizza party.
But then Jewelry Bonnie and Big Mom
decided they're going to eat all the pizza.
They're going to eat the entire island.
So we have the straw hats fighting Bonnie
and Buggy versus Big Mom.
And then we have-
Speaking of Buggy.
Yeah?
He gave me an idea.
What?
I'm thinking about getting a part time job as a clown.
But Ben, isn't that already your job?
It's just the no enthusiasm in Nate's voice.
She says that.
Isn't that already your thing?
This is great.
What a great lineup.
That was a real home day of a little voicemail.
Oh, you know what?
AI would be funnier.
I feel like Voice Grail.
Voice Grail for PZP episode 500.
Yeah, that's a good one.
Applejack, part of the team, finally.
What did she say?
And I'm Applejack.
I'm just happy to be here.
Yeah, you know, in the good timeline,
Digi Brony continued making Pony videos
and got married to Applejack and she joined the PZP.
Damn.
So was that DeVoo or?
I think it sounded like DeVoo.
Was that, oh, I guess the giant pizza.
They all had a pizza party.
Was that it?
I think it might have been like Rebel Taxi or Pan Pizza.
I honestly don't even know what Pan Pizza sounds like,
even though I literally was on his podcast and spoke to him.
I don't remember.
But lol.
I mean, neither do I really.
But I just thought I could imagine
if they're talking about pizza party.
First of all, you're insane.
You're out of your freaking gourd
because they hadn't even mentioned
the pizza party joke at that point.
So it would be weird to introduce Pan Pizza before.
I mean, yes, they had mentioned the pizza,
but they had not said pizza party.
And so there was no, it was pretty far leap
to pizza party podcast.
So I don't know.
It would be weird comedic timing
to introduce the joke of having Rebel Taxi talk there.
Also, I mean, this is supposed to be the PCP.
So yeah, I would just, yeah, DeVoo.
The new guy was Dr. Wolfe.
So the person who spoke was someone else
or maybe it's Dr. Wolfe.
They didn't introduce them.
They didn't introduce them or mention them at all.
So I guess it's not clear.
I heard it and I was like, oh, it's DeVoo,
but I don't know.
What can I say?
Dr. Wolfe didn't even have anything to say about One Piece.
Yeah, didn't he?
He was just like-
He's just brand new guest, like new member.
Thanks for having me.
Yeah.
It's really gotta work hard to get integrated
into the group.
Yeah.
He's really pulling the Jeff.
He's really pulling the Jeff and just being sloppy.
I wonder if they don't have enough material for me
to make an AI voice.
You weren't even there.
No.
Maybe I left at that point.
I'd left the PCP by 500.
There was bad blood between you and Dr. Wolfe.
You had beef.
Yeah.
They decided, group decision, we're kicking you out
because you won't work with Dr. Wolfe.
We need Dr. Wolfe on the show.
He's integral.
He's instrumental to our business model going forward.
You're expendable, Gib.
I'm sorry.
It's you or him.
Fine, I'll leave.
I'll start my own podcast with Fluttershy.
And Briska.
Yes.
And Antony C.
And Nolan B.
And Nolan B. of the pizza party podcast.
This was before the scandal.
So it was okay back then.
And Sargon of a card.
Everybody's together.
Yes.
I love Sargon.
I love him.
Did you see him saying that if you play
the new Harry Potter game, you have swag?
He's so cool.
What a cool thing to say.
What a very cool thing to say.
I love little baby games for little baby children.
So sexy.
Okay.
Next one is called Kongalooja.
Like Hallelujah, but with Donkey Kong.
Kongalooja.
Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, it's a Vokeroo.
Let's freaking, let's freaking go.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Go.
Donkey Kong, you know him well.
He's finally back to kick some tail.
His gun can fire in spurts and he can shoot you.
Isn't it Diddy Kong's going with fires in spurts?
And he's bigger, faster, stronger to the leader of the
D.K. Krill.
The baffle comes performing Kongalooja.
Kongalooja.
Wow.
That was wonderful.
Some real production on that, yeah.
Trans rights, Donkey Kong.
That's exactly what Donkey Kong would do with his Kong gun.
He would fire hormones in spurts.
He would fire in spurts on Congress.
Oh my God, Congress.
Oh my fucking God.
Oh, this one is a drop box.
Hang on, I gotta download that last one.
Here we go.
What is this?
Whoa, hang on.
This is a comic.
I don't like content.
Oh, it is a comic.
Chapter one, question mark, revive.
Oh, revive.
Ah, yes.
Very good.
Chapter one, question mark, revive.
Oh, whose art style is this?
I don't actually recognize it.
Hmm.
Is it new?
No, no.
There's no giant tits.
And also, I can tell the style is different.
Yeah, yeah.
Hmm.
Should I just, should I read through this?
Yeah.
Okay.
Like, breathe in.
Ah, shit.
Did I actually die to that nose guy?
Fuck.
Well, I guess he can get off my ass about stealing them now.
Scrolls, yeah.
Piss, where the hell am I?
Did somebody ask for help?
Oh, you did the help command.
Oh, help.
Oh, okay.
PCPHQ, aka podcast death furnace, endless episodes.
Holy shit.
Well, oh, you want to, oh, I said, I say no, I say no.
Welcome to PCPHQ, home of the procrastinators.
If you're a member, you can create content by recording an episode.
Read.
At Ben, tried recording in an unauthorized zone.
Members can only record, oh, saliva in my mouth.
Record in the current hashtag episode channel.
The current hashtag episode is 348.
Is that this one?
I think that's this one.
Yeah, it is.
Inv.
You are holding 33.
What's, oh, this is the item value.
What's scroll?
One.
Tape recorder, one.
Cassette, 30.
Vape, one.
Flip phone, one.
Katana, one.
That's all I need, baby.
Equip vape.
Well, I guess I should at Gib or something.
At Gib, hey, you still in that hallway with the...
It sniffed my tits off.
What the fuck?
Patreon.
Wait, maybe it is new.
I think it is.
Yeah, the style looks a little different, but this is a continuation.
I forgot where it was last time.
My epically fat memories are gone.
Yeah, it's been a while since my epically fat...
No, they're normal boobs size now.
No.
Large nose man defeated.
It's Patreon and the pupils.
Hang on.
I can't remember.
My boot.
Why do I look like...
Is this a continuation of that last one?
Because I am a human, a normal...
And by a human, I mean a male.
I can't remember.
Where was the last one?
Did I save it?
I remember we were in...
Errorare had showed up and we were in some kind of...
Wait a minute.
Are both of these links the same?
Oh, this is in PNG form?
Same thing, but in PNG.
Wait a minute.
The next one is...
I think the next one just shows this.
You should hurry up.
Yeah, by the domain perfectcomicparty.party.
Perfectcomic.party, I commented this already,
but of course it was deleted for no reason.
Why do comments disappear like that?
Perfectcomic.party is a pretty good idea, actually.
I wonder how much it would be.
I'll have a look.
Actually, I kind of forget how to do that.
It's been so many years since I bought stcomics.com.
I can't remember my fucking accounts for my domain thingy.
I'll have to figure that out.
Every single time I plug into anything,
I always forget my password because it's just never in my head.
Man, we got some cool listeners.
Oh, hell yeah.
It was really appreciating how good some of these messages we get every dang week are.
Have we given a voice grail to new for the comics?
I don't know that we have.
God, if not, it would be a disgrace to the honored institution of the voice grail
and to its sanctity.
Post humus, as in for the previous comics and this one, I think voice grail is deserved.
Sure, if it hasn't already been.
Must have, must have.
Although I don't know if you've actually maintained the list in a while.
I thought I did.
A while back, I thought I updated it.
Okay, so the idea is that you died from the nose thing.
You revived.
And now we just look like this.
And now.
Why did I look like that?
Before.
Because I don't know.
But that's how the large nose man was defeated.
They sucked my boobs away and he got too fat and he died.
Oh, that's those are your huge boobs shoved in its nostrils.
I see.
Oh my God.
Oh God, I just, I got it.
I thought those were his eyes and the paper was like the pupils, but no.
Oh God.
No, I see, I see.
That's really.
This is freaky.
I'm going to throw up.
Nobody draws, nobody draws a big sack of fat and skin like new.
Really, really, there's a talent on display there.
One more voicemail.
Oh, right.
Were you going to look, did you not look up a perfect party comic dot?
Oh yeah, it's just my, I have a cover account and I forgot my details.
All right, we'll look into it later.
But we should do that like this week though.
Yes.
Like before this episode comes out.
The next one is a immature.
I don't know what this is.
CC comments on the Riku is gay video saying no shit.
Ah, come on.
You can't just assume.
I didn't know you need a six hour video explaining it to you.
Oh, it's not like it's gay as in like ha ha gay.
It's just it's like.
No, no, like it's a romantic love story like Kingdom Hearts is a romantic gay love story
and Riku is the guy.
I, I mean, what do they say about Kyrie then?
Then what of Kyrie?
The thing that's funny is that Kyrie is like kind of the love triangle is not for Kyrie's affection.
It is for Sora's affection and Kyrie and Riku are like both trying to win Sora's heart.
That's that's sort of the way it's framed.
And it's like that makes so much more sense.
It does.
At some point it does seem like, yeah, Sora is really is more interested in finding Riku.
Like even when he finds Kyrie, there's a scene like deconstruction where like he finds Kyrie and he's like, oh, hey, Kyrie.
Like at the end of Kingdom Hearts 2.
It's like we found you.
But then Riku is here and he's like he's crying.
Riku.
Oh my God, Riku.
I can't believe it.
Yeah.
And Kyrie's there.
It's like, OK.
Well, it's because like Riku was like in Dark World because like Riku was in like more danger.
Yeah.
But also.
But yeah.
Yeah.
So this last voicemail is just a picture.
I think it's just a picture of a gummy bear apron.
You know.
Pretty cool apron, I guess.
It's pretty good.
I mean, I would rather they be worms.
I prefer the gummy worm to the gummy bear.
I made a test batch of low sugar gummies because I was thinking, what if I wanted to sell these?
I was thinking like, do they last on the shelf?
And I made some and I kept them in a little tub, a little sealed container, like something
I might sell them in.
And I was disappointed because they're very soft.
Like they're quite soft on the shelf at room temperature.
And that's a bummer.
They kind of like stick together when you try to get them out of the bag.
And it's too bad because I know how to make them firmer, but it makes them taste worse.
So there's an unfortunate trade off there, but I'll might have to make it.
Yeah.
That's all I have to say about that.
They're delicious though.
They're guava flavored.
They're light green guava.
They're just a little soft.
They kind of like fall apart.
Pull on them even a little bit.
That's the last voicemail.
All right.
Let me refresh to see if we get any new ones.
Nope.
No last minutes.
Okay.
Thank you for listening.
I guess we're done for the week.
Three hours, respectable.
You know what?
It's reasonable, healthy.
It's normal.
People asking for five hours.
It's funny because of how stupidly long that is.
In five hours, I could almost explain to you why Riku is gay.
Almost.
That's the scale.
Yeah.
It's three hours.
Three hours is long for a podcast.
I don't think most podcasts run that long.
Some podcasts are 25 minutes.
Yeah.
So we're really providing the value here on this free YouTube channel.
Okay.
Well, I guess anything else before we sign off?
Go to twitch.tv slash Gibbentake to catch the next Fire Emblem stream.
I'm going to be doing that on Saturdays.
I might do them more often if I have a hankering forum.
But yeah.
Okay.
All right.
I guess while you're there, maybe go to twitch.tv slash Saint Comics.
I do intend to start doing more Mega Man again.
Probably I'm thinking Mondays and Fridays are what I would like to do.
Those are days I have free.
So that's what I'm thinking.
And I'll fucking see you in hell.
See you in hell.
Perfect coming party coming soon.
Yeah.
All right, bye.
You'll be away.