Hello, and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's another week. It's another low-energy week, everybody. The streak continues.
No, Nate. No, watch. See you next week. Bye, everybody.
We've got sleepy Tom Oliver here.
We have the tragically, I don't know, Gibbontake who sucks.
Where are you going with that tragically?
I was going to say, I was going to do another synonym for low-energy, but I couldn't think of anything other than low-energy.
Tragically, like asleep, like dead?
In a coma.
Yeah, tragically comatose. Tragically removed from consciousness.
Blip, gone.
Oh, no.
And there's me. You all know. I don't need to say it.
Comic book shipper extraordinaire, Ben Singh.
Oh, yeah. You got my ratings.
Dude, Pogger's moment.
That was Pogger's moment. I was excited. I was excited to see your tweet.
I hope other people will tweet like, oh, look, I just opened up my copy.
Especially, I've been doing drawings, right?
Like sketches and drawings in the cover, right?
For people that paid extra for signed drawing stuff in there.
And some of them are pretty high effort.
And I hope that people will like, it would be very gratifying to me to be like, see on Twitter,
like people take a picture of my drawing in their copy, post on Twitter at me.
I would retweet the shit out of that.
It would be really cool if I could just have like, my feed or just all that.
Yeah, I am unsubtly telling you, hey, I would really appreciate it.
I would think it was cool if I could do, if you do that, you know, if you want to, if you're down.
I'm ready. I'm ready for a flood of that.
Although I probably won't be shipping those out for a little bit because they take a really long time.
I've managed to get like three done today.
Ooh.
And I have like 50 or 60 more to go. I don't know.
I'm glad mine came so quick going like literally 40 minutes down the road from where you are or something like that.
Yeah. Yeah.
Have you done the UK ones? Have you done the Europe?
I didn't. Yeah, I did them by tier.
I have sent out all of them from, okay, every tier that didn't involve me doing like a signature and a sketch.
I have sent out almost all of those except there were like a few in the like both books, $25 tier that were like,
I had, I made a trip to the post office, but I couldn't carry anymore.
So I had to leave like a box of like 20 of them behind.
So a few of them haven't made it out yet.
But for the most part, all the like non signature and non sketch tiers are shipped out and hopefully people get them.
I mean, how long does it take to ship like to the UK? Not more than like a week, right?
No. It's just an envelope.
It depends. It depends. Like international shipping is all fucked now because of the Rona.
They gave me, they gave me a little bit of a hassle.
They gave me a little bit of a hassle of the post office, right?
Because here's my, I'll like, I'll have these boxes, the same boxes that the comics came in from the printer.
I take them out, I put them in envelopes, I put the envelopes back in the boxes.
I put the boxes in stacks and put them on sort of a cardboard pallet.
And then I call an Uber and the Uber shows up and I put it in the trunk and I get them to take me in like the,
the like eight minute drive down the road to the post office because it's too heavy to carry.
And I can take maybe like 50 or 60 envelopes at once.
And then I go in there and I stand in line.
And the first time I get in there, I go up to the post office counter and the lady's just like,
ah, you know, you should have, you could have postmarked these ahead of time.
You know, you could have just put postage on these and use stamps.
And I'm like, I couldn't, I really couldn't have.
Earn your keep wage slave.
I would have had to know to postmark them or to postage them successfully and accurately.
I would have had to know how much they were going to charge me by weight,
which like, I could have done extensive research and like gone and found, oh, okay.
Well, it's technically this class of mail and this is the size and this is the weight.
So calculate, calculate.
Okay, I think this time is how much so I need this much postage,
but I wouldn't have known for sure until I brought it in and gave it to them.
As someone who did all of that for Radcon rewards, it sucks.
You made the right choice passing the baton.
Well, after the first time, because I got the receipt and I was like,
and I was able to look at it and be like, okay, these ones cost this much.
So I did end up was like, okay, give me a whole bunch of postage and I went home and I did, in fact,
put stamps on a lot of them because I was like, based on the previous ones,
I know how much these will cost a ship.
So I don't have to because it takes forever.
I like stand there for like 45 minutes while she like takes like a minute per envelope to like scan it,
type in the information, put the stamp on it, put it in the box, you know, it's very time consuming.
You don't have to line.
And I had people and I had people in line behind me like literally like turn around and walk out
because they didn't because they were so mad to be behind me in line, which I could makes total sense.
But like I got to do it at some point.
Surely surely there's a way to do like bulk sending out of items to people like like that isn't a piece of shit.
Surely there's a way to do that.
I didn't pre-label the Radcon three rewards.
And so what I did is I went to like Postal Center, which is like a business that does like multiple shipping services in from one location.
And so I just went there and none of them were labeled because I wasn't smart enough to pre-label them.
And I was just like, I need this.
And they're like, Oh God, you fucking loser.
Just give them all to us and we'll go through them one at a time in between other orders.
This is going to take us like a week and we'll give you the total when we're done and you come in and you'll pay for them and then we'll ship them out.
So I had to wait like a week for them to like slowly go through them day after day.
And so like one of the people who works there now knows my name because like they mailed all of them and saw my address like 200 times and they want me dead.
Rightfully so.
And they know where you live.
Exactly.
It's not good.
Yeah, I have spent over $1,000 on postage in the last like week or two.
Dude, it's brutal.
It's really brutal.
And it costs because because the envelopes with two books in them, the ones with two books cost like 320 to ship domestically to send an envelope with two books to like anywhere in the Europe or South America or anywhere other than like Canada,
Mexico, U.S. costs like $11 and change.
It's one thing.
One of the Radcon four one envelope with two books in it.
The Radcon four rewards went to some country.
I don't remember what it was, but it was just the pin and the poster and the pin and the poster itself to ship to this country was $52.
Jesus.
And I'm just like, why?
God, why?
Was it because was it in the tube?
No, this was just a tiny poster like the letter sized poster and a pin.
That's that's bizarre.
It was it was criminal, I tell you.
And all the international ones were like $20 to $30 to ship normally.
How do you know how much they weighed?
Because like it's by it's by weight and it's by right.
Okay.
They they the lady at the.
This was on my second day bringing like a big shipment of boxes in to have them post my and this the second day because the first time she got annoyed with me because she was like, you could have just postage these ahead of time.
But she was like, okay, it's kind of understandable for the for the foreign ones because like that varies country to country.
So the next day I brought in mostly just the foreign ones to be like, okay, these are the ones that I can't post.
And then the next day I was like, okay, these ones I all pre stamped and you don't have to scan them.
And that was like, it was really easy.
And I think she really appreciated it.
But the second day I'm handing over these foreign ones to send to other countries.
And like the ladies got a like, it's like a different woman than the usual one is like scanning it.
And she's getting like confused.
And I don't know why.
And I'm telling her like, she's asking me questions about like, like, what like category of shipping and I'm like, I don't know.
I sent these all like yesterday and it was fine.
Like there wasn't any problem.
Like why, why are you asking me like what I am trying to do?
It was why, why is it not simple?
And she like brought the manager over and the manager like flexed a little bit.
I think she wanted to like flex her nuts on me.
And she was like, hmm, what did he say?
What did he say was in these?
Oh, okay.
The books.
It's all paper and bubble wrap.
I'm putting bubble wrap in them.
I'm getting really fancy and a pin or a metal pin.
Like, oh, you know, technically, you know, technically, if there's anything other than paper in there, it counts as a package and not an envelope.
And it should cost like a million fucking dollars to ship it.
And she's just like, you understand that?
And I'm like, yes.
And she's like, okay, and leaves.
And then let's me continue to scan them and ship them as envelopes and not packages.
Like, what was the point?
What was the fucking point of coming over here and asking me to confirm that I understand that she is doing me a big favor by letting me ship these envelopes as envelopes?
That's probably like her one thrill in life at this point.
She has so little reason for existing.
And this is like, she can arguably, she can argue, but she can have an, this is a situation where she can have an impact.
Not a positive or a good impact, but an impact nonetheless.
She has power over you.
She's choosing not to enforce it, but the option is there at any moment.
She could.
Living fear.
I could really, hey, you know, I could really fuck you over right now, right?
You know, I could really fuck your whole day up.
Yeah.
You know.
All right.
Have a good day.
See you tomorrow.
She was so wet after that.
Fortunately, I have not, that was, I only saw her once.
I have not seen her since.
I hope I never do again.
She didn't seem, I don't know.
She didn't seem to be like, she didn't seem like threatening.
She wasn't, but she like, why?
Like, why are you saying this to me?
Like, go away.
The first time in a month, she should be able to like flex her postal center knowledge.
Just like, yes, I can do this.
I was afraid.
I was, I was afraid I would go back and she'd be there and they'd be like, no, no, we warned
you last time.
We warned you last time.
We were going to, we were going to charge you quadruple for these because they're technically
packages because they have.
It's like a links awakening when you steal something from a store and you go back the
next day, they just kill you with lightning.
Right.
I was, um, I was watching a speed run of links awakening the other day and I saw that.
I didn't know that was a thing before, but I, I just so happened to have very recently
discovered, like, found out about the thing you just referenced.
Oh good.
I'm glad.
I'm glad I kept that in my back pocket until right now.
It wouldn't, it would have been wasted before.
Damn.
Hmm.
Um, yeah.
So that's, uh, that's what the, that's what the fucking vapors shipping is like.
It's really, it's really time consuming.
It's takes so fucking long.
Yeah.
Shipping sucks.
Yeah, it does.
I feel like I kind of like it because it's mindless and I don't have to, it's not like,
I have to think about it.
You can ship radcon five then.
Uh, cause let me tell you, you know, four shipping was pretty rough.
If I, if it means I can just like sit at my desk and like address envelopes and like
put on fucking like every GDQ run from the, from the, from the last year on a playlist
and just autoplay it for like days straight.
Like, yeah, share whatever.
No problem.
I'll take it.
That does sound pretty nice.
Yeah.
That's what I've been, that's what I've been doing.
God, I miss mindless work.
All of this creative shit is just too much.
I gotta think about things.
Oh, it's a little bit like a vacation.
Gotta make decisions all the time.
To just, to just do busy work for a long time.
It's like, oh, I don't, I don't, you mean, I don't have to make any decisions.
I don't have to think about what I'm doing.
Thank God.
Sounds like, sounds like just what the capitalist want you to think like.
Well, I can't help it.
I can't, you know, capitalism was designed to prey on, on humanities, uh, uh, worse
creatures.
And here it is doing that to me.
Turning me into a drama.
Turn me into obedient workers.
Oh, God.
I, you know, I, I'm, I'm kind of craving some busy work.
I feel like, like I've been drawing a lot, you know, all that stuff.
And then I stopped.
I was like realizing I was stressing myself out.
It was weird because I like, I had no idea.
And I thought about it for a second.
I was like, oh my God.
I had to stop everything.
Um, but I could, I could quite easily sit down and like turn bell jpe into a PDF.
Like that is a lot of mindless copying and pasting and like getting stills from gifts
and putting them all in pages.
I could do that.
That would be a good use of my time while I'm like low, like creative juices.
I do that when I'm low.
Yeah.
I have things that I can do that are useful when I'm like low creative juices.
Um, in particular, like, um, banking and stuff, like looking at like, and like, like
making notes about like my, my taxes from like 2019 and stuff when I'm, I don't know,
like, because I, because I have to file them by October.
When I'm, when I'm feeling like, yeah, low energy need busy work.
I'm just like, let me just pull up my, my bank statements and like go over that and like
a list, add up some numbers and be like, oh, okay.
And it's great.
It feels, it feels good.
Let me just, let me pay my, let me pay my credit card balance.
Like, mm, mm, delicious.
Uh, let me, let me do some online grocery shopping.
Ooh, do I need hot dogs?
Yes, I do.
Done.
I forgot hot dogs today.
By the way, I ordered groceries and I was like, mm, yes, I'm going to get all this good
stuff and I forgot hot dogs and I can't get them now because I can't just order hot dogs.
I need to order like $35 worth of ship to get free shipping or like.
Where are you ordering from?
Just get $35 worth of hot dogs.
I, I could.
Um, I was using Instacart.
Does Instacart take EBT now or are you just paying with cash with real money?
No, it doesn't.
Um, but I don't, but I don't, I don't get enough EBT that I'm like worried about like
running out or that I'm worried about like, oh, I'll never be able to spend this.
So it's like, uh, whatever.
Uh, I'll just, uh, you know, you know who did start taking EBT?
Um, I think, I think, uh, food stamps.
Oh, right.
Poor people.
I think, I think specifically in response to COVID, you know, who does take EBT now is Amazon.
What?
Yeah.
You can, you can, you can, like it's not everything, but you can buy food on Amazon and like pay for it with EBT.
Oh wait, Ben, did I tell you?
Maybe you already know this, but you can get Amazon Prime for 50% off if you have EBT.
Really?
Yeah.
If you're a Prime member, you can, you can cut your subscription cost in half if you have EBT.
The, I don't, what do you, what do you get from being an Amazon Prime member?
You just get like Prime shipping.
You get like Prime music and Prime video and all that kind of stuff, which I never use.
I just use it because it gives me like good shipping.
The only things I think, I mean, you can sometimes get a discount at Whole Foods, but
like I'm trying not to shop at Whole Foods because like fucking almond milk is twice as
like more than twice as expensive there.
Uh, so it's not.
As someone who worked for Whole Foods, Whole Foods is a scam for white people.
Don't go there.
I wish, it makes me really mad.
It makes me really mad to think about all the money that I have wasted because I had
to shop at Whole Foods just because it's closer and because I didn't want to risk exposure
to COVID by taking a bus to Wegmans like I used to.
Don't you feel like the people who would most likely like not be practicing social distancing
would be the people that's smelling their farts so much they go to Whole Foods?
Whole Foods seems like an epicenter for COVID in my book.
No, I don't know about that.
I think that the Whole Foods is like the liberal elite yuppies who probably are like, oh my
god, if only Hillary had won in 2016.
I'm still with her, you know?
I guess that's true.
That's the kind of person I think.
Random people riding the bus though.
Those people seem scary.
Those are the ones.
I wouldn't be going on the bus.
I have avoided taking the bus.
I did have to take the subway one time since COVID started.
That's even worse.
It was kind of dicey and they would announce over this megaphone like wear a mask at all
times while on the train or whatever.
But there were some fucking blue collar looking guys who got on who were not wearing their
masks.
They didn't even have masks.
They looked at each other.
They heard the say, hey, wear your mask and they noticed each other and they're like,
we're not going to do that.
That's so stupid.
I'm just going to cough on like deliberately.
So yeah, that was on the day that I was coming back.
I was going through the city on my way back from like Cassie's dad's house or whatever
and I stopped.
It was on the 4th of July when I stopped to do the March.
Yes, that was the day when I was like, well, I have to make my way through here somehow
and the train is the best way.
So I did it.
Struggle.
I've been on the bus and a train a couple times.
They've been off peak hours.
So there wasn't that really many people.
Yeah.
The one thing I will say, the train was pretty empty.
There was only like seven or eight people on the most crowded car that I took.
I don't know if it's still like that.
The thing I always think about though is like on the bus when you're like, because the famous
double-decker buses, I was set at the top because I like that.
I like the feeling of looking down upon all the people.
Your rightful place above the peasants.
Yeah, but obviously you need to walk up the stairs and hold the handrail because sometimes
the driver starts driving before you get up the stairs.
And the handrail is like the primary like, if somebody has COVID and they touch this,
the mask is never going to do anything.
You're fucked.
You have to be very vigilant to not touch things with your hands if you can avoid it.
I like sort of do like the wrist, the back of the wrist sort of like balancing technique
and swinging around like the poles sometimes in my elbow.
And I'm sure I look very strange, but at least my hands are safe.
True.
I am very scrupulous about like sanitizing.
Like when I go into a store, like I'll like, you know, pay with a card and like type my
number into the keypad or whatever.
But like as soon as I'm at first thing I do is I bring, I have a big bottle of sanitizer,
which I, which I put green dye in and put an endless war sticker on.
So it's slime.
Fuck yeah.
So I have a big, I have a big bottle of hand sanitizing slime that I carry around in a backpack
everywhere I go and I use it constantly.
I mean, if it looks like slime, I would use it constantly as well.
Yeah.
It's, it was like the best, it was like the best 1099 I ever spent at a CVS by a mile.
So I'm, I'm sanitizing.
I'm sanitizing all day, every day when I'm, when I'm out of the house.
Yeah.
Every time I come home from going somewhere, I'll always wash my hands or use hand sanitizer
or something.
Just be like, you know, I don't want to risk it.
I bring it with me and I do it.
I sanitize every, like every time I go into a store or every time I come out of a store,
like when I, when I take an Uber, like I hand sanitize before I get into the Uber and then
after I get out, you know, make sure not to touch my face at any time in between.
Oh man.
I've taken three Ubers to the post office so far and the second one, the second guy,
the first guy, he had like, he had like a big sort of like minivan and he had like a
big plastic sheet hanging up between like the front seat and the back seat.
So he was like sealed off from like his passengers, which I respect.
I was like, cool.
Second guy, small car.
That's fine.
Wearing his mask improperly, nose out of the mask.
Fuck you.
What an idiot.
You piece of shit.
Stupid.
Yeah.
I hate when people do that.
I've seen a few people, even like employees working at stores doing that.
I'm like, why?
A guy at like the, at like the Italian restaurant that like sometimes me and Munchie have gotten
like pizza at a few times.
He is the same guy.
This guy also, Munchie ordered Buffalo Wings.
The guy gave him, Sauceless came out with no sauce.
That's even worse than not wearing your mask.
What a douche.
Despicable.
And to top it all off, he had his nose out of his mask.
Oh God.
I have not, I have not gone in there since.
It was topped, it was topped with COVID, not with Buffalo sauce.
Because I was so of off, off put by the, by this improper mask usage.
I'm like, fuck, fuck sake.
If you're going to, if you're going to not wear a mask, just commit to the bit and take
it off.
Be a man about it.
Have you seen, have you seen those, or I saw like a post somewhere about like people,
there's like a, there's like fake masks you can buy that are just like mesh that literally
don't do anything.
But it's like, ha ha, if someone tells you to put a mask on, you can put this on and
then it's easy to breathe.
Ha ha.
It's like the only benefit to that is that like I can see your entire face before I punch
it.
I don't, I don't understand.
I don't understand the people that are like, oh, it's hard to breathe in a mask.
It's not.
I have never found it difficult to breathe.
The one thing that does annoy me about it is that some, the ones that hook around my ears
are a little uncomfortable, but now I have a couple that, that like fasten behind my head
and those are perfectly comfortable.
The one thing that sucks about them is that like my breath get catches in it and it fogs
up my glasses.
That's the one thing that I don't like about.
I don't like, like the only reason I could ever imagine to get your nose out is so that
it doesn't like push the air up inside your glasses, but people who have the nose, they
never have glasses.
They're just stupid.
They just can't, they can't handle a tiny bit of uncomfortableness.
It's, it's, people say like it's uncomfortable.
It's hard to breathe.
And I just, I just don't agree.
I do not find it uncomfortable in this place.
Neither do I.
It's like, it's a little bit.
Except for the glasses.
I haven't had a problem with it.
A little bit like warmer.
Yeah.
If I'm already like sweaty, then yeah, I guess, but like, if I'm not.
That's like such a small price to pay for like being on the, you know, the down swing
of this, which we're not.
America is still in the thick of it and always will be.
Massachusetts.
It's all everywhere.
It seems to be like researching everywhere.
It's going to get worse.
India just reported the highest number of new cases in a single day ever of any country.
So yeah, it's not Massachusetts is still, it's, it's low.
It's low, but it's higher than it was like a month ago.
So, you know, it's not going away.
That curve.
God damn it.
We've, we've more or less flattened the curve here in the, in the, in the base state.
The base state.
It is.
It is the, it is the base state.
That's all.
Fuck.
That's so good.
That's genius.
You're a genius.
I have my moments.
What can I say?
I can coin a phrase with the best of them.
I'm going, I'm going.
I'm going to take that moment of genius and put it on a shirt and sell it on the PCP store
so that we all have to split it and you can't argue with it.
That's, that's fine.
Cause you, you set it on the podcast so it belongs to all of us.
That's fair.
That's how it works.
But what would it even be?
Like Massachusetts is the base state.
It's just, it's just a silhouette of Massachusetts and it just says base state underneath it
in comic sans.
And that's it.
All right.
It's a little different than I was envisioning.
That's the, that's the shirt.
All right.
What more do you need?
It's fair enough, fair enough.
Good to wear on top of your, I'm just feeling cool or just being cool t-shirt.
You know, also in comic sans.
I'm just being Massachusetts.
I saw, did you see that meme going around on Twitter that was like, um, draw yourself
in what you're wearing right now?
I saw that multiple times.
It was way too lazy to do it.
I did that.
I saw it first time when I was in bed naked and I was like, ha ha.
No clothing.
Sick.
Somebody, um, wait, uh, uh, you know what?
I'll, I'll, I'll report a name.
I will, I will name names.
Uh, it was, uh, I saw it was done by Stefan, Stefan Tantana, who did the meme and they
just, they drew themselves wearing the, I'm the reason people are dying shirt.
And I thought that was fucking epic.
Yeah.
So I had, had to get on the PCP Twitter and retweet that because I thought that was pretty
sick.
I could hear a tragic story of someone wearing that shirt to school and getting like suspended
because of supporting violence or something done like that.
Hey, if you, hey, oh, oh, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're Republican parents sending
you back to school, uh, in the middle of a pandemic.
Hey, uh, go to the PCP, uh, uh, uh, uh, Teespring store by the, I'm the reason people are dying
shirt.
Get yourself suspended so you don't have to go anywhere.
We'll get you out of all that bullshit and just keep wearing it every time you get unsuspected.
Just go back in and be like, back.
Then just buy more PCP merch and buy that.
Just buy another shirt and wear both shirts.
It can even be like, like fast food for the occasion.
You can just wear it while coughing, uh, sporadically.
And then like, is it a COVID shirt or is it a PCP reference?
We'll never know.
Dude, new PCP shirt design idea.
Big bold letters, just white, uh, black on white.
I have COVID.
I, nobody will fuck with you anymore.
Does anyone sell those?
Probably.
They can't.
That can't be me.
Hmm.
What's the thing?
Be patient.
I have autism.
I have COVID.
Be patient.
Oh, man.
Uh, well, that, that'll be on the storefront.
Um, by the time you're listening to this, uh, of listeners.
So, uh, a link in the description, I think, right?
Yeah.
We probably have the link somewhere in the description to our Teespring.
Which we don't plug enough, by the way.
We got great stuff.
We really don't.
I'm not good at chilling merch.
We really don't have great stuff.
No, me either.
Well, it's just sort of like it.
But we could be better.
You know, the t-shirts, you wear them and you have them.
But, uh, and, and you wear them and you should buy them.
I don't know how to do it either.
I actually, maybe I am kind of good at chilling merch because I sold, sold a bunch of those
yang shirts, sold a, I sold a bunch of the, uh, I sold at least, I think I sold one of
the phantom horn feel the burn shirts.
I sold all those, uh, uh, cancel Ben shirts, you know, a handful of those.
Uh, once, once in a while, once in a while, when I put my mind to it, I can, I can chill
a shirt.
That's the trend.
You got to respond to people on Twitter who are wearing the bullshit masks and then mention
that they can buy the I have COVID t-shirt and they'll probably get kicked out of it.
For really, you really want to make it where the fake mesh mask and the I have COVID shirt
and just go around really complete to the look, you know, just go, just go everywhere.
That's how you show up on your first day of school.
Okay.
What, what font?
What font is I have COVID?
Oh no.
Um, impact.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
I like that.
Just the words.
Yeah.
And no PCP like branding at all.
It's just, it's just, if you want to make a statement, buy our shirt.
It sure does.
It sure does make a statement of some kind.
Okay.
Well, I feel like we've, we've really hit, we've really struck something vital and true
today.
We've made, we've made progress.
We've, we've created something.
We've brought something out of creative juices yet coming up with all these great shirt ideas.
I think it's because I've taken a little break.
It's, it's, it's always good to do that.
I just don't know like the, the, the, the frequency at which it is like actually beneficial
because you can't take too long of a break because then it's hard to get the wheels turning
again later.
Yeah.
I am, I have been, I haven't only been doing envelopes, I have been working on a little
thing, a little, a little slime and punishment related project that I'm going to not, I may
have talked about it before, but I'm going to like stop talking about it.
Cause I don't want to like, I don't know.
I feel like it might be a little while before it's done.
And I don't want to have a situation where it's like the finale where I talk about it
for months and months.
And then I feel stupid when it finally comes out.
And I'm like, this shouldn't have taken as long.
I just, it's, you know what?
Phantom horn reviews, um, slime and punishment.
Phantom horn reviews, the slime and punishment finale.
Like TBAP episode, uh, 239 or whatever.
Yes, I'm ready.
Uh, yes, yes.
And, oh, speaking of TBAP, I feel like mentioning on the show that just that thing about how
the right opinion mentioned TBAP.
Oh, right, right, right.
Some video about like scammers that steal YouTube channels and sell them.
I guess he found, I guess he fucking found a listing for the TBAP channel and someone
responded to it.
Like, hey, I bought this channel, but then it went away.
What the fuck?
Presumably because YouTube gave it back to us from whom it was stolen.
Yeah.
LaMalle.
Uh, very, very funny.
And, and, and it pissed me, it pissed me right the fuck off because he shows TBAP on these,
TBBBAP, but he says TBBAP like everybody fucking does because nobody can read that third B.
People's eyes just glide right off it.
Like, it's like, they can't see it.
It's, it's like, it's like, it's like.
Fake fan, bro.
Fake fan.
I just, I just, I just don't understand why people don't see the third B. There's three
of them for fuck's sake.
Everyone's just in such a hurry.
It's not, it's not two brothers bitch about ponies.
It's two best brothers bitch about pony.
Cagged phantom, like teeth and gums.
Of course.
Uh, wait.
Oh, Gib, you said you were taking a, you're taking a break during that break.
I'm delighted to see that I successfully got you into Mr. Boop.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
You talked about this on the, the heckles for shackles Minecraft streams that we do
every so often.
Yes.
Which I have started to commit to doing more often because we got this whole fucking
Minecraft server that has all this like awesome shit in it.
It has all this like really cool stuff.
And like, I get in there.
Showcase, like a showcase, like standalone showcase video edited like, look at all this
cool shit you can do in the Minecraft server.
Maybe you should like do it.
We, we haven't done a edited video, but Marin Pan did make a video explaining how to get
the server running.
I think he looks at a few things.
He should like flies around.
How to get the server running is one thing, but like just, just for instance, the last
um, yeah,
It was an intro video that like did show some of the stuff they had, but I, maybe I'm wrong.
Oh, okay.
I haven't, I haven't seen that, but um, yeah, this past, this past time I was, um, I spent
the whole stream trying to fight my way through the, the, the lethal Aurora mage Jim and face
off against mages team, which I, I, well, I won't spoil how it ends.
But, but it was like, it was really involved and it was really irritating sometimes cause
there was like a lot of shit to do with like the Minecraft mods that I don't understand
because I'm a stupid boomer.
Um, but if you know how Minecraft works, there was like a lot there that like Marin Pan had
to be like, no, Ben, no, you gotta, you gotta do the, no, no, go back to that other thing.
You missed it.
No, look, just follow the instructions.
There's a sign right there.
Just read the sign and do what it says on the sign.
You fuck.
Um, but I, but I got there.
I got there eventually.
Um, and I built a Minecraft house.
I, building is cringe battle collect, building a Pokemon team is based and I got my contrary
milestone.
I bought, I got my contrary Malamar and I got my, oh, and I got my new, uh, my new, uh,
my custom age slash with phantom force.
That thing is sick.
Phantom.
And it's huge phantom force.
So phantom horns.
Uh, it's so big.
It's like 10 feet tall and it looks like a fucking bloody mess because it's like custom black
texture with like veins in it.
It's crazy looking.
Uh, it's so good.
It's very exciting for me.
I wish, I wish I could convince myself to care about Minecraft trying really hard.
It doesn't work.
But can you care about Pokemon?
Uh, maybe.
Okay.
What about both of them together?
This thing, I think I may be like, and this thing I don't like, put them together.
What do you get?
Put them together and mmm.
It's the definition of more than the sum of its parts.
You know, that's right.
Synergy.
We've got, we've got to leverage our synergies to create brand recognition.
PCP Minecraft, putting the sin in synergy.
And that's, that's what we've done here.
Um, but anyway, anyway, no, I just wanted to be, I just wanted to celebrate.
That you, uh, got into, uh, Mr. Booth.
What are your impressions of Mr. Booth?
Um, all right.
So Mr. Booth, uh, I got up to date.
So I'm eagerly awaiting the, the, the next update might be a little behind.
It might be like a week behind actually.
Uh, it's like Mr. Booth.net.
And it is, uh, as it, it's like, um, it's a comedy thing.
And it's like unassuming, but, uh, but it's like.
It's farcical to the point of almost seeming sincere, which is really fun.
Yeah.
Um, the, the story is about this artist.
Tom, are you familiar with Mr. Booth?
I'm not.
I'm hearing about it for the first time right now.
Okay.
So there's, there's this artist who, um, is the creator of the comic he's drawing.
And he, uh, he calls himself Mr. Booth.
And he's married to Betty Boop, the cartoon character.
And he thinks she is so hot and he talks about how hot she is.
And he talks about how much he hopes she doesn't leave him.
And she says, no, I won't leave you.
And then, and then thought bubble, she says, oh my God, he's so hot.
And then he smiles to the camera is like, yeah, she's so hot.
I can't believe she's my wife.
Things like that.
I can't, I can't believe I get to have sex with my wife.
Now I understand why Ben is into this.
This is such a band core thing.
What the fuck does that mean?
You're into all this weird fucking cringe shit.
Oh, that's no.
It's not cringe.
You are.
It is.
I mean, it's.
Okay.
I understand how, I understand how it sounds.
I can see what you're saying, but it's not like, it's not like Sonichu where it's like,
oh, this, this weird person.
No, it's very, very self aware.
No, it's, it's completely self aware.
It's deliberately funny.
And it's, and it's awesome.
Okay.
It's like if a family guy joke just never, ever stopped, like it just kept going.
It does.
If you had not seen it and you just heard the description, I could see how you would
think that it was the product of some like deranged person, like the guy who made that
song about Reshiram.
You know what I'm talking about?
Oh yeah.
The guy, the guy who sang the song about how he's married to Reshiram.
Yeah, it's not, it's not, it's like, it's, it's parodying people like that, but is,
is totally self aware.
And he, he cranks up the ridiculousness of stuff like that.
And he introduces so much like nuance that you wouldn't expect into, into a whole thing
like that.
But it's also still like goofy, silly, stupid at the same time.
It's like,
Like it never, it never breaks the con, the central conceit that like, well, I guess it,
it does go off in a couple of different directions.
It never breaks the conceit that like it's completely reasonable for these characters
to just like mug the camera and say, my wife is so hot.
And then Betty Boop, my husband is so hot, I'll never leave him.
I sure hope my wife, Betty Boop doesn't leave me.
And then, and I also, we can have sex, which is pretty hot.
Yeah.
And that's the, that's the fourth panel.
But it, it's like, you know, there, there, there are developments.
There's a whole, it's, it's, it's, it's got a whole cast of characters.
You know, it's got, it's got luminaries such as Goku, Mickey Mouse, Sonic the Hedgehog,
Dr. Sonic the Hedgehog.
Oh yeah.
And there's, there's Bugs Bunny that works at Amazon after a time.
And they won't let him pee.
And then, and then Amazon.
Yeah.
The running gag is that Amazon won't let him pee.
Is this like Tails gets trolled?
Or is this like on that?
It is exactly like Tails gets trolled.
Okay.
So it, it absolutely is a Ben Core product.
I was right on the money from the beginning.
Okay.
It's, it's, it's like that.
But like, it's, I mean, it does not come across as like something that you think is real.
Like you could easily understand that, oh, it's, it's obviously like a funny joke that this guy is making this comic.
It's like, okay.
The characters, the characters in the story.
You don't ever feel like there's like a, maybe he is deranged actually.
There's like, there is what Tails gets trolled.
I mean, it's, it's, it's almost like, like what Tails gets trolled, it's like he wanted to put the characters in there.
Like he wanted, you know, Timo from League of Legends to be in the story.
So he put Timo in there, but then he didn't have any idea what Timo would do.
So he just kind of like has Timo, you know, make some funny jokes and then, and then like die off screen for no reason.
And that's Timo.
It's like the reverse in, in Mr. Boop.
Mr. Boop.
Mr. Boop is like, he just, he needs, he needs supporting characters to be like his roommates or like, you know, the person who, you know, wants, like, gives him like sex advice or whatever.
And he will, and he, but he will just like, for no particular reason, he will make that supporting character just be Sonic the Hedgehog or, or Bugs Bunny or, or whatever.
Or, or girl version, Ranma or Gina or Gina from Porco Rosso or whatever.
Gina, Nina, whatever.
And, you know, they're, they're just, they're, they're just there.
And it's just exists, exists in this, I think it is probably takes place in the exact same universe as Tails gets trolled, though, if I'm being honest.
Yeah.
I don't, there's no contradiction.
It's just a timeline thing.
There's one takes place, one takes place earlier in the timeline and the other takes place later.
God, this is too complicated for my baby brain.
But it sounds sick and I'll have to baby check it out if I ever remember after this conversation.
It's very sick.
And the guy who makes it, he does like video bits too.
There are like,
Here's Mr. Boop.net.
You can immediately see the, the, the comedy.
A couple of the, a couple of the updates are like him doing like a fake interview show where like a guy asks him about like his creative process.
And he's like, yeah, well, I don't, I don't even remember, but he, but he, you know, he talks about how he is in fact married to Betty Boop in real life and how the comic is just an autobiography.
And in the comic, he talks about how like, oh my, my, one of my favorite lines is the one, if there's an offhand like throwaway line about how like,
you know that me making these comics about our marriage is part of our thing.
And like it's part of what gets me off about it.
Oh my God.
It's part of it.
The website's incredible, by the way.
I just can't recommend Mr. Boop.
If you read the first one, it's, I mean, it very quickly gets like, like, like, like intrigue.
Like it's almost immediately that he's, he's talking about like, I'm never going to get a divorce.
Like, oh, what does that imply that he's saying that?
Oh no.
But, but now, but now he's so worried about what if he divorces his wife, Betty Boop?
Like what's, what's he going to do?
He's, he's fraught.
He needs to, how's he, how's he going to tackle this?
This, this next hurdle on their path to happy marriage.
What's wrong?
Betty Boop thought bubble.
She's my wife.
I know that was the moment where I was like, okay, this is really funny.
Incredible.
She is my wife.
I can't believe I get to have sex with my wife.
God, I hope my 90 year old wife will let me have sex with her.
Oh God.
Incredible.
I love it.
I honestly feel like doing like a version of this, but with me and Vriska.
Because it's like, it's too, it's too correct.
It's too like, exactly the same.
I mean, Vriska is already canon to Mr. Boop.
She is.
One, one panel.
I got such the wrong impression of this.
Cause you, the first one you linked in the chat was the, the, the homestuck one.
And I've never read homestuck.
So it did nothing for me.
I can, I can only imagine.
Yeah.
Like not, not having the context for what this comic is like and reading that as like,
yeah, this is the newest update in, in this comic I'm reading.
Yeah.
Carcat.
Come on.
Please just suck me off.
Okay.
Yeah.
No, I, I get you.
I get where you're coming from.
Yeah.
This is happening.
Gotta leave with the first comic.
That's much more effective.
This is happening at the same time as Mr. Boop in the same canon.
Thanks.
Jack Noir to himself.
It's all connected.
Okay.
I just had, I just had to take a moment to appreciate it.
Do you want to take a moment to appreciate Canada and how they're probably going to implement
UBI like soon, apparently.
Uh, you mentioned this before we started recording.
Yeah.
And I, and I am still kind of shocked about it.
I don't, I don't know anything about it other than I saw a tweet and it could be a complete
lie, but, uh, the guy has emojis and a check mark.
So maybe, maybe he knows what he's talking about.
Can you, can you, can you say what it is?
Can you give the backstory for the listeners?
Uh, I mean, sure.
No.
No, I cannot.
No?
Yeah.
Fuck the listeners.
Yeah, yeah.
No, I just, I just scrolled through Twitter and I saw this tweet from Scott Santens, a
writer and unc, of unconditional basic income UBI advocate with a crowdfunding to basic income
via Patreon.
Uh, so he's got a check mark.
He's like a real guy and he's like huge UBI news flooding out of Canada today that a
basic income guarantee for all Canadians has now become the ruling party's number one
policy resolution to adopt at their national convention in November.
Will Canada be the first to adopt basic income after all?
It's now more possible.
I don't know.
I mean, it's strange to say that like it's become the number one platform of the ruling
party.
I don't really know much about Canadian politics.
I'm not, I'm not exactly sure what that means, but it does make me a little suspicious that
this is like a UBI guy saying this.
It's very strange, right?
But, but at the same time, like it would be interesting because like Canada had like a
way better stimulus program than America did.
So I guess that probably woke a lot of people up over there like, Hey, this is kind of a
good deal.
I heard that, yeah, I heard that like around the time, around the time that like we were
like Americans were hearing that like, Oh yeah, we're all going to get the $1,200 stimulus.
I, you know, Canada, I thought slime is Canadian and he said like, Yeah, everyone in Canada
is getting like $2,000 a month, you know, Canadian dollars, but still, in just like,
in just like, you know, stimulus money or like relief money or whatever.
And like, I had assumed that that would be temporary, but apparently it's still happening
and I can't fucking believe it.
I think it's still happening.
That blows my mind so hard.
That's crazy.
Imagine.
How do they do it?
They probably just, I mean, I can only imagine, I don't know exactly, but they're probably
just paying for it.
Maybe they're taxing the rich or something.
I don't know.
Like maybe they're paying for it and then pushing the cost of that onto something else down
the line.
Like, I can't imagine that they could successfully tax the rich just suddenly just because they
wanted to.
Yeah, it can't be that simple.
They're probably just like creating more debt as everybody is.
They might, they, you think they're just going into like some crazy deficit or whatever?
I mean, that's what we're doing.
Um, are we?
Yeah, we're just, we're just, we've like doubled the national debt.
It's like more than our GDP now.
Like there's no way to pay it off.
Lamal.
Yeah.
Um, that's, it's fine.
I'm sure that's fine.
My big worry is if we ever get past this inflation is going to hit us like a fucking
tidal wave and the only good thing about massive inflation will be my student loans will all
of a sudden be pennies.
And I'll just be like, they're not worth as much as a loaf of bread.
But so is everything I own.
Exactly.
So it's just like, you know, ups and downs, you know, starving.
But it all comes out in the wash.
Well, speaking of massive inflation.
Oh, God.
Over on the.
Are you going to talk about your discord server?
Yeah.
Is this about Big Titty's Mommy Milkers?
Big Boobies Mommy Milkers.
Get it right there.
Sorry.
It is, it is, it is bustling in there.
It is burgeoning.
It is jiggling in there.
Everyone's, everyone's having a great time squeezing and jiggling.
It's great.
That's all I wanted to say.
I saw an opportunity to talk about like inflation.
Looks looks like there's at least like a hundred people in there.
Incredible.
What a good launch.
Congratulations.
Who would have thought who would have thought that that tits would prove like a big box office
success.
You know, it's really riling up the industry, you know, this new.
I had my doubts that there was a market for such a thing, but it shows what I know.
It, it turns out that being horny on main is actually cool and everyone wants to do it.
And now we've made like a sanctuary for being horny.
We can just be like, I had boobs are cool guys.
Is it, I mean, are people actually horny in there?
Are people actually going in there to like, to like jack it?
You know, I mean, I see there's, I think, I think there's like tongue in cheek, like
horny-ness, but like, there's not a lot of like, there's no role playing.
I see the NSFW posting in the big boo bodega, you know, for sure.
For sure.
Obviously.
And that's good.
I encourage it.
Sure.
Yeah, it's not so much of like a, like a sexual deviancy thing.
It's just it, because the bot is based around you having a like breast size based around
some number that just keeps going up.
If you squeeze in the titty bar that is just, there's a lot of like, you know, it's just
like endless war.
It's a video game and it's very easy.
And there's a lot of like.
It's, it's just like endless war.
Yeah.
You just sort of like, there's, there's a framework through which conversations can begin.
And people are just really enjoying that.
And it's fun.
Yeah, pretty cool.
When do we, when will our, when will our, the endless war dev team be receiving their
royalties though?
We're going to, we're going to charge you for that milk.
We're going to charge by the gallon.
I'll just, you know, I'll just like allow you to like publicly execute red man or something
like kill him off.
Well, I mean, all right.
Okay.
I'm satisfied.
This is all a ploy.
It was all just a ploy to be able to execute red man.
Gun girl does it all the time.
It's well, great fun.
Sure.
Um, somebody.
Oh, I think some, I don't remember who I'm sorry, but somebody requested for their vapors
like sketch, right?
Sketch and signature tier or whatever.
Uh, I think someone asked me to draw big as in your, your, your character big.
Oh, wow.
Uh, doing something or holding something.
I forget.
I didn't, I didn't get to it yet.
So I don't remember.
But yeah, so I'm going to be stealing that one from, from you.
Cool.
Whoops.
No, that's all right.
That's all right.
People can draw big.
In fact, I encourage it.
Um, I, I'm, I'm going like, I'm going like pretty all out.
I'm drawing like full like color, uh, like drawings in like the, the bottom of the, the
uh, uh, forward page, uh, with like Copic markers that I use literally once a year
for this, this exact purpose and no other.
I have like hundreds of dollars worth of Copic markers and this is the only thing I do with
them, but it's worth it.
Um, it's great.
I'm a genius.
Someone asked me to draw slow King and I did it and I shaded it and I colored it and he's
giving a thumbs up and it was like, yeah, that was the last thing I did before we started
recording this episode.
Hmm.
What are we talking about?
Uh, I don't know.
I interrupted to talk about something about like, uh, like, like, like, like, like Canada
and tits, you know, just the usual fare on the PCP.
Oh yeah.
I just, I just can't believe.
I just can't believe that like the tooth that like everyone's just getting like, maybe,
maybe they are just going into crazy deficit.
I don't know, possibly, but like, maybe it's fine and doesn't matter and it's worth it.
Maybe it's still a good thing.
I have no idea.
What was that?
What was that fucking video Tom, you tweeted or mentioned, um, that was on Twitter about
like how banking is like, doesn't make any sense.
Oh, it's all like, like everything is held up.
Everything is held up by everything else and there's no like foundation.
Hey, was it okay?
Deficit is like, is money or something?
Oh yeah.
Wait, wait, wait.
Was it, was this video, was this video like, did it sort of look like, was it like a cartoon
thing and like the main like metaphor of it was like 300?
Maybe.
I've seen like three videos talking about banks to a long time ago and one relatively recently.
One I remember most is if you watch Zeitgeist 2, there's a whole section on banks and debt
and how fucked up it is.
I don't know how voraciously that was researched, but it paints a pretty grim picture.
Like how debt is currency and how everything cycles around and it's like.
Every dollar that you've ever owned is owed to somebody and that dollar has interest attached
to it.
So if all the principle of the money goes away, there's still outstanding debt.
So there's more debt than there is money, so it can never be paid down.
And so foreclosures and home and you know, shit is inevitable.
It's part of the system.
And it's really, and then there's fractional reserve banking, which is super fucked.
Banks make money out of nothing.
They're allowed to loan out 10 times the amount of money they actually have because there's
never going to be, everyone's never going to collect all their money at the same time.
So they just create money out of thin air and add to the currency value and stuff because
they're allowed to lend out more than they actually have.
It's super fucked.
And that's why like when markets crash, people like run to the banks to get all their money
and everybody withdraws at the same time and they don't have enough money to pay all the
actual money that they have because they've loaned all of it out to other people.
And that's where like bad things happen.
Yeah, it's super fucked.
It's too intelligent for me.
I'm saying it really badly right now.
So don't yell at me in the comments.
Oh, you forgot this obvious part you retard, but like it's a nightmare and it's scary and
I don't like it.
It was, it was enlightening because I never really thought about it on like the largest
scale of how money has got out of hand and I don't think it doesn't seem to be a way
to fix it so that bad things stop happening.
Exactly.
Like crashes will just eventually happen.
It seems like this seems like a great time to again plug a debt the first 5000 years by
David Graber, an extremely interesting book that it, it taught, you know, it's about like
it touches on the fact that like money is basically just debt notes.
Yes.
And like and like the myth that like before money, we had like a barter.
They use like a barter system, which is like not really true.
And, and how like other cultures like pre money cultures like conceived of debt in like a
different way and like like the introduction of like currency just completely like change
the way we saw like human transactions and whatever.
Sad news though, the guy who wrote that book and a bunch of other really good books and
he was like an awesome like, like, what's the word?
What was the 1% protesters was like the Wall Street Occupy Wall Street.
Occupy Wall Street.
He was like an Occupy Wall Street guy.
He just died like a couple like a week or two ago at the age of only like 59 or something.
David Graber, a based fucking dude and you know, probably could have lived and written
a whole bunch more books, but no, he just died.
I'm not sure of what maybe COVID.
I don't think I'm not sure if they've said exactly what what happened to him, but he's gone.
Yeah, it's a bummer.
2020 hits keep on coming.
Hmm.
I feel a little weird bringing this up, but I feel like I want to do it.
I feel like I should do it.
I don't know if you saw a comment on our last episode of someone commenting to say that their
their brother, who was a big fan of the PCP died.
Yeah, like a month like this month.
Yeah, the really, really sad.
I don't know how to feel about it exactly.
I asked I asked them like if we would know the name and they said they gave a screen name
that might have been and I didn't recognize it.
But apparently this person was like a donor and a patron.
So I feel like we might have like seen their name and like know maybe known of them at
least a little bit.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I thought about maybe like going through like Patreon records and like seeing if I could
find the name or whatever.
Yeah, I'd really like to know because it's like you never I mean you always know like
statistically speaking blah blah blah amount of people die and like it is a large enough
audience.
How many subscribers of mine have died?
I don't know.
I like it's you know, it's a fact, but you never like ever think about it until it's like
an individual is like shown to be, you know.
Yeah, there was.
It's terrible.
I remember I think I have a memory and I don't know.
I could be imagining some or all of this, but I feel like I have a memory from like years
ago so long ago in fact that I'm not even sure if this was like on a PCP video or it
might have even been on a TBAP video.
But I feel like I remember someone commenting to say that like they something about them
like a terminal condition and that like they only you know they weren't going to be alive
for like a particularly long time.
I don't know if this rings a bell.
I feel like I remember that from a PCP episode, but I don't know how long ago it was.
It was a little while back, but no.
That definitely happened.
Okay, okay, cool.
Well, I don't know.
I wonder if this was the same part.
Well, it's cool that I'm not delusional.
I don't know.
I wonder if this was that person or unrelated.
What a nightmare though.
What a fucking...
Shout out to this anonymous fan, I guess.
Apparently talked about us enough that there was it their sister?
Yeah.
Yeah, that their sister knew about us enough to search us up.
And leave that comment.
I feel bad.
Obviously they liked the show and they liked us.
I hope that she is not listening to this and like feeling mortified that we're discussing it.
I apologize, but I don't know.
God.
I felt like it was worth mentioning as a point of interest, if nothing else.
Yeah.
I have thought about this.
I've thought about like someone in like, I don't know.
There's like, you know, there's like 500 people in my Discord.
There's like over a thousand people in the Endless War Discord.
These are people that like, you know, that I see like talking and these are part of like a community.
And I've thought like, what if something like, there's enough people that it's not that impossible that like someone in there could just like get some, some kind of thing could happen.
Like they could, someone could have an accident.
Someone could develop some medical condition and like die.
And it would be like, I don't know.
I would go from like, oh, maybe this person used to post here and then like, oh, remember that person?
Oh yeah.
They're dead.
Right.
And like, oh geez.
And I'm like, I don't know.
I get in the, I was thinking about this a while ago being like, I'm glad that that hadn't happened yet.
And I guess now it has.
But I guess it's inevitable.
I guess it's inevitable that it is, you know, this kind of thing eventually happens.
And I mean, I know people who've, do you guys know people who've died in real life?
Like people you like knew at like school or anything?
Oh, I've known, I've known a couple people.
Yeah.
Not at school.
And I mean, I mean, I've known people who have died and I've gone to their funeral.
Yeah.
Actually, my brother, one of his friends died in a murder.
Oh, which was like weird.
He just heard about it one day, like after school had finished and they'd got, you know, gone to like college and stuff.
He heard about his school friend.
I was like, oh shit.
That was a weird, like a very unusual circumstance.
It wasn't, it wasn't like while they were in school together.
No, no, no.
His classmate was murdered.
Okay.
Still though.
I had, um, this is visit grim, but whatever.
I had a, I had a friend who in college who I heard years later had like just gotten married.
I think, I think they had just gotten married.
They were like on there and he was on his like honeymoon to like the Bahamas or something with his like new wife.
And he drowned.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
Um, that was cool.
That wasn't cool, Ben.
You can't say that on live TV.
When I say that it's cool, I mean the opposite.
Obviously I'm being.
You're being all flustered right now.
I'm being completely sincere.
Uh, I don't know.
I don't know.
It's, you know, what do you, what do you even say about something like that?
It's, it's too, it's too fucked up.
It's, I mean, death is a comes to us all and like all that stuff.
No, we got it.
We got to, we got to get myself.
I have thought myself about like various moments where it's like, what if I died and I, all of my friends online didn't know.
Dude, I think about that all the fucking time.
Like what, I haven't driven a will.
Like where, who would get my video games?
Like, like what, what, what would happen to all of my stuff?
All the stuff, all the files on my computer.
Like would, would people look through them to find out what's going on?
They're going to find my internet history.
God, so screwed.
I mean, it's not like I'm worried cause I'd be dead.
But it's like, it's just like, what should I put like systems in place to do anything about that?
Or should I just let whatever happens happen?
There's like people that I know that I talk to online, right?
But I'm not like super close with.
They're like, oh, if I just like died, they'd never know.
They just thought I turned into a dick.
That's so fucked up to think about.
Hmm.
I don't know.
That's not usually, when I think, when I think about dying, that's usually not the part that I'm preoccupied with.
I mean, that's, that's like after I have like a, you know, 45 minute existential crisis on the futility of life and like how nothing matters.
And I just kind of curl up in a ball and like really just like start thinking too harshly on like the inevitability of mortality.
And then I guess we like think about like Deus Ex.
I'm like, please, please can we get robot body soon?
Please God, nanomachines now.
I want to be Senator Armstrong.
Please God.
And then I like have a tiny little glimmer of hope that maybe Elon can save us.
Maybe capitalism can serve a greater good.
Elon is, is, he's making a fucking moon base that him and his, that him and his pedophile friends or whatever.
I'm sorry, that's, it's not hashtag not all billionaires or whatever.
You know, they, they can escape and leave the rest of us to fucking die.
That's the whole thing.
That's like the problem is they're like, oh, like if we ever get, I was having a conversation about this with somebody recently.
I don't remember who it was.
And I'm like, yeah, if we get transhumanism, it's going to like, you know, it's just going to make classism even worse.
Because then you're just going to have the, the immortal, like neo feudalists who just own the mortal populace and dangle the elixir of immortality over their heads to keep them in line.
And like only the top 1% will not know death.
And then the ruling class will never go away.
Hillary Clinton will never die.
Oh my God.
Hey, hey, Elon, why don't you elongate my lifespan, you dick?
Hey, why don't you elongate my dick as well while you're at it, please?
It will be just like Homestuck, where the trolls that are the ruling class live for thousands of years and the trolls on the lower humo spectrum, the slaves, they live much shorter lifespans and they die real quick.
Viewers, I just want you to-
It's already a little like that, but it could be a lot worse and it will be too.
It's already kind of a little like that through like, um, dynasties and, you know.
Yeah, and also like, you know, health insurance, Lamal.
Oh wait, you're a Britbonger, you don't know.
You don't know about private health insurance.
What's a hospital?
I don't know.
Nothing, don't worry about it.
I don't need them over there.
Viewers, I just want you to know every time someone mentions Homestuck on here, just imagine, uh, uh, Jay from Red Letter Media, like his reaction every time Mike mentions Star Trek, that's me.
God, not again.
It comes up all the time.
I have no idea what they're talking about.
I can see it now.
I can see him cursing his little chipmunk lips and looking right directly into the camera like, hmm.
That's me every time for the last five years or however long we've been doing this podcast.
Mike believes in ghosts.
I had a fucking terrifying realization a few days ago when I realized I've watched every episode of Best of the Worst.
I'm like, oh, God, no.
That's good though, those are fun.
They're super fun, but like, it was like.
I have probably watched them multiple times.
I had a kick, I had a kick lately where I just put them on.
Yeah, me too.
Like, lately it's been, lately it's been GDQ.
Before that it was like Red Letter Media and I just watched like everyone on autoplay.
And I just put them all on, but I've been watching them out of order.
Uh, and so when I realized there were none left.
I mean, why watch them in order?
I mean, yeah, I just kind of was, because they eventually had a playlist, but I'm like, at first I was like, oh, God, there's no more.
And then I was like, oh, God, how many hours of that have I watched?
It was like the same feeling finishing Campaign 1 of Critical Role.
Like that was like 124 hour videos and I binged all of them.
Dude, I've got a big number for you.
On Water Warcraft, you can do slash played to see how long you have played on that particular character.
And on my main guy, because I was just doing stuff, I was like, I wonder how long it's been.
Um, so this is like total time logged in playing the game or, you know, just logged in 119 days.
And that is over a course of like 10 years.
I started playing in like 2009.
So more than 10 years.
So that's, that's still a long time though.
119 days in on that character, not even just all the characters, just that one.
That's a big number.
That's like, that's like the time that's like all the time you would be awake for like half a year.
Right?
Yeah, yeah.
Because like half a year is like about, it's like 180 something days.
And then like, you know, you're awake for about two thirds of a day.
So like two thirds of that would be about like 110, 120 hours.
So yeah, that's like the way you're waking life for like half a year or something.
You know, pretty good.
It's funny though, because it's like, it's a big number.
And I know I've played this game a lot and I've, you know, done a lot of grinding, a lot of achievements.
I've got over 9000 achievement points.
I remember what I, when I got the achievement for getting over 9000 achievement points.
Amazing.
And I'm like, damn, I've put a lot of stuff into this.
But you know what?
My mind, I like, I like this.
I like this game.
It's good.
The only thing I may, maybe regret is the amount of money that the, you know, the months of game time I've spent.
But it's probably not that much.
It's like, I mean, what is it like $10 a month?
So yeah, something like that.
I mean, I used to, when I first started, I did like the discount for like multiple months.
Like I got like 12 months for less, like eight pounds a month or something.
It might, I don't know.
In the past, it might have bothered me to be like, oh man, that's like, what, that's like $120 a year or whatever.
And like, oh no, but like, I don't know.
I spend like, I feel like,
I spend more than, I spend like probably like two or $300 on like just food and necessities a month anyway.
So like, what?
Yeah.
Like when you're, when you're a youngster, when you're a little boy, you get like pocket money, maybe.
And you think about like how much things cost you, like the first time, I will never forget this.
But the first time I heard that a suit cost around a hundred pounds, at least.
I was like, you can't be, you've got to be fucking shitting me.
That's clothes.
Yeah.
That's just clothes.
And it's just clothes.
A hundred dollars is like, part is like half of like a, it's like a, like half of like a PlayStation 2.
Yeah.
That's exactly the thing.
I was like, I knew the consoles because I like those.
Yeah.
So like, but then you, you realize that there's a lot of money that goes around, goes, passes through your hands over time.
It's like really a monthly subscription to a video game.
Isn't that bad when you consider that some people have been, you know, subscribed to Netflix since it began.
I mean, like I've never done things like that.
I minimize the amount of like monthly subscription services and I groan whenever I think of one because I just don't like them.
I don't like the idea that, I don't know, you've got to make the most of, because that's what I would feel like is like, if I have a Netflix,
I've got to be watching stuff constantly.
Otherwise I'm not making as much, I'm not getting as much out of it for the amount of money I'm putting in.
So I like, I steer clear of stuff like that.
I don't buy triple A modern games.
I don't buy a lot of stuff in general.
It's like, when I think of like the amount of money I spend on World of Warcraft is like, I don't spend a lot of money anyway.
So it's really, it's not a problem.
I mean, if you're getting something out of it, then it's not wasted money.
Yeah, I guess.
Every, every time, this is, this is sort of related.
I'm just, I get so much satisfaction whenever I can find some way to like cut my costs.
Like when I, when I realized how much cheaper buying almond milk from Aldi or Costco is than buying it at Whole Foods,
I was like, this is a game changer.
This is literally going to save me.
Aldi in general was a game changer for me.
Did I introduce you to Aldi?
I don't think so because there was, I knew it for a while.
I have introduced some people to Aldi.
But like we, we definitely had a moment on a podcast or in like a call.
We were just like Aldi and we both Jonesed about it because it was great.
Well, I got an Aldi down the road.
Costco is actually better than Aldi, but it's kind of hard.
Well, yes, but the thing about Costco is you need a membership, but you can get around it if you use a service like Instacart,
because then you can just have a shopper that has a membership go and shop there for you.
So if you're, if you're, if you're shopping with something like that, then it's better than Aldi,
because it's basically just like things in bulk for like lower net costs per item.
But you know, you can't get just like, there are some things they don't have there and like you can't, you can't just get like a jar of peanut butter.
You have to get like a pack of four, like large, you know, big tubs of it or whatever, like wrapped in foil or something.
But yeah, if you're, if for like stuff you don't need to buy in bulk, yeah, Costco is the, is the, is the best.
And yes, yes, yes, Kirk Kirkland brand, everything, everything Costco sells on their own is Kirkland brand and it's the cheapest stuff you can get.
Fuck yeah.
But, but yeah, when I realized that like switching from whole Whole Foods almond milk to Kirkland almond milk literally probably saves me like $60 a month.
Yeah.
Or well, 30 to 50, I don't know.
The amount of money I saved on Red Bull, switching to Red Thunder from Aldi is.
Oh yeah.
Asked you a fucking nomicle.
Oh, well, yeah, that's, I mean, you know, I drink, I drink Bang, which is not, I drink Bang or like Rockstar, which is like, it's not as cheap as Red Thunder, but it's cheaper than Red Bull.
That's the, that's the, that's the main thing.
I mean, I don't particularly like the taste of Red Bull, but in particular, I object to how much it cost, how it costs more for a smaller can.
That's always been the ultimate insult of Red Bull.
But then like you can get, you can get four 12 ounce cans of Red Thunder, which is just as good as Red Bull for $329.
It's, it's less than a dollar can.
You just, you just win.
You just win.
I remember Red Thunder.
I've seen, I've seen that.
I think I bought it once and was like, lol.
No, I'm, I'm committed.
I'm committed to the bit.
It's good.
It's worth it.
It's so fucking cheap.
It's amazing.
Mmm.
Sometimes I'll be tempted to like just when I'm at a convenience store, like, oh, maybe I'll get a Red Bull.
I'm like, no, I can get four for the price of this can of Red Bull.
Get fucked.
Yeah.
I, okay.
I have a, I have a problem.
Well, first let me tell you that I have good news and I have bad news.
The good news is that like I made some gummy worms earlier this week and they were like the best batch I've ever made.
The consistency was like perfect.
I was like, this is, this is what all true warriors strive for.
Like this is the product.
This is the product I have been striving for and I have achieved it.
I have, I have perfected the recipe.
I am like 100% happy with this.
And at like at the exact same time, um, they don't sell the stuff that I make them out of anymore.
It's just no longer available.
Did you say this last time?
Did I, did I say this last time?
I feel like you've told this story.
Did I say it on the, did I say it on the stream?
I actually, I don't know.
Yeah.
Maybe, you know, I might, I very, I very well might have said it on a previous episode is that they,
the isomalto, isomalto ligus saccharides, the tapioca starch,
I've been looking, I like, I can still buy the syrup, but it's in like small amounts and it's not a good value compared to the powder.
First I bought the syrup from a company called Fiber Yum.
And I, and then they were like, oh, the syrup's no longer available, but you can buy the powder.
And I'm like, well now I have to reformulate the recipe.
And now I have to like figure out how much powder to water to use and how much do we cook it down.
And oh, I have to, I have to buy a candy thermometer so that I can like cook it down the same amount every time,
because I need to have a consistent, you know, thickness or whatever.
Fine.
And I did all that.
And I was like, okay, I jumped over that hurdle.
And now I've, it's better than ever.
I've perfected it.
And now they're like, oh no, now we don't sell the powder anymore.
Nope.
Now you can only get the more expensive syrup.
Fuck you.
And I don't want to.
I don't want to do it.
I just, I just want, I just want a little stability.
You know, I just want, I just want things to be normal.
I just want a normal, I just want a normal life of buying isolated tapioca starch
and boiling it in a pot to make gummy worms.
That's all, that's all I want to do.
Now I have to use this fucking other shit.
Fuck this shit derived fruit, uh, fructoligosaccharides derived from Jerusalem artichokes.
Like, are you fucking kidding me?
I didn't even know what that means.
Artichokes from Jerusalem, I assume.
Hold on.
I want, no, they're probably like, it's like an artichoke,
but it's like actually just a potato.
Jerusalem artichoke.
Yes, it's, it's, I'm right.
It looks like, it looks like a cross between, it doesn't even look like an artichoke.
It looks like a cross between a potato and like ginger root.
Look, look at this shit.
Get, get ready.
This is, this is what a Jerusalem artichoke looks like.
It looks like pigs in blankets.
It looks like, it looks like ginger.
It looks like, it looks like nothing.
It looks, I don't, not like an artichoke.
I don't like it.
Like roasted ham croissants.
Making me hungry.
Oh my God.
I cooked an incredible meal yesterday.
I took half a pack of bacon, chopped it up, fried it, threw in chopped Brussels sprouts,
and just seared it in a pan, just baked it in the, in the, in the bacon fat.
And that was it.
It was incredible.
Sounds pretty weird.
It was, it was life changing.
I love Brussels sprouts.
How do you guys feel about Brussels sprouts?
You know, I used to be pretty down on them.
I've come around recently.
They're pretty good.
That's good.
I had like never had them before I lived in the south.
And then I tried some and they were, no, that's not true.
I had some at a restaurant one time.
I had some at a restaurant one time in Medford and I was like, these are really good,
but I never see them on a menu and I don't know how these were prepared.
So I never ate them again.
Yeah.
I moved to Georgia and they eat them sometimes down there.
And I was like, these are good.
I should make these.
And now I do.
Brussels sprouts in the UK are like part of the traditional Christmas dinner with the
turkey and the other things.
Really?
It's one of the vegetables you have with it is Brussels sprouts.
I don't know why.
Tell me more, tell me more about the traditional British Christmas dinner.
Well, you got a turkey.
Some people do chicken, but turkey is the normal.
The traditional one.
You got the...
Because you guys don't do Thanksgiving.
So you don't get sick of turkey before Christmas.
You're not having leftovers for like two weeks.
So you have the turkey.
You have usually potatoes, carrots, peas, you know, just bunches of vegetables and
particularly Brussels sprouts because for some reason Brussels sprouts are just not
that common in everyday meals.
So they're like, oh, yes, the Brussels sprouts I associate with Christmas.
And I never liked them because they were cooked badly a few times and like boiled
in a way that was just sort of rubbery.
And I'm like, I can't get through this.
You know, you know, much, much love to my parents, but honestly, they were both pretty
bad at cooking.
And I learned to hate vegetables because they, my parents were just shit at cooking
them and they would just boil them.
They would just, they would just boil, they would just like boil spinach.
And like my experience of spinach was just that it was like a sort of nasty green
like mush and like it's so bad.
I mean, you can boil things well.
I think some, some things.
I feel like I have enjoyed like roasted Brussels sprouts.
But even when they're like well done, like properly done, cooked Brussels sprouts,
I just, I don't know, they're just too thick to get to the middle.
The middle is like not as good.
You got to cut them in half.
You got to cut them, slice them.
You got to cut them in half and cook them and cook them.
Yeah.
I mean, you can't just roast them whole because then yeah, you will never.
Well, not roast them whole, but like if they're, if they're like boiled, like the
way that they should be like, oh, like dad cooks them all correct.
And like, yeah, there's a real good Brussels sprouts.
Delicious.
Everyone says I'm like, I don't get it.
I don't like the taste.
I don't, I feel like, I don't think I can't imagine a Brussels sprout tasting good boiled
unless it were boiled in like stock or something.
I just, I can't imagine anything being good just like boiled in water.
Spinach is all right.
No.
I like it.
It's not, it's not.
Well, it's sort of like it's, it's, it's a, it's a, it's a sloppy mush, not like not
too mushy, but like so that you can cut it pretty easily.
And then you have something nice and crispy and salty to go with it, like a potato.
Then it's good.
No.
You're simply, you're simply mistaken.
I'm sorry.
I like spinach.
I like eating it.
Any vegetable is good.
You just have to like butter it.
You just have to eat it raw.
You just have to butter it?
No.
You just butter it or oil it and you add salt and pepper and you roast any of it.
I mean, that, that I agree with.
And then literally any vegetable tastes good.
That, that I agree with cause like, like one of my favorite things is like, it's like a
roast of, you know, peppers, onions, fucking aubergine, courgette, like all these.
Do you know, do you know what we call aubergines?
Eggplants, I know.
Lol.
It's so weird when I, I don't know, that's, that one always catches me off guard.
And, and you know, various other things.
And then like sausages and you, and you cover it with like loads of olive oil and salt and
pepper and you put it and you roast it in the oven.
And it's just sort of, it's delicious.
Actually it might be keto, maybe.
I don't know about vegetable keto ability.
Most, most vegetables are pretty keto, more or less.
It's just really like all of the great, you know, the oil and the fat of the sausages
and then all the tasted, tasty vegetables.
But never Brussels sprouts.
I never put Brussels sprouts in that.
Christmas dinner here.
I mean, we don't, like we do turkey at Thanksgiving.
And so usually, sometimes you'll have turkey at Christmas, but usually not cause it's more
of a Thanksgiving thing.
I think it's the most traditional thing would be a ham, like a Christmas ham is pretty,
is pretty standard.
I don't know.
Christmas dinner is like, there's no like, there's no like set thing of what it is.
It's just, you have a, you have a big dinner and it involves, it just, it's, you make a
lot of stuff and you invite your family and then everyone brings some shit and you have
a big feast.
But there's not, there's not, Christmas ham.
And I guess some fruit, I don't know.
People associate fruit cakes with Christmas, but I've literally never eaten one or seen
one served at like a Christmas thing.
So I think that's like an old thing that has gone by the wayside.
Yeah.
It's before they had good shit.
They liked fruit cake.
I don't know.
I've always been kind of curious to try fruit cake cause everyone says how bad it is.
I mean, it's not that bad.
It's just sort of like, when you're a kid and you're like, oh, cake, oh, I love cake.
Hmm.
Chocolate cake.
Then you get given fruit cake and you're like, gross fruit.
That's not chocolate.
Oh, that's like cookies with raisins in it.
Like, yeah.
Yucky.
I see.
And then you just sort of like associate it being bad even though it's fine.
Right.
If you go into fruit cake wanting fruit cake, you'll enjoy yourself.
I don't know.
I think I remember, I remember seeing in like a cartoon and it's like, oh, it's like brown
and it has like little colored like bits in it.
And like, what, what is it?
Like what, I guess it's fruit.
I don't know.
I saw it as a kid and I heard people say it was bad.
And I've always wondered, what's fruit cake like?
And I've just, I don't know.
I've never had the opportunity to try some.
Could you make a keto cake?
Is that possible?
I have done it.
Yeah.
You just have to use like a weird recipe.
It's like almond flour.
Yeah.
You use recipes that involve like almond flour and coconut flour and like heavy cream and
stuff.
I have made, I have made keto brownies and I have made like a keto like vanilla cake.
It's, they're pretty good.
Yeah.
They can be, they can be pretty good sometimes.
I've got the, I've got the, I've been making, I've been making buffalo, I've been making
my own buffalo wings lately.
I don't know.
I feel like I might have mentioned that before, but I've.
Yeah.
I've mentioned that.
Yes.
Okay.
I'm a son.
What about gummy flay, like gummy, buffalo flavored gummy.
Buffalo, buffalo.
Frank's red hot flavored buffalo wings.
Did I, did I tell, I hate to think that I'm repeating myself, but the latest batch of
gummies that I made, I like burnt the syrup and it sort of tasted like, I didn't think
this would happen with the isomaltooligosaccharides because like they're not sugar.
They shouldn't behave like sugar does and yet they do.
And I like heated them up too much and they got this kind of like slightly burnt sort
of caramel taste to them.
And so I made, I had, I happened to have some like cream soda flavoring.
So I made cream soda flavored gummies with this like caramelized, the last of my, of
my syrup and it was great.
The consistency is, is perfect better than I ever could have dreamed.
I, I'm also the second to last batch on like when, when I burned it and I, I made, I was
making passion fruit, my favorite flavor, but it ended up having this weird kind of caramel
flavor, which like doesn't quite go, but like it's fine.
It's still good.
And I made it and I put it in the molds and I was like, Oh no, it's not setting.
It's not coming out as a worm.
It's just, I have to scoop it out and eat it as goo like, okay, but it still tastes good.
So I'll do it and I'll try putting it in the free and I'll put some of it in the freezer
and see if it like hardens.
Oh, it doesn't harden.
It just stays as goo.
Oh, how disappointing.
But then I went back and I looked today and the ones, the ones that I had left in the
fridge, they were just sitting there.
They were just sitting there in the fridge.
They weren't like freezing.
I don't know.
They shouldn't have solidified any more than they did.
They should have been as set as they were going to be, but somehow over the like the
day or two that they were in there, they set up and they like dried out or something.
And they, and they were worms now.
They're worms now and they're passion fruit and, and, and it's a miracle.
It's a Christmas miracle.
It all returns to the worms.
I feel, I have had, I have had batches before that have not set up and have like just been
goo and I've been like, oh damn, wasted over a recipe.
And now this has changed everything.
Now I'm like, maybe I just like judged too soon.
Maybe all I needed to do was just leave those in the fridge for like two days and just wait
and they would have become good because these ones have not only become, they went from
being inedible to being not only good, but like the best.
They have like the best and like softest and like most chewy and appealing gummy consistency
of any batch I've made up until now.
It's incredible.
That's weird.
The other, well, it might not be the only, that might not be the only factor because
there's one other thing that I've changed, which is I switched from powdered gelatin
to sheet gelatin.
And sheet gelatin, it turns out is a million times better.
Sheet gelatin is more expensive, but it is like a lot, it's a lot easier to deal with.
You don't have to like, you don't have to like fuck around with it as much.
And it doesn't stink up your house and make your, your kitchen smell like a glue factory,
which is pretty nice.
It doesn't smell like anything, which is exactly what I want my gelatin to smell like.
It's another miracle.
Of course it costs like $20 for like a package of it.
I was about to say it's probably more expensive.
It's kind of expensive.
Yeah.
Unfortunately.
Unfortunate.
Yeah.
You have to buy it with EBT.
It's not, no, I buy it on Amazon, but it's not, it's like too, it's like too specialized
or something.
Oh, fuck you, Jeff.
It's pretty random, like what you can use the EBT on, like you should be able to use
it on anything that's food and like that's not like pre-prepared food, which should be
most things.
Like that, like that should include sheet gelatin, but I think just like some distributors
just aren't set up to accept it.
And so it's kind of just random who takes it and who doesn't.
Oh well.
Hmm.
Fuck.
Dude, I'm like so close to finishing the 3D print right now.
Just printing in the background.
It'll probably be done before we're done with this podcast.
I'm reprinting the one that I tweeted earlier.
I took that 3D model, made a 3D print of it.
It's super fucking cool, but it had like some issues, like the tail got a little fucked
up.
It was like a little zoomie print with a, with a drink and a little can of soda by a vending
machine.
Oh, this one with the, is that a zoomie with their hood up?
Yeah.
Hmm.
So I did that.
I draw Kaia did a fan art of a zoomie, like hanging out in like a hoodie, uh, drinking
a soda, uh, like in January and it was fucking sick.
I said to myself, back in January, I'm going to make a model based on the south because
it's fucking lit.
And I finally did it like this week.
And then I projection painted their drawing onto 3D geometry to make the background 3D.
I was going to say like who, like where did these textures come from?
So this is, this is draw Kaia's like art as a texture on this environment.
This looks great.
This 3D thing here that I'm seeing.
It was really cool.
I was, I saw, I found a video on YouTube about projection painting and stuff and I had done
it a little bit before because I had taken a bunch of photos of like a can of beer for
Digi, like when he's doing, uh, how they marketed and projection painted it onto a cylinder.
So it was like a can of soda that you could like spin or a can of beer you could spin
around and like 3D and stuff.
So I just kind of did a similar thing where you just kind of line up the reference drawing
to the camera and then make geometry in the relative shape and then you project for view
the graphic onto the geometry.
And like, if you like turn it a little bit more than the camera is in the video, like
it starts getting fucked up because it's just flat projected.
But for a little effect like this, it works great and it was sick and, uh, came out awesome.
And then I was like, fuck it.
I'm going to try and 3D print it.
So I got a 3D print going, it's going to be real.
If it's flat projected, I imagine like the opposite side of the vending machine just
like doesn't have any texture on it.
It's just like a smeared abomination of the other side because it just goes right through.
Oh my God, I just had a brain blast guys.
You should collab Tom.
You should make a mo, like a 3D print, like inverse model of a zoomie and then Ben should
use that as a mold to make a gummy a zoomie.
You know, I, I was talking to, I mentioned the idea and I think I talked to Smirig a
little bit about it, about, um, making like endless war gummies, which, um, you know,
if I had, if I still had ready access to the fucking ingredients that I need, like this
would, like I've, I feel like I've perfected the recipe now.
This would be the time.
It's like, hmm, I wonder if I should get some custom molds, mate, because I think Smirig
said that she could was able to make like custom molds if I wanted some, maybe once
I figure out the supply, supply issue, the slicer I use for 3D that lets you make molds.
It just like inverts the geometry and it'll 3D print a mold that you can cast instead
of just, but it would be like, wouldn't it be like a solid like plastic mold?
I don't know how it works.
I've never tried it before.
I was just, I actually just found it yesterday, just looking through settings and cura.
Which is like the slicer software.
Could you 3D print like a soft silicon mold?
Uh, if you use a soft material, like I think PETG is flexible.
I've never printed flexible only printed PLA, which is like the baby, like easy stuff
to print.
I mean, it would need to be flexible and it would also need to be like food safe and
not something that's going to like leech toxins.
If like, you know, it's exposed to like a hot substance, like plastic, like plastic
often does.
I know some people do use certain materials that are food safe, but I don't know what
they are.
It's off my head, but it is possible.
Yeah.
It's never done it before.
Okay.
Interesting.
There's options.
Fascinating.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
It's pretty, it's pretty fucking cool.
Oh, okay.
I haven't, this is sort of related.
I haven't posted this anywhere because I'm waiting to have it in hand, but I got, they
made the slime coin.
They made two like, like molds of the slime coin for the endless war pin thing.
I had them print two versions.
One was, I think I talked about the hard enamel versus soft enamel thing and how they were
saying, they were saying that like, ooh, hard enamel might run together.
The polishing process, that was just bullshit.
I looked, I looked at the hard enamel version.
It looks fine.
There's no problems with the polishing.
It was a waste of time.
I wish they had not even troubled me with it.
Wait, do you have images?
Do you have pictures?
Oh yeah.
I do actually.
I will see.
And these are, neither of these is final.
Oh fuck.
Where did, where did I put it?
I sent them to Munchie.
Oh fuck.
Okay.
I'll have to go, I'll have to go get them from that.
Here.
Which, which one of these is the best?
I don't know.
I guess I'll try this one.
There was the soft enamel, they're both with gold metal, because it was decided that gold
metal is probably the best.
The top one is soft enamel with like a darker green color, and the bottom one is hard enamel
with a lighter green color.
And I'm going to just wait to see them in person and decide like, which one of these
is better.
I mean, I think I like the look of the hard enamel, but as for the color, I'm undecided.
That's a picture they sent you of what they look like.
Yeah.
I don't actually have them yet.
This is, this is, they, they took a picture of them holding it and send it to me.
I really wish they were over the same angle so I could see how the shine, yeah, like
the top one looks shiny because of the way that's catching the light and the bottom one,
it looks like it's dark, but if it were catching the light differently, it might not.
I don't know.
That's why I have to like, I can't decide until I have it in hand and can like hold
it and turn it around and be like, hmm, fascinating.
The top one does look really good though.
I can't wait to hold that thing.
There, there is, I don't know, there's, um, like all the bridges and bumps.
There's three.
I mean, the hard enamel is kind of, I don't know, my instinct is to see like, oh, hard
enamel is just better.
But like, there is a little bit of something kind of compelling about the like, the non-uniformity
of the surface on the soft enamel one.
Almost like it's like, almost like the ridges are indeed filled with like liquid.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
The sort of like squished on there.
I just feel like it would feel real fun to just rub your finger on it.
Just hold it.
Yeah.
I know what you mean.
The ridges.
Yeah.
I mean, it's, like I said, you can't see them from the same angle.
So it's a, one, the top one just looks better in this image, but like.
In this image, the top one definitely looks better, but it's too early to sell.
Yeah.
It's just sort of the, the gloopiness I think of the indent is sort of cool.
It is.
It is, but I'm, hmm, they're, yeah, no, there's definitely something compelling.
I'm actually really, I'm actually shocked that like, not only did none of like the
circuitry lines like get like smushed together in the final product, there's a little bit
of uneven unevenness in a couple of places, but like that was there in the like vector
file as well.
So like that's not their fault.
I'm amazed at the degree to which not only did the lines not smushed together, but also
the text is like not, the text is like perfect and like there's, there's parts in the text
that like, like if you look at the very bottom on the end, like in the gap between the lines
of the end in new Los Angeles city, there's a little like square.
And I was sure that the little like square bit was going to get like mushed into the
line because the gap between the square and the end itself is like minuscule, but no,
it's completely distinct and it didn't get mushed together at all.
The polishing didn't have any negative effects.
I'm super happy with how it looks.
Uh, yeah, I think I got the coin and I'm, I'm, I'm almost positive you did.
I'm almost sure there's so many good pins, but the coin is like, the coin is like such
a unique thing.
Like you can't not have the coin.
I like a long time ago, I talked about like, we're doing a Kickstarter to get the coin,
to get the coin made.
And then like later on, when I pitched the idea of the pin, the pin Kickstarter, I was
like, hmm, what if we did the coin as part of it and it just seemed like a good time
to do it.
But like back then when I first thought, I was like, that would be so ridiculous.
Like that would be, that would be like a crazy, a really crazy thing if we like had slime
coin made in real life.
And now we did it.
It's just coming true and I just, I think that's so cool.
I'm so excited to just like hold it and flip it and you know, try to try to pay for things
with it in real life and then like act confused when, when people don't accept it.
First thing you do, put it into a vending machine.
Yeah.
First thing I do is go to like a, go to like a restaurant and try and tip with it and say,
look at the change to its put, push it across the table with a sly look on my face.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's my slime coin news.
It looks good.
I was tempted to post it in the endless wars, like in the pin server, but I because neither
of these is final and I haven't decided on like which version or which color I want to
go with.
I'm like, eh, why show these now?
Why show these now?
I'm in the show notes now so everyone can see them.
People just argue.
It would just, it would lead, I feel like it would lead to strife.
I feel like it would lead to like a rift.
It was like, there was a big, there was saying, we just talked about it on a public podcast
for like, yeah, you're right.
I fucked it up, but like there was a big rift of people who, between people who wanted
like 1.5 inch diameter and two inch diameter and like, you know, these two groups could
not be reconciled with, they just had fundamentally opposed worldviews and like there was,
these coins, like 1.5 and 2.
As a coward centrist, I went with 1.75.
Uh, that's alright.
It's, I, I, I bought a bunch of like other coins of various sizes.
I bought some 1.5.
Ah!
Oh my God.
Oh.
Did you hear that?
I did.
I heard that.
I knocked my microphone over.
Lamal.
Oh, no.
I'm glad you can still hear me.
I bought a bunch of other challenge coins of different sizes.
I bought 1.5, 1.75 and 2 and I like held them and I looked at them and I tried flipping
them and I showed them to Munchie and we discussed it.
And I think we, we agree that like 1.75, like bigger is better, but flipability is good.
And 1.75 is like two inches is slightly cumbersome to flip 1.75 is not particularly cumbersome
to flip, but it's like almost as big.
So we figured it was like the best of both worlds.
So yeah, I went with that one.
Ah.
And now I have all these used, I have this one with like a bald eagle and an American
flag on it and one with like a Roman soldier on it and one, one made up like an obviously
inferior metal with like an objectively bad drawing of like a night Templar like kneeling.
This thing is like a piece of shit and like whoever drew this was incompetent.
I'm going to take a picture right now.
Oh, you didn't like my drawing?
No, you, you fool.
You failed.
No.
Shit.
This is probably, this is going to take me a second.
So in a, in like two minutes, I will treat you to a picture of a, of a poorly drawn night
saying, greater is he who is in you than he who is in the world.
One John for four.
Does that mean like fucking dudes is better than going out in the world?
And then on the back, there's a cross in a shield and it says, I can do all things through
Christ who gives me strength, Philippians 413, 413, homestuck number.
Oh, my phone just turned off.
Okay.
I'm going to show him the mouth in the show notes, maybe in the show notes, maybe.
That's all I have to say about coins.
In fact, that's all I have to say about anything.
Yeah.
Should we do voicemails?
I guess we could do voicemails.
I guess, I guess if that's still a thing we're doing, if, if we're all, if we're all ready
to move on, we can, we can stop doing voicemails whenever you want.
All right.
Yeah.
Let's, let's go.
Let's, let's, oh my God.
Oh my God.
How many are there?
Oh, is there a lot?
No.
There's a whole page full.
At least 20.
There's exactly one page of them.
You know what?
It's good.
More for it.
It's healthy.
Okay.
Keeps us strong.
No, no.
We're going to go lightning round.
Okay.
On the second page, the first one is from, is from best guy ever, if you can, if you
can believe it.
Didn't, oh, for some reason minus that one is played, but yeah.
Okay.
That one, yeah, it was played for me too, but I listened to the last episode and the
last one we played was from prole jester.
So best guy ever is the first one.
So all right.
Here we go.
Uh, three, two, one, go.
Hey guys, it's me, the best guy ever.
Just want to say you're doing a great job.
Bye.
Wow.
Heartwarming.
He's on the podcast.
You better watch it now.
You better watch the entire podcast to see Nate wherever, wherever he is.
I'm glad that he's, that he's looking down from heaven and he's glad and he's pleased
with the job we're doing.
Cool.
Uh, next one is from every listener, three, two, one, go.
One of you guys just going to end the podcast already.
I mean, it's basically dead says you idiot.
Every listener says that this is, I guess this is, I guess this is what everyone is
saying.
It's true.
Every week, the comments are just, they're dumbfounded that we continue to do a podcast
that isn't very difficult to do.
More like they're dumb and unfounded in their opinions.
It's almost like making this podcast is really not that much of a, of an ask and you could
do it at any time.
Well, you could do, you know, a couple of hours a week.
So easy.
Like why would we stop?
Um, I don't, I don't know.
Yeah.
No, I can't, I can't imagine.
I really, I really cannot think of any good reason not to just do the podcast.
Well, it's what happens when you have a bunch of people who've built cult of personalities
around themselves and then when they disappear, those people who are into that cult of personality
exclusively are going to voice their disdain.
It's true.
So, um, but, uh, you know, I mean, it's only so much.
I was thinking about this a little bit and it's like, I could feel bad about this, but
there's, there's nothing I can do about people who just want there to be someone else on
the show that isn't here.
Like I can't do anything about that.
I'm not them.
So like, yeah, I've been, it was really annoying to me for a while, but I think I've just,
I think, I think maybe I let it get to me and I think I've made peace with it.
And now I'm, I'm, I'm just like the podcast is what it is and the podcast has always been
whoever wants to show up shows up and that's, and that's the show.
And we just, we just do that.
We work with whatever that ends up being and it is, and it is still that.
And uh, you know, of course it has gone, it has gone through phases and this is just another
phase in the natural life cycle, much like the, the pupa stage of an insect's life, you
know, before it forms into a beautiful chrysalis, right?
We're in the, we're in the chrysalis phase right now, uh, and the butterflies is coming.
Dude, dude, I love cream chrysalis.
What a great villain.
Um, uh.
Until they ruined her when they brought her back.
But before that, what a great villain.
Hey, why did like the changelings become like good guys or something?
I literally don't know.
They turn into people.
They like all turn like green and stuff.
That there was, there was one changeling who was not like other changelings.
He wasn't that, he's a shit.
And so he met spike, he met spike and spike became friends when he's, and he's like, Hey,
this changeling is okay.
And everyone was like, okay.
Um, then chrysalis is evil.
And then the good changeling was like, no, spikes, cool, uh, ponies, they're nice.
Um, maybe we shouldn't be evil and chrysalis was like, no, we're going to be evil still.
Um, and some sort of magic happened and, uh, the good changeling, uh, instead of feeding
on love, gave love or some bullshit.
And he changed into a different character design.
Isn't that just like, that's like, Hey, I'm a human.
And you know, humans are shit because we like eat meat.
And I don't believe in eating meat.
I think that's like cruel and it's bad and changeling.
So, so, so instead of consuming meat, I'm going to expel me.
I'm going to like, I'm going to like puke me into out into the world.
I'm just going to like carve chunks of meat off my body.
Yeah, right?
Like, like, okay, I, I get like not consuming love, but he, where does the love come from
if he's just going to like spit it out?
Oh, I guess.
I don't know.
Oh, he has to like give up.
He has to be nice.
He has to be a nice person.
You know, I guess that actually makes, I guess he just probably just comes from his
heart, the same place that like all love comes from, so stupid question.
You know, wouldn't, wouldn't you say, though, that we all consume love?
Like when we are loved, aren't we consuming love of other people?
Aren't we all changelings deep down?
There's a different, different ways like, like cool metaphor about the changelings love
like manipulators or something like a relationship thing, but I've never thought about it.
Did you ever read sideways stories from wayside school?
Uh, no, but I've heard of it.
I was too busy reading Animorphs.
I read these a little bit before I got into Animorphs.
These was like this elementary school.
They're like, they're like funny stories about this like this wacky school with all this
create all these crazy shit happens.
Um, and, uh, I don't, there's one, there's one story I remember and it's about fuck.
I don't remember like which of the kids is doing it or like whatever it's someone is
going around just saying like, I love you to people and they're like, and everyone's
like, Hey, that's great.
Hey, I love love.
Hey, this is awesome.
And then someone is like, I think it might be like the teacher tells one of the kids
that like she loves him or something.
And he's like, what about, and he's like, what about Mrs. Mr. The teacher's name is Mrs.
Jules.
And he's, and she tells this kid that she loves him and he's like, what about Mr. Jules?
And she's like, the thing about love is that it's, it's not like other things.
It's the only kind of thing that when you give it, you end up with more of it than you
started with.
So I think maybe that's maybe that's the principle that these, um, that these, these good changes
are operating on.
Like they, they thought they had to consume love to get it, but it turns out, turns out
love is just like, it's just non-Newtonian like that.
It doesn't obey the natural laws of arithmetic in the way you might expect.
Mrs. Jules was right.
Hashtag justice for Mrs. Jules.
Uh, uh, okay, based, uh, next.
Next one is called, uh, Sessho eight Nate, three, two, and it's short, which is, which
is epic.
Three, two, one.
Go.
Thanks to Ben Tom hippo for holding down podcast.
Okay.
Welcome.
You're welcome.
Was that Sessho saying that?
After eating.
I don't know.
Okay.
Hmm.
The camera says that next one is Matt Damon, and you know, and you, yeah, you know that
it's him because his email is real Matt underscore Damon at Hollywood dot mail.
So, you know, that's thanks for joining us, uh, three, two, one.
Go.
He use his gingers again.
Anat Odemur.
You know, son, he's my best friend.
Goodbye, this old knucklehead.
This ruins goodwill hunting for me.
Uh, he's like studying for a new role.
He's getting into character.
He's method acting.
He's a little too good.
He's a little too effective at this.
Hmm.
Uh, ooh, I don't know.
I should stop watching movies.
You start watching a movie.
You think it's the movie advertised, but then, uh, you know, the samurai.
You think you're watching the MGM Lion Roar at the beginning of a movie, but it's actually
Oh, Ben no Sainto-san.
Did I, did I talk last week about that movie I watched?
The Virginia Woolf movie, Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?
You did.
Yes.
I haven't watched yet, but I did download it.
I can't fucking remember.
I fucking COVID, fucking lockdown.
I can't remember like which week is which and whether like things happened last.
It really is.
I really am just like, hmm, what's new this week?
What's old?
Who knows?
Next one is titled Very Unsuspiciously.
You'll Never Catch Me, Chris Hansen, uh, three, two, one, yes, go.
Hello.
What's up?
He's a samurai.
He's everywhere.
Ben no Sainto-san, have you been called by a Hollywood actor, a reatory?
Haha, not a meto demo.
Tozo ai, samurai-sama.
Mastery of the Skies.
Haha, fuck you.
I'm so scared.
Ben no Sainto-san.
Anywhere.
In any time.
Of samurai revenge scheme.
We have a kidnap.
Ben no Sainto-san, Garufarendo.
Aristian-chan.
Weston-chan-dura.
No.
You pay three million yen, or you never see Corisu-chan again.
Zipuroto-thikan.
But until next time, sayonara.
I don't know if I'm willing to pay three million yen.
Me and Chris are around a little bit of rocky territory lately.
Yeah, you're at war right now.
We, yeah, yeah, Mlachikam has officially gone to war with Quickville.
And Chris has continued to deny that this is taking place in the alpha timeline, despite extensive documentation proving it to be the case.
So I don't know if we're talking right now.
How can you profit here from war without an enemy though?
Maybe I'll just send a slime boy over there to be like a puppet dictator.
Maybe they'll just send them to disguise themselves.
Can't you just say as a dimensional prophet that this never happened in this timeline and that it just doesn't happen and you don't have to worry about it anymore?
With this kidnapping?
Yeah, this kidnapping just didn't happen in this timeline.
I mean, ordinarily.
Seems to work for Chris.
This samurai's genjutsus are pretty powerful, I don't know if that's true.
Hey, samurai-san, voice grail, I think. At this point, you've earned voice grail.
No, I would rather not. I would rather keep him out.
Tom, you will also agree with me so we can outnumber Ben.
I don't know if you should do that.
It's a good bit. It's a good bit. I like it.
I love it every time.
I like the accent and I like Ben's suffering. It's like a win-win for me.
It's really scary.
It's like you never know when he's going to strike and when he does, it's the best.
But if he's in the voice grail, that'll mean he's close to me and he's within striking distance.
I know, that sounds like fun times for all.
Oh god, if only I could vote twice.
If only we had mail-in voting here on the PCP so I could vote once by mail and once at the polls
so I could lock this vote down, but I can't. I'm only one man.
Have we done it? Is he grail?
I think he's grail.
Oh god, alright. Okay, well, this is fucking, this is going to be sick.
Alright, see you in hell, sensei.
Next one is from Free the Pee-Pee. 3, 2, 1, go.
It's not enough to free the nipple, free the pee-pee and free the poo-poo, but what about the children? Fuck the children!
Yeah, you know, sometimes I just want my junk outside of my trousers.
Sometimes I just want to quality it.
He's talking about junk, I think he's talking about pee-pee and poo-poo, I think he's just talking about fluid.
I think he's just talking about excrement, yeah.
Isn't that already free?
Well, no, I hope not.
It's the act of doing it that's banned, but if it's just on the side of the road, no one's going to go to jail.
I think they just mean like the penis and the butthole.
I think that's what they meant, but if we take them with their literal words.
You shouldn't be allowed to shit in the street because it stinks.
Pee-pee is urine and it is the penis.
The poo-poo is the poo-poo, but it is not the butthole. Nobody calls the butthole the poo-poo.
What about when you're keeping in line with the pee-pee terminology?
I think that you've been had, I feel like this was a misdirect.
When I read it, I thought he meant the penis, but then you can't say pee-pee.
He said pee-pee and poo-poo, he's talking about the pee-pee poo-poo, that's unambiguous.
Ben, first of all, this is a terrible lightning round because we've had a huge discussion about every voicemail,
but there are two more parts to this voicemail that might clarify our question right now.
Maybe we should hold our questions to the end.
I hear the nipple doesn't mean free the milk.
Yeah, I know, but he said pee-pee and poo-poo.
Alright, let's move to the next one.
I'm just taking him out of his word.
Next one, free the pee-pee part two.
Three, two, one, go.
But I don't want to see the pee-pee in public.
Well, you know what, I don't like looking at black people, but I'm just fucking you with it.
It doesn't matter.
Yikes.
Oh, no.
This guy has like marbles in his mouth.
I didn't see the racism coming.
Oh, dang.
Oh, Jesus.
He's here for a good-natured romp, and it just got dark really quick.
He said clock the children, so he's a pedophile and a racist now.
Oh, no.
Are we going to go to part three?
Are we really going to do that?
We're really going.
Maybe he can redeem himself.
This is the anarchy that Ben has brought in.
It's like that gift from community.
It's like, I can tolerate racism and pedophilia, but I draw the line at wanting to free the pee-pee.
Alright, free the pee-pee part three.
That's the dramatic conclusion.
Three, two, one, go.
Like, you know everyone used to be naked just like all the time, right?
Like, nobody's going to be fucking mentally scarred because they saw a naked person existing.
Your brain is wired to already see naked people.
Who fucking cares?
I do know what you mean about the marbles in the mouth.
Like, he sounds like the stereotype like nerd side character in a cartoon.
Yeah.
I'm not sure if he's doing a voice.
I think he's doing a voice.
I guess I'd feel a little bad if like, that's just how he sounds.
And I'm like, he sounds impaired, lamal.
But I don't know.
There wasn't a punchline.
He was just continuing the thing.
Yeah.
Just putting one in voicemail.
Yeah, you could have said all this in one voicemail.
Hey, free the, free the, free the peepie, free the, free the black peepie.
And don't fuck kids.
Just that one.
And don't fuck the children.
Those are my, these are, so I, I'm with you on one out of three.
Okay.
Anything else to say about that?
No, no, there really isn't.
Excellent.
All right.
Good.
We're sorted.
Next one.
Pancakes.
I was wondering, what would you guys think of a tier list voting system?
Let's say in this system, you're voting for president and there's three candidates.
One that you think is great.
One that you think is mediocre.
The third one that you think is poo.
So when it comes times the vote, you go to poll and there's like three slots.
There's a primary, secondary, tertiary, and so on and so forth.
So in the primary, put the one you really want secondary, the one you think is mediocre and tertiary, the one you think is shit, or if you don't like them, leave it blank.
So when it comes to tally up the votes, they go from primary and the one you vote for primary, let's say you just, there's no way you could ever win.
So then your vote would go down to your secondary and that's the one it would kind of go to.
What do you think a system like this would do?
What do you think a system like this would affect stuff like third party voting?
Do you think people like Bernie Sanders would still be in the running if we had this system?
Bernie Sanders would be president if we had this system and it would just be better.
I'm wondering about like the, if there's three tiers then the third one is like I dislike as opposed to neutral.
So like would that count as like an anti-vote?
You guys have surely seen the CGP Grey video about like alternate voting systems, right?
I feel like this is like that, but like that's like way more involved.
Is it called first pass the post?
No, that's the one we normally have.
What's the one called that's like, yeah, you rank them and then it's like, okay, well, anyone that doesn't...
I forget the name of it all the time as well, but yes.
It's like you combine like ones that are like that don't get enough of the votes.
So single transferable vote, right?
Yes.
Single transferable votes.
I believe that's what it's called.
You vote for your, you rank them, but then like if your favorite doesn't hit the threshold, then like your second vote, Deri, gets your vote.
Those votes go to their seconds and like similar candidates will gather like similar seconds.
And it literally makes it makes like it makes third parties like not pointless like in American politics and like in most like party politics system and like sing first pass the post voting like third parties are a completely waste of time.
Yeah, it's just it would never happen because it's fake anyway.
The people in charge do not want it to be like that. They don't want to let third parties have a chance because then it would be like harder for them to just continue to gain control.
The people of everybody who's in a position of power to make positive changes are the ones benefiting most from keeping it bad.
So the only way to fix this is to murder everybody.
Bernie would have made, I mean, I mean, Bernie would have probably, I'm sure he would have approved of something like this.
I obviously like it would have taken like the it would have taken like bills through Congress and stuff to get like voting change like this.
But you know, I don't know.
Some people would want a system like this. And it's just that it's some people would prefer this objectively better system.
You know, I guess is my most optimistic take on that.
Yeah, it's a shame. It's a shame that our system sucks.
But what are you going to do?
But next one is from vintage three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP. So last week was my first ever voicemail in the show.
So this week is going to be my first, my first ever drunk voicemail into the show.
Okay.
So I'm randomly watching this YouTube video by this YouTuber called the right.
Is he saying he's drunk right now?
He has 875 K subscribers.
It's about YouTube channels that have recently been hacked and about 20 and a half minutes into the video.
There's like a five second segment about the PCP getting hacked.
And the first tweet he shows in like the.
Yes, it's your tweet.
PCP getting hacked is my fucking tweet complaining about the back getting hacked.
My first exposure to anyone is a fucking tweet from me about some funny shit.
The now imagine how we all feel.
Our entire career is going to start with the right opinion is talking about he's talking about like channels getting stolen.
And he mentions this TBAP thing.
It's like someone bought and then it's like, oh, I don't have it anymore.
And he says that like he says that like TBAP was restored because it belonged to a group of creators who like had some some some cloud.
Who were who were able to like, you know, get YouTube to get it back, which is a little bit true.
It's you know, it still took us like a herculean effort to do it.
But it is it is true that we do have some level of a platform which made it like possible at all, which is so that's true, I guess.
But he yeah, he says it.
He only he mentions TBAP mispronounces it.
He says TBB AP.
And then he says it belonged to a group of creators and he shows tweets from the PCP Twitter account, but he doesn't mention the procrastinators specifically, which is kind of a bummer.
But I don't know.
On my tweets, I saw a red man's face.
That's right.
He did.
I remember that.
I don't remember what it said.
Yeah, it's on screen for not long enough.
Yeah, he just showed like a couple of tweets, like two of the PCP and then like yours and like vintages and I don't know.
It's funny that TBAP got like mentioned and the PCP didn't lol.
Okay.
Next one from vintage again.
Hopefully drunker this time because I couldn't even tell you were drunk that first time was pathetic.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay, so I just send in some voicemail about the PCP hack being featured in some pretty decent sized video and I also I forgot to add to the voicemail already sent in that he shows a screenshot on a website where the PCP or actually specifically
TBAP channel was sold on and someone bought someone named Tofifi bought the TBAP channel for $45.
So I'm just curious how that makes you feel Ben or Nate ever comes back on the show again.
You got a good deal.
Huh?
That is 35 dollars for TBAP.
TBAP has like 15,000 subscribers on it.
Like it hasn't posted a video in like a year plus, but it's got 15,000 subscribers.
Yeah, that's an incredible deal honestly.
Like, damn, maybe I should buy a YouTube channel.
Kickstart my career again.
You want me to sell you TBAP?
No.
Oh, well, okay.
At this point, we would probably...
I want to start with a channel with like 99,000 subscribers and then just like get the extra 1K and then get my plaque and then be like, I did it.
Every month, when Nate does like the pay calculations, he includes like TBAP ad revenue and it's like one cent.
So every month we're making like one to two cents off of like TBAP video ad revenue.
I'm so glad I get like one sixth of a penny of TBAP money.
No, it doesn't.
No, no, no, no, no.
That only goes to me and Nate actually.
Ah, well fuck both of you.
Fuck you.
Yeah, I get fucked, idiot.
Disgusting.
Next one is from Yuck, a penisqueef.
Three, two, one, go.
Konnichiwa.
No.
It is a samurai.
One more time.
This is the fate you brought upon yourself.
It's not.
Voice mail.
One no guy, a fucking idiot.
Say your sayonara.
No work in context I use.
That is the joke.
You're fucking retard.
Okay.
Until you next time.
Sayonara.
I, is it?
Is that intentional?
Is that the joke?
I don't know.
I thought you could just say sayonara.
What was it?
It's like sayonara is like when it's like goodbye, like for good or for a long time.
For a long time.
I'll see you in 20 years.
Sayonara, motherfucker.
Right.
Well, who fucking cares?
Listen, you're a voice girl now.
You're above such petty concerns.
What other voicemails say about you?
About your quote unquote, about your Japanese skills.
Next one is from is Margar's realization.
Three, two, one, go.
Margar here.
It's worse than I thought.
I was under the impression that Ben St was purposely targeting me for whatever reason.
As a victim of this corrupt police state that we find ourselves within.
I am.
But the reality is far more trouble.
No, it's not.
Ben St is not the perpetrator of the victimization that I have suffered.
But is instead a byproduct of the very system we live within.
I've fallen by the wayside and the system as if it were some love, crafty and horror
is not malevolent towards me and like others like me.
But is instead unaware of my suffering altogether.
I thought that your harassment was the worst of it.
But the realization that my existence may as well be irrelevant is somehow more terrible.
I'm so glad Margar made it to seventh grade.
This is this is just this is such it's such a cope such a cope.
This guy he's just he's just wants to he just wants to
Oh, philosophy.
He wants to wax philosophic about all these goons that are coming to his cell and kicking his ass all the time.
No, no, I'm there's no there's no there's nothing to be learned here.
There's nothing to be gleaned about the system or systematic injustice.
I just I paid them.
I said beat him up and they do it.
And there's nothing more to it than that.
No, you were right the first time you are being systematically targeted.
The system is just I am a single lone wolf single bad apple malevolent actor working within the system to bring about bad outcomes.
Don't so so rest assured rest assured the universe does know about your suffering and encourages it and by the universe I mean me.
You just earned yourself a whole lot of goon visits with this voicemail.
I'll tell you that much.
Next up.
I'm excited for this one.
Best Ben bits slash s or something three, two, one, go.
Got to say one of my new favorite bits on the podcast is the Ben being racist bit or the Ben being misogynistic bit.
It's honestly pretty funny.
Keep it up.
Okay.
I will.
Thanks.
I'm glad you like it when I'm raised.
Maybe I should rebrand.
You know, you know, ever since I I've been trying out this new racism thing and I got to say it's paying dividends.
Like my patreon is like skyrocketing.
Like the Koch brothers are calling me up.
They want to give me a show.
It's like, damn, maybe there's something to all this after all this whole this whole racism, this whole misogyny thing.
Hmm.
I don't know.
I don't know what I was so mad about before.
Now I can, I can see them see in the other side and it makes a lot of sense.
Okay.
That's it.
Nothing to apologize for.
Three, two, one, 29, three, two, one, go.
Konnichiwa.
Sessha wa somurai.
Dekosa datai.
I am not the samurai.
But I do know a little bit about samurai.
I live in Japan.
I work in Japan at a Japanese company.
And I speak Japanese every day at work.
And I'm calling to respond to vintage.
Now I'm not going to say he was completely wrong.
He was saying that Sayonara is typically a long term or permanent goodbye.
And that is what it typically is in everyday life.
But someone I spoke with a very formal register compared to peasants and compared to Japanese people today.
And in a formal register, Sayonara is a regular goodbye.
And it's the kind of goodbye that you would say to a teacher, for example.
But honestly, I've never really used it in my life except as a long term goodbye.
But if I were to do so, it would not be entirely wrong.
So, Samurai is in the clear.
He has my seal of approval.
Wow.
But he just, he just said it was a bit though.
The samurai himself submitted it was a bit.
No, I think that, I think that was.
Many layers.
I think that was cope.
I don't think it was a bit.
He could, if you just held out one more week, he could have been in the clear.
I think he, I think he, I think he had a knee jerk reaction.
I think he just, I think he just pulled a, a, a, I was only pretending to be retarded.
Sort of.
Sort of move there.
That voice growl.
That voice growl we just gave him.
Looks to be a little rusty.
Shakey.
A little chipped.
A little premature.
The show's not over yet.
Yeah, yeah.
We could always like completely destroy anybody we, we so please.
At any moment.
Of course.
Obviously.
You could, you could find yourself in a Margar situation at the, at the drop of a hat.
Okay.
Next up, barefoot on the freeway.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
So I'm in a tunnel under freeway right now.
Unfortunately, maybe my brother is not here, the one who's in the car with me before.
He's at college right now.
But what I noticed is there's some graffiti around here and one of them says, I heart ghost bone.
Your thoughts give.
I heard ghost bone.
Was it ghost bone or ghost boner?
Ghost bone.
I assume both mean boner.
Ghost bone sounds like it might be like someone's like DJ handle.
That's the Lord of Ghosts.
It's a fan of Lord of Ghosts, clearly.
Oh, they just like getting boned.
By the Lord of Ghosts.
By log.
Yeah.
Okay.
Sure.
You see, you see that in the seedier parts of Lockecom.
I love ghost bone.
The less reputable brothels.
Hey, we got another one though from barefoot on the freeway.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
Let's see.
There's a dinosaur.
Uh, Sarah, Tim, Joey, Daniel, Wesley.
We're here in 2013.
Pablo and Amber, we're here in 2017.
There's the hamburger helper.
Uh, I'm trying to find the thing I saw before.
Yeah, your local druggy, TikTok soldier camp, number one.
Uh, Rob White people, July with a licky tongue coming out of the, uh, the Y.
I'd be peaking his little squinty face.
All right.
That's about all I see.
There was an American flag, but there are stars in the American side.
As you can see, they're deep.
I like that.
That's something about.
Well, something about that feels like you're walking around in a fallout like post-apocalypse.
You find like a, uh, a recording of someone's voice, just talking to themselves.
I, um, you're like, huh, well, what do you know?
Someone used to be alive, walking around in like sewer pipes and looking at weird shit on the walls.
I may have mentioned this before, but I'll say it again.
There was a, there was some, some graffiti.
There was some spray paint on a stop on the orange line on the Boston subway system on the orange line of the stop.
I think it was at Sullivan Square was the stop and waiting on the platform at Sullivan Square,
which I used to use that when I lived in a different house.
Um, there was some, there was a painting of the power puff girls and it was pretty bad.
Uh, but that's fine.
But what annoyed me about it was that they got the girl's personalities wrong and they drew blot, they drew, um,
Buttercup smiling and, and bubbles looking like angry.
And, and it's like, yeah, fake fan, like what were you thinking?
No, they're just doing, they're just doing inversion.
They're just doing like, what if they were different?
What are they the opposite?
They're all universe.
Maybe.
I don't know.
What if Buttercup was secretly like a tsundere?
Like ha ha.
I think she is.
Yeah.
So, so there.
Bubbles is like, yeah, it's always the nice ones that are like,
Bubbles does have that hardcore episode where she like got really mad and like beat the shit out of everybody
and like had her hidden rage.
Yeah.
It's a common trope that the, the, the cute one is secretly evil and the evil one is secretly,
well, the mean one is secretly nice.
So what was these secrets?
Um,
Women be crazy.
You got it because you got to have like, oh, you got to have set up a character and then subvert expectations.
Okay, I guess, like, oh, I guess we'll have a character be different than you thought she was so predictable.
You know, terrible.
I hate, I hate fiction.
Like predictable characters like that.
It's all I want.
If a character is what they are and they look like they are a thing and that's what they are, then that's also predictable.
Writers next time surprise me by having the character be completely one dimensional exactly what they seem on the surface.
Nothing more to them.
Get, get on it.
Give me, where's, where's, where's my, where's the story for me for my taste?
Um, anyway, next one from phallic person.
Gear second.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, I heard you had a big cock.
Nice.
We did say that again.
It was better this time.
He won up himself.
Voice grail, voice grail, I'm thinking.
Yeah, you know, we could only do one voice grail per episode.
I think we need to like get rid of Samurai.
Samurai man, get out of here.
This is where the voice grail is going.
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, I've got, I don't know.
Has he, has he, I mean, I want to, I'm tempted because he complimented my cock.
Um, I don't know, I might be a little corrupt of me.
That might be nepotism.
What do we think?
Um, okay.
I like, I like it when they say that to me.
Voice grail.
Okay.
Grail.
Fallic person.
So close.
Glad you like, glad you like my cock.
Oh, are we taking Samurai out?
Yeah, only one grail.
This is a new rule.
Only one grail.
Just because it's really funny to do that.
Okay.
Okay, cool.
Just cause it's funny.
Yeah.
Phew.
Oh, I'm safe.
I'm safe for another week.
Thank God, Fallic person.
Uh, no, we just, we just angered the Samurai more to take something away from him.
Uh, no, don't talk, let's not talk about him anymore.
Uh, uh, he's too scary.
Uh, next one is from, uh, is funny story three, two, one, go.
Hello there, PCP funny story.
I once dated a girl that worked at a radio station and she was on the prowl for potential guests.
Obviously she invited me cause I like, uh, wrote a little novella best of my mountain blade playthrough inspired by DJ's light novel.
The one he wrote in a day.
The radio station was completely deserted except for me and her and it was really nice.
Then when the broadcast started, my brain completely farted and I ended up explaining the entire concept of light novels and Aromanga sensei live on national radio.
Ancest and Isekai's and everything in between.
Needless to say, the girl backpedaled the fuck out of that conversation and our little stint didn't last much longer.
The whole mishap probably didn't help, huh?
So, uh, what other, do you have any sort of stories that, and like this?
No.
With the production, like with the music in the background and like the sort of well spoken first part of it.
I thought this was gonna not end like that.
No.
Like redid his like fuck up on the radio on the voicemail.
He really, he really, he really lost the thread at the end there.
That was a funny story.
Why would you talk about incest on a radio station?
Why did you, why did you have to talk about incest explaining the concept of light novels?
Yeah, why would you go to Aromanga sensei of all things?
I don't get it.
Talking about Aromanga sensei and it's like, oh, what's that?
Well, it's about this like love thing between a boy and his sister kind of, but here's the thing about incest in anime.
I can see how it happens.
I feel like this is the product of some like Digi related brain rot.
I don't know.
I feel like blaming Digi for this.
He said he wrote his light novel because you read Digi's light novel.
Yeah, but I, but I, and I feel like we can, I feel like there's correlation here.
It's like if it's, if Digi's responsible for one of those things, he's probably responsible for the other.
That seems fair.
Yeah, for sure.
What was even the question at the end that has, has you had a story?
Have you done anything cringy on a date or something like that?
Yeah, I guess been cringy on a date or embarrassed yourself on national radio.
Well, he said he was dating this girl.
Oh, I missed that part.
I just ended the relationship.
Yeah.
Well, it didn't help.
No, I've never embarrassed myself.
I certainly have never like accidentally said some weird racist shit on a podcast or anything.
Never.
No, all the ladies want to date me actually.
So get fucked, nerd.
Same, but I always reject them.
I say no.
I say, you know, girls don't even know what light novels are and they've certainly never read Irumanga Sensei.
So what's even the point?
Am I right?
I'm right.
All right.
Next one from Zinthos.
Like Azorath Metrion Zinthos?
Maybe.
It's called About Balding.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey there.
I think Nate once brought up that Ben is by far the closest one to going bald in the PCP.
Do you think your personality will change at all when it all goes down?
I've been balding for the past four years and for the first two, it looked pretty all right.
But recently it started looking terrible and I finally gone and shaved my head.
At first it was really surreal, you know.
Suddenly half my wardrobe wore spaghetti sauce stained wife beaters.
Potbelly basically grew on me overnight.
My musculature has been in the town outside of existence.
Started to beat my wife, fuck my kids.
But you know, still trying to be cool.
It's not as bad as you might think it is, really.
Eat your ass.
Zinga.
My head is fucked.
I don't know.
My head just looks like crap and it's bad.
My forehead is huge.
I have like a...
Got a hold of this big idea.
My hairline is kind of swept back.
I don't know.
I'm still not convinced that I'm going bald.
But I just have like, I don't know.
I feel like I kind of look like, I don't know.
My head is huge.
My head is huge and shaped badly.
I don't know.
I probably will be bald and like, eventually.
I don't know how close I am.
I'm probably getting there and I just can't see it.
I mean, I know that I'm like going bald a bit.
And then I look at my dad and he's like, he's got the same like pattern.
But hair still grows on quite a lot of his head.
It's really just like the front, like he's got the vegeta.
Like it goes down in the middle and then goes really high up and then back down.
That's what I've got.
Yeah.
I've kind of got a little bit of that, but like I hate it.
Mine's like uneven.
I have like an uneven widow's peak.
It's very strange.
Mine is my hairstyle.
Mine is a little uneven.
Um, you know, a couple of my, oh man, this makes me like upset.
But I'll say a couple of my uncles have the thing.
Do you know, do you know what a St. Peter's Puff is?
No.
It's when it's like the widow's peak, but you only have the front and like you're
bald other than that.
You know what I mean?
What?
Like you have like a widow's peak that just goes to nothing and it just, the
hair just goes away.
No.
You've got like a four, you've got like a fringe, but then behind the fringe is
nothing.
It's like you're bald, but you sort of have a little tuft that grows like at the
front, like where the point of your widow's peak would be.
Oh, okay.
A couple of my uncles have a little bit of that going on.
And I got to say, I am afraid that one day I will have that.
Just save it, you coward.
I mean, yeah.
I mean, if, if I was at that point, it's like, I need, I might just get fucking
laser hair removal on my head at that point.
Cause like nothing is going, nothing is going to be worse than that.
Like I will, there's no conceivable circumstance in which I would ever want to
grow hair ever again.
If I was, if I was rocking that.
Yeah.
I mean, I have the biggest forehead.
So I guess that makes me the closest to going bald.
You know, you know, fellas, I've been thinking about that estrogen, like, like
unrelated to bolding.
Although I think bolding is just makes everyone think, what if I was a woman
and I could have my hair still?
That'd be good.
So I like, whether or not I go on that would determine whether I actually go
bald, but I feel like even if, like I decide against it and I'm like, I'll
just, you know, be whatever.
If I go bald, I think it'll be all right.
I have like, like a face that's all right.
That's a, that's a, that's a good thing.
I can, I can wear a hat, you know?
I mean, people, people can look good without hair.
It's just like 14 year olds will laugh at you and you just got to accept that.
14 year old boys will say ha ha, because they're 14.
I don't know.
I, I, I shaved my head in college one time and I don't think it looked very good.
I don't think it's really is a, I'm not convinced that it's a look I can rock.
You need like the right, like physique underneath it.
Like, I mean, if you've got a weird shaped skull, whoops.
But like most people have a normal skull, I assume.
But like, I feel like I'm, I'm saying what I'm saying is that I don't think
my head is shaped right to look so, so great, you know, awesome, spectacular.
Look, I don't know anything about the future.
I don't know what, what would work or not.
I just think people, people don't really think about it as much as the person who has the, the boldness.
So it's just like, it's just like everything else in life and in appearance is like, it's whatever.
The, I mean, objectively, it probably would affect my life almost not at all.
But that doesn't stop me from like dreading it.
Same.
You know, yeah.
I don't like it.
Every time I like run my hand through my hair and there's like one or two full out and I'm like, you,
you motherfuckers, you fucking cowards, jumping ship like all the others.
Hmm.
Indeed.
Okay.
Anything, anything more to say about that?
No.
All right.
Next one up is cross Jaden animations porn ethicality.
Three, two, one, go.
Here's my take on Gibbs thing about whether or not porn of Jaden animations is okay or not.
So first of all, we can all agree that drawing porn of a real person,
not an animated puppet isn't okay unless you have their consent.
By the way, this is why I think that the game grumps porn is probably fine to my knowledge.
Dan and Aaron are fine with it.
So drawing porn of them is a victimless act.
But Jaden obviously hasn't given consent to rule 34 of her.
So it shouldn't be allowed, right?
Well, this gets into whether or not porn of her puppet can be considered porn of her because drawing pornography of fictional characters is completely okay.
No consent required.
But when an illustration is meant to represent a real person or even if that illustration is inspired by a real person,
you start to get into a gray area of whether or not they can be considered real.
On the side of the spectrum, closer to real people, you have characters like Mitsuaki Kano from Shirobako,
who may as well literally be Hideo Keano.
And on the side closer to fictional characters, you have someone like Grunkle Stan from Gravity Falls,
who while being loosely based on Alex Hirsch's actual grandfather is obviously his own character,
not meant to be thought of as one and the same with the real life person who inspired his creation.
Obviously, it's up to the individual to decide where any particular character belongs on this spectrum.
But I'd say that Jaden's puppet very clearly falls extremely close to the real person end.
This is because Jaden is speaking directly to the audience with the puppet being meant to represent her real self,
seeing as she uses it to depict actual events that have taken place in her life and actual thoughts and feelings that she has.
So the final verdict is no.
Rule 34 of Jaden Animation's puppet is not okay.
Don't do it.
No.
Bad.
No kisses.
No.
For you.
Die.
You know, all right.
I was thinking about this because it's like the thing with YouTube and parasocial relationships is that people, audiences,
they see YouTubers, Twitch streamers, whatever, internet personalities,
they see them as cartoon characters that aren't real regardless of whether they have a cartoon avatar or not.
They think of people's lives in terms of arcs that happen and events and drama is like a TV show.
They don't think of them as real people.
If you look at comments on loads of really popular videos or even ours,
they don't really think in terms of like these are people.
They think of them in terms of this show of these people in it suck or is bad or like, you know what I mean?
There's a level of dehumanization going on across the board on these sort of platforms.
Yeah.
So I'm like, the porn is just an extension of that, I think, because they don't think about it being like a person that they need to ask for permission.
And also it has a cartoon avatar that has like a design that they can already use.
Okay.
But so what does that mean in terms of your conclusion about this?
My conclusion is really just the same as before.
It's just sort of like realizing that it wasn't just about people who have cartoon avatars.
It's really just about people who live on like are presenting themselves on the Internet in some way.
The people will not like think in terms of like this is a person I need to respect or have empathy for.
This is a cartoon character who has like a TV show called drama that I like keeping up with
and seeing what happens in the next arc of Digibro or whatever.
You know, like it's already stupid and bad.
I think that I disagree with this guy's like initial premise, which he seemed to just take for granted.
The thing about like it's not okay to draw porn of real people.
I don't know if I agree with that.
I kind of think you're allowed to do whatever you want.
I mean, I think you're allowed to do whatever you want, but I think it's...
I don't know if I'm willing to be like, oh, you shouldn't do that.
Like why not?
Yeah, this is the thing.
It's like, are you allowed to think of a person as they appear online as a character rather than a person?
Of course, like you're allowed to get like invested in drama and stuff.
No, you're being a little reductive.
I'm not saying, oh, well, it's not technically illegal.
That's not what I'm saying.
No, I'm not arguing with you.
I'm just sort of like making the connection that like the way we interact with Internet personalities,
porn included is already like non-personal and that is considered okay because like you think of the way celebrities are treated.
And like you can think about it like an individual level like, oh, yeah, I guess it sucks that the paparazzi do those things to all those celebrities,
but people love the stories.
They keep up with those things.
They don't really think of them as a person.
They think of them as a show.
And so in that vein, it's okay, but like you can decide to not participate in the paparazzi in a metaphor sort of way.
You can decide to not like play into that, like not watch drama videos, not draw porn of people.
I don't really understand what point you're making.
The point I'm making is that there isn't, you can't make a rule about this because it's just like humans don't act.
Like obviously you can't litigate it and I wouldn't want that litigated because it's impossible and also stupid to try to like make it illegal
for somebody to not see someone as a human because like you can't do that.
Like there's a lot of ways to explain this.
I'm explaining it badly.
I feel like you could, I feel like the act of drawing porn of someone and like forget about the cartoon avatars thing.
Like a real person.
I feel like the act of drawing, you could set about drawing porn of them in a way that is like harassment.
Like if you do that as like a, you do that and then you like distribute it like to like people they know or something.
You spread this around as like an act of like, you know, to like embarrass them or something.
Like I feel like you could do it in a way that is harassment, but like in that case, I think it's the harassment that is like what's unethical.
Not the act of like drawing another person.
In what is unambiguously like a work of fiction.
It's not meant to be like a photo, like oh, it would be wrong to like deep fake a picture of someone having sex in some compromised position.
Like that would be wrong, but if it's a drawing you just made because you wanted to make it.
I know, I don't think that's, not only do I think it's not wrong.
Why would a deep fake be different?
Well, it would be different because that could be construed as reality.
Right.
If, but if you're, if you're making a deep fake and you're calling it a deep fake and everyone knows it's a deep fake and it's just,
Well, I mean, there's a level to which like, no, if you're making it clear, no, no, no, shut up.
If you're making it clear that it's, if you're making it clear that it's not real, then no, I don't think it's wrong.
Okay.
I mean, the only problem there is that it's someone, it might be negligent because maybe the image could be released.
Yeah, that's what I was trying to say.
Is that like a deep fake is, is what you have to understand that if it's posted without context, people would believe potentially.
You have to, you have to accept some culpability of creating something that could be used like that.
But anyway, my whole point was not to cast a judgment on the ethical, the ethical-ness of it.
I was just sort of thinking about how it relates to everything and not like, if it's okay or not okay to draw porn of a internet personality.
It's also okay and or not okay to do all of the other things that we do associate with like dehumanizing an internet personality.
Yeah.
That's my thought.
Like if you don't think of them as a person already, like I, I guess like when it comes to like making a decision, individual is up to the individual.
Like I wouldn't like lord over people saying, oh, you can't do that.
I wouldn't tell people not to do it.
I would, I would, I would, I would say cringe if I thought something was cringe what people were doing.
But like there's no, there's no rule that I could stand by like for everything.
Dancing around the issue.
I'm saying it, I'm not asking about rules.
I'm, I'm, the question is, is it like wrong?
Is it like bad?
Well, I don't know what that means.
It literally just means like, I don't know.
Do you think it's bad?
Do you think it's unethical?
Do I think it's bad to draw porn of Jaden animations?
Or people in general, but yeah, okay.
Oh, as we can see Jaden animation specifically.
I think, I think I just don't know what would constitute bad.
Like if it is bad, what action do I take from that?
Like, I don't know.
I don't know what I believe about whether or not it's bad because I don't know what bad means or wrong means.
Okay.
Well, I mean, what, what do you think bad means?
What would it, what would it mean for something to be bad in, in this or any context?
Uh, I don't know.
I think it would depend like it, like if something, I don't know.
What do you think make, what do you think makes something bad?
Well, this is like huge, like, I don't know.
I can't answer what I think makes something bad because everything is bad in a different way.
That can't be true.
I don't know.
There must be some kind of unifying thing.
We're getting to like, like, there must be some unifying quality that two bad things share about that, that links them in their bad.
Well, I must be something similar.
What I'm, what I'm struggling with right now is that I don't know how to say I don't like it in because that like something other than like more substantial than I don't like it means it's bad.
Because that does not answer the question in any way.
In my, in my opinion, saying it's bad and saying you don't like it are literally the same thing.
Exactly. So like, how do I explain what I think is bad in a general sense?
I don't understand how that could even happen with language.
Well, well, um, I don't know.
I guess you would have to like reverse engineer what about a thing makes you not like it and then explain like, okay, why, why does this thing meet these criteria?
Well, I mean, I think the goal, the goal would be to come up with some kind of rule that like,
And that's why I was talking about rules, like you can't make rules.
No, but I'm not, I'm not, I'm not talking about like a law.
I'm talking about like an ethical rule that's like, ah, okay.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
I'm not talking about laws and talking about like systems that you use to determine whether or not something is good or bad.
Like a rough definition for bad, like empirically, I feel like willfully and intentionally making someone else uncomfortable, you know, are going against their wishes.
You know, because if it has to be willful, you're doing it on purpose has to be intentional.
I don't know. I don't, I, I, I think, I don't think, I don't think people are always entitled to have their wishes abided by.
No, because like there, there are times where like, things, things will happen circumstantially, you know, like you can do, you can do something unintentionally causing someone discomfort and that's not wrong.
That's just kind of like circumstantial, you know, like if we're both trying to get a job, and I get the job and you don't, and you feel bad about it, I didn't do something wrong.
That was a circumstance, you know, but if like, I fucking slashed your tires so you couldn't get to the interview and I got the job, well, then I did something wrong.
Yeah, um, okay, but like, this, this, say, alright, we'll take the job interview, like, this person, this other person would probably want you not to apply for the job because it would like create competition for them.
And like, it would make it less likely that they would get the job, but like, that doesn't mean that you shouldn't apply for it just because they don't want you to.
Like, you are, you are deliberately going against their wishes and making them and like causing them discomfort by doing it, but that doesn't mean you shouldn't do it.
So I don't know. I don't know if that, I don't know if that rule does it for me.
I feel like the thing I said earlier that you can't define like a system that works with everything. That's why I said it depends.
Sure.
Sure. But like, with specifically the Jaden animations pornography thing, I think what like what I said last time where I went to the guys Twitter, and they were like, they were being an asshole about it.
And saying they don't give a shit what she thinks they're going to do it. Fuck you haters who don't you are like preaching to me about it.
And I was like, that's a shitty attitude. I don't like it.
Yeah.
That's that's that's really it.
Okay.
I don't know. I don't know if all of the people doing Jaden animations porn are doing it with a shitty attitude, but I don't I didn't like the tone of that guy.
Sure.
Okay, well, I just thought that would be interesting to deep dive a little bit on.
Yeah, I mean, there's a real big philosophical like addition to that conversation, like what is bad?
What is good and bad?
I love that. I love that kind of shit.
I mean, I got a little flustered.
I mean, yeah, we won't we're not going to answer it because like, you know, people have been trying to like define like what is good since like the ancient Greeks and before and like we haven't we haven't done it.
So, okay, that's fine. That's fine. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun to talk about my opinion.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think I think that it is bad and I don't like it are the exact same statement.
Yep.
Yeah, I think I don't know.
Whatever. Okay.
I think all right.
Fuck it. Hey, fuck this.
You know, let's listen to the next voicemail from shallow thoughts.
Last one.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, just wanted to say I do miss the other PCP members, but things aren't as bad as everyone in the comments.
Make it out to be.
You guys are doing great.
The comments is so shit.
And yeah, fuck the comments.
Fuck comment sections are all powered to aren't putting voicemails in the speak pipe so they can go to hell.
That's right.
Later.
If they really wanted to make their opinion known, they would have the courage, they would have the stones to make a voicemail, to make a voicemail saying no Nate, no watch.
See you next week.
Yeah.
Oh man, the podcast is dying.
Can't believe this podcast is still going with only three people on it.
Like they know that we play all the voicemails.
Why aren't they doing it?
It's true.
It's truly cow.
It's the lot of them.
Um, no, um, I'm, I'm just, I'm fine with it.
I've, I've, I've like, I've reached Nirvana and I'm like, there's nothing, there's literally nothing wrong with a podcast.
That's like me, Tom Gibb.
That's great.
And I'm have absolutely no problem showing up.
And I'm, and I'm, and I'm actually grateful for the opportunity.
Dev.
Hey guys, thanks for being, thanks for being here with me on this episode of the procrastinators podcast.
I appreciate it.
I'm talking to you two, Tom.
Oh, not the audience.
I thought we were wrapping up.
Well, I was kind of, I was kind of doing both at the same time.
The audience and the co-hosts.
Yes.
It's always, it's always a pleasure.
It's always a good old time.
Do we, do we have anything else we want to get out there into the world before we wrap up?
Go to the big booby mommy milkers discord, link in the description.
Yes.
And enlist boober and jiggle.
I still, I still can't decide.
I haven't, I haven't made up my mind between, between big boober and mommy milker.
But as I said in the, in the server, I like the, I like the name mommy milker better than big boober.
Big boober sounds like, sounds like booger and that's gross.
But, but I like jiggle is so much better than squirt.
The jiggle command is better.
So I'm like, there's just two, two sides with like, they both have their pros and cons.
And I just can't, I can't just pick a side.
You're gonna have to, you're gonna have to choose, you're gonna have to choose one, one of these days because default position is like flat freak.
You're like into flat chests.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna start this, the stay flat revolution.
No, no, stay flats can get fucked.
They can get flattened by us.
Are you going to add smothering?
Um, I mean, it's, it's up to Doon Coon because she's doing all the coding, but it'll be cool.
A lot of things would be cool, but a lot of things would also be work.
Hey, you should add slime.
No, no, you should put some slime in there.
Like why not, right?
No, I think that's terrible.
What if like slime girl, what if like slime girls had big booby mommy milkers?
I mean, they do.
Yeah.
Hmm.
I don't know.
I just thought that was interesting.
Um, did you know that, did you know that people die in car accidents all the time, even with big booby mommy milkers?
They don't actually work as airbags is the unfortunate thing.
Uh, terrible.
Unfortunate.
What are you even good for?
God damn.
Tragic.
Uh, okay.
Well, uh, fucking, uh, patreon.com.
The procrastinators.
Slash the procrastinators.
Uh, speak pipe, send us a voicemail.
Tell us how you're not, how, tell how you don't watch the show anymore because it's too low energy at the, at the.
PCP voicemail.
Speakplate.com.
Um, join the fucking Minecraft server.
Uh, PCP Minecraft server.
When was the next stream?
I guess this will be out.
I said I, I said I was going to do it on Tuesday.
I might.
That will have happened already.
Yeah, I might delay till Wednesday, but I will be either Tuesday or Wednesday today this week.
So we will have done another one and I'll probably do another one this weekend because I don't know why not.
I've been, I've been enjoying them.
Oh, I think, I think let me just, let me just look at the, the, the dates.
This is going to come out on the 18th.
Um, I'm going away for a bit on the 21st or the 20th.
So I probably won't be on the next PCP and I'll be gone for like two weeks.
Oh, why?
Where are you going?
Just a little dog holiday.
We're going to, we're going to go, we're going to take the dog on holiday and go to a secluded house family, family secluded house with a dog so we can run around.
Um, just as a change of, change of pace for everyone.
I see.
Okay.
Um, well, oh no, oh no, we're going to, we're going to go even lower energy.
I'm going to be, I'm going to be stuck with me.
It's just going to be me and Tom.
Oh my God.
No.
Are we going to get, are we going to get like a Tom solo cast?
That's what I want to know.
Maybe someday.
We almost did.
We almost did that one time.
Did we?
When?
And then get on.
Yes, that's true.
I was a little late.
You know what, Gib?
I mean, you're such a, you're such a toxic and hostile influence that maybe you being gone.
We'll bring back, we'll bring back some of the old guy.
Everyone comes back like, God, I hated Gib.
I can't believe.
Indeed.
I guess we'll just, we'll have to wait and see.
Okay.
I guess we'll have to wait and see.
That's it.
End of the show.
Big, big, big, big success.
Big win for the PCP.
Yet again, we did it.
Give us money.
Buy our shirt.
But check the shirt in the description.
I'm going to go make that shirt.
Buy the, I have COVID shirt.
Right now.
It is the new thing.
Hey, the new.
Oh my God.
I have COVID shirt.
Right now.
Buy the, I have COVID shirt.
It is the new thing.
Hey, the new.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, the procrastinators podcast.
Oh yeah.
I love them.
Ha, ha.
I have COVID, right?
That's that thing that they say.
Cool.
Make it real.
All right.
End the podcast.
Goodbye.
Sweet dreams.
Bye.