My friends ask me why I cry.
It's cause I feel like I wanna die. These tears spring from my eyes. Every since you said goodbye.
Oh, I'm gonna cry like a man. Cry like a man. As hard as I can. Yes, I can. And if you had a heart, then maybe you'd start to understand. Oh, I know you understand.
All the cool shit on the internet. I'm the best guy ever and I'm joined by my basket of deplorables as always. Ben Saint. That's me, every buddy. Digibro. We're gonna put some pro crass right up yo ass. And Hippocrit.
And so, as everyone famously knows now, we are doing a new thing where we're getting suggestions for topics off of Twitter. So everybody can go to, yeah, it's famous. You tweeted it like five minutes ago.
No, that's not what I'm saying. Like, we, I, last episode, or before last, because we decided to do Pokemon on our own. But before that, we're doing a thing where we're just questions, topics people ask us on our Twitter is what we're just gonna talk about on the show that they've asked just throughout the week. So anytime, go to Twitter and tweet at tpcrestinators.
But by the time you're hearing this, it will be too late.
Well, for next week. No, this understanding that the concept, this podcast, the crying podcast was suggested on Twitter. Who suggested this name?
Oh, yeah, the right, right. So this was suggested by Palm Top Vulture, or at Pop Vulture. And their suggestion was, as a suggestion for a podcast topic, how about art and moments in media that make you cry? So thank you, Pop Vulture.
I think we're going to expand that a little bit to...
That made us cry, or that made us cry.
That make, apparently.
The tense there is important for me.
So they asked make. They asked make you cry. So still to this day.
I don't think there's anything that will make me cry consistently. And if there is, then I don't know how to test it.
Like, I'd have to watch something every single year and update my, did this make me cry, ometer, which is not something...
I know some people who do that. I know some people who are like, I watch it every month and I cry every time.
But I don't usually watch something more than once every few years.
That's what's funny, because I am probably the biggest media cry baby that I know. I cry all the time when I'm watching stuff.
Like, whenever I watch, whenever I just hear, Sorairo Days come on the radio, or not on the radio, but on my fucking MP3 player, whatever, I cry.
My friend Ghostly, I know he's cried many times just hearing that song.
Wait, I do it to all kinds of animals.
Which one's Sorairo Days?
Well, specifically, it calls to mind.
Oh, the girl, when you say the girl in login theme, did you ask?
Well, everyone, yeah.
Okay, but the thing is, what makes me cry listening to songs like that is the emotions that evoke.
So whenever I listen to that song, that song is the insert song, which every time they do the theme song of a show during the Big Climax finale, it's always a 10 out of 10 best thing ever they do.
I cry every time I hear Ro Ro fight the power, and I think of that picture of the bird sitting on the sign that says no birds.
Yeah, that is a good one.
It's good to me.
So when I hear that song, because that song plays in its entirety throughout the climax, I just in my mind play the movie of how it starts up with the da da da da da da da da da da da.
That's when someone's like, no, not yet!
and then Lord Genome is like, she-bon!
And then the whole like the whole sequence plays up to the ultimate victory over the antispirals
So it just calls that whole greatest scene ever to my mind and that's true of just like every I kind of want to
I mean, I don't like tears don't form in my eyes
But there's lots of like things that I like get really emotional about and I'm like, oh, yeah
Yeah, it's the coolest thing ever but tears don't come. I'm wondering like
I don't well. Yeah, I don't actually cry a lot personally. I'm gonna try to be very rigid with this
I'm only going to select things where I have shed
At least one actual tear not just teared up not just welling like eyes full of tears
No, something has to fall down my cheek because I have a less sensation of the tear rolling down
I never get tears
There's maybe two
Times where I can remember that happening of the top of my head two times. Well, yeah, like a
For a podcast right welling up as far as I go
Emotion I felt tears rolling down my face just watching shelter the other day and I've kind of cooled off on it
But at the time at its peak but the reason I ask about the tear thing is that I think just some people make tears more than others
Yeah, yeah, and you get to an emotional level where you would be crying if you made as much tears as someone
Even I can be like I can be like sobbing and tears aren't actually rolling down my face. That's interesting
Yeah, I think if I think if it's sobbing it counts
I think we're gonna classify this as
It was not something that lasted like a half a second
You know just like I have lots of things that will make me tear up for like half a second when it's right at the emotional
Climax like right at that moment, but then you know the second it's over it all just
Drives right back out. You know the problem, you know, it's not there anymore. The problem with you guys is that
I'm I'm a golden god and you guys all your tear ducts are clogged with all that fat all that fat
Fill it up that shit. They can't squeeze them through. That's your problem. It hit the treadmill my friends
You got it. You got to be a vegan like that guy in Scott Pilgrim. Yeah
Yeah, you know, you know how most people only use 10% of their brains because the other 90% is all full of curds and way
Yeah, that's true
So, yeah, it seems pretty clear that people have different like degrees of their crying capacity
It's it's it's it's something that I've got like
Rolled eyes are like people like oh, you don't cry because I don't often but it's like I don't literally
Tear up but I do get emotional about things and people always say, uh
You're just you're just pretending to be tough. You fucking loser. I don't like that. It's like I want to say
For the record, I also don't don't cry much
Which is why
Like I'm being so strict about it because there's such a small tiny pool of times
I have shed actual tears that I literally have a list. I have a list of every individual tear
I've shed while consuming media. So Jesus Christ. Well, that's interesting. I'm gonna go through it in the course of this podcast
I could I could list too many to name. So, uh, I really am a big cryer
I cry a lot when I when I do all kinds of media stuff
So there's no point in going through my I could bring up one that
A lot of you might also agree with which is the ending of Toy Story 3
Oh, yeah, well, which part specifically because there's any part and then there's the
It was it's the bit cry at the ending of Toy Story 3. It's the bit near the end
Uh, where Andy's giving the toys away and he's like, oh, yeah, that's the one I'm 17
But I still sort of care about these for some reason but I'm giving them to a little girl
I'm saying goodbye forever and it's like I don't know everyone gets their little moments when when he's just like this is ham
He's like the evil baron
Oh my god, I want your dark souls
Ravenpure
It's a lone dinosaur
I hope you're recording this jesse because this is gold and the people are gonna want to hear it
Well, I'm glad you're here jesse. We were just talking about how we wanted you. Well, we what's the topic this week?
Jen's crying. It's media that's made you cry, which I know you have basically everything
Let me tell you people about crying, you know old uncle endless has been doing a lot of that lately
And uh, you know, but by lately, I mean the last 27 years
I've cried a thousand tears and I'll cry a thousand more
I have yeah, I have both on video and in person witnessed jesse literally crying while describing something
Uh, I know it happens in the batman versus superman video when he reads um reads that passage from that batman comic
And I believe you shed an actual tear that glistened in the light of your of your uh basement that glistened in the light of my yellow room
an actual
He stained tear
Rolling down my jaundice cheek
And I could hear that you were crying in the the the second panel cast and you described the spider-man
scene yeah, I I cried I cried twice in that panel cast and I cut one of them out because it was it was too much
Jesse and me I think are birds of a feather when it comes to crying. Uh, we you seem more predisposed to to this kind of uh
Gay activity as opposed to you guys
You know, I have it's the most straight thing in the world
I agree over time. I have I mean as a kid
I always didn't want to cry and that's still sort of true like I every time tears come. It's like it's unnatural
It's unusual. I don't I'm not used to this and I try and stuff it back even though I'm alone
That's true. I feel that I feel I feel like kind of weirdly self-conscious about it when it when it happens
I'm like, is this right? Is this right? Yeah, I know what you mean
Uh, I feel I want I feel that about not crying
Like I have so many times where I'm witnessing something emotional
And I'm starting to get there, but I don't cry and then I worry that I'm just such a jaded like
Like that that I've I'm so broken that I can't even cry at anything
And I have I have a real legitimate jealousy of jesse's
Like whenever I see jesse feeling something so strongly and like why can't I feel anything that strongly? Why can't I feel?
Oh, I so know it's a it's a gift and it's a curse buddy. Let me tell you
Yeah, it's my burden. I'm sure I wouldn't want it if I was on the other end when it would that pendulum swings in the other
Direction, I think I you know I I might be like the most emotional person I've ever met in my life
And it's a it's a terrible terrible thing
You know, that's funny. I actually kind of feel guilty. I also second guess myself like ben
When it's like is this right? But the thing is I'm usually already crying by that point and I'm just kind of like
Oh, am I
Do do I because that's the thing I feel like I cry too easily and I worry that it's uh, it's cheapening it
Even though it doesn't matter to anyone except me, but I kind of value my own cries
I don't want to pass them out like fucking candy. You know, I wanted to be important and yeah
I guess when when you you you talk about something you like and you said, oh, yeah, it was so good
It made me cry. That's like a like a an indicator of how emotional and how good it is
And if you cry it's something that you're like, oh, I guess I don't really care about it
But I cried so a man's tears are like a woman's vagina
They need to only be shared with the public on very rare occasions
Or else you're trash
That's right. That's right. That's real quick before we even continue any further. Let's do a sink test with jesse
On the count of three say cry
one two three cry cry
Okay, that's good enough. Okay
Um, just had to make sure before that I don't I don't want us to get to the end that we don't remember at the end
That's right
So all right. Well, we've talked a lot about our like philosophies of crying to media
We need more actual examples. We know Nate cries every time he hears the opening theme of girl in the gond
I do every time. Oh also the one where um, you know, like there's what there's one in the middle of the episode where
Simone becomes a man when uh, when he finally, you know, sacks episode 11 that one too
When we're nears behind him when he's for a recent example, that's right. Um, she bought up
But uh, but uh, shut up
All right. All right for a recent example
Um
The the show that we watched for a plebe in the weed planetaria got me pretty close once or twice there
Yeah, I remember I kept looking over it
Emotional narratives. I kept looking over seeing Ben and Jesse almost made us cry. It was the fucking closest that hadn't a while
Okay. All right. All right. Honestly, it looked like Ben was crying
I don't know if there was any tears
But I kept looking over at Ben and Jesse who were losing their shit and that's why
For for anyone there were there were some tears welling up and my lip was quivering. You know, that's okay
for anyone who doesn't know why we ended the plebe in the weed that way because it was
Because it was such an emotional episode and we had just been watching baby cakes diary number two
Which is the episode where uh, you know, baby cakes and his dad and his granddad
They all just like break down crying
After this like this huge like it's just this crazy emotional turn the episode takes where they all start singing and crying
And they just destroy everything in the house and burn it down
And we all thought it was like the most emotionally poignant expression ever
So after watching this this show we were all like standing around talking about how feelsy it was we were like, oh my god
The emotions. Uh, we can't take it. I was like, what if we just unleash and we just like break everything in the set
Just like a baby cakes and it would be the perfect expression of how emotional this show made us feel
Um, though it it ended up being portrayed more that we were all mad about me, uh, not giving the show
It's true. Yeah, it didn't it didn't quite have that baby cakes pathos
Uh, but I mean what does no nothing true true
I so okay. Let's hear some more. Oh, sorry. Yeah, go ahead. Oh, get there
There uh
Well, uh, the the only other one I can think of off the top of my head. There's probably more. Um, is the ending of okami
I don't know if any of you've played that
Not at the ending of okami, but I don't I'm interested in your reason remember the ending very well
The ending was like you go through the whole world
The whole of japan and then you save the world
But then okami has to to leave forever and he never and she never gets to come back and you mean amaturasu
Yeah, well, I think okami's a pretty cool guy
That's you know, what I just I think okami literally means great god, which is what she is so technically that's appropriate
okay
And then you soon has to go and and spread the tale of of everything that happened to everyone alone
And I'll tell you I'll tell you what was oh, I'm sorry
I didn't mean to interrupt but what I what I did really love about that part
The best part to me was when you're fighting
I forget the name of the big bad, but you're fighting the big bad in that heaven ship and uh, you have to
This is a moment that might have brought some tears years ago
And I just don't remember but it's when over over the course of the game
You've helped everyone in japan in all these various ways and at the end
It is their prayers to you the god that give you the power you need to finally defeat it
No come and become god mode amaturasu now that was a great emotion powerful moment of that bending and then the credits song as well
The the thank you reset or whatever it's called
That's just got all the the cool parts
It's a great game, man. It's a really good song. I cry to that occasionally
almost cry
Uh jesse you had you were about to say one it sounded like what oh, yeah
um
You know, I don't know there's there's a lot of like
Like I could name like a million movies and stuff and like things that video games that make me cry
But what really always
Just just really opens up a hole inside me
Just like just rips me open and destroys me all the time
Is just when I think about my friends not you guys my actual friends
The ones right of course the ones that when I hang out with you guys
I feel guilty about not being around them and I resent you guys a little bit for even being a part of my life
You know we're enablers. Yeah
um
Yeah, so like uh, where we where are you going with that just I just I just I just really wanted to confess how much I hate
all of you okay
I hate to say it nobody gives a shit because this is about media that makes me cry
Nobody cares about this is our media and it's gonna make everyone in the world cry when they hear it
Because I'm connecting with my audience like I always do because I'm the best guy at that
Damn you. You know
Fucking you what the fuck? I hate him. So sure. Okay. All right. That's fair. This is a media this show
Makes sense to me. No, it's terrible. Oh, yeah, every time I listen to the procrastinators podcast. I well up a little inside
It's a bummer now, it's you know, I really
I really have a lot of sentiment inside me for the people close to me and it really
It really makes me a a wreck if I if I if I dwell on it too much
Like uh, you know, like uh, like I'll have some friend
Or you know and she's like going through a breakup or anything and she's like all crying
And and I'm just like trying to help her and I'm just like trying to tell her how much that she means to me
But then just saying that is making me cry
So now I'm crying harder than her and it's like who the hell is supposed to be cheering up who at this point
And so then I'm the weirdo and so then I've got a fucking everyone's judging me
So then I go to a party and I I'm the fucking guy at the party crying
Nobody wants to be the the crying guy at the party
Nobody wants to be sitting there crying into another man's birthday cake
And everyone's yeah, no no no one no one came there looking for a reenactment of the day of the clown cried, but they got it
You know, uh, that's really that's interesting jesse, uh, you seem like a very empathetic person, uh, and it's it it amuses me
Or this is
Well, it does it does
That's actually kind of the thing because like I've been thinking lately how you know how I'm all about like I'm I'm a
I'm a futurist and I want I want humanity to succeed and go to the stars and I want all these things to happen
You fucking yeah
I'm in the middle of an emotional breakdown at a party and I'm crying. I'm I'm losing my mind and it's like oh, I'm using
That amuses me
All right, it does because I was just thinking about how
Uh, I want all these things for humanity and I interests would have been a better word than amusing
Yeah, okay, it just interests me. It it makes me think of something else that relates to me, which is cool
Uh, which is just how I I don't give a shit about people on an individual level basically at all
Uh, like I'll see people and I'll just I'll hate them. I'll just hate them for no reason
We're like I I want the best for humanity, but I hate everyone. I want everyone dead. Nate. Let me let me let me respond to that
I I feel the same way a lot of the time, you know
I feel all misanthropic and like oh, I hate people and I hate everyone
And you know, I get frustrated at people a lot, but I always
Like every single fucking time when when I actually
Come to know someone I always think better of them than I did that is true
Like saw them and got my you know initial impression was like oh this person's just this this person's just that this person
Must suck and these are that ways and then I'm like I'm always I always change my mind
So I try I try to keep it in mind
I try to tell myself like don't judge that person
You know, you would like the more if you got to know them you always do
But like it's it's it's you know, it's my natural inclination is to be like oh fuck that guy
But that's a very mature point there ben. I try to find a point
You know, it's funny because much like with the like what we said about crying earlier where I said I kind of like
Feel broken because I can't cry as much as I want to
I feel similarly
About like other people where like I I kind of always assume that everyone's great
Like I assume everyone I see I'm like that guy's probably doing something interesting or has something going on in his life
More than what I have
You would think that
But then I but then I have no ability to connect with any of those people and I don't feel like
Pressured to do so and like even like what jesse talking about his friends who he's like, you know
I miss them and wish I connected with them more like I've kind of
Completely don't even talk to any of my friends anymore like ever since ben and divu moved in
I've gotten to the like I mean
I was already pretty alienated from my friends because the fact that they all have different interests and we don't do any
The same stuff and I'm not the type to go out of my way to put myself
In a situation where I'd hang out with them and now that I've got ben and divu
I just don't even talk to him anymore
Like I haven't even seen half of my friends in three months
Plus to be fair like we haven't seen each other in days because I haven't left my room
Ben has been straight up in his room for like three days now for like poke a lot
I've been sick. I haven't had any desire to leave my room lately
I have I saw divu once and I saw you for like a second when you'd ask me if I left water boiling
Which I didn't because I'm responsible. Thank god. You've got the cure to power of the vape to nurse you back to hell
The vape is what fucking caused this problem. I'm convinced. I'm convinced it dehydrated my throat and caused this whole
Nonsense, I don't know possibly
Well, I still see victor and divu so
You know as long as I see like one person a day even if it's only for five minutes
I feel like I've got a ton of social interaction for that day
Something happened in between me making 300 videos
Every single fucking day of my life
But we have gotten
Completely off the topic of crying in media. This is now just a piece of media for people to cry to as jesse
Expected this to be just a sort of a general emotional discourse
I mean because I don't think the guy really cares that much about like when the tear physically comes down you cheek
it's about it's about
Oh, it's like that future drama episode where you know when when that
Fuck the the asian girl. She's gonna marry that little green alien man. Yeah, the kiff right
It's it's not about the fact that he touches lila and it was lila's dna that became his his little babies
It's it's about the person who evokes that feeling that causes him to be able to reproduce
Which just happens to manifest in the first person incidentally
You know what I mean who all has cried watching future drama. There's so many times. Probably absolutely
The dog man
Yeah, yeah, he waited. He waited. He always waited. He didn't forget
I because I mean it's been in fucking ages since I saw any of those episodes for the first time the dog one's emotional
The one about his brother
Everyone mentions the dog one I'd forgotten about yancy fucking yancy yancy's a really emotional one and then the one where
At the end we see how lila's parents took care of her for her whole life and it plays baby love child
By pizzicato five the one where a obscure japanese pop band the one with fries mom where he
Um went into her dream at the end
Oh, yeah, I remember that I don't think I saw that that wasn't I remember I either I watched a bunch
Yeah, that was that was a new one too. Yeah, I was one of the new wish
It was okay. No, I didn't see it. I also really love the the very last episode
Which just has of lila and fry just spend their life together and then at the end
There I don't know
There's something really emotional about like you want to give it one more round and then they just like start
Like time loops and it's just something beautiful about how like these two of this connection
Good never even even now. It's just it's just really getting to me. How much these two guys have come to care about each other
That's that's beautiful. This podcast doesn't end until one of us makes someone else cry by way of remembering a scene
It's not gonna happen for me. I'm distracted. I'm distracted training for the pokemon race
Yeah, ben. Did you have any uh any particular examples of something that has made you at least even well?
You said planetarium. I said planetarium. I have another one. I have another one
And maybe you guys can help me
This is there's a movie that like I cried more watching it than I might have ever cried in my life
And I don't remember what it was called eternal sunshine of the spotless mind. No, I haven't seen it. That was a good one
Everyone tells me how much they cry at them. It's like a romance
Sort of between this like gothy teen girl and this like schlubby middle-aged man
Hmm and it's it's got a name its name is like it's not harold and maud, but it's got a name
That's like oh that sounds familiar two names
Uh lowlita
No
She's like a fucking goth or something and he's a beetle. I don't know I
People in the comments comment on this shit
It's a it's a sad romance between like a teen goth chick and this like and this like fucking middle manager
Ty wearing that looking yeah, you're definitely talking about harold and maud. No, that's that's definitely beetle juice
Wait, it does sound like beetle. I know there is a harold and maud, but I don't think that's it
Oh, yeah, I don't think that's it either well looking at it. You have to do some research and uh, I don't know people in the comments say something
Now harold and maud is like a dark comedy
Hey ben here's a here's a moment uh that I believe we both cried at the same time
Uh, this is a deeply emotionally moving uh situation so ben and I when we were very young
We're playing mario rpg and we got to the very last boss. This is not exactly what people are asking
This is what they want so
Wait, you told the story. You've told the story on the show before
I remember
Who I don't care who cares did you go on Nate? All right, so tell the people what they want to know
I will I'm sure somebody wants to know now
So we're fighting the very last boss smithy and at this point we're we're babies. We are not veterans
This was like one of our first rpgs. I use I used malo. He has an ability that shows you how much hp the boss has
He had like psychopath. He had like no hp
He would have died in one hit if I had one attack that turn
One died and then the guy fucking summon boulders or whatever like twice in a row and just wipe the whole party
And we've been trying to be we flipped our shit
We've been trying to be the boss for so long. We've been playing mario rpg for like old man
We fucking cried and went ballistic that that 26 hp. He had left is burned into my mind
I'm never gonna forget. It might it might have been 46, but it was one of those our dad got really upset because the game made us
Cry he thought he wasn't out of the game for doing that to us. Yeah, I remember this video
Why did you tell the story before maybe it was about parents reacting to video games negatively?
You definitely told it before though. I might I might not have been there for that, but whatever
How could you not have been there? You told the story. It was you. I thought you were saying ben to told it
No, you told this story before
Well, whatever they heard it twice. Okay, let's move on. That was a joke. Anyway, I didn't want to dwell on it
Uh, has everyone gone except did you now give did you do one already?
Uh, yeah, I went I I couldn't really think of I can't really think of any
Specific times. There's probably lots of times as a kid like playing fire emblem where a character died after like 40 hours
playing a single level
Yeah, you know to try and grind through that's fair. Oh, you know what? Uh, sorry
May here's just one short one. I've probably told the story before but when I was
Reading one piece on the day that uh ace died luffy's brother died
I was supposed to go on a date with my girlfriend and a bunch of our friends
We're all gonna go out and do shit in the snow and um
My ex gonna go out and shit in the snow
But but like she comes into my room
I I didn't I didn't shed a tear but I was just sitting in my room
Ace was dead luffy was never going to be the same
He was a broken man and in walks like my girlfriend and she's like, all right, Nate
Let's go. Let's go fun in the snow and I'm just like what the fuck
My friend my friend just died and he wanted me to go play in the fucking snow and she did not understand
What was going on? She did I explained it look luffy my my my buddy luffy his brother just died
I can't fucking go on a date right now
And uh, she just was like she was so mad at me for so long after that. She did not get it
That's why I hate you lauren the worst person i've ever known. I hate you. I'll never forgive you for what you did to me
Oh god cut this please
How could you do it um
There you go. Um speaking of tragedy. Um, I don't know if this counts. I don't know
I think I might have teared up a little bit when fucking goose died
Oh, really but not his lovely roulette. Yeah, my well. He was a yeah when when monkey killed my my fucking uh
Flight commander flight or no flight lieutenant goose. Look, it's not that it wasn't actually sad
I think I was I was much more angry than I was
That's okay. I think I might have just just just had like fucking tears of tears of like just frustration and like hating myself for having for having
You know, that's that's fine. That's like a father's I went through the stages of grief like so hard
I was like no, it's he's not really gonna gonna gonna kill goose and then I was like, okay
But like it's not it's not it's not really that bad, you know like and then like oh, but but
Yeah, it's and there's just mad just probably did some bargaining like maybe I don't have to nuzzle like this
Particular pokemon. Maybe I can just let this one live bargaining. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, but you know, that's
I I want to ask uh
Angry tears angry tears
We're all very much thinking like, you know consume piece of media cry
Uh, have any of you had times because I've had a few of these where it was more that you watched something
And then like what it made you think about eventually made you have a total fucking breakdown
Like, um, well, you know, yes, and even I'll give an example to kick us off just so I can just so I can finally
Share one, um, this is I did not cry watching this show
But an example for me was when I was uh, like in when I was going into 11th grade
And I watched the show manavi straight, which is an anime series about a bunch of high schoolers who basically the main character is this girl manavi who like
Um becomes a student council president and she's trying to have like a great student
Festival on like the last you know the last year that she's going to be in high school
And this high school is kind of shutting down because it's in a future where high school is like not really a thing anymore
And everyone just doesn't take it seriously
And she tries to have the most fun high school ever and then the last episode is like all the characters are graduating
And they're all talking about what they're going to do in the future
And you know, like most of them have plans except manavi and she's like i'm just going to become a freeder
Which just means like go around and get random part-time jobs and just do whatever
And everyone's like what how can you how is that possible because you could do anything
You're such a great leader you did all this stuff over the course of the show and she's like, you know
I could be happy doing anything
So i'm just going to go do whatever I want and like I was about to start
Uh like taking all these advanced classes in school
And I was trying to like fast-track myself to do like some kind of successful
Collegiate career, you know like thinking oh, I really got to succeed in school
If I ever want to make anything of myself and then I see manavi like just yeah, I can be happy doing whatever
I'm going to be a freeder and I was like
And I had just a total mental fucking breakdown that night and like just cried all night long and couldn't like just trying to figure out
What I was going to do with my future incidentally 11th grade miserable
Everyone's heard about it probably on the depression podcaster on my let's play show very bad year
But yeah, manavi incited a total breakdown. That's that's really interesting to me because I uh when I was in high school
I
So it was sort of in a similar way. I didn't really know what I wanted to do
But I insisted my ego demanded that I take
Even even the valedictorian didn't do this, but I took every single ap class that was offered and like it's fucking psychotic
It was really dumb
But I passed them all but I got like b's and c's for the most part because I I didn't actually care about them
Nor did I care about what they would do for me
I was only interested in like proving to everyone how smart I was and in the end
Like I got worse grades than most people or you know like the higher level people
So it was it entirely shot myself on the foot for no reason
And it wasn't even you know to accomplish anything other than satisfying my own ego
So yeah, it was just a big waste of time to do shit like that
And living living your life like her and like she just wants to be happy
You know, you you don't need all this extra bullshit. This is kind of tying into the whole school thing
You don't need these don't listen to procrastinators school sucks. I was gonna say go listen to uh fucking uh the college dropout
And uh and shit
Um my degrees are gonna keep me warm
My dad gave me all his degrees and I wear them on my clothing and I feel so good about them
And I'm gonna get more degrees so I can get more degrees and it's just gonna make the happiest part of the world
It's cool. Go watch the school one. Does anybody have examples of shit that made them break down crying?
I have a lot of examples man. Let me tell you people about the probably
like the thing
That has like the the highest the piece of media that has the highest ratio
Of moments that utterly destroy me and and turn me into like a balling sobbing mess. It's the rocky series
Oh, just that fucking
Oh my god, that fucking whole series is so emotional and that score the music if I hear like one note of like the music from those movies
Not the ones that everybody not not not like the
Yeah, not bad, but I mean like there's this there's this piece of music that plays in rocky every time something sad happens
And every time I fucking even think of it if I just like try to picture the notes in my head
I'll start crying at notes. There's so many parts the whole fucking saga because it's it's the greatest
It's the greatest saga in the history of fiction. It tells
It's the it's just like a guy's entire life story
It's it's just like 30 40 years in a dude's life. He like he starts out
He's 30 in the first movie and in the most recent movie creed
He's like 70 and you're just and you're just seeing this guy get older
And all of his like triumphs and his trials and tribulations everything he gains and everything he loses
And it's like the most real human saga that was ever put to film in the history of mankind
That that's fucking you know the the the first movie when he's when he's you know, he's all pissed off
You know because uh mickey is grilling him about what a bum he's become and how he's never amounted anything
And he's just getting pissed off and he's like
And he's like punching the wall and yeah, I feel it
I feel it's so hard that frustration of not accomplishing what you want to accomplish in your life of looking at yourself
And hating yourself and being a bum especially especially because mickey was the one who would kind of ignored him up to that point
And only now is mickey into it. Yeah, like does that scene where he's like hey mickey? Why are you always pushing me?
Yo, why are you always, you know, you know, why are you always yelling at me and mickey's like, you know
Why I hate you rock because you had something you could have been somebody but you didn't you ended up breaking thumbs for some
two-bit mob boss and and rocky's like
The whole movie is just
And i'm watching it going
Me too man
And he's fucking and then there's that part in rocky 3
Where mickey dies and mickey's you know, it's after he fucking he he because because rocky wasn't listening to mickey
He had to fight clubber lang and mickey kept telling him rock. This guy's gonna
Clapper you he's gonna kick your ass unless you take it seriously
And and rocky was getting all full of himself because he was a champion and he was like
You know, I'll just I'll just you know training this high tech gym
I'll take a I'll take a selfie with these fans and you know, I don't really give you
Then he goes and he goes
And and like right before the fight, you know clubber lang like pushes mickey
And then they have the fight and clubber lang just kicks the shit out of rocky
He beats the shit out of him and rocky loses the fight and it's this humbling experience
And and he realized you know, you know, I should have listened to mic mic was right
But then he finds out that mix like in the in the locker room having a heart attack and dying
And he runs the mic and and mic's dying and he's sitting there and he's crying
You can't even understand what the fuck he's saying because he's fucking sylvester stalone
He has too many emotions sylvester stalone has the same thing that I have
He has too many emotions and he's got a half paralyzed face
And it's this perfect concoction that makes him the greatest actor of all time and it makes him, you know
Like something about sylvester stalone has the ability to convey emotion on a level on on a grand scale
Beyond what any other person in the history of mankind is capable of and it connects with me
And I feel I have a I have a spirit bond with sylvester stalone and when I see him sad
I get sad and I feel everything he's feeling
And and and mix and mix like
Oh, did you do it rock? Did you win the fight? Did you win the fight? And he goes? Yeah
We well, he's lying to mic
He's telling him he won the fight and then mic dies and it's the saddest fucking thing ever and then in rocky 4
When apollo creed dies, he gets killed by avan drago and and you know and rocky, you know, he has he's he's gonna throw in the towel
He's gonna throw in the towel for for apollo and apollo looks at rocky
You know apollo his old enemy who's become his friend through the years because they've they've had so many battles with each other
That they're like they're the original goku and vegeta
It's it's apollo and rocky and you know, they're friends now and and he's watching this fight
He's watching apollo creed get his ass kicked by this fucking russian superman super villain
Ivan drago
He's got the towel and he's like I gotta throw in the towel apollo and apollo's wife is there and and his wife is like
Come on rocky throw in the towel. What the fuck and apollo looks at rocky. Don't you throw in that towel, man?
Don't you do it, man? He's got too much pride. He's got that warrior pride
He won't let rocky throw in the towel and then apollo goes down and he dies
fucking Ivan drago just
Punches him to death and he dies in the rig and and and rocky finally throws in the towel
But it's too late apollo's dead and then he has then he goes to apollo's funeral and he's like
You know, uh, apollo always did things this way
And then
And then you get to rocky five and it's like the worst movie ever rocky five. It's it's a piece of shit
Nobody likes it. It's
It's the bad one. He's there's this guy called timey gun, but even in the bad one
There's great scenes that make you cry. There's that fucking part, you know, because rocky can't fight anymore
He's got brain damage from all the punching he's he's had if he gets punched anymore
He'll die
So he can't he can't box anymore, but he's trying to relive his glory
He's trying to train this up-and-comer timey gun and timey gun is a huge dick
And he's taken advantage of rocky's kindness and he's going off with this other promoter and he's just being an idiot
And and everyone knows it and everyone can see up at rocky
But rocky doesn't want to see it because it's all he has left
It's all he has left
He just has to to train this guy and so he can live vicariously through timey gun success
So he's fucking trying to fight him and adrian's yelling at him. She's going god damn it rocky
Don't you see you're fucking he's taking advantage of you and rocky's like
What do you think i'm stupid? I know
And then there's just the fucking there's that part where where rocky has that flashback
He's he's got a flashback to like where he was younger training with mick and mick
He gives him this uh this uh little crucifix. No, not a crucifix. It's golden gloves
It's silver gloves from like some boxing thing. He's like, I don't even remember what the fuck it is
But he's like, you know, you know, rocky machiano gave me this back in the day and now i'm giving it to you rock
And and and and and and so and so rocky's remembering mick his his his dead mentor mick and in this flashback
mick is giving him this speech like uh, you know
Yeah, you know rocko
Uh, sometimes when you get older
Yeah, I think nature is smarter than us rock
I think we get older and everyone around us that we love
They all die rocky and and you look around and you ain't got no one left and you says to yourself
Who what am I still doing here rock?
And and and then so I want you to have this I want you to have this
And when you look at it, I want you to hear my voice
And it's gonna be saying get up you son of a bitch
Because mickey loves you and then at the end of the movie where he has to street fight with tommy gun
Tommy gun is beating him up because he's got brain damage. You can't fight anymore
He's getting headaches and like migraines in the middle of his fucking fight
And tommy gun he tommy gun beats up pauli. He beats up everyone and but so so so rocky's down
And but then he has that flashback and he remembers the voice of his old mentor mick get up
You son of a bitch because mickey loves you and he just somebody punches the guy
He punches him with his fucking feet and fists. He punches him with his feet. He doesn't care. He's out of control
He's a street fight. There's no rules in a street fight. You can punch with your feet
And then you get to rocky six rocky valboa where he's old as fuck and he can't even fight anymore
And the boxing commission won't even let him box anymore because he's a fucking dinosaur. He's a thousand years old
Yeah, and he has to go before like the tribunal of boxing the old wise men who control the boxing industry
And he's got his like pletus case. He's like, hey, you know, you don't you guys ever have something that you always wanted to do
That you didn't want to do and you feel that you see your last chance to do it and they're like, oh god damn it
Rocky, you've moved us to tears. We're gonna let you fight even though you're even though you're a fucking ancient wizard
And your bones are as brittle as fucking as as cookies
of Santa Claus cookies and
Merry Christmas everyone
It is a merry christmas. It is a merry christmas. He fought Ivan Drago on christmas day
That's right
Does he fight Ivan Drago on christmas day to save us all from sin?
Oh
God
And the last movie adrian's dead and and you fucking you know, he talks to he talks to poly there's that scene
It's not even in the movie. It's a deleted scene and even the deleted scenes are an emotional fucking
Maelstrom where he's talking to poly and poly's talking about adrian. He's like, oh rock
Oh, oh, you treated a good rock. I treated a bad. I don't want to remember and then he's oh fucking rocky
And then there's the fucking the new movie where he's he gets replaced by a black and that's the saddest part of all
Now you have to watch a bunch of movies with some black guy and rocky's probably gonna be dead in the next one
Rocky gets cancer in creed. He gets cancer and and he has to fight cancer
You know, he's fought Ivan Drago
He's battled Apollo creed
But now he has to battle his strongest boxing opponent of all cancer and he and it's a beautiful saga
And that's my favorite and not even just rocky also Rambo the Rambo series
Sylvester Stallone is a fucking machine for emotion. He's an emotional fucking
It's not good enough for him to make one to make the bed
Just the one most emotional fucking journey of all time
He had he had to make Rambo at the same time all the Rambo movies are amazing
The first fucking Rambo movie at the end were like he he breaks down and he's talking about, you know
How how sad he is and all he's got this PTSD and then the second movie where he meets
He meets co and and he falls in love and she teaches him that he's not expendable
But then at the end of the movie, you know, he he says
Coming for you because he found out the government used him they used him again
They don't care about the soldiers. They just use you up and they throw you away. They is and then in the third movie
The third movie is not very good, but then in the fourth Rambo movie
The fourth Rambo movie is he finally goes home to his family at the end
It is also another thing and speak enough how the government they don't care about the soldiers the metalgear solid the fucking
Oh my god
You are my best friend have no fear
I am your godsend if I had to choose between
Merrill and metalgear
Merrill would lose three cheers for metalgear
But it's my duty to kick some real booty beat down the baddies
That's what I that's what I sing to myself. I scream sing that to myself to ward off the tears so they don't over take me
Whenever I have an emotion I start thinking about the metalgear song, but it reminds me of metalgear. It makes me cry even harder
So it's a worthless song
Sensible strategy. Oh my god the fucking part in metalgear solid
Where sniper wolf dies and she's talking about that's like oh man. That's a beautiful thing
You we're dogs of war, but you you're a wolf. Oh, you're a wolf
Oh my god, I love your handkerchief. It smells so good when when liquid snake is is killing gray fox
And he's like in the middle east without hunt foxes
We hunt jackals and gray fox is like i've carried foxes more dangerous than a jackal you got sucker
And he shoots at him and then he dies and then he gives that speech and he's like snake
We're not tools of the government or anyone else
You gotta fucking get up and you gotta get a boner and you gotta fuck the world by your own standard
How how beautiful was it that that snake took that message to heart and started philanthropy with
To fight against the evil corporations trying to fucking
Kill us with machines. Yeah, man. Remember when remember when Tommy Wiseau shot himself at the end of the room
That was fucking point poignant. Now it's so it's so sad you have to laugh. It's too sad for tears
He's true
Ah god
My favorite parts for the shit. Is he dead? Is he dead? He's got a fucking bullet in his brain. You dumb bitch. What do you think?
Remember when that remember in the party scene when that guy shows up and just starts
Chastising the girlfriend and the lover as though he's been there all along even though no one's ever seen him before
I think that he's the doctor recast inexplicably, but I just love it so much
It's I don't want him to be the same guy. I wanted to be a new man
I think he's just a stranger that showed up to fucking moralize at these people
I think he just goes from party to party looking for people to preach at the room is the greatest piece of
Oh, man, never considered you men. Just gonna totally mess up our circle of friends. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Who are you?
Have we met sir?
That's the perfect line for that character. Holy shit our circle of friends, you know, you know our well-established circle of friends that we have
Oh my god
Well, I'll tell you what's it. What's a tear jerker another one. Yeah, since you mentioned the doctor
Man, good old doctor who every fucking every season of doctor who like every four episodes
There's there's got to be one that just that just wrecks everybody
It's the doctor is such a great man. He's such an emotional hero. Oh shit
I remember that there's another time. I cried. It was it was when rose got trapped in the the alternate dimensions
Yeah
That music playing that was that was really big. Oh man. Yeah, it was I thought it was a choice to go. Hey now
You're an all-star get your game on go, but it works so well. It works. It really works
Good Shrek cameo
You know to shift gears a little bit, um, wait, I just want to say, um, you know, our movie wasn't that sad
Was that grave of the fireflies?
I agree
Because what I mean, it would have been sad except that it didn't make any sense. Why she died
She died because the dude had too much pride. He wouldn't go ask for food. He let his sister die
But like that's fucking sucks the the very day
No, like like he the kid had money, right? Like he had money in the bank and then
The girl starves like almost to death and then on the day that she dies
That's when he decides to go and maybe get some of the money that he has out and buy some food
Like what are you are you fucking kidding me? Food wasn't available. I don't I don't know
Okay, we get exactly this detail, but I don't well
I don't I don't even understand like like the day that she is too far gone
To that she will die from starvation
Why don't you steal food if you had money? I don't I don't get it
Like he stole food like that very day
He has money and buys her some food and she can't eat it because like for me the the thing about grave of the fireflies
I'll extend this to a lot of stuff like it that like
I feel like what is meant to make that movie sad is the realization that it's that it's like real
And this is all like real things that happen to real people and stuff like that
But I don't feel like as a movie and maybe this
This is something that's hard to say without feeling like I'm some kind of inhuman jackass or something
But it's like I already know that people are suffering everywhere
I kind of take it for granted that everyone that life is terrible and everyone's suffering forever at all times
and and children are dying and mass
uh
everywhere and so like
For if you want to actually make me feel something then the movie has to like actually have characters
I care about and grave of the fireflies. I don't connect with anything like the characters are all assholes
Everyone in the movie is an asshole
The little sister is not an asshole. All right, and that's the one who dies. You're supposed to cry. She's she has she has no personality
She's just some kid. You know, it's like yes some kid died. I mean that is that true
Speaking of movies that totally tried and just completely failed to make me like connect to characters and like feel something about what was going on
song of the sea
Was like so I didn't see that yet. It's so
emotionally
I don't know like it it strives for this big fucking grand vision
And there's this big emotional scene at the end where all the girl or like the mom has to like take
Like she wants to take the daughter to like the spirit realm and all the spirits
All the spirits have awakened and they go back to the spirit realm and all the mom is in the spirit realm
And all the daughter's got to go to the spirit realm
But um, it sucks. It's fucking gay and it sucks. You know, that's interesting
Because the one they made before that's basically all I have to say the one they made before that the studio's the studio's previous movie
Secret of kels. Secret of kels. It's not it's not it doesn't it's not as tear jerky, but it's it's I don't know
It's just an infinitely better movie
I fucking hate song of the sea not because it's terrible just because it's so much worse than secret of kels
Secret of kels, I consider to have one of the worst endings I've ever seen in a movie
What the fuck are you talking about everything about that movie was
Do not let this devolve into an argument about secret kels
All I was gonna say I just I was gonna say was that I well whatever
I think the ending would like the book it wasn't satisfying to me. No the ending was great. Stop. Stop. Okay, but
I don't care what you wanted. What does that have to do with crying? Is it gonna? Yeah?
Okay, okay, it's just it's it's in secret of kels
Like I don't know the sequel apparently failed the corn event. I want to see it
But in the first one I think I think I actually might have cried a little bit at the ending of secret of kels
So there fuck you buddy. Okay. All right. Good for me
The what I what I did like about the end of secret of kels is the relationship between the boy and that silver-haired girl
Yeah, father aiden
Father no, no not him. Um, I'm talking about the girl in the woods and the kid Brandon or whatever
It's like aishley. It's like a weird spelling, but whatever spelled eisling, but it's pronounced Ashley
That's right. It's a weird Celtic thing. Anyway, uh, just their relationship and the way he like leaves and you don't know
What happened to her for like decades and then at the end he sees her years and years later briefly
And it just there's just like a there's like a sad lost friendship there that really got to me
That was the one emotional thing. I liked father aiden a lot
I liked father aiden more than I liked eisling
But whatever. Yeah, it's great. It's great. It's a great fucking movie and song of the sea
It's just it's just fucking empty in comparison
I'm gonna try to go through these as fast as I possibly can
Okay, please go I'm gonna go through all the animes that made me cry
I have a list of the exact tiers of shed during each show so the first in a little jar
Uh, yes
No, I actually made I made a post about this back in 2009 and I'm looking at the post right now
So I could keep track of you know the older ones from back in the day
So all right the first tier I ever shed watching anime apparently according to this list is from the anime series canon
Which is this uh sad girls moe show where everyone fucking dies
The part that makes me cry is that the like the main character is staying with his cousin and her mom
And her mom gets hit by a car in like episode 22 and she's just like this cool side character
Who's just a super lovely mom who's awesome and she's the best mom ever and she gets hit by a fucking car
She doesn't die, but there's like a scene where her daughter is like all emotional over it and uh got one tear out of me
Tier number two
Tier number two the ending of her reka seven
Holy shit. It's a good one. It's so fucking beautiful and in tier number five
Which we're skipping to because it was also from the last
No, the previous episode of reka seven the last two episodes have made me cry
But on different times watching the show
Um because the second or last episode is about the end of the relationship between anemone and dominic
And it's like anemone is this girl who's been this total bitch through the whole show
She's this evil cruel motherfucker, but this guy dominic's like in love with her and obsessed with her and she doesn't appreciate it at all
She's just this entitled brat through the whole show
But then in like the last arc like things stop going her way and like everything just fucking dog pals on her and all this
Bullshit happens but then dominic's there for her and she realizes that you know what he's been doing all this time
And she finally appreciates how his love for her and they have this fucking beautiful scene where they're falling through the air
And they've they've fucking embraced in mid air. It's beautiful made me cry then in the last episode when renton and reka finally, you know
Have their big payoff like they they I mean they are already kind of
The the whole last episode has this 10 minute song called niji which means rainbow by denki groove
That's what I was trying to say the whole last 10 minutes of the uh of the of the episode
That was an insane bit. That was so odd. That was like a speed racer ending. He fucking goes god mode
Save his bitch. It's a little rushed, but it is beautiful. Nonetheless. I'm sure he would describe it
As he needed to reclaim his property and he did it
um
Anyways tears numbers three and four were apparently shed during f a tale of memories
I don't remember what scene because it doesn't list here. What scene made me cry
So I I just know that happened during that show. What a shitty list this is. Yeah, and then it says uh
This the last entry on the list is tears number six seven eight nine ten nose run number one and choke up number one
All happened at once while watching uh, this is the last one on the list
All happened at once while watching clenad
Uh episode nine of clenad. Yes clenad the crab with testicles
An episode nine of clenad then there's this girl called fuko
She's like this little girl who turns out as a ghost holy shit the crab with testicles. I remember the crab with testicles
What happens to the crab did you
I have multiple times received like fan art of the what people imagine the clenad is like the crab
Um, so what happens to this crab ghost? Well, okay, it's not a crab. It's just a little girl. She's a ghost
The little girl like she she just like her sister is getting married and she just wants to be able to like see the wedding
Uh, and she'll be able to pass on to the next life
And so in episode nine there's like they do the whole wedding scene
It's just it's just so like the way they directed it and
Animated it and everything is just so fucking emotionally, you know manipulative that
It was a huge it made me cry like crazy even though I didn't care about the character or anything about the show
It's not even a good show. That sounds that sounds good
That sounds almost as good and similarly emotionally resonant as this uh this one hentai watch about a ghost who couldn't go
She couldn't pass on until she got fucked real good by one dude
And then she did and she she felt at peace. It was great
I bet I've seen that so to just follow up because that list was from 2009
I've had a few more times I cried another big one was another show from the same guy who wrote canon and uh in clenad
Which was angel beats the last episode of angel beats because
Oh my god
That one's so fucking emotional because the whole show takes place in purgatory
And it's like all these fucking kids who are like trying to
Figure out why they're there and like how to move on and then the last episode
It's like most of the whole cast has already moved on from purgatory
There's just like five characters left and they've basically resolved all their major issues
And they're just like having like one last like uh like goodbye. They literally stage a graduation
They all meet up in like the auditorium of the the purgatory that is high school
And they uh
They each of them one at a time gets up and like gives their graduation speech and it's all fucking emotional and they you know
They vanish after they give their speech
So it's like you're literally watching the characters one by one exit the show to go to heaven. Oh my god. It's so fucking emotional
um
That's that one definitely made me break down
Really fucking hard. Um, and then some more recent ones
uh
The most recent time that I cried apropos of nothing was watching kaon and thinking about hippocrite because
It was after we had I've probably told this story before but uh at least to you guys
It was after we had met up at brony con in 2014, I guess and it was like everyone got to go except for hippo
You know 2013 then no yeah 14 whatever in 2014 everyone met up. We all went to brony con except for hippo
and it was like
I realized because we had this we made up these little memes and stuff while we were at brony con
Which is still survived with us to this day like the lord of shit mountain little things that we were just giggling about like all night long
yeah, and uh
Double batman was the next year. I think that was the year hippo was there. So was it yeah
Lord of shit mountain was the first year though
And like we just kept like all night staying up like saying whoo shit mountain and then we'd all giggle for like
10 fucking minutes because we're idiots
Um, but we had all these memes and stuff and it really reminded me of the scene in kaon where they go on the school trip
And uh, they're all just like laying in bed at night and they keep going like
Like a peen and then they all laugh and then one of them's like should it go bad and they all laugh
And then it comes up later in the show and like during the most emotional moment in the show
In episode 20 when like the band has just done their last performance and they're about to like
You know this is the last time that they're ever going to do something major together again
and they all just break down crying at the realization and then
Like ritsu to try to cheer everyone up says like go peen and they all start laughing while crying and oh my god that scene
Absolutely makes me cry every single fucking time. I watch it. Um
As does the ending of season one now
Basically all of kaon makes me cry now because the more I think about it the more emotional I get about it
But that's the scene that that got to me out of nowhere was because you know, I made that connection between us cry on
Yeah
You know, I made that connection between us taking out
And in that scene but then I'm watching the show and I'm halfway through season one and azusa shows up
Who's you know, the the youngest fifth member who joins the crew later?
And I suddenly like upon seeing her I suddenly remember
That in that episode where they were on the school trip. She wasn't there because she's a grade lower
They all went to Kyoto and they had this great time
But meanwhile she was stuck back at home and she was just hanging out with her like underclassmen friends
And so she had this other sort of adventure that was going on with her friends
And she you know has her own little stories from that but it's obviously less interesting
um and hippo at the time had been at this like uh
Like this camp for retarded kids, I guess and he cleaned shit for retarded kids or something
And uh, and he had been doing that and like he had said, you know, it was it was a it was a good time on its own
But you know, it was not the same trip that the rest of us were on and like I remembered all of that when I saw
Azusa and I was like, oh my god
It's the same and then I just fucking lost it and I was crying like all day
I all I could think about and I was just like like babbling to myself. Oh my god hypocrites. I was in yon
It's so a chaos perfect
um
And it didn't help that I think the reason I was so emotional is that I was like hopped up on painkillers because this was after
I'd broken my foot
So I'm like laying I'm like laying in a chair watching k-on like half
Half asleep like just downing oxy cotton and crying my eyes out thinking about azusa
Uh, and then yeah, and then I cried at like every major episode from then on um
And then k-on became my favorite anime of all time officially
interesting
I have
I think I cried at the end of shiro bako too. I don't know if I shed a hole here, but the scene where
Oh, I hope you does anybody care if they get spoiled for shiro bako is anybody I do care
I don't want to be spoiled though. It's been a long time. So I wouldn't really see you nerd. I am working on it
I want to talk about it though. Do you can you cover your ears for like one minute while I freak out?
Yes, yes, I can I'm gonna take off my headphones. Okay, so at the end of shiro bako
Uh, like the whole show the five girls have all wanted to work on an anime together
Like that was their dream when they were in high school
They had an anime club
They all wanted to work together on this one show and then
They they've never gotten the chance because they've all gone to different jobs and they're they're all in different places in their career
Some of them are having a lot of success some aren't and the voice actress girl the whole show is just getting shit on
She never gets work the whole fucking show
She never has any success and in the second half of the show all four of the other girls get to work on this show together
In some capacity and like they have to have meet-ups with the other girl like they're all hanging out and they're all like
Oh, yeah, we're
Yeah, we're kind of on the show too and you know the voice actress girl's just like yeah, I I understand
You know it's it's hard out there for a voice actress and there's like beating down out of the whole show
But then they like the whole second half
They're like talking about rewriting the script for the show and then it turns out that they end up writing
Rewriting the last scene of the last episode where they're going to have them go to this like a
To meet one of the main characters in the show
They're making to meet one of her like her little sister
And so the voice actress girl ends up getting to voice the little sister and they all like find out
At once and like they bring her in and she gives us really emotional performance
And she's like crying because she got to be in the show with all her friends
No, I'm still going and then fucking Emma who's the animator she gets the anime
Emma gets to animate the scene that she was voice acting shut
Jesse got to go on for 15 fucking minutes about rocky. I can talk about sure
He used up all the fucking goodwill. He used up all the goodwill I have then you have had no contribution to this so far
So I'm going to talk about sure my contributions have been concise and pointed
They had nothing to do with crying and chose. I fucking seen shirobako. Okay. Yeah, it's a really emotional scene
It makes you fucking watch it may be cry when when Emma is animating the scene that she got to do then that was extremely
Emotional
It's a good ending. I didn't I didn't cry. All right. You're good. I wanted to say um
There's the the ending of lucky star was always quite emotional. That is a good one
It's uh, it was really just that that idea that
It's the end of school and
You know all the friends they've made and all the stuff they've done. That's it after that
Everyone's gonna go away and never speak to each other again. That's also a genius ending
It really it really makes me think I mean I think I cry most when it's like
An idea or a concept that I can closely relate to like a character dying
I've never seen somebody die in front of me. So that never really affects me that much
Like, uh, you know the lion king
I can't really relate to that because I'm not a lion and also
I
And I'm not african so I can't
Lions attack him. Yeah, I can't really that's true. No empathy
But um, I was thinking like if there was
Something like one of my worst fears
Not one of one of my worst fears, but if there was like a character death
From the perspective of somebody who just didn't know because I've had nightmares
Or rather just like I've waken I've I've cried in my sleep
To to the idea of just coming home one day and then
Like my brothers or my parents just not coming home because they died
And I just didn't find out about it. And if if that was in like a tv show, I would cry probably there
But like things where it's like all dramatic and
There's music and there's like, oh no, he's dead, you know
Hippo you're bringing a tear to my eye
I just I can't I can't relate to things like that and I don't cry so much
So if it happened if it's happened to me or if it's something I fear
Then I would cry more go back to lucky star
That scene where they like reminisce about konata's dead mom
That's yeah, I was gonna say and the funny thing about that ending of k
Or of a lucky star that you described that like it's all of them graduating and like this sort of emotional thing is that
It always works and yet every single one of those shows has done it like lucky star has that
He didn't really sketch us elements of that azumanga dayo ends that way
K-On ends that way obviously. There's no other way
Like an end. It's it's not even that I had a good high school experience
It's just that I was starting to make one or two friends at the end of high school
And I was like, oh I have to start again
I'm not not so basically I'm saying like even though they all do it
It always works like every single one of those is an emotional ending
Even when the show wasn't like azumanga dayo has like a surprisingly emotional climax for a show
That was never emotional, you know, it's kind of hard to avoid being emotional when like it's the end of you and all your buddies
Like you reading it. They're like your friends, you know, tomo and the classic one
My friends in high school like any of the ones I kept talking to after high school
Like by that point we didn't see each other in school anymore
We only saw each other outside school because like most of them are people because in japan
They stay in one class typically
For like three, you know, you have a lot of the same people
Especially if you're in the same grade range, you know, and of course anime will you know skew it
So everyone ends up in the same class
Or they're all in the same club or something
But you know for me and my friends it was like by senior year
Nobody was in classes with me or half of them had dropped out. So, you know
Hey before we move on from lucky star
Let me just say how genius that ending is in that the the whole like
Performance that they're putting on is the opening that we've seen every episode. Yeah fucking genius. Love it
I just want to ask about the school system in america. I don't really know how it works
Do you have like a a class of people?
that
You stay with throughout the school time or is it just like
It's all just based on you you move between classes every in the uk
We have like two two groups or at least my school had two two groups where it would be a group of people
And we had a name and we stayed in that class
The whole way through but when we get into different subjects, we would be in different classes
Like if we chose german, we'd be all with all the it changes every year
You have a homeroom, but like you don't stay with them through the day. Yeah, it's just like where you go
I mean it's it's almost
It's almost completely because like I remember in in uh
I mean in elementary school, we were in one class the whole time in middle school
I remember the homeroom meaning something but like in high school for me
It was just homeroom was just whatever your first class was like there was no
We didn't go to a homeroom every day. It was totally pointless and they never understood why they even bother
Well, did you guys have an a and b did you guys have a a and b days like we had like a b
We had like a six day cycle. I think
Holy shit. How the fuck does that work? I mean, I I don't know. Yeah. Yeah, we did
I mean for my school it was you took four classes on one day and then four classes the next day
And they were all totally different. So you did not go to the same room at all two days in a row
So the thing that's that's different about uh, the uk is that
um
We have like middle school middle school and high school combined into one and then also a few years added on at the end
So if you were to go study like year seven and you would go through to year 12 or 13
You would be with that one homeroom or tutor group
for many years
It's nothing like that here. It feels kind of similar to the way Japanese things happen
Well, that's cool. Uh, but hey, I wanted to kind of bring things in a different direction
If are you done get would you anything else you're gonna say? Okay
I was just gonna ask about and this might be something interesting uh to talk about from a from a crying perspective
specifically since we're all content creators
I don't know about you guys, but I've on many occasions
Well, I guess not many but on several occasions stuff that I have been making has made me cry kind of on an intellectual level
As I just realized so well, it's maybe it's because like I'm so I have such a pension
Where I thought you were going with that is I thought you were gonna say
I've got lots of comments that have said they cried watching my videos. I was not
Care about them. I don't care about them. Yeah
Well, yeah, I mean the comments too people do say that I've not cried at my own videos
I never I have never
I mean I have gotten really emotional in various ways about my own stuff
I've not crying like usually crying is not a feeling that I like, I don't know
It doesn't just like spontaneously well up inside me. I guess like when I'm with the stuff that I'm working on is not
Like that. I don't know. I guess I was the closest is brunswick brunswick's kind of a tear jirker, you know
Yeah, but I didn't like cry making it, you know, right?
Sadness and was not the feeling in me as I was producing it even though it was
All malfunctioning people say I mean some of the best
Yeah, people say that brunswick makes them cry sometimes and that feels great. I love that
Um people when when people told me that they cried at the end of nuzlocke genocide
That was like one of the proudest moments. I felt I was so happy. No, it wasn't no, it wasn't the end
It was the second it was the penultimate episode
Yeah, yeah, because I mean I really tried to go all out and make it an emotional moment and people were like
You're fucking nuzlocke let's play series made me fucking cry, dude. I was like, yes
I did it. I did the impossible
I uh, I think
Go on Gib
I was just gonna say I don't know whether I would cry even if I deliberately tried to make something emotional like that
Yeah, like brunswick is sad and emotional, but like at no point in actually making it. Did I like oh did I like, you know
Yeah, well, you know like when I listen back to uh to to my gur and lug in part two
You know when I was making it even now like I I use I use tracks in there that evoke certain emotions in me
So like like baby universe, which is uh, what I use when I'm like describing the the two types of characters like the
Communists and the rosses or whatever
And then later on with the um like the the next song is uh
From bravely default. It's like the the finale song and like that's like the emotional client acts of the video
Like I use that song because it really gets me
So, you know, kind of just through through the fact that I I steal
I steal content from other people and use them in my videos
I kind of get to experience the same emotion as other people if I had made the song
Maybe I wouldn't feel that way, but you know, I the brave little toaster, you know, yeah
I think that when I think that it's hard like that. You're worthless
I mean, maybe some of the ideas
Behind and a work that you're doing might make you really emotional like
See that that's what I really want to get at with this making of the thing
I I don't think I would ever be in danger
Of that happening in danger never like the fucking no like I don't know just when when you're seeing the actual sausage making process
You know, just like like making a thing and experiencing a thing are just so fucking different from each other
I cry when I think about how long it took to make these things
When I think about how when I think about how far behind I am and how much I hate myself in my life
Yeah, I get really emotional about my own stuff in that sense
The one I thought would be most likely to have experienced this was jesse
So jesse, do you ever cry when you're making or watching your own work?
boy
Like that, uh, like the wrestle the wrestle boy, you know toast for the douchebags. Oh, yeah. Yeah, that one seemed like it might
I don't know about watching them
I don't know. I haven't been fucking
Oh, jesse hates his own work a little too much for that. I think no, no, I think it's a different sort of feeling
I'm uh, oh doing this podcast has opened something up inside me
I'm having trouble deem it out here. Do you feel a tear coming out of your eye? Oh and another one fallen from my other eye
Um, I'm sure you all know what the intro for this podcast is going to be
Yeah, yeah
I don't know I've been
I can definitely write things that like while i'm writing them it's bringing
Like an emotion out of me that I hadn't confronted yet
And you know like while i'm putting it on the paper or the fucking board pad document or whatever it's like while i'm writing it
I'm crying
Or scribbled on the bathroom wall in my own feces, you know, however the writing process takes me, right?
Yeah, like I've yeah, I've been writing a thing recently that's been making me cry a lot the whole time
I've just been oh cool. It's not for public consumption though. It's a private thing
But I've been writing it through through like just a veil of tears
I'm writing isn't that fanfiction about ray playing smash brothers because that's
It's not a fan
No, I've yet to finish that because I know it'll be too emotional. I'll have to kill myself
Yeah
You know, uh, I'm glad to see that uh, you're not a man who only appreciates osca like a lot of the osca fags out there
You're you're too too to jump in on this question. You know who I also um
I think a lot about misado and I think a lot about that one scene in particular
Where she's just like coming to terms with the fact that kaji's probably dead and she's crying at the kitchen table
And that little like just that like piece of animation of her like crumpling at the table is like so raw and real to me
and like yeah
I always think of it
and
I wrote a little song
Just to that piece of animation because it's always in my head
And so one day I started just singing
And what I ended up singing was the song desperado by the eagles. Yeah, but instead of desperado it was hey misado
And oh
And it stuck with me and this is like I've always thought about making this a video
Because I I do this all the time where I'm like pacing around my room
And I'll just start thinking about it and going
Hey misado
Why don't you come to your sense? And I'll just start crying like an idiot
Wait a minute, that's such a great song the dark soul song. What no nigga fucking eagles
And Orlando, why are you such a cocksucker?
Talk to bottom mother fucker. It's not even
It's not even like it makes me cry because i'm sad it makes me cry because it's so stupid and silly that I've like
That I've ruined the scene in this show because whenever I see it from now on i'm gonna be thinking about the fucking eagles
Wow
I hate the fucking eagles. Oh god, you know stupid stuff's the coolest stuff
It's odd because I'm I'm thinking like I'm racing through all my videos in my mind trying to think if there's any
Like that I've made that would make me emotional
But it's odd because I have I have some videos that people have told me make them cry
And I have ones that are definitely more emotional like you're gonna carry that way the cowboy bebop video
Um, you know people told me that made them cry or some of the more personal stuff the like
S4 diary stuff from the pony days and shit like that
Um and like but I don't know I feel like I go out of my way to undercut emotions in my videos
Like where I I I tend to go more for like a numbness
When I do get emotional and if you watch my philosophy is if I have to feel it then god damn it
You're all gonna feel it to your sons of bitches
Yeah, I don't know it's it's odd like I when I think of because nat I know you use music to make things emotional
And you always have these this sort of overpowering feeling in your videos like hitting like here's all the emotion make
And I feel like I'm taking people on a guided tour when I do this shit
And it's rare for me to use music in my videos
But when I do I almost always pick stuff that deliberately
Won't feel that way almost except like and I'm thinking of the the migraine reviews and insomnia analysis
And probably the most emotional thing I've ever done which was just copying jesse's usage of this song
Green bird from cowboy bebop and I used it at the end of my migraine review
But like all the music used throughout that up until that point
It's all like depressing songs but have this very like numbing jaded kind of depression and like
That's sort of the way I always present
Myself is like I don't usually try to say like oh, I'm very emotional right now
It's more like I feel dead and I feel like I wish I could feel something
I guess this is that's what this whole podcast is this has been my stance this whole podcast is
I wish I could feel something but I'm just so fucking dead inside and I feel so neurotic and broken
That I don't I I'm like struggling to eke an emotion out of something
I have a similar sort of feeling that I feel I don't feel like I'm dead inside
I just feel like I want to be able to cry more. I want to be more emotional because it seems like
You know, maybe it's a it's a curse, but it
It results in a lot of cool things
Yeah, like I'd probably be funnier if I could be more emotional
You know, it's uh the podd cast is a good place to go
Listen if you want to hear like me be emotional every single week about the amazing things that happen in one piece
If you want to hear the exact same speech about how amazing one piece is and how gratifying it is
That there's all these things that were set up. It's our 10 years 10 whole years of setup paying off 20 years now. Yeah, all right
Yeah, I do like the body cast but you do give that speech every episode. I can't wait. I we did this one. Oh, I'm late with that one
but yeah
um
All right, that's cool
shout out shout outs to um
Specifically the second genova fight in final fantasy 7 where eras is theme plays while you fight this evil
Disgusting genova every every. I'm sorry man. I'm sorry in final fantasy 7 every part of that game
Yeah, it's too much the scene with tifa and cloud under the air ship
Oh my god
The scene in eras is mom's house and there it's talking about marlene and how he wants to be there for it
But he has also got a fight for the planet and stuff and when when barrett goes to see dine
And the scene where all right regret 13 meets his father and his father is a dead statue
He was a hero
It was all
There's that scene where you take barrett on a date
I knew that
No, that's too real dude the first the first interracial kiss in video games
Other shout out groundbreaking the final scene in uh in in in kingdom hearts 2 where where roxas and nominate are reunited via
Sora and kairi's bodies that via the sweet release of death
Well sort of
Shut up
I'm still mad that ben i rolled me out of my shirobako thing. That was the only examples
I had the one thing that made did you feel like you ruined it? Yeah, you took it away. It was just i'm i'm sorry
I was just really bored
You know what you know what academy award music to be out of my only emotional moment
And now these guys are going through all their examples and I have nothing left
I'm like struggling. Oh, there must be something else that made me cry. I have nothing
Speaking let's talk about ben for a minute. Let me tell you people the most ben story that I could that that's ever happened
It happened in our fucking in our discord server about maybe three or four weeks ago
Maybe ben remembers this
I don't
I think I uh, I had like offhandedly mentioned that I was oh, yeah
No, I do remember and I stand by it shut up. All right. Let me tell the story fag
all right
I'm just saying I stand by it, but um ben showed up and he's like
Hey, jesse you offhandedly mentioned that you were depressed. Why don't you tell me what's got you so sad?
That's not how it shut up and let me tell the story
fine
Go on and I was like
Well, ben, you know, I feel kind of heartbroken lately
I feel kind of sad and depressed about a lot of real deep personal stuff
And ben goes oh on second thought it's boring and I don't care. Goodbye
Ben you mad man. First of all, I was being tongue-in-cheek right here. I was confiding in a friend
And you and you guys wonder why I present you all
And like I was like
I made some because you said you were depressed and I was like, but jesse you just got laid. How could you be depressed?
You know, I was joking. I was joking
And then you're like I was and then you're like, oh, I don't know. You get well sometimes ben
Sometimes ben getting laid, you know romance can bring out emotions
You know some normal people have emotions and you're like, let me let me fucking all right
Let me just let me just completely love with you like I was being jokie about and I was being but you know
But there was kind of I was okay. I'm I'm I'm mad right?
I'm mad because I live in virginia beach and I have nowhere to go and I haven't gotten laid in a long time
It feels like I'm really mad and I resent you jesse. Wait, what I resent you for having had sex recently
So there there it's out there. I said it and then I come in I come in here and I'm like, oh jesse
I'm making a joke about how why would you be depressed when you just had sex and then and then you're like
Well, there's just other girl. Oh, she said some something and now I'm in love with her. I'm like shut up
I didn't I just didn't want to hear it. Okay. So yes, it was stupid and retarded
And there you go. I'm not really I'm not really mad. It's just it just strikes me as such a well. I'm fucking mad
You had sex with a girl
You know what if you guys are going to be mad at me every time I've just had sex with the girl
Then I guess you just always hate me because I've always I was trying to keep I was trying to keep my resentment fucking bottled up
And buried deep inside and now it's going now. You're making it bubble. You're boiling that channel
Okay, let's all just let's all just let it all out
Okay, good
I'm zipping other guys
Let me uh, all right, I wanted to give one last shout out to uh data from star trek
What that's not a joke
It's the way you're phrasing it as a shout out, I think that's
What
Friend of the show data, you know coming all the way from the federation
To big bird guys
He cares about me. He understands what it means to be human. I like you
You know when mr. Hooper died and big bird had to learn about death and he had to confront the reality that we're all mortal
We all died
That we all die except for him because he's a muppet who asked that he's cursed with immortality
He has to watch all of his friends die forever
You know, I really want to give a shout out to big bird for feeling that feel for me
All right, well you've ruined it thoroughly everyone congratulations. I hope you had I hope you're happy with yourselves
This is the best part because anyone have any last
Anyone have any comments we before we started this show we randomly decided to start a new thing
I have one work. I have one comment before we go
I have one comment before we go into the ending show and that is that I've been looking this like half of this time
I've been looking up lists of sad movies on the internet and I cannot find this fucking sad
Like weird pseudo romance between like a gothy teenage girl
And and like a and like a shrubby middle-aged man. It's like a comedy, but it's a role of romance
It's really sad and it made me cry and and I have no and I think it's named
Harold and mod or butch in Cassidy
Is it the one where they like do they go around like killing people or something? No, no anything like that
No, no, no, no, it's just like if anyone knows what the fuck i'm talking about
Please tell me in the comments because I really want to remember what it's called now
Anyway, just yeah, I just want to point out for the record that I didn't actually ruin a party by crying into someone's birthday cake
That was a hypothetical. I don't believe you. I do not believe you. That's a lie
That's a lie. That was too. I was trying to go off on like a funny tangent
And but then did you like oh man? I'm really into this story about how Jesse ruined a birthday party
I'm like wait a minute
I didn't think the detail about the birthday party was real, but I did think the crying get a party was real
I just assumed you got drunk and cried at a party because that's what happens at every party
Me and my friends have ever thrown is that someone gets drunk and then cries about their life for like six hours and
That's generally how our how our greeta our meet and greets tend to go. I love parties
Parties are all good
They're all fun. I'm not referring to like party parties. I'm talking about like me and three friends hanging out and drinking
That's what a party means to me
Um, and it usually ends in one of those friends crying about whatever's going on in their life
For hours. No wonder you've lost touch with all your friends. Yeah, exactly
Uh
So we started up a segment this time where for whatever reason at the start of the show
We put out a tweet saying we will answer one question that someone has for us on twitter
And now we will answer one question. Nate. What's the question? We have no questions. Okay. Here we go
I I searched started through them and I think I found the most provocative of them all
Uh quick shout out actually to uh at rabbits foot 99 for their incredible cute duck from princess two to icon
But anyway, moving on the actual question is uh by at quincy ackerman
The question is John. Is there a middle road our fifth? Yeah, that's right
He didn't live up to his father's legacy, but uh, is the question is from quincy ackerman
He wasn't there about he was friends and family about 17th century politics or 18th century. Okay. Here's the question
Here's the actual question quincy ackerman. Yeah, is there a middle road for normies and non normies?
Uh, what? No, I'm completely
Next question I'm gonna say the answer is uh, it's sort of
Uh, because you see you can you you need to in your heart of hearts be a non normie
Because if you're just a normie then you're just worthless
But you can put on a mask of being a normie and that's the way that you survive in today's uh, you know
Does that count as being a normie or is it just wearing? No, no, it doesn't. Well, that's why I think that what they mean is like is like
not being
Like being a normie in some ways, but then being a non normie in other ways
Can you be a mature normie in terms of like I think my brother victor would be like a perfect middle road
between those he's you know a handsome
uh
Personable guy who works with other humans and gets and he's out all the time and has like a functional relationship
but he also like hates everybody and is incredibly neurotic and every part of his body is broken and he's
Uh, and most especially his brain doesn't function, right?
So he is like he's like the most non normie person to ever walk in the skin of a normie
So he's the day walking about yeah, so how about that? Are we satisfied with that question?
Sure. No, uh, you could ask another one because that one was terrible. So
That was the thing. None of them were very good. But okay. Here's one. Maybe you like this retarded one. None of our fans are very good
But we try what is okay? This is this is from at true start true stardust 97
What is the canonical power scale of the pcp weakest to strongest does that tickle your fancy people?
Is that what you want? That's such a big question. That's that's nebulous. I don't know how to quantify
We can eliminate what end of the spectrum because we know cult is both the cutest and the strongest
That's probably its own entire fucking podcast. Yeah, wait, we could we could find that out
We can find that out at rad con 2 with
That's true in console mania 2. Oh, yeah, the video game let that decide
So right now would it be would be hippo is the strongest? I mean he won right?
He had like didn't like cane win or like triple h or something one one and
And uh
Okay, that's enough uh, so people we're gonna do this again next time
Uh, we'll we'll put out another tweet uh saying that we're recording the pcp submit your questions
And we'll look through and we'll answer one at the end
So uh, go subscribe to at tp crastitators. Uh, if you want to do that shit
Oh, and again, thanks to uh at pop vulture for the question everybody go submit over the whole week
Go submit your topics and we'll talk about it on the podcast next time we do one and uh, it's gonna be it. So uh
Thanks for listening everybody. Hope you enjoyed yourself having yourself a good cry
Go uh play king of march 2 go cry about how sad and beautiful it is and uh, have a wonderful day
Bye
Yeah
I'm supposed to be working right now
I'm supposed to be making money
I'm supposed to be creating funny
Think that the people
Gladly will pay for
Artistic genius
That's what they came for
Instead i'm tweeting
Hashtag repeating
That's why there's no heat and holes in the ceiling
Yeah, it's quite the burden
It's a hard knock life
Being a genius