Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Radcon funded by you. We can be Pro Crastinators.
Hello, welcome to another PCP episode. We took a bi-week last week because of all the fuckery with that laser-bought episode getting up, but we're back. It's been two weeks since we recorded. We are ripped, fucked, to go energize. I'm Ben Saint. Gibbontake is here.
And we have the kids from the down the block. We've got some dudes from the Shreddit podcast. Hello. Well, introduce yourselves.
Hello. I am Reborn Pyro. I am the guy that grabs Ben's reddit post every time he comes on to torture him with.
He grabs my reddit post. Yeah. The one you read on the episode? Oh, sure. Sure. Yeah. Because your podcast is about real. I thought you meant, okay, yeah, no, I got it. Somebody else. Go.
All right. I'm Kai. I'm a kiddie man. Nice. But not really. Deb. Deb. Don't forget that you're basically our audio engineer. That too. Don't tell them that I'm the brains. I'm simply here. I don't do anything.
Okay, gotcha. Who else? Hi, I'm Lumia. I'm the VTuber rep, representative of the group, and they torture me every day with a BDL post. Help me.
No, that's, that's, that's just reborn. Deb. You supported Kai. Fuck you. You're not wrong. Okay, we got one more. Go, go, go. Hello. My name is Aspley. I do the thumbnails and shit talk a lot. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. So the story. Yeah. Go on. Shreddit. You guys are from a podcast called Shreddit. I haven't actually watched an episode yet. Sorry. I'm very sorry.
You're fine.
What the fuck is the show about?
The story with Shreddit, from my perspective, is that Reborn just, I'm eating Brussels sprouts with bacon and eggs, by the way, for the viewers at home. That's, so, you know, you're just going to have to deal with it.
Reborn basically got in the PZP Minecraft server where we do Pixelmon and challenged me to a Pokemon battle. And for winning, he shanghied me into being on the Shreddit podcast. And that's why that happened. And then I did it again one other time.
Lumia.
Link in the description to their podcast, I guess.
Hell yeah.
If you're interested.
Yeah.
And shout out to the Chad PCP Minecraft server and the Chad Marin who runs it. He's amazing.
Patreon, get in the server and have some fun.
I would agree. I would agree with all of that.
But so to answer your question, Gib, so what we do is every week we take on a new subreddit and we have a wacky cast of diverse guests. Every episode has a new guest.
And every week is a new subreddit. And we all grab posts from that subreddit. What we all personally think to be the stupidest post on the sub. And then we make fun of them and editorialize the posts as the episodes go on.
Others of us may or may not spend exactly 10 minutes before we start recording to locate posts and or delay it by a few 10, 20, 30 minutes looking for posts. But that, you know, that's neither here nor there.
I imagine you could see you could spend hours trawling through shitty subreddits looking for posts from weirdos.
We have.
There's no end.
We do a little trawling.
There's no end to the amount of time you could spend just like digging up weird shit on there if you wanted to.
Yeah.
And sometimes there's so much just good posts that you could make fun of and it's hard to pick between the ones you want. So you spend time.
Quote unquote.
Okay, which is the worst.
Yeah.
I haven't been on Reddit in a donkey's age.
A donkey?
I haven't been on there in an age of time.
It's a certain amount of time I haven't been on there.
You're lucky.
You're very lucky.
Don't go.
It's not any better than what it was.
I've exclusively used it for Shreddit.
I'd never use Reddit.
It's just for looking for terrible posts.
That's my experience with this.
I used to look for like local events on Reddit.
I found one or two back in the day, but I haven't done that in a while.
At my experience with Reddit, I'm like, hi, I never used it before Shreddit, but I knew it had a really bad reputation.
It's funny.
Since starting Shreddit, we've actually had a few moderately famous micro-internet celebrities reach out to us,
and there's a huge consensus of almost all of them universally just hate Reddit.
It seems like most people hate Reddit, which is good for us.
Yes.
It's great when you join somebody that's kind of famous and you join their Discord and you start shilling your show,
and then they go, oh, shit, you guys make fun of Reddit based.
Let me on.
Dude, me too.
Is there anyone that actually likes Reddit?
There must be.
No.
People still post in there.
True, but I've never met anyone that likes Reddit.
Every social, not every website or every community has their own kind of bad reputation.
I use Twitter.
Twitter is the only one I use, but I don't like it, and everyone knows that it's bad for various reasons.
Yeah, because there's people on there.
Well, yeah, for starters.
Although, I guess maybe the people that use Facebook don't mind Facebook because they're all boomers and they don't know any better.
So maybe that's different.
Everyone who does mind Facebook left Facebook a while ago.
Yeah, true, but the alternatives are just not that good.
If you're willing to leave Facebook, you're probably not going to be happy anywhere.
You're going to be more of a nomad.
I've used Reddit a little bit in the past, like branching off from browsing like,
I can has cheeseburger.com looking at cat memes.
That's a meme place.
You go to Reddit for other memes, but I never really got into the habit of using it recreationally.
I only went back to like, shill my channel, and then I learned that shilling is bad, so I just never used it.
Yeah.
The rule system about that is very weird, like you yourself are not allowed to shill anything,
but if you create an alt account and then just go, hey, check out this show, it's okay and encouraged.
I mean, I've done that.
Yeah, I mean, different subreddits have different rules or whatever about it, different rules of enforcement.
I've, sometimes, I've gone on Reddit to like, oh, I spammed the Jennifer Diane writes lecture, like, all over like 20 different subreddits when it came out.
I mean, I don't know if it like got much attention anywhere.
When you don't even check, you're like, just in case.
Well, I mean, what does it matter?
Like, if it gets views, if it doesn't get views, it's not like checking on my posts.
I completely agree.
It's not like you care about your reputation on said subreddit.
No, not at all.
It's about getting eyes to YouTube, where I make, where I make my, my, my pittance in ad revenue.
Always sell, always sell merch.
Don't sell ads.
I like selling ads.
I don't have to think about it.
You could sell ads if, if you're like doing a contract with the actual company, because then you can get like decent cash payments and you can like keep most the margin.
If you, if you're willing to do the, do the legwork, but like selling merch is hard.
You have to actually sell it.
You have to actually convince someone to buy it.
I mean, I'm, I'm speaking from a position of privilege as someone who actually has like a couple of videos that get regular traffic, the lecture videos.
So like from my perspective, I love that ads run on there because it's, it's just like, it's just like a little, a little bit of money.
Just kind of, just kind of passively trickling into my, into my hands.
It's what we call passive income.
It's, it's great.
It's not that much, but I'm like, oh, this is, it's kind of the greatest thing that's ever happened to me.
You know what?
I'll just say it.
No cap.
No, no, no word of a lie.
It's the best thing that's happened.
That's the game.
You just got to keep doing that until you have enough money that you go, you ain't got to do shit.
You just leave those videos up and you're good.
That's why, that's why it's been such a huge mistake that I have made and continue to make to not post the Sanchu lecture volume too.
But at this point, I'm in for a penny in for a pound and I've made up my mind that I won't post until the game is done.
So I just have to live with the consequence of that.
You got to do the big brain move and just cut it up into like 20 minute chunks and then have a bunch of different videos, all of which getting ad-rev.
No, that's not how it works anymore.
Now the algorithm is about watch time.
Well, it's technically about a watch session.
So if you go from one video to another to another to another and you continue to watch it, all of that entire duration is applied to that first video and the rest of them.
Yeah, but like splitting the video up with-
I feel, yeah, like people's patients would like, I got to click on another one.
You piece of shit.
I'm bored.
The YouTube meta.
Allow them to passively continue to watch the one video.
The YouTube meta used to be 10 minute chunks to maximize views and that was when-
And I remember that because that's when we were doing a fucking on T-Bap, me and Nate did Equestria Bound and we did like 200 fucking episodes of that game.
And yeah, it broke it up into like 10, 15 minute segments.
How much money did you get from that?
Like nothing.
Was that like a super profitable-
No.
Okay.
No, of course not.
I remember the views were like a few, like maybe a few thousand.
No.
On Equestria Bound?
Wait, actually-
I mean, T-Bap was pretty big in the pony sphere.
I mean, for a pony channel, it was modestly-
I wouldn't even call it large.
I would say it was medium.
He had a few videos with hundreds of thousands.
Did we?
Yeah, but that was gonna-
I would have CPMs of like a dollar though, right?
Jeez.
T-Bap plays Equestria Bound.
Let me see how many views-
The trailer for T-Bap plays Equestria Bound got 2,000 views.
The first episode of T-Bap plays Equestria Bound got 3,000.
And I have to imagine-
Okay, so that's actually more than I thought.
T-Bap plays never even hit 2,000 subscribers.
So, oh man, I wonder what the drop-off was.
I wonder what the drop-off was, hundreds of episodes later.
Is there a playlist here?
Ten viewers.
Two viewers.
I would be shocked.
T-Bap, okay, I'm gonna go.
I'm gonna find the numbers.
I have to know.
I remember watching the entirety of your-
Let's play of the-
It was like a Game Boy game, Pony-
Legacy of the Pony.
It's so good.
Yeah.
That was fun.
Honestly?
But I got so bored of the other ones.
Yeah, I can see that.
Like, I mean, Legacy of the Pony.
Like, to this day, I think about it and I'm like,
damn, there were some really great like little fucking personal project
like game mods Pony theme.
Like the Pony dev scene.
I mean, it wasn't anything like professional,
but like for a little-
Fuck.
Like for a little fucking-
Yeah, thank you.
Take a game and mod it to make it a Pony thing
and put it out into the world that people can play.
It was amazing.
The quality was insane and there was so much of it.
Ponyvania, Equestria Bound, Mega Pony,
Legacy of the Pony, Genius.
Legacy of the Pony only had 12 episodes.
Okay, okay.
By episode 100, less than 200 people,
less than 200 views per episode on Equestria Bound.
Oh, no.
The drop-off was immense.
Yeah.
I didn't realize there was that much Pony content.
Say what now?
I missed that.
What'd you say?
I just said I didn't realize that there wasn't-
that there wasn't or was so much Pony content out there.
What do you mean?
My first-
Yeah, you must be new around here.
That was my first contact.
I've said this before.
My first contact with MLP fandom was on Newgrounds.
Someone made the game called Story of the Blanks, I think.
And it's about-
Was that the scary one?
Yeah, the kind of scary one about Apple Bloom in the forest.
The forbidden forest?
She gets fucking murdered.
That was too hard.
I couldn't beat that.
I did beat it.
What's the forest called?
The evil forest near Ponyville?
I think that's-
Everfree Forest?
Yes.
I think it was the Everfree Forest, yeah.
That was it.
Pony games, man.
And you know what?
And I'm making another one.
Phantom's Revenge will be the last and greatest Pony game ever made.
Fun fact, Aspoi is new here.
I don't think he heard of the PCP before us.
No.
Lucky him.
He's from the chains that bind him.
Another fun fact.
This shredded actually started in a PCP server.
I mean, I had a feeling.
Like Lumia, I've seen you in servers around.
I've seen you in servers around.
In particular.
Yeah, I'm in a lot of several PCB servers.
I'm very active in Minecraft.
I kind of got the-
Or was.
Poddy casking represent, yeah.
Poddy casking.
I recognize Reborn from the poddy casks server.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, since since since you got me on shredded by challenging me to a
Pokemon battle in the PCP Minecraft server.
Yeah, that makes that makes sense.
You're not the only podcast to start out of out of a discord server out of a PCP
discord server.
So how does it feel to not be unique?
Hold on.
Are we the first one that started in a PCP discord server and actually got on the
PCP?
No, I think that the pro and on get on here.
I guess they kind of-
Well, well, Eleazar, I don't know if Eleazar really counts.
He was kind of friends with them and he became our editor.
So does it count?
Does it count in the like, oops, all guests episode?
How many people are in there?
I feel like there was a whole like a bunch of pro.
Yeah, some some of the yeah, some of the pro and on people were in there.
There was also the crow masticators.
Everyone forgets about the crow masticators.
I think even they forgot about themselves.
There's so much stupid lore.
Well, there's the teen CP.
I've been I've been seeing spiral spirals been going through his his rewatch of the
show and taking extensive notes.
And yeah, one of the things that came up was like, oh, yeah, anyone remember the
pro mask?
The pro crow crow masticators.
I don't remember them.
I don't even know what that is.
And I'm scared.
Don't worry about it.
I don't know either.
The name is the only people or people that eat crows.
I'm not really sure.
Well, it's based.
I mean, they were supposed to be like our rivals or our enemies or something.
I think it started off as a joke on on our show.
Yeah, like all the rivals of the PCP, the crow masticators, like stupidest name we
could come up with and people like, yeah, let's roll with that.
Nice.
Do that.
This is going to be big.
Yeah.
Well, I don't know whether they made anything actually, but I know people said they were.
I think.
YouTube has the answers.
We can find out.
Chrome masticate tours.
I feel like you might be getting something you might not want.
No, because it's kind of similar to crow masturbators.
And I don't know.
There was a channel called the crow masticators to choose her.
I think there's one video.
It's nothing wrong with chewing.
There's a there's a there was a crow masticators fan meetup.
I mean, the timing is right.
Yes.
This.
This is it's real.
Okay.
The chrome the first it's really wasn't a fever dream.
Look at this.
No, I'll prove it.
I'll prove it.
Look right right there.
They made their own version of the logo and everything.
They had a look.
They had a fucking fan meetup.
Man, they spent a whole minute to like export it and everything.
Oh, my God.
The audio quality is terrible.
They did interviews.
This is a whole fucking thing.
This is a whole fucking thing that you could argue the sketchy people podcast is a PCP off
shoot because they were all fans of the PCP and met through that.
Yeah.
Now they've got like a like all thing going on.
They I think, yeah, they did all meet because they were PCP listeners.
I think so.
Yeah, that probably counts.
I mean, I guess arm retrieval counts in a way.
I don't know.
Actually, no, no, that's a much larger project.
Yeah, I wouldn't say that counts.
Looks like I did not know my history.
I mean, there's a lot of it.
Well, Spiral is the lower master now.
He remembers it so we don't have to.
I think he's compiling it.
He's compiling a images like screenshots of all our quotes.
I think he's going to make a big like Imgur album with like a chronological list of like all the all the stupidest things we ever said.
I don't.
I don't know.
I don't know if it's going to beat the.
The potty.
The potty is cord one.
That one's so good.
Yeah.
That's the best Imgur album I've ever seen.
What's in it?
So on the podium scored.
There is a guy named Greg.
That's just his discord name.
And every time someone said something stupid in the discord, he screenshots it and uploads it to the Imgur album.
He's been doing this for two years.
I never knew about that.
It's good.
Am I in there?
I do not think so.
Hold on.
No, you would never say anything stupid.
No, I've said stupid things.
I swear.
No, I don't believe it.
I don't believe it.
Oh, here.
Here.
I'll share it.
I have a bookmarked.
Okay.
I love this thing so much.
There you go.
Enjoy.
I'll have a little look.
Because you'll probably know some of these people.
Reborn's in it.
He's on the second one.
Man, pug.
Anyway, enough about the PCP.
Enough about the PCP.
I've had enough.
Enough with the procrastinators already.
Who even are these losers?
I'm like 364 more images.
Okay, well, I'll look over that in my own time.
Yeah, it's a thing to do when you got time.
Would this be a good time to give our deep lore origin story?
Please.
Okay.
So about a year and a half ago, a guy named Soyboy Theories.
You might recognize the name.
Oh, you're going way back.
Soyboy wanted to play D&D with me.
So I joined his campaign.
Just don't make this a mere logic hour long story.
No, no, no.
This is quick.
I'm just setting it up.
Hey, if you're logic, if you're listening, fuck you.
He's actually mad that I'm on.
Oh, wait, no.
I forgot, but you're the guy who introduced me.
Yes, he's mad that I'm on this show right now.
I forgot about that, but you're the one that got him to come on in the first place.
That guy sucks.
Did I explain how YouTube works to him and he called me a Jew?
Because you explained how YouTube worked?
Yeah, just how the algorithm worked.
He just said I was Susan Schill or something like that and then stopped talking to me.
Fascinating.
That's exactly very classic mere logic move.
All right.
So Soyboy and AfiSama, another big YouTuber.
I was playing D&D with them and it was the first time I ever played D&D,
so I made an ass about out of myself.
And one of the other players named Sean Breezy made a Reddit post making fun of me.
He made five.
A few months later, a big YouTuber, CrickCrab, picked up the story and started making videos.
So I joined VC in the podium squad and I have everybody else join and we start making fun of CrickCrab in the Reddit post.
Kai randomly joins.
This is the first day I met Kai and we spend about an hour making fun of the post again,
except this time with Kai and we were like, let's make a podcast out of this.
Yeah.
I mean, what else are you going to do?
What else are you going to do with that?
Nothing.
Meanwhile, I passively actually know how like audio engineering and stuff.
So I'm like, yeah, we could do that.
Amazing.
And look how far we've come.
Yes.
What's that about?
We're sure doing this.
Sure am reading Reddit every week.
Damn, you're on the procrastinators.
This is like that episode of The Simpsons when Lisa's thinking about what school she wants to go.
When I went to the procrastinators podcast.
This is just like when Homer Simpson was a guest on the procrastinators podcast.
This is just like when Lisa's thinking about what school she wants to go to.
And she wants to go to Harvard and someone suggests Brown and she's like Brown and then Otto.
It's like, hey, hey, don't worry, don't sweat it, kid, kiddo.
I went to Brown and look at me.
Now I drive the bus.
And it's like, that's you right now.
It's like, now you drive the bus.
You're on the PCB.
Hell yeah.
You've moved up.
Life goes on.
Wait, does Otto do that twice?
Because I thought that moment was like Bart gets an F where he's like, oh, I'm going to have to repeat the fourth grade.
And it's like, Otto's like, I repeated the fourth grade myself twice.
Now I drive the school bus.
You're right.
I was mixing up the episode.
I don't know.
The Simpsons retcons a lot of things.
I remember.
Now that you say it, I'm sure that you're right.
It's the Bart gets an F episode.
That isn't a fire episode.
That's the episode where there's that sweet moment between him and Mrs. Krabapal when she lets him pass because he just barely failed.
But she gives him the one extra point he needs because he really proved that he was willing to put the work in or whatever.
It's a good episode.
I don't even want to fucking pray through it.
Camp crusty or whatever.
You know what's really weird about the PCP?
All kinds of things.
We have a strange overlap of fans.
Like even people that randomly find us, I have talked to them and they've mentioned, oh yeah, I was a fan of the PCP and I saw you guys and recommended.
I mean, I knew we started in a PCP server, right?
So there was going to be a little bit of overlap.
There's that.
And I mean, there's also the fact that I was on, I was a guest.
So maybe if they found you.
Oh, that's true.
So that doesn't really surprise me very much.
YouTube will recommend your videos based on the viewing habits of the people who currently watch you.
So that makes sense.
And if like actually like 100 or 200 or so all have that in common, it'll just start showing up in everyone's recommended feed.
Yeah.
Yes.
It just makes sense.
It is Mother Brain AI Bolshittery.
Fascinating.
See, this is why Kai is the big brain of our group.
You know, he just knows these things.
Ben, I owe you an apology from like a year ago.
I agree.
Yeah.
Do you remember when the PCP Danielson was coming out and then a week before the demo came out, a shitty fan made game came out that didn't work?
A shitty fan made game?
Well, it worked.
But it was like really shuttly put together deliberately.
Oh, it was like a parody of the dating sim.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's my fault.
It's your fault that I didn't work on that.
I was the programmer behind that.
Damn.
I like forgot.
I like forgot that that happened.
I do remember now that you mentioned it.
Because there was like a school shooting ending with Mumkey.
Yeah.
No need bro.
Oh, fun fact.
No need bro makes us send all of our audio files to the email address they made for the spoof of the PCP Damage Sim.
Yeah, you're like, all right, where do I send my audio files?
You're like, it's at the real PCP dating sim and fucking Gmail.
I can never.
Because of that.
Oh, and everyone's like, is this really where I send it?
Yep.
That's our editor's email.
Whoever controls the PCP dating sim, I think they still log in occasionally.
I think they retweeted the Tales of the Laserbot interview announcement, which was pretty nice of them.
I'm not sure who it is that runs the account, but I sure it's one of the devs.
What a period in history.
Oh, speaking of like PCP stuff that exists for some reason, did I mention on the episode yet that I finished writing the Road to Radcon Chapter 5?
Or was that before that I mentioned?
No.
Yeah, I want to...
That was pre-episode.
Yeah, so I just want to take a minute and be like, yeah, so viewers, you've probably all forgotten this.
But during the Radcon 4 Kickstarter campaign, the promise was that Trixie would write five chapters of the thing if the goals were hit.
All the goals were hit.
And then if we hit another goal, we would print it and give $100 plus backers the printed version of Road to Radcon.
We hit that goal.
So she only wrote four.
So I wrote the fifth chapter.
It's the longest chapter by far.
It's probably also the best.
Honestly, I can't judge.
I feel reading back through it.
I read it and I'm like, hey, I kind of like what I wrote.
I kind of like...
I think it's funny, but I can't judge my own writing, so I have no idea if it's good.
It amuses me.
That's all I can say.
And then, yeah, so I guess we'll probably be making a Kickstarter announcement soon that like, hey, if you pledged $100, you know, either let us...
If you've changed your address or something, let us know your new address or otherwise we'll just be sending out those books to like everyone's same old addresses.
But I'm sure a few people have probably changed address.
So I don't know.
We'll make an announcement.
It's been like seven years.
It's been a year and a half since Radcon 4.
It's been probably over a year since like the other merch went out.
Yeah, I've been getting...
I got Michi, Michi Fossard.
I got her to make the cover art and she's been sending me sketch sample.
I showed you guys a little before the call and it looks so good.
It is going to look so great in like pamphlet form.
I'm not exactly sure what format it's going to be in.
It's going to be a little booklet or pamphlet or zine or something.
It will arrive in the mail for everyone to enjoy.
Maybe we can sell extra copies on Gumroad.
Yeah, I mean, if we...
For $100.
Yeah, you have to order them in bulk.
We can figure it out later.
How many what?
I looked it up.
I was wondering how many hundred becas there are.
I counted it up before.
It was 126.
Okay.
So probably I'll make like 150 or maybe 200 copies and there will be a few extra.
Just for fun.
Yeah, I counted that out before because I was looking at local print shops and thinking like,
it might be cheaper for me to just get it printed at a local print shop if it's just a zine or something.
Instead of...
Because you know, the comic printing service that I use for the comics,
I feel like there are probably cheaper ways to print a text only booklet
than something that is meant to print like high resolution images like a comic book.
I think, I suspect.
Someone must be using like a...
What's the word?
Like a movable printed type printing press.
Who was the inventor of the printing press?
I was going to...
Mr. Print.
No.
Inventor of...
Mr. Press.
Yes, that's it.
Technically it was the Chinese.
Johannes Gutenberg.
Someone must be using like have like an old Johannes Gutenberg gas movable printed type machine
that will just let me use for free.
I hope.
Yeah.
Anyway, I'm excited.
I'm excited about that.
The cover looks great.
Me, she's a very, very good.
Very good drafts person.
Will you be distributing them signed by you?
That sounds labor intensive.
I'll fucking...
God, if someone gives me some money, I'll do that.
Yeah, whatever.
If someone gives me money, I'll do anything.
I'll do anything for money.
Yeah.
I mean, if someone wants...
If someone...
That we didn't offer that as like a reward, but if someone is like Ben, I will...
I will just send you $20 through PayPal.
If you just signed my copy before you put it in the envelope, I'll do it.
That's right.
Those...
That's my promise to you.
So I hope...
So since you asked, I assume that's something you'd be interested in.
Yes.
I was not a hundred dollar backer here.
I'd have to buy the book itself and then pay you extra to sign it.
I would pay the $20 and he sends it to you, never having sent the original hundred.
Oh, you know what?
You know what?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Since I'm sure we'll have extras.
Yeah, I bet there are at least a few people who would find it amusing to have a copy of it.
And yeah, I'll probably offer them on like Gumroad or something.
Why not throw more into the PCP coffers, I guess.
Hell yeah.
You know, about Kickstarter's, I just had one.
Oh my God.
It was pretty good.
It was really good.
Can we talk about the...
Can we talk about the ending?
Can we talk about the hype as fuck ending?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
So for the month of the Kickstarter, I had been...
I decided I was going to stream with my little VTuber punk avatar.
It's just like to build up hype, to build up like hype moments.
Just to get people thinking about it so they can chill it constantly.
The Kickstarter as it was going on.
And right at the end, I was playing Hollow Knight as I had been.
I'd beaten the game already, and I was doing a new save file on SteelSoul,
which is like one death and your save file is deleted.
And I was just...
I initially did it.
Jesus.
Yeah.
Initially, I did it just as a little thing.
Like, oh, well, I beat the game.
What else can I do?
It's like pretty good at video games.
It has like a weird knack for like hardcore games.
I mean, Hollow Knight is just so fun.
It's so fun to play and it's good.
True.
But yeah, I...
SteelSoul Run did not expect to get to like the third boss or whatever,
but just sort of casually playing through it.
The final day, I was like, okay, let's just play it.
Let's see how far I can get.
Turns out, near the end, there's a feasible...
There's like a...
It's feasible for me to actually complete the game,
because I have enough of the things I could go to the boss.
It wouldn't be like 100% completion,
but I could beat the final boss to get to the credits
within the last like 20 minutes of the Kickstarter ending.
The time on screen.
It was like 15 minutes away from the Kickstarter ending,
and you were like, okay, I'm going to do it.
And then you started like doing last minute preparations
and doing your badges and whatever.
Yeah, like I needed to get one more Dreamer,
and then that was it.
I could just go to the final boss
and try and win on a like no death run.
And it was like the biggest hype moment,
because obviously a one mistake would mean that
all of the hype deflated right at the end of the Kickstarter.
It would have been really upsetting.
It was so tense because you did kind of fuck up a few times
and it kind of looked like you were going to lose.
I kind of thought you were going to lose.
You were on one health when you beat him.
I thought you were going to lose.
I was on one health.
I made a clip of it.
It's the coolest thing ever.
It's really good.
Yeah.
Like when you beat him,
I see like the explosion animations
and I'm like, I don't...
I'm not sure if like,
whether that means it's over
or if there's like another phase or something.
So he starts blowing up and I'm like,
Pog?
Is it Pog time?
God yeah.
Oh yeah.
You beat him with like,
I think there was literally like two minutes left
or something.
It was four minutes and 20 seconds
when the credits were rolling
and that was funny.
Blaze it.
And then the Kickstarter.
Oh yeah, that's right.
The Kickstarter was like,
it was doing really well the whole time
in that last day
and it was just sort of like,
everything that could go correctly did.
Including the fact that we did not hit
the 666 amount of pounds on the Kickstarter
which would have summoned the devil
which would probably be a bad thing.
Narrowly avoided the summoning the devil.
Thank God.
It would have been an absolute travesty.
It was a lot of explaining to do.
It was like only like 50 pounds away or something.
It was pretty close but no devil.
We can all breathe a sigh of relief.
Delicious.
Yeah.
So I had a good month
doing playing that game
for the first time by the way,
the first playthrough
and then the second playthrough
was the Steel Soul Run.
It was just unbelievable.
And then the Kickstarter hit all the stretch goals
and even some joke ones
that I had to come up with.
It's great.
And now I have to do a lot of stuff.
Did you already show me the graph,
the final graph?
Or I think you might have showed it to me
like the day before.
Do you have the final money graph?
Yeah, let me have a look.
I love the money graphs.
A Patreon shows you a little graph
of how your total pledges progress over time
and it's always like,
it shoots up at the beginning
and then it kind of like levels off
and then towards the end it like,
up at the, as FOMO kicks in
and everyone's like,
oh, I guess it's now or never.
I got a pledge.
Yeah, it was like,
I was so worried before the Kickstarter
because I'd had a Kickstarter fail.
Look at that.
Hell yeah.
D.
Initially,
I did one stream.
Goal was hit within two hours
of me making it live
and it happened on stream.
That was fun.
And then, you know, it slowed down
as people who were already,
you know,
people who really wanted it got it immediately
and then slowly,
but surely it creeped up
and then I announced the plush,
the Lord of Ghost plush tier
would be possible
if we got like a few backers.
And I did all the calculations
for the costs of the delivery,
which is really, really expensive
and it's annoying,
but it's how it works with packages
overseas, I guess.
But then that's the spike
that happens around the 11th,
12th of July,
is when I opened that up
and then each big pledge,
all of the big fans
got the plush
and it's like 25, 31 plushes I need to get.
All the plujers.
The fucking plujers.
Wait, I'll post it in the chat.
The one to 99 year old
blue chair.
That was oblivion.
Oblivionfall made the joke in the chat.
He said,
I'm gonna pluge and I just,
I just thought that was the funniest thing I'd ever heard.
So I had to go and make this immediately.
With only like an hour left,
but it was worth it.
He's based.
I've already ordered the pins from China.
So those are flying in.
Did you use the company that I recommended?
I don't think so.
I just shopped around
and found like one that was good
and on Alibaba.
Yeah.
And I just got to, you know,
get a hundred and fifty or a hundred.
I can't remember how many pins, but enough.
Shit is so damn cheap on Alibaba.
Holy fuck.
Yeah, that's good.
That's because they get you with shipping.
Like have the prices.
Try to ship things.
A little bit.
Yeah.
A little bit, but like pins are so light.
They could, and you know, bulk order.
That's the cheap that the shipping is all in the in the costs.
It's like getting pins, getting pins made.
Okay.
Yeah, the shipping is a bit of a bitch,
but like getting pins made in the UK
from the company that I had make the Puba pins.
It was like the cost was like three dollars,
like two or three dollars a pin.
Getting them made in China
through Alibaba, they were like 40 cents a pin.
And like, yeah, they did charge me a little for like having,
they made the mold and they charged me like a mold making fee.
But when you're, I was ordering the hundreds of them,
so it was still like by far, it was by far cheaper.
I probably saved like a thousand dollars or more
just by ordering from there.
All the benefits of not having a minimum wage,
but none of the actual consequences
because I don't live there.
They have, they must, they have, they must.
They must have a minimum wage.
That's anti-China.
Yeah, we have a minimum wage.
Do you mean in the UK?
Of course we do.
No, he's talking about China.
Yeah, China is like absurdly like open market.
And it's a little, it's an issue.
I haven't looked it up, but they must have something.
There must be some kind of bottom floor.
They are remarkably capitalistic
for as like imperialistic as they are.
It is, it is, it is a weird mismatch.
I don't know, I don't know why you say those are,
are those a contradiction?
I thought you were gonna say they were weirdly capitalist
for how they call themselves communists.
That too.
Yeah.
That's what I thought you were going with that.
It's about what I was going with.
I mean, we're imperialists.
We love that shit.
We love, we love empire building.
Yeah, not wrong.
United States empire.
Do I love Age of Empires?
Yeah, we love our forex.
It's good.
Actually, I suppose imperialism specifically,
it does tend to be a, yeah, you know what,
a recanted, recanted.
Okay.
We've all learned something.
I've got also the red man comic.
The zine.
But in putting the, putting yes, the zine for those,
for the, because that was one of the stretch goals is a,
along with the Lord of Ghost comic,
every physical tier will get a red man comic free of charge.
No need to increase your pledge.
And those are looking pretty good.
They're so stupid.
I put a few like authors commentary under a few of them.
And it's funny because they were just put on Twitter.
It's half of them are like jokes I came up with half of them are
just like things I was thinking in the form of like the same
format as a joke.
So it's like, is this a, I don't see the punchline.
I don't get it.
And that's why I find it so funny.
Yeah.
Cause there's no punchline.
Red man's like kind of a terrible standup comedian.
Nobody knows what he's doing.
Neither does he.
Did you, did you say that you were going to make like the cover
and the back cover are just like also going to be red man comics,
but they're going to be.
Yeah.
Every, every part of, every part of the comic, the,
yeah, the zine is going to be a red man comic.
So the cover is just going to be like a red man comic with red
man saying, oh my God, it's the red man comic.
You're reading the front.
Hey, hi.
You know, some, some stupid thing.
Yeah.
I said before that like, I love the red man comics, but
they're all buried on Twitter.
To read them, I would have to like scroll back through posts
and posts and posts and find them.
And I'll never do that.
So the only way I'll ever see them again is if,
is if I get the, the zine and now I'm getting the zine.
So, you know, it's a happy ending.
Yeah.
It's a lot of work coming up.
I've, I've got, I've got to, to like put together the red man.
I've put all of the pages that already exist.
And I'm thinking I should, I should write some new ones and
like add some like value to people.
Like if they want to see exclusive red man comics,
I can't think of anything.
That's how I felt.
I felt with vapors, the vaporettes.
I was like, uh, I guess I got to write like something to happen.
Uh, okay.
I felt that way as well for the Lord of Ghost stories,
that the ghost stories that are in the Lord of Ghost comic.
God, I haven't started working on mine, but I came up with like,
moving soon and then I will work.
I will work.
I promise.
Yeah.
Don't worry about it.
I'll have to, I'll, I'll kick people in the behind and
about that in a little while.
But for the moment I need to, I need, I have my own things to do.
So I got to, I got to prepare.
You got to like get the packaging.
That's a whole lot of stuff.
I sure hope I don't fuck it up.
Yeah man.
That would be, that would sure would suck.
If you have fucked it up.
Yeah.
No, it's good.
It's going to be good.
I pledged and I've never, I'll never regret it.
What else?
Did it?
Okay.
Here's a thing.
Here's a thing that happened this week.
Did anyone play the Google Doodle for the Olympics?
No.
The what?
Oh my God.
What's that?
I hope it's still go, I hope it's still like this by the time this episode airs.
You know like how Google will make its logo something different?
Uh-huh.
Well, damn.
I'm, I'm.
Oh, I can see.
Now I think this might blow your minds.
The Google Doodle this week, it's a whole video game.
It's like a big video game that you can play.
This is Pog.
Yeah.
It's awesome.
It ruled.
What the fuck?
It's got an animated anime intro.
Yeah.
It's got like cutscenes and stuff.
It's, it's a whole fucking like adventure game.
Apparently there was another one.
There was like a Halloween one that they did a previous year.
Like the same, the same company or the same developer made like another Google game.
But this is, I guess the second one.
And yeah, you're this little cat who is going to some island and like it's an Olympic thing.
So it's like you go into like become the champion and all these different sports.
You go around and you like do quests and like, you know, solve people's problems and stuff.
It rules.
It's amazing.
I'm just watching this intro.
This is, this is great.
Oh, this is fun.
It's just a bunch of games.
Oh, okay.
I, I don't know if I 100% of it.
Like I think there might have been some events that I didn't find.
But I did do all of the like side quests, like all of like the, the story side quests where
you got to find someone's lost key to the basement or whatever, like all that shit.
So I feel pretty good about it.
I just wanted to, I just thought I'd mention that because like someone told me, damn, who was it?
Was it someone on the stream?
No, we didn't stream this week.
Oh no, I think it was one of our roommates.
One of my roommates told me like, Hey, do you see the Google Doodle today?
I was like, no, it's like, you should check it out.
It's pretty good.
It's like, okay.
Then I went and I found it.
I was like, wow, my God.
And then I spent like three hours playing it that I should have been writing Road to Radcon.
But I got it written in the end anyway.
So it's fine.
It all, it all worked out.
Yeah.
So now, all right, let's take a break, break from the podcast for everyone to go play that
and we'll convene in two hours.
Base, base, base.
It's called, it's called like the summer games or something.
Champion Island, Champion Island is what it's called.
And it's fucking rules.
I liked, I liked the race.
I liked the racing event the best.
Which race did you like the most?
I don't, wait, actually, the climbing one is really good too.
The climbing one is pretty fun.
Although the second, because they have like a basic one you have to do to like call it complete.
But then there's like a secret, I think every sport has a secret second and third like harder
version of the sport that you can find.
And I didn't, I don't think I found all of those.
But I was like screaming at the like harder version of climbing and running.
Those ones, I think the other ones I found very easy, but those two I like had to play
them like a dozen times each to actually beat them.
They're fricking, they're fricking hard, bro.
I'm team blue, by the way.
I'm the team with the buff minotaurs living in the city area.
I thought that was cool.
I think we're way behind, there's like a leaderboard.
It's like, yeah, there's like a global leaderboard and like you can join a team.
And then I think probably how well you do, like your high scores in the different sports will like contribute to your team.
Yeah, yeah, there's like a global, it's like a global, it's like slime.
Crowdies versus killers, like global slime counter.
That's pretty pug.
Yeah.
It's so pug.
Is this going to disappear?
This game.
Probably.
Damn.
I think it will disappear, but I feel like it'll be archived somewhere.
I hope so.
This is really cool.
I kind of want to go and find the old halloween game that they apparently made for a previous halloween.
Can we look up the game developer?
Made it.
Maybe they'd have it.
Google champion island developer.
You know, maybe it was like an in-house, maybe it was like just an in-house Google.
Okay.
Well, the animated scenes were animated by Studio 4C.
Google champion.
What if I tried Google champion island halloween?
Hmm.
Okay.
I guess it was Google Doodle Halloween 2020 full game.
This is like a video walkthrough.
I think so.
This isn't the actual game, but this is proof that it's real.
Yeah.
Okay.
It looks, it looks different though.
It's not like a walker out pixel spray.
Are the characters references to other media, do you know, because I was just playing it
while we were talking about it and I got to the archery minigame and the guy looks almost
exactly, has the same facial design as the guy from Ger and Lagann, the one with the purple
eye shadow.
Wait, the archery guy?
Yeah.
He looks like Leron.
Is that the name of the guy from Ger and Lagann?
I don't remember.
No, he doesn't.
It's the eye shadow.
What are you talking about?
It's the purple eye shadow.
That's outrageous.
You're, you're on, off your rock.
It won't let me play.
You're cracked.
Dude, it's a deer.
That sucks to be you, Kai.
It's Undertale.
I had Deltarune.
It's, wait, what's that other Undertale Deltarune?
The one where you're, you're the cat and you have to carry the light bulb around?
One shot.
Oh, I haven't played that, but I have.
I, yeah, I played it and then I never got the like true ending.
I, I, I wanted to.
That game was pretty good.
I played it on stream a long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long time ago.
Oh boy.
All right.
I can't play a video game on a podcast.
Yeah, it's, it's, it's not like, I'm, this was a mistake.
Bring it up.
I hope, I hope and think that probably the Halloween one must be around somewhere.
Although I'll be, I'll be honest, just the fact that this like Olympics one is a like
top down sprite graphics walk around game.
Yeah.
Just makes me like it.
Like that's, that's just my favorite kind of game.
Yeah.
So I'm sure that this other one's not as good.
Also, I don't like Halloween that much.
Oh, that is fucking fair of you.
But then again, I don't like the Olympics that much either.
So whatever.
That's a wash.
Yeah.
You lose one cool point for not liking Halloween, but you gain it back for not liking the
Olympics.
You're at a net pot.
You're at a net neutral right now.
Okay.
Okay, I'll take it.
Oh man.
I got really into Hollow Knight during the month of streaming to the point where I wanted
to try after I beat the steel soul, like I felt so cool and I was like, you know what?
I am the best.
I'm going to speed run as my third playthrough.
I'm going to do a world record attempt and it was going quite well actually because I
had been watching a lot of like Hollow Knight YouTube.
I'd really just gotten completely into Hollow Knight in every aspect.
Wait, what is the world?
It's one of my favorite games.
Oh, any percent.
It's like 45 minutes, I think.
I can't remember.
There's lots of different world records, but you have to be quite quick and you have to
be able to do skips, platforming tricks and skips to get past areas earlier than you should
be and I couldn't do those things really.
You have to do weird pogo attacks off of explosions but without getting hit by them so that you
can bounce up into an area that you shouldn't be able to get to and stuff like that, but
I had watched all of these and I'm like, yeah, you know, I could fucking do that.
I beat steel soul on my second playthrough.
I'm the guy who did that and I tried it.
I got pretty far.
I died three times in the same place and I rage quit, deleted the save file.
It was the biggest idiot mistake of all because it was a really good run other than that small
mistake.
Ben said I have a neck for really difficult games.
Maybe I do.
You beat Dark Souls like your first try without even trying.
I did level up a lot.
I've never steel soul Hollow Knight.
I've tried to do that and I just can't get over the time loss of each run and I'm also
trash so I die within the first hour and then it's like trash.
My first playthrough of Hollow Knight right now and I'm crying everywhere I go.
I'm shit.
Speaking of Hollow Knight, when is Steel's, what's the sequel called?
Silksong.
Silksong?
I asked this.
It's like nobody knows.
They haven't announced a release date yet so definitely not this year and probably not
even next year.
I feel like so with Hollow Knight there's two or three Kickstarter pledges that the devs
really wanted to get to like two fully fleshed out areas that they were just that they didn't
hit the goal to include and they talked about how they wanted to include it really bad.
I feel like with Silksong, since it's not a backed game, they are just trying to include
everything.
Like every time they think they're about to get the game finished they're like, but wait,
what if we add this area?
They have so much money they can kind of just sit on it and work like as long as they need
on the new game.
I mean, I can respect that.
I guess I'm somewhat lucky that I haven't been waiting this whole time for Silksong.
Having only just got into Hollow Knight now.
I could be waiting for years afterwards.
They set up a whole thing.
They have trailers and everything.
Yeah, I've seen gameplay like little demo things.
You can't play them though.
Maybe they'll just like drop it out of nowhere one day.
That would be Pog.
I could see them doing that.
They seem like the kind of studio that would.
Gabe, are you going to keep streaming?
I've heard that they, you know, I kind of want to.
I guess I should.
There's a lot of the days where I'm like, man, I got work to do, but it's not really
that much work.
And for the Kickstarter, a lot of things I have to wait for things to be delivered or
people to draw the ghost stories.
There's going to be points where I'm not doing anything in particular.
So yeah, I feel like I could.
I would continue to stream Hollow Knight though.
I would be doing speed runs and just raging like extremely.
I'm not shy about rage quitting.
I do it all the time.
I was thinking because I'm still really excited to create the sun in Noida and
Shekels for Heckels.
I guess hopefully by the time this comes out, I will have already done so.
Hopefully.
I'm hoping to be able to do it on the next stream.
It might take two streams depending on how it goes.
But I was thinking like, I don't want to just stream Noida on Shekels for Heckels.
I do want to go back to the Minecraft stuff.
But I was thinking like, why not?
I want to keep playing Noida.
And when I looked at all the in-game achievements that there are, there's like 30 achievements
in the game that I have never gotten.
Like I made a list of them here and like there's tons and tons of them.
So like after I make the sun, I might just go, I might just, if I'm going to play Noida,
because I'm going to play Noida one way or another.
I might just start like streaming when I play it.
Just because why not?
And because it would be fun.
Because like I want to, I don't know, I want to show it off.
And like there's a, even after making the sun, there's more stuff.
Like you, you got to make the dark sun.
And then apparently if you bring the dark sun and the dark and the regular sun together,
you can like collide them and some shit happens.
And I don't know.
That sounds pretty neat.
I have a deliberately, yeah, I was like, I should do that on.
They have a sibling rivalry.
I should do that on my Twitch, I guess.
Um, Gib, since we started in the podium squad, they would flame me alive if I did not ask you
if you have any updates to the podium cast.
Oh yeah.
I asked Nate a while ago.
Hey, we've, it's been a while since we did a podcast.
When are you free to record?
We could do one on the God, when did I ask him?
Let me look.
Let me look at the DMs.
Um, he basically replied saying, uh, sure, I'm a little busy with stuff right now, but
I'll get around.
I'll, I'll, uh, we, we, yeah.
The June 27th is when I asked and he said, don't have much spare time.
I'm going to be busy for at least a week.
And, uh, yeah, I guess we haven't followed up on that because it's been more than a week
or I think it has.
Um, did you hear about the mutiny?
Um, I don't know about anything pertaining to the part of the discord because I left.
Oh yeah, that's right.
So yeah.
Um, there was a mutiny.
Um, so big got big the person that you modded.
And everyone was upset that there was a mod.
Uh, he got his discord account banned.
Um, for promoting violence from discord.
Yeah.
For promoting violence.
Lol.
Um, okay.
So he made a new one.
Fucking idiot.
He made a new one, rejoined the server and he asked Nate if he could be remodded and
apparently Nate told him no.
Perfect fucking chaos.
I mean, that's typical.
Um, wait, he got, he got banned for promoting violence for what?
He didn't say why he won't tell anyone why.
He just says in another server.
Was it?
Or is it?
It was in another server.
We have no details.
If he's asked.
So he says a secret double life of, of like, I don't know, the double life.
According to him, he woke up to an email from discord saying that his account was now banned
for promoting violence.
La now.
Sad, but true.
So there's no, there's no mods anymore.
Yeah.
Except Nate.
Chaos reign supreme.
Well, Nate never did any moderation.
That he actually has broken that and did some moderate.
Wait, what happened?
There was a mutiny.
Um, a guy named veil.
I don't know if you guys have heard of him.
He's a veil.
Veils that decided to make a server called the podium scored two.
And he started telling people to spam fire emoji spam.
We're burning down the ship in the podium scored.
So a bunch of people spam.
There was a bunch of that everyone's and then Nate turned on slow mode.
So you can only send a message once every 60 seconds.
Wow.
This sounds like a fail.
All right.
I, the thing with the podium scored is that the, there's a patreon.
So the, the higher tier chats are like safe ish from like the big spam of the larger user base of the, you know, the show.
Yeah.
It's just politics.
And yeah.
So I would have thought, is it slow mode everywhere or just in the major?
It was just, well, I, I'm not a patron.
I don't know.
I do know most of the patrons were on board with the mutiny to join veil server,
which was the funniest part.
Like a lot of the blue names just turn white.
I mean, there's no new episodes.
So like if it's, it's fair enough, I guess, what else are they going to do?
Yeah.
It's fan fire emojis in main chat.
Um, I am really glad that they remembered to turn off slow mode though because a bunch of people were worried that he just forget that he turned it on.
That, that sounds like something he would do.
Yeah.
Um, but yes, that, that was the great mutiny of the podium scored.
And now the server's dead because both, they split the, it's active user base in half.
Wow.
Tragedy.
How's the sequel server going?
Uh, it's also dead.
Oh.
Okay.
Based.
Um.
It's a real pirate war.
Yeah.
As, as captains has had, um, we weren't, we were like, hold up in our, in our captain's quarters and we weren't communicating with the crew.
And they're like, where are we going?
We don't know.
We're just sailing into, into like dangerous waters.
This is no direction.
We need direction.
We need a new video.
We're pirates.
We need, we need a one piece.
We need rules.
We need rules and regulations to follow.
If we don't get Gibbs nuance take of this one piece chapter, we're burning the ships down.
I still, I like, there's no, like, it, there's no, like, it's over.
It still could happen.
I just need to keep pestering Nate about it and we can get together and record.
I think Nate was busy because he was working on that video that he dropped the nickel.
He's also got the, the, the radcon.
He needs to work on the OVA.
He needs to finish the OVA.
That's after, well, after a road to radcon, there's just that and then the dojin, which is, I don't know.
Is the music video even out yet?
Oh, that was done.
No, the song, I think, I thought he said it was done.
The song came out.
Oh, it did.
Was there a reason why the music video didn't come out yet?
Was it?
Oh, it was waiting for the lecture, but the lecture's out.
Yeah, I feel like that should be out, but it's not.
No, you're right.
Okay.
That's another thing that's really got to get done.
I guess lots of, lots of things to pester Nate.
I would, I would, I would love to complain.
I would love to complain and say like, oh, why don't we just, why doesn't he just get that done?
But like, it took me a month and a half to get around to actually writing the, the radcon chapter.
So like, I'm not any better.
Yeah.
It is what it is.
Imagine it all being done.
Imagine road to radcon being finished.
I can't deliver.
I know.
I know it's a curse.
It is a curse.
I felt the same way after radcon three, when it took a year to get the fucking, the t-bap resurrection done.
I felt like, like I was under a curse the whole time.
And I feel that way again, even stronger now.
And I can't wait to be free.
I feel like this must act like has to be the most confusing series of conversations for us, boy.
Having not known.
Oh yeah.
I am entirely lost.
No, that's his problem.
Talk about basically everything.
Yeah.
Like every, like offshoot thing related to the show.
It has been inside baseball for an hour.
Yeah.
Have we, have we been going for an hour?
At least.
Hour seven minutes.
Time flies when you're having fun.
True.
All right.
So let, so shred it, right?
Shred it.
What is, what is a subreddit that you guys have heard of that is horrible?
Yeah.
Like what would be a subreddit worth?
We said we were going to cover.
It would make you go, holy shit.
I need to see this.
I hate that subreddit.
I was, I was, I mean.
Procrastinate as podcast.
Honestly, if you did one about our subreddit, that would be really funny.
Uh, I was reminded by YMS the other day of, I think it's gone.
I don't think it exists anymore, but like there was one called like watch people die.
I think it was a real subreddit or it was something like that.
And it was really just like videos in which people are killed.
Jesus.
Uh, obviously it doesn't exist anymore, but it did at one point.
Um, let's see.
I mean, shit.
Uh, I haven't used Reddit in a long time.
So, uh, I mean, I don't know if there's a lot of good content to come from this, but
I remember, I don't know what it was called, but I remember the, when I was doing my hypocrite
reviews, I was looking for places to show them to show off like, oh, I make video game reviews.
Guys, look at them.
And there was this one Reddit I came across, which was, you know, a bunch of, of wannabe
video game review channels posting their video game reviews.
And, you know, every single one of them, no upvotes, no comments, no likes, no nothing.
Uh, because nobody was there to watch them.
They were all there to promote themselves.
Yeah.
So it was, it was, it was sad.
I posted my thing there and I was like, you know what?
I don't want to be here anymore.
Yeah.
Like, yeah.
So it was like just a weird promotional.
There's, there's, there's all kinds of places.
That's the exact opposite of r slash vTubers.
Cause it's just, oh, that's just like literally like every, like all like these are virtual
YouTubers, just like helping, supporting each other.
That's why it sounds like the exact opposite.
I don't believe you.
Oh, yeah.
I don't, I don't believe you.
A little bit.
Game reviews.
When we started Shreddit, there was a sub that the podium scored, begged us to do and
it was called r slash horse walkers.
Uh, a week into Shreddit's existence, that subreddit got permanently pruned, deleted.
No, you fools.
Oh man.
And can you find archives or something?
I have not found anything.
I just know it existed and it got the, it got banned from Reddit because people were
just posting pictures of them having sex with horses and it was disgusting.
Oh, it was just people having sex with horses.
Yes.
And people talking about their experiences.
Well, it's advertising is on point.
Yeah.
I mean, it just sounds like a Mr. Hands fan club.
Forgive me if this is a stupid question, but like, that's not illegal, right?
Like pictures of pictures of you fucking the horse are not, are not illegal.
I think it depends on the state.
Hmm.
Why Ben?
What do you want?
I mean, wait, like, I'm not going to get in trouble.
Am I?
I don't know.
I just like, wait, what was it banned for?
Was it banned?
Is it, is it simply, is it a crime to fuck a horse and take pictures of it in America?
I mean, I didn't think it was, but maybe.
I don't know what I'd be able to spot.
If not, like, what was it deleted for?
I think you, I would assume this like animal cruelty laws.
I think you're not supposed to have a discord server that's more than like a certain percentage pornography.
I think that's a rule somewhere.
Wait, it was a, wait, it was a discord server.
I thought it was a subreddit.
Oh, but same thing.
I don't know why it's a.
Okay.
Um, I don't actually know.
I don't know if that's true.
There was also r slash incels.
No, that doesn't make sense.
That's definitely not true because there are dedicated porn subreddits.
Should I mention I don't use Reddit.
You, you, you have said so.
Okay.
No, that, that can't be a reason why.
There's like hundreds of that.
Like, I feel like a lot of Reddit's user base is just people going to specific, like porn Reddit places.
Where they get the specific porn that they want.
You know, I wouldn't know.
Yes, I would.
It's nice to, I mean, they segment it into, you know, highly, highly specific.
Misha's catering to every, every taste.
Like horse fucking.
Like horse fucking for instance.
Yeah.
Speaking of highly specific there, we wanted to do an episode on the incel subreddit because
obviously making fun of them is just easy.
Sure.
Too, too easy.
But there was a specific subsection of our slash incels was banned two years before it started.
There was another subreddit that we were like a week from covering and it got banned.
And I forgot it was something like Asian hoppers or hoppers something.
Hoppers?
And it was a subreddit for Asian incels.
What is a hopper?
Is it just an incel?
I don't know.
Shit.
I remember this.
I can't remember what it is.
I think it's H-A-P-P-A.
I think I've heard it before, but I don't know what it means.
All I know is that it was a very specific niche of incels who were Asian and believed
they were superior to other races and that girls should be Asian men.
Sure.
But also that they were involuntary celibate because they're just so bad even though they
have an advantage.
Well, it's because Western, it's because Western media has disseminated, you know, the Jewish
global homo security that has made them all want to date, to miscegenate and date black
men to weaken the white race and also the Asian race.
What are you?
Natters.
I'm just spitting facts is what I'm doing.
And that's what I would say.
Dude, I could be a hopper.
I could get on there.
God, I hope that's not a slur or something.
I hope that's what I think it means.
I mean, they call themselves that, so I don't think so.
Okay.
I don't know.
I'm just saying, I think I could blend in.
I know how they think that anything can be a slur if you try.
I mean, do you want the definition?
I looked it up on Urban Dictionary.
So I mean, it's Urban Dictionary.
Why don't you read us the Urban Dictionary?
Classic.
Man, he's just bringing it back.
He doesn't even know about the peace.
He's a natural.
Yeah.
Yeah, true.
A Japanese term for people who are half Asian and half white.
It means half in Japanese.
Usually they have big almond brown or hazel eyes.
North Asian hoppers are pale whereas Southeast Asians are extremely tan.
Most have freckles.
I knew it.
I was going to say this, but then I was like, oh, it must not be what I think it is.
I thought the word for that was like, when you said a hopper, I was like, wait,
isn't that the word that means you're half Japanese?
No, that must be like, I thought it might be like hafu or hafa or something.
But yeah, okay.
Yeah.
So it's about mixed race, Asian people.
And they had their own.
Who think that?
Wait, they think that white girls should date Asian people.
Yes.
That's the idea.
Okay.
They think Asians are better, but maybe they curse the non-Asian side of them.
I'm not sure.
I mean, I'm not sure if they curse the Asian side or the non-Asian.
They're definitely cursing one side.
Are they cursing one side or are they cursing the other side?
Or are they there because they believe in hapa supremacy?
They're like, I'm the best of both worlds.
I'm a genetic perfection.
I combine the two things that are good.
Why aren't the girls, why you don't the girls understand this?
You see, this is why Reddit should not ban subreddits.
They should just archive them so everyone in the future can just make fun of them.
Stop people from posting, but because now we'll never have those questions answered.
But that takes up server space.
Really?
Is there no wayback machine archive of any of this stuff?
I have a very late man, but there probably is.
You might want to give the wayback machine a try.
I'm just saying that's the first thing I would try if I were looking for old deleted shit on the internet.
We still have a ton of subreddits though.
I mean, sure.
It's not like you're running out of material.
Yeah, no.
I do kind of want to infiltrate some of the private Reddit communities,
because there are some communities that know they're toxic and know they're bad.
So they're private.
Do you know what FDS is?
No.
FDS, no.
Female dating strategy.
Oh, no.
Imagine women with the charisma of themselves.
So it's for women that can't get a date?
No.
It's for women to say, oh, I don't need to get a date because all the men in my life are no value and I cannot use them.
So therefore, I am a strong independent woman.
So why is it called dating strategy?
That's a good question.
It was probably started off.
Maybe it started as, yeah.
Well, they do kind of like something different.
If a girl joins the subreddit and she starts posting about how she has a date,
they give quote unquote advice by saying that, oh, if he plays video games, dump him.
Yeah, yeah.
That kind of like really stupid, just generalizations.
You got to go for them HVMs.
You don't want an LVM.
You want that high value mail.
Oh, yeah.
That's some video games.
That's some pretty hardcore, some basic LDM behaviors right there.
Make sure he has a bed frame.
If he doesn't have a bed frame, you got to walk out.
You got to, you don't want to fuck with that.
What is so great about bed?
I saw a tweet about this today.
There's more bed frame discourse.
What is so important about bed frames?
Why does everybody love bed frames?
What is the, what is the deal?
Is it bed frames or is it the Olympic sex bed debacle?
No, no.
I'm talking about when ladies say like,
uh, men, why are you 25 plus and still don't have a bed frame?
Like get, get serious.
If you want a girl to come in your bedroom, you better have a bed frame.
That is the exclusive reason I have a bed frame.
What is a bed frame?
I'll be honest.
Woman.
What do they mean by bed frame?
Do they mean just like support for the mattress so that it's not touching the ground?
Yeah.
You know, you know, the thing, the wooden structure that you put your box spring and mattress on.
I mean, you got to get off the ground.
You got to get like one with a headboard.
If you're going to go for it, you got to make it obvious that like, ah, yes, I am.
What does anyone need?
What does anyone need a headboard for?
I think it's just aesthetics.
I think it's, it's a, it's a form of peacocking to be like, to be completely honest.
Honestly, honestly, it seems like it's just a decorative thing that is just like a status symbol.
And it's just like, it's just like people that unironically buy into like the fucking bed frame meme.
They're like, it's just something you got to have just to show that you're not a loser.
And if you don't have one, you're a loser.
It just makes you look a little more like, you know, what you're doing.
Even though it doesn't actually mean anything.
The one thing that I can, like, yeah.
If that, like, I can see it like the headboard being the thing that you like, oh, that's the status symbol.
But the bed frame is just like a utility thing.
The one thing, the one thing.
Is it just more comfortable to sleep on a mattress on a bed frame than it is on the ground?
I don't think so.
The one thing that I know that it does do that I can understand the utility of a bed frame is that it gives you more floor space and you can store stuff under your bed.
And like, I get that.
Isn't it also a sex thing so the bed doesn't, you know, go too far off the box spring, you know, it has a frame to keep it centered on the box spring?
Um, I guess.
I mean, I mean, I guess that's potentially an issue.
Sex or no sex.
Uh, I guess.
I don't know.
How far does your fucking mattress slide?
It just feels like such a normal utility, like part of a bed.
You get a bed, that's it.
That's part of the bed.
It's like saying, oh, I'm gonna get it like a microwave without a door.
Why would you get a door?
I think that's where the controversy comes in because it's such a basic thing that not having it, I guess, is notable.
How is it?
It can't be that notable because I feel like it's not that uncommon for you.
I have not met a single person who has a bed frame.
If you, if you can't tell, I'm very defensive because I also do not have a bed frame.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I have a big problem.
That wasn't obvious.
This post was made by no bed frame gang.
I mean, if I didn't have one already, none would be on the floor.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't have a bed frame and I just, I don't know why I would want one.
I don't see how my life or my situation or even just the aesthetics of my room would be improved by having one.
Yeah.
And so I was like, ladies, he better have a bed frame.
I was like, what?
Why?
Explain why?
Just give me one good reason why you, you wish for a bed frame.
What would having a bed frame provide you?
And I have, I have yet to see an explanation.
I genuinely just think it's like a peacocking.
Like it's just something you're supposed to have.
Yeah.
Just because.
Well, I guess I never thought about it before, but I'm not exactly going to go out of my way to not have one.
I don't know.
I feel like bed, I've never seen.
Well, yeah, like, I mean, I have never been in a house that doesn't have a bed with a bed frame.
To be honest, the way that my room is like one, one side of my room has like an angled, you know, ceiling.
It kind of tapers down and my bed is under the tapered down part.
If my, if I had a bed frame, my bed would actually be like kind of too high up.
And I think I would feel claustrophobic because like the angled ceiling would be sort of like right there.
And I would be, I mean, I could probably still sit up, but I might feel like, oh, I got to like avoid the ceiling.
I don't know.
I kind of think I like it just the way it is.
I think I do actually, even if I had a bed frame, I might not set it up.
I might take it apart and put it away.
It's like, no, I don't have the space for it.
I don't have the vertical space to spare.
You just put the headboard up.
You leave the rest.
That's all you did.
Just lean it against the wall and push your mattress up against it.
It's not connected to anything.
You just, you just drill it.
No, no, you just drill it right into the wall itself.
Let's get some bungee cords.
Just rig it up.
Just hang it from the ceiling.
All about the headboard.
Got to make it look like maybe some duct tape.
You got to make it look just terrible.
Now we're talking.
The worst, the better.
I don't know why this scenario popped into my head, but I'm thinking like you got your mattress on the floor.
And then, you know, you bring like, I don't know, some soup in to have a meal at your computer.
And then whoops, you spill it.
It goes on the floor and then it goes straight onto it, like rolls over to the mattress.
It's on the mattress.
If you had a bed frame, it'd be on the floor instead.
And the mattress would be okay.
I know that's a straight.
I don't like the idea of the mattress.
That's a very specific situation, but I think it's just that reason.
I think I might have to get a bed frame now.
Suspend your mattress by using cables and pulleys.
Anchors on the floor.
I mean, that works.
That sounds cool.
It's just like a really heavy hammock.
Hammocks are good.
I should get a hammock.
The biggest reason for bed, brought to you by bed frame gang is that when standing up,
you are, your ass is at normal ass level when standing, like when sitting.
So it's like getting up in the morning is no work at all.
You don't have to like try to like get up and shit.
You can just like roll over and you're up.
Are you kidding me?
It's great.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Like, oh, I struggled to stand in the morning.
Do you have gravity on my side or I can't do it?
I smoke.
Give me a fucking break.
Give me a break.
I was going to say this earlier, but one of the things I want to really start doing is
infiltrating those subreddits like FDS.
They have a private subreddit.
Now this is where they talk about the real dating strategy, the strategy that if they
made public would get them all in a lot of deep shit.
And in order to get in, you first have to be verified as a woman on their discord server.
You also have to be a verified feminist.
I have to.
I got to imagine.
I have a feeling they probably don't like trans women do they?
Half of the mods don't.
So there was some discourse when we covered their option.
Am I going undercover?
You have to do six interviews.
I think it was in order to get into like it's this lengthy process.
You should record them all.
You should record all of them.
I'll put my sister to this record the whole process.
Yeah.
Just like make it like a deep dive highly edited video about the secret subreddit.
That's so terrible that you have to jump through these many hoops to get it.
It would be like a documentary about like how I joined the the Scientology culture something.
Yeah.
There are a lot of subreddits like that and that people recommend like, hey, I heard this subreddit is really bad, but it's private.
So I don't know how to get in and then you look it up and it's some lengthy.
The FDS one is by far the worst example.
They are really strict about who they let in.
But there are some other ones that do similar things where they require you to send like IRL photos and pictures of ID before they've been considered letting you in.
For a show like Shreddit, I feel like those would be the...
How do we know they're women?
Huh?
Those moderators.
Oh my God.
What if they're just men running a racket because they want they want pics?
For the next interview, you have to show your feet.
No!
Yeah.
But yeah, I feel like if they are so bad that they recognize the fact that they need to be private to avoid major backlash.
I feel like those would be the best subreddits to make fun of.
It feels like it's like months to do.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
You know, just thinking about it, I do imagine a lot of it is just extreme turf-y, like ranting.
A lot of it's got it.
Probably.
I know that they have a sister subreddit called r slash fds leveled up and fds leveled up.
Leveled up?
I'm so reddit.
So it's where you look into the personal life of some of the most active fds users and they post about routines they do.
And it's all dumb.
It's all dumb.
We made an episode on that.
They're really stupid.
But I do know one of the rules on the fds was like no trans people.
Oh shit.
Yeah.
That's what I said.
That's what I was saying.
It's like half and half because on the regular subreddit they don't have that rule.
You know what I mean?
So it's like this probably sister subreddit is like they are down with trans people who hate themselves, I'm guessing.
Possibly?
Well, who isn't?
Trans and hating yourself?
Who isn't down?
I was referring to the Blair White types.
The Blair White types?
Blair White?
The Blights.
Someone posted, I think it was like a Blair White version of another meme that the meme is like, hey, I saw you posting about how trans suck.
And you know, despite being trans myself, I know, right?
I totally agree with you.
You know, I'm one of the good ones, you might say.
It's like not like other girls, but a trans, a Blair White version.
Blair White is just like a grifter, right?
Like, there's no question.
Absolutely.
She is like openly said.
She's like said like, yeah, like a bunch of the other like conservative grifters that I talked to, like a bunch of them don't even believe what they say.
Like they're all, she made a video that was like, a bunch of these other people don't even believe what they say.
Yeah.
They're just grifting, they're all just grifting.
And then, and like, I don't know, she's just like that.
I think she was talking about Steven Crowder.
She made a video saying like, Steven Crowder is just drifting.
He doesn't even believe his own bullshit.
And then just never mentioned it again and nobody cared.
Nobody, nobody acknowledged it.
I remember during the time on the dark internet where Gamergate happened, Blair White, I remember her existing around then and she basically said, hey, I'm trans.
So I have the correct opinion.
Listen to me.
All this hate is good.
Dab.
It's a persuasive argument.
It was like, who the fuck are you?
Why do I care?
Yeah.
How did we get on this?
Don't remember.
Oh yeah.
FDS.
The horrible subreddit that is FDS.
And there are many spinoff sequel subreddits and their private subreddits.
I think, I think it would be funny if you went through all the rigmarole to infiltrate FDS and then write a, write a memoir about it.
I don't know.
Write a book.
No, no, you write a spy thriller.
All you do is you just review some of them on your stupid show.
That's, that's what you do.
That's the move.
I mean, you could do, you could do so many things.
You could do so many, honestly, I think like if you recorded a process of actually getting in, I think that would be interesting too.
But yeah, also, and then you have access, do you have secret access to all of this fucking bullshit?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I love it.
It becomes, it becomes a running monthly Patreon podcast.
A little mini podcast.
Hey, yes, to do it.
For this exclusive content.
Oh.
After, after we save a couple hundred posts and then just like out ourselves and then.
Well, you don't, well, or just don't out yourself and like they'll just know like that.
Yeah, there's a spy in here.
We don't know who they are.
Ooh.
They have a fight amongst themselves.
Get a backup.
They have to decide the imposter.
They'll only throw in each other out the airlock.
Ooh.
Accusing each other.
It could be fun.
Like a game.
How would, how would it be like to be sus in the FDS?
What if we, what if we both were sus in the FDS subreddit?
And we were both girls in the real world.
Commencing operation sus.
It's become like an actual spy for the government.
Yeah.
I can't wait to be sus when I grow up.
Sounds, sounds pretty exciting.
Think, think of the intrigue.
Oh my God.
One of these people is not like the other.
It's a spy.
I do James Bond is so sus.
He, I mean, yeah.
Shut up.
He did some raping, right?
I think he's done some raping.
Which binds?
Well, they're all the same.
Sean Connery specifically.
Yeah, true.
One of the, doesn't one of them like Rufi, some, some lady?
Or am I thinking of someone else?
I'll be honest.
I've only seen the most recent run of James Bond movies.
I have not seen much James Bond.
It's been a minute since I've seen the movie.
The only James Bond movies I've seen are the, um,
who was it before the current guy?
Pierce Brosnan.
Pierce, the only ones I've seen are the Pierce Brosnan ones.
I don't know why I watched them.
So tomorrow never dies.
GoldenEye.
Uh, there's another one that he did.
I guess.
Um, the only, the only thing I know about old school James Bond
was there was a movie called Octo Pussy.
And it wasn't a movie.
A character was named Octo Pussy.
Five year old Brazos.
Seven Vajanas.
Is that what that means?
Like the aerial, like the vanilla,
the Neal C.C.Riga aerial cartoon.
Yeah.
When she's got seven Vajanas.
Eight legs.
Seven West Virginia's.
The, the, the, the, the aerial, the little mermaid one.
Uh, the, the, the butler tells Prince Eric
eight legs, seven Vajanas.
Right.
Yes.
Yes. Genius.
You got it.
I got it.
Woo.
Great.
I want to complain.
I want to complain about last week
and about why the episode didn't go up
and we got content, uh, uh,
was it community guidelines struck
and we couldn't upload for a week
because I said this on Twitter
or I said it, I said it in the comments of last episode,
but I'll say it again here.
The reason why the episode couldn't,
it went up for a moment and then it was taken down
and we had to re-upload it the next week
was because we talked about a rule 34 piece of fan fiction.
It was, um, Spike the dog, fucking Jerry or Tom, Tom.
No, Tom, Tom the cat.
With that face.
With that, with that famous like unnerved Tom face.
And we, we linked to a piece,
we linked to the rule 34 link to that fan art in the description
and that link got flagged as porn
and the video was given a, a content,
a content violation strike.
And, uh, yeah, and we couldn't upload for a week.
That's the point.
And it's funny because that's not even the first time that happened.
There was another video that we,
we talked about Shad Man
and there was a Shad based link in the description
and that it didn't get us a community violation strike,
but it did get like, it got some,
it got like a warning, I think,
which is maybe the thing that happens before that.
So yeah, we've been warned for this exact same reason before,
but we didn't listen.
Oh my God.
I mean, it was a while ago.
That was, that was like a long time ago.
Yeah.
I think, you know, I, I think, um,
now that this, once the, once the strike is like gone,
I think I'm going to dispute that because like,
I don't know why I didn't do this before.
All we had to do was just take the link out.
Yeah.
And, and there's a link to dispute.
I can just be like, hey, dispute, the link's gone.
Can you please be unwarranted?
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I mean, a warning doesn't do anything.
It would probably work like that.
But, um, I actually had something set up for next,
for last week and I was really sad that didn't pan out.
Um, I'm so sorry.
Kai here is a big fan of Tom Oliver.
Why am I getting involved?
He has the exclusive merch here on Tom's Patreon.
So I messaged Tom and I was like, hey, Tom, you know,
Kai, your biggest fan,
he would fangirl for about an hour if you came on the PCP episode this Sunday.
Is this a bit?
No, it's not a bit.
And Tom said, yes, he would come on.
He was like, yes, he was like, oh, I know Kai.
Yeah, I'd love to come on and make a fangirl.
Oh, you're lying.
You're lying.
This isn't real.
This didn't happen.
Hold on.
So I am.
Okay.
Well, if that's true, then why didn't you just ask him to come on this?
I did.
He just never responded.
Okay.
I am.
In fact, I see the guy,
the first one who started giving him that money.
So I'm like, oh, no one's doing that tier.
I'm like, hmm, so I could get some cool shit.
So I started doing it.
Amazing.
Here.
I have a lot of Izumi shirts.
Check your DMs.
Leak screenshots, epic drama.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
He said he'd try to be on.
But we skipped the week.
I'm sorry.
It just, it just didn't work out.
We could have, we could have tried to tell him again.
We eat.
Yeah, we eat.
We could have, we could have just said.
I was trying to make it a surprise.
You could have just asked him.
I mean, on the other hand, on the other hand, he did say I'll try to be on this week, which
is not, which is not exactly a guarantee.
So who knows.
Yeah.
Who knows if he even would have shown up.
He did.
We'll never know.
Another timeline, perhaps.
Yeah.
And a better timeline.
That was when, that was when the timeline split.
Yes.
Not coronavirus.
It was that.
It was Tom.
It was, it was the content ID strike on the laser bot episode of the procrastinators
podcast would split the, the universes.
Um, I have one more thing I wanted to mention.
During this, this part of the show, which is yesterday, you'll never guess what I did
yesterday.
You went to Reddit.
I went.
No.
I went to a show.
I went to a live musical performance at which our friend of the show, Zen Huxtable
performed as part of a band.
And it was great.
It was based.
That's it.
That's all I have to say.
It sounded great.
I had a great time.
I was there with, uh, huh?
What, what, what, uh, kind of music was it?
I don't know.
I guess it was kind of synthy, pop, punk rock kind of, kind of music.
Uh, yeah.
Rock.
You know, rock, you know, normal music.
The band.
Human music.
Um, it sounded great.
I was there with Kazi, uh, and, uh, yeah, good, good times.
Oh, uh, so I don't know.
I just wanted to brag about that because, uh, you all, nobody else went.
Nobody in the audience went or even knew that that happened.
But I know, you know, I know all kinds of things, all kinds of secrets.
I, I sure should.
Don't.
Yeah.
True.
Speaking of music, uh, it's been talked about, but nothing has been
done yet, but we have been thinking about doing a Shreddit album where every song is
a parody of a famous song and it's just making one specific subreddit.
It was just you and me talking about this late at night.
The other one, the other member is, it doesn't know what you're talking about.
What the hell?
Kai is barely online, so everyone's aware of things but him.
Um, I, I dropped like $200 on a banner.
And Kai didn't even know it was going to be a thing.
You're not wrong.
You're like, oh, I got brand new like, like drawings of new logos and avatars and everything
just overhaul everything.
And I'm like, oh, uh, cool.
Uh, I just posted it.
It does look amazing.
Shout out to Alexi Millian.
Persona.
I am glad I have, I have fellow hosts who can just do other things.
And just get things done.
That's pretty, that's pretty, that's pretty Pog.
What is FSCF?
Uh, free speech correctional facility.
Because we free speech, free speech, because free speech.
Uh, that is a reference to the time where we were covering a subreddit and there was
a post that enraged ass boy and it enraged him to the point where he started making
credible threats.
So we had to cut the episode.
So he is forever in free speech.
Okay.
Yeah.
Like there are too many credible threats of violence.
And if I cut them all out, the episode's gone.
So like this is it.
It makes sense.
Very upsetting.
Yeah.
This looks great.
Who drew Alexi Millian?
I don't, I don't know.
I will link their Twitter.
He's amazing.
They are an inspiring manga artist.
They plan on going to Japan to enter Shonen Jump's contest.
You forgot he already, Alexi already worked on a manga.
Like he was like an editor or like he did like support drawings for like a manga.
I forgot which one.
There you go.
Pog.
He is really good at art.
It looks good.
I love works.
It's really good.
Dirt.
Shit.
Fuck.
I'm out of, I'm out of, I'm out of stuff to say.
I put a thing on a manga.
I sent my, well I didn't put it in there, but I sent the, the Clarissa thing to Shonen
Jump contest, the Tezuka thing.
That was fun.
Oh yeah, I forgot about that.
I, I know that Etra Oda laid his eyes on Clarissa Gunsmoke and I'm sure he liked it.
I was, I was tempted, I was tempted to like put in one of my old comics in there, but
I, I couldn't do it because like I felt wrong.
I didn't draw this for the thing.
I drew this like two years ago.
I can't do it.
Yeah, you'd have to do a dedicated thing, wouldn't you?
It would just feel, it would feel stupid if you, especially if you want.
It would be, it would be a little scummy.
I mean, I don't even know if it would be scummy.
I don't know.
I, I kind of, I couldn't really even think of like, why not?
Like I probably should have done it like just because, but I just didn't because it just
felt wrong.
And then I could say Etra Oda laid eyes upon something I drew, but alas, it will never
be.
Do you think the artist for the Diary of a Wimpy Kid series has ever sent his comment?
What's his name?
Like Craig something?
I thought it was Jeff Kaplan.
No, that's the Overwatch guy.
Wait, no, Craig is, um, Craig is the guy who writes the Captain Underpants.
Craig McCracken.
Oh yeah.
Um, put on Diary of a Wimpy Kid.
There is Google for this.
I still, um, I, I follow.
Oh yeah, it's Jeff Kinney.
Jeff Kinney.
Uh, for some reason I still, I follow, um, I made a tweet about some books that I used
to read as a kid.
My teacher is an alien and the guy who wrote them, Bruce Coville.
Those books were based.
Do you read them too?
Yeah, I don't know if I read all of them.
I just read them.
I think like all of them.
That's so fucking good.
I think my school's library only had the first three.
I made, um, I read, I think there's five.
Um, I read them all as a kid and I made like a little Twitter thread where I was like sort
of reminiscing about them and Bruce Coville responded.
And now I, I still see his, uh, his tweets, everyone, I followed him and I see his tweets
every once in a while.
He's a, he's a very, um, you know, he's, he's very boomer Democrat.
He's very much like, uh, you know, it's not, it's not that exciting really, but I, I
appreciate him.
Uh, he tweeted about reefer madness, the movie musical.
There's a musical reefer madness.
Oh my God.
I'm not surprised at all.
Bruce Coville says that.
Oh, he's, he's very much complaining about, uh, you know, how the, the GOP failed in
their response to COVID, which is true.
Of course, uh, uh, complaining about Tucker Carlson.
Yeah.
Good.
You know what?
Keep doing what you're doing.
You're doing a great job.
Yeah.
He's only, he's only got like five.
He's got less followers on Twitter than me, but he's also got like a publishing career.
Oh, get him on PCP.
Honestly, what if I fucking did?
What if I fucking did?
Ah.
Oh man.
Oh.
Um, shit.
Well, I mean, uh, anything, anything else?
Any other topics for discussion?
I have a swipe sign.
Oh, you don't mind?
I am a.
What's up?
So I got a model from Mage for my, uh, for my live 2D and I'm debuting that soon on August
6th and that's exciting for me.
Fascinating.
When you say a model for me.
Oh, so, uh, for V tubing, as you know, you got like a, you got the model and then you
get someone to rig it.
Sometimes you get both and I had been a wanting me to do my model cause I love her art and
I love her model cause she, she made a new model under REM.
Kaushmar.
Yeah.
Rem.
Rem Kaushmar.
Rem Eleazar.
That's your new model.
Oh, that's right.
You haven't seen it.
I've shown you it off.
I'm in love with it.
Yeah.
It looks man.
I don't pay attention.
I can tell Mage.
Okay.
I imagine that when she makes this, she has to draw everything on its own layer.
Yeah.
Right.
And then you give it to a, the rigor and then you give it to a, the rigor and then
you give it to a, the rigor and the rigor like, you know, programs it or gives it like the
logic of how it.
They pretty much animated the logic of where would it be where your face and eyes are.
Yeah.
I don't understand the rigging process.
It's confusing.
The whole, the whole rigging thing.
I like, if you've seen my VTuber, it's, it's like the base, most basic thing of all.
It's just, it opens its mouth when it hears audio and it blinks occasionally.
I, I tried to do the whole rigging thing, but the webcam just can't see my eyes properly.
I try to always be fucked up.
I tried to make and rig a very simple VTuber model and it kind of worked.
Like it pretty much did work except the one thing that I couldn't get it to do was that
it's eyes were like, it wouldn't track my eyes very well.
Apparently.
And it's pupils were like jittering.
It's pupils were like kind of like jittering and shaking all the time.
I was like, I couldn't figure out how to make it stop doing that.
If you want like eye tracking that doesn't suck, you basically have to have like an
iPhone X or newer and use the iPhone tracking.
Like it has a bunch of hardware on it that you can hook up to.
Like that's what the big VTubers use.
Like they have to use an iPhone because apparently the tech doesn't exist for less than like
thousands of dollars.
It's just, it's a lot of, it's too much.
I'm going to find a clip of me beating like Hollow Knight and you can see the punk VTube
thing, how it works.
And it's just, it works.
It's really good.
It just works.
And I can press a button to like change the sets of like frames so I can be angry.
I have to go.
It's like a little more involved, but like the barrier to entry has been significantly
lowered.
I feel like most people trying to get into VTubing are like bombarded by so much technical
and like money stuff.
That's why there's a lot of PNG VTubers, which is pretty nice entry level.
Oh, it's just they just people who like have a picture that lights up and close turns off
while they like get a model ready normally.
Normal VTubers also use that when like, like they don't have a very good rig or they're
playing like a game, right?
That's very work intensive and they don't want to have to also be like rendering their
model and stuff.
So they'll, they'll have it light up.
Yeah.
VTuber stuff is interesting.
It also gets very expensive.
That's a commission thing.
I mean, I know Mary said that he paid like thousands of dollars for his model and his
that makes sense.
I've thrown about 900 in for everything.
Yeah.
Incredible.
I mean, I can tell how work intensive it must be.
I mean, and if you're, you know, the rigging processes must be very complicated and like,
you know, it takes like a certain degree of expertise to get it working really, really
well.
So it's worth it.
I've seen how the model works.
I'm still like getting everything set up for the debut, but it's like, I'm a super excited.
It looks beautiful.
Hmm.
Based.
Oh, yeah.
Where, where can we see it?
I'll drop a link to my Twitch.
I don't have, I don't have the thing.
Based.
It's not ready yet.
If you give me like a few minutes, I can go pull up the YouTube studio.
It's still, I still have some bugs.
I'm at my teacher's working.
Drop a link to the Twitch.
Thank you.
Link your Twitch and when it's ready.
Well, yeah.
There we go.
There she is.
Hell yeah.
Yeah.
Um, well shit.
Okay.
Can we talk about how the collab meta is the best meta on YouTube to grow?
No, it's not the best.
Currently shorts are the best.
Oh, are there shorts still the best?
What are you talking about?
Shorts are crazy.
You said YouTube?
If you wear shorts, people love this is true.
What?
I don't, I genuinely don't know what any of you were talking about.
There's a new thing I've seen.
I don't know much about how good it is, but like you put hashtag shorts in your title
or somewhere and it turns into like a,
Oh, it's like Tik Tok, right?
It's like a YouTube Tik Tok.
Yeah.
Tik Tok, Tik Tok asks.
So like it's a normal upload, but it appears as though Tik Tok.
If you're on the mobile app, it, it feels pretty much it's just sort of like 15 seconds
of,
There's a couple of rules.
It has to be less than a minute long and it has to be either a one to one or taller
aspect ratio.
And you don't actually have to put hashtag shorts in it.
Like there's, they're pumping in like extremely old videos.
We're talking like 13 year old just clips that someone threw up.
They, they didn't put hashtag shorts or anything in, but it's still getting ported in.
And you can get like, it's weird.
The views you get on it, you're not, you don't get directly paid form from it,
but like the sub gain and just the mere exposure to your channel itself is actually
like, it's rather crazy.
Like if you're willing to put in the work and just make a ton of them.
It's like, that's the meta at the moment because it's new and it's still going.
Yo, that sucks.
That's cringe.
I hate that.
Just make stuff, make stuff that nobody watches.
It's more fun.
Yeah.
Woo.
That's the PCP way.
God.
I hate when they change platforms.
I hate when things are different.
Oh no, that's just one aspect of it.
That's just a new thing.
They have so many working parts.
YouTube is pretty Pog.
They got so much going on.
That's not Pog.
No, that's not Pog.
Don't call it Pog.
It's not Pog's friends.
Ben, let me ask you this.
Do you know, do you know what's going on with tags nowadays?
No.
Tags?
Look at me.
Who do you think you're talking to?
Of course I don't know what's going on with tags.
Tags are no longer important, almost at all.
It's all about description.
YouTube now pulls its metadata from the description, the first 10 seconds of the video, and the
title, way more than tags.
Basically, nobody cares about the tags anymore, especially the algorithm.
You can also detect what is in your thumbnail.
A little rudimentary, a little rudimentary.
Wait, I remember a time where people would, in the description, post a bunch of keywords
to gain the algorithm that way.
Is that now more effective than it has been?
But that can be a scream.
I'm going to scream.
There's nothing I hate more than fucking YouTube shop talk.
This is why I'm glad that Nate and Digi aren't on tricks.
This is why I'm glad that Nate and Trixie aren't here anymore, because all they would
ever talk about is YouTube shop talking, how the algorithm works, and tags.
Fuck off.
It's so boring.
This is why we're in logic called Kaiju.
Yeah.
You know what?
Maybe he was on his own.
Deal.
All right.
I'm sorry.
I had to say it.
Let's continue.
I'll suffer through it.
We've had this conversation so many times, and if anyone cares, they probably already
know.
It's fine.
I'm just fucking over it.
Don't feel too bad my eyes have already glazed over.
It's like what?
Don't feel too bad about it my eyes have already glazed over.
Hey, I think Gibb's phone just died or something.
No, I was talking over them, so I was silent.
Okay.
No, I was just going to make a joke, and now it's the timing's off.
No, no.
Say it.
No, timing.
No, who cares?
The timing doesn't matter.
All right.
You know what?
I'll sacrifice the timing.
Okay.
In the future, the way to get YouTube views is you've got to post an image, a thumbnail,
and then that's exactly whatever you'll be doing.
Oh my God.
Ass boy.
Your timing has come.
No.
So fun fact.
Finally.
I made this joke in our little private server, but there was a thumbnail, right?
And it was the last thumbnail Kai ever did because he was just done with making thumbnails
and being the editor.
So what he did is he found a one-piece Dozen porn and put it in the thumbnail itself.
Like, dude, shout out to my boy Bartolomeo Bari.
Don't link it because apparently it's fucking your shit removed.
But he draws some pog-ass porn.
Find him on Twitter.
He's cool.
But I made the-
You know I will.
I made the joke.
That was like a virgin PCP.
Links porn in description.
Gets community strike.
Chad shred it.
Puts porn directly in thumbnail.
You know, strike.
Yeah.
Yeah, true.
I mean, I don't understand it.
I don't understand it at all.
You took it off anyway, you bitch.
Yeah.
The second you said-
The second you guys posted there, you guys got a strike, I was like, all right, we need
to remove this before it eventually catches up to us.
No, they'll just-
They might get you later.
Yeah, that was how it was with the shad-based link.
They didn't strike us.
Well, they never struck.
They didn't warn us for it immediately.
It was years or a year or two years after we posted it.
All of a sudden one day we just got a like, this has been removed and you've been issued
a community guidelines warning for having porn, for posting like adult content.
They're like, oh, okay, I see.
It's like the way YouTube works is that they send out like a shockwave of like new rules
and they're just like robots like call you out for things that were fine before and
now they're not.
Yeah.
And then some people just get completely fucked in an instant.
One day, one day it'll happen and some rule change at YouTube will mean that my lectures
no longer are monetizable.
And that small trickle of passive income that is just such a treasure will disappear.
And one day, I know one day it'll happen, but I'm just bracing for the shockwave.
No, not today.
Please, not today.
Every time I log into YouTube and look at my analytics, please don't let it be today.
It hasn't come yet, so I'm happy.
I'm waiting for the day that filthy Frank loses his channel.
Oh, retroactively.
He's already lost like most of his videos.
I think they've, I don't know how his channel has been up because it's been more than three
and I gotta imagine each of those is a strike, but YouTube has like been taking them down
slowly, but surely.
Sometimes it's not a strike.
Sometimes they'll remove content, but it's not a strike.
Yeah, I mean, they did that with us.
That's the end of Ava and Galli or the end of YouTube episode got removed.
I don't remember why that one got removed, but it's not on the channel anymore.
I don't think for some reason, but it wasn't a strike.
We didn't get in trouble.
They just deleted it.
Luckily, we've got it on theprocrastinators.com where, oh, by the way, I want to say this,
people were asking for the MP3s.
We had been posting the episode MP3s in a Google Drive folder.
I'm going to stop listing the Google Drive folder because I don't want to update it anymore.
And all the MP3s are on the website.
If you go to theprocrastinators.com, we have all the episodes there, including downloadable
and MP3 form.
So from now on, if you want the MP3s, just go get them from the website.
I don't want to deal with the folder anymore.
There's no point.
There's no reason.
We have a website for sure, but we've just been too lazy to actually upload the episode.
Imagine being the person who edited most of the episodes and then just never getting
around to making an RSS feed or any of that bullshit.
Someone Zug from RFCK.
Someone from RFCK messaged me the other day, be like, Ben, did you know that the last chapter
of Slime and Punishment is just not up on webtoon?
It's up on Topastic and it's up on your website.
But I just forgot to put the last two chapters, I think, of it on webtoon.
It's where you just say fuck it.
Because I don't want to.
I mean, I don't get much traffic on those websites.
There's not really even much reason for it to be there because no one reads it there.
But I guess a few people do and someone was like, hey, why isn't it up there?
Okay.
Yeah.
I just forgot.
I just got lazy to put it there.
I'm the same with The Lord of Ghosts.
I have all of it on Gibbentake.site.
But for Topastic and webtoon, I was updating it initially and it's only the first three
chapters or sets of pages.
The champion did get featured on Topastic one time and it got some views once.
But other than that, my stuff on those comic websites are just double digit views.
It's like, ugh, what's the point?
So for the past six months, I was tasked with creating an RSS feed so we can put our show
on Spotify and I just am lazy and have not.
I am also supposed to be uploading the episodes on our website, but again, I'm lazy.
And a certain hub, a certain p-hub, I'm also supposed to be uploading there as well.
Why?
The toilet?
No.
So what had happened was...
That's base though.
It was funny because I saw a Call of Duty streamer uploading his content there.
I was like, I wonder if I apply to be a p-hub content creator and affiliate with them.
A partner.
I doubt it.
I put in the application, hi, we make fun of Reddit.
We're probably going to get mass flagged by Reddit one day and taken down.
We just want to bully Redditors and I got a response immediately approved.
Apparently the guy read my reasoning and said based.
Are you sure they don't just auto-approve everyone?
I don't see why they wouldn't let you make a porn.
No, because I'm not just uploading stuff on there.
I have fan club features.
I have like the whole nine yards.
I am a verified content partner.
Well, congratulate a lot, Eda.
Currently p-hub.
I never even made Twitch partner.
That's great.
But yes, I'm supposed to be uploading there as well and I haven't done it in like two months.
Well, I'm sure you'll get around to it.
We've been going for two hours now.
We just passed the two hour mark and I feel like we should move on to voicemails soon.
So, I don't know, anyone got anything they want to say real quick before we do that?
Or can we...
Aspoi.
You have been quiet.
Do you have anything you'd like to say?
Any shredded deep lore that you'd like to get into?
Any wisdom?
Okay.
This is like...
I got nothing.
Check this out.
The first voicemail is not a voicemail.
It is an image.
And here it is.
I like it.
It's true.
It's absolutely...
Also, I'll be honest.
I never really understood this meme.
Like, you've seen this format before, right?
I haven't.
Yeah, I think it's a joke on the Schizophrenics because I know the original is the UN busting
into a room and then a troll face hiding behind a counter going, I hate the Antichrist.
I hate the Antichrist.
So, I think it was a...
Yeah, I don't really get what the format means.
But, I mean, whatever.
I still like this.
I'm laughing.
I like the fact that I'm not having an episode, but there I am still with dual pistols ready
to shoot.
Is it supposed to be that the person behind the table is having a Schizophrenic episode
and they're being barged in by...
I think so.
Detain...
Is that what it is?
Okay.
I hate the PC.
It's the cyber pigs or the whatever, the hogs, the whatever, the squeal.
The voicemail ghost pigs up here.
Yes, the scary pigs.
Cool.
Next...
All right, next voicemail.
This one, I will put it in the chat right here.
This one is called Enlightened Skeptics Be Like.
All right.
Let's play it in three, two, one, go.
It's always equal parts funny and infuriating when people who are, say, skeptical of the
validity of trans identities express that idea by saying they don't think gender exists
as a separate concept from sex in the first place because they don't seem to realize how
much broader that statement is than what they intended.
Sex is a classification based on physical characteristics and then gender is just an
umbrella term for the social and internal implications of being ascribed one of those
classifications.
Like, that's how the words are used in academia.
So to dismiss the latter is to suggest either that you don't believe there are any such
implications from being, say, a man or a woman, which is just patently absurd, or that you
don't understand what the word agenda means and you should probably listen to some experts
on the subject themselves before dismissing it out of pocket.
Yeah.
True.
I agree.
I was thinking about this.
I was thinking about this this week as, and I thought, because I don't believe the gender
is real.
And I was thinking maybe that being the case, maybe the right thing to do, maybe the ethical
thing to do is to be, is to be a they them, no gender.
But then I was like, yeah, maybe, but I kind of just don't want to, I selfishly just don't
want to do that because it sounds hard and like it would be work.
And I would gain no material benefit by doing so.
That is the most base take.
Yes.
I wholeheartedly agree.
Oh, yeah.
My entire issue with the pronoun ish thing is that it is so much work to keep track of
who's do, who's what.
It's literally just easier.
It's just easier.
And I'm like, can I just like, like, I don't care.
I'm literally, I'm literally just not willing to put the work in.
I'm too lazy.
My pronouns are anime and Japanese colloquialism.
That is so brave.
This is awful.
This is the worst.
Why?
I'm not joking.
No.
I don't like it.
I'm cringing.
I don't think gender is real.
So when I say, so when I'm, when I'm a he, I don't think that means anything.
I really don't.
But I'm going to, it's just going to keep doing it because it's easy and I don't, and
I don't care.
Time isn't real either.
It's, it's as real as time, the concept of, it's less real.
We keep track of it though.
Time is, time is more real, I think.
It's money.
No.
It's about this.
It's about as real as money is real.
Well, yeah.
Money is real.
They're all equally like made up by humans for the convenience of living in a society.
We come up with time, money and gender.
Yes.
We come up with all these things.
That's true.
No.
No, I disagree about time.
Yeah.
Time is, time is real.
No, see, we did invent time because we invented time travel 400 years in the future and then
we went back in time to say, hey, 400 years.
We time traveled to Rome and gave them a modern day calendar and said, here, just base the
months off of your names.
And then we, and then we went back and we gave the Mayans their ziggurats and all kinds
of all kinds.
We went to the Mayans and we said, hey, you want to play an epic prank on people 200,000
of course, and they said, of course we do.
What do you take us for?
Okay.
Next.
I don't really understand what's said, but I'm annoyed now.
Why?
Why are you annoyed?
I don't know.
I'm not joking.
I can't explain.
Okay.
Next voicemail is enlightened skeptics addendum.
Uploading.
Okay.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
I also forgot to say that accepting the academic definition of gender does not preclude you
from thinking trans identities are invalid.
Like those are separate questions.
It just allows you to articulate that position in a way that is intelligible to people who
actually know the definitions of words.
So really, whether or not you treat it as a sticking point just serves as a litmus test
for whether or not you actually are trying to be informed on the subject.
All right, buddy.
Okay.
Calm down.
You all got too much time.
I mean, it's like, I don't disagree.
I mean, I don't think I'm big brain enough to know what the point he's actually trying
to get across.
But you know, I was, he's as much to do about nothing.
This is what that was.
I feel, I feel, I feel like the first voicemail was sufficient.
Now, I'm just thinking about like the way that I have to defend my existence all the
time.
It's just, it's exhausting.
So I don't like it.
Yeah.
No, I'm annoyed by the whole, by everything.
I'm, I'm sure, I'm sure it is.
You know, I mean, people, snow snowflakes, snowflakes cringe about like, oh, I'm gonna
They, they make us, they make us memorize their pronouns.
Oh, they make us use different pronouns.
And I'm like, how it's calling someone else pronouns is so easy compared to like, imagine
if you had to be like, Hey, actually, you know, I prefer they them, you know, actually
I don't, I'm not a, I'm not a boy.
Please don't call me he, him.
I don't like it.
That's not, that's sad.
Yeah.
Where you have to, you have to remember to like correct people.
I'd forget that so.
As a certain point, yeah, I just gave up sometimes.
Yeah, it sounds really, really hard and like irritating and like, I'm glad, I guess I'm
glad, I'm glad that I don't feel, I'm glad that I don't feel uncomfortable being a he,
him or whatever that, that I'm like, feel like I need to make the effort to like, I need,
I need to do something, but I need to correct this.
It's not a problem.
I guess, I guess what's annoying me about this whole just thinking about all this is
that I, like it, like I similarly find it an annoyance to change things, but not changing
them causes me pain mentally.
So I'm like, okay, well now my whole life, like being trans and transitioning is so fucking
like time intensive and stressful in and of itself, just all of the stuff you need to
do.
Yeah.
Or like, you know, it's not like the same for everyone, but the stuff you feel like you
need to do all the stuff that would make you feel better.
It's a whole lot of extra stuff you have to take care of now.
I would prefer to just be comfortable with how I was before.
It's so much easier and I just, it's annoying.
I, I of course, as a cis person have no room to talk on anything, but I have a lot of respect
for trans people because it, I'd imagine the amount of like work and mental stress it is
just to change everything like that.
No, I mean, of course it's for a good cause to feel more comfortable in your skin, but
I just respect the amount of dedication and hard work it takes to get to a point where
you're happy.
It just really annoys me when there's like, you know, the whole like, oh, you're pretending.
Like if I really was pretending, why would I put myself through all this?
Hard work and I'm lazy.
Yeah, I want to do it.
Uh, I mean, I mean, yeah, exactly, uh, uh, it's the, I don't know, since, since I don't,
since I, since I understand that it is all a social construction.
I'm like, well, you can't ever, everyone's pretending.
Every, every gender is just a game of make believe.
That's where I'm like, I'll just, I just, I just fucking, I'll make myself a girl
out long hair, we fine.
Where would I want to fucking have stuffed animals if I want to be shit?
Fuck you.
That's my standpoint.
That's the.
Are we ready to go to the next one?
Okay.
Next one is call.
Next one is Janess.
Three, two, one, go.
The earlier PCP episodes taught me how to become a productive artist.
How the later PCP episodes, especially the last 20 or so, taught me how to be a
more patient.
I mean, I'm glad you're getting something out of it.
I don't, I would pause it that maybe roast it, maybe it's.
Oh, I guess that is a roast is a roast.
I guess that, I guess that is, or I didn't even catch it, but it's, it's a bit of a
roast.
10 out of 10.
I don't know.
I don't know if that's the intention though.
Well, what does, what does patient artist mean though?
Like, like being patient, like it would be a roast if they said the newer ones, you
know, they make me teach me how to be patient, like implying that we do things too
slow or whatever, but they're talking about their own artistic endeavors.
So I don't know.
That's what I took it as.
That means.
Um, it.
I don't know.
I honestly, if I don't know how we're making you more patient, I would, if you're
becoming more patient, I would pause it that maybe, maybe it's coming from inside
yourself and it has nothing to do with us.
Uh, uh, no, uh, take credit.
Always take credit even, even when not deserved.
You're right.
When someone asks you, are you even when it's bad?
Ever.
First thing anyone wants to know is who is responsible for this?
Never take responsibility.
Uh, why is it?
Simsie says God tier starter voicemail and CC says no.
Why?
There is this, this, this episode is in its recording phase and there is already an
argument in the comments.
I don't, I don't know what, I don't know why they're arguing.
The next one is called question about Jojo's bizarre adventure.
Three, two, one, go.
Is Jojo good?
Yes.
Jojo is one.
Sure, Jojo.
No, I've only seen the only good.
So that's the only one I can really.
Okay.
I didn't even finish it.
I watched like half of it.
Oh, it was good.
I liked it.
That's good.
Uh, Jojo is weird because it's the only, it's one of the only series that I could
think of where they make the German Nazi party explicitly, the Nazi party, the good
guys and nobody gave a shit.
The anime came out in 2014 for part two and everyone was just like, oh, the Nazis
are the good guys.
They are the heroes in this show.
Oh, babe, I don't understand.
You were fighting, it's the Nazis in the Undead Vampires.
Well, naturally we're with the Nazis.
Got it.
Oh, I think Simsie and CeCe are arguing about whether Jojo is good.
I think that's what they're.
Oh, it started.
They're having their own text based podcast in tandem with this one.
Only there were only we are privy to if only, man, someone should invent the text
based part.
It's just like, it's just like one of those old school video games where you
type in a walk to the door and then it says you walk to the door.
The next point is the type of listen to podcast.
You listen to the podcast.
And it starts you hear bad Jojo and then you type done at the end and that's the
end. The next voicemail is called Mohammed three, two, one, go.
Mohane.
Mohane and the Hades.
That was amazing.
I'm blown away.
Next voicemail is called Violet Neon.
He they minute 20.
Jesus.
What did we say about long voicemails?
Three, two, one, go.
Kill the code to comrades given saint.
Sorry if this is a bit of a ramble, but I run the game DevCorp in Wellington
and I just thought for a couple of quick tips.
Number one, cops are pretty easy to implement into a
pre-consisting limited liability structure.
Most of the time it just involves updating your company's constitution to align
with a company's act regulation.
I translate and how your nominal share value I would translate if this motherfucker
wasn't speaking at an average volume of negative 40 fucking decibels.
Dude, are you kidding me with this?
You're going to put all this effort into just this crazy long whatever the fuck
you're doing and then I can't even hear you because you're like you're lower
than like my room noise.
What in the hell are you doing?
Is he is he is he responding to something that I genuinely don't know
a cop or finding one to participate in?
Well, who cares about that?
Wait, give is called a piece so she can listen to it.
I don't I don't know.
We're we're moving on.
We give now we're moving on.
We're moving on.
No, no.
Next one is called.
Next one is called PCP bad comments.
Oh, we can't do this one without give.
Give your back.
We stop. We stop listening because it was a bad was it good?
Well, it was about forming a co-op.
I don't know whether he was talking about like us as comic creators
or a podcast or something.
It sounded like it sounded like he was talking about programming stuff.
Oh, well, then I completely have no idea.
I could have listened to the voicemail in all this time, but I'm not sorry
that I get louder next time.
I couldn't fucking hear it.
Piece of shit.
I don't know.
You got it together.
Audio levels between negative twelve and negative six.
Don't at me.
It was also quiet.
It had it had that as an issue as well.
Next one is called PCP bad comments.
A word show number two hundred sixty nine.
Three nice three, two, one, go.
Hello, I'm the comment critic.
I find bad comments and then shove them in your face.
And there weren't any particularly bad comments on episode two hundred sixty
nine of the PCP.
Sure, there was some assorted bad advice and work life balance and low
effort non-statements and lamenting to the void about departed PCP members.
But nothing with that oomph.
Nothing that makes you feel, wow, that was a shitty comment.
So I'll just be using this opportunity to give a lifetime achievement award.
Put your hands together for S.H.C.W.
No, Nate, no, watch.
See you next week.
Classic. Well, you've earned it.
Well deserves well deserves.
I would be really curious on what this guy picked as the worst comment
for the Merle logic episode.
He wasn't doing them back then.
So he he only he started doing this maybe like a month ago.
So yeah, although I think he might work backwards.
I'd be curious about that, too.
If you if you listen in, please get the worst comment on that video.
I heard Merle logic replied to every single comment religiously.
Yes, he did. He did.
Yeah, he was amazing.
He's a what goes on in that man's mind is is is a mystery.
Next voicemail is called unauthorized made tapes.
Number four, M.A.Y.D.E.
tapes. Number four, three, two, one, go.
I always grab my stick when an earthquake.
And my hand automatically strokes.
I feel as if I have sex with the earth.
The fear takes away.
This is crazy.
Wow. Chad Chad.
She is relatable.
No, no, no, he looks he goes to his group of friends and his guys.
Guess what goes?
I just had sex with the earth.
See you later, virgins.
This is this is this is I wish my hope.
I dig my dick gets big as the Eiffel Tower
so I can fuck the world for seventy two hours, right?
Isn't that a Kanye?
I know it's a lyric.
I don't know if it's like it might not be Kanye.
I don't it might not be Kanye, but it's someone.
It's definitely said by a person.
Hold on, remember, I like the idea that during an earthquake,
usually you have to try and like, oh, I've got to be safe.
Nah, I'm going to wrap my hand around my dick.
So the weather, the weather, the weather told me not to crumble below me.
Yeah, around me.
The building collapses.
Still go shredded research department has reached out to us
and it's informed us it is a Kendrick Lamar freestyle.
OK, Kendrick Lamar.
All right, I am of ignorance.
Next voicemail is unauthorized, made tapes number five, three, two, one, go.
I went to take a piss while still wearing my microphone.
And the whole conference heard me call the year and all
a thirsty boy.
Oh, that was god to you.
R. Kelly, I hope the microphone also had that effect on it.
Yeah, it was auto tuned in.
He just does a conference like their business meeting.
R. Kelly be like, I'm trying.
I'm trying to use gender neutral pronouns when I don't know.
Yes, the whole conference heard them thirsty, boy.
I can't do it. I can't figure it out.
R. Kelly be like.
OK, next one is unauthorized, made tapes number six.
Let's let's finish them off.
Three, two, one, go.
Whoopie, the scoop.
Scoop, they do.
Whoop, they scoop, they do.
Face and gamer peeled.
I have learned a lot.
That was definitely the most informative of that was like Joe Joe.
Part two was the best part.
That was the best trilogy ever made by God.
I appreciate it.
Earthquake pissing neck.
The whoop.
Next one is called.
It's another gen S three, two, one, go.
If you want to understand capitalism and socialism in a more
easy to understand way, then I recommend the YouTube channel.
Second thought, I recently discovered him and he explained
current events in a easily accessible mainstream way, not the academic jogging.
So I recommend that you watch him sometime.
Second thought.
Oh, he's big. He's a million.
He's a million sub boy.
There are a million sub person.
They need the shout out or such a big penis.
I don't know.
I don't know. I'd never heard of him.
OK, consider second thought plugged, recommended.
Next one is, yes, it's true.
Next one is called.
Here we go.
How to discord bot three, two, one, go.
So discord bot is sort of like a Minecraft server.
It's an actual program you have to have running on a machine somewhere.
So you can run it on your own machine or you can get like the free cheap.
Oh, AWS, I don't remember why we're talking about discord or something like that.
But it just has to run on some machine that has internet access.
OK, I did vaguely remember the reason the making the bot was difficult
was because it only works when my computer is on, otherwise I need a server.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
To be running it.
I had, yeah, I ran into that issue as well when I when I was still thinking
that I could I could run endless war, I could build it all myself well now.
Oh, no, that was because when it during endless war,
I was running bots that were the mega slimes.
Like every time someone made a mega slime, I would make a new bot
that was a mega slime and it would be like an NPC bot
that was running in a certain server.
But they would disappear when my computer was offline
because I had to keep my computer running or the bots would stop running.
And it was a big that's why I stopped doing that is because, well,
I don't want to fucking keep my computer running
and I don't want to fucking pay for server space for these totally inert bots.
And also slime inflation is happening and millions of slime are no longer a lot of slut.
So, you know, the issue solved by the way,
if any Chad listener wants to send a voicemail
or comment on how to create an RSSV, too lazy to look it up.
Bruh, it would be appreciated.
I don't understand RSS.
I've been for years, like websites have like an RSS button.
It's like, oh, yes, subscribe to our RSS feed.
And I I have no I mean, do people still use it?
I use RSS feeds.
It is only used, I think, by the majority of people to get their show
on Spotify and iTunes because that is the only requirement to get on them
to get on their platforms is what is an RSS feed?
Well, shit, we're on iTunes.
Really stupid system is what it is on iTunes.
So we must have an RSS.
No, well, iTunes changed that before.
It was you had to sign up and that was it.
Now you have to have an RSS feed.
RSS feed is just is just like a word document that it pulls updates from.
And then it's just different programs will just read that document
and then be able to port in episodes of stuff.
It's that's all it is.
So you know how to you know what they are.
I assume you know how to make one.
Why don't we have one?
Kai had this conversation many, many times.
I am even lazier than you.
We'll try to ever be on Spotify.
Find out never.
No, probably not.
OK, next next voicemail.
I already put it there.
It's called its PCP bad comment award show number 270.
And by the way, 269 was the Hollow Knight and Lord of Ghost Kickstarter
episode 270 was Vax Millions.
I'm pretty sure it was the Vax Millions.
Yes, episode. So here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
Kramer, are you the one who wrote this comment?
What comment, Jerry?
What are you talking about?
This comment on my podcast, it's terrible.
It's the worst comment on this episode.
Well, what's to say?
Give funding in an even more than usual this episode.
The Patreon can't run dry fast enough.
Let the dog die.
Can't you hear its pain?
No, Jerry, why would I say something like that?
I don't know, Kramer.
Why did you threaten to lynch an audience member at the Laugh Factory?
Oh, come on, Jerry.
That was a long time ago.
Uh huh.
It's like I'm there watching the episode.
You know, I mean, that's a that's a mean comment,
but I wouldn't say it's a bad comment.
I mean, I guess it's bad because it's you agree with it.
I do. I mean, I, you know, he's he makes a strong argument.
But you know what I mean, there's different.
It's it's it's not it's not like a stupid comment
that is like pointless or annoying.
Like, I don't obviously don't like it
because it expresses an opinion contrary to my own.
But in terms of like it does exactly what it was trying to do.
So I don't know if I would call that a bad comment per se.
Well, the argument is silly, isn't it?
Like they don't like the show anymore.
And so we should delete it.
That's always been the stupid like he.
Why would we stop it if we don't mind continuing?
Well, I think it's a little more than that
because he doesn't say stop doing the show.
He says that he hopes that our Patreon runs dry.
He he wishes ill upon us.
He hopes the show loses all its support and is destroyed.
And as someone who wishes ill on my enemies,
I I can understand where he's coming from.
I have to respect it.
I have no choice.
But fair, I understand the selection.
Um, next voicemail.
I haven't put it in the here.
Here we go. There it is.
It is called flanged silicone three, two, one go.
Does anyone else think that the flanged
Ben icon on Twitter looks kind of like a butt plug?
I think about it every time I see it.
I have a friend who wants to know where to get
a flanged Ben brand of butt plug and maybe some keto lubricant.
That's really hard to say.
There you go.
I don't. There you go, Aspoye.
There's a good thumbnail.
I've almost done with it.
I can't start over now.
Fortunately, by the time we listen to this,
I have already changed it.
I'm no longer flanged Ben on Twitter.
Just in time.
I think I think this is the point
when you know that it's run its course.
So I did it.
OK, next voicemail is called rest in podcast three, two, one go.
PC poopers, it's been a week and there's no soda.
Yep, I know it's 1 a.m.
And there's no episode PC poopers.
Where is it?
I've already explained, but your confusion is.
Hopefully now, you know, just just just disappointment.
I mean, where is the episode?
Why? I explain this on Twitter.
You couldn't say.
If you if you don't know what's going on with the thing,
you just got to check one of check my Twitter alpha.
And that's that's my advice.
But now, you know, OK, sorry to cause you such grief.
Next voicemail is called tarbuck transom,
the fan pilled hot pocket three, two, one go.
So at Archway six, a.k.a.
our apartment, the air conditioner is really loud.
Just constantly remind the surfs that they live
in a state of perpetual wealth extraction.
And that means that if I want to record anything downstairs,
I have to turn it off.
Well, I had forgotten to turn it back on when I went upstairs
to do computer things for the next 12 to 14 hours.
And I noticed that getting a little warm.
So I switched on the new nine inch fan.
I illicitly acquired hashtag shop.
And it was surprisingly effective at keeping me cool to the point
where I didn't even notice until the following morning
that I didn't turn the air con back on.
It costs less to operate and it works way better than I thought it would.
Kind of makes it seem like spending a bunch of money and energy
to cool the entire air mass is a little bit wasteful.
What do you guys think?
Don't don't tell me that a fan works as well as an air conditioner.
I keep my house at 64 degrees, sir.
A fan is not going to do it.
No, no, no, no.
If you're really hot and you need to cool off,
the best thing to do is to put your face near a toilet and flush it
so that the cool air blows on you.
That's a reference to my shredding episode.
That was one of the posts.
You just need to go to your local amusement park,
stick your head in the toilet and flush.
It works. Go to the.
It's just refreshing.
I will say, though, there is a fan.
It's at Best Buy and I have been thinking of grabbing one myself.
You take your own implication,
but it doesn't have a spinning spamblade.
What it does is it has a it has a hole in the back,
oval hole that vacuums in air and then hits it with a freon coil
and then shoots it out the other side.
So it's technically a fan,
but it's like a glorified air conditioning and it's cheaper than an air
conditioner and it's sometimes better because you could just point it at you
when you're really hot and it's like, well, the whole room's not cool,
but I feel better.
It sounds pretty.
It sounds pretty poggers.
Yeah, if it were, it just sounds like a many air conditioner.
Yeah, kind of just.
Isn't that what an air conditioner is?
It's just an air conditioner.
It's just called a fan because it's shaped like a fan.
You would an air conditioner has to have somewhere for like an air conditioner.
Yeah, hold on.
I'll post a picture of what I'm talking about.
They are very expensive.
The OK, Dyson Humid.
No, wait, does that mean it's not cost effective then?
Wait, yeah.
Is it more expensive than an air conditioner?
Jesus, holy shit.
Where? Where? Where does the hot air go?
That is an air conditioner.
Where does the hot air go?
I don't know how it works.
There's no physical fan.
I think it is.
Is it literally just a is it literally?
I mean, I mean, I've wait.
I've seen these like air like holes.
I've seen these like holes that blow air without blades.
I know these are. Oh, wait, no, these suck.
Yeah, these suck.
These are. I think this is a different product than fans for the money.
I've never used one of these.
I think this is specifically for like.
They're louder.
They're louder than rotary fans.
They take more electricity and they don't significantly increase the cooling.
It's just more. It's just more worse.
It's just eight hundred dollars.
Uh, it looks funny.
It looks. But that's it.
It does look fancy.
The next OK.
The next voicemail.
I already posted it there above the the Dyson link.
It's called. Well, it comes with this link to.
GitHub audacity and its air actions we propose to take on the PR number
eight, three, five, three, five.
Subsequences of it's like a technical issue about audacity, whatever.
OK, voicemail. Here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
Remember when the developers for audacity had the audacity
to announce a telemetry update?
Well, there was such an overwhelming backlash to the telemetry update
that they responded, fine, guys, no telemetry.
Jesus, shut up.
We did it.
Bling works.
Bash the bash.
This has been tarmac transom.
You are beacon of truth in the dark.
I don't know what's a limit.
OK, so basically I got the rundown.
I don't have to use. I don't have to use.
So audacity released an update
where they said they will do three things and you have to agree
to these three things to continue to use audacity's newest version.
First of all, anything you recorded will get will get stored as data
and possibly be sent to law enforcement if requested.
OK, number two, they reserve the right to listen to any data
that you record using audacity.
Oh, this is that audacity spying on you thing
that oblivion false that is not real.
Well, it's in their terms of service.
So, yeah.
And the third most important thing that pissed a lot of people off
was it said that, oh, we can also sell any data we keep.
So any date.
Yeah, so they could sell your recordings without your permission
if you use the newest version of audacity,
at least in their terms of service, who knows if they'd actually do it?
Oh, OK.
Should surely data means like analytics about what you record,
not literal recordings of your voice.
I mean, that's a fun thing about these.
No, that's what that's what oblivion false said.
It's like it's not recording you and sending the data.
Some if that would be a lot of data, it's just it's recording like.
Yeah, when you use audacity files are fucking gigantic.
Yeah, it can't it can't be sending your like.
Yeah, your whole audacity file.
OK, I honestly, I don't really care about this.
Next voicemail is is called my anti gay agenda.
Only straight people can know.
Oh, I hope three, two, one, go.
Oh, I can't make a really interesting point.
You on? Oh, shit.
You know, did you guys agree?
Yeah, they they made a really persuasive argument
back to my facts and data can't can't can't agree more.
This this this guy should this guy should to have a fucking podcast.
This guy should be on this guy.
The voice is very deep and smooth.
It sounds like it sounds like a ethnic Markiplier deep and smooth.
That's right. Deep and smooth. 100% deep.
Oh, OK.
Why did you say it like that so many times?
And next voicemail next voicemail is.
Wait, oh my god, there's another.
All right, well, here's the here's the fucking link.
And here's a link to.
I don't think this I don't think the whole link works.
I think they get they posted a broken link.
I assume you just add an end to the end of that link.
What?
Court court probation.
Maybe.
No, it's court probation.
Court probation.
It's a Colorado judicial branch.
Well, who cares?
Yeah, I don't know.
OK, let's listen to the voicemail.
Three, two, one, go.
OK, Ben, I will forgive you for not joining the Anamorphine
Time Discord because, you know, you didn't ask me to send you
an invite in March when I asked you if you wanted to join it.
I'll forgive them. Fuck it. We're done. We're past it.
Fuck you.
Uh huh.
Did you all hear about Mark Redwine?
No.
This dude killed his son in 2012 or something
and was just convicted and he killed his son
because his son found pictures of him in a red bra
eating shit out of a diaper.
And I kind of relate to that like rage.
Because, I mean, what?
This is this is funny because I know the person who sent this.
I recognize his voice.
It's fucking pie whip.
He didn't know we were going to be on, but the biggest meme of Shredda
is that we make fun of the ABDL community.
I see. Yes.
Yeah.
No, I haven't heard about this Mark Redwine.
He says very relatable fellow.
Obviously. Listen, listen, listen.
I didn't know if he meant I relate to the son or the dad.
Listen, it's OK.
He looks like his files got sealed or something because it's OK.
He just had a heater game and he just had a heated gamer moment.
We all have them.
Yeah.
Eating shit.
Was it the son's shit?
Was the son like he would have been fine with it?
But he's like, wait, that was my shit.
Dad.
That's what you've been doing with my shit all these years.
I don't want to I don't want to think about this one anymore.
OK.
Next voicemail is called.
What is it called?
It is called Read One Piece.
Please, Ben, three, two, one, go.
OK, guys, I need help.
I need you to choose one for me.
Berserk or Homestuck?
Homestuck. Choose one.
Sorry. I read.
I only know Berserk.
Sorry. It's my default.
I hate to do it, but Homestuck is more is more important to me.
I see.
I wanted to have to get into Homestuck,
but then somebody told me not to because the third arc
adds a self insert character or something like that.
And it just becomes bad.
So stupid.
That's literally the dumbest.
What that doesn't even mean.
I mean, I was like, oh, my God.
Who?
Whoever? Who?
There's plenty of things to complain about with Homestuck.
Whoever told you that doesn't know what they're talking about.
That doesn't make any sense.
Oh, dude, do you know that Berserk had like a girl in it?
You shouldn't read that one.
It sucks.
The third arc added a self insert character.
Don't remember which member it was,
but it was one of the pro-anon people that told me that.
Whoever told you that can't fucking read.
They can't read.
That doesn't make any sense.
They must have been fucking with you.
I don't know what I haven't read it because they said that.
Oh, my God.
Imagine listening to anyone.
That's so that's literally that's literally
the like the dumbest Homestuck take I've ever heard.
Yeah, the author, the author does appear in the story
occasionally to give like a recap and it's like a total like non event
and it doesn't impact anything.
Imagine what a weirdo you did.
Just it's just weird.
It's just like a weird thing to not like about it.
It has like no bearing at all.
Oh, my God.
Obnoxious. That's obnoxious.
It's it's hard to compare the two to say like choose one.
I don't know how I could choose between them.
It's easy Homestuck.
I like it better.
I like them so much, both.
I guess.
Berserk is unfinished.
I haven't read either.
The Homestuck guy is
is the winner because he is still alive.
Berserk is unfinished versus Homestuck did finish.
But the ending was bad.
So shit, like yeah, the ending was bad
and the epilogue was exhaustingly terrible.
Yeah.
Berserk is also only good.
Well, you know, Homestuck has risk.
True, that's that's a that's a big point.
That's at least real here.
Berserk is only good during the Golden Age arc.
It drops off hard for after that.
Yeah, I mean, that's it.
I being a big question mark
in everyone's head, like, oh, what's going to happen with Griffith?
What's going to happen with this whole thing?
You know what? It's it's fun.
Just assume that those two, they're both awake.
They're they're just going to they're just like she has her memories.
They're just going to, you know, do their own thing.
Just just that's where the that's where the story ends.
I it's it's great.
Leave it.
I can't choose just one.
I just can't do it.
The Golden Age arc is so sad.
It's a good it's really good.
Golden Age arc is really good.
I really like the whole Kushan arc ending with the giant
like demon tree thing so fucking.
So fucking the in the imagery that it shows
just conjures up so many things.
I mean, it's it's super influential for a reason.
And it's just
it can't do it.
It's it's yeah, won't do it.
It's not a fair. It's not a fair, obviously.
But I mean, this is the point.
The point of this question is to make us discuss and discuss we have.
Well, this I mean, if I really wanted to get down to it,
I wanted I would want to like go on it for like an hour and I can't.
I can't draw that out for just one voice now.
Hold on. I do have a no.
The moral of the story is yeah.
So about the title, Ben, why haven't you read one piece?
What's going on, buddy?
Yes, I'm just one piece game.
I'm just letting it I'm just letting it build up.
I'm just letting it build up until
and I'm just binge it at some point.
I said this on the over.
I said this on the stream and I'm not trying to step in any toes
because if Nate is going to do pot, podi cast,
then that's fine.
But like if Nate doesn't intend to continue the podi cast,
I would consider taking it over base, base, base.
That's only that's only if that's only if his intention is not to to do it.
If he intends if he's going to keep doing it, then then then, sure.
So now the offer is on the table.
Next voicemail is
it's my IQ Mima Q A
would you to be to OK,
wait, yeah. OK. Three two one go.
God, that new Nate video was ass.
I didn't watch it.
It was very confusing.
To be to be honest, his name made a video.
He did.
To be honest, I didn't watch it because I heard people talking about it.
And I got the impression that I might find it annoying.
And I didn't want to watch a Nate video that would make me annoyed.
So I was just kind of like, OK, I think I think I get what it's about
from what people are saying about it.
I'll just I'll just let it be.
It was just it was a it was sort of like a.
A series of video game industry opinions about how games are
the the hype culture, you know, expectations for developers,
how games should be good or worse or.
But they weren't like cohesively linked together.
They were just sort of one after the other.
But it had a a veneer of a cohesion in the the title nickel acronym,
which is so confusing because it's sort of like a formula,
a mathematical formula that is supposed is supposedly to link
all of these things together in a single term that you can use.
But it has no like conceivable use.
I don't know how you would even use it in a sentence.
And it's hard to even explain right now.
I saw the equation and it seemed like the only I mean, the equation is just.
Anything that like asymptotically approaches a limit,
which is like a very normal thing for a for an equation to do.
I don't I don't I don't like Nate.
But OK, I watched a video because our based editor for Shredda is no need.
And he's also Nate's editor.
And every time I watch a Nate video, I'm like, God, I'm glad we still no need.
He has talent.
So wait, this entire thing, he just explains like the 80 percent rule.
That's what I say.
It's something that 80 percent of where you need it to be.
It's good enough.
Like that's that's that's the that's just parts of it are about that.
Other parts are completely not about that, but they're still under
the umbrella of that term, which has no bearing on the thing he's talking about.
He just has a lot takes 10 minutes to explain just that.
Jesus Christ, it's an hour long video.
Well, it's I think I think he said that
people told him it could be shorter.
And he agreed.
Yeah, yeah, I mean, at the end, yeah, at the end, he does admit
that he it was it was like a difficult script to write because he was trying
to think of a way for all of these things to connect.
But I feel like the problem was they inherently do not connect.
They are different topics that maybe you should should just make a different video.
They should have been we Aguas.
I really think that a good 10 minute video
is better than like like six good 10 minute videos is better
than like a bad, weird hour long video like.
You know, in theory, in theory, I guess I guess so.
Well, I mean, I don't know how many hours of content
is the Christine Chan documentary, and would those be better split up as well?
You mean you mean the gene?
You mean the Geno Samuel documentary?
I think so.
The one where there's like 50 something.
But those are those serve a different purpose.
Those are I mean, there's so fucking many of those.
I fucking hate that guy, by the way.
I hate every fucking historian.
They all suck.
They all they all misgender her.
They're all a bunch of like dipshits and they all like mutualese people.
People in my comment section, I see comments that are like,
you shouldn't call Chris a she because she's just a fake trans.
And my evidence is Geno Samuel made a video explaining
about why Chris is a fake trans.
So, you know, you're actually just hurting women
when you use those pronouns, Ben, fuck you.
So the fuck horrible, horrible community full of horrible people.
But it is what it is by criticism of them.
Is they is they always tend to side with the trolls like, oh, yeah.
So this troll did something really funny or this troll got into it.
And it's like, why are you making the troll seem like the good guy?
Wouldn't this be better content has like the depressing story
of the Internet taking advantage?
To be honest, I have never actually I have never actually watched the Geno Samuel.
I have only watched like what I've heard.
I don't like of all the like of a single part just because.
Ben Ben's lecture is all the Saundra content I have seen.
I think I think I read the comic.
I actually like it's fun.
It's fun and silly parts of it are fun and silly.
It is very hard to understand at times.
Yeah, that's the fun part.
Yeah, like what in the fuck are they trying to get across here?
It's great.
I mean, when when you know that the whole like
the the Jerkop Tastropai is just an extended reference to an episode of Excel Saga,
then you kind of are like, oh, I get it.
It is kind of funny in a way.
But you would never know that unless unless someone told you.
Um, yeah, um, but I agree.
It is it is kind of funny.
I've heard I've heard there's fun if you like crossover episodes on TV.
I mean, I do.
Like what's on like if you were a big fan of the Jimmy Timmy power hour,
I've heard you will like Saundra to just because of the idea of all these characters.
I don't I don't agree with that.
I think that's that's true of tales gets trolled.
But Sonich Sonichu is not a conventionally good story.
It's sad, but true.
Anyway, next voicemail is wait, fuck, I didn't I didn't put it next voicemail is message for Ben.
Wait, I missed one, but it's OK.
This one is message for Ben.
No, no, let's OK.
Play the one before this, the three, four, five, nine.
This one is called It's All Dust.
OK, three, two, one, go.
And the new major deal so made I remember when I could talk to people
in the pod, the discord of my favorite manga, One Piece.
Yeah, now it's just a desolate wasteland.
They're dying like Dennis Frogman.
My people are dying coming in now was was this.
Was this like during the lockdown, like the podicast lock lock on the 19th?
Let me let me just search the fire emoji in the one piece for really quick.
OK, yeah, please.
Oh, my God, the rebelling again.
Oh, my God, it's still going.
Oh, no.
So is it going to get locked down again?
Is that was that who started this?
Why is it happening?
It's so unfortunate because I've heard that the people
this court, it was so busy.
It was so it was I've heard that the I've heard that the people.
I mean, you should just you should just kick the spammers out.
You should just kick out people that spam there are no mods.
Well, yeah, so the rebellion happened on the fifth of this month.
So 20 days ago.
Oh, OK, so that was that was well before.
Yeah, I wonder why.
OK, well, all right.
Next voicemail is called Message for Ben three, two, one, go.
I don't speak Morse code.
I don't know how to read Morse code.
And I feel like it would take a long time for me to translate it.
So viewer, fuck you, fuck you.
It's assumed it said to read one piece viewer.
I bet it's like a I bet it's like a slur.
It would be it would be kind of funny in a shitty way if it was like a slur.
But like, I'm just going to be like viewer, figure out what it means on your own.
And then at home, you work it out and it's the n word or whatever.
And you go, oh, they said it. Oh, they slipped one through.
Well, I mean, wouldn't you know by like the third letter, you're like, OK, OK.
Well, yeah, I mean, by then it's too late.
I don't know.
It's I mean, it can't be more than like a single word, right?
There's just not that many letters. I bet I mean, I don't know.
Commenters, let us know if you translate it.
Let us know what it says.
Give me two words.
So, oh, I heard it.
I heard there was a gap.
So I don't know that's just going too quick.
I don't know how people listen to that and like hold on.
Understand when the when the when the letters are finished.
I don't want to translate it right now.
But it's big break.
No, no brain.
We're a no brain podcast.
Next voice. I don't care.
Next voicemail is called simp off three, two, one, go.
What's worse, a jigger or an eight head?
It says fuck. I would say a jigger.
Oh, I would say that's where, you know, what is what is what?
A ye a ye a yeeg head.
I would say you can find. Oh, oh.
You it doesn't exist.
Like it's a terrible has the channel name, but the net her and Riley break up.
Well, the.
Well, I mean, the they are the group is split up.
The channel is still called that.
So technically, Yeeg Studio is continuing, but it's basically just.
All I mean, it's all the stuff that she said the channel is going to do.
I mean, they haven't said this,
but it's pretty obvious that it's all canceled.
It's just it's just a.
Even if you're talking about anime again, I feel I feel like the channel
is just the same as it was.
You're like, oh, it's all changing and stuff.
I'm like, not really.
It seems the same because because it's because she just let
she just let Riley run the whole thing and tell her what to do.
And he told is terrible marketing.
And he told her and he told her, do this, make the channel this.
And she said, OK, and then and then flipped out at me for it.
When I told her, like, this is stupid, you're ruining the channel.
Rage quit the PCP over it.
LaMau get fucked.
And and and now it's just like, oh, yeah,
lol, none of that's happening.
It was all a stupid idea.
I'll just make I'll just make anime videos where I summarize a Wikipedia
article and get like 3,000 views.
Do you think Trixie is going to rebrand soon since, you know,
the split happened? Yes.
Hard to say. I could maybe, maybe not.
I don't know.
They have a very long track record of constantly rebranding.
That's true. That's true.
It'll be real. It'll be really funny this time, though.
Yeah, it'll be a more shameful one.
I think so.
Just considering the.
Yeah. Yeah.
A few, a few too many torches have been applied to a few too many bridges.
So so are we in it?
Yeah. So are we in agreement that that Yig heads are worse than I am?
I would say.
Kids.
I suppose so.
I don't I don't interact with either.
People who are interested in specifically the Yig studios,
Riley, Void, Gazer's content, then yes, those are worse.
Yeah.
Nate heads are just sort of normal anime losers.
Nate heads are Nate heads are very.
I mean, Nate heads kind of.
I shouldn't say those are. That's no some.
OK, they're not all like this, but a lot of them are losers.
A lot of them are like weird, like what's the word?
Like like unsocialized.
They're just mean.
I think a lot of them are no, genuinely, I think a lot of them are
unsocialized weirdos who legitimately like need
like a father figure or something.
And like they've like they think Nate is like they've read him
as like a like a like a model of masculinity, which is like very, I don't know.
Not to say he's entirely unmasking or anything, but like, I don't know.
I think I think I genuinely get the feeling that some of these weirdos
really like take him as like a role.
Yeah, I I find that.
And I find that I was going to say, you know, a lot of times
because he has this whole thing is he has the bravado of best guy ever.
You know, he has the confidence.
He says it without holding back.
That's that's the message.
Yeah. Yeah. But yeah.
And that gets people like, oh, my God, I wish I was more confident
can do that. And they start seeing it as a role model.
I've seen it happen to like a lot of like secular online communities.
It's just it's just it's just that like it's weird because Nate's not here.
He doesn't make like self improvement content.
And yet people, some people, it seems like they sort of.
Imagine that like his content is meant to improve them.
Like he is some like he is presenting some sort of model to aspire to like.
And like he that's just not what he's doing.
I don't know. I don't know.
It could be what could be a sort of thing like, oh, my God,
somebody that's into anime is actually cool.
Maybe I could be.
I guess. I mean, I guess so.
Sure. Whatever.
OK, next voicemail is is called
I am sans undertale.
Here, let me put it in the chat.
OK, three, two, one, go.
I am sans undertale.
It's true.
You see, I don't own a copy of undertale.
Therefore, I am without I understand.
Impact of logic.
Does does the sands have a signature laugh?
In the Patrick Star laugh.
Yeah, yeah, it is.
Yeah, kind of a little bit.
OK, the next voicemail is not a voicemail.
It is an image.
This is the image.
Virgin voicemail and the Chad picture.
This is nicely drawn. I like this.
Although it reminds me that this week I saw a tweet and I retweeted
a tweet that I agreed with strongly, which is that the Virgin versus Chad
meme has been bastardized.
It was originally now it has become bad thing left, good thing right.
But it was originally the thing on the left is like normal.
And the thing on the right is like hyper masculine insanity,
like something like the original Chad, like he's a freak.
Like he takes like beetle like strides and he's perpetually in counterpost.
And he's he's barely even human.
And like the other the other like, you know, the early versions of it were him
like like like pissing in a like like shitting in a toilet.
And like he like bends over and like squirts of a shit stream
like across the entire bathroom and like piles it up inside the toilet and overflows it.
Right. Like it's like that's the the Chad.
It's like, yeah, like just excess.
Yeah, excess like explosive.
And it's like, yeah, that's good.
But it's like the joke is that it's kind of is it's ridiculous.
You would not want to shit all over the bathroom.
That and it's true.
I do feel like it's been bastardized a little bit.
That being said, I'm guilty of this and I still like this.
Like I drew the the Virgin Yerk versus Chad and the light picture for Tom's lecture.
And like, I don't know, it's I like it.
It's it can also be funny in its own way.
Let's let's let's go through the Virgin voicemail versus the Chad picture.
The Virgin voicemail takes three minutes to say nothing.
Needs expensive audio equipment to record it.
Cares about being part of the PCP Canon threatens to fuck Nate.
Doesn't.
Oof.
That's a big one.
Devastating.
The next the Chad picture can be understood in seconds.
The only equipment you need is talent.
Harkens back to yield drawcast days defeats the only point of an audio podcast.
Ben is too big to do it.
I have no defense.
I can't I can't stop.
That I think is this the same person who drew that Sarah Z.
I think so.
I think because they're holding that image.
Well, well, like it's a Chad is holding that image, isn't it?
Well, this isn't.
Wait, the Sarah Z.
Image was not drawn for the PCP.
Someone edited it for the PCP, right?
I thought somebody sent it in.
Am I crazy?
Did they did they send the original to?
Yeah, maybe right.
OK, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
OK, yeah, I think I think this is that guy, whoever they are, that person
trying to stay gender neutral.
Well, I mean, they're just right.
They're just right.
And I can't rebut any of this.
I hope that Eleazar shows the images on screen.
I think he does some of the time.
I hope he does this one.
I really I mean, I really hope this is on screen
and that you don't have to go down to the to the links and link to it.
That would be lame.
Well, well done.
Well, well said.
Yeah.
Next voicemail is called Quentin.
There it is in the chat right there.
Three, two, one, go.
Hi, Ben St.
And give and take.
Yes, I hear there used to be other people on this podcast.
That's true. What happened to that?
Dead, killed him.
You see, what had happened was
there there was a time passed and people moved on to other projects.
It is a yes.
The the Virgin gone first, the Chad here.
Now, yeah, the Virgin past versus the Chad present.
Yeah, there we go.
Exactly.
I can't I this isn't a serious question, right?
Because I'm not prepared to answer it seriously.
Listen, listen to the entire history of the podcast and you will know
next voicemail is called let me put it here.
It's called Ben's best friend.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, Ben.
I'm sorry, I haven't sent a voicemail in a while.
It's OK, but things have been rough.
I hope things are going all right.
Please have a good day.
Thank you.
I'm having a good day.
That was it.
This. Hey, this guy is nice of him.
This is a solid guy.
I want I'm having a pretty good day.
I'm so glad that I got the the rat road to Radcon chapter five done.
Happy to be moving on with that.
I have about a week before I have to move house and I'm going to try
and use that week to do work on my video game.
So that's all pretty base.
Thanks for asking.
Next one putting here is called.
Colin Ridgway, three, two, one, go.
College.
You know, cool.
Sure. Sure.
Yeah. Sure.
Of course, I guess.
Yeah, I agree.
I agree. I concur.
We did it.
I will say this week, I'm happy to see that almost all of these voicemails
are under 30 seconds.
I feel like people actually listened and took it to heart when I said,
keep your voicemail short.
I don't want your fucking minute long voicemail.
They they actually did it.
There's only been like one or two that have been over a minute.
Thank you.
Voicemailers genuinely.
Nobody wants you do not have a minute's worth of content of you
do not have a minute's worth of thoughts to share.
I promise next voicemail is called by the way, we're almost done.
Actually, we're like three more next voicemail is called feelings.
We're hurt.
Three, two, one, go.
You guys didn't play my whole voicemail where I asked you guys a question,
but you guys fucking play the whole voicemail where the guy just fucking
piece for 40 minutes.
What the fuck's up with that?
It's bonus content.
It's my accent.
It was your accent.
Yeah, Paul.
That's what Taylor guy was just cooler.
What do you want?
Damn.
Well, I guess feelings were hurt.
And that's just something we have to live with.
Look, piss is just good at revenue generator.
People tune in for that.
The poop, though.
That was a joke.
Don't do that.
Don't actually piss.
It was we did play.
Didn't we play the piss one, but we didn't play the poop one, right?
I I did not want the poop one.
The poop one is a lot if it's real poop.
If that's a real poop from a real audience member, that's uncomfortable.
And I don't like it.
But I mean, I'm sure that was the point.
Next one is called sad.
Three, two, one, go.
Also, being able to hear about Simon Hanselman comics,
Meg Morgan, and now it's good.
I think we're going to like Meg Morgan now.
Yes, I have I have heard of Meg Morgan now.
Well, I'll post I'll post an image.
Meg, Mog and Al.
Yeah, I see this this witch around sometimes.
I don't know if it looks good or not.
Maybe it does.
I've I've seen a few that are really funny,
but I need to look at it like read the whole thing.
Yeah, I've never really been taking the time.
So I don't know. Yeah.
Um, I should probably check it out.
I've had a few other people recommended to me.
So there's what was the one is like, Al really needs to get inside
because he needed to pee or needed to take a shit.
And and Meg and Mog were looking at him
and they just like, hey, I don't open the door.
And that was the whole comic is just a series of events
when we like, please let me in.
I think I think that that was really funny for some reason.
I think the the indie comics that I've been recommended the most
that I have kind of been sort of meaning to read are this.
Meg, Mog and Al and Crow Killers.
You know, Crow Killers by Kate Woods. No.
Uh, I don't know. Oh, I've heard of Kate.
Words. Yes, I've heard of any relation to Bill.
No, Bill. Who is Bill?
Words is the guy who made the words is the history of Japan video.
Oh, yeah, probably not.
And the music and the stuff.
And he made lots of things.
They were all dank.
Wait, Bill, that's not the my spoon is too big guy.
My spoon is that the guy who made those movies.
I think my spoon is too big.
I think that is Bill.
Words as well.
No, Don Hertzfeld. No, it's Don Hertzfeld.
Words, words, spells.
Yeah, OK, that. Yeah.
Yeah, Kate, words.
I have a furry friend who likes Kate words.
And you can see they have a strong aesthetic.
Wait, that's not.
Is that a Kate?
That doesn't look like her usual style.
It's got her name on it.
OK, but that doesn't look like her style.
Hold on, Kate.
Let me just like stuff stuff stuff like this.
Words is like this shit.
Yeah, yeah, OK.
Yeah, this this fucking kind of.
Yeah, OK, maybe that first one is just
she doesn't usually draw furries while.
I think we got one more.
Yeah, we got one more voicemail.
This is the last one unless some unless someone send the last one
last minute in.
Let me check if that happened.
No, this one is called guests suggestion three, two, one, go.
OK, guess you guys might be able to pull now that you had
the creator of this guest role on the podcast.
Now you have this fucking street crowd cloud.
You guys could have cloud, baby.
The guy who created Mr.
Boop, he probably knows about him.
He probably knows about things that get through.
I don't think we can get out of the podcast now.
I don't think we can get him.
You know, JQ, Rebecca Sugar's husband.
He knows about Sonichu.
So he probably also knows about things that throw that would be funny.
Why would we want Rebecca Sugar's husband?
We need the best guy ever.
OK, dude, do you think we can get the best guy ever?
I don't know.
He's got 100,000 subscribers.
He's pretty based.
I don't know if he's he would grace us.
I will say that.
Oh, God, man.
I just looked at Rebecca Sugar's fucking Wikipedia.
And I see that they're 34 years old, which is basically my age.
And they've already fucking they've already rocked the fucking entertainment industry.
And I've fucking done shit with my life.
So that that's great.
Hey, hey, voicemailer, thanks for ruining my mood by reminding me of Rebecca.
This is my whole week down the drain.
You know what?
How am I supposed to work on the game now?
Huh?
Don't blame the voicemailer.
Blame Rebecca Sugar.
Blame everyone.
Oh, cringy.
Anyway, what are we talking about?
Oh, yeah, I wanted to say, oh, yeah, Cybershell said he would like to be a guest on more episodes.
And in particular, he said he wants to do a guest episode with Gamer's Tavern.
So I think one of the pretty soon, I will probably suggest that the two of them be on a guest episode together soon.
Maybe maybe two episodes from now.
I think I've got another guest in mind for next week.
Dur.
Um, I would like to I would like to have Cybershell on a little more often.
He's he's we have a so Ben before before all this.
What's up?
Um, yeah, your previous episode of Shreddit, we didn't get to the A.B.
Dale post of the week because I couldn't find a good one.
I have a last minute voice.
Oh, okay.
You know what?
That's fair.
Oh, my God.
Hello, everybody, and welcome back to the best part of Shreddit, a A.B.
D.L. post of the week.
Yeah, Ben, take it away.
Uh-oh.
You want me to wear it?
And this is where we don't get into the back.
Here we go.
Good run, guys.
Hey, everyone.
Now, nobody better clip this out of context or anything.
Uh, hey, every forced to wear diapers tagged as NSFW.
Hey, everyone.
About a month ago, I introduced myself and spoke about going 24 seven.
And it's now been a few months since doing so.
A few weeks ago, I hit a snag, though.
The desire faded as it often does being A.B.
D.L. with ups and downs.
But since then, my wife has not just become used to me in diapers, but now says
she finds me more attractive.
So I went a few days without wearing and she said she didn't like it.
She now checks every morning and every night that I have my diaper on and
does regular checks and tells me if I need a change or decides to change me.
There's even been moments when I said I didn't feel like wearing and she said
that it's not up to me.
And as of last week, she's taken away my underwear.
I now have to ask for underwear when seeing family and friends and most of
the time, unless it's very close quarters for extended periods, she says
no, it makes me wear a more discreet diaper.
To be clear, I asked for this when I started down this path.
What I did not expect was that she would truly enjoy keeping me diapered
and that I would and that I feel required to wear diapers now to wear diapers
now versus figured she'd just do it to support me, but I could still decide
not to TLDR.
I no longer have a choice in being 24 seven and my wife keeps me in diapers
and it's a dream come true.
Anyone else out there forced to be kept.
I could honestly, I couldn't tell how he felt about it until the Stockholm syndrome
does.
I kind of thought I kind of thought he was saying like, guys, I was just
fucking around.
I'm in too deep and I want out like this is scary now.
But no, I thought this was going to be like and now she wants to divorce
because I don't want to wear a diaper anymore.
I thought it was going to be sad.
I thought it was going to be good for him.
I thought it was going to be.
I want to divorce because now she's too into it.
She's too into my thing and I don't like it anymore.
And it's a dream come true.
Honestly, honestly, I don't believe it.
I think this is a fantasy.
I think this guy is just he's just writing his fantasies out on his Reddit
account.
I mean, possibly with the ABDL a lot of times you get weird posts like this.
Like I saw one where a guy was like I wear a diaper and no pants to my
office building and everyone loved it and high fived me.
No.
Yeah, they want they want to for some reason they want to act like that
it's more accepted in society than it is, which I mean, I can see
wanting it to be more accepted if you have a really niche fetish or something.
I bet for some people that's part of it where it's like part of the fantasy
is like, what if everyone could just see my diaper and just think it was cool?
Like, what if they liked seeing me?
No, no, it's like what if what if the diaper was accepted?
What if everyone just appreciated the diaper and like, I don't know.
I bet I bet that that has an appeal all its own to some of these people.
Now, Gib, you do not have to read this, but I also got you on.
Oh, bro.
Above and beyond.
Yeah.
All right.
Why not?
Little's bro needs you to answer a very important question.
Click me.
Smiley face and SFW and let me just emojis is a rose and there's two genies.
If you had your very own genie and this genie could give you two wishes instead
of three, what might I wish or what might you wish one for big life and one for
little go flowering genies?
See, told you.
What is this?
I don't understand.
So I hate that I can interpret what this is.
I hate one one for big life and one for little the genie will give you two
wishes, but one wish is like, what would what would your normal big self
want?
And the other one is what is it?
What wish would your little self want?
Oh, that's the name of the so that people who wear the diapers, they talk of
themselves as they're the little CS versus the CG is the caretaker.
It's when it's when you it's when you it's when you are in it's when you are
in the mode.
It's when you're in the mode, you enter little space and you become and you're
your little self.
That why do they got to come up with like your fantasy?
Just, you know, just like fucking younglings.
There's always a different term for it.
Um, they have like a killed all the little lot of weird terms.
All of them.
What's hmm.
Be is miniscule's nano particles quarks.
Is this okay?
So this is from this is from the ABDL board.
Okay, because I know I know that not all littles are into diapers and not all
diaper lovers are our littles.
Yeah, some people like shitting on the floor.
Yeah, no, they call it messing.
No, I thought that was a joke.
That is not a joke.
That is actually reality.
Nope.
Some of them get bad.
I did picked one.
I was, I was, but I figured it was too far and I'm like, I'm like, bro,
could you not honestly do these?
Did you have what do you stockpile them?
Do you have a folder full of them?
Why are there more?
Well, okay.
Okay.
Well, I was posting this as an example of them talking about messing,
but I was going through and I was trying to find one and I put out three
that would possibly be funny and I was going to use two.
I didn't use messing because we'll been funny.
I'm sure the PCP audience is not prepared to read this one.
I'll read this one.
Oh, no, no, no.
Enjoying messing.
No, here we go.
You don't have to.
Here we go.
Hi.
I don't know why I didn't listen to this.
I'm an AB and I use diapers, but when I'm in them, whether while I'm in my
little space or big, I never want to mess them.
And if I do parentheses forced by my mommy due to suppositories.
Oh God, I instantly want out of them and I was wondering how I could enjoy
the feeling of them rather than hate it.
I think you're not into it.
I think that's what I mean.
Oh my God.
I naturally hate shitting myself.
What can I do to fix this?
It's weird because like I love shitting myself, but like when I do it,
like it's awful and bad and I'm like, I just don't understand.
I love the idea of shitting myself.
I don't actually like.
I feel like in a, in a previous.
Why would they?
Yeah.
Why would they preface that like while whether in little space or big, like,
is there a subset of like messers who do it in adult mode?
Probably.
Like there's there's probably some who only do it in little space and this guy
is saying, yeah, sometimes I'll do it in big space as well.
It's a it's a white color or something.
No, no.
See, there's a specific difference.
Uh, I hate the fact that I know this.
I got it.
I got a prefaces.
I hate the fact that this irony is going to eventually become.
I mean, we do a show that has it every week.
No, no, no, that's how it always starts.
But I have, I have seen people talk about, right?
Some of them enjoy being in big space, messing themselves
and just soaking it in, sitting on it for hours, not doing anything.
But I feel when you're, when you're in little space and you do it,
you get off on the idea of being changed and treated like a baby.
I think that like on a previous, I think maybe on like the, no, I wasn't
on the fetish cast, but on one of like the previous, an old PCP,
I think we talked about ABDL stuff.
And I think someone said that some people will like shove like oatmeal up
their ass and then like, and then shit it out so that they can sit
in the oatmeal and it feels like shit.
It feels like they're sitting in shit, but it doesn't smell like shit.
And it doesn't like, you know, cause the fucking legions and infections
from sitting in shit.
So I would, if I were on this board, I would suggest that to this individual.
My, I think I think he could get real results that way.
That's I'm a problem.
I'm a problem.
Be scared of this part of every episode.
Jesus Christ.
I genuinely, I genuinely have advice for this person.
Maybe you're the one that's in 2D.
You know too much.
I just remember, I remember hearing that and being like, wow, you know,
I guess it would kind of feel like you're shitting, but without like all the,
without most of the terrible, fascinating.
What, what do they think of next?
Technology has come so far.
Jesus Christ.
Holy fuck.
What a way to end an episode.
I think that's going to do it for this episode of the pro-crastinators podcast.
Crastinators podcast.
Unless anyone's got any last words.
I have some, I have some required things to say.
Okay.
Number one, Marin Pan is again amazing.
I promised him a shout out.
He's one of the best.
We run a streaming channel with him called shredded a fickle and it's only spelled
shredded a fickle because I spelled official wrong.
Check out our channel.
We do, we have an ABDL segment at the end of every episode, but of course that's
not the main draw.
The rest of the episode is funny too.
It's just that the ABDL, there's always a stupid post on there.
Like you just go on the website and within three seconds you found like a perfect post.
This person is just terrible.
Especially when they talk about sneaking in public and then relieving themselves in like
a public area and then just leaving it there.
That's when it turns into, okay, we're not kink shaming, we're making fun of somebody
who deserves it.
When you're a public nuisance, that's when we cross the line.
Yeah.
Check out Lumia Stargazer.
She's an amazing VTuber.
She's also our fourth host.
Aspoi is our thumbnail artist.
Kai is our big brain.
He doesn't do anything anymore.
Okay.
I have outsource.
That's a real big brain move.
That's the four hour work week.
Anyway, continue.
Oh, and then just a Lexi million on Twitter.
Links below, hopefully.
He did our new banner.
He did our logo.
He does really good art.
You forgot one more.
That's all my shilling.
Yeah, check out.
I forgot.
I'll check out the peace fee Minecraft server.
Mariners does an amazing job.
I'm giving you another one.
I already did that.
That's true though.
That leads into my plug, which is patreon.com slash the procrastinators for bonus episodes,
including the big bonus episode coming out with me and Cybershell having a intimate discussion.
Not really, but it's funny.
It's a funny.
We just fucking went all day.
And also you have bonus episodes and you get access to the PCB Minecraft server where
you can fucking challenge me to a Pokemon battle and Shanghai me onto your podcast.
Maybe.
Yes.
It worked for some people.
Yeah, there's really cool stuff on that server.
Like they have gyms for like every PCP member.
It is kind of a masterpiece.
The PCB Minecraft server is kind of a masterpiece.
Mostly thanks to Marin.
Yeah.
Okay, are we concluded?
Yes, I think.
Okay, send a voicemail if you want to.
That's it.
Goodbye.
The end.
Bye.
Okay.
Goodbye.