I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Hello and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators. As I move my microphone and I move my mouse,
I realize that the Who Are These Podcast guy was absolutely right. My mouse is right next to my microphone.
I basically do have my mic right directly on my mouse, so recording the loud sounds of my mouse clicking.
Honestly, it's not even exaggeration. That guy really had me pegged.
I guess I don't hear it because Discord has a default noise gate for little things like that.
But no, it's like inches away from my microphone, so I'm sure it is audible.
What's up? Once again, a week has passed.
Oh my god.
What the fuck? Nothing even happened.
Well, I had a thing that happened, but it's not the story of an adventure, but it's hard to tell without it being just me reciting a list of things that happened.
I went to Canterbury and it was nice. It was a nice day out.
What's there to do in Canterbury?
Nothing much. It's an old sort of medieval English town. There's like bricks, there's like old walls from castles occasionally just strewn around.
And it's like, yeah, it's nice. We found a cool museum there and they had bagpuss in it.
Oh, right, bagpuss, right.
And the clangers and noggin the nog and Ivor the engine and Rupert Bear.
These can't be real. They're so real.
You're making at least some of these up.
No, no, I actually remembered them all. There was one or two I hadn't ever seen before.
And then there was Basil Brush, the fucks. I didn't know Basil Brush.
Who could forget Basil Brush?
Who could forget? Ha, ha, ha, ha, boom, boom, the classic catchphrase of Basil Brush.
Is that true? I don't know.
He goes, ha, ha, ha, ha, boom, boom, like it's so silly and obnoxious.
But I remember watching it like a, I don't know if it was late 90s or 2000s or whatever.
They had like a Basil Brush came back for a TV show and that's where I knew about him.
Like a revival?
Yeah, because I had no idea that he was like in the, in the olden times, in the 60s,
when he was first invented as a little cartoon fucks.
I asked you about...
Anybody remember Basil Brush?
Wait, so Basil Brush...
So, okay, so Bagpuss was like a show and these were all characters in the show, right?
As we were talking about.
Bagpuss, well, these, this was all in one room in the museum, which was like this particular artist,
puppeteer, craftsman, animator, stop motion guy.
And these are all shows that he worked on or created.
So Bagpuss was one, Basil Brush was another,
Nog in the Nog, which was, I think, a Viking.
But it was like two dimensional, like South Park, but not like South Park.
Paper cutouts, but with like hinges on their arms and legs and they would walk.
It's like, you know how the old Norman tapestries that would depict medieval people?
Yes.
They sort of have a weird...
From the side, from the side view, because they didn't know how to draw a person in three quarters view.
Yeah, so they, it was like a show based on that sort of way of doing things.
Yeah, cool.
They've got all the, like the original puppets, the original little paper people.
They got everything.
And I was like, we had no idea any of that was there.
We were just like, oh, that's a cool building.
Let's go inside.
And we saw it.
That reminds me of, do you know a YouTube channel called Atrocity Guide?
Nope.
Atrocity Guide is a pretty cool channel.
They have a bunch of videos that are about weird, just kind of about weird things.
Like there's one about, I hope I remember the name.
It's called The Throne of Fred Hampton.
Okay, you've probably seen the Down the Rabbit Hole about Henry Darger and Realms of the Unreal.
No, I have not watched Down the Rabbit Hole before.
I see them, but I'm like, eh, whatever.
That's my favorite Down the Rabbit Hole, Henry Darger and The Realms of the Unreal.
It's about a guy who worked as a janitor his whole life, but his whole life he spent
cutting out magazine clippings and tracing over them to create this huge volume of illustrated stories
about these, I think it's like seven twin, seven sisters who were like princesses of this magical, like, other world.
It's awesome.
And yeah, I think it was, I think it was Sporktown Heroine that turned me on to this channel.
She recommended me a video called, huh?
No, nothing.
Oh, called The Throne of Fred Hampton.
And it's a similar thing.
This guy, Fred Hampton, who I think might have also been a, maybe not a janitor, maybe like a garbage collector or something,
but yeah, he had this little like warehouse space or like a storage unit.
And in the storage unit, he spent years collecting trash, like aluminum foil and light bulbs,
and he would take any piece of like glittery or like reflective or shiny trash that he found,
and he would make it into, he would form it into a piece of this throne
and all this like, this like royal like, like adornments to go along with like, he built this throne room
out of like aluminum foil and light bulbs in this storage unit.
And I guess he thought he was like a prophet who was possessed by God.
No, it's not that he, he didn't think he was a prophet, but he did think he was tasked by God to build a throne like for like the return of Christ.
Or something to like ascend to.
It's so cool.
And then this, hold on.
A glittery room in a storage unit wouldn't surely, I mean, obviously that's probably just what they had.
But like, you can't see the glitteriness if there's no light shining in.
Well, I mean, there was a light, eternal light bulb on.
I think I remember he brought like a woman over and he was like, hey, check this out.
And like he just, he went in and just turned the lights on.
And like the lady was like, oh my God, what the fuck is this?
But yeah, anyway, there's an atrocity guide.
I think it just came out and it was about this, I'd never heard of this before.
Russian cartoonist making a, he's been working on a movie for like 15 years.
Well, it's him and his wife, they're like a pair.
So yeah, these two Russian animators have been making this movie.
It's called the, it's called like, is it like the cloak or like the coat, the overcoat, I think.
But it's, okay, you know that when you think of like old Russian cartoons, you think of like, yeah, like,
like sort of South Parkish, like like paper puppets, right?
That like kind of move on hinges.
Yeah.
They sort of look like the Monty Python cartoons.
Well, it's like that, but it's like the most complicated form of that you can imagine.
It's like that, but with like every individual like finger of like the hand is like hinged and like it's all,
it's not like flat colors.
It's like, it's all like painterly.
And like they do like, you know, 20 different images of the same like face or whatever at different angles.
And so as the guy turns his head like they're replaced, they're moving it slightly between frames,
but they're also replacing it with a slit to make it like a smooth.
It's so weird looking.
It's bizarre.
Honestly, this guy has been making this move.
These people have been making this movie for like 15 years.
It's never, it's probably never going to be finished.
This is just going to be the rest of their life finishing this movie and never actually doing it.
And I got to say, it's an admirable work, but it looks scary.
It looks scary and creepy and unsettling and uncanny and I don't like it.
I just don't like it.
What's it called?
I believe the movie is called The Overcoat.
Let me look up Atrocity Guide and make sure.
Atrocity Guide.
The newest video is called...
Okay, it's called The Animators who've spent 40 years on a single film.
Maybe in the description it has a...
Yeah, it's called The Overcoat.
Like there's clips that have been shown of it.
I mean, the whole, the movie, it's not done yet.
They've made other...
They've made other animation work, like to fund the project.
You know, I guess they are...
I guess they like the Russian style of, you know, like paper puppet animation.
And they're basically doing like taking that to its logical conclusion, doing like the most advanced form of that a person can do.
And I guess that's fair enough.
But I truly feel that the resulting product is horrifying.
I want to see it.
It's hard to Google.
Let me...
Oh, Jesus.
I just clicked to like a random point in the...
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
A clip of the movie.
I'll sort of find you the exact...
I'll find you the exact timestamp.
Here.
Okay, share.
Start at 25.09.
Here's just like a little clip of...
Oh, yeah, there's something...
There's something uncanny about the fluidness of that hand movement.
I think it's...
I mean, I think it's part...
I don't know if it's entirely the animation style.
I mean, I think the illustration style, like the way that he's drawn is part of what is making it creepy.
And I think it's got to be somewhat intentional.
Like they drew him like that on purpose.
But like, I just hate it.
I hate seeing it.
40 years in a single film.
I said 15.
I guess I meant 40.
Yeah, they've been...
They made another...
There's one about like a fox stealing a baby.
And they made that movie like...
I guess it's based on a myth or something.
And they made that like, you know, 40 years ago and it was a big hit.
And they were like, well, for our next one, we're going to adapt this piece of folk literature called the Overcoat.
And that's what they've been doing for 40 years.
Crazy.
Yeah, I know.
The dedication alone is inspiring, but also I would never want to do that one thing for 40 years.
Later on in the video, she says like, it seems like the guy just sort of is like a weird misanthrope
and kind of just doesn't care like what people think of his movie.
And he's just doing it to do it at this point.
And it doesn't seem like he's in any hurry to like finish it up and get it released.
I mean, why would you...
At this point, it's his life, I guess.
Why would you stop?
Like if somebody says, huh, this has taken a while and doesn't even look good.
It looks creepy.
And it's like, oh, I guess I should can it then 40 years in.
He, it must be, it must be supposed to look like this.
Of course.
But like...
Movies don't have to look beautiful.
They can look fucked up.
I just don't know why you would make it look like this on purpose.
I don't know who would want to see this.
I don't know.
Freaks.
I don't know, man.
I'm...
I...
God, not...
Jeez.
Art enjoyers.
Art enjoyer.
The average, the average Russian paper, paper doll style of animation enjoyer.
The soy jack.
I don't know.
Anime connoisseur.
Anime freak.
Something, something, something, something, something, haha, good, bad.
Anyway, what were we talking about?
I was talking about the museum in Canterbury.
Right, right, right, right, right, right.
Yeah, I asked you about that on the Shekels for Hekels because I was not familiar with
any of these characters.
Yeah.
The reason I don't really feel like it's worth, like a story worth telling is because there
wasn't really anything particularly exciting that happened.
It was just like a nice day and like if we went to the seaside, we saw the sunset over
the sea as it receded into the ocean.
And it was really nice, but it's like, I can't really describe it in a way that anyone could
really get anything out of it.
Yesterday, I saw the moon, right?
I know, but it was really low over the horizon.
It was really low and it was so like yellow.
It was like orange.
It was the orangeest moon I've ever seen.
It looked very spooky.
I missed the lunar eclipse.
There was a lunar eclipse like this weekend, I think, but it was cloudy.
I couldn't see it.
Bummer.
Oh, well.
Guess I'm fucked.
Oh, you know, another thing is the only sort of interesting thing, but it's like I'm mostly
interested in how many people in our audience who are British remember this one thing.
Me and my brothers, we have this in-joke that started from Michael Owen, who is a footballer
who plays football.
Who is this guy?
Michael Owen.
Oh, okay.
And the reason he's a meme, like an in-joke, is because we had a cereal box where it was
Michael Owen themed shreddies or something.
It was a shreddies box and Michael Owen was on the front.
He was hot shit.
He was like David Beckham, but at the same time, it was like Michael Owen and David Beckham,
but David Beckham was more famous for longer lasting and Michael Owen, nobody remembers him.
But Michael Owen was on there.
He's like, cool, the sports guy.
I don't know why we had this cereal.
There was this how Michael Owen eats shreddies, like how to eat shreddies with Michael Owen.
Are shreddies like Wheaties?
Yeah, yeah, very similar.
So there was a four, it was four pals, I remember, and it's like step one.
Wait a minute.
I Googled shreddies and I do see the cereal box, but there is also apparently a line of
underwear and other fabric goods that are designed to filter your farts and make them smell better.
That is also called shreddies.
Well, that's very unfortunate.
I don't like that I know that now.
The original shreddies, they claim.
Well, the underwear?
That's what their website says.
I just wanted to know.
Now I can't help but picture fighting through a piece of cereal.
I kind of don't believe them.
I think they're lying.
I think that probably the cereal came first.
But what do I know?
I mean, it's like a grid, a lattice grid.
Yeah, yeah, I'm looking at it.
Anyway, there was like celebrities being on cereal wasn't that strange.
But the thing that was funny was the how to eat shreddies or shredded wheat or whatever it was.
Yeah, I've always wondered, Michael Owen, how do I eat shreddies exactly?
Yeah, and it was like panel one, like put spoon in to bowl.
Panel two, lift spoon.
Panel three, exercise taste buds.
And then panel four, repeat.
And I found it so funny because at no point does he put the cereal in his mouth.
If you follow those steps exactly, you lift the spoon up out of the bowl.
You put it in, lift it up, just move your mouth around a bit and then do it again.
You'll die of starvation.
And it was so stupid and me and my brothers laughed forever.
We've laughed until 2021 about fucking Michael Owen.
And now whenever we want to think of someone who's an idiot, a stupid character.
We think of someone who's an idiot.
Whenever we have like a stupid character for something that like, oh, what if, I don't know,
what if you had a grape that could tell a time, you know, Michael Owen, brand grape.
We would just put Michael Owen there.
It's very stupid.
It's very in-jokey.
But I'm really curious as to if anybody remembers Michael Owen's How to Eat Shreddies from the back of that cereal box.
Comment below.
Please comment below if you remember Michael Owen's How to Eat Shreddies.
I mean, do you Google it?
I Googled it.
All right.
Here's one of the images.
This is what he looks like.
So open your mouth or like whatever.
Back, I think, I think this is like an edited photograph.
They put the word back in there because that's the back button of their website about...
Okay, okay.
Are you sure it was Shreddies because I'm seeing it on a box of sporties?
Another cereal that sounds ridiculous to me.
I think that was like a version of the thing.
Nestle is the same company.
Nestle Shredded Wheats.
I don't think it was Shredded Wheat.
It's not quite the same product.
This looks more like, this is Shredded Wheat.
Does it sort of look more like Chex?
I don't know.
Yeah.
I guess Shredded Wheat was like the original one, but then to make it cool for the kids,
they made Shreddies.
And that was the one I know more of.
It's got more sugar on it.
But yeah, Michael Owen, I found this one image.
I can't find the rest.
Like Shreddies How to...
Like it's so stupid and nobody would keep track of it.
Except for this one website that seems to have images of the old Michael Owen box.
When I Google this, all the results are him not on a Shreddies box, but on a sporties box.
Are you sure you're not misremembering what cereal it was?
Well, Shredded Wheat.
It was like a limited time version.
It's like, oh, Lucky Charms, but with only nothing in it.
And you call it Shitty Charms.
It's the different name for the same cereal, but branded with a celebrity.
I'm looking at it.
I can tell that Shredded Wheat is not the same thing as Shreddies.
Okay, we had Shredded Wheat.
I mean, it's very similar.
Yes, I made a mistake, whatever.
But that's what it was.
Michael Owen on Shredded Something.
Wait, well, hmm.
Wait, I found a...
Damn it.
I don't think this is it.
But I found some box images.
Maybe this is just a different box, actually.
Here's some important imagery for all of us to remember on Christmas Day.
Here's another one.
But here, I'm about to show my favorite one, which is...
Oh, there's more.
There's more.
You found more?
Well, there's these three boxes.
And then there's three front cover boxes.
But what I like most about this last one here is in the bottom right corner.
Or sorry, the bottom left.
What is this power zone?
It's like new Shreddies with power zone.
Yeah, if you want to be good at sports, you need the power zone Shredded Wheat.
What does this have? Cheese inside of it? What is that?
No, it was just a layer of sugar.
It looks like cheese.
It looks like maybe honey, something or other.
I don't know.
But it's got the...
These Sporties have the power zone.
Oh my God, I found it.
Really? Which? Where?
Open image. I just need to...
It's on Reddit.
I'll just copy paste.
Oh my God.
Michael Owen's morning workout.
Anyway, yeah, here's how to eat the fucking cereal.
The winner's way to start your day.
You lift your arm, you stretch your mouth, and you don't eat it.
Yeah, you don't actually put it in your mouth.
It's such a bizarre thing to include.
And he's just so boring looking.
Yeah, he seems totally uninterested.
He's...
Oh my God.
This is like a magazine or something, man.
Yeah, and the Beano, that's probably what it was.
The Beano?
Yeah, the Beano's a comic book.
Oh.
Like a weekly comic book with cartoon people.
It looks like a wiki-how.
Those wiki-how illustrations?
Yeah, a little bit.
Yeah.
How to eat sporties.
I don't know.
Stupid.
Fucking Michael Owen.
The diagram for exercise taste buds is like a circular motion.
You're meant to rotate the cereal through your...
over the tongue, and then under the tongue, and then back and forth,
back and forth in a circular kind of motion.
The last image is the same as the first one,
but it's ever so slightly smaller.
Yeah, it is.
Yeah.
Oh, I love that I found this.
Well, now I know how to eat sporties, shreddies.
It probably works for any cereal, honestly.
Yeah.
So as long as you have the winner's spirit inside.
Base.
Well, now I know.
Thanks, Michael Owen.
Speaking of...
Speaking of Michael Owen.
Speaking of athleticism.
Speaking of being fit and powerful.
So I've been continuing to lift and become extremely strong.
And I hit my PB.
I hit my personal best on the bench press this week, 160.
Nothing too impressive, but it's pretty good for me.
So that's pretty cool.
Kazi and Munchy are also PBing.
Kazi is hitting their PBs on, I think, the overhead press
and maybe the bench press and maybe the squat too, I think.
So they're powerful also, which is nice.
But this week, every time I went over there, they were like,
Ben, after we get done lifting, let's get drunk.
Let's get drunk.
I was like, and I'm like, no, no, you're terrible.
You're terrible.
You're a terrible influence.
Friday, I said.
We'll get drunk on Friday.
And we said, okay, we'll get drunk on Friday.
And then the Friday comes and then they're sick.
Everyone's sick.
Munchy gets sick and then Kazi gets sick.
And now I'm probably going to get sick because I probably got
whatever they got.
So that's that shit.
Speaking of being sick, I think I said last week my dad got the
coronavirus.
Did I mention that last week or was that the...
That may have been during the stream.
The stream.
Oh yeah, my dad got the test positive for the coronavirus,
which made me very worried.
But he says he's not, he's got no symptoms.
And he said, I haven't talked to him in a few days,
but I haven't heard anything.
So probably nothing, hopefully nothing has happened there.
He said, he suspected it might be a false positive.
So he said he was going to get tested again.
And we'll see.
And I mentioned this on the stream, but I'll say it again.
I felt, I felt sad because it was his birthday this weekend.
And I had planned to go visit him as like a surprise.
Like, hey, I'm here to hang out for your birthday.
But then he got tested positive for the coronavirus.
So we canceled that.
So as not to spread the virus.
So I didn't get to do that, which was kind of shit.
And it would be kind of shitty if it turned out,
oh, it was just a false positive.
I could have gone anyway, but I didn't.
Whoops.
But I mean, I guess Thanksgiving is like this week anyway.
So whatever.
I'll be there either way.
It doesn't matter.
Nothing.
Nothing matters.
I hope it is a false positive.
So I don't have to worry about catching it.
Yes.
That would be helpful.
That would be optimal.
Yeah.
Oh, by the way, for, for my adventure,
there was a lot of walking involved.
And it's my first big Pikmin bloom outing.
Oh, God.
And I got so many nectar.
I got so many flowers bloomed.
Wow.
That sounds incredible.
And guess how many steps that was for that entire day.
For what, for one day walking around in museums and shit.
Walking around in museums and then also walking like to the ocean.
There's quite a lot of walking, really.
Okay, let me think.
At a rate of about one step a second,
let's say a day out is maybe,
if it's a long day, maybe eight hours, right?
So 60, 60 steps a minute times 60 steps is 3,600 steps per hour.
Times eight would be 24, 25,800 steps.
And let's say maybe you were walking for half of it.
So I'm going to guess about 12,000 steps.
Hmm.
Well, well.
There's actually 21,656 steps.
Wow.
Damn.
That was a lot.
My legs hurt quite a lot afterwards.
Because we planned it badly.
We didn't exactly know where we were going.
It was really just sort of like, let's get the fuck out somewhere.
And then we did.
And we had to walk a lot.
We could have got more buses, but we thought,
no, this is an adventure.
We can walk.
We can walk through this forest.
Oh, oh, we can't.
So you were like, you were on like a family trip to Canterbury.
And while you were there, you were like, let's get out.
Let's just go walk around somewhere.
No, no, no, no.
We just, it was just a day trip.
We got on a coach to Canterbury at like 8 a.m.
Just you and your brothers?
Yeah.
And then we explored the town.
We walked through some farms and some woodland on our way north
where the coach was going to pick us up.
That was the plan, generally, is we go to Canterbury,
then we get the coach back in like seven hours.
But we thought like, oh, seven hours, that's plenty of time
to get to a place like, I don't know, one town over.
It's not even that far, like a, you know, whatever.
We're walking there.
And it took a while.
And we had to sort of, we had to take a bus near the end.
To get there.
And it hurt.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
At least we saw the sea, though.
That was really nice.
Hey, you ever seen the sea?
Oh, of course you have.
You're in Boston.
You see the sea all the time.
I'm in Boston, yeah.
Well, I mean, I see the Charles River all the time,
which is very close to the sea.
I see the sea occasionally.
I've seen the West Coast too, you know, once or twice.
Yeah.
It's something just magical to me about an X,
like a huge flat, no, nothing in your line of vision.
Seeing the ocean just keeps going.
The, you know, if you guys were walking around all day,
does that mean that Henry's leg is better?
Didn't he have like a broken leg for a while?
No.
All right.
Here's the silly thing.
Okay.
Henry has been getting better.
He's on a medication that is, you know, for most of 2020,
he was like, my leg's fucked and I can't get a doctor
because coronavirus, everyone, all the doctors are busy.
Right.
And so his leg got worse and that was really fucked.
Yes.
Now coronavirus has eased up a bit.
He's able to have, he's been able to have more doctors
looking at his leg.
He's got things going on, so it's improving.
And now he has to, it's at the point where he needs
to walk a bit in order to build up strength
because if he's laying still, it's not going to improve.
So he has to do physical therapy for it basically.
Yeah, a little bit of physical therapy.
And we thought, okay, this would be like, you know,
maybe you could come with us on this fun walk.
And that was, I mean, it was kind of his idea.
He wanted to get out of the house.
It was just a lot of walking.
Luckily, we thought this was a stupid idea,
but he brought like a light, like an aluminum metal chair
and he strapped it to a backpack
and he had that carrying around the whole time.
And he had a walking set.
To just say it if you needed to?
Yeah, and we were like, okay, but there's going to be benches.
There's going to be like places where you can sit.
But it was actually very useful because the bus stops
where they had benches that were like anti-homeless benches.
You can't lie down on them.
You sort of slip off them if you, you know, try to relax in any way.
It's basically just like you're supposed to lean up against it
while standing basically.
They're not really seats.
And so when we were waiting for the bus, it's stupid.
I hate it.
It's like a metal cuboid that's slightly tilted downwards.
What?
I've never seen such a thing.
I mean, I've seen anti-homeless benches,
but I've never seen one that's just a slanted cube.
Well, like you got the bus area like a shelter, right?
Oh, wait.
So you're saying that it's basically just sort of like a featureless metal like slab
that just kind of sticks out of the ground
and has like a sort of horizontal surface on top
that you could maybe sit on, but it's angled.
I can kind of picture what you're talking about.
You could slip forward.
Does it have like handles or railings or a back?
It has a back.
It's like, you know, bus stops that have like a back
and then like a roof to keep you out of the rain.
Yes.
It's like one of those with like glass on each side.
And then the bench itself is just a metal cuboid
that's slightly slanted downwards so that you slip off it.
And so he wouldn't have been able to sit on that
for any extended period of time.
So that chair actually did come in handy a few times.
So good idea.
I see.
Fascinating.
Honestly, really weird.
Our bus stops, I mean, we have benches that are just, you know,
they're benches you can sit on.
Yeah.
Most of our bus stops just don't have a bench in them though.
Most of our bus stops around here are just,
they're just, you know, a little like, you know,
glass and metal shelf you can stand under.
What would you call a bus stop thing like a kiosk?
That's not really it.
Maybe a kiosk, maybe a little...
Oh, this is kind of coming up.
Not a pagoda, I don't know.
Overhang?
No.
You're coming, we've mentioned this before,
but you're planning to come visit in January, right?
Yes, I'll be coming over.
Very cool.
That'll be epic.
It will be a little bit epic.
Okay, I can't find a good image of this.
God dang it.
Are you looking for the bench?
I'm looking for a type of bench that's similar enough,
so I can illustrate what it is,
but these images are like tiny,
I'll post one so you can get a, maybe zoom in.
What?
It's just a little pole.
It's just a little pole and it's sort of slightly angled.
That one in particular, that red one,
that's the London one, those are okay.
You can sort of sit on them.
But the ones that we were at in Canterbury and Whistable,
they sucked.
That's so silly.
Yeah.
Most people just stand next to them,
but you don't even bother.
I could see leaning again.
I could see leaning against it for sure.
Hmm.
That seems like aggressively like,
we're giving you as little bench as we can get away with.
Yeah.
Oh well.
This is billions so they can just not spend it elsewhere.
You know, not to revert the topic,
but I forgot to mention something else about lifting yesterday.
We were doing it and we were in Kazia Munchie's basement
and their boiler, their house boiler that heats the water,
heats their house through radiators,
just started belching steam.
It just started blasting big steam cloud out of a pipe
and it was billowing up into the ceiling
and it heated up the room and it made it all moist and sweaty.
And it was...
Yeah, it was very uncomfortable.
We had to move the bar over to another section of the place
a little further away from all the steam.
And it was very upsetting.
It was very uncomfortable.
It made me very mad,
but we thought we were being poisoned by gas for a minute.
But I went over and I took a big lung...
To test the poison gas theory,
I went over and I took a big lung full of it
and I survived so I was like, no, no, it's steam, it's fine.
I mean, would gas...
Would there even be a gas pipe?
Yeah, it's a standard feature of most boilers in American houses
that there's a big pipe that comes off it
that periodically just emits huge amounts of poisonous gas.
I know the emitting part is not part of it,
but does the house use gas for the stove?
Well, I believe it's an oil-burning boiler, right?
It burns oil to heat the water in the boiler
that then circulates through the radiator system.
So it could have been oil.
Did I mention...
Did I mention that I had a leaky roof?
Did I tell you about this?
Yeah, a couple weeks ago, I forgot to mention it.
Yeah, okay, oh shit, my headphones just got unplugged.
Yeah, a couple, like two weeks ago,
my ceiling in my shitty apartment, it's made of those...
You know, in an office building,
the ceiling might be made of corrugated rectangular tiles
that just kind of fit together.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, a little bit.
Yeah, my roof is made of these corrugated cardboard-y tiles.
Cardboard?
I don't know if they're not actually cardboard,
they're stiffer than that, but they're these cheap tiles.
And one of them over my radiator has kind of a brown stain on it.
Well, and it's sort of bowed out.
Well, from that brown stain bowed out area,
one day I just started hearing a tip, tip, tip, and I look over and yep,
there's just water dripping out of the tile in my ceiling.
So I'm like, oh god, oh my god.
And I put my trash can under it to collect the water.
And I am like, what do I do?
At first I was like, you know what,
maybe I'll just hope that it will go away.
So for one day I waited and was just like,
maybe it just won't happen again.
I think, I actually think, and this is not something I'm sure of,
but I think one time I went, I think I was drunk, I was kind of drunk,
I came home, I woke up, and my face was kind of wet,
and I was like, and my pillow was kind of wet,
and I was like, did I spill something on my pillow?
And in hindsight, I think that maybe the ceiling was dripping on my face,
and I just didn't notice.
Because it was pretty close to where my bed was at the time.
Fortunately, the water was not, it was not like sewage or anything,
it did not smell bad or anything, it smelled like nothing.
So a day went by and it kept dripping,
and I'm like, oh god, fuck, I have to call my shitty fucking landlord,
my psycho landlord, who was a fucking slumlord scam artist piece of shit.
So I call her, she's like, okay, I'll call the property manager.
That guy couldn't come that night, but he came the next day, he showed up,
and he took a look, and he figured out it was like the radiator system
was like emitting steam, and the steam was condensing into this water,
and so he just had to like, he just had to like drain the pipe,
and he like tightened up some shit or whatever,
and now it works, it doesn't leak anymore.
So that's pretty cool.
I had to rearrange my room to keep my bed dry for that one night.
So, you know, it was pretty bad, pretty disgusting,
but not as bad as it could have been, a happy ending, I guess.
That's what happened.
Anyway, what was that, steam, leaky roofs, shitty apartments?
I don't remember what the point of that story was.
You said something about lifting and then gas.
Yeah, oh right, the poison gas, I got paranoid.
I get paranoid about carbon monoxide poisoning while I'm asleep,
so I bought a carbon monoxide detector.
I actually had a carbon monoxide detector, but it was kind of broken,
and I think like a battery that had been in it had leaked or something,
so I wasn't confident that it still worked, so I replaced it,
and now I'm good.
It is reading zero right now.
It has been reading zero the entire time since I installed it,
so your boy is safe from suffocation.
Don't worry, it's gonna be okay.
Hooray, hooray.
There's a boiler in my room.
It's behind a cabinet.
Yeah, there's a boiler in my kitchen.
I also am scared of carbon monoxide, and I've been a little short of breath,
not like all the time, but only during the night
when I have my door closed and the window closed,
and I think there's just not a lot of ventilation.
I feel like if it's not carbon monoxide, it doesn't seem to be.
It's carbon dioxide that I'm breathing out into a room that isn't getting any fresh oxygen.
I feel like if I don't open a window a little bit,
I'm gonna fucking die.
I'm gonna suffocate.
I have the same fear sometimes.
It's probably unfounded, at the probably won't happen,
but I get it.
It's like the slight lightheadedness that I can't exactly determine
whether it's sleepiness or lack of oxygen.
And lack of oxygen is the scariest thing,
because lack of oxygen, you just sort of slow down and stop.
And once you've stopped, would you ever be able to get out
if somebody doesn't open the door?
If I'm unconscious, I am completely vulnerable.
Yes, yes, true.
Even though it's winter, I have to keep a window open just a little bit,
which means it's really cold outside of the duvet.
Otherwise, it just doesn't feel right.
Makes, yeah.
I still have my air conditioner in the window,
even though it's definitely too cold for that now.
Also, kind of, yeah, for the same reason,
I don't want to be like I'm sealed in here.
It sort of gives a little bit of air flow,
but it's limited air flow, because it's not just like a hole.
I don't even know if it does allow air through, actually.
It might just be a mental thing.
I feel like it provides ventilation, whether it does or not.
I got new curtains.
I had no curtains, and I'm on the ground floor,
and I have two big windows, so I had no privacy.
I just tacked up a bed sheet over most of my windows,
and I put some pieces of cardboard, literal cardboard up.
I stood them up on top of the hung bed sheet,
just resting on top of it to cover up the rest of the windows.
I bought some actual curtains,
but the curtains that I bought, they got here,
and they were, because I didn't want blackout curtains,
because I want the natural light to wake me up,
to maintain a certain amount of regular sleeping schedule.
I got these thin curtains, but they were so thin
that they were completely see-through, completely transparent.
They didn't obscure anything.
So I bought another sheer curtain,
and I was like, if I just put two on top of each other,
that will obscure things.
No, it wasn't enough.
Even with both on top of each other still transparent.
So I'm like, okay, okay.
I will buy a thicker curtain, and I did.
So now I have all three of them stacked on top of each other,
and I think that maybe all three stacked on top of each other,
I think it's not quite enough to...
I think it's mostly enough to obscure me from the outside,
but also it blocks more of the light than I wanted to block,
because I want that natural light, and now I'm...
The bedsheet, the bedsheet let all the light in,
and completely obscured the view.
So the bedsheet was literally the perfect solution.
Why can't a curtain just be made of the same sheet as my bedsheet?
It did everything I wanted it to do.
Problems upon problems for me.
Wait, how...
In your apartment, I forget.
Are you in the one up stairs?
No, I'm on the first floor.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The low down where the people could just walk right by your window.
Yeah, okay, I can understand that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
See, if I was up on a second floor,
I usually wouldn't really worry too much about people looking up.
Oh, no, like, people can just...
I mean, cars pull into my driveway, right?
Like, it's at the level where if a person pulled into my driveway
and parked in front of my house,
their eye level would be exactly at the level of my windows.
They would be looking directly into my room.
So, yeah, I have to have something.
What a weird window.
Ah, but it's just a weird...
It's just a weird location relative to the outside.
Oh, well, it's fine.
Yeah, the room came with...
It had, like, metal bars.
It had these bars over the window.
Supposedly, it's some kind of, like, an anti-breaking measure.
But I was like, well, I need an air conditioner.
It's hot. It's still summer when I moved in.
So I had to get the guy to just take the bars off.
So, you know, now I'm vulnerable.
Now anyone can just climb in my window.
It doesn't even matter.
I'm sure those tiny, those tiny, thin little metal bars
would have stopped someone before.
Um, yeah.
They would go up to the window,
see the Bensaint lives there and say,
ah, man.
Ah, nothing, there's nothing here.
No reason.
Yeah, I hope so.
Unless they want Road to Radcon.
Then they'd smash it.
Yeah, they would steal my, like, 50 leftover copies of Road to Radcon.
Oh, I could sell those for $15 a copy.
Oh, damn, yeah.
Uh, please buy my extra copies of Road to Radcon.
Uh, please DM me on Discord or Twitter
or just PayPal me.
Arigato.
Okay.
Um, right.
So on the subject of selling stuff,
I, okay, I'm still not ready to publicly announce
what my little side project,
aside from Phantom's Revenge, is.
But, um, without getting into two specifics,
I will say that, uh, it's coming along.
It's, it's getting, it's getting ready to be public.
But I had a, one of the, I can't say what it is,
an item, an item that I needed to do it.
Uh, I got a new one, and then it broke immediately.
It broke, like, instantly.
And, uh, I am trying to negotiate for a refund on that.
Progress is held up for a moment
because I really don't want to buy a new one,
and I really don't think I should have to buy a new one.
And I really don't think anyone should have to pay for this,
except for the manufacturer who gave me a product
that just broke instantly.
But I, they are being, uh, annoying.
And I, I don't, just don't, I just,
just doesn't seem right.
Just, it just doesn't seem right.
It's just the principle of the thing.
Um, so I'm just trying.
Do they just not have a refund policy?
Uh, I don't exactly know.
It's, uh, the, it's not clear at the moment to me.
Uh, uh, uh, yeah, that's all you can really say about it.
Uh, but very, but very annoying.
Hold on.
I'm, I'm, I have to, quick, I have to extract some files.
I have to extract some.
This is part of the whole thing.
This is, these are the files.
This is, this is the work that my man Slobodan,
I got, I got a guy, I got a guy from Serbia named Slobodan
to work on this for me.
He's, he's done, he's done great work.
So let's see the clues are an item that breaks instantly sometimes.
A Serbian man.
Slobodan.
You know a guy.
Not just any Serbian guy.
Slobodan.
I told, I told Slobodan, I explained to Slobodan what I needed from him.
And he responded, he responded with a smiley face and said,
Okie dokie.
I love Slobodan.
So.
Okie dokie.
Slobodan and digital files.
I wonder what it could be.
There are, there are in fact digital file.
There are, there is digital, there is digital work afoot here.
We're living in the digital age.
Sad.
Sad but true.
That means it's not even interesting.
It means it's normal.
Then saying, how could you dare do something normal?
Unfortunately.
Yes, it is.
It's just normal.
It's just some normal shit.
Okay.
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
Well, less, less I be tempted to spill the beans.
I might, since, since it's going to be a thing that I'm going to have to sell because
I'm spending money to make it.
I might not announce it until January.
I might not announce it until after New Year's.
Strictly because, like, if I'm selling it for money, I want it to be in the New Year
because of, for tax reasons.
Because I think, because I think I'll be taxed more heavily on it if I sell shit this year
than if I sell, wait till next year.
And it's only like a month away, so I might, I might do that.
And it might not even be ready until then anyway.
I've got to do my tax return for January.
God damn.
I just, I just finished my taxes.
I just got my taxes, like, filed for 2020 because, like, I filed for all these extensions.
But they finally ran out and I had to do it.
I think I still owe my, I filed the returns.
I think I still owe the federal government, but I paid my state taxes.
It wasn't as, it wasn't as, I found some, I found some loopholes.
I found some, like, I found some, what's the word, some, some, like, tax breaks for, like, certain categories of things.
Like, I qualified for some, for some breaks that I didn't think I was going to cat, cat, kit, qualify for.
So it wasn't as bad as I expected.
Yes!
Yeah.
Based.
Oh yeah.
I've just realized, Lord of Ghosts income, I'm going to have to, like, to figure out how to do the taxes on that.
Because I haven't been able to buy all of that.
Like, a lot of the cost is postage.
But if I don't have all the things ready to send by the end of the year,
and I don't start posting them, I can't put that on my taxes as, like, money spent for business or whatever.
Oh yeah.
Oh no!
I mean, you could buy, you could, like, buy stamps ahead of time.
Yeah, yeah, I could, I could do all that.
It's just, I'm really stressing out.
I'm stressing out about a lot of things, but it's mostly just the Lord of Ghosts Kickstarter, everything around that.
And then the needing to do it before the end of the year, and now the taxes are like, oh yeah, that's also a thing.
I should try to get it done by the end of the year.
I'm still waiting on a few people to get the ghost stories finished.
Yeah.
But unfortunately, Kazi is sick right now, so they can't draw.
Why can't you draw when you're sick?
Well, they, I don't know.
They just said they'd try to get better first.
I thought they were, like, done.
I don't, they said, like, two of the pages are basically done, and then there's two others that they're working on at the same time.
And then just recently they got sick, so what would it, and there's-
They're sick for like two days.
Whatever.
I don't want to be, like, angry at anyone.
I do.
Because it's, it's, it's like...
Mm-hmm, gone, gone.
Well, it's not like I gave them a deadline.
I said I would like it to be done, but, you know, take your time, because I've got a lot of other things to do.
I've got the plushies to be made, and that's really the thing I thought was going to take the longest.
But now I have all the plushies, and I need to do a little, like, test prints on, like, the, how to figure out the green on the Redman comic,
but then I can print those, and then everything will be ready as long as I have the Lord of Ghosts themselves,
and then I've got to do the signing, and I've got to do the doodles,
and I've got to get a bunch of envelopes and packages and figure out the, do the Kickstarter, like, send out a request for addresses,
and then all the people have to be prompt with that, and it's like, oh my god, everything's going to go wrong.
I just feel it.
True.
And I don't like that.
That's upsetting.
Yeah, I was asking you about shipping, because this thing that I'm working on is something that I would have to ship,
and I was looking into, okay, so the Road to Radcon are books.
That's paper.
I can put those in an envelope and mail them as a letter, so that keeps the costs down significantly.
The pins.
I kind of cheated with mailing the pins.
I put them in an envelope, and I sent them as letters, and it probably shouldn't have counted,
but I got away with sending most of them as letters in the mail instead of as packages, so that also kept the costs.
I mean, it was higher because some of those were sort of heavy, but yeah, that kept the costs down.
This thing that I want to sell soon is, I don't think I'm going to be able to send it as a letter.
I think it's going to have to be sent as a package, which is not so bad for domestic shipping,
but internationally is pretty bad.
I was looking around, and I got really scared, because I was picking worst case scenario.
What's the worst country that I would have to send something to to find out what's the upper limit of how much this shipping is going to cost?
Australia.
Okay, Google, how much is it going to cost me to ship a small four ounce package to Australia?
$116.
And I'm like, are you fucking shitting me?
Are you fucking kidding me?
That doesn't make any sense.
I know it would be expensive, but like $100.
There was a reason.
The reason is that apparently, first class is what you call just normal send a package for cheap.
So normal first class shipping to Australia and New Zealand and maybe a couple other countries is just suspended right now because of COVID for some reason.
So yeah, it's just that they don't offer normal shipping to Australia at the moment.
So I would have to go with some other like priority mail that is like rush delivery costs $100, right?
So that's why.
And it turned out that shipping to other countries was not as bad as I thought.
It's kind of bad.
It's going to be like 15 bucks to ship to basically any other country.
A few countries might be a little more like Brazil was $19 for some reason, but like 15 up to maybe 20 seems to be.
So I would probably just charge like $15 shipping, which is less than I thought, but it's it sucks.
But like if that's I think that's the best I can do.
Yeah, so that's why that's why I was asking you about the shipping stuff.
Yeah, it turned out not to be it turned out not to be as bad as I thought.
A lot of ghosts is like hundred pages.
It's not going to be an envelope.
It's going to be at least a large envelope.
A large envelope or like if it's got a plush, it's going to be a box, small box.
And all of the ones that have the comic have the red man comics that makes it even thicker.
So, oh, everything's going to go wrong.
Yeah.
Man, after this never again.
Never will I ever do shipping of any kind.
You know, after I did the first I think after I did the first Vapors, I found myself being like this was so hard.
Like this Kickstarter was really difficult and it and it was not quick and easy.
And I like for months I was still fulfilling orders and I was like, this is so hard.
This totally wasn't worth it.
But like I've done more of that thing and I think I have.
I think I don't really mind it.
I think I don't mind the work of like, you know, addressing envelopes, going to the post office, putting them in the mail.
I think it's it's work and it takes a while, but I don't think I mind it that much.
And it like this kind of thing selling like selling physical products makes money more easily than like, I don't know.
Then then like, you know, donations online, right?
It's just kind of a.
I feel like it's a model that works pretty well.
And so I think I have decided that I don't mind it and I might continue to do this sort of thing into the future.
I'm just it's because it's the first time doing such a big thing.
And it's I'm I'm just stressed out.
I'm nervous.
Yeah.
I made sure I feel like I made sure to be like extra.
Like, like what do you call it, a margin of error, margin of too much money for shipping?
Yes, yes.
When I came up with all the original things.
But if the shipping in general is just more expensive now, I don't know that that's going to cover it.
Fuck.
Well, I got to do it, but I might cry.
I might cry about it.
The stakes, the stakes are.
Well, I'll do it either way.
It's just a question of whether I cry doing it or not.
It's a question of how much like tier like the volume of tears, how much you would displace in a cup.
And don't don't cry too much because tears are heavy.
And so they'll add weight to the packages and they'll make it cost more of a ship.
So I'll I'll ship them to myself.
I won't need I won't.
Tears are extra.
Yeah.
Speaking of stuff, I showed you the Edward Edward D. Al's progress on the Radcon for dojin.
Yes.
Which I'm sure I say this all the time.
I'm sure everyone believes that that's vaporware and will never materialize, but it will.
Edward is maybe not quite halfway done drawing it.
Thereabouts, something like that.
It looks really good.
I'm looking at a sample page right now.
It looks great.
Yes.
I'm going to be I wasn't going to do this, but I think I am going to I'm going to print I'm going to print some copies.
I'm going to I'm going to offer print copies to anyone that wants to buy them in the same way that I'm offering a road to Radcon to people.
Because maybe it could be a double a bonus.
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do it like dojin get a free road to Radcon or slightly more like a discounted road to Radcon.
I gave anyone who was a PCP patron five dollars off of road to Radcon.
I think I will with with with the dojin.
I think I'll say like you get five dollars off the dojin if you either are a five dollar patron or you bought road to Radcon.
So that like if you were to buy both and you were a patron, you would get like a total of ten dollars.
You get five dollars off one and five dollars off the other.
Right.
I think it'll be the same because I don't want to do it that like, oh, if you're a patron, like if you're a patron and you bought road to Radcon, you got five dollars off the first the road to Radcon and now you get both stacked for ten dollars off.
The dojin so 50.
I don't want to give that much.
I want to give that much of a discount.
I want to give ten dollars across both books.
That seems fair to me.
Yeah.
Anyway, it's it looks good.
Edward, I want to say Edward's work looks really great and I can't wait for the final product, but he did annoy me a little bit by kind of disappearing for a while.
I was a bit worried that he was just gone and I would not be hearing from him again, but I was wrong.
He did eventually get back to me with the progress on the comic.
So it's all it's all good.
Yeah.
He seems to be working on it again.
Funny, funny shit.
Yeah.
It would have been pretty funny, though, if like he just he just disappeared.
He was like, well, I started it, but goodbye.
No, no, not what happens.
Lamal.
Well, we're coming up to the ending of twenty twenty one and the and the Radcon four stuff is still it's still coming out.
Not quite finished.
Told me Nate has been in Communicado lately.
I asked he told me as I told him Edward is getting the dojin done and he said that yes, he will work on getting the the OVA and the music video done.
And I have not heard anything about it from him about it since then.
So I don't know if he's been doing it.
I'm going to guess probably not.
But I hope he will do it because he said he would and we need him to.
Yeah.
I guess maybe I'll ask him again and say like, hey, so remember how I said the dojin is coming out?
Well, that's more true than ever.
So can we get those videos, please?
Just put a nice big bow on this whole Radcon four debacle.
Put it all behind us.
Have it all break break the curse.
Well, this is the only way to break the curse of Radcon four is to deliver on all the Kickstarter promises.
Just get that shit sorted.
Yes.
Yes, we're so close.
We're pretty we're pretty close.
We're pretty fucking close.
Should I release the should I post like a PDF version of Road to Radcon?
I suppose.
But then would people not want to get the physical version?
Well, they would.
I mean, I think everyone who is going to get a physical version has probably already gotten one.
Maybe a few people might see the PDF version and be like, oh, this is cool.
Maybe I do want to own a physical version.
I suppose it's not like that strange of an idea.
I think it could be worth it.
I think I had planned to maybe post a PDF version at the same time that I posted the dojin.
Whenever that happens, I don't know.
And I guess I was yeah, right.
I keep meaning to ask Tom because I want to post I was going to post it on the website and I don't know how to do that.
I have not asked.
Oh, well.
Um.
Yeah.
In other news, I guess I'd been still working hard on the second secret project.
Wait, one more.
Would people be mad?
Would people who bought the physical book be like mad if that I posted the PDF version?
Would they be like, if I knew there was going to be a public PDF version, I wouldn't have bought this piece of junk.
Throws it against the wall.
Does anyone care about that?
Is that a concern?
I don't know.
I mean, people who bought it probably bought it because it's like an item, not because they wanted to read it.
Commenters, let me know.
Of course, they don't actually want to read it.
Commenters, it's more interesting as like a thing that they could be like, I have this.
Commenters, if you bought Road to Radcon, let me know in the comments whether you'll be annoyed.
If I post the PDF version on the website for people to read digitally.
Also, please buy more copies.
I have a box of 50 copies.
I don't need 50 copies of Road to Radcon.
Please, please take my extra stock.
Yeah.
Okay.
I guess that's all I have to say about that.
Oh, you were going to talk about your...
Well, you started talking about your secret project.
Yeah, it's really not because I can't talk about what it is.
But it's getting to the point where I'm a little worried that it may go into December, still not be ready.
And then...
Oh, I'm sure that my stock is going into December.
December will be like, oh, suddenly you got to do things like family.
No, I don't want to do all that, but I should.
I mean, you can't just ignore social gatherings entirely because then they'll have happened and then you're like,
I don't know how to speak to anyone anymore.
Yeah, the holidays always feel like a big thing.
I'm always trying to work on something and then it's always like,
I have to take like two or three days away from that to go do some bullshit,
go see my fucking aunts and uncles.
I hate my aunts and uncles.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't hate mine, but they're not friends of mine.
Yeah, I don't hate them, but I don't want to stop doing my shit to go and catch up with them.
Oh, how are you doing?
Oh, who got married this year?
Oh, that guy?
Okay, cool.
Oh, who had a kid?
Oh, that guy?
Oh, cool.
Wow, that's great.
I love that.
All right.
Oh, I love the, I love the, I love the Guam keys you made.
These Guam keys are just to die for.
Yeah.
Incredible old family recipe.
Okay.
Bye.
You just get that clip and then play that on your phone.
Yeah.
Instead of speaking to them.
That's all.
Like, ultimately, I enjoy the break because Christmas time alone, even if you get a lot
of work done, it feels hollow afterwards.
You're like, dang, the holidays are over and I didn't speak to anyone sucks.
Kind of.
I like to, I like to indulge in things I don't actually like.
And like Stockholm syndrome.
Like, I'm stuck with this family.
Absolutely.
Like drinking a bit and talking about nothing in particular and just saying hi.
Yeah.
That's not so bad.
Nah, you're right.
It's never as annoying as I think it's going to be.
Yeah.
I mean, I always think it's going to suck shit.
And then it usually only sucks a little bit.
Yeah.
Especially when I was younger, I would always hate the idea of it.
And then I'm there and I'm like, you know, there's chocolate.
There's like peanuts.
There's a dog.
You know, it's people saying hi and I don't have to do anything about it.
Yeah.
It's like, you know, this is fine.
Family is actually good.
If I'm at like a thing like that and I don't want to be there, it feels like an eternity.
It feels like I'm like, God, there's so many other things I could be doing.
There's so many things I could be doing with this time.
But then if I step back and think about it, I'm like, okay, that was maybe like six hours,
maybe 12 hours if I had to spend the whole day.
I waste 12 hours all the time, right?
12 hours comes and goes without even noticing all the time.
It's stupid to get bent out of shape about one day, right?
I waste most days of my life, frankly.
It's like I've never been to a social gathering with friends or family that has lasted longer than the longest streams I've done.
Yeah.
True.
That's right.
Yeah, I'll stream for like seven hours sometimes.
Yeah, you're right.
I think it's just sort of like a holdover.
When you go to those things in your young time, obviously feels like it takes longer.
Yeah.
At a place for two hours is like agonizing.
But two hours, even if you're bored, it's not that bad as an adult.
And also, we've got phones now, so we have an excuse to just distract ourselves with some bullshit.
Yeah, two hours is nothing.
Yeah, you're right.
And maybe it is.
It's just, I remember being bored as a kid and feeling like it was interminable.
But now, yeah, just goes by in a flash.
No problem.
Merry Christmas.
Yes.
Excellent.
Oh, did my files extract?
Oh, did my files?
I think they did.
I think my files extracted.
Let me check.
Yeah, essential oils.
Let me check on my, oh, did it?
There it is.
Ooh, that's a good file.
It's the right size, too.
Hmm, that's a great file right there.
Takes a extraction like no problem.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let me compare it to my other file.
Six, seven, six, eight.
Okay.
Ooh, very nice.
Very nice.
A sound of an accountant.
Well, that's me.
I'm I'm all about I'm all about adding up the numbers
True
Sure, I'm you know, that's that's the churning lifestyles. You got it. You got a key you got to get a count all your pennies
Stack them up
I'm stacking pennies some some people some people
Stack Benny's I'm over here stacking pennies
But all the same tease Ben Ben. Yes. Yes, exactly
And Benny's but it all gets us to the same place eventually just mine gets me there slower and I never get as far
I think my audio is really quiet for some reason my microphone is quiet
Eleazar you're probably gonna have to like increase my volume a bit. I don't know why I'm just quiet today. Sorry about that
Do do something about it?
I don't know man
Dog
What's up? Yeah, what were we talking about?
Well, I mean, I basically said everything. That's I've been working on the the secret project
Stressing out about the Lord of Ghosts. I've been playing fucking
Tower defense bloons. Oh god
And that's been fun. I've been putting monkeys down and they've been throwing darts
Putting monkeys down putting them down like dogs taking them out behind the shed
Ah
Duh-duh
Went on that one adventure
We talked about Michael Owen
Yeah, and yeah, that was like on the adventure. Remember all the all the memories remember all those times
remember remember those times where we
Came up with like the Michael wave as a dip as an alternative to the microwave
Michael Michael Owen. Yeah, the Michael wave
He waves his hand around food and it cooks it just like a microwave
But it's Michael Owen doing it and that was that was one of the many jokes
So we came up with as we were walking across Canterbury and the fields and the woodlands beyond and that was like
Yeah, what a story really not really good for a not a good for a podcast that one. It's kind of stupid
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah for real
That's true
Hey, there's this one farm that like had
We were looking on the the Google Maps and stuff and that was like a public footpath
That goes straight through this farm out into the woods and this farm did everything in its power
to imply that it is private land and you can't go there
and
it's all like
You like they didn't have
legal authority to kick you off because
The road like the driveway road through their main gate
It had to stay open
but they had loads of signs in
Red with bold white letters saying private property
So but it was a public road, right? You say it was a public road that just happened to go through a public footpath like
Like there's like sectioned off little places with
With signs wooden signs with arrows saying, you know, yellow triangle saying this way is the
Is the continuation of the of the public part that goes through forests
there's things like that all over Britain and
They sometimes go through farms, but farmers don't like it, but they can't really do anything about it
So they have to imply if they don't want people walking near their their buildings
They have to imply that it's so fucked up that you're here and we're gonna shout at you and shoot you if you
This is anything this this is not a place of honor
Nothing. Nothing is no great deed is esteemed here. You know what I'm talking about. Yeah. Yeah, I do not oh
There's a reference something the the
The the like thing about like like how would you how would you?
Denote a like like a toxic like radioactive place in a way that like would still be
Comprehensible like thousands of years later. I
Don't know. There's like
Hold on if I Google this is not a place of honor
Okay, yeah, the Wikipedia long-time nuclear waste warning messages
Hold on here. Yeah, here are some like think things that like this is just sort of like a theoretical
Idea of like how would we communicate?
Don't go here to like future generations
It's like what would we want to evoke and some of the the phrases are like this place is not a place of honor
No highly esteemed deed is commemorated here. Nothing valued is here. What is here was dangerous and repulsive to us
This message is a warning about danger
The danger is to the body and it can kill the form of the danger is an emanation of energy
and
Like yeah, the idea was like maybe they were like maybe we could maybe we cover the entire like
Surrounding like square kilometer with like, you know giant spikes
We just like cover it and like Giants like wooden spikes to just be like this place will kill you don't come here. It's deadly
I don't know so that they do that is what I'm saying
The sign with all that language on it seems like oh thousands of years later
Surely the language would be
Changed. I I think I think the idea is that it would not literally say that in English. These are like
ideas that they want
To yeah, they want you not here's it yeah a 1993 report from the Sandia National laboratories
Aimed to communicate a series of messages non-linguistically to any future visitors to a waste site
It gave the following wording as an example of what those messages should evoke
right hmm
The end you're is unleashed only within danger is unleashed only if you substantially disturb this place physically
This place is best shun and left uninhabited
Oh
We would know this is good this place is a message and part of a system of messages pay attention to it
Sending this message was important to us. We considered ourselves to be a powerful culture
This place is not a place of honor, etc. Etc
I feel like no matter what very right
People will still curiously go there and die
Yeah
Probably because I guess the sign would then they would be like oh sign
Says something somebody died in maybe it's dangerous in yeah, I mean
There's always the chance that like no matter how strongly you try to convey like
This place is dangerous. Someone might get the idea like oh they want they want to keep me out
You know, they must be guarding something good
Right like they must want to do something valuable
They must they must hmm. This must be a place of lots of honor
There must be some extremely highly esteemed deeds commemorated here. There must be some very valuable things here
Otherwise why would they tell me that there aren't you know, what what are they hiding right?
They're scooby-doing it
They go the spooky scary guys saying
Get out of here so that I can steal the money
Yeah, you're scared away
You're right
Yeah, that is that is one way to interpret
Scooby-Doo as a verb is to do something scary to make people leave you alone
So you can get that you can reap the rewards so you can collect the insurance money or something
There's insurance money, there's
Buried gems or like a deed to a house is gonna expire and ownership is always some sort of thing like as long as people are scared
And they're gone then I'll have all this money. I gotta scare people truly we live truly capitalism sure is fucked up that it
Incentivizes like putting on a goblin costume and running around and scaring people
These are systems broken man
Fuck I was going to say so. Oh, yeah, isn't there maybe it's not in England. Maybe it's in like Wales or something
but isn't there some
policy of like
You're like anyone is allowed to walk anywhere
Or like like farm like anyone is allowed to walk on a farm even if it's private property like as long as they don't like
Take anything. I feel like there's some countries that have laws that are specific. America's not one of them
Yes, America's very get off my land
I
Think you that might be Scotland. There's a row of right to Rome. Yes
Yes, I think Norway also. I'm not sure if England does. I'm not sure if Wales does either
Okay, this is I feel like what wasn't that guy who like walked in a straight line across
The con the island. Yes across Wales or Scotland or England. It was across Wales
Yeah, maybe okay. Maybe that's why I was thinking Wales because I remembered that guy
Just walked but he probably had to trespass at some point. He did do another one where he attempted to cross Scotland in a straight line
Hell yeah, yeah
um
Okay, I just uh, I thought maybe
That was why the farmers can only imply
Yeah, well, I don't know. Um in England. It's it's a different thing. It's not you don't have the right to go on people's land
Yeah, um necessarily but there are
Built into the countryside
um
Like hard and fast like this needs to be accessible by foot
You need to be able to walk through these fields
To get to a river or whatever. There's just like a network of public footpaths
You have to be able you have to let people walk here
Um, the public owns these little walkways and things and they're signposted by councils or whatever
And farmers sometimes it they go straight straight through their land and nice farmers will make it very clear
They'll upkeep the sign saying this is the way you go and people generally walk on the edge of a field
Right to get to like a gate or a style to go into the next one and then it goes, you know this way and that way
It's like a curated little
series of paths
And I like it I
It was one of those things where I didn't I never really thought about it until I realized that not every country does that
Yeah, I mean
Got it just like gotta gotta have usually if there's a field if there's a farm and there's a field
Usually you're allowed to go through
some of it
I would hope so
It would be a bit shitty to let someone's private property impede, you know the public's ability to move about freely
In my opinion
Uh
Um, uh, you want to talk about you want to go to voicemails? Um, I'm out of stuff
What else happened?
Oh, there's kyle written house, but I don't really know anything about that still
Oh, well, I was I was
It was funny
I was listening back to last week's episode and I heard myself talking about kyle written house and how everyone
I follow on twitter said he was gonna get a full acquittal
And uh, I was right or they were right. Um, yeah
Even he even got off on charges that seem unambiguously true like illegal possession
Like he just he just did illegally possess the firearm like it's not even a question
But he just got off on the charge anyway
Yeah, that seems weird. I feel like
Like, uh, obviously they were pushing for guilty or nothing for to get him off
But like sure I feel like if you are in possession of a gun or you're you're an owner of a gun
You're in charge of this gun and this gun while in your possession
You know
You're kind of responsible for what it does you're responsible for what happens to some extent if it's a misfire
Or it's an accident, but two people end up dead
Or whatever. Yeah, I feel like at the very least there should be should be like
A fine and like a removal of gun rights for a certain period of time
Well, there's a very bare minimum something like that. Well the fact that nothing happens is a bit well the the um
There will be the okay. I I am genuinely
shocked and befuddled that like
None of the charges stuck that I was pretty sure he would get off on the murder charges
But I thought there was no way he was dodging, you know
Illegal possession illegal open carry that kind of stuff, but he did somehow which is very weird
um
But uh, you know, none of the criminal charges stuck
But like there's still civil suits to be filed like the family like the families of like the victims and uh other people are gonna
Be like they're gonna be in court for like damages and stuff, right? So like it's not
Not it's not nothing is gonna happen. Nothing criminal is gonna happen. He's gonna have to deal with this for a long time, which is good
But of course right-wing psychopaths will like pay all his bills for him and raise money for him to cover anything he gets sued for so
uh, whatever
Yeah, um
Anyway, right so everything everything I was saying would probably happen with kyle did last week. So
Uh funny funny shit
Love it
That's depressing that's pretty depressing. I guess that's just the the news there's not really much else I can think of
funny funny funny funny thing, um
Friend friend of the show spiral the guy who was compiling the n-word counter
For the pcp he's going through every episode and keep in count for all everyone
Uh, he he asked me to help him with a school assignment. It was very funny
He I guess he had to like interview people about times things went wrong. This is how he described
This is how he described the assignment to me
So he asked me if he would he could ask me some questions and I was like sure
So he did a voice call and he asked me about he asked me about like uh the falling out with trixie
That was what he what he wanted to me to talk about
So I I he asked me a bunch of stuff about that and I just gave him some sound bites about it. Uh
I guess I just thought that was funny
Um, it's something I'm always down to talk about um as I continue to see and cope with rage
Uh at all times
Yes, about that. Yes
Speaking of of of that then did you know that the streak?
The streak was broken last episode
A few people pointed it out. Yeah, I read a voicemail
The title that had the n word in it the soft with the soft a though, but uh, yes, I know it's it's still
It's still the n word. I I I do have that in in my head. I'm like, yeah, it's okay if it's the a but like
Why is there a discrepancy? Why is there a difference in the first place? It's really just to get away with it
There's no reason that's used. I said it
I said it. I realized after I was like, oh jeez. I said it lull. Uh, I mean I was reading the voicemail
Uh, I don't know. I've said it before
Uh, I don't know. I'll just say it again. I'll just I don't know it it's it's not it's not I mean it's a dark day
It's a dark day
It's sad. Let's let's let's face facts. It's not the first time it's happened on this show
Uh, oh well
What's what can you do? What can you do?
Uh, what can you do but say you're welcome?
Let's say what can you do? What what can you do but pledge to patreon.com slash the procrastinators?
Uh
For for for all for all our freedom of speech. We're we're all about free speech here
Uh, fuck your feelings
Um
Don't censor me. Uh, don't tread on me. Uh
Okay, that's it
clipped
voicemail
Yes, okay. Do you got we're sorry. We're sorry about the n-word. We please please restart the the streak and and count from now
To zero yes
Zero it has been zero it has been zero episodes since the n-word was added
Um, okay, let's let's get uh, let's let's get these goddamn messages
Uh, looks like the first one this week is called digimon ghost game. You ready?
Uh
Yes, yes, okay
Get digimon ghost game three two one go
In the slim chance at tom is on this one. What are your thoughts on digimon ghost game?
If he's not on then uh, what are your thoughts on digimon ghost game?
Never seen it
Give
Digimon ghost game
I know I hardly knew is that a new one. I've never heard of it
digimon go
Digimon ghost game
Ninth anime series in the digimon franchise
Uh, oh, oh, yeah, it's it's running right now. It's current. So I have no idea. I have no idea
Is it like squid game but different?
Yes
Did you watch squid squid game?
No, I've seen the some of the character designs and I was like, yeah, it looks pretty good
Yeah, oh, I saw the why I saw yms's review of it
He thought it was pretty good. I turned that off because I didn't want to be spoiled because I
I didn't one of those
I didn't care about one of those things that probably would like to know about
Yeah, I was like, yeah, fuck it
Okay, next one is called a question three two one go
Hey Ben you talked about a book with a guy trying to write the perfect sentence
If you remember the name of the book, I can be free of one of my brain worms also. Fuck Trixie
yes
uh easy actually
I mentioned the book
I would be should I could be a real shitter and say that the book in question is one that I mentioned on the last episode
Uh
But I won't do that. I won't make you go back and listen to it. Yeah, the book is the plague by camu
It's not like a main plot point. It's just what it's just kind of a side
Uh bit in in this sort of sort of a side story in that book
The guy who wants to write the perfect sentence and what is he the one he comes up with like
one
One it's like one one fine. I mean this doesn't translate perfectly because the original book was in french. I think
Like one fine day in may
A lovely young woman
Writing a black sorrel mare strolled down the boo de boo yon
Something like that. And I don't know if I'm pronouncing that name correctly
Um, it's the plague by camu
Um, next one is called Alaskan weeb to gibb re kino's journey
three two one go
All right gib so for kino's journey, whether you want to finish it or not
If you're looking for some sort of big payoff at at the end where it all comes together and goes full circle
You're not going to get that neither the original version of kino's journey nor the
2018 I want to say version of kino's journey
Has some big payoff at the end. What are you what you're getting in the first three four episodes?
That's what it keeps what it keeps being. It's good. I recommend it
It's one of my favorites, but you're not going to get a massive payoff at the end
So bear that in mind if you're just say deciding on whether to finish it or not
wait
They remade kino's journey in 2018
I had no idea
When I gul that I only found the like 2003 or whatever it whenever it was version
I think it wikipedia says it was it started in 2000
Yeah, um
the first episode of kino's journey is like
It's a backdrop of some sort of melancholic
like
Not really dystopia, but kind of dystopia-esque future
And and this kid
and a bike
are driving around and they're having deep conversations about philosophy and humanity and
I
Yeah, if that's the entire show, I don't know whether I'd want to watch all of it because
I feel like it's the sort of thing that I would have found deep if I was younger listening to them talk about it
I'm like, yeah, I've thought about this stuff before that. This is like teenager. Shit. It's not exactly like low brown
um, but it's
It's
Not would you say it's not that interesting. Would you say it's I'm 14 and this is deep?
I would say it's approaching that that's a bit of a that's a bit of a derogative way to put it
Yeah, it's it's not that like dumb
smart if you know what I mean is it's just sort of like
Are they going to is this going to actually
Interest me as an adult or is it the sort of thing?
That is good when you're younger and you haven't thought about what if
What about the the reason religion exists?
Like I've thought of that
That's old news. Yeah
Yes, I
I watched I think I mentioned that I watched a few episodes of it
I must have seen the old version because yeah, there is a new version called kino's journey the beautiful world
Uh, I didn't know they remade it. I guess they did
Yeah, I watched some of the old one, but I never like finished it and I guess that's fine because I guess it doesn't really have like
An ending so okay
I'm gonna watch a few more episodes. Do you ever watch do you ever watch high bonnet renme?
No, I've heard that name. What is it? It's another
It reminds me of kino's journey and it's like in its tone
It's another one that I kind of think doesn't really
Have much of I mean it has a story and it has some lore
It's about these like girls in like a village, but like the girl they grow
Like wings they grow like wings and halos
And it's just like
I don't even remember
They're just kind of like living they're just kind of like living in this little commune village
and just hanging out
And they just go through this weird like oh sometimes we grow wings and halos
But it's fine and we're just uh
I think it might be some kind of like oh some of us are actually like dead and we got to like deal with like
The trauma of like our life. I genuinely don't remember whether the twist is like they were dead all along or not
I genuinely don't remember if that twist ever comes
Uh, I remember thinking it was probably coming
um
But it's like you know, and then it's just kind of a sort of meandering sort of
calm
Sort of like let's just kind of talk about life man sort of anime
Yeah, yeah with a with a muted color palette
That's a weed smoking show
That's a calm weed smoking show. Maybe yeah, maybe a weed smoking show
Uh
High bonnet ran me is a bit somber for weed smoking
Well, I don't know I haven't seen it but like you know, it's journey. I feel like is yeah
Perhaps perhaps smoking weed and driving no motorbike
What more could you ask for?
um
Next next voicemail is not a voicemail. It's just a question. Do you enjoy making pcp content?
I mean the only the only real
Content we make now would be the podcast and yeah, I enjoy recording the podcast
I enjoy it being a thing
It's like ben sain and I like talking up to ben sain and it's like that's easy
I like talking to you too give
If I if I didn't I probably wouldn't still be doing it
um
If you mean okay in terms of I guess the radcon stuff is
Still is pcp content which I have been you know having get made for a while I
I
I feel a certain sense of
I feel a sort of uh
Yeah, I think I do even though you might think oh my god
It's been like a year and a half almost two years since this fucking radcon thing happened and I'm still working on it
It doesn't bother me
I just feel a sense of like anticipation of like boy. I can't wait
I can't wait until it's done and everything's done and I can look back and I say
Yeah, it took me two years, but I did it. We did it
Uh, uh, uh, uh, fuck fuck everyone that said we weren't gonna do it. I did everything
Um, every everything that I had everything that had to be finished was and I know that that day is coming
and uh, it makes me
Happy so it's not yeah, I guess I do enjoy it in that I enjoy in sort of the sense of a job well done
Not in terms of like, oh, this is fun. I'm having fun right now
Um, because I mean most of that stuff is yeah
Like um, the fact that it isn't done. I am not enjoying. Um, but like yeah same as
Getting it done is not like something I dislike
It's just a lot of work. Hey having it not
Done is a is a source of unenjoyment
And I would consider I would consider the removal of unenjoyment to be a form of enjoyment
Which I will derive from
the completion of
Radcon
Yes, and even just in general like pcp content
is
largely
fun
And not really work because if it was
Then we would have tried harder to like push the algorithm and do things more
And all of us knew like at any point
We're just like just making things that we kind of were interested in
Damn the algorithm damn large success
Yeah, there came a point there came a point where I think we all kind of were just like
There's not like
The pcp is not meant to
Be like an algorithm appealing
Yeah thing. This is not designed to you know catch catch fire and go viral, right?
Uh, yeah
Uh next
Let's do it. I'll do it out of love. We do it out of love
I do it for you the viewer because I love you
Yes
The next voicemail is janes three two one go
Ben saying you mentioned the golden girls a couple of times throughout the pcp
And it reminded me of this youtube video called golden girls buys a dangin rompa class trial
I think it's the most that any zoomers on the internet would have watched of the show
But I am curious how you came across the golden girls
Because I don't imagine you as the type of person to ever watch a sitcom
golden girls
buys a
Golden girls buys a high bump not high bonnet rend me a dangin rompa trial. That sounds really funny
um
I
That's funny that you think i'm not a sitcom. I mean I did watch sitcoms as a
Kid. I mean the simpsons is is a sitcom. I watched so much of that. You know, I watched seinfeld
uh, I watched uh
You watched a fresh principale
A little bit a little bit
That was my main one aside from simpsons. I guess
Uh, I mean I I mean when I was a kid kid. I watched, you know, I would watch like full house and and uh
Step by step
Wait, is that a is that a show step by step, right?
I don't know family, you know family matters. I was an I was an urkel fan. I guess for a while
Um, I remember one called my wife and kids
I've never heard of that one
It's yeah, it was more modern
Then but like 10 years ago. Uh, yeah
The hell when when was that step by step is a sitcom um, but I
But I did not watch golden girls as a kid. No, uh, the the the answer to that question is that my my uh,
My ex-girlfriend was a big fan and she got me to uh
She got me to watch the the entire series with her
Uh, and uh, you know what? I don't even regret it because I mostly enjoyed it. I thought it was a pretty pretty good series
Uh, had some had some memorable moments that I continue to
Bring up in conversation
Uh to this day mostly the the one about uh, uh dorothy
Having the like the chronic fatigue disorder and not being able to find a doctor that would like, uh
That would diagnose her
That one really stuck with me
Uh
I don't know that's a pretty good show
I don't know if I would recommend watching the whole fucking series. I don't know if it's worth that
That's pretty enjoyable for what it is
Uh, rose and rose is rose's best girl, of course
Blanche's worst girl obviously
Do they wear my my my ex like blanche so so, you know, that's why I got a pick first girl. Fuck. Fuck blanche
Yeah, well
Blanche blanche is the worst though blanche is very obnoxious
But I mean obviously like that's on purpose right she's supposed to be kind of a snooty
snooty southern bell rich girl
Oh, now I want to watch it. Oh really?
I love snooty rich girls in media. That's my favorite. Uh, I don't know if you would like
You know what golden girls is about right?
Uh old women. Yes. Okay. As long as you as long as you realize that these are old women we're talking about
Well, uh, you know
I
Risk is gonna get old one day. She's gonna be in a home
I mean, yeah, I honestly give it a shot. Give it a shot. You might like golden girls. I did
Yeah, I I it's hard to imagine that it would be good because I I always thought of it as like
Because they're old
characters
The show must be very old and therefore bad
It's like it's before it's before jokes and were invented
But no, believe it or not believe it or not the show like the just the older the characters are the older the show is
Just like that's that's my head just goes to 100 years ago everybody who acted in on tv was like ancient
It was like a hundred years old
It was like a prestigious position. You had to work your way up before you could act
Uh
Minimum of 80
You would you would you would probably like rose but for me rose is best girl and I I feel I feel like that's pretty
Commenters, let me know in the comments if rose is best girl or if you who's who's best girl, right?
Rose is like the funny one rose is like the pinky pie
Uh, what about fucking garenet? What about no the worst golden girl?
um
Wait gold's not even a gold's not even a jewel gold's not even a jam
New new show but the girls are made of minerals golden girl. It's she's
She's made of molten metal
There's there's fools golden girl
That's blanche for sure
Uh
Yes, so that's the story of why I watched golden girls
Uh, next one is called a keyblade spirit. She hurt three two one go
Holy fucking shit
Oh my fucking god get to the point. I'm a fucking girl
anyway
I'm establishing the consortium of gibhuggers to combat the nate fuckers
I uh
I hope you don't join
Bye
Did we
I feel like we didn't comment. Yeah, it was this week that nate released a video
Tempting many off the path of righteousness and causing them to fail no nate november. Oh, that's true
Yeah, I I hadn't gotten around to it and then people mentioned that and I was like, oh, that's true
I've got a whole true to my roots to my
To my cause the delta rune video. I would I would describe the delta rune video as the 9 11 of no nate november
Uh, it was just catastrophic
I did not watch the video because I do not want delta rune spoilers because i'm still going to play uh
Part two at some point
I haven't gotten around to it, but it definitely will happen first phantom's revenge or delta rune
Genuinely, I might finish phantom's revenge first because like I why would I play another video game when I should be making one?
I actually that's might actually be what happens
um
I guess I approve of the gib the consortium of gibhuggers gibhuggers. It's pretty good
It's pretty good
Which is better is is a consortium better than a league?
uh, well
I wonder what the the etymology of those are consortium
Is like everyone's consorting together. Yeah, I feel like a consortium is just a bunch of people that's like a military thing or like a
A measurement of distance
Lee league really used as a military thing league really feels like it's a group of people that have gotten together to do something
Consortium feels like it's a bunch of people that have gotten together to talk about something
So maybe the hugging of gibb is gonna make remain mostly theoretical
They're just gonna talk about the heart of gibhuggers. Think about what if they did
battalion
uh
The battalion the legion
I like le I like legion it kind of sounds like league but more violent
Yes, like roam roam roam like roam
Next next voicemail is not a voicemail. It is an image. So here here it is. Let's see what we got
uh
Okay
What is
So we so we've got
We've got a whole all right, so ben saint in the middle here
Can I just have just had a little phone session with my dad about the rise of american fascism? I feel better
Maybe it'll be okay. Oh, I see vermark performing nazi salute. I don't know why i'm connected to that
But okay, this is a dab the so-called dad. Oh the so-called dab. Oh
Okay, these that string should go from me to the dab to the vermark salute. Okay. That's fucked up slime corp israeli flag
Jew jewies. Oh, not jew. Oh, okay. This is a
nuzla nuzla conquest of a hat looks like a nazi hat. Oh
destroy israel
No
Damn this makes me really got gut. This makes me rethink everything
It's just it's all true. I like I like it's all I guess I mean, it's all it's all right here in black and white
I like that he used the picture. Maybe that's the best
Picture of me dabbing is me at the the rfck lecture
It's a pretty it's a pretty good picture of me dabbing. That's really great. I love that. I'm in like the dark hood
Uh, I love this I approve of this 100% and
You know what? I just said the n word too. So it all it all comes together lamel. Oh god, ben
It's bad. I'm gonna have to put you down. I'm backsliding
Next next image is uh another image. Here we go
Oh
Geez
Oh geez rick. It's true. It's true. It's ben saint going. Uh, what was I talking about?
I say it all the time on the hit podcast the procrastinators
Was I
Did I was it before we started recording today that I mentioned to you that I was listening back to last episode and I was
A bit disgusted with how much I go uh and uh and pause and that was before the episode started
I was I was noticing it really bad last episode. I've been trying to not do it as much this and repeating myself
starting a sentence with uh
And then a pause and then
Start the sentence. Oh, so I realized uh, okay. So I realized that what I all right
So I think I realized and repeat the start three two or three times while I like think of what I'm actually going to say
In the sentence. It's a bit of a cheat that I
Uh uses a crutch. I think sometimes
Anyway, stay quiet. Actually. No, that's not true. I also do a bit of like
um, yeah
Well, I what I do is I I'm doing it right now
So I don't exactly know where I'm going
but I leave long ish pauses for me to
Find the words that I need to use
Yes, yes
It was weird thinking about that as I was saying it and I'm doing it
Um
Okay
Next voicemail is called paying people to unsub Trixie
three two one go
Ben, how dare you
affect Trixie's livelihood like affecting someone economically is just going too far
Absolutely. You're just like the union during the civil war
Don't you know plantation owners needed slaves
And then the union economically affected them. That's you
You're radical abolitionist ben saint
Uh, not a good look. Um, we've got to abolish Trixie's patreon. Uh, yes, I would like in Trixie two-way and antebellum
Slave-owning cotton plantation owner. Yes, I would agree with that comparison
I wouldn't because there's no way she would be able to organize such a thing
Hey, oh, she couldn't afford it. Ha ha because she's poor
Whoo, yeah
Um, also she doesn't also she doesn't want to be white
So she doesn't she she doesn't like being white. She she wishes she could become a trans
A trans racial individual. She wishes society was ready for that
So that's a little different too. So it's not a it's not a one-to-one comparison
But uh, you know
It's a metaphor
Was it uh, was it this week that Trixie made that
That's that's substack post about being a bitch online. Was that this week?
I don't remember. Hold on. I gotta check twitter
There's something about um, I
Trixie I'm going to be positive
It was like some something of a oh, no, it was it was this week. It was the 15th. Yes. Oh
Yeah, it was something of a uh, a walking back of how she treated me
Uh after after she saw someone else. It wasn't really though. It wasn't really though. Well, yeah, I was getting to that
it was just like
an attempt was made but like
It really wasn't like I'm going to
Make amends. I'm going to not be a bad person. It's oh, no
Being a bad person is bad for me
economically
Um, so I will just not do that anymore. It's not about it's not about caring that she hurt
People or myself or whatever. It's just that the repercussions. It's yeah, uh, we're bad and that sucks for her
She's she's literally in in in so many words. She's just saying uh, I got owned
I should probably not do that or I'll get owned again
Yeah
in in this this article really annoys me
because
what it says
This is okay. She she's
She's adopted. She started to adopt this whole like like positivity thing. She's like no, I'm I'm different now
I'm I'm like I've left all the hate like I've left all the hate out of my heart now. I'm only positive
I only I only like things right
Um, and she's and then this started she says I'm not I'm over. I'm done with being a bitch
I'm not going to be mean anymore being mean
Is bad being nice is good, right? And this is in
Not not as an apology but sort of as a response to yeah to the who are these podcasts
appearance
And to that and it's very it rings completely hollow for many reasons
But the thing that galls me the most about it is that yeah, it's it's adopting this stance of like
I'm no longer going to be mean. I'm being nice now. I'm above I'm above being I'm above petty
arguments and and spite and and and uh drama and bile, right?
But this comes as a response to her doing something aggressive
and getting
Owned for it getting backlash. It totally fell on its face and failed. This is literally just
She's posturing now like she's like she isn't
Gonna attack anyone but like she did she literally she attacked us. She came after us. She tried
To hurt us with the what the who are these podcasts?
She wanted us to get made fun of us to get a backlash people to say hey, these guys suck. I hate them
Uh, it failed
But that's what she was trying to do. She was trying to hurt us
And it's only because the attempt failed that now she she'll walk it back and be like
I'm not about I'm not about attacking anyone. No, no, I'm actually not
Like that at all. I don't do that kind of thing. I'm I'm only nice
Right. It's like the way she
After her after after her attack fails. It's so easy to be like
Attacking's lame. Actually, you know what being aggressive being the aggressor. That's cringe actually. I'm not um
I'm just gonna I'm just gonna let things roll
Yeah, the way after you try and you fail because you're too weak and nobody cares what you think
the way it reads is is definitely like
Not from the perspective of someone like say for example, it worked and she didn't get backlash for it. Yeah
I don't think she would come to the same conclusion because the way it reads is like
It's it's like bad for me
To be a bitch online
Because it comes back to bite me
It's not that I feel I feel bad about what I did
It's just I guess I shouldn't do it again
She says I don't think the results of operating that way have been positive for me. I e I got owned
I got corn cobbed
Uh
Yeah, I mean it's it's
We'll see we'll see
Whether she actually stays with that. I don't I mean I I know I know that it's just completely hollow
And if she ever and if she ever feels like an opera if she ever senses an opportunity
To attack us and hurt us she'll do it. Of course. This is all total empty posturing
Just hot air. Yeah, right
um
But but she can't but she can't because she's weak
She's weak and she can't do anything about us. Uh, she wishes she could
But she can't so this is this is the next best thing to pretend that she doesn't want to anymore
Uh, oh well
That's life. I guess
um
Next voicemail is called what?
three two one go
All right guys who what win where why of retcon?
What's gonna happen at the next retcon? What are you gonna do?
Everybody ask this there's not much more to what
What you I don't know
Shut up shut up. No, I don't know. I don't know the answer to this question
We haven't thought about it. We're gonna play pikmin 2
Like any given thing could happen when you
Give when you when you come to visit in january will that be radcon 4.5?
I
Don't want to record anything. I just want to hang out. So well, we didn't record well
We didn't record anything at 3.5 either or no, we sort of did
Well a little bit we sort of did there was new goal. There was new goal remember that
um, but like uh, that was a beating uh, like
Uh, the the point of that right hit around
Around organizing pcphq or something. I don't fucking remember not not even it wasn't like a big
Not even pcphq. It was just about like whether nate should move to virginia
Yeah, and it was just like oh everyone's meeting i'll fly over
Yeah, because it was fun because I like my friends
It was fun me and munchie were talking about this a little while ago and like radcon 4 3.5 was like the stupidest and like most
pointless
thing of all time
And like practically speaking like there was absolutely no reason for you to come and be there for it
But like we're still glad you did because it ended up being fun
in spite of the fact that like
The reason for it was so asinine
Uh, there was no need for nate to
Get together with trixie and like hang out literally your house just to talk about
this
Was it literally like they couldn't organize getting into a call together
On discord. I mean you would think they could just do a call together. You would think that would be I think that was it
I think it was that they were always on a different sleeping time or like
Trixie was hard to get in touch with for a call and nate was like, I guess I can't
Is it I guess I'm just gonna have to go there physically and talk to them
Is it just that trixie was like so unreliable that nate was like fuck it. I'll just go there in person
I vaguely remember that being much of the reason. Yes. That seems impossible even trixie even for trixie. That seems unbelievable
I mean, I know she was always very hard to get a hold of
But wow
Wow, okay
Yeah, well, obviously there was like
They were gonna look at places nate and michelle. Yeah
But they didn't so there was a reason to go there, but they didn't what was it?
Whatever. I don't think I don't think they did
But no no no because um
Because they weren't talking about moving to boston because that was in boston or brain tree
Yeah, so so they couldn't have been going house hunting for virginia houses
Yeah, so it was all yeah, it was all theoretical. They they got together in person to talk about
Should we move somewhere else so it couldn't have been about like scouting out the location
Yeah, they literally could have just had a fucking voice call about it and gotten like the exact same amount figured out
I think I think we all decided this
Nevertheless, it was fun to hang out and you know
All the other stuff was was cool and we it ended up being a good time
But like yeah, the reasoning behind it was so goofy
Uh
Yeah, I that's where I got my iam games shirt that I still had I lost mine. I don't know where my iam game shirt is
Uh, you're not games anymore. I'm not games. I'm not games
When you when you make a game do you stop being games? I think we think you become even more games
Uh
Nobody knows
Well, at least you'll be able to get a saberspark 64 t-shirt
To replace it god. I hope so god. Can I just can I just say fucking hate listening to saberspark?
He sounds so annoying. He's so obnoxious
His voice
He doesn't sound like a human being he doesn't inflect like a normal person
I don't have like a youtuber voice but like extreme. Yes. Yes. He has this bizarre like
It's like he's trying to do like a radio announcer
But like he doesn't know how and it just comes off like the most stilted and like artificial thing
Uh, I've met him in person and he sounds normal. It's kind of the same
As with uh with with I love Kim possible a lot. I love Kim possible a lot
Legitimately sounds like she has a speech impediment in her music music in her in her videos
And she talks really fast and she yells a lot and she takes forever to say nothing
And she sounds like she's got a speech impediment in person. She doesn't in person. She sounds like normal
And I don't know why why do they do this?
That I notice the thing about myself when I would record like voiceovers for hypocrite or whatever
Talking off the cuff in a podcast or with a person is very different from reading and speaking
So I would put on a voice unintentionally because I'm trying to like
I don't know. I'm not even really know why I'm changing my voice, but it just happens
And I feel like unless you notice that you just do it forever
Yeah
maybe uh
You know you might yeah, maybe I'm maybe I'm throwing stones
Maybe I'm in the glass house here throwing stones because like maybe if I read more scripted content, I would sound weird as well
I mean
Did you script your Winnie the Pooh videos? No
Okay, so it wouldn't feel different. I hardly script. I hardly ever script anything. I didn't script um
Yeah, with the with the Winnie the Pooh videos and with tbap too
I would just go in with notes and I would just go in with like points to hit that's a convo. So
It's a little different. Yeah
It's sometimes there would be it's impossible to have a full script for a conversation between two people
True, but sometimes there would be there would be bits that we would think of that
We would want to deliver and we would make a note of like, okay at this point, you know
Make make a joke about make this joke, right? But they wouldn't be like written out and scripted
They would be just like a little note that I would take a cue from
Uh, yeah
Uh, that's right
So maybe I'm
Don't have any actual
Bases to criticize. Maybe I would be just as bad. I don't know. Maybe if you did that audiobook
You'd you'd you'd find god fucking oh lillia. I fucking hate him
Just fucking let me let me make you some free money idiot you fucking moron die
Law he stole it from me. I was gonna be the guy, but he just doesn't care
Ah
Next voicemail is called nnn week three three two one go
Hey, nonators. We're going three weeks strong now. We only got a bit left to go. I'm on the road this week
So this will be a short voicemail as always. No, Nate. Yes watch
Well, I hope uh, I hope we all remembered I hope we all kept our cool and and kept our our uh, self control
In light of the new the new deltarune video if you failed no, no, nate november. Well, there's always next year
Uh, yeah
Okay
And if you didn't stay strong
Next one is a uh paste bin
Link
Yes, oh text. Okay
Do you think mainland china is or will become the most powerful nation on earth?
If so, what are the consequences if you don't consider yourself sufficiently informed on the matter just ignore this
Well, good news. I do not consider myself sufficiently informed on the matter. So
I'm not
sufficiently informed on the matter, but I have
watched a few videos of by this guy who used to live in china
Okay, and he has opinions about how china loves to
Like emit the air of them being a growing superpower that's going to become the most powerful
Nation in the world. Yes, and in reality
They're they're kind of it's kind of a front. They're not really doing as well as they'd like people to think they're not
They're not as powerful as they
pretend to be
Yeah, because they used to be more
like
lifting everyone up, but now they're more
Or
He had to leave china. He was having a really good life in china. I can't remember the name this youtuber
Um, he was having like a real good life in china working and living and and all that
And he had loads of friends and he spoke chinese fluently and it was like there for years and then slowly
like
something in government changed and
It was just sort of becoming worse and worse for a lot of people
And at the same time they were becoming more
There was more like nationalistic pride
um, and
like
Oh americans are the reason for all your problems. And so it's it's all it's it's muddy and not like
Not what you would expect given
Vague notions of china being like a looming threat that's going to take over the world from american
Or other western media. I saw a tweet this week
Someone was making fun of and then they posted four screenshots of headlines
That all claimed to be claiming that like, oh china is china's momentum is slowing down
You know china is stalling out china is not as powerful
It's not it's not, you know, gonna keep growing and growing forever like they claim
But I guess the idea was that people have been saying that for like a long time
Like people been saying that for years and they keep having to say it. I was like, no, no, no
It's kept growing but like now it's stalling like now it's stalling. Well, yeah
I mean, I don't know whether this one youtuber has all the information. Yeah, I just know that he did live there and he's
For years. I'm like, I guess he has more of an understanding than I do. So yeah, whatever
I just I just don't know
I have no I have no insight into this whatsoever. I believe that I can take over china single-handedly
All I need is a butter knife and
15 minutes, you know
Wait, I gotta check
Gotta check bitcoin
No, you don't this makes me want to check bitcoin
No, you don't no doesn't bitcoin dropped a bit this past week. It may be bound rebounding
But you hopefully Ben are not gonna rebound and buy into it
Listen ice I have said that if I thought bitcoin was going to the moon
I would buy it. Yeah. Yeah
It's only a question of do I think that is going to happen and I genuinely don't know
Uh, it's just
It could it it's it's at a position where I think it could make another big leap
But it could also likely
I think it's more likely that it will continue to grow slowly for a very long time
And crash in the in the future at some point. I think I don't think it's going to like zoom up, but
Why do I think I know anything? Yeah
I mean true
Well, okay, never mind never mind about that. Um
Next voicemail is uh may mayday
Dishane desk chain
three two one go
Okay
First time voicemail a long time. Listen. Oh, what up? My name is may mayday. Dishane
Uh fellow trans woman. What's up? Give love you big inspiration. Anyway, um
I'm actually just here to talk shit about Trixie
A trans person that I don't respect
Okay, yeah, that fucking appearance of one of these podcasts is like, oh dear. Oh my as a fellow trans woman who, um
finds it really
Difficult to do a fan voice because I'm afraid of coming across like this is what a man thinks a woman sounds like so I see
um
Yeah, it's a big ouch
Like, okay, fine. Um
Also while I'm at it their scripts have never been good and I don't understand why people are going on about how like
Oh, they're they've really fallen. They've really dipped. They've really dropped their scripts. I mean, who are these podcasts?
Incredibly lazy and rush. Who and who's like they've needed at least two more drops
I
People really underestimate how
Much DeVoo really did to make those videos watchable back in the day. Oh
It's really painful. It's real. I don't know either of you have
bothered watching any of the anime outfit
videos, but not yeah
The scripts need a lot of polishing
Um, I have not watched like an entire video. I've seen little bits and pieces here and there and my my impression is that they
lean pretty heavily on just kind of recapping
the events of the of the
anime
Which is whatever
and uh, yeah, I've heard that uh
DeVoo, well, I've heard a lot of people say that like DeVoo was the reason the videos were good back in the day
Uh, but I don't know. I haven't watched the new one. So I don't really have any
strong opinion on what they're like myself
I don't know gave you anything to add. I've uh, I listened I watched the first
Up to the Digimon one I think
um
and
The first world was bad. It was just a recap of the show the other ones were sort of
Had more to about like the the the external like nature of the show where when it came out and stuff
I feel like
talking about the idea that Trixie's
Scripts for anime videos were always bad
It may be true
In it in the sense that the only reason
I believed a lot of what she said was because I didn't know anything about anime and I just assumed
The things she was
positing or throwing out there were like
informed and smart and whatever
But I don't know whether I can make that judgment exactly because I haven't done
My own anime research and then gone back and listened to those videos to figure out whether or not they were smart or
Like surface level on the I mean on the subject of like anime knowledge
I don't have yeah
I don't have any room to criticize it because like I don't know that much about it
And so I can't say like oh, she did or did not know what she was
talking about
in terms of like
In in terms of like other
Aspects that she might have talked about in her
So much in her anime videos been like her other stuff again her after dark stuff in like her vlog content and stuff
I know
That I definitely feel at this point that like there may have been a time that I might have like
I might have respected her opinion about stuff
But I have come to understand that I just don't think she is smart or knows what she's talking about or or like
Has much of value to say and I don't and it has retroactively made me think that like lots of things that maybe I would have just
Accepted as an opinion before now. I have to shake my head and be like well. That's just fucking dumb
Uh, yeah, so I don't I don't know
Yeah, no, that's not true for everything but for some things. I I feel
uh
my
Because just yeah, and any anything that I didn't know about myself
Anything that I did not have a personal opinion on that she said I might have gen I would have generally just taken her word for it
But now I've it has to I have to question everything
Uh, and you know often the the questioning does not lead me to a positive
Conclusion about the yeah content. I guess I guess the the thing that also
I'm not sure about is the people who do know
About this the the things she talked about. Um, I haven't seen people
Saying in comments
Anywhere that much when it you know when they were happening
The Trixie didn't know what she was talking about
So I feel like she had a basic grasp enough to make a video on these subjects and I was
Like at minimum acceptable
I feel like now that Trixie has gone off the rails
Yeah, uh, it's easy to look back and say well, they were always bad, but I didn't think it at the time
I don't know if that's true
You know, I I I think it's okay. I think it's a combination
I I think it's
There is there are some things that I now would think more negatively of just because I know
More about the person who's having them who's saying them. I think but I think it's also
That like she has just gotten worse
Insert like I don't think she could make
Asterisks war sucks now Asterisks war sucks was an interesting analysis and it
Touched on, you know, it was it was pretty like, you know, honest about like
Feelings and stuff. I don't know. I feel like it was a good little series
And now she's she's a different person now and like now she's on this whole thing about like
I
Don't know she's she's like gone into this like contrarian positivity thing and she's all just like I like things now
Digi bro was bad because because he didn't like things, but that was actually just a character
I was playing that wasn't really me
That was just a character Trixie is good Trixie likes things Trixie is nice Trixie's positive
And I just feel like it doesn't come from an emotionally honest place and I feel like it would not
I don't feel like she could write something that I would be like
Hmm. You make an excellent point. Hmm. That speaks to something that I feel
Yeah, is relatable anymore. I suppose a lot of
The the content of the videos that she made was not merely
This anime is good. Um, it's it's like
Using the anime as a framing device for talking about the internet or her
self yeah, or like
various
Things that people can relate to on an emotional level
And that's that's you know
People like that. That's okay. I feel like if she tried to do the same stuff now
She would not relate to anyone because she is
So
Different she's such a she's such like a closed
You know, you know like she's so cagey. She doesn't she doesn't tell anyone what she's up to
She doesn't like nobody
I know I know where she lives because I'm smart and I figured it out and it wasn't even that hard
But like nobody knows where she lives because she's like a secretive about it
Like she doesn't uh, she's she doesn't want people to know about her anymore
Uh, and it comes through
In her scripts
This that what you just said about like how the videos are really they're not they're sort of about the anime
but they're really about like
They're about the host
Yeah, I've been thinking about that
Tim tim rogers has made me think about that lately like those videos are not like they he does talk about the game
But like the the point of those videos
I really think is just for him to talk about himself, which is like fine. I'm not saying there's anything wrong with that
um
But it's true of just I think it's just true
Of youtube I saw a video that was a criticism of
It was a a specific philosophy tube video where like some someone who worked for like a university who was like an actual philosophy
Professor gave like wrote like an essay about like, you know
Learning philosophy from philosophy tube
Is kind of like not a great way to do it
Because those the philosophy tube videos
Are only sort of about philosophy like the the point of those videos is not to is not principally
To exposit ideas
But to profile the host right the point of the videos is to
Feature the personality that makes them and I think that's true of so
That's true. I think that's just true of like everything
I think that's like the point of youtube the point of youtube is to provide a platform for people to
nominally talk about stuff you might be interested in video games you like movies you like whatever but the point
Is for them to sell themselves to you as someone that you like and that you want to give money to
And I don't know
I'm not even talking about tricksy anymore. Although it's true of her as well. It's true of everyone
I don't think uh, yeah, that's probably bad. That's probably a bad thing
I mean, maybe I'm my my brain immediately goes to someone like tom scott who is
Yeah, obviously very well recognized because of his videos being very popular
And he's got his signature look and the way he talks and he's like it's tom scott
I like tom scott. I see tom scott and I click sure. Um, but the content
I don't know whether I could describe it about being about tom scott
Other than the fact that it's things that he thought would be interesting to put into a video
And in that sense, I don't know whether there's anything wrong with that
I don't know. I guess there's there's there's certain aspects of parasocial
Like there's a there's a gradient I guess here's here's where it could be more about the host than it is about the stuff
That is being talked about what what if I phrased it like this. What if I said that the the business model
Regardless of the actual like content of the videos or how educational they are the business model of youtube is not
explaining things
Educating people the business model of youtube is to make people like you invest people in you
Sell them on you as someone they want to give money to
By whatever means yes, I think that's only
Due to the fact that most youtube channels are run by an individual and not a company
Because if it were if it were all companies it would be the same thing
But like to get people invested in the brand or whatever
Well, yeah, yeah, okay. I get okay. Yeah, I guess
I guess in a way that's kind of the point of any brand
And some brands are just a person
So I guess maybe I'm not really describing anything new, huh?
Yeah, in fact, you might be an idiot Ben saying
Perhaps perhaps. Let me just check bitcoin again real quick. No
Oh, it crept up a little bit. Ah, it's creeping back up toward it. It dipped below six hunt 60k
But it's creeping a little bit back up towards it
I hope that it doesn't like
Pass 60k and then shoot up again because it's like oh, oh, we've we've beaten the resistance point. We're past the resistance point
Whatever fuck it
um
Duh, what were we talking about youtube?
Whatever man
Yeah, Trixie sucks. Uh, that's all I have to say
One last thing about that. Okay. Uh, male is uh fem voice is tough
Yeah, and I totally get the
the the the the
the aversion to
I guess I guess flippantly or like without practice put on a voice
That people can hear and make judgments. I'd rather perfect it in secret and then suddenly start using it
I don't know if that's possible. I feel like your voice would gradually change
um
But it's I I don't want to I don't want to without having
under undergone like a rigorous
training
It's just start doing a voice off the top of my head because it's gonna sound
Very bad
Hmm
Just like it would be with any sort of accent thing you're trying
Probably yeah, probably yeah
um
okay
Uh, one more voice mail this one is uh
This isn't like they used another website that's fast upload
Okay, you got it open it's called bends bends crass and cast formerly nates
You got it wait wait, that's the joke
And press it needs needs feed and seed formerly chucks
Well, it doesn't make any sense because
Sneeds feed
wait
Sneeds feed and seed
I'll end with eed
Yeah, so your brain automatically goes chucks
Suck and suck
So if this is okay, so if it's bends crass and cast formerly nates then it would have been nates crete and kate
So that doesn't make any sense. Yeah, this is okay
Are you are you ready?
Yes, okay three two one go
I mean, have you been following the uh the the kyle written house stuff?
The the details are iffy in my I mean in my corner of the internet obviously everyone thinks he's he's guilty
If he gets an acquittal
the messages
White people
Yeah, why bring such a large gun?
Yeah
what
I thought the message is the message is white people
I thought it was going somewhere else
I'm not sure exactly what the message of that was supposed to be
uh
I thought it was going to be I thought I was going to end on like what did I say?
I said like, you know white people go out and kill protesters
I thought it was going to end on a dramatic beat of like me
You know the music stops and I say white people go out and kill protesters
Uh, but it didn't so I guess it subverted my expectations
What a strange voicemail. That was a strange voicemail. Oh, we got another one a new one 17 minutes ago
It's called rod surling the crypto zone. Yes, please
Are you ready? Yes. Okay, three two one go
Imagine if you will the world in which the only rational option would be to invest in bitcoin
Impossible why it is not so in the mind of ben saint internet comic artist and game developer extraordinaire
What if you knew for a fact that your money would double after you invested
Forget that in this scenario the whole point of the speculation market that bitcoin relies on would be deflated
Because it relies on some people losing out for others to make gains
Which is made impossible when the stock rise and fall is made predictable to everyone
Or imagine that bitcoin became the only currency and you would become a literal
Vagrant in a mad max wasteland if you did not invest
These are the scenarios we wrestled with in the crypto zone
Where ben saint goes when he must once again justify why he still feels the subtle temptation to invest in bitcoin
Though at the same time admitting that they are a scam pyramid scheme with necessary victims
Not the least of which is the environment
Gotta get that bag i guess
If i wrote to radcon so that ben saint becomes secure enough in his finances that he no longer feels that
Survivalist instinct that tempts us all to slice the achilles tendon of our federal man to steal his meat
And his crypto wallet his meat
Uh that is a completely that is a very emotionally
Honest that is an that is exactly how it feels. I am living in the crypto zone
All the time
That's very eloquently put as well very eloquently put. I love i'm gonna fucking voice grail that one
Yeah, voice grail rod serling goes right to the voice grail
And and ser it's an honor to have you among our esteemed
Right, you you said you said it you said it better than I ever could have
uh
Yeah, I I do uh
What more is there to say you just hit the nail on the head that that music should play every time you check bitcoin
Yeah, it should it should
Uh can we get elia's r2 start editing in the
The twilight zone music whenever bitcoin comes up
Elia's are uh, I'll get I'll get you I'll get you the music. I will get you
I will get you the music. Uh, we're gonna make it we're gonna make it happen. This is a new bit
Yeah, um
Congrats, okay
Anything else? Are we are we done?
I suppose we are
God
another pcp
Gone behind people have been complaining that they're not four hours long
Yeah, I saw a couple people were like I got so used to four hour long podcast and this one's only two hours and 15 minutes
I don't even know how we were able just the two of us to go on for four hours
These days I don't because nothing nothing happens to me anymore
I just fucking sit in my room and I work on my gain and I lift weights
That's all I do
We just gotta finish these projects. Yeah, and we can talk about them
Genuinely, yes true genuinely the case
Uh, well, but that day not yet that day is not today. So until that time comes
You want to you want to wrap up?
Next pcp time next pcp channel next time in the crypto zone
patreon.com slash the procrastinators bonus episodes tricksy drama
Um
Mother is shit probably fun fact challenge fun fact challenge gay wizards
Ancient stuff from the before times think of the bird men bird men
There were bird men in there. I remember that
Yes, what else was there? I think there was some world war two shit. I don't know
And speak about com slash pcp voicemail send us a voicemail if you want to do that and
Buy a rogerad con like rod surling says rod surling says you got a buy a rogerad. Send me a message on discord or in on twitter
Buy it and ask me how to buy it and then do it. Okay
I guess that's it. Okay. Goodbye
Goodbye