By the time I reached my teenage years, I was kind of a film snob and I went through a bit of an anti-Star Wars phase.
Perhaps I felt it was a kid's thing and I grew out of it.
But another thing that may have attributed to my brief disinterest in Star Wars was how
unoriginal the movies seem to me at the time. It's true that George Lucas was influenced by several films,
but that's only what makes the movies so great. The characters are all famous archetypes.
Luke is the classic hero, Obi-Wan's the classic mentor, much like Frodo and Gandalf from Lord of the Rings, or
King Arthur and Myrtle from Sword and the Stone.
But there's so much more to it. I've barely scratched the surface and it's not like nobody knows about this.
There's a wealth of information on Star Wars influences all over the internet.
But the fact that Star Wars takes old ideas and makes them into something new shows how ingenious it really is.
It's not like it's plagiarizing. It's just that all ideas in general come from somewhere.
It pays tribute to all these old movies, literature, folklore, mythology, and ultimately reflects our culture.
The movies were a prime target for video game adaptations.
They were full of all kinds of action set pieces, so how could I fuck that up?
So I know the Angry Video Game Nerd made a video about Castlevania 2's Simon's Quest and I love him and that video, but I'll give a f***
Number one, Game Feel! Number two, Day and Night! Number three, The Plot.
So with all these complex elements left totally unexplained, George starts throwing the plot at us.
You know those Star Wars reviews I'm ripping off?
Where the guy says that the prequel trilogy can never be on dog.
I'm not telling you yet. I want to build some suspense first.
We need to build up some suspense first.
Not yet. I want to build even more suspense.
No, not yet. Let's build some more suspense.
Kamino is the coolest guy. Period. He's just the coolest.
For me, a real man is one that never abandons his beliefs. That always sticks to his mind.
Sometimes, you know, we really like to just do our version of peanuts.
Hey everybody, welcome to yet another Procrastinator's Podcast.
We got like a huge gang here to talk about influences, starting with Mr. Endless Jess.
I can't talk right now. I'm replying to a commenter.
Oh!
F*** you! You don't understand the first thing about art, you piece of shit.
Followed by the best guy ever.
F*** you, you piece of shit! You don't understand the first thing about art.
Mr. Tommy Oliver of Rebel Pixels. Speak up again, Tom.
F***! F***!
This is all to establish what we sound like, so people can tell us apart when we all start screaming over each other.
The new regular member of the Procrastinator's Podcast, formerly a guest, Jeff Thu, of his mother's basement, the professional shitbag.
Hello. Hi, people.
Hello, everyone. Welcome him.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Whatever way you choose to do so.
I take cash.
That was a good intro. That was a good title.
Okay, we've got a couple of other people to go.
We got Hippo Crit.
A hippopotamus by day. Critic by day.
Sleeps by night.
And Ben St., whose Patreon shall not be mentioned because it took him an hour to get into this damn podcast.
Welcome to my nightmare, viewers.
And last but not least, The DeVoo.
My thoughts exactly, sis.
So today we're going to talk about influences, what they are and what ours are in particular.
That'll probably be the bulk of this podcast.
But I want to start by talking about how, uh, you know, there's, there seems to be, I've seen this in criticism and in people just generally talking about stuff before,
where some people like really don't like to show their influences, or they really like to try to make everything like really unique and, and be like, oh yeah, everything, everything should be, uh...
Its own island of creativity.
Yeah. And I think it's, I think that if you work within a medium at all, you're already showing influence, right?
Like if you write a book, it's assumable that you understand the concept of a book from having read other books.
So I think that you can't escape showing your influence.
It's true. Every single medium was invented by someone.
So the mere fact that you're doing it shows that you're taking inspiration from the people who came before you to do it.
And you know what? On the subject of that, uh, when I, I, I was kind of sensitive to that myself back in the day, but I watched Jesse's videos and think he was really funny.
And then one day I realized that, like, it's entirely composed of quotes from other things assembled in just yo, uh...
One day I realized he's not funny. He's a fraud.
It was funny before I got it. And then once I knew, I was like, this is also hilarious because now I just get all these references.
But I will say though that if you are a genius, you can just come up with things.
I came up with larping, uh, fanfiction and summons from RPGs before I even realized they were actually a thing.
So take that influence.
I actually invented YouTube videos, actually, by the way, before anyone else did it.
I just didn't have the means like 20 years ago when I thought of it, but yeah, I know, right?
It was my idea. Yeah. By the way.
Yep, going.
Oh, nevermind. This is totally off topic, by the way.
So yeah, well, I think it's really cool when people show their influences.
Wait, wait, I want to respond to what Guy said before. Guy, you said the thing about Jesse and noticing his influences.
And I agree. When I, when I see, when I realize like where something came from, I don't like it anymore.
I like it less. Really? Yeah. You like it less, huh?
Well, honestly, like, like in terms of how much it engages me as like a thing, yeah.
Like, like if I'm watching a, if I'm watching a movie and it's like, oh, wow, this movie's great.
And then like a month later, I see another movie, an older movie, and I'm like, oh, wow, this must be where that comes from.
This did it better first. I lose some of that respect. I lose some of that respect for the one that.
Aren't you working on a Pokemon comic that's entirely based on Nuzlocke?
Should I not read your comic? Is it shit? It is shit, but yes.
I think what Ben just said is what a lot of like people, a lot of people you can talk to,
they'll usually express that kind of sentiment. And that's true.
That's a very normie sentiment. It is a very normie sentiment.
Well, I think it could also be a cultural thing, because like I used to be like that kind of,
but then Digibro over here, like really made me realize how cool it was to embrace influence.
And even though it's mostly a personal thing, I think there's a big, a big element of a cultural thing,
because over, because he's big otaku, right? You're into that anime stuff.
And over there, they seem way more embracing of the idea of iterative creativity, like when
video games were invented, Atari made a point. We will never make the same game twice,
but then Japan got in on the scene and it's just like Mega Man 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, you know,
that kind of stuff. Hey, are you saying Atari isn't from Japan?
Correct. What the fuck are you kidding me right now? Where the fuck are they from?
It was from America. It's just that he named it after-
It's from the Silicon Valley, man.
Yeah, it's just that he named it after-
I thought you were being-
Oh, am I making a joke?
Yeah. No, no, no. He named it after-
Atari is a move in the game called Go, which has no other-
No, it's a state in Go.
It's-
Yeah, yeah. So it's a bunch of leads in America.
That's what I mean, yeah. It's a state, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so it's-
So Weebs invented Japan.
Yeah, Weebs invented video games. That's what we're taking away from this.
So, um, yeah, to talk about the influence thing, though, which is the point of the podcast,
incidentally, I mean, it sounded like I was bringing up a side topic for some reason.
But, um, yeah, I'm a big fan of, like, creative stuff that, like, deliberately shows its influences
because I think that you are basically recontextualizing things and I think you can often make it better.
Like, I think a lot of Jesse's humor improves on the context of the original quote he's quoting
by, you know, bringing it to something new. Like, for instance, one of the ones we all found out
about recently was when he says, ah, you unzipped me.
Yeah, yeah.
And it was originally from It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia, but the way that Jesse did it,
like, the delivery of it and the timing was, like, perfect in his video.
And it was, I think, even, I think, in the, in the original context of the original joke,
that line is more of a throwaway thing that Frank says in the middle of more stuff.
I don't want to suck Jesse's dick too hard on it because it doesn't really matter how good or bad
he did it.
Are you sucking my dick? It sounds like you're all calling me a heck fraud.
Did you was?
I'm saying, I'm saying that when you showed me that clip from It's Always Sunny,
I thought that line didn't stand out in that, in that, like, in Frank's speech.
Okay, well, when you said it in your video, it was, like, a huge punchline.
Let's not have these simpletons in the audience walk away thinking that everything I've ever
said is a line from something.
Yeah, no.
And you do the references really well.
And you know, I am the greatest writer in the world, the most creative,
articulate, intelligent person in the world.
Everything that I've ever said in my life is 100% unique.
I have no influences.
I influence my influences.
They take influence from me in hindsight, in retrospect.
All my heroes in their ranks are listening to my words.
Someone, someone who really put into context, like, for me, like, what is great about references
was Roger Ebert, and he wrote this review of Kill Bill, where he was talking about how...
Roger Ebert, another guy that I influenced greatly.
Tarantino would take, Tarantino would basically take bits and pieces of other movies that he
was a fan of.
I don't know if he was a fan of, I taught him that.
I showed him that, yeah.
That was my...
God damn it, Nate.
I cussed it out.
Because he's never gonna end if you do this.
Okay, go on.
So, he was talking about Kill Bill and how that movie, you know, takes bits and pieces
from all these other movies and sort of combines them into one, but he was saying how,
like, for instance, the song that, uh, the girl with the eyepatch whistles, the, like,
that one, he was like, this is from a movie from, like, the 40s, but this movie doesn't have
that song as a reference to that movie.
It's just something that this character happens to also sing, you know, it's not,
it's not like it's there to say, hey, remember this movie from the 40s?
It's like...
It's been given new life in the new context.
Well, that doesn't sound like a reference at all, then.
That just sounds like two movies happen to use the same song.
But it is a reference.
But he, I mean, he definitely deliberately, that song is from a 1940s movie, and he has
put it in his movie, but in this context, it is not referencing that movie as in, like,
like a callback to it.
It's more like this song happens to exist in both universes.
Even though he didn't invent the song, he repurposed it.
The movie takes place in the real world, where that song...
What, Kill Bill?
Does it?
Shut up, yes.
The movie takes place in what is ostensibly the real world, where that song exists.
I don't know.
I mean, I think that kind of a reference is way different than, like, I don't know.
Well, I think that a lot of the, um, our culture's backlash towards references and tribute came
from the fact that it was overdone by people who weren't very good at it.
I believe it really took off in a good way from, like, the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles,
which had all sorts of references.
But I think around the 2000s, some shows were going too far with it, particularly some kid shows.
Much celebrated was their, uh, their reference of stuff.
Yeah, but like, uh, I remember, like, as a kid watching Kids Next Door, and that show's
references are terrible.
It's just annoying.
That's bullshit.
That's a 10 out of 10 show.
There's no problems with it at all.
They just ripped off other whole storylines and didn't add much to it.
And even South Park, I felt, sometimes was getting really lazy with its references.
Like, you know, in some episodes...
Sure, some people have said that.
Well, that's the whole problem with references is because they are lazy.
You can be like, hey, remember this thing that exists?
And people are like, well, they can be.
They are.
They can be.
I think they can take a lot of effort.
The funniest point, the funniest reference ever that I saw in South Park was when, um,
was when everyone was dressing up like Bane and like, and like the newscast, they would
show like the news and the news person would just say like, South Park is under attack
by Banes.
There's a lot of Banes coming around and kidnapping people.
Um, I believe you're the one who said like sometimes references are just, hey, remember
this thing?
Yeah.
If the references point is just to go, hey, remember this thing?
Then that probably sucks.
But there's a million ways for references to have a point.
Right.
I think if I was going to take two Western cartoons to use for examples, I'd go with
Johnny Test for a bad example.
There was a whole episode of Pokemon parody.
The whole thing was just, hey, this is like Pokemon.
Isn't that funny?
And it wasn't.
And then if I was going to use good references, Steven Universe has a whole episode that's
like in a weird Akira parody.
No, it doesn't call attention to itself at all.
Which one was that?
The cat one.
The one where the cat turns into like a blob monster.
No, he grows cat fingers.
Where he turns into a, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
He turns into like a cat Akira monster.
And it's like, what the fuck is, how is this happening?
I didn't realize that was an Akira thing, but thinking back on it, I totally see it.
You know, I don't know if I completely buy that, but whatever.
It's dude, if you watch it again, it's definitely an Akira.
It's definitely horrific, and a similar thing happened to Tetsuo.
The actual, like, the way that it looks and moves is really fucking.
Okay, if you say so, I'll believe it.
That show does-
If you want me to go all, get a different reference, the revolutionary girl Utena references
when Pearl fights her shadow.
I did a whole video on that.
That's a brilliant one.
Because the people who don't know what that is, no one's going to give a shit.
It's just a cool fight.
But if you do know, it's like, holy crap, that's so cool.
That's like a show I watch.
Steven Universe, in general, it handles references really well, I think.
Like, the episode that made me fall in love with it was when they go to the movies,
which is a whole pastiche of references.
And then they end with Lion in the MGM logo, and that's just-
Yeah, I remember being a kid, seeing reference stuff, and I'm always like,
I know this is a reference to something, but I don't know what.
But I know it's a reference because it doesn't make sense in context.
And it just made me feel uncultured, uneducated, and pissed off.
And Steven Universe is always like,
hey, this is funny in the context of the show, but if you get it, you're like,
oh, they're paying homage to the people who influenced them making this.
And that's the right way to do it.
As long as it's still entertaining, even if you don't get the reference,
I see absolutely no problems.
The wrong way to do it is just fucking Peter Griffin walks out,
gosh, this reminds me of the time that Eclectic Scene from Movie happened,
but with Liam Neeson in it.
Well, I kind of like that.
I kind of like the way Family Guy doesn't really did it,
because part of the joke is you don't know what any of this stuff is referencing,
because you're not 35.
You guys fucking love your references and whatever.
Oh, it goes, cultural context, but you guys are all dumb,
because the fact of the matter is, at the end of the day, no matter what it is,
no matter what is being said, if it's original, it's better than if it was a reference.
You disagree.
You're dumb.
Anything, any reference that you can say,
oh, it's so cool that she did the revolution,
shut the heck up, whoever's talking.
It's so cool how she did the revolutionary girl,
Udna thing in Pearl, and whatever.
But no, it's not.
I mean, it might be cool, but wouldn't it have been even cooler
if they thought it up themselves?
Yes, that's my basis.
I think, Steven Harris thinks up plenty of its own stuff.
God damn it, you're not listening.
I'm saying that particular thing would be better if it was original.
If it was original, here's why, because I think that,
let me talk, God damn it, because that's the reason I am called-
Oh, I hate all these fucking people.
They all make me so mad.
The reason that I called, shut the fuck up.
The reason I called myself the 21st century digital boy
is that I like stuff that's new.
I like the, I like stuff that's coming out now,
because I think that we should constantly be taking all the old shit
and just making it better and making it new again.
I'm not saying that it's wrong to make references
or that references are bad.
I'm just saying that if something is original, it is better.
I don't think so, because I think that what we have to do
is take something older and say,
well, this thing is cool, but it's not that cool.
So what if we took all the coolest ideas from that old thing
and put them in this new thing with all these other cool ideas?
And we made something that's just all the coolest ideas
from all these old shit.
There's at least one time in one of my videos
where I almost plagiarized a short Mr. B tongue sentence,
not like as a shout out or a callback,
but because I just thought this sentence makes exactly the point
I need to make at this particular time,
better than anything I can think of.
Well, let me tell you, Davoo.
And there's a couple of times where I've almost plagiarized an AVG inline
because I just thought this is the perfect thing to say.
Davoo, Davoo, in my current login video,
I specifically rip off the whole section of Mr. B tongues
and I made it into a joke.
So I recontextualized the whole thing.
I think it elevated the use of references to that.
Pat yourself on the back a little harder.
Well, look, Ben, think about it this way.
I mean, when we, when people make movies,
like most of the shots are shots that have existed before
because they are shots that we have realized
make sense for conveying certain things.
Like, you know, if we wanted to show someone doing a knife throwing thing,
like there's a certain way you cut that that makes it work.
And so there's no reason to make it completely different every time.
If there's one cut that's off the movie.
The scene is with Pearl fighting the hologram of herself.
I can appreciate that, but I still believe,
but I still believe that if two things,
if you have two options and one is original and one is derivative
and they're otherwise equal, I think the original one is.
Well, okay, Ben, let me ask you real quick.
What if the original thing sucks?
No, I'm saying if it's, if two things are equal, except one is,
one is a reference and one is a reference,
what two things are equal ever?
That doesn't even matter.
I'm just making a thought experiment here.
If you're saying about the exact example, though,
what is going on in the specific example?
It is a sword fight.
How much do they really have to work with that?
Yes, perhaps.
Oh my God, I don't care about the specifics of the scene.
It's not important.
That's exactly what you're arguing.
The point is they chose to turn that scene,
which was just a fight scene,
and make it into a reference and add that layer to what was going on.
What does that add?
What does that add to the scene?
All of us like it.
Oh, great, but what does it add?
Well, no, Ben, what it adds,
when you make a callback to something,
to me anyway, you're calling back to what the meaning of the original was,
and it allows you to put more meaning into your scene by like,
for instance, if a show makes a reference to Evangelion,
then it's making reference to what that show stood for,
and it sort of pulls that meaning into your work in a very easy way.
What does it mean, that as fighting?
If you reference...
With a revolutionary girl, Utano fight.
Isn't that a little lazy?
Isn't it a little lazy to fall back on the meaning and the investment built up from an old show,
to try and convey that into yours?
Would you rather that they entirely retell the story of Ava,
just so that they can have all of the emotional buildup of Ava,
and then put it in their show,
or would you rather that they made a quick reference
that completely summarizes everything of this show that's already happened,
and we don't need to happen again,
and then puts that purpose into this new show,
so that we can have an even higher density of ideas.
Yeah, that only works if you know the original source material.
Ben, your entire position makes absolutely no fucking sense to me.
Ben, you are writing a comic about Pokemon right now, are you not?
My problem with your stance here is the logic of it,
because basically you're saying,
if an original version is everybody as good as a reference,
then the original...
But here's the thing, I remember in my Q&A people asked me,
if killing a baby was the right thing to do,
and you had no other option, would you do it?
I'm like, yeah, that's a very...
Why would they ask me this question in your Q&A?
I know what you're gonna say, Davoo, you're saying that...
That's an overpowered question, and you're saying,
it's basically like saying,
if a salad is better, it was more healthy...
If a hamburger was more healthy than a salad,
the hamburger would be more healthy.
Yeah, no kidding, you just defined the terminology to be whatever you wanted.
No, that's not true, Davoo, you're wrong,
because what I'm doing is I'm setting all other aspects equal,
except for the fact that...
I'm the biggest idiot ever.
Except for the fact that one is original and one is derivative.
That is the variable, that is the fucking variable.
Then if that's the only variable, then maybe, yes.
Yeah, I wouldn't give the original ones a better idea.
I don't think that will ever be the case.
Right, it would be a perfect...
And I would say that with the Perl fight,
that's just a little quick training fight,
that's not like the big finale or anything,
so just let it be something that's easier to make.
So like, why do you guys love this scene so much?
What is so great about the fact that it looks like Utena?
It's a cool little reference.
What's not so great about it?
I don't know, maybe it's because I don't give a fuck about Utena,
because I've never seen it.
Well, it elevates what otherwise would have been a totally...
Like, meaning the scene into something that you now care about.
Elevates it.
Yeah, whatever.
Here's the problem.
That means anything.
It's just like, oh, that's the thing I've seen.
Here's the...
It has to be super meaningful.
Like, does the animation in something that's really pretty,
like, is that really elevating?
I've never seen revolutionary girl Utena before,
but I watched that scene and I thought the animation looks cool.
I didn't know what it was referencing until everybody told me,
but it just looks...
It looks cool, and they copied it because they're not as good as animators or whatever.
I mean, yeah.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Yes, come on.
Right, that's what it comes down to.
Nate, that is not what it comes down to.
That is totally...
I'm not saying there is good, but I'm not saying...
My point was, my point was that,
does it really matter that they're taking shortcuts?
Do you care that much about, you know...
Yeah, it's not a shortcut.
I'm not against it.
I'm not against...
It is a shortcut.
It's not.
They're deliberately deciding to do it a certain way.
No, no, I don't agree.
I do not agree.
I do not agree that that would...
I do not think they said, hey...
Everybody shout, everybody shout, everybody shout.
Jeff's been trying to say something for like 10 minutes.
Yeah, I have.
What the heck?
Yeah, okay, so Ben, like, seriously,
your entire argument is predicated on the idea
that like, a scene can nebulously be better
if you extract all inherent meaning
from everything that they do in the writing, directing,
everything about the scene.
If you take that out and it's just like,
okay, so technically speaking,
this is on the same level as this.
That doesn't mean anything though.
Like, the only question is,
is it better for your story if...
To see your point, what was that book
that Vincent was reading in the Vapors?
I think you should take that out, Ben.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
No, Ben, you fucking idiot.
No, that...
You piece of shit, garbage.
I hate you all.
Oh, okay, well, you do a reference.
No, no, what that is, what's with it, right?
It was really deep and it was...
No, no, no, he should have been reading for that book.
It is fundamentally different.
Everybody shut the fuck up right now.
Everyone, listen to me,
that kind of reference is the sort of reference
of the girl in the Kill Bill singing a song
that really exists.
That is a reference to a real thing
that exists in the real world.
Ben, I just like to ask...
I did not have him do something exactly like...
Did you copy paste the text?
No, it's not copy pasted or anything like that.
It's not like the revolutionary girl
Odin, a thing with Pearl,
where she just does the thing the other character does.
But it would have been better
if you wrote the original thing real quick.
But I think just ask you real quick, Ben,
because isn't it just a little bit hypocritical?
Now, don't get mad, I'm just...
No, it is not.
Listen to what I'm gonna say,
because what you're doing is you're introducing something
that has all this context in the outside world.
Is it really that raw?
I mean, based on your argument,
wouldn't it be better if you had somehow constructed
a book in that universe that has all this meaning
that you're applying to the situation?
Yeah, no, exactly, exactly.
Putting an element that really exists in the real world
into a work of fiction is not the same
as copying another work of fiction.
I get your point now, Ben.
Your fiction.
Yeah.
I see your point.
I think that the reason...
Don't agree.
I'm gonna try to justify this exact...
Disagree entirely.
...the scene that has come into question,
because the reason that Utana was animated the way it was,
the reason that they showed her do those specific movements,
was because the show was supposed to have this sort of regal,
like, it's this old-school fencing,
like, you know, the characters are meant to feel
like they're from the 1800s almost.
Like, it's supposed to bring back this image of nobility.
It's a show about princes and princesses fighting,
even though it takes place in a high school.
And that connects to Pearl's character.
Yeah, and it matches Pearl's character,
because she's supposed to be a knight.
She's supposed to be a regal, noble character.
Okay.
So using the same iconography was because
it would communicate the same point.
It would still make...
I tend to agree that that's...
No, I do understand.
I understand that the reason they did it
is because the sort of theme or tone conveyed
by that bit in Utana was basically similar
to the tone that they were trying to go for
with Pearl's character in Steven Universe,
so they kind of, you know, copied...
You know what, I just agree with the whole basis of this.
Just let me finish, just let me finish.
And but, the thing I'm saying,
it's not that it was wrong of them to do that,
but I am saying that the fact that it was derivative
and not original is, in my opinion, a weakness.
Well, I don't think it takes anything away from the scene.
I don't think you have to explain yourself
or apologize for putting a reference to something.
I don't think they have to apologize.
I just don't think it's as impressive
as it would have been if it was completely original.
It's more impressive.
It's less impressive.
Because I see it and I go,
wow, they did a thing like a thing on purpose
so that people like me who recognize the thing
would see it and appreciate it more.
If that same exact scene were in Steven Universe,
but Utana had never happened before,
it would be a way more impressive scene.
Nobody would even remember it if it wasn't a reference.
Let's let Tom say something.
It's interesting because I definitely am empathizing
with what Ben is saying.
I kind of get where he's coming from.
And I think the reason I understand where he's coming from
is because we both draw shit.
And you kind of want to be more creative that way.
Like you want to be more original
because you're more driven to do that.
Whereas if you guys would just analyze things,
being able to have those references lets you appreciate that
because you're able to extrapolate more from that medium.
Can I just make a comparison of that fight?
Because I want to bring up,
because this fight is a direct ripoff.
Hang on, this fight is a direct ripoff of the Utana fight.
That's true.
And then we were arguing that that has a meaning
and it's a good thing.
But if you contrast that with a thing like in Naruto,
they shot for shot copied this fight
from the cowboy bebop movie.
And it is absolutely vapid.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no, but that's such a great reference
because it calls back all the emotional weight
of the cowboy bebop.
You're not listening.
I'm arguing that it has no value.
That is them literally being super lazy.
And it's the same thing.
It's not the same thing.
That's where we disagree.
Because I think that that one doesn't have value.
I think that in the cowboy bebop movie,
that fight made sense because the two characters
were both supposed to be real people using real kung fu moves.
The fight itself is a reference to a Bruce Lee film,
even in the cowboy bebop movie.
So because of the fact that Spike uses
the same fighting style as Bruce Lee,
he, I think it's Jeet Kune Do, something like that,
he uses Bruce Lee's fighting style.
I believe he uses a Jufro Jitsu.
And he even quotes Bruce Lee sometimes.
So he is meant to be a Bruce Lee character.
And cowboy bebop itself is a huge
pastiche of references to everything possible.
Yeah, I guess cowboy bebop shouldn't exist.
I guess we should get rid of it.
Yeah, cowboy bebop just got to go.
Listen, Ghost Lightning did a series of posts
that chronicled a lot of the references in cowboy bebop.
Now listen, let me, let me, let me, okay.
So them copped, okay.
So obviously Naruto just copying the cowboy bebop fight,
that's bad and derivative and shameful.
Because of the intent behind it.
If you are deliberately trying to make people
recognize it as a callback to something,
then that's a reference.
If you're just trying to take the dick out of your mouth
before you make a movie.
We're meeting a fucking steak.
The cowboy bebop movie, the cowboy bebop,
okay, I don't know exactly to what extent it was copied,
but if the cowboy bebop's like,
It's like, it's too much, dude.
If the cowboy bebop would be copied to Bruce Lee fight,
I mean, I don't think that's as bad
because it's translating a real world thing into animation.
But I think it's fundamentally the same thing,
even though it's much worse than another.
There is meaning in the scene in cowboy bebop.
But because of the fact that Spike
is supposed to fight like Bruce Lee,
that is his fighting style.
And in Naruto, there is no,
like, I mean, maybe if Rock Lee had used it,
if he was the one in this fight seat,
maybe it would have been more clever.
That would have been a better connection.
But it's characters have nothing to do with that.
Like your whole argument, Ben,
is it's like predicated on this idea
that it's inherently better to create your own iconography.
Yes, that is exactly my argument.
The thing is that if you are arguing that,
then your scene where your character
is reading your book, the only difference
between a character using a thing,
let me finish my point.
I'm gonna let you finish.
Let me finish.
I've been trying to talk for like 10 minutes.
Because it is a fundamentally different kind of reference,
but go on.
Okay, so it's still fundamentally a reference, right?
So the blanket idea of you can do a reference right,
or you can do it wrong is what applies here.
Like if you just have a character reading fucking Catcher in the Rye,
because you want them to seem edgy,
that is a bad reference in the same way
that the Naruto fight is a bad reference.
That is not a bad reference.
That is totally different.
Can you not see how it would be different,
how it would be a fundamentally different kind of reference to,
one, frame by frame copy a fight from a movie for the movie,
or versus having, you know,
fucking Spike Spiegel watching a Bruce Lee movie on TV.
Those are two completely different kinds of reference.
Let me, so the argument that you're making
is for like the exact same distinction
that people complain about all the time about music in movies,
and how if you have like a pop insert song in a movie,
some people say that that's bad,
but if the character is listening to the pop song,
suddenly the fact that it's existing within that world somehow legitimizes it.
And I think that that argument is purely coming from this
perspective that a world of a show needs to be all the time 100 percent
diagetic.
Believe, yeah, diagetic.
And it has to stay within the fourth wall.
And the thing is that we as an audience know that this is a cartoon made out of
individual drawings for babies, right?
Yes.
It's not, Steven Universe isn't a real person.
So it doesn't, like it wouldn't make a difference if Steven Universe
was sitting down watching TV.
I wouldn't buy into that universe any more than I already do.
The fact that I know that this is something made by a creator
is another level of interest for me as somebody watching this.
That's a good point.
And I have no idea what you're talking about.
I think what Jeff's trying to say is that there are,
like there's a level of meaning that you can get from having the character in the work,
be in our world and read Infinite Jest.
But then if you had a reference to Infinite Jest in the way the character is acting,
that's also another kind of meaning that we can appreciate as an audience.
Well, Jeff is saying that when you look at something as art,
and you see that there are references to like old anime in Steven Universe,
that tells you something about Rebecca Sugar.
It tells you something about the artist and that's valuable.
Right.
How is that valuable?
How is that valuable to the work itself?
It's all part of the package, man.
For me, it's extremely inviting to my appreciation of the show
because I feel like the people making it come from a similar place to me.
Like I watch Steven Universe and I think, huh, references to Dragon Ball,
Sailor Moon, and Akira.
This is obviously made by someone from my generation who also grew up watching anime in the 90s,
who has the same kind of cultural reference points that I do.
And therefore I relate to the work itself.
Ben, can I try to interpret your position here?
Because I think I might be able to phrase it in a way that like,
go for it.
I'll interpret his position.
I'm a big dummy.
Okay, so like, okay.
I'll interpret my position.
All right.
That's about it.
Because someone can read a book, right?
That makes sense.
That's something that a normal person would do.
And sometimes someone might quote a movie intentionally.
But the human mind is so complex that there's no point at which someone's mind is going to be taken over
by a scene from a movie from 1993 and just suddenly they will act like this scene for five seconds.
That's just not something a normal person would do.
And it's not something that you can relate to.
So if all of a sudden this actual night like Pearl is suddenly doing everything that a 1997 anime character did,
you're like, oh, she watched Utena and is copying it.
But that's obviously not what's happening because she would watch anime.
Anime exists in the Steven Universe universe.
The problem I have, I don't know about that to do.
And Pearl was like, wow, this is a pretty good TV show.
I mean, you know that's not what happens.
Has Pearl ever shown interest in like, Earth culture ever?
Again though, I think.
Right, you're fanning it.
No, you know that's not what happens.
It's just that this thing that a night does exists in both universes.
It's not, in context of the show,
it's not a reference to Utena in context of like the universe.
It's just the way she fights.
But the way that they chose to present that.
Don't you think that it's fourth wall breaking?
Yes, that's it.
Don't you think that that clear kind of reference pulls you out of the work
and makes you aware of its artificiality in that view?
We already know!
But Jeff is trying to say, I'm already out of the work because I know it's a work.
Hang on, hang on.
Okay, I get it now.
Ben is making a case for those people who are not interested in a fourth wall breaking scene.
They're more interested in something being all contained within a universe.
And that's, I think you're actually making a good point here.
Yeah.
If you, depending on what your values are, that's going to be valuable.
I don't value that at all.
I don't value being kept within the work.
But the thing is, Ben, the thing is though, if you don't know it's a reference,
it won't matter.
But I think a general audience, it's way more valuable
that a thing doesn't take you out of the work.
Like, look, I think that's the thing.
Nobody knows.
I think it's very something to think that most people even feel
that they are in a work.
Like, I don't watch something.
That's the way you're supposed to feel when you watch something.
When I watch a TV show or an animal show.
Thank you, Tom.
It depends.
Like, look, my brother.
Go ahead, go ahead, go.
When I watch anything or read anything, I look at it and I,
sometimes I get references, sometimes I don't.
And then I enjoy it based on how much, how cool it was.
And then I go about my day.
That's it.
Why can't we just be that simple?
Why is it going to be so complex?
I don't think about other things.
I don't think at any point when I'm watching a show, do I feel like,
man, this is so real.
I am totally here.
You know what really bothers me about Ben's position is that,
to me, it seems like you're making the same case as when I say,
oh, another YouTube channel or a Facebook page stole my video and uploaded it.
And then people say, well, you referenced things in your video,
so you're a plagiarist too.
Oh, boy.
You are equating deliberate references with sneaky plagiarism.
So that is not what I'm doing.
And you're undermining actual plagiarism by doing it.
Here's my question for the whole, the purpose of any work of art is to get you immersed in it.
If that's the case, if the purpose of storytelling is to make you believe the world and that's it,
then why are shaky cam movies so much fucking worse than movies with subjective
artist-driven camera placement?
Because immersion doesn't mean an actual one-to-one interpretation of reality.
When you say you were immersed in something,
it's that you feel like you're ignoring outside stimuli.
You're just like, you're invested in what's going on on screen.
It doesn't mean like you feel like you're actually in the position of the character.
But my question is, if pointing, if doing something with a camera that the human eye
can't possibly do, which is done all the time in movies, totally OK, doesn't take you out of it,
then why does making a reference to something that influenced the creator,
which just as much acknowledges the fact that there is an artist guiding your vision of this product,
why does that take you out of it?
Jeff and Jesse, you guys are both misunderstanding his point.
No, no, I changed my mind.
I agree with Ben now.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You agree with me?
No.
Well, here's the thing.
Really?
Jesse's just like that.
I'm switching sides.
I'm on Ben's team.
Why Jesse?
I'm on Ben's team, too.
What changed just now, Jesse?
Well, because I remembered that sometimes I get guys who say they're influenced by me on YouTube
and then I watch it and they're just stealing my word from word, and that pisses me off.
How do you think that the person that animated that scene in Revolutionary Girl,
Ootna, feels when she watches Steven Universe?
OK, well, no, I'm not on your team anymore.
OK, I just deleted these Steven Universe people actually watched my show from 30 years ago.
OK, OK, fine.
Only because that was like 30 years ago.
You know what? I'm off Ben's team.
I almost agreed with him.
You almost had it.
You almost had that Jesse vote.
What we're really talking about here is what we're really talking about here is suspension of disbelief
and it's totally different for everybody.
What will break your suspension of disbelief?
How big your cord is.
My suspension of disbelief gets broken by totally different weird random things
that have nothing to do with references.
Like I still feel like even though I don't like when I watch Steven Universe,
I think, OK, obviously this is a show.
It's animated.
It's made by people.
I know how the sausage is made.
I know what goes into it.
I know how each shot is meant to make me feel an emotion.
And more so than feeling that emotion, I just think about the technique used.
But that doesn't mean that I don't have any attachment to the story
because when I when I see the references and things,
I just think they're cool and I like the story overall.
I'm willing to suspend my disbelief because here's an example going on.
My brother, when he looks at cover art,
like I was showing him like panning and stalking on Mal
and he was like the cover art bothered him
because the characters were facing with their weapons toward the camera.
But the enemy that they should be fighting was behind them,
making a dramatic pose.
And my brother was like,
why aren't they aiming their weapons at the enemy?
It completely threw him off and he hated it.
But whenever a cover is such a weird I know right.
But it really pisses him off because he's like into weapons
and fighting and stuff and hunting and shooting.
But whenever a cover art is just like abstract,
like there's just like a photoshop filter in the background,
he doesn't mind because it's that level of abstraction.
But panning and stalking, that cover art's in a city.
And so it throws them off.
I would have never, ever, ever thought of that.
So that's different levels of suspension of disbelief.
That everyone has different stuff that will break it.
And so we respect your differences.
We understand.
All right.
And we respect them in your life choices.
Let me just defend myself one last time.
Vincent reading infinite jest is not the sort of reference
that will that can break your suspension of disbelief.
Because I agree with that.
That is true.
That is what's different about that.
Now that we have settled that question,
perhaps we should move on to the next part.
Right.
Yeah.
Part two of this, we actually talk about our influences.
The actual point of the podcast.
The actual point now.
Well, I intended from the time that I first suggested it,
this podcast, for us to talk about influences in like how they work.
And then for us to talk about influences,
I just thought the first part would only be five minutes long
because I didn't expect a complete disagreement.
Oh, you guys want a more specific example of influence chains.
Go listen to, I don't know if this plug is okay with you, Digi,
but you have this old podcast where you talk about Pacific Rim
and how people say it ripped off Evangelion.
So you spent an hour talking about its lineage of Evangelion
to prove how everything is a rip-off.
And that was a very interesting podcast
that really makes the case one-sidedly, my dad,
about why references are omnipresent and good.
I know that everything is a rip-off to some degree.
I just think that that's not a good thing necessarily
and that the less of a rip-off you are, the better.
Yeah, I'm back on Ben's team.
If you want the continuation of that whole idea train of thought,
yeah, go listen to that Pacific Rim podcast, I guess.
And then now let's get into this.
Nate, you said that you had the shortest list of references or influences.
That's not true, but I did say I could go through it quickly.
Well, someone has to go first and throw themselves in front of the bus to set the tone.
I have the least desire to talk about mine at great length
because I'm currently ashamed of how small my channel is,
so I can just bang this thing out of my mind.
Nate, tell us about your influences.
Okay, so first of all, to set the context,
what I'm really describing here is the things that are affecting
the way that I make videos, how I came to this point,
and that's it.
I'm not talking about anything outside of this shit.
Okay, so I've been saying for a while that I wanted to be the John Tron of anime,
and that was at a time when John Tron was good,
times have changed, and he's shit.
But still, there's an ideal of John Tron's golden age that I want to be at,
even though our styles are totally different, so whatever.
Demolition D is another guy who's my current hero,
who also is a totally different style who I'll never be able to be like exactly,
but whatever, he's a guy.
So the two guys that really kind of kickstarted the whole analysis shit on YouTube in the first
place were the Red Letter Media guys, specifically the Mr. Plinkett reviews,
and in particular the Mega Man Sequelitis that Egoraptor made specifically.
Those two were kind of the things that made me realize that like,
oh wow, you can go like so fucking hardcore in analyzing shit online and people are into it.
So you know, those were a game changer.
Jesse Wood is a big one.
He has, I don't like him at all, but it would be, I cannot deny that he's been a large influence on
me, and to an extent every single person in this chat.
Probably, I mean, Ben is my brother, and we collaborated for a long time, and even today.
I would call that a form of mutual influence.
Yeah, I mean, I could say, I could go and be like, oh my dad, and like my teachers,
but like whatever, but still, Ben is someone who to this day, I still
share my stuff with and ask his opinion on stuff.
I think there's a lot of both of our unique preferences in T-Bap, and when I look at them,
I can often see like, oh, this is a me thing, and this is a Nate thing.
Yeah, like all the good stuff's the Nate stuff, all the bad stuff, that's the Ben stuff.
That's correct, that's correct.
No, all the emotional pathos is me.
No, that's all me.
No, I care about feeling this.
No, with Keg and Phantom sitting on that island, looking out into the sunset,
sad about their failures in life, that's me.
Okay, that's all me.
But Keg tucking in Phantom after his horrific nightmare dream, that was all me, and let's
be honest, which of those is more impactful?
All right, moving on.
Now, this probably hasn't been seen a lot yet, but I am kind of obsessed with musical numbers.
Everything that has a musical number.
It has been, because you have like three whole videos of just musicals on it.
I know, and in fact, but you see, that's not really my ideal, and I'll get into this in
a little bit, but I absolutely lose my shit when there's like, and Jesse is the guy who
does this the most, will make a video, and then there's just like a related song in it
that might, that is usually related to what's going on.
That is my favorite thing, and I've aspired to be like that, and you see that in a bunch
of T-Bab videos, and I've actually just wrote a song yesterday to put into a video that's coming
up, and it's going to blow everybody's minds, so I'm being into that shit, and when I was
younger, I did musicals, I did plays, and stuff on stage in high school, and then college a little
bit, so that was, that's something.
And on this note, kind of the one video that I aspire to be like, I know not everyone's going
to be excited about it, but it's Antony C's reviewing his magic part four, Cantralot wedding.
It didn't even have a musical number guy.
No, I know, I was going to say the only thing that could have made it better would have been
musical number, that's the, technically on the technical fronts, not everything is perfect,
but the structure of it, just like laying out shit, and then having a big like catholic reveal at
the end, that is exactly what I love about it.
You know Tommy made that too, right?
I was going to say, I was going to say, Tom was in it, and had a strong, but we know that it was
Antony who wrote it, and did all the, you know, the structuring of the video, so Tom, certainly
to be celebrated.
Is that so?
Um, I mean, I would say he did a lot of the general structure, but there's a lot of writing
stuff that I do as well.
Oh, okay, I heard that he did like a hundred percent of it, and you just did voice over,
so if that's not true, I'm not mistaken.
I wrote all of my lines and made a point to interject a lot of the things I said that he
wasn't going to talk about at all.
Okay, I stand corrected.
So thank you for that, Tom.
Papa bless, moving on.
Okay, the last guy here, the last two, the two specific guys, oh sorry, there's three are just-
Oh my god, how long is this list going to go on?
I don't know dude, there's, I'm almost done.
These three guys are kind of linked together.
Mr. Beetong, Twin Perfect, and Matthew Matosis are just YouTube and a lot of analytical guys,
whatever, they make their shit.
They're someone who I look at a lot, just to get ideas.
And then, I don't know, just at the end, it's just like all the video games I've ever played,
all the anime I've ever watched, and all the manga I've ever read, all that shit.
And shout out to Gurren, Logan, and Kamina as my personal favorite.
That's it.
Okay, let's move on.
Pretty good list.
Yeah.
Hippo, you want to go next?
Yeah, okay.
I don't really know how to start, but I got a lot of-
At the beginning.
Yeah.
I've got a lot of comedy thing, because my comedy is my sole talent, I think, it's my main thing.
Yes, I can confirm that, that's true.
So yeah, I got a comedy, guys.
There's quite a few old things.
There's the Goon Show, which is an old radio show, an English radio show, where these guys,
they just did silly voices, and I liked silly voices, and that's the Goon Show.
There's Monty Python, obviously, we're for sort of the weird out there situations, and
not explaining really anything, and I like all that stuff.
Laurel and Hardy has got a lot of great slapstick, and it made me appreciate comedy timing.
I don't know how well all of this stuff translates into my videos, but I just like it.
Well, the stuff you're saying so far sounds like it's in your videos.
Yeah, like the Monty Python influence, I just totally see that with your live-action stuff,
and you're editing too.
Yeah, I mean, my editing comes mostly from YouTube poop, and then to, I guess,
there was John Tron with all his text stuff.
I don't know, there's AVGN, I'm just reading off a list now.
And then there's Jesse, and Davoo, and Digi, and yeah, I like all your stuff.
Yeah, very recently, Davoo, because I watched all your videos, and I'm like,
you make videos about a singular point, and I like that, and I'm going to try and do that.
I think my puzzle pirates video was made mostly because I watched all those.
Oh, that's cool, but hippo, please, please give us more hippo vits.
I really want more sad hippo, I really liked your April Fool's video,
because it was more of that hippo than I liked.
That was amazing, hippo more than I like you.
For the record, I still love everything that gets posted to the Give and Take channel,
I still always usually find it hilarious.
Yeah, me too.
Just the stuff that he records in five minutes and doesn't give a single fuck about it.
By the way, I also like cold corona more than I like myself.
Absolutely, cold corona got me into vaporwave.
Me too.
I'm not kidding about that, by the way.
Dude, that's totally true, that's totally true for me as well.
All right, Jeff, you want to go next?
I guess, yeah, I just finished typing up my list now pretty much, so that's perfect.
Yeah, so, oh man, I try to take influence from a broad amount of things, but not consciously,
I guess I'd say.
I consume a lot of media, and I think that just informs how I create things in general.
There are some obvious points of reference that, no question, these guys influence how I make stuff.
The Extra Credits, I've been a fan of Extra Credits for a very long time.
Oh no, you blew it on the first one.
I blew it, that's fine.
Hey, wait, what's wrong?
Hey, Extra Credits was at a time, was really great, and they were part of what influence me as well.
Yeah, they were instrumental in my thinking on video games today, like they were big games all the time.
I really like the Extra Credits series, I still like it, I don't know if you guys still like it,
but that's a matter of taste, and like more to the point.
I make the press time, my voice is high-pitched.
Yeah, he sounds like an idiot.
We really gotta make more of these games, so it's just conscious, I know his feelings get hurt.
Let me talk, guys.
Go force your way in.
Yeah, so, A, the voice thing is like something people expect at this point.
You don't have to defend it, but we believe that you like it.
It's one octave per video.
I don't even mind the voice thing, I just hate their fucking milk toast, middle of the road,
like fucking weak ass politics.
That's like a newer thing.
If you watch their older videos, it used to just be they took a fucking game design principle,
and they explained it, and it was really interesting, and they had like 100 great videos.
Who cares, we're talking about influence, like John Tron's not good anymore,
but fucking me talking about him being an influence.
Yeah, he's an influence on lots of people, but yeah, so like, and like I have to-
He was here in his early days, like man, there was a lot of people like that guy.
Okay, I have to acknowledge them like straight up, because as a direct influence,
because Dan's a friend of mine, and he actually gave me a lot of advice for video editing that
has made my videos better, so right off the bat, I've got to acknowledge him.
That's great, next time you see him, you can just punch him in the arm for me.
Just give him one, boom.
And then there's like my film school teacher, Paul Jensen, who taught me a lot about narrative
structure and film analysis and stuff like that.
So those are like the people who I know who have made what I make better,
and then I watch a lot of every frame of painting.
I've watched all of his videos at least like four or five times.
He's kind of what I want to be in a lot of ways, and in the same respect,
Cinefix is, I don't know if you guys- I do not know them.
So Cinefix is one of the best movie channels, probably the best large movie channel and large
list channel on the entire internet, because A, they do movie analysis from a very interesting
in-depth perspective.
They have these videos called Seven Things You Might Not Know, where they just list really
interesting and minute trivia details about different movies, how they were made, what
influenced the story behind them, different details about the differences in the adaptation from
a comic to a movie or what have you, and then they also do these big broad lists that I totally
ripped off the style of in my top 10 anime openings of 2015, where basically they will say,
these are the 10 best scenes in movies of all time, and the way that they do it instead of
like listing just 10 scenes, they list like 50, and every time they get to a point they're like,
we could have gone with all of these different things, which are all great, and that totally
validates like your feeling that this scene is particularly good, but we went with this,
and then they justify why this thing that does say in there is sold me.
I really want to watch this channel.
They are seriously the best movie channel on the internet, and like everything about how
I write my lists is derived from the just that awesomeness.
Yeah, I need something to replace movie Bob now that I finally unsubbed him.
Yeah, they are, let's not dive into that, because that's an example of somebody who's
politics. I just realized I had to out the window. I actually don't even
mind Bob's politics, but whatever. I was just going to say, I forgot to bring up the influence of
all the people who I swore I would never ever become like. Movie Bob is up there for me,
kind of up there in the same vein, but also I really respect what he does is Spoonie,
because I love Spoonie's videos, but how he treats people online, not great.
Oh, that's bullshit. Spoonie doesn't treat people harshly enough. Spoonie should be meaner than
his fucking fans. Jesse, yeah, Jesse, he'd get more Patreon money that way for sure.
Jesse's Patreon money is only exclusively because the people who give him money love
to be abused. Every time I shit on somebody, it's skyrockets. We just saw this like yesterday
with your new video. No, that's true, but yeah, so there are people I'm definitely never want to
be like, but who I take some things from, like Spoonie and John Trun don't want to emulate their
production schedule at all, but their sense of humor definitely influences me. And Aaron's signal,
Mr. Beetong, you guys brought them up before, Egoraptor, Super Bunny Hops, another guy who
I try to get to that. I'm very impressed with how George is able to just like
find the point of something and explore it fully. To your credit, I'd currently describe
you as the bunny hop of anime. I don't think so because he only does OPs. I only do OPs.
He's broadening a little bit. I think the most similar thing between Jeff and George is the
production schedule rate. But I would say that bunny hop is much more about like covering up
like, well, he finds he like, like Jeff said, he finds the point of a game, but he does find the
point of the whole game. Whereas Jeff is mostly focused on individual levels or individual,
you know, OPs or like, you know, elements with the exceptions of some of his game reviews.
They're similarities. I'm trying to do more stuff like that, but it's a lot easier to get
out a weekly video while focusing on one specific scene or one specific thing.
The biggest praise that I've ever gotten was somebody like comparing me to every frame of
painting, which I don't think I deserve. Oh yeah, that's lofty praise.
He's the best editor on YouTube, period.
So then beyond, beyond sort of this, well, I guess we're not beyond the sphere of YouTube yet,
because I also derive a bit of a, a lot of stuff that I never, ever want to do with my videos
from Channel Awesome, just as a general production thing. I think we can all agree on that. I think
we all have them as like our worst guys. A guest's person, what are you doing here?
Nate, you took the words out of my mouth. I know, right? Just, just, just say a word.
Somebody pops in at the end of the review. You try to murder them, that whole thing.
Cat Icarus does that some, a lot of the time, but yeah, so Channel Awesome in general,
there's a lot of stuff I would never fucking do integrating a narrative into my videos. No,
not fucking happening. I'm sorry, Linkara. No, no, I'll,
wait, why are you apologizing to Linkara? I, I don't know. He doesn't deserve any apologies.
Exactly. I like the idea of doing a narrative in a single video. If you could do it easily,
but over a bunch of videos, Jesse does it with every video he puts out as part of a continuing
narrative. Yeah, but, but Jesse integrates it into his script instead of having like a skit
on the side where it's like, now I'm on the bridge of the Starship Enterprise.
And just, if, if the video is about a narrative, then sure. And, and you know,
it uses like a review or whatever as sort of like a framework for the narrative. Yeah,
but if you're just tacking on a narrative onto the outskirts of a video that is supposed to be
a family review. Yeah, Jesse does, like Jesse, I think, does what Spoonie kind of tried to do,
but a lot more efficiently and just better integrated, which is this. Spoonie puts these
like big teasers at the end of his videos and then he won't make another one for like two years.
Yeah. It sucks. But like the, whereas Jesse, it just has a man losing his mind. Yeah, I gotta,
I gotta keep powering through. So there was one person on Channel Awesome who did influence me
in a very, in a very positive way. No, shut, shut the fuck up. Yeah. So no, in how I talk
about anime and how I understand it, Yezu Otaku, Jacob Chapman now working for A&N, who was like
the only good anime reviewer doing video anime reviews on the internet for like a couple years.
And like a lot of what started getting good if you're thinking about anime was
Slim Pickens back in the day, did you? Yeah, it was very Slim Pickens.
And if you're watching video. Watching her videos kind of got me hungry for that kind of
thought about anime and made me want to do that. And I don't think that she's right
a lot about a lot of stuff or he is right about a lot of stuff. But
Wait, is Jesse Otaku a man now? Yes. That's, huh? How about that? Yeah. So anyway,
I don't agree with a lot of his criticism of stuff. But for instance, the fact that he did those
big top lists of the top 10 anime OPs of every year is totally where I got the idea for what's
in an OP. Like just like talking about OPs, I was like, there is not enough of that on the internet.
I am going to do that. So if that is a very obvious point of reference. Now, finally,
I can break away into people in text who influenced me. We gotta speed it up a little bit.
Okay, I'll try to speed it up a little or a lot. Sean Baby, one of my favorite writers on the whole
internet definitely informed my sense of humor quite a lot. Pitchfork, who's a guy who wrote for
SoxMatePeopleSexy.net. Not Pitchfork.com. Life of Pablo 9 out of 10. Yeah, I remember that.
Life of Pablo9outof10.com, yeah. Not that. Oh, you should get that domain. Okay. I should.
Yeah, so definitely not them. But yeah, so he did these epic reviews of the entire Final Fantasy
series that I really appreciated. And, okay, moving forward, faster pace. Okay, Chris.
Just read all the names. Just read them off your list.
Okay, writers, Christopher Moore, Douglas Adams, Terry Pratchett, all informed my sense of humor
and sort of how I string ideas together. Very good writers. Highly recommend you read their stuff if
you want to do more stuff. Forgot your movie sucks. Obvious reasons. Your movie sucks is great.
Monty Python, Abbott and Costello, Justin Rowland, Dan Harmon, James Roday.
You should have got the music that they play at the Academy Awards when we're on Blushy.
Just, I'm feeling this fucking hook around my neck because I'm trying to get through this.
Trey Parker and Matt Stone are movie creators and actors who inform how I make stuff. Also,
Team Four Star kind of informs some of my sense of humor and delivery and whatnot. Sure.
All right, don't fuck you off. I'm fucking bored of listening to you.
Okay, one more. One more. The best friends play, they kind of gave me a lot of how I
want to structure podcasts because they do podcasts without crazy arguments and people
talking over each other. How does this one stack it up by that standard?
It's terrible. Go listen to the best friend cast instead.
We're not friends here.
This is the best group of people who all want to murder each other.
We're the best enemies podcast.
Let's get an artist talking about art shit now.
Cog and a half. All right. Well, my list isn't is pretty short. As an artist,
I think my two major influences are Brian Leo Malley, the Scott Pilgrim guy, and Hiro Oda,
the one piece guy. And when I look at my own art, I can really it really looks like both of them
to me like this. I don't know. Vincent reminds me a lot of
Sanji. Yeah, kind of Sanji. He kind of he kind of looks like Sanji. What about Andrew Hussie?
Oh, yeah, you know, I was gonna say Andrew Hussie. I don't know. There's no like direct
eat a dick. Hey, here's. Hey, everyone. At least he's gotten to the point of knowing who Andrew
Hussie is. That's like we've we've friends, friends and listeners. Hear me. Once you're done,
anyone that hasn't read, then everyone who hasn't read Homestuck should be put through
a fucking meat grinder. That's what I'm home stuck and I'm the biggest idiot ever.
That isn't pretty accurate. That is a pretty accurate parody, honestly. Okay. And yeah,
there's there's yeah, art wise, definitely. Brian Liam Alley and Hira Oda. Hussie, I wouldn't
there's no like direct influence other than that, you know, what he was making and the rate at which
he was made it really, really wanted to made me want to do something like that. I wouldn't call
it a direct influence, but Bakuman, the manga about a bunch of hot blooded Shonen trying to
become great manga artists. Yeah. Again, not so much a direct influence, but like a big
pushed me into wanting to do that with my life.
You know, I think that's it. Oh, and I will. It's one more thing. The Vapors story is largely
inspired by Watamote because like that, it's just about a young person being really shitty. And
that's the whole story. And that's what Vapors is about. I forgot Tim Schaefer and Hideo Kojima.
Tim Schaefer and Hideo Kojima are on my lists. I got three names. I'm just saying quick.
My I got storytelling inspiration and influence from Hira Oda, Okami and Dark Souls. And I'm
not going to elaborate because I'm not very good at telling stories. Okay, cool. All right. Well,
Ben didn't give us enough art stuff. So Tom, now it's your turn. All right. Um, yeah, it's funny
because like originally, I just had to know it. I said YouTube. I don't know sequel artists. I don't
care. I don't remember to have another YouTube channel that I actually care about.
So like reviews, fuck it, whatever. I've watched sequel artists and then I made a horse one and
then it all devolved from there. But Rebel Pixels, like I got the idea for that. Just because I really
I watched way too much technology stuff like I've read and gadget daily for I think
12 years now. So like I know too much about that shit, but I watched the shit out of MKBHD,
who does like ridiculously good tech videos, Linus Tech Tips, another one. And then the idea of
for half of Road Pickles came from a guy on Tumblr called Rebel Pickles. That's what I call my dick.
No. I would have thought that's what you call your balls because you know, there's two of them.
What the fuck Nate? Balls don't look like pickles. Oh, wait, wait. What's wrong with your balls?
But there's it's plural. God damn it. Okay. Maybe the whole set of three you can call the road
Yeah. Oh my God. Wow. I think we've made it. I think we've covered a lot of ground here today.
All right, so
no, so half of Rebel Pixels came from a guy called friend and he's on Tumblr. He reviewed like
Cintiq alternatives. And that's kind of where I found out that those even existed. And as a poor
person, I was initially attracted to the idea of like getting something expensive for less money.
So but he just does text reviews and text is boring. So I was like, if I didn't
make videos about these, I'll make a million dollars. And I was completely wrong, but it's
still fun. And then the other half came from this guy pressed and smiles. He does like a lot of
motivational kind of videos. And I wanted to kind of do something like that with an artist
focus, I guess, because I'm like super impressed and hate myself and hate everything I make. So I'm
like, maybe if I go on this journey, I could not hate myself. So that's kind of I just blended
those two together. And that's where the pixels came from. And also, I've been notified of Roberto
Blake, who I hate. I don't want to ever become as bad as that channel. Who's who's that? He's
a guy who makes like two videos a day. And he just sits in front of a camera. He's like, Hey,
everybody, bro Blake here, helping you create something awesome today. Today, I want to talk
and how does he do that? He does it with like no effort. There's one take. And he has like 80,000
subscribers. He got 70,000 last year. I don't understand why. And if I see him in public,
I'm going to kill it. No, he he has like the same amount you have on Tommy Oliver. Yeah,
but he got that in here. Just talking in front of a camera with no script. And he has a he has
fucking sort of online. Nobody watches his videos. That's the whole thing. He got subscribers. Like
it's really weird how people do that. You if you want to get subscribers really quick, just make
like five videos a week. And you'll get tons of people clicking on them. But no one watches
your other shit because you just like flood your feed. And then nobody cares. You burn them out.
Yeah, that's how I don't know if I don't know if I miss this time. But are there any more
specific influences on like Sorceress Lost? Did I miss that? No, I haven't gotten it yet.
Because like this is just like the YouTube. Yes, stupid. I thought it was wrapping up.
I thought it was wrapping up my bag. For like the artistic side, like I mean my visual style,
I feel is definitely directly influenced a lot from Bill Watterson of Calvin and Hobbes fame.
I just I've read that comic cool religiously ever since like third grade. And it's like my favorite
thing ever is the first comic I ever really got into. Because he has like kind of like the really
cartoony features like the thick outlines. And then like I really fell in love with watercolor
from his color work. Bruce Tim is a huge influence. He did like the DC animated universe,
like the Batman cartoon from the 90s and Justice League. Oh, yeah. Like I like his really like
simplistic kind of blocky figures. Like this main guy or in Sorceress Lost, which I haven't
seen much his jawline is like a square just like Superman. So like I'm totally just aping that.
And like anime in general. But the first one that I read because I watched like Pokemon and
shit as a little kid, obviously, and that was my first exposure to anime. But the first anime
or like manga that I thought was like legitimately beautiful was when I watched
Cardcaptor Sakura and then later got chosen. Yes. Clamp blew my fucking mind. Yeah. Yeah,
that's awesome. And like to this day, I still like love Clamp. So I never would have imagined you
were like influenced by Clamp. Like your style does not at all remind me of Clamp. I mean like
well, you never know. Like I think like the thing that I took from them was like the really big
expressive eyes. Like that's one thing I really latched on to. It's like a Pokemon. Clamp. Clamp.
Jesse is obviously not familiar with the work of Clamp. It's like it's like the it's like the evolved
form of Clannad. Clannad is the baby. Clamp is the peach. Clannad has even bigger eyes than
Clamp. So yeah, Clannad would be the evolved form. Clannad would be the final evolution.
Okay, so if Clannad is a crab with testicles, then what is Clamp as the baby? Clamp is a crab with
one testicle. And if testicle looks like a pickle.
Anything else? The last thing I mean, I just like got a note for like lifestyle slash personality
because like a lot of artists like I don't really take much like visually or like aesthetically
from their work, but just like how they work. I was really influenced by Scott McLeod, who wrote
Understanding Comics. Is he really into Fox McLeod? No. Yeah, he's the same guy. That's just his
persona. But like he did like a really great book called Understanding Comics. It's a comic book
deconstructing how comics work. And he did this like when he was like in his mid 20s. So he's like
a fucking genius. Oh, Ben, is this manga about drawing manga that is awesome as well? Yeah, we
remember when we're, are you showing me that together? Yeah, that's right. That was like.
Oh, um, um, show, the Shojo manga artists. Oh, wait, I have it right here.
I still need to read that book. I was really intrigued by it. It's the coolest. It is called,
it is Shojo Beats Manga Artist Academy and it follows the, and it follows the life of Hitomi,
who is this retarded panda who wants to be a Shojo manga artist. What? And so, no, I'm fucking
serious. And then, and then this guy, Mr. Manga Star, like just like, he like rockets out of the
sky and is like, I'm here to show you how to become a Shojo manga artist with hot-blooded passion.
And she's like, yay, but I'm so stupid. I can't do anything. And he just like beats her.
He seriously beats the shit out of her and like sends her off to train with like other
like famous Shojo manga artists who like give instructional, it's like an instructional book.
And there's like, you know, they talk about their techniques for various things,
and then she'll come back and he'll be like, Mr. Manga Star will be like, so, Hitomi,
what did you learn from fucking, uh, uh, you, you, you Kako Isaka? And she'll be like, hmm,
I learned. Oops, I forgot. And he'll just fucking beat the shit out of her and send her to another
one. I want to make a quick add to everything I learned. I learned from Mr. Manga Star. Forget
this is a guy. And, and I won't, I won't spoil the ending, but there is a heartfelt twist
ending. I don't even know what that is. I'm totally serious. Yeah, there is a heartfelt twist ending
that really makes you, that really recontextualizes the whole thing. Awesome. I won't spoil it.
All right. So Tom is that Shojo beats Manga Artist Academy. Go find it. Tom, is that all of your
influences? I have two more that there's m dot strange. He's a YouTuber and he did, he made
three animated feature films by himself over the course of five years. That sounds like a cool
rap name. M dot strange. He actually, he does do really horrible music as well. Awesome. So if you
ever want to check that out. But I just got really, because before I watched him, because I found him
like 2006 when YouTube like still didn't really exist. And like they have like featured videos.
You remember those when they used to have like featured videos on the front page? He had a
trailer for his first movie on there and it blew my mind to a million fucking pieces. First movie,
he makes movies. He made three animated feature films by himself over the course of five years.
Yeah. The first one. Wait, who's this? Jesus Christ. What a champ. Who's this? M dot strange.
You can just, he's just youtube.com. Tom has done a review of one of his films. I don't think anybody
watches your videos as much as I do, but I'm well aware of M dot strange as a guy who you even worked
with at a time, right? Yeah, we talked a lot. I did help him do some animation for, he did a music
video for my self-indulgence and I did some animation for him on that. Whoa, what the fuck?
I never heard about that. Yeah. Tom has worked on an MSI music video. I do remember you. I do
remember, I do vaguely remember your review of that. Yeah, he's super cool. He's like a total
weirdo. Did you fully disclose that you have affiliations with him? Yeah.
Collusion influenced by people you know. So, Tom, is that it? And then also this guy, Alec
Longstreet, he does really personal slice of life, zine kind of comics things. I feel like
bind and photocopy all of them in his house and then ship them out to people. Has he heard of
the internet? He has, but it's like just checking. There's a weird underground indie scene where they
still just do that hardcore old school way of doing things. That's cool. His thing is he just
works on comics every day. He's done comics for like 10 years. He's done comics every day,
that entire time except for like three days. He missed them because I used to watch his podcast
that like they interviewed all these like indie guys and I was like super into him and he's like
this is the coolest guy. He's super like positive and happy and shit and I met him at a convention.
He was super chill. We talked for half an hour. So, yeah. Sounds like a hero. So, I think Jesse
should go last and I believe I should go second last. Oh, I forgot you haven't gone yet. Oh my
gosh. You're next to Vue. All right. Cool. I forgot about you. So, trying to co-opt my hosting
duties. I know what order everybody's going in. All right. Well, let's see. My influences are here.
The two that are in this chat in this call is Digi Bro and Jesse Wood because they both got me
into making videos and stuff. Let's see. James Rolfe for obvious reasons. Hang on, Vue. I just
want to ask when did you start making videos if they got you into it? Well, I mean, I first started
making videos in 2008, but they were the ones really who made me want to do it as a career thing.
Because it's just because you're a great editor, better than me, and it makes me mad all the time.
Seriously? Maybe I'm faster than you. I guess like edits per minute, I'm better than you,
but I don't think I have as much polish as you do. And you have like,
you didn't make videos at all until like 2013. But whatever. I guess edits per minute, I'm pretty
high, whatever. But yeah, I have. Well, anyway, I was just interested. Yes. So, yeah, it was really
Digi Bro and Jesse. Oh, man, I said his last name. Ah, beep, beep, beep. Them doing their early
horse cast episodes, constantly bitching about doing YouTube. And I was like, those are the kind
of problems I want to have. And James Rolfe, not just for the idea of making videos, but also a
lot of his writing style. I think he's like the best at conveying simple ideas or no, conveying
obtuse ideas very simply. My brother, who's my number one comedic influence influence,
because he's a very funny person. And we always iron out one another's comedy.
And I assume he's a younger brother. Yeah, he's three years younger, three inches taller.
Trey Parker and Matt Stone was early into me getting inspired to like, I always knew that art
was going to be my career. But those people really, those guys lit a fire under my ass kind of because
I heard about them constantly bitching about how hard it was. And it was really inspiring, you know,
and South Park in general was a big influence for me. It was like my awakening to more complex
ideas, you know, Rush Limbaugh. I take a lot of influence from him on how to convey ideas,
how to present yourself as a person and not expect that one. Okay, how to how to like,
be a personality, how to communicate with an audience to make the audience feel like you're
talking to them. Okay, how to inspire people to kill everybody that you don't like. How to,
how to like, like, be a persona, like his persona is very, he's got a persona. That's for sure.
It's very similar to like an internet person. Wasn't Rush Limbaugh the villain in Biker Mice from
Mars? I don't know what that is. You know what, he could actually be and I would have no idea.
No, no, no, sorry, he was like a fish monster named Limburger. I think it might have been like
Rush Limburger. Okay, okay. It might have been a pun. And also like his persona is very internet
like like Maddox and Jimquisition even kind of reminded me in similar, in different ways,
although I think Rush is a lot more interesting and fun than Jimquisition, but whatever.
Yeah, I would say I would say I would think I think Rush Limbaugh has had more influence on me
than any other one individual person who I personally know. Look, man, look, here's the
problem of the arguments we've had. No, no, not that. But look, here's the problem. I can't
recommend his show because it's a radio show. It's it's a half it's an hour and a half of show
and an hour and a half of commercials. It's unlistenable. If you just released a one hour
podcast once a week, everyone on the everyone I know would be super into it. He's really funny.
It's just that the format of the show is dated and terrible, but hit the content is great.
Just take my word for it. Okay, I'll believe I used to have a blue collar job. So it was a
it was I was able to listen to that. Here you can eat my issue the way he animates the universe
is the way I wish the universe could be. Movie Bob was really the beginning of me understanding
the idea of like an intellectual thesis on things. Very interesting in that regard. And now he's
and for a long time he's also been my counter influence of who I don't want to be.
But I agree with his politics. I think that everyone is a fat neck beard and everyone should
be ashamed for it, except for me. I should get fat and have a neck beard and be totally fine about
it. Okay, Popeye also portrays the world. Not really the character so much as just the show.
What about the character or the show? Mostly the show. No, the character himself. The real live
Popeye. What the fuck is going on in here right now? Mostly the show. It also when I first watched
Kill La Kill really, it reminded me of Popeye, the way it like abstracts the world in a really
over the top energetic way. I thought that was really fun. I just I want the world to be like
that. It's just a cool nice escapism that really is really nice and fun and everything bounces.
Wow, this is a fascinating list so far. Let's see. I knew all this was coming too because I've
seen his. This is exactly the kind of list I would expect from the movie. I love it. I love it.
The little rascals, which was I think it's its original title is Our Gang. That's a really cool
thing. That's an old film serial black and white series thing. And I think it got me into like
long protracted comedy because at the time it felt pretty long. Are you talking about the show or
like there was a movie little rascals that was in color? Right, I'm talking about the show. Yeah,
that little film series thing. Yeah, I just I thought like because the situations are kind of long
and protracted and I think that gave me a taste for that kind of stuff. The Marx Brothers obviously
that got me into like slapstick and all that stuff. I have economic science written here because
that really portrays the world in a way that makes a lot of sense to me. Economic science was a big
influence. Yeah, you know, specifically, that's a that's a book. Well, there's that one book,
basically economics with Thomas Stahl, which I was talking about, whatever, you know, a more
interesting one was an episode of Planet Earth about rainforests and it talks and it shows this
tree falling and how all the different plants try to get some sunlight. And I was like, that's what
the world is like, you know, there's like something out there, like, whether it be money or like
success or like friendship, there's always like a source of it and everyone rushes to get it. And
that a big tree that tries to become huge is going to have a harder time than a little tree.
That's why I guess that was part of why I was like, I don't have to become a millionaire doing
something huge. I can be like a thousand air making YouTube videos and I will be more happy
than a guy trying to get all this stuff. No, I totally am with you on that.
Russia is a big rush when Bob, he lives that lifestyle and he loves everything about it,
right, Ben? I love being dirt poor. I want to I want to make as little money as possible for me
to survive on no work. If I can do that, then I've achieved everything I want. All right,
adventures of Sonic the Hedgehog, big influence on my slapstick sensibilities. I love that.
Although I was a chili dog one. Yeah, yeah, yeah. You know, I rewatched some of it because I was
trying to get a clip of it for my most one of my recent videos and it doesn't hold up that well,
but man, very inspiring to me. Okay. Daft Punk, you know, because I don't know, maybe I have
latent autism. So I'm really I was really into them when I was 14, you know, have they inspired
you to stay up all night to get lucky? I don't know. I don't know if that was a joke or anything,
but that was a good reference. Roger Vanderweet, the other YouTuber who really influenced me,
Roger Vanderweet, who like introduced me to the concept of an analysis as distinct from a review,
although he didn't introduce me to the word analysis. That's what Digibro did, but he really
got me into the idea of... Wait, wait, sorry. Did he taught you the word analysis? Well, I knew
the word analysis, but I never really thought of it as the word to use to describe what we do.
You know? Okay. Roger Vanderweet just thinks of it as theories or something. He doesn't really
know what word to use because English isn't his first language. His writing sucks. His animation
sucks. His voice acting sucks. He really is just bad at everything. Everything sucks about this guy,
but he's one of my biggest influence. But he's awesome. He definitely does more good than anyone
else who sucks that much. He really is amazing. I love his thought process, the way he thinks.
Like, he can make a blog about him moving out of his family's house and how everyone was fighting
over the furniture, and it was fascinating. I was on the edge of my seat the way he wrote,
even though every sentence had a typo. D'Vu, here's... D'Vu, I've thought about it a lot because I
went and watched Sonic dissected and I didn't like it, but upon further reflection, I really think
that where it failed for me was in not providing any context for someone who doesn't know the
Sonic games to enjoy their thoughts that much. I didn't know the Sonic games that much, but now
I practically know I can probably recite all of the main games in order, things to his videos.
Very interesting. Like a Mr. B-Tongue video, like this video about Jango. I can enjoy that video
without having seen Jango. I cannot enjoy Sonic dissect without having played Sonic. You didn't
watch it, so that might make it harder to follow. In regards to that Mr. B-Tongue, I got into Mass Effect
because I watched Mr. B-Tongue's video over and over and over and over again, and now I'm...
Yeah, Mr. B-Tongue's been a really big influence, too, because I have like... There was like a whole...
There was like a summer where I just was at work playing his videos like every day
to the point that I was starting to almost trying to imitate, obviously not well,
imitate his writing style. But yeah, Roger Grandeur, I love his train of thought. Every
time I think, you know, this guy is just so bad and inconsistent, but then he comes out with a video
that blows my mind. So yeah, I just... Like he recently came out with a 40-minute video analyzing
his own 20-minute parody animation and just hearing his thought processes.
So what you're telling me is even though he sucks in every way, he's the best guy ever.
Yeah, pretty much. Okay. So like you?
Yeah, let's see here. Mr. Bean, big influence on just like... I don't know, more comedic sensibilities,
you know, more protracted situations. Didn't influence me on talking, though. I still talked
way too much. And I got three more items left. Steve from Blue's Clues, big influence on me.
I just want to point out, Davoo, you were giving me shit in the chat, in the text chat for talking
too much. I got three items left to go. Steve from Blue's Clues, definitely the biggest influence
on my persona, the way he talks, presents himself. Why would you pick him? It wasn't intentional at
all. You see, the way my persona comes from these really unwatchable sketch comedies I did with my
brother. And that was sort of a parody of like kid show hosts. But I realized it was just a parody
of Steve from Blue's Clues. So that whole like, sort of like weird, like dozing off personality,
really like that. Take a lot of influence from food, because if I have to make a metaphor for
something, I'll use food, you know. Wait, wait, in what like, you want to act like food? Well, like,
for example, a couple weeks ago... Do you have a food sauna? Well, let's see, a few weeks ago,
Digi and Jesse were like making rap songs together. And I was like, I want to get down the action.
I want to make a beat. What's something I can make a hamburger. So now they made a beat about
hamburgers, right? So I just always use hamburgers. Big influence on my artistic group. I've seen
that before. You've listed food as a big influence. I mean, if you... All of this was on his chart.
You know, I have flashbacks now to it. I remember, and I didn't, I thought it was playing real fast
and loose with the concept of an artistic influence. Yeah, me and Ben discussed it. We thought like,
okay, well, DeVu like has to eat food to live without it. He would die. He needs to be allowed
to make stuff. Obviously, there's some connection here, but you're saying, okay. And the last
influence is video games and the specific way of like, it's a way to like systemize life. Like,
I wonder what's up with all those business guys who like making money, even if they don't like
spending it? Oh, it's like an MMO. What's up with people who want to start a family? Oh, it's like
a stimulation game. You know, so I just looked at through video games at the lens to process the
variables of life and come to an understanding. I think it's more that those games just tap into
the kind of, you know, desires in humans. Well, duh, it just gives me an understanding.
Yeah. So, so I think you have, you have the chain of which resembles which reverse. Yeah, well,
yeah, but not whatever. All right. I disagree. All right, Jesse, do you want to go next or should
I go next? Oh man, can anyone follow DeVu? Yeah, like, damn, it's tough. Rush Limbaugh,
a tree falling down, economic science and Popeye. Look, man, everyone who says anything
you've ever heard about Rush Limbaugh is in the past year. These are the ingredients chosen to
create the perfect DeVu. Look, man, I gotta say this, anyone who's ever said anything about Rush
Limbaugh is someone competing for his time slots. They're not going to represent him properly. It's
just that you can't listen to his show because it's a bad format. I have listened to Rush Limbaugh
before and like, he does speak very well. We're not here to question your influences. All right,
Jesse, do you want to go next or should I go next? Um, yeah, I guess I'll go next. Okay. Alrighty.
I have influences. At least one.
I'd like to hear it.
What's happening?
It's just, it's Jesse saying goddamn influence.
Fucking no, these guys. You're like, you're like, uh, who is it? The Hulk, your favorite
wrestler. I know. You like the Hulk. You're like, you're like Shredder from Ninja Turtles.
Jesse, you made an enormous chart. I know, I'm looking at it right now as a matter of fact.
I know you listed a bunch of influence at the end of Horseshoe.
Yeah, I did. I bought a bunch at my base. That was a really cool thing. I love that.
And now, and now Jesse's just looking at this chart and he's like, what the fuck?
It's more like the chart is looking at me. It's going through me. Like in every one of Jesse's
videos, he dumps references to stuff that he loves and all of them. And now he's not able to
fucking articulate it. We can all do a better job. Let's go right now. No, I can tell from Ninja
Turtles. No, no, no, no, no, no. That's what you jumped to. Of course. Like I thought you were
going to be legit. Donatello, Commander Shepard, Vegeta, Goofy. There you go. There you go.
Helga from Hey Arnold taught you, man, and you'll love. Yeah, definitely all my fucking
waifus and daughter-ruiser on there. They're influential. Yeah. Okay. I was thinking about
this lately or I think about this a lot. Yeah. I mean, is that there's a disconnect I feel
between how my viewers view me and how I view myself because they all view me as like a reviewer,
but I don't see myself as like, if I put the word review on a video, it's not really a review. It's
usually just retardation. Yeah. I do not see you as a reviewer anymore. Like none of my influences
are reviewers or critics. Like they're all like stand-up comedians or professional wrestlers or
musicians or like fictional characters. Except for like AVGN. That's true. AVGN is a pretty good.
And like Sean Baby was a big influence on my writing. Yeah. Yeah. The greatest writer on the
whole internet, pretty much. Who is Sean Baby? Sean Baby used to write for EGM and now he writes
for Cracked and he writes pretty much the funniest things that you can possibly imagine. Yeah. He
has like their descriptions of shit. His, my favorite analogy that I've read of his lately
is just like the writer of this show is the reason that they don't allow pregnant entrants
and belly flop competitions. Oh, he wrote these guys. No, he is that guy. He invented that on the
internet. I think his Twitter says that he invented being funny on the internet. Yeah. And it's kind
of true. His Tumblr is Liartown USA where he just posts the best photo shops in the history of the
world. Like, for instance, the what, how book of horse arson?
Enough about Sean Baby, though. We got to get, Jesse has a lot of influences. No,
fuck that. I want to talk about Sean Baby. Sean Baby's the, oh god. One of my favorites was,
he was describing the Gamecube controller and he described it as having been vomited by a moon octopus.
By the way, I went to his website just now and I see that on it is an advertisement for a
make it yourself fuckable Easter fleshlight. I think I've probably read a bunch of his stuff
if he writes for Cracked because it's a time where I read like every Cracked article and I can't
even remember that some of them had amazing articles. He is the funniest guy on Cracked,
period. That quote that I just gave you was from one of his Cracked articles.
Oh god, he also was just like, this guy's such a liar. It's like fucking John Travolta telling
the guy on his dick that he's not gay. And then like he brings up John Travolta like 10 other
times in that article. It's just like, you know, it's like John Travolta saying he genuinely
doesn't know the gender of the guy on the other side of the hole in the menstrual.
Okay, this guy rules obviously. Yeah, and like this is all related to, these are all metaphors
related to how bad Superman is at hiding his identity from Lois Lane. And how Lois Lane's
the worst fucking human being in the world. It's like, like 20 people died because you wanted to
build a giant electromagnet to trap Superman, you fucking cunt. Oh god, and just his like he makes
the funniest, funniest photo shops. My favorite, my favorite one that I remember is a book that's
out or loud and allowed one bisexual man's struggle with society's acceptance of and
total indifference to his lifestyle. So now I'm looking at my little influence map I'll go
into like the comedians corner. Doug Stanhope is a big influence. I think you can probably see
that if you watch him. He's his whole shtick is that he's a drunken slob but also occasionally
profound. Yeah, that sounds like you. And then Norm McDonald who is like totally irreverent and
like complete retardation. And and then George Carlin is obviously the biggest one. And the
the biggest thing about George Carlin that influences me is that he knew dead. Yeah, my dream
in life. George knew like when to be smart but he also knew that there was a place for being
completely retarded. Like he's famous for like saying profound things and being like the thinking
man's comedian. But my favorite George Carlin bit is the one where he comes up with like a new
sports cheer and he goes this is a new sports cheer that you can say at like a football game.
Ratshit batshit dirty old plot 69 assholes tied in a knot hooray lizard shit fuck
it's just completely stupid and it's like and it's sandwiched between all this like really
intelligent social commentary and then it's just hooray lizard shit fuck yeah I mean you gotta love
how that I mean that you're so right that like that kind of completely retarded stuff juxtaposed
against brilliance is like man it's such a potent potent potion you got there's too strong of a
potion for me. I think the seven words you can't say on television is one of the single greatest
just speeches of all time not even bits of comedy I don't know I don't get I don't get
either I'm a huge fan of Carlin's uh thing about time it's from like when he was really young and
he does the speech about how like time doesn't make any sense as a concept it's like yeah the
planet is like the most philosophical humor I've ever heard. Anytime he talks about religion it's just
incredible. I think with Jesse like if I could just uh you know compliment you for how Carlin
like you are because I think you totally nail like his delivery of like rants where it's like
he really does sound angry but it's still funny yeah like he he comes off as like he definitely
legitimately cares about this he's never like flippant about it he's like I can't fucking believe
I live in this fucking world you know but it's still hilarious the man was the man was a poet you
know and then and then you would see like interviews with him like sort of offstage and
out of character and he's like a totally chill guy and he you know yeah like he's like he saves it
for his performance like all that I think one of the most Carlin-esque jokes that that I remember
from you that I that that is the one that nobody laughs at because I get you just it was too like
obtuse but at the start of the Hello Kitty review where you just do this like
like it sounds like you're talking normally but you just make these name associations and it's
like a whole minute of you just saying names that create this weird train of thought to connect
back to Hello Kitty yeah it just sounds like nonsense yeah but when you like if you actually
pay attention to it then it's like it all has a logical present one of his his later ones like
later in his life his modern man bit which yeah that's the one that I was thinking of isn't even
comedy it's not even a joke right it's just a poem that he wrote but because he's George Carlin he
can do that on a comedy special and just like it's cool shit and I feel like whenever you do your
your like whenever you describe yourself it's very much like that bit where you're like you know I'm
the the old school fool with that old school cool it's that makes a carlin and wwe wrestler dudes
you know yeah um yeah the wwe wrestlers like or any wrestlers you know like wrestlers are like
probably my primary influence on my comedy and my persona or whatever my performances wrestling
promos and um I was thinking about this too because I made that fuck off video where I was
railing against that shitty commenter right and um like the thought process behind that video was
you know I've been thinking for a while that it would be fun to rail on shitty commenters in the
video and I got a comment that was really shitty so I just said I'm gonna cut a promo on this guy
and it'll be funny so I did that but like so many of the commenters were like I don't understand why
you care so why it bothers you so much like they think that I'm like that I'm sitting in the shower
like a rape victim about my commenters and like really stewing about this when in reality what it
is is I think I just I enjoy having an enemy that I can cut a promo on and it's just fun like it's
it was fun to rail on that guy like because that's where my influences is it's perfect like Roddy
Piper would like watch anyone who like if you do if people don't understand like what I'm doing when
I cut promos on people are rail against commenters just watch like any Roddy Piper promo where he's
just like insulting people in hilarious ways and going really off Jesse if I if I had watched
wrestling as a child would I better understand what you're doing when you cut promos because when
you because when you say things like this it makes me think that maybe I don't know what Jesse's
actually going for well I think people take my anger like way too seriously I think I mean what
you say I mean what you're saying right now is tell me that yeah I do but like shit I couldn't I
couldn't tell that you weren't serious I don't want to know I don't want to know whether or not Jesse's
actually angry when Jesse started up the drowning in kayfabe channel like because I never known anything
about wrestling and then like as Jesse taught me about wrestling by like giving these long speeches
about it it was like everything immediately made sense to me about Jesse's persona like every
wrestling video I have ever watched that Jesse has sent me has made me go oh my god you did this
like gross is something that you've been trying to do like the horse finale is literally the
fucking CM punk pipe bomb made into a film you know it's like like don't get me wrong I am I am serious
in the sense that like yeah dumb comments annoy me those these armchair psychologists on my comment
section really do annoy me but I blow it up to 11 that's like what it's that's what performance is
all about that it's fun because I get this this complaint too where people are like you can't take
criticism or stuff when I respond to criticism and it's like no it's more that it's really interesting
to me to respond in in kind like you know yeah it's like someone left a comment on your video and
you then made an art piece out of that comment in a way exactly it's like when I was growing up I
didn't get WWE at all I thought it was gay uh and then I learned it was also uh for Jesse so you
know what does that say about him it says that I'm super gay yeah yeah but yeah like yeah guys like
I don't know what you thought would happen if you thought you would end bad comments forever no I
thought I would make fun of a stupid guy and it would be awesome and hilarious and cool which it was
yeah like I mean I was surprised that I ended up watching the full 15 minutes of that video when
I started I was like oh it's gonna be one of those videos and then I watched the whole thing I was
like it was one of those it's pretty riveting yeah I don't think I've ever stopped watching a Jesse
video halfway through it's it's hypnotic oh bloody dead man I'm gonna have to take a while to get
through I couldn't watch bloody dead man I did not finish bloody dead man because I stopped to go do
something else in the middle of it because the last episode of a race came out and I had to watch
it I didn't get I can't blame anyone for not finishing bloody dead man but at the same time I'm
really proud that I made bloody dead man yeah that's good I don't get the wrong character I was laughing
consistently through bloody dead man but it was around the part where like you started up the
songs and everything and I was just like I yeah or when you were in that girl's live stream for
like 20 minutes yeah well you got further than me yeah that video fucking sucks yes you all
suck for not watching it and I take back what I said I don't blame you I do blame you I need to
go back into your homework and watch the bloody dead man from start to finish so fuck you yeah
I watched it but I didn't watch this one man Batman I can't believe it
I made up for it by not finishing the other one okay okay um yeah the wrestlers oh my god are we
gonna hit two yes we are yeah we're talking about my influences yeah all right all right let's not
bring that into it yeah okay Roddy Piper was a great like improvisational insulter and he's
really cool and funny and out of control and great and like frenetic or whatever I don't know
frenetic is a real word but um energetic I think it would ever who cares CM punk is another one of
the big influences because like CM punk like brought so much like fire and passion and anger
and like conviction to everything he said like with CM punk nothing is ever like I don't like you
and I'm gonna beat you up CM punk is you are the problem with this fucking world and I will kill
you motherfucker like that's when I do stuff like that that's probably a little bit of CM punk in me
macho man just said weird fucking shit and he had so much style and charisma and he was just like
way out there and Mick Foley uh Mick Foley is probably my favorite of all of them in terms of
like promos because I think Mick Foley uh dude love cactus jack mankind all of his monikers
his different personas which is also a thing that I do I guess yeah bottom yeah definitely learning
about Mick Foley there was this great article on like the attitude era yeah it was good about it
and like reading about Mick Foley made me go like this must be where like not not just like not that
all your characters are like that but like when you get into the really emotional stuff yeah
the characters are really interacting with each other that's like I think is like the best actor
that wrestling has ever had like Mick wouldn't just cut promos like I hate this guy and I'm gonna
beat him up he would like draw from like real big emotions and like childhood trauma and like
you know when Mick Foley was a little boy I ate a worm to try to impress these kids they laugh so
I did it again oh Jesus but then rumor got around us as kids tend to make rumors and soon it wasn't
Mick Foley ate a worm to make some kids laugh it was Mick Foley eats worms every day you think any
girl wanted to kiss me after that you think I had a prom date that hurt JR that hurt my feelings
and like that is JR you monster that is so awesome that's like the best promo ever I love Mick
he has so much emotion and that's another thing that I get like people love to dismiss anything
that you say on the internet by saying oh you're crying you're whining you just you're on the verge
of tears because you're complaining about your comments like do you not understand what acting
is yeah exactly like if you're fucking delivering a performance you convey emotion you dummies you
you're dumb um I I just I just I couldn't I couldn't tell it was a performance because I'm such a good
actor I'm so good I could not you know maybe maybe you're right maybe you're right you know I I too
have a difficulty distinguishing when Jesse is being serious well because it comes from a real
place you're just arguing for immersion in media and Jesse's I always understand you get immersed
in his emotional plight and I enjoy being there I like to if you know it's taking emotions and
turning them to 11 it's taking like a it's taking like a consistent minor annoyance and blowing it up
to I'm gonna blow my fucking brains out in front of you people just to prove a point because I hate
you you know all of us talk about how like wrestling influences you it like it it kind of makes sense
of that whole um the fact that I kind of connect to you in my brain to Spoonie and the stuff that
he makes except that you make stuff much more frequently yeah I think he sort of does the
same thing yeah he's definitely obviously very wrestling influenced mm-hmm yeah like he always
talks about like I think his his biggest influence is like Hulk Hogan and the ultimate warrior and
that beef and like that that sort of amy style whereas you take the more natural um style but
like a lot of the creators who I enjoyed on YouTube seem to take stuff from wrestling like
Takahata one-on-ones a big wrestling fan and he uh you see that show up in how the team
for star does DBZ a bridge and you could you could almost say that wrestling promos were like the
precursor to YouTube it kind of they kind of are yeah um and like now that's coming full circle
with the new day being a yeah the new day our youtube act like yeah like their gimmick essentially
is that they're three fucking youtubers who also wrestled yeah um three dorks and it's great
they're yeah they're jesse great guys talked about the macho man brandy savagery did talk about
the macho man I ain't laid a lift out not today no sir no all right whatever it is all right I
have a couple more uh the muppets are a big influence on my on my more cartoonish qualities I
guess my more zany stuff the horse head stuff yeah I love the fucking muppets is that muppet
related yeah I'm gonna say yes the muppets actually taught me to feel I was born a psychopath
there you go there you go the muppets taught me to the muppets taught you to like stick a hand
up your proverbial butt and fake emotions like the felt puppet you are I will never forget when
Jesse described that he was on the flight to brony con in 2014 and he just started thinking
about kermit the frog and just burst into tears trying the whole flight I think about kermit the
frog so cute I don't think that any joke in the history of television has ever made me laugh
quite as hard as the very first episode of the muppet show where kermit is drinking a glass
like a milkshake out of a straw and the milkshake is slowly going down in the glass as he sips
and he just turns to the camera and he says think about this for a minute folks
holy shit that's that's brilliant wait what's the joke he's a puppet he can't drink where's it going
yeah I think about this word that's oh my god I love it yeah that that that plane ride story
because it's like it was my first time being on a plane or going to brony con and I was like
being there to like be a celebrity and it was really like kind of overwhelming and I was on
the plane just thinking about it and I was like looking out at the clouds and I started thinking
about like you know I bet kermit would be really proud of me right now and then I started looking
out at the clouds and I started thinking rainbows are visions illusions
oh man this is this is making me tear up I came to really understand Jesse's like mindset of like
how emotional you really get like because there's a lot of you know jokes and kayfabe and all that
stuff about your videos it's like hard to parse and stuff but like when you told me that story I
was like yeah Jesse like really legitimately cares about like these stories like not just in like an
intellectual way but in like a he will cry just thinking about kermit kind of way you know kermit
kermit's like a surrogate father I mean like that that that shit is making me
me
weird owl is a huge influence on I've always been like a parody songwriter kind of guy like
everything I do is a parody essentially yeah um yeah weird owl I'm sorry I don't have more to say
about weird I think weird owls a bit of interest to me yeah yeah weird owls weird owls he's
fucking weird owl he's the man he's he's very clean he invented comedy yeah that's right he invented
comedy off the internet yeah yeah yeah um and then uh my two biggest like influences in terms of like
my writing are Rod Serling and Hideaki ono I guess ono is more of like a directing than a writing
but like Rod Serling from the Twilight Zone he was the narrator of the Twilight Zone he wrote like
every episode almost yeah he was the greatest genius whoever lived one of the greatest philosophical
minds in human history the narrator wrote the show yeah he I thought that was just a guy they got
no he was his party it was it was his thing wow yeah and dang like that's how I can't
fucking believe you like didn't know that he wrote the whole fucking show you like piece of
track Rod Serling was like he was so human like his his stories had we're all like like sci-fi
horror stories but they had this really human soul to them and that's like human center and like
his narration I talked about this in my christmas video how like he was so good at like
summing up the emotional point of something in like one or two sentences that was so powerful
like that show it was like it was like the horror star trek you know it just got to it had an idea
it got to the heart of it and it was fucking awesome the whole time Rod Serling is the coolest
in short there's nothing mightier than the meek oh all right I'm moist yeah he's incredible he's
the best guy who ever lived and uh Anno Keiaki Anno the director of Evangelion is a huge influence on
me not just because I constantly talk about Evangelion not not just because you want to marry
Asuka he wants to adopt Asuka and give her a real home oh god when people say Asuka I want to kill
everything it's Asuka come on I oh yeah you're a fucking anime guy you're Azuka of course
Azuka is really cool Shinji he really rules Shinji and Rei I really like Rei Rei
all right anyway why is Ava influential yeah or Anno okay because Anno is like the best guy
in the entire world ever in the history of art at in terms of conveying huge emotions through
just his directing like if you watch like the end of Gunbuster when they see the message on the earth
and they're flying in that moment like that is the end of what you're gonna do my Hogan video
is so influenced by Anno like just it's like a wordless just the I I'm not I'm just sounds like
I'm patting myself in the back here but I'm not I'm patting Anno on the back man for making me cool
it's so weird to hear you reference Gunbuster like that I don't associate with you at all but
yeah I mean that is Jesse said that he's he has he's had like a video written about Gunbuster
forever I know but if you put it out that would change my perspective probably isn't it is there
gonna be a best anime ever about Gunbuster I've got a aim for the top best whatever in the works
already it's already written so hot dog yeah all right Jesse what else you got um yeah I guess
that's fucking it I mean there's fucking yeah Maddox is there Maddox has always been an influence
and lately his best buddy Dick Masterson is like equally as much of an influence yeah that's like
an influence that I love Dick Masterson is a fucking hero a gentleman and a scholar
he's a gentleman and a scholar he's so much nicer than Maddox he's such a much of a better you know
he makes me realize that I was wrong for being influenced by Maddox all these years I should
have been on the Dick Masterson train man this is really fascinating for to hear me praise you
you should admit you're all you guys praise this yeah I should have written the dick just
cuz I I just I listened to like two or three episodes now do not have this love for him I'm
really looking for you guys have hyped him up so much dude can't wait to get into this dude my love
for dick increases every day yeah yeah I like when I listened to the whole podcast I felt like I
was kind of half and half but now that I'm re-listing to it I'm like I think I agree with Dick on
everything it's just so much easier to agree with him it really is that his persona in the podcast
changes a lot over it where he starts off really trying to be like flippant and he saw it as like
this is a comedy show this is like we should be in character and then over time it's really around
like episode like in the 30s or so and they really start like every episode is a huge social issue
that it becomes that like the facade kind of drops and uh it's kind of inevitable with every
discussion even early on he's complaining about things like too much swearing right what a fucking
he's kind of a big trash yeah he's even when he was trying to be like his satirical character
all right so I guess I'm going last uh thankfully saving me for the end has made me really have
to piss so now I'm gonna try to go faster just so I can piss at the end of this all right so Jesus
man where do I even start though because like for me I guess the first big influence on like what I
do now is magazines like reading magazines when I was a kid because uh you know growing up I was
really obsessed with everything I got into it was like I was super obsessed with Beast Wars for a
while and then Power Rangers and then like Godzilla and the Lost World and then Pokemon
and like when I got into Pokemon I would I just get everything related to it you know I'd buy like
there's a magazine with Pokemon on the cover I gotta have it you know so I had like all these
Beckett Pokemon collector magazines oh god I had those things yeah those are awful uh I had their
DBZ collector too god yeah I've seen some of those yeah and and Beckett Yu-Gi-Oh collector
which they came out with every uh so I had an intellectual publication I had all these Beckett
Pokemon collectors and then my mom had gotten us a subscription to Nintendo Power because it came
with like a free uh Pokemon trading card game for the Game Boy like um it came with that so she
she got a subscription for that purpose and then like so I had Nintendo Power coming in all the
time and this made me into a huge Nintendo fanboy just because I was like you know reading the
propaganda essentially but it was funny because I didn't really like reading at the time so I
didn't really read these magazines so much as like really take in their structure and like the
and the like the meta elements of it so I loved that every every magazine would open with like
they'd have the letters from fans and then they'd have the like top 10 lists where like fans had
voted on what were their top 10 games like Nintendo games and stuff um you know then they'd have like
a fan art section and then they'd get into the articles and be like big features and the small
features send an email to players pulse because I sent a couple I sent a couple of those I was
I was a big Nintendo power fan too but yeah but yeah and then they had the reviews at the back
and I was really into like I wouldn't like read the reviews per se but I'd look at the scores and
like and I when I say that I don't mean that I was looking at the scores to like make a judgment
on what the game is but I was fascinated with the idea that there was like the highest scored game
because at the time it was like Ocarina of Time in Perfect Dark had like when I first read the
magazine they had a percentage system and it was like 98 percent for Ocarina of Time and 96 percent
for Perfect Dark and like no other games were close to that so I was like really fascinated with
this idea that there was like the best game and that it was somewhere out there you know and so
like a lot of my obsession with lists and scoring system and like systems and like looking at other
people's lists and trying to figure out like what are the most highly valued things a lot of that
comes from Nintendo power and um and I would just look at these all the time and I had a bunch of
other magazines over time like uh once I got into video games I had EGM um when I got into anime
there was anime invasion which later became anime insider so I remember reading all of those we read
a lot of the same magazines as kids um yeah well we're probably about the same well I'm a little
older than you yeah you're a little older so I picked up anime insider when it had become anime
insider yeah um well funnily enough I had this was a huge part of how I got into anime was that
like because I've been into Pokemon for a long time and I was kind of waning interest you know
nobody cared about it that much anymore and I've been into it for like four years and then uh like
my my cousin and I discovered anime and then my cousin picked up the first the first ever issue
of anime invasion and he was like there's this thing called anime and it's like it's all like
ninja scrolls it's a Japanese colloquialism yeah yeah anime a Japanese colloquialism and I was
like whoa and so uh it had it had um Goku on the cover like Kid Goku and like their their big cover
story was like all the stuff that was uh left out in the American version of Dragon Ball because
they had censored it you know so it's like talking about how Goku used to pat everybody's crotch
and stuff like that to see what gender they were and how that was cut out it was just like a huge
list of everything that was cut out all the like how they changed the the hell to fulfill the home
for infinite losers yeah so it was all just like explaining all these cultural differences between
uh like you know what was acceptable in Japan versus here but like yeah in this magazine like
it just so happened that like adult swims started at the same time so like we were watching anime
there and I read this magazine cover to cover like I read every single thing and when I say that I
mean like you know the credits they'll have in a magazine like I read all the credits like I
really wanted to know everything possible about anime and so then from like from there
I would say my next big influence would be like forums because I discovered forums through Yu-Gi-Oh
and like I started using internet forums big time and that's where I started seeing like people
you know sharing different opinions about stuff and uh so I would get in on these forums and you
know share my opinion but I was always like this bratty kid who was like off the handle and I was
always like uh you know I cared about my opinion I didn't really care about other people's opinions
so like really being on a forum wasn't that good of an idea because a forum is about
discussion ostensibly I mean most people just kind of post past each other like they don't read
each other's posts they all just share their opinion and move on yeah but like uh it made me mad
that people weren't discussing my posts in the forum because like to me the point was I posted
here so that you would respond to it and then no one would respond you know partly because I had a
bad attitude and terrible writing skills but then um so I was bouncing between forums and I ended up on
the megatocchio forums which is a webcomic that just happens to have a bunch of really really
intense anime fans in its forums and I learned from all of them and they all had anime blogs so
I started following other people's anime blogs and sort of like copying the formulas that they
were doing where most of them were either episodic bloggers or they talk about like more general
stuff related to a show or like just what they were watching at the time so I would like copy
their styles and I was really attracted to blogs because of the fact that everyone has to respond
to your point like it's not a discussion where everybody's equal it's you raise an idea and
then people respond to your idea which is sort of how youtube is as well and like all the stuff
that we do so it's kind of like it elevates it to to an artistic place you know it's not about
everyone's we're all just a bunch of do you know that's very funny I want to bring up something
from before my whole life Ben can attest to this whenever I've like been reading a new chapter
of one piece or whatever nobody around me ever gives a shit and yet I want to tell them like
endlessly about what happened and why it's so awesome so the channel I have now is pretty much
just like the result of channeling that feeling into a thing yeah people have no choice but to
listen or exactly off which is yeah the amount of time I spend rambling to my siblings and parents
and friends about all the things they're going through my head has reduced significantly ever
since I got on youtube yeah and I think that's probably something that's like innate in people
doing stuff like what we do yeah we're translating we want people to hear it you know and for me a
lot of that was because of the fact that growing up most people weren't into the stuff I was into
so like trying to justify my interests was a big part of you know growing up for me where it was
like I was into all this stuff that no one cared about and I'm trying to explain yeah why I care
about you were talking about how like a lot of reviewers especially and analytical ones get a
lot of flak for not representing populist opinions and you were theorizing that that that having
our skewer random different opinions is what motivated them to want to start sharing their
opinions more than anyone else exactly yeah like that's why I that's why it's so important to me
to make like like my k on video where like other people don't seem to understand the appeal of
this show so it's very important to me that I have a video explaining why I feel the way I do
so that people aren't constantly making posts like they always do like really k on's your favorite
and it's like yeah here's the two hours of reasons you know like that's that's kind of like the place
that all of this comes from but in terms of like influencing my actual writing style because like
so once I started up my blog my style was just completely rambling off the cuff like no structure
no anything it was always um stream of consciousness you know and like I thought that was super cool
because I was really into like writers and stuff who were like very postmodern and who didn't give
a fuck about like formalism and stuff like that you know so uh I a huge influence on me has always
been boogie pop the book boogie pop and others because it's told anachronically it's like five
big chapters and each of them is a different part of one story but like each doesn't know anything
about the other person's part so basically
so anyway catch you up here guys come on I I uh there's a giant dick flying into my
moon
all right so this this book is told out of order and I thought it was really fascinating the way
it's like each character is telling their perspective on this story and I've always loved like
doing experimental out of order stuff also like quentin tarantino films how they're out of order
and stuff so like um you can see some of that in my videos where I feel like everything is
contributing to this one big narrative like to me you have to whoa what your videos don't have
a no they have a the series ones definitely do you know I think everyone's videos inherently
have a narrative and I don't think you can really I don't think you can appreciate someone's
content until you understand who they are like if you read a roger ebert review and he shits on a
movie and you're like but I liked that movie it only really makes sense to you once you understand
his taste and you understand like where he's coming from like roger ebert gave like one star
to kick ass it's like the reason is literally that he's old and he felt like he was too old
for the movie you know we're like a 20-something guy would have a totally different perspective
and if you you know if you read that article knowing that he's a 75 year old man it makes a
lot more sense you understand the narrative of who he is and so I write all of my videos from
the perspective of the more of these you watch the more sense this will make you know and that's
why I constantly try to like call back to my old videos or remind people that I've made old videos
you're like hey here's all the like when I people are accusing me of being too negative and I'm like
here's the 95% of my videos that are positive go watch them because it's kind of important to
understand you know they're interested that what have you done for me lately
mentality you know that's yeah well yeah that's that's the only right that's right as far as I'm
concerned yeah so so I you know I think that having a narrative across your stuff is important
and to me like seeing stuff that that is kind of like a bunch of pieces that become a whole like
it's the kind of stories that I've always been really interested in and and I tried it there's
some of my videos standalone complex other yeah the standalone complex as I would later come to
call it because it goes to the shell where you know each individual story is a part of a of a
bigger grand narrative so so but as a writer I was terrible and I just I didn't spell check my stuff
I just ran through it and I had this I had this very entitled attitude like it made me mad that
no one read my stuff even though I wasn't doing anything to make it readable you are you are
describing me on forums to a T and I yeah I learned to write basically because people on
forums kept giving me shit for not capitalizing things and finally I was like fuck it fine I
remember seeing on deviant art doing like comic strip stuff and like just like doing desktop
background art and being like okay I need to calculate how to get popular that I calculated
the top ways to get popular the second way to get views is to make comments on other people's
stuff but then I realized the number one thing to do is to make good art and I was like oh right
yeah I've actually recently put that pretty low on the list if you're just getting views these days
but yeah well on deviant art having good art is important no yeah I didn't understand I didn't
understand how to make good art and I just thought that like people had like I just thought that if I
had my stuff spread out enough eventually like if I cast a wide enough net people will find it like
the people who will appreciate this will eventually find it and what I didn't realize is that no one
will appreciate this because it's terrible you know like there's no one for whom this is great art
so like you know my writing was pretty bad and then finally I started like because I you know
posted a lot in the animation is this really your influences thing this is like your whole story
yeah this is important you didn't expect this to happen yeah yeah it's important to the influences
I know what I planned this all right I know what I'm talking about because I was talking to other
people in the community and because I was bad eventually people found me who's who taught me
that I was doing everything wrong so I got these bloggers these other bloggers who like I would
you know comment on their stuff and I'd be like why is no one reading my shit and they were like
you're you're terrible they're like you're not spell checking anything you write nobody wants to read
something that's all spelling errors nobody wants to read this or that and so like meeting these
bloggers like uh like ghost lightning who would go on to be like my biggest influence
which is why this whole story was important is uh like they they were literally telling me what I
was doing wrong they were like well the attitude you take because I had this very confrontational
attitude like my opinion's the only one that matters fuck everybody else and it's like
you want comments and you want people to discuss your ideas but you keep telling people that their
ideas don't matter and like you know pushing them away so ghost lightning taught me about
the way that he acts is he said I am extremely arrogant and I really really like think that
I'm great but I never tell anybody that I put on this persona of being humble and it makes people
respect me but I know how to like defend myself when people attack me you know and it's just very
Captain Picard mindset is the way I would describe it like he's the character who represents
this the best where Captain Picard never puts on errors he never makes himself out to be amazing
but he will always be the guy like when when it comes down to authority he's like look I know
what I'm fucking doing you know and uh and will be that guy so that kind of mind and that's the
reason I love Picard so much is that he reminds me of like ghost lightning and uh and my dad also
has a similar attitude that he's developed over time like of recognizing that that's how you reach
people is by you know saying you're not wrong but uh I'm also right you know yeah yeah so it's
hard to argue with Picard yeah and and ghost lightning had this way of doing stuff where he
would answer every comment that he got he would respond to everybody no matter how asinine the
comment is because it would make people in turn improve their comments which I keep telling people
is like the way to go if you want better comment sections let them know that you're reading it
and then it makes them self-conscious about what they're writing so and in general he was just
really fucking good he was someone who had you know studied he was like a long time english and
literature major um so he was like really into deep reading and deep into philosophy and stuff
like that so just generally talking to ghost lightning like taught me so much about the world
and like brought in my perspective so much um you know I came to visit him for a month uh in the
Philippines where he lives and he literally like read me a book on literary theory he was like here's
a bunch of like you're gonna know all these terms now that people use you know it's like now I know
what postmodernism is and what feminist theory is and like all this stuff that you know I learned
from this literary theory book and then he would just explain to me all these like really deep
philosophical concepts you know gave me a lot of reading material to to learn so that's why I always
describe him as my mentor because like not just that reading his blog did influence me and I was
also influential to him because like the biggest thing that I taught him was how to like make stuff
fast because I've always been super prolific like just by nature I like things to come out as fast
as possible as soon as I've had the idea and um you know he was more like the kind the type who
would worry about like uh is this finished or not and I was like just publish stuff dude like
I because I want to read it that's an influence you've had on me lately that was something I was
always I was always slow to get stuff done and it made me realize just do it fast and it'll actually
better than if you worked really hard sometimes well because Andrew Hussie Andrew Hussie taught
me that you gotta fucking churn it out and it doesn't matter it doesn't matter if any one
particular drawing is shit you just put it out and I'm gonna get to Hussie too because like
at this point can we please hurry this thing along I'm dying here this fucking this is literally
digi bros draw my life Jesse Jesse and I just like how did he was like 30 minutes
everyone has to hurry up so digi can get to his grand narrative as much as 12 minutes guys it was
just I was talking about you pussies this is the best podcast it should go for five hours
you can look at the waveform whoever edits this my whole my whole segment was like 10 minutes and
then like two minutes of follow-up that was a fair enough whatever I did I take it away so I I was
really impressed by these bloggers these guys who taught me how to write you know this is the most
like all of this was the most important part after this is just going to be like a list all
right that was all the stuff that was like the big huge okay I was just really afraid that everyone
of your influence is going to include the influence of how I like became a writer that I am now
like that these people's like that the mindset and the attitude of why I started writing combined
with the way that people taught me what to do and then said like here's what you should do and then
from then on it's just been like I love taking other people's styles and deliberately writing in
their style and I feel like it's it's kind of like a like a power stealing thing like I eat you and I
gain your powers like yeah that's kind of my mindset towards other content creators like mega man
yeah you'll see it all that's yeah exactly like mega man you'll see it all the time on my channel
where I go out of my way to do another person's style for like one video and then like whatever
elements of it I like I incorporate forever so like your anime sucks videos are a huge
send up of your movie sucks yeah I did a should you watch in the style of demolition d I've done
tons of stuff where I took elements of Jesse's work Jesse's probably the biggest influence on me
as a video maker in terms of like like not a writer but just as how I make videos by the way
just keeping score that is now for people in this call that excited me as a direct influence so
anyone right anyone of you watching who doesn't think that I'm the shit now you know that I am
truly the shit Jesse what is the shit Jesse's biggest influence on me was like um deciding to
try to incorporate more like emotional factors into the videos like thinking of it more as an
artwork you know um thinking of it more as like yeah I am doing something that's special and new
and different you know and like looking at Jesse's work in particular just like thinking about how
it relates to other people where uh we had this discussion the other day that like YouTube um a
lot of it like doesn't have a lot of self-respect necessarily I think a lot of YouTubers like
want to be filmmakers or they want to be doing nothing that pisses me off more than the fucking
you to like John Trine is the perfect example we know he's dying to get on tv he'll do whatever
it fucking takes well he just he wants he wants his stuff to look like like television as opposed
to looking like YouTube and I think Jesse's art suffers as a result it's right I think Jesse has
done the most to like elevate YouTube as its own medium that has its own message that it can send
where like the way he's used his multiple channels the way he's used the ongoing narratives in them
like is something that you couldn't do necessarily elsewhere like it is a unique story to YouTube
that has a an interesting point to it and so like that's kind of made me start to look at YouTube
as like what can I do that is distinctly this medium um and I I used to love John Trine so much
for how he used his whole house compared to like yeah yeah like AVGN would do that he was really
creative like I have a whole vlog planned about John Trine that I'm finally gonna do probably
maybe tonight I just gotta get this out there about how he he's misunderstanding the the medium
of YouTube and but um and now he's got these fake sets it's it'd bring in a fucking horse for the
joke that he brought in a horse wow 10 out of 10 joke writing John Trine you're really elevating
the media but yeah everyone everyone's had little bits of influence I've I've done I've written stuff
to be like hippo I've written stuff to be like uh to be like Nate in smaller ways I've written
stuff to be like you know everybody um even me I don't know about writing like you but uh not not
me because uh you've only known me for like seven months so right but like there's a there's a lot
of YouTubers who have copied the the biggest ones who got me to go onto YouTube were uh ego raptor
and uh errant signal because ego raptor taught me that that you could do this in video and then
errant signal taught me that you could do this lazily in video yeah that you don't have to animate
everything and make it funny you could just do an analysis so I hope that I realize that one day
yeah mr. Plinkett's obviously a huge influence uh just all the great everyone who's in my
subscriptions if you if I'm subscribed to somebody I've probably incorporated some small element of
their style into mine yeah you know I've got a video coming up that's gonna be like somewhere
every frame of painting was big if you you can see the moment like you can also find the moment I found
each of these guys because there will be a video that's like them right afterwards like right after
every frame came out I did all these videos about visual uh like style in anime like just like I've
got really focused on visuals for a while and then I've got one coming up that's kind of like
somewhere between every frame and nerd writer but like yeah I love assimilating other people's
stuff and then like turning it into my own and I think that what the reason I consider like the
asterisk war series to be like my first real masterpiece is that it wasn't copying any one
person but it kind of took everything I knew everything I'd learned and like put it into one
place yeah so it was like the ultimate here's everything I've got as a youtuber right now
and let's throw it all into one video um and then work ethic Andrew Hussie is my biggest influence
and uh I've always said that if I ever had a wall of heroes because the uh my little pony
writer M.A. Larson has behind his desk he has pictures of all of his like his favorite writers
and all the people who he like looks up to and he calls it like his wall of heroes and I always
thought I just want to have Andrew W.K. and Andrew Hussie the two Andrews because Andrew W.K. has
the mindset of everything is great like his he he describes everything as a party in his world
everything is a party but if you follow his twitter it's like by the way two days ago Andrew W.K.
formed the party party oh that's just a bit of news okay if you if you followed his twitter there'd
be times where Andrew W.K. would say things like just pissed on my hand life is fucking awesome
you know it's like that mindset of like no matter what it is it is awesome like is very much how I
try to view the world as like even though some stuff is like fucking terrible it still is interesting
and informs you in a way what does this man do is he a musician yeah Andrew W.K. was originally a
musician and he has later turned into like a just a weird personality that exists in the world um
he's done all kinds of shit but his first album is fucking great uh the album I Get Wet and uh
yeah so I love his attitude but then Andrew Hussie has the work ethic and there were other
people who inspired me like uh like just hearing about Stephen King I never actually read any of
his books but I know that he was the one who said like if you're a writer all you should be doing is
writing like you know that's like how if you want to get good at writing just write all the time
you know it's what he said but Andrew Hussie had the most inspirational quote to me where he said that
Homestuck is not a work of art to him it's just a way of life like he doesn't do anything else
he was like all I do is I write Homestuck and I put it out and it's not like I'm doing it to
create this one thing like this this this thing that you know is meant to be read just and by
itself he's all like it's just what I fuck bitches and write Homestuck and I'm all out of bitches
he also he also said that it's his chief leisure activity yeah that's like that's great but it's
all he does like and the the production rate was so insane like for the first year of Homestuck
coming out it was five posts a day every day and it would never stop you know and then like it only
started slowing down because of the fact that he sold out to that damn video game but he it only
started slowing down because the things he was doing would take longer like he would always say
every time there's a gap in Homestuck it's not because I'm not writing Homestuck it's because
the next update is that much larger so like you know Homestuck would go down for a month and then
and a full fucking animation would come out or a video game would come out as one of the chapters
you know like there's never a time where he just stopped and was like I'm gonna take a break because
he didn't view it as work he viewed it as a lifestyle he viewed it as this is what I like doing
you know so that's what a kind of mentality that I like to have about my work as well as like
there's no sense in me being like oh I need a break from YouTube because it's like YouTube is
all I want to be doing you know so like I feel the same way I feel the same way I just have like
crippling self-doubt I feel the same way to that yeah so yeah those are my uh those are my influences
the major ones so yeah I feel the same way to holy sh I wanted to say by the way that uh upon
listening to yours did you I reflected on it myself and I realized that there is probably the biggest
influence out of all of these that I didn't even mention and it's specifically 4chan uh yeah I mean
I know that's gonna you know people are gonna think that's retarded but well your sense of humor is
very clearly yeah oh yeah for sure just for my last video people or whatever it was people yeah
it's a real disadvantage but you know it's it's really changed uh the way I talk the way I write
I mean when I when I talked about how I will you know just yell at people like the things that I
think are awesome and they'll try to stop listening that's what 4chan is for me now that's where I
do that like when you have a conversation with someone you just hold up a picture and hold it
next to your conversation that you're having for an epic reaction meme lol love them yeah that's I
don't know just I would cite 4chan as an influence as well on the way I think and like interact with
stuff yeah yeah I think 4chan has influenced like how all internet media works yeah that's true
that's for sure I think 4chan has halted human advancement forever and doomed us as a community
outside looking in my friend you just don't get us you just don't get it you you just don't get
why kids love the taste of cinnamon toast crunch and by the way I think the most important thing
that 4chan teaches the world is how to like be investigative like 4chan really is all about like
it's a great aggregator of information so it really encourages you to go out and find things
yeah it encourages you to like because their whole policy is like no hand holding and stuff
and no spoon feeding and like they go too far with it to an extent that it's kind of stupid where
they're like clearly showing you something that they know you don't know what it is well listen
to fuck with you sometimes it's an aggregator of information but it's also an aggregator of stupid
dummies how you say that it's just I don't know it's just a community of like minded people really
people to like learn how to find stuff and learn how to like investigate and learn how to like
you know find things for yourself I get bothered sometimes when I I know some people who will
like ask me shit that I know they could find the answer to like in 10 seconds yeah but because they
know I know the answer they just ask me but I'm like I have the I have the 4chan mentality of like
fucking google it like look it up yourself like you can find out the answer quicker if you just
looked it up then if you wait for me to respond people just don't kind of think that way because
they're stupid they have to be educated yeah I mean you know they're ignorant people have to
try learning how to program before they realize that everything's on google and you shouldn't ask
anybody unless you can't find it on google yeah yeah dude and by the way I while I was saying that
before I remembered a couple other personal influences um let me see it was Gary Ridgway
Jeffrey Dahmer uh John Wayne Gacy and Ted Bundy and then recently I've really been getting into
Dennis Reynolds from always sunny in Philadelphia those guys are kind of the the pentagram
I like how he's listed among serial killers yeah what no I'm a big I'm a big admirer of the
I really admire the work of John Holt his masterpiece made a big splash you know you know this is
this is underground guy you might not have heard of Vlad the impaler he's really great stuff you
know I support him on you know Adolf Adolf Hitler his paintings are kind of bad but some of the
stuff that he wrote man he did a lot of like uh uh you know people should have listened later on
his career it was no that he was a true bohemian if there's one person I should have mentioned
that I didn't more than anything it would be Yahtzee I think oh yeah I kind of glossed over
zero punctuation too yeah well like like I have you know I have a lot of comedic influences some
of them are the same as hippos like uh like old sketch comedy like I've always been huge into
like watching sketch comedy shows and stuff like that but I think in terms of what I do
in my main videos like the way Yahtzee just kind of flippantly throws jokes in the middle of ranting
is the way I do my humor where it's like I never take a break from the point it's always just like
and then he fucking threw a piece of shit into her face like you know like what I'm saying is
still what's happening but I'm just saying it in a funnier way by the way I'm the only one of us
who's actually met Ben Yahtzee Korshaw yeah you are I'm jealous yep met him one on one I had a
convention I shook his hand got a signature it's hanging in my room yeah that's right I met Linkara
so damn I I met Spoonie so actually I met I met here in Obusaka Gucci oh yeah Ben met Roosh
Ben met Roosh I met Roosh V if anyone knows that actually reminds me uh this isn't really a big
thing much these days but I was big into the pickup community you know oh yeah several years ago
in college so I'm just it doesn't really apply to my life much I'll even say change my perspective
on things what I'll even say that like even though I don't write fiction anymore the last time I tried
was a story called Cyrno and purple Steve that's still online and it was like literally I read
Mogworld by Yahtzee and I was like I want to write a funny thing yeah that's cool yeah so yeah that's
that's cool I've never followed anyone more than I follow Yahtzee like I will watch or read
everything he does just like out of habit and uh yeah that's so I'd say he's like the biggest
person I follow that's how I feel about his literally he's literally the biggest person you
follow other than Jeff now yeah yeah like six foot five six foot five yeah so how tall is
movie Bob on a completely unrelated six foot two really no he's six foot too wide he's a tall
dude yeah I I you cannot tell though because of how wide he is do you think do you think he would
be taller if you tipped him on his side do you think he's perfectly spherical do you think like
all angles are the same I so I I did omit something and I touched on it briefly but I feel like I have
to uh might be the only one who got all my work done on my one try yeah no that's you are off of
your chart didn't yeah I made another list with the ad I I had a list but I I missed one in compiling
it which is uh I like I mentioned him briefly but I can't overstate really how much Tim Schaefer
influenced me and I know people yeah okay yeah I said him but like I know people don't like Tim
Schaefer very much anymore he's a sellout he's he's all these things that people say about him but
like playing Psychonauts and Grim Fandango back to back as a kid like Psychonauts came out for the
PS2 and I played that game and it was the funniest thing that I've I'd ever experienced in my life
up to that point because it blew me away with how funny it was yeah it was a good point because
everybody hates Tim Schaefer now for these kind of meme-y reasons yeah but he was I hate that he was
a he was a great creator yeah and he's like yeah like the same thing you can say for like
Joss Whedon everybody hates Joss Whedon now because always he's a cock and he's fucking feminist
they did he did really fumble that whole Kickstarter oh absolutely he's fumbled a lot of things PR wise
although what I respect him for is he went on Reddit and he actually like answered questions
where they were like how did you fuck up this thing and he's like well we yeah what a hero
face the music on Reddit over his internet connection in an AMA most most people like most
people yeah like I respect that I respect his sense of humor a lot and like the biggest thing for me
is playing Grim Fandango and Psychonauts back to back because I played Psychonauts and I was like
I have to consume everything that this man has ever made so I downloaded scum vm
download a day of the tentacle played that played Grim Fandango which was really fucking hard to get
running on my computer by the way that game oh man the grime engine does not play nice with
anything um but playing all of those things and like starting to understand who Tim Schaefer was
as a kid that was the first moment in my life that I was like holy shit art is something that like
I could do as a person and that was like the moment when I was like I want to make video games
which eventually transitioned into I want to make YouTube videos so oh what a low yeah yeah
just you know look no no it's not just keep lowering that bar it was an accepting of like I
want to make art and I started out wanting to make video games more than anything but then I was like
you know what what I do best is acting editing and writing and YouTube is the place for me
before on the show but the number one advice to all creatives is you have to like doing it
not like the idea of having done it so if you like I think most people who try to get into
making video games that is like what you realize is that making video games is one of the hardest
kinds of art to make because programming is so much not art process of like coding which is
fucking boring you know so uh and I think that's why like I have I have like four different full
fleshed out games that I want to make but fuck man programming right not happening all right we
gotta wrap this up because I have to pee really bad okay let me are we are we finishing follow up
I've got a one one thing to say um I don't know who I am and I don't know why I do what I do
at all yeah yeah sounds about right I'm with you I'm with you man if our if the if the point
is over I have a story to tell that I've been wanting to tell the whole time how long it's
completely off topic just let digi page listen to the podcast later did you go pee let's let him
let him do his thing or I hear this just go ahead and tell it okay so a couple weeks ago our topic
was normies re yes and a famous one yeah I last night had the most normies re moment
probably of my entire life um I was out with my friends in the city in Flint because that's
where all of my ridiculous stories take place um I was out with my friends and we went to like
this place that was like a coffee shop and also like a crepe restaurant sounds hipster which is
yeah yeah super hip okay super gay um yeah you know real gay crepes it's like little pancakes
with like ice cream on them and shit yeah yeah so we went there and I was standing in
the crepes are a hugely important part of the story the fuck hey you know what I call your crepes
like oh I'm crap I have dinner waiting for me for like an hour and a half
he was gonna he's can't couldn't wait to get the story this is this is relevant to our topic
tell the story then you guys are interrupting me you dumb shit faggot asshole cocksucking dummies
oh god we've lost okay all right go you got the crepes you're at the restaurant place
okay I was at the fucking restaurant I'm not gonna rush to this fucking story people okay I'm gonna
tell in my own goddamn pace and you guys gonna sit there and fucking shut your mouths and listen
to it you're not gonna make me rush you're not gonna be funnel me you're not gonna mess up my flow
how you're gonna tell it just tell it no no the people need to know the people need to understand
and you know what now this is going to turn into another long rambly endless just one this is what
this is gonna be now I'm just gonna sit here and I'm gonna talk about my method of telling this
story and I'm gonna keep going on and on and on he just keeps talking and talking and talking
in one incredible yeah now I gotta wait now I gotta wait did he did you come back I can't
fucking tell them all right well if you're gonna take a break no shut up everyone all right I gotta
I want to take this moment to say that Tom you mentioned before that I'm doing a Pokemon comic
and that's true and unless this podcast gets edited and posted super fucking fast it will probably be
out by the time you the listener are hearing this so but it'll only be on my patreon because
you're not allowed to talk about your patreon what we made a rule because it's because it's going up
because it's going up on patreon before I put it on my site because I have to spend some time
and do the html to actually get it on the site so if you're hearing this go to fucking ben patreon.com
slash ben sainton become a pleasure and then you can read my thing my pokemon come on you can just
wait like edit in a big the big sound of a man second another man's penis put that in or you
can just wait like four or five days or a week and then it'll be out did she did she just cut in
cut in this sound
agreed no no I haven't mentioned that on the podcast I wanted to let the podcast listeners know
there's I make things guys I put things yeah but the story okay he's waiting for you actually
and then you ever think it was so hard that your fucking bladder hurts after yeah I just did
because I did exactly what you didn't wait for two hours to take a piss taking a piss I assumed
you were taking a crepe
back to crepes go um oh yeah I was in the crepe store with my friends and I didn't have any money
so I was like why am I standing in line mm-hmm so I saw my two friends um they were my two friends
who are women's that's important to the story they were like out of the corner of my eye I saw them
go and sit down with their crepes so I figured I don't have any money why am I in line I just
can't hear that word without just hearing craps now yeah some craps shut up guys shut the fuck up
so I so I saw my friend sitting down I thought okay I shouldn't be in line I don't have any money
so I went to go sit down with them I sat down next to them and I just like I sat down and I
immediately said hey that's a nice crepe like commenting on her crepe and so they both looked at
me they looked up at me and they had this look on their face and I looked at them and I realized
these are not my friends I don't I don't I don't know these women
so wait you sat down next to them right that's what's happening yeah I saw them out of the
corner right I thought they were my friends I sat down and said nice crepe and they looked at me
like who is this fucking crepe trying to fucking hit on us via crepe and I just like it was like
this like moment of silence when I looked at them and I realized what was happening and I just got
up and I was like wait how was that a normie because yeah I was I don't know because they were
normies oh they were normies I don't know it was like an rk9 kind of like a green text I'm a frog
man pepe moment I guess yeah yeah where where were your friends though were they just at a
they were still alive they were still buying their crepes and then you like walked back and
hoped none of them noticed no I told them because it was hilarious okay good but it was also like
like the the entire rest of the time we were in the restaurant I was like spacing out like I was
just I was like thinking about what just happened I couldn't like join in the conversation I wasn't
even they were like having fun talking and I was just like waiting for these two women to leave
so that I could feel safe again who I fucking accidentally sexually harassed and like I started
like I started like really like going into like the what just happened and like sort of like concocting
scenarios like oh god what if it gets even worse because then they had a guy with them and I'm like
oh god what if the guy comes over and says like why are you hitting on my girls via crepe and so
then I was thinking like oh my god I'm gonna have to fight this guy and then I was like and then I
was thinking of like how I would take this guy down like how I would use this mental
battle against this man okay you're just like figuring out we're not even there movie with
jet lee hero where you know he they vision the two warriors visualize a fight between the two
and it's all a battle inside the mind only this in this case it's all in jesse's mind yeah so it's
just like it's just like imagine like all my friends eating crepes and talking amongst themselves
and then like me just spaced out like all around me and then and then suddenly it's just someday we'll
find it
I never leave the house so that'd be difficult I have experiences like jesse's all the time we're
like anytime if something awkward happens to me in public I imagine like this incredibly elaborate
scenario of where I think it's gonna go but I have a safety mechanism for that which is that
there's always one moment where I imagine something so ridiculous that I then become
convinced like it hits me I'm like wait the fact that I've thought about this means it's too stupid
to happen and that's always how I get through those because I start to get paranoid and I'm like oh god
what if it always ends with the police with me it's always like I'm gonna get arrested and then
like dude once it hits dude I'm like wait the fact that I've imagined all this means it's so
unlikely that this will now happen that I could have predicted all this is is that like a common
thing because I do the exact same thing I tell myself because I've imagined like things never
happened the way I picture them happening so because I pictured it that's why I'll never be
successful but whatever all right folks that's enough for that is time to wrap this bad boy up
and ship it thank god or two and a half hours deep
this will be the podcast we just throw in the trash
patreon.com slash ben sainte