I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch.
Wibbity-wobbity-wee.
It's The Pro Crastinators.
Uh, canned intro.
Okay.
So, what are we talking about today?
Canned intro?
Canned intro.
You can put an actual, you can put an actual canned intro, you're just gonna say that.
Uh, I'm sure Eleazar will, uh, cut in one of the many, many canned intros.
You know, actually, we actually recorded every Pro Crastinators podcast like four years ago.
We had a big session, we recorded every segment we could ever need.
We predicted like news and stuff that would probably happen.
We recorded different versions for different alternate futures, and we said, you know,
whenever this inevitable historical thing happens, just throw that segment in, mix and
mash them up Eleazar, create episodes in the future.
And so that's just, pull one of the many hilarious intro jokes that I made, insert that in there
at the beginning instead of me saying canned intro, which would be a really, really embarrassing
way for an episode to begin.
No, no, no.
Here's the canned intro.
I'm gonna record it, and then you put that at the beginning.
Okay.
Wibbity-wobbity-wee.
It's the Pro Crastinators.
Another banger.
Another banger in the bag.
Another banger with mash.
Yeah.
So good.
People love it.
They can't get enough.
They can't get enough, and that's why, that's why we make the big bucks.
That's why we make the big podcast money.
That's why we're a bunch of coked up New Yorkers with the podcast.
Hey, Ben.
In case you were wondering why that's the case.
Hey.
What the fuck?
What the fuck indeed?
I was saying a minute ago, before we started recording, that I have to keep it a bit short
today because basically, as soon as the podcast ends, I have to run over to Munchy Kazzie's
house for Friendsgiving.
Oh, yes.
I have to get there early because I have several dishes.
I have several dishes I am bringing that have to be prepared on site for that.
Turkey brains and all that.
I will tell you, I have some secret dishes.
I have one, bacon wrapped Brussels sprouts, a classic, but they can't carry them over
there.
They get cold immediately.
Last night, I prepared them.
I bought the sprouts at the local bazaar, at the Russian bazaar, and an old Russian lady,
as I'm picking Brussels sprouts out of the thing, she turns to me and she says, like,
oh, very good.
Those are very good.
Yes.
You like those?
These are very good.
I love these.
I'm going to make them for a late Thanksgiving, I said.
She said, you cook?
Oh, you cook?
I said, yes, a little bit.
She seemed a little bit like, oh, what did she walk away?
You do not strike me as the type to cook.
You look like a slob.
You look like a disgusting.
You're pajama pants, and you look like a fucking idiot.
Those are great.
My favorite of their many desserts from their fine Russian dessert menu, the same display
case where I tasted bird's milk, which Mage told me about so many years ago.
If you remember our conversation about bird's milk, they have it there.
They've also got dulce de leche waffle cake, which I really like.
So I'm bringing that.
And then the third thing I'm bringing, I'm going to tell you this because this episode
won't be published until after I've already gone, is one time Anthony Munchie-Lol was
walking through there and he noticed something that he found really funny, which was a freezer
display containing something called, something he described as Siberian ravioli.
And he thought Siberian ravioli sounded really good.
I went back and I looked for it.
Turns out it's not Siberian ravioli.
It was Siberian dumplings.
But I mean tomato, tomato.
So I'm also bringing, I'm also bringing Siberian dumplings.
What is the, what is the filling of a Siberian dumpling?
I think it said it's like, it's like veal, it's like veal pork chicken.
Siberian tiger.
I think it's just some, it's just little, they do look like ravioli.
They're just little, little round, little round ravioli things with like a veal pork mash inside.
I don't know.
Probably pretty good.
Just got to boil those in a pot.
Sounds good.
That's going to be pretty funny.
Everyone's going to be like, whoa, the long prophesized Siberian ravioli.
Hell yeah.
So I can't be late.
I can't be late for that, obviously.
Yeah.
We had, I had actual Thanksgiving.
My parents house posted on Twitter.
Last week I said, my dad got COVID.
Or at least he tested positive for it.
This week I just posted a picture of me at Thanksgiving.
He is testing negative.
He's fine.
Very relieved about that.
I did, I did take the opportunity to hit up the Patreon.
No, no, no, the procrastinators teespring.
Yes.
And buy him an I have COVID shirt.
Eleazar, please post this.
Please, I'll just get, I'll get the tweet.
I'll grab the tweet for you.
Here's my, here's my dad.
Yeah, I saw that image and the I have COVID shirt.
It took me a while to remember that that was this shirt that we sell.
Yeah, of course.
It's so normal and boring, but it's like, it's perfect.
Because nobody would think you have to be into a obscure podcast.
Yes, exactly.
To have a shirt like this.
Link in the description, right?
We have a link in the description.
We have something.
We have like a teespring like something or other merchandise.
We have a page.
Yeah.
If you want to have your very own, be cool like my dad and have your very own.
I have COVID shirt.
It's so, it's so like dumb.
I love it.
Yeah.
I was like on it genuinely when my dad was like tested positive.
I rubbed my hands together and I said, yes, a marketing opportunity has presented itself.
And here it is.
It's paying off.
What did you think of it when you gave it to him?
He, you know, I sent it to him a few, like a few days before it arrived.
And then I didn't look at my phone the day that it did arrive.
So I didn't, I don't see his like immediate reaction.
But he, when I met, when I saw him for Thanksgiving and talked about it, he seemed very amused by it.
And I was like, you know, okay, good.
I'm glad for that.
Yeah.
It's certainly a good shirt to wear if you had recovered from it.
I think if, if you had got it and then you died after, if you died of it, I wouldn't personally, I wouldn't want to be buried in it.
It's not that good a joke.
No, but never.
No, no, but it's close.
No, I want to be, I want to be buried in something really funny.
You know, not just a little funny.
Like dog shit.
Yes.
Exactly.
Looking at my Twitter replies.
How mad should I be?
Very.
Okay.
That's fine.
That's good.
Oh yeah, you don't have Thanksgiving.
They didn't invent Thanksgiving over there.
And it hasn't figured out how to do it yet.
That was an American invention.
Yes.
I mean, you don't have Guy Fawkes night though.
So.
No, we don't have Guy Fawkes day or night.
I was just going to say, everyone complains about Turkey and it's, you know what, they're all, they're all pluses.
It's fine.
Everyone says, oh, Turkey's bad.
Nobody eats Turkey except on Thanksgiving.
And the reason is because it's not actually any good.
It's just a tradition, but it's not actually a good meat.
It's fine.
It's totally fine.
I think in terms of like poultry, if it counts as poultry.
Yeah.
It's, it is like chicken is the best.
And then it's like Turkey and duck afterwards.
That's a bit too fatty, I feel.
I like, I like duck a lot.
I mean, we just, you just, you know, nobody, nobody eats sliced Turkey.
I eat, I eat turkey sandwiches all the time and buy cold cuts.
It's great.
Turkey curry is good as well.
That's a, that's a good, like a, like a Christmas, a Christmas like leftovers thing is to get like the Turkey that you didn't eat and make a curry out of it.
That's really interesting.
I mean, we had, we have Turkey, Turkey, Turkey at Thanksgiving.
We make Turkey sandwiches, Turkey sandwiches with like stuffing and cranberry sauce on them.
Traditional like leftover.
We do that as well at Christmas.
It's really just the same thing.
That's funny.
That was so funny about it.
Well, I guess curry in general in America is like less.
I think we just don't, I think we just don't make curry that much.
Yeah.
I never, I never had curry.
It's the heavy Indian influence and the, the, I guess, all that stuff.
I guess so.
I saw them eat curry in anime and I thought like, I thought it was like a funny foreign food.
Fucking weird.
Yeah.
That was the only my exposure.
Fucking animation.
Love it.
When now to eat this, this little Prince Curry brand that's too spicy and fully cool.
I was like, hmm, I can't possibly relate to this, whatever there's going on here.
This doesn't make any sense.
I have had like a Japanese curry before, like from, I don't know, like a Chinese restaurant.
They have like, oh, all sorts of things.
You can do Korean, we can do Chinese and Japanese.
And they have a Japanese curry and it's like very different from an Indian curry.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Definitely why, but like the spices used are different, I guess.
I've gotten like a curry mix, like a block that you break into pieces and you sort of,
you cook in the pot to like season it.
The brand I've usually get is called Golden and I think it's Japanese.
And the thing about Golden Curry is that it comes in various spicy levels, like mild to medium to hot to very hot.
And they're all not spicy at all.
They're all total bullshit.
It's sad.
It's a bit of a discipline.
I wanted that little Prince experience.
The curry being too spicy.
I'm wondering, do you, could you even get like a curry takeaway in America if you wanted one?
You would have to go to an Indian restaurant, I think.
Well, well, of course, but like, how many are there?
Are there like one or two in the whole of Boston or something?
I mean, in the whole of Boston, I'm sure there's quite a few.
There's probably like one Indian place like in my neighborhood.
Right.
I don't know, I don't know where.
I mean, they're around.
They're not super common.
They're less common than Chinese.
I would wonder if the Americanization has taken effect on Indian restaurants and if it's different from UK Indian restaurants.
Because there's a lot of really good Indian restaurants in the UK.
Hmm.
I like me a fucking madras.
I don't even know what that is.
A fucking phall.
Kitchy a tori.
There's all sorts of words that I've heard in passing.
A phall, itchy a tori.
No, a phall.
The phall is like an F-A-A-L.
Oh, I don't know what that.
A really hot curry.
I don't know what that is either.
You would order like, oh, a lamb or a chicken and then the name of the spice, the sauce.
So like a madras is a pretty hot, pretty spicy.
I like that one.
I actually had Indian food.
Last time I had Indian food was for Crack's birthday, which was like two months ago, six weeks ago, something like that.
Yeah, I know.
What do I know?
I know mango lassi.
I know naan.
I know tandoori.
Naan, yep.
I might know one or two others.
Tikka masala, of course.
Tikka masala.
Yeah, the tikka, I think it's the tikka that means like a drier sauce.
It's not like a creamy sauce.
It's like a sort of marinated in...
Like a rub.
Yeah, yeah.
I think that's what that means.
Like some sauces are nice and dry or like sort of oily and some are like really creamy.
Live for a creamy sauce, if you know what I'm saying.
I was saying, I think I was maybe talking to...
I think I was maybe talking to Kazi about this because I remember telling someone, we were talking about eating slop.
And I said, the best slop you can get...
I was like, you never been to an Indian restaurant?
They got some great slop there.
Because half the time when I order something in an Indian restaurant, it comes in a side bowl and it's some sort of unrecognizable slop.
But you put it on your rice and it's delicious.
They all look the same except maybe slightly different colors.
Sometimes it's a little greener and sometimes it's a little redder.
But either way, you slop on your rice and you mix it in and it's great.
Were they talking about being slop sensitive?
Slop sensitive.
That does ring a bell.
That's something they've said before.
I don't know whether that means they like slop or like...
Have they said slops?
Blah.
It's funny.
I feel like I am slop sensitive.
If there's too much slop, if it's too sloppy and you could move it around with a spoon
and it goes... or something, then I'm like, oh, oh no.
I don't want to put that in my mouth, even if it is good.
I do.
I need some texture, some crunch, some...
I'll take your leftover slop.
No, what I'll do.
Here's a tip, like a fucking cooking tip, like I know what I'm talking about.
You get like, this is not so much an Indian thing, but you get like a chili con carne.
Maybe it's too sloppy.
Maybe it's too much slop in there.
Classic problem.
You got your chili con carne, but it's too sloppy.
It's too sloppy.
Black and white footage of a housewife like picking up a spoon full of it and like shaking
all over the place and like it's flopping over the sides of the spoon.
I can't hold it in.
There's not enough meat, there's not enough kidney beans or like rice to soak it up.
So it's like, ah, it's just slop.
Get some Doritos, crunch them up, throw them in.
You could probably use any corn tortilla, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
It's really good.
That sounds pretty good actually.
I like, I like, I think, no, I'm not slop sensitive.
I actually think my favorite thing to eat is a slop.
Mashed potatoes I would call a particularly viscous kind of slop.
I would say that's...
You would not call that sloppy?
I would not call it sloppy because it can stand on its own.
It's like a, it's an independent food.
It can, it can make, you can make a mountain out of, if you can make a mountain out of
a food, it's not sloppy.
Okay, okay.
But anything that I can just, anything that I can just literally shovel into my mouth,
like dig it with a spoon and shovel it in, put the plate up to my mouth and open my mouth
and just push volumes of the food into my, my waiting mom.
Yeah, the way that every anime character eats when they don't want to actually animate
the eating in the show.
Yeah, yeah.
Just like, oh, I open mouth and I'm finished.
I'm going to go be a shonen battle.
Not even, not even move my teeth, not do any chewing.
Just push, use the spoon to push food to the back of my mouth to my continually working,
you know, tonsils and, and uvula.
You know what I, in the back just glugging it down the tube.
Just chug, chug that slop.
Chug the slop.
That's what I like to do.
You know what I think?
I'm thinking, I'm thinking 2022, we're having slops giving.
Only slops.
We're going to do, we're going to do like a radcon, but like a new version of radcon,
new branding.
And the only thing we're going to do is do slop streams.
We're going to stream making and then eating slop.
Yes.
And we're going to have a slop side.
We're going to have a slop, a suggest a slop, uh, uh, like mailing anonymous tip, tip section.
Send us your slop.
Show us your slop.
Do.
All right.
Obviously you wouldn't know.
I don't know why I started saying, do you remember?
Like, cause this is a British thing.
Do you, uh, dick and dumb in the bungalow, right?
That sounded racist.
No, no.
Dick and dumb in dick and dumb in the bungalow.
Dick and dumb in the bungalow.
Okay.
Two, um, TV presenters, comedian duo.
Uh,
No, I've never heard of this.
Yeah.
Of course.
It's, it's very, it's obscure to everyone except British kids.
Okay.
Only British kids would understand.
And like two thousand nineties.
Dude, dude, give remember, remember the Mohegan son.
Remember, remember, uh, uh, uh,
Oh, I gotta pretend I know.
Um, yeah, sure.
It pays to play.
You can play every night in a city by the sea.
You can play every day surrounded by luxury.
Step back in time.
Come along to the new, new Port Grand.
Oh, you wouldn't know about,
you wouldn't know about Newport Grand Radio jingle.
That's specifically to specifically the,
the Southern Massachusetts Providence area.
Sounds like an idiot would like that.
And remember,
it's like sister radio jingle for a casino that they,
that is around here.
Uh, anyway, yes.
Yeah.
So, so Dick and Dom in the bungalow, uh, it's,
it was like a, it was a Saturday morning.
Like I can't even describe, but like children.
There was like, it was like a game show and like just a chaos show.
Dick and Dom, um, they had like, uh, you know, wacky, like, uh,
Wait, was this on the radio?
No, no, no, it was on, on TV.
Okay.
So Saturday morning show, they would,
they would be wacky presenters and they would have cartoons play
and they would be in this, um, Pee Wee's big adventure,
not Pee Wee's big event.
Who's Pee Wee?
I know Pee Wee's Playhouse.
Pee Wee's Playhouse.
So Pee Wee's Playhouse-esque house.
And they would have a bunch of kids who are rowdy as fuck.
It's the most rowdy thing you've ever seen.
Um, they were thrashing.
They would, they would often be really badly behaved
and throw things and scream.
And it was a nightmare, but it was great
because as a kid, you would, you wished you were there.
Um,
Absolutely.
And at the end of every show, they would have like a fun-
At the end of Evangelion.
At the end of every show, they would have the muck fight.
What would they call it?
They had creamy muck muck.
This is what they call it.
Was it muck bang?
Did they call it the muck bang?
No.
They had buckets of like custard and, and slime and slop
and various, various gross things.
And they would have like a slime, a slop fight.
And they would throw buckets of creamy muck muck
all over the place and slime would dunk
and the kids would throw it at the cameraman
and, and Dick and Don would throw it at each other
and all the kids and they'd be like screaming.
It was the coolest thing ever.
I love that shit.
We should do that.
We should do, we should do Ben and Gib in Da Bungalow.
We should get a bungalow.
Ben and Gib in Da Bungalow's Creamy Muck Muck Battle.
Is that the title of the episode?
I'm thinking we got an episode title right there.
We gotta do it.
I think there's a bunch of episodes on, on YouTube.
They had, it was, it was like two hours from like 9 a.m. to 11.
Where they would just, they would do,
they would have this fun game, a segment where they would,
it would be called Bogies.
Bogies being like, um...
Like boogers?
Boogers, yeah.
Gross.
It's the British word for booger.
I remember because when Hermione sticks her wand up the troll's nose.
Troll bogies.
They say troll bogies, yeah.
Yes, that's why golf is really funny,
because they have bogies in it.
That's right.
I don't know what they are, but I know that they're there.
It's when you go one over par or something.
Oh, okay.
I was, damn, I was gonna write something.
I just had a thing I was gonna write on my things to bring up in conversation list,
but I forgot.
But it's okay, because Ben and Gibbin to bungalow and the creamy muck muck battle is better.
So, okay.
Um, yeah, yeah.
Bogies, where they, the two of them would go into a place that's usually supposed to be quiet,
like a library, or like a public place that's like, people are just doing things,
and they would candid camera, like secret hidden camera be there,
and they would have, they would play bogies, which was a game that caught on,
and that I have played with my brothers.
Did they invent the game or?
They invented the game.
The game is that you have to say bogies out loud, one after the other,
and the second person has to say it louder than the previous one.
Oh, I know, wait, I know this game.
Wait, there's no way they invented it.
Maybe it's called something else.
Maybe they didn't invent it.
I don't know, but that was the thing.
I remember a lot.
Obviously I didn't.
No, the version I've heard is you have to say sex.
You have to say sex as loud as you dare to say it in a library.
That's crude and rude.
That's not good.
Saying bogies is better because it's like, people don't really know how to react
to bogies being said very loudly.
It's sort of like, it's innocuous enough that people aren't going to tell you off,
but they're going to give you a weird look, and they do this.
A lot of weird looks when you play that game, I would imagine.
That is a game I've definitely played multiple times with my brothers in an art museum,
or just a place where it's quiet and it's awkward,
and it would be like, wouldn't it be really fucked if we said bogies?
If we did the bogies game.
It would be so fucked up.
It would be so fucked.
Memories.
Was that, so that was like live when you were a kid?
That was going on back then.
Yes.
Dick and Dom in Da Bungalow.
Da Bungalow.
It reminds me of, I don't know, there were various live action shows on Nickelodeon
that had cartoon segments in them.
What was that?
What was that one?
How fuck?
Was it, there was one with like a puppet called Bonesy.
Do you ever see that one?
I don't know.
Oh jeez.
It wasn't salute your shorts.
Hold on.
Bonesy puppets.
They had the underpants dance.
It was, it was, because underpants, you know, why fronts?
You put some underpants on your head.
Why fronts?
Like, like briefs?
Briefs?
Is that not a term?
Why fronts?
I've never, I've never heard them called why fronts.
I think I've heard that before.
I've never said it before, but yeah.
You put underpants on your head and you dance.
Wienerville.
Wienerville is the show I'm thinking of.
Like the dark?
No, probably like, like a hot dog.
Like, like this, like the snack.
Anyway, okay, whatever.
That's a different show.
Eddie, continue.
I didn't have anything else.
I was just sort of remembering the underpants dance.
But how did we even, how did we even, did we get here from COVID?
Oh, everything comes from COVID.
It all comes back.
COVID's the great new thing.
The hot new trend.
It's pretty big.
Oh, I want to ask you.
Did you hear about the new variant, the Omicron?
Yeah, I've been seeing Omicron on Twitter.
You know, the, I think, was the last variant, I think was Lambda,
and that one kind of didn't go anywhere.
That one sort of just, nobody really cared about it after a while.
Yeah, it didn't, it wasn't very, it wasn't viral success.
No, no, that one didn't catch on.
So, I mean, hoping Omicron is the same, but I mean, I guess we'll see.
You know, because the news is like, they found a new variant.
Oh, is it vaccine resistant?
Oh, is it like, you know, does it circumvent the human immune system?
I looked at the articles and it's all just like, there's something new.
Scientists are unknowing, they don't know anything, but we should be scared, maybe.
It's like, I'll wait, I'll wait until it's actually, you know, some.
I'll wait until the article says like, yes, the Omicron variant is coming to your,
is coming for your children and it is vaccine resistant
and it does circumvent the human immune system and it will fuck you.
Then I'll be like, shit, but not until then.
I care obviously about like, the fact that new variants are still happening,
but in the short term, I just care about it not being a problem until after I have visited in January.
Yeah, I saw, I saw there were some like South African travel restrictions
and I thought, wouldn't it be really funny if like, they put some new travel bans on the UK
like right before Gib was gonna come visit, like again.
I just want to fucking hang out.
I know, I know.
Well, no use worrying about it.
Yeah, if it happens, it happens and hopefully I can get a refund, but whatever.
Fucking sucks.
Dude, did you know this COVID virus is bad and I don't like it?
Nah, nah, it's like less than 1% fatality rate though.
Oh, that's lucky.
That's good.
In fact, that's better than it not existing.
It's like a cold, you know.
And as we all know, it gets cold in the winter, so it's really just part of nature.
I looked, I heard my dad tested positive and I was like, I was like, oh fuck, how scared should I be?
And I looked it up and like, I looked at the stats.
I looked at the stats for his age bracket.
Stop me if I did, if I talked about this last episode.
I don't think you did.
Okay, well I looked up stats for his age, I looked at the survival rate for his age bracket.
And the survival rate for his age bracket was like 1 in 20.
And I was like, that's not great.
But then I was like, okay, but there are mitigating factors here.
He's at the young end of his age bracket, like he's just barely in the like 60 plus.
It's like 60 to 80, right?
So like an 80 year old is going to be a lot less likely to survive than a 60 year old.
And also he's double vaccinated and also he's got no underlying conditions that are like respiratory in nature, et cetera, et cetera.
And I was like, okay, so I mean, he's probably actually much more likely to survive than merely 1 in 20.
So like, you know, but still, you know, if I had like a 5% or a 1% chance of dying, you know, that's still very upsetting, you know.
I've rolled, I've rolled the 20 sided dies and gotten a 1 before.
So, you know, it's not good.
But it's like, okay, I think it might, I think it might have been a false positive though, because he like, he said he didn't have like any symptoms at all.
And it seemed it was gone in like a week.
So maybe it was a false positive or maybe it was just like, he just barely had it or something.
I don't know.
It all worked out.
We'll never know.
Omicron, I don't know.
Yeah, they haven't actually found any positive statements.
They must probably think that maybe it's bad because it's like become very prominent in South Africa or something.
Yeah, there's a bunch of African countries that are like on the red list because of it.
That must make them think it's probably a pretty bad variant, but I guess we'll see.
I don't know how these things work with regards to like information dispersal.
Yeah, like journalists.
I mean, I would have to see like, well, I mean, is there some other reason that may like a new variant could have done it in these countries?
Like were those countries like extremely relaxed about their, you know, about their like,
Well, a new variant can come about for reasons of like people not being vaccinated enough and stuff.
It's really just like how bad the variant is because variants are always going to happen
as long as the virus is still alive and able to like reproduce through people.
I mean, a new variant, new variants are inevitable, but like...
A scary new variant is like, I don't know if that's this yet.
If one becomes like the dominant variant, then it makes you think like,
okay, well, this one must behave differently.
Maybe this one behaves differently in a way that is like, okay, it gets around the vaccine or it does something.
The thing that I'm thinking though, this may be just like random speculation, not scientist disclaimer.
This is medical advice.
No, but like the fact that it's coming up in South Africa,
I'm not totally sure how the vaccine situation is in South Africa,
but like a lot of the wealthier nations are hoarding vaccines.
They're not really giving them out freely.
So I have a hunch that it's a new variant.
South Africa is one of the more wealthy countries in Africa, I think, right?
Yeah, yeah, but I would be more scared if a very heavily vaccinated country came up with a new variant
because that would imply that the vaccine is not effective against stopping that,
or like it evolved to counter the vaccine or something like that.
I have no, like, it's just a guess, but I feel like coming from South Africa,
it's probably going to be the vaccines that we already have will do most of the work in stopping it.
Still, we've got to be careful of course.
Yeah, one would hope.
Yeah, I'm not going to like drop my guard because I think that,
but it's just sort of like it's not making me lose sleep, I guess.
Wow, so the percentage of the population fully vaccinated in the United States,
it's not even 60%.
That's embarrassing.
Actually, let me see if I can UK.
South Africa, I'm looking up South Africa.
Come on, I was looking at the wrong graph.
The percentage in South Africa is...
What, was there so backwards in African, that South Africa?
I bet theirs is like, I bet theirs is a pathetic 60%.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, 24%.
Okay, that's not great.
Yeah, it's really just a case of money.
I thought South Africa was pretty westernized, pretty first world,
like it's just parts of it that are heavily infrastructureed.
I don't know.
I hardly know anything about South Africa.
Yeah, I don't know what they have in terms of like the world stage,
like markets and trade and stuff.
I don't know how wealthy they would be.
Yeah, well, so yeah, it's only 24%.
So, I mean, okay, that's not great.
That could explain something.
I'm looking at the fucking vaccination rates.
Oh, God, there's not a single number.
It's just like a big list of information.
I don't want information, I want quick facts.
Well, I do see some articles here, run from the Wall Street Journal
that says, Omicron variant highlights risks of low vaccination rates in poor countries.
Washington Post says, Omicron variant symptom of vaccine inequities.
Yeah, so seems like these people are saying like, yeah, it's because the vaccine isn't.
It's almost like sharing the vaccine with everyone would mutually benefit all of it, every country.
It really annoys me that there's going around like, oh, get your booster shot on top of the second half of the vaccine.
Get your booster shot now, because we have the ability to just give third shots in the UK.
Don't do that, please just send vaccines to everywhere.
That's why variants exist, that they're constantly being made.
But they're not the same shots, right?
Like a booster shot is not the same thing.
Or maybe it is, I have no idea.
But the fact is, resources being spent on a third booster, a third jab, that is largely unnecessary as far as I know.
Maybe it's for very vulnerable people need it, but I don't know.
Actually, I hate to burst your bubble, but actually I was disappointed to see that the resistance rate actually drops off fairly precipitously.
You're like 90-something percent protected from becoming seriously ill with COVID if you're double vaccinated, but six months later it drops to 50% and it just keeps dropping.
So it does do something.
I mean, you're right that distributing resources evenly is probably better.
I want my booster shot, and I think I just became eligible for it.
They said I had to wait six months since my second shot, and I got my second shot on May 26th, and it's the 28th today, so I just became eligible two days ago.
So I should go get that, I guess.
I mean, since they got them.
Yeah, well whatever.
I guess I'll get mine.
If I get a text from the government saying, hey, get your fucking jab, you idiot, and I'm like fine.
I'll do what you say.
God.
It's free, so I guess why not, but I still frown about it.
Mr. Big Government, I love the state.
I love Big Government.
I will do anything to support my queen.
As a Democrat, I am slavishly devoted to the state and Big Government, yes.
I will do.
I do pray to Dr. Fauci, my little Fauci shrine every single night.
Whole pocket Fauci.
I did look up, what is the UK vaccination rate?
I tried to find it.
I think it was 50 million people, more than 50 million.
I thought you were going to say 90%, and I was going to get mad.
I found it almost 9 in 10 of those aged 12 or over having had a single jab and 8 in 10 having had a second.
Fully vaccinated according to Google, it's 68.9%.
You guys have about 9% more than we do, so that's embarrassing.
This thing on the BBC is saying 8 in 10, that's 80%.
That seems...
For both jabs?
For both.
Yeah, that's different than what this Google graph is telling me.
Well, I'd assume it's more likely the lower number.
That's fair.
There are quite a few vaccine idiots in the UK as well.
The United States is a whole, just under 60.
UK, just under 70.
Massachusetts though, 70.8%.
I read a little Twitter thread.
I may have mentioned this because it made me happy.
I read a little Twitter thread where a European guy was saying like,
Hey, Americans, tell me what state you live in and I'll tell you what Europeans think about your state.
And I scrolled down to find Massachusetts and he was like,
I think we like Massachusetts.
I think Massachusetts is sort of like a little pocket of Europe over in America.
Thumbs up.
And I was like, yes, fuck yeah.
I hate my fellow Americans.
I hate my fellow men.
It does feel very similar, especially in how cold it is sometimes.
That's true.
New England has worse.
Okay.
My understanding from things that I've read is that New England has worse weather than Europe,
even though much of Europe is further north and it's because of like the Gulf Stream,
like European weather, like a little bit more moderate.
Whereas in New England, we get like really cold winters and like really hot summers.
The UK.
You wouldn't think we get hot summers because of how north we are, but we do.
We hit 100 degrees once in a while.
Yeah.
Fahrenheit.
The Gulf Stream is what stops the UK from literally being like an ice block.
Oh shit.
You there?
Yes, I spoke.
Sorry, headphones fell out, but I caught it.
I need a better cord.
You mother fucker.
It's always something.
You just need to get an ear trumpet or something.
Yeah.
What were we talking about?
Vaccines.
I love it.
Here's for something I was going to say.
Have you heard that the queen is in a cocoon and she is going into a new state?
Yes.
I saw those bizarre headlines saying she's entering a new phase.
A new phase, whatever the fuck that means.
It's definitely like they're trying very hard to be truthful, but not to say she's dying
because that's what else could it really be referring to if she's in the hospital
and she's going into a new phase where it's a good phase.
We won't see her for months.
It's just a new phase.
She comes out.
She's got like a goth makeup and earrings.
Was it coronavirus related?
No, no.
I think she's just very, very, very old.
And now her husband is dead.
So her emotional rock is gone and now she's like, fuck it.
I just want to die and I'm like, yeah.
Yeah, true though.
Same though.
I also want you to die.
I did see those.
I felt nothing.
I feel nothing about the Queen.
She had like a place in my understanding of what my country is.
It's like, oh, the Queen's cool because she's got crowns and stuff.
And now I'm like, why does she have crowns and I don't?
The fuck.
Childhood is thinking the Queen's cool because she wears a crown.
Adulthood is wondering, where's my crown?
Exactly.
Yeah, yeah.
Hell yeah.
So I'd be interested when she dies of what happens.
What ceremonies are they going to do?
How many trumpets are they going to do?
Do they blow?
I think they blow, they like let smoke out of like the tower, right?
They like white, like black smoke when she dies.
That's the pope thing.
And then the council convenes and they vote on the new queen
and then they put white smoke out, right?
No?
No.
Okay.
It's going to be Prince Charles will be the crowned the king,
which will be interesting, I guess.
So God save the king, we're going to have to say.
Is he the one that married that American woman?
No, no, no, no.
That's his son, Prince Harry.
Oh, Harry's the one that wore that Nazi Halloween costume, right?
But what?
I swear, he swear he did.
Prince Andrew, the weird sex guy.
Weird sex guy.
Dude, I want that guy to be king.
Please make the weird sex guy king.
Prince Andrew is like a friend of Epstein,
sort of like weird controversy, motherfucker.
But Prince Harry.
Really?
Prince Harry.
No, it was Prince Harry apologizes for Nazi costume.
I mean, it was when he was like a kid.
Yeah.
Why do you do it, huh?
Okay, so Harry is the son of Charles, right?
Charles, yes.
Charles was married to Princess Diana, I think.
And now, and then he married someone else.
After Princess Diana died in a very funny accident.
It was really funny.
Wait, wait, wait.
We're still asking about it.
No, no, this is the lady who I was thinking of.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure she was born in America,
so people said she could technically run for president.
Like, Prince Charles's wife could run for president.
And I think some fucking, like,
kaha of warrenite psychopaths were being like,
oh my god, the queen of England should run for president
so we could finally have a woman of color.
Because she's like, I don't know, like half Lebanese
or some shit, I don't know.
What are they?
Is she like the only woman of color that they've ever heard of?
Any woman who could in any way be described as not white
would do, put that on, put that butt on the seat
in the Oval Office and they'll go,
and they'll go, progress.
They'll say yes, queen, because she'll literally be a queen.
They will say they will elect Crown Queen,
Meghan Markle as a president of America,
and they'll literally say yes, queen,
and then they'll be like, we did it.
And then I'll forget about politics again.
It's just very funny.
But yes, this is the woman I was thinking of
because I saw interviews with her earlier this year
or last year, they had some kind of PR kerfuffle
where they had an interview with Oprah or something
and they said some weird shit,
some weird, unrelatable rich person shit.
Yeah, I can't remember exactly.
The thing with Harry and Meghan
is that they've left the royal duties of the royal family
and Harry will, I think, he's given up his heir
to throne-ness and he doesn't have to go to royal events
and smile and wave anymore because he didn't want to do that.
He's living in the spotlight your whole life, I guess.
He's the rogue prince.
What a badass.
But he's still super rich and fuck that guy.
Of course, yeah.
He said some shit about like,
sorry, he's like, sorry, I got canceled,
but no, I'm not racist or anything, so fuck you.
Uncancel me, please.
I don't remember something like that.
It looks like such a lazy costume.
I'm looking at an image and it's just a t-shirt
with the it printed on it.
Yeah, I mean, he looks like he's like 16.
Yeah.
What a fuck.
Charles, the son, the son headline, Charles Rages at Nazi Harry.
In doghouse at a high grove after huge row,
ordered to pay private visit to Auschwitz.
Son, son to punish you for dressing up as a Nazi for Halloween.
I'm putting you, I'm gassing you.
You can see what it's like.
Uh, based.
Crazy.
Yeah, royals are insane.
The only reason people like them is because the media says,
look at how cool they are and everyone's like, yeah.
Well, it's because...
Because they're cool and rich and impressive.
That makes me cool and rich and impressive
by being associated with them by country.
There's a great little comic by a little Twitter artist I follow.
They're called Red and Black Salamander.
Wait, wait, wait.
Is it 9mm?
Their Twitter at is 9mm ballpoint.
They're called Red and Black Salamander,
and they have a comic they did.
It's like a big top hat capitalist guy in a castle
being like, look how rich I am.
And then all the peasants are all like, where's ours?
What about us?
And then the second panel is,
he just draws a line in the ground around them all.
And then he goes, look how rich we are.
And they all go, hey, yeah.
And they have guns and they're defending the border.
LaMalle, pretty good.
Point made.
Shit, what was I going to say about that?
About being Harry, being some rich guy?
Oh, we know that the reason they like the Royals,
we know from CGP Grey is because they technically generate
tourist revenue.
They're actually good for the economy.
And we know from Sean that that isn't necessarily true.
Yeah, yeah.
That was the first big like, oh my God, CGP Grey's flawed.
Wow.
CGP Grey said something that was a little cringe?
And then more recently...
What else has he said that I believe but that was cringe?
Oh no!
Yeah, more recently, I don't know who it was,
but one of the many popular city infrastructure YouTubers
was talking, was doing like a CGP Grey's take
on self-driving cars being the way of solving traffic is dumb.
And here's why that's dumb.
Yeah, I've seen his video about self-driving cars.
And it's like, no, don't use cars.
Fuck cars, more trains.
Like he sort of missed the obvious solution.
Yeah, that's...
Yeah.
And on my corner of Twitter, everybody loves trains.
So, at the time I remember thinking like,
you know what he was saying made a lot of sense,
but yeah, now I'm more...
I've never liked cars and like politics,
politics, right, have leaned me even further into the position of like,
it's not just a me thing, fuck cars, cars are a social ill actually.
A public transit and rail is like, it's actually just better.
It would be better if more people used it.
And also if more cities were built to accommodate people using it.
Because I've also seen a lot of stuff about like how cities in America,
certain cities are built for the car and to such a point that there's
almost nothing but roads.
Like everything is so spread out because of the amount of roads they need to build.
A lot of cities, especially smaller cities, are just not walkable at all.
Yeah, you're basically expected to have a car to get anywhere.
It was always weird.
Like when I first came to Virginia for Radcon 1 and I saw how flat everything is.
Virginia sucks.
I hated living in Virginia and in hindsight I think this is why.
It's not a place built for foot traffic.
Even like Richmond, there's no subway system in Richmond or in Virginia Beach proper.
You have to have a car.
Yeah.
Or you're fucked.
It was very like, oh, are we going somewhere?
Well, there's only two cars.
So if people are out in their cars, you have to stay at the house.
I didn't really have anywhere to go regardless, but it was weird.
Not to harp on it or anything, but when Trixie moved to Boston, she had a bad time for a number of reasons,
but among them was that she was like, oh, my friends live here.
We'll be doing stuff.
But then in practice, she never left her house.
She never took the subway.
And part of that, I think, was just that she grew up in Virginia.
She was in a car family.
Her dad was like the BMW dealer, gave her BMWs and stuff.
And living in Virginia, you got to use the car.
So she was not open to the possibility of subway transit.
I remember talking about it being like driving in Boston and finding a parking space that's not expensive was a nightmare.
It does suck.
It is a nightmare.
Yeah, that's good.
I'm glad it's a nightmare because it means people will use the train more.
But there are alternatives, but she did not take to those alternatives, which I think is pretty cringe.
But in her mild defense, she did live way down south in Braintree,
almost as far out of Boston as you can be and still technically be on the subway.
Yeah, it still would have been a bit of a hassle to get the train, to get the bus and the train into the subway.
I'm going to estimate walking to the bus stop, taking the bus to a red line stop,
and then taking the red line into the city probably would have taken her at least 45 minutes.
So a bit obnoxious, but doable.
But she never even tried.
She did not even know that buses came near her house that would take you to the subway.
I had to inform her.
She was like, how are you getting home?
And I looked it up on my phone.
A bus comes just a few blocks down from here, and she was like, what?
But the buses come here?
I was like, yeah, they come almost everywhere.
Walkability, highly valued.
My dad's a car guy.
I'm not a car guy.
I don't like him.
And now I have political reasons.
Now it's not just a me thing.
Now it's personal.
Yeah.
I've never had a car or done my license in order to be able to drive.
I don't have a few lessons, but I've always been like, why?
People are not getting their fucking driver's license.
Whatever.
I guess I should do that.
But I never needed it.
There's a train to anywhere in London.
Yeah.
And there's a bus to anywhere local.
It's really easy to get around.
Yeah, that's fair.
Kazi never got their driver's license, and I think for the same reason, they just take the subway everywhere.
But then Michelle also has never gotten her license, but she doesn't take the subway.
So what's she thinking?
Wait, yeah, she lives in Virginia now, right?
Well, it was in Cincinnati, which I don't think has a subway system.
And now she's in Virginia Beach, which definitely does not have a subway system.
Not like a robust one at all, not one that actually gets you around.
She lived in Hawaii, didn't she initially?
Where you also a place where you need to drive everywhere.
I've heard people say that about Hawaii, that you have to drive everywhere.
There's definitely no subway in Hawaii.
Maybe there's some rail.
Maybe there's some light rail here and there.
I don't even know.
Can you like hike through the jungle?
I mean, it's a small island, but it's not that small.
It's not like you can just...
You can have a Pokemon journey adventure.
Can you just walk halfway?
Can you just walk across Honolulu?
Wait, is the main island called Hawaii?
I don't know.
The major city of Hawaii is Honolulu.
The main island is either called Hawaii, it's also, or it's called Honolulu.
I don't know.
I think the largest one would maybe take the better part of an entire day
if you walked straight through it in a straight line.
But maybe I'm stupid and I don't know actually how big it is.
Well, I mean, it's mountainous terrain, so it would not be a straight shot.
Walking through the middle of it, I think, would be quite difficult terrain to walk through.
I'm just trying to find a scale map here.
How many miles across is it?
This is such a simple thing, I'm asking you, Google.
Why will you not...
Okay, it's like 50 miles.
It's like 50 to maybe like 75 miles across, depending on how.
So yeah, you could walk 50 miles in a day.
It would be a hard day's walk, but you could do it.
But not like across a mountain.
Maybe if you walked all day along the beach, you could get like most of the way across one of its edges.
Hawaii or Volcano?
Yeah, yeah, I'm just looking at it.
Funny.
Oh, yes, I was right.
The main island is called Hawaii.
I was right, I'm a genius.
Okay, Honolulu is a different island.
Oahu and...
Kauai?
So kauai.
It's so kauai.
Kauai and puai.
Crazy, those crazy natives with their crazy gobbledy cook.
Hawaii means family.
Does it?
No.
Wait, that's the Lilo and Stitch thing, right?
Yeah.
Lilo and Stitch means family.
Remember that.
Okay, I will.
Thanks.
Let's see.
There's something on my list here.
I guess it doesn't really need mentioning, but the podcast has officially ended.
This was on my list.
I saw this mentioned in my discord and I was like...
It's a shame.
My first feeling is like, oh, that's too bad.
My second feeling is about time.
It's been like most of a year since there's been one.
Has it really been more like six months?
I think so.
I recently saw a screenshot of Mumki doing his one-piece videos and he had the running tally of days since the last podcast.
And the last time I saw it was at like 240 days.
We were going for the full 365.
I don't really have a statement about it.
How do you feel about it?
I think it was obvious that we didn't want to do the show anymore.
Sure, yeah.
So I was like, yeah, let's just make it official.
In the very back of my head I've been like, if Nate came to me, this is in the back of my head,
I was always like, if Nate came to me and said, hey, do you want to do some more podcast?
I'll be like, yes.
But the fact that he came to me and said, I haven't been wanting to do.
And I was like, yeah, me neither.
It's sort of like, if one of us wanted to do it, I think the other would have.
But if neither of us want to do it, why even pretend?
Yeah, I guess that makes sense.
Well, it's a shame.
Yeah, I mean, it's just talking about One Piece.
I love One Piece still.
I still read it.
Damn, I never fulfilled the prophecy.
I said that one day I would catch up with One Piece and be a guest on Potycast and I never did.
I had a little thing planned.
I was going to draw a new face bubble for myself.
I was going to draw a little...
My idea for when I guessed it on the Potycast was I was going to draw a little attached boat to the main boat.
That would be like a little Hawkeye-Meahawk raft.
Oh, yeah.
That would be my little side boat.
And my little speech bubble would come out of that little side boat.
You know, one thing I always had in my head when I would listen to One Piece music on my MP3 player occasionally
was like, what if we animated an episode of One Piece?
But it was me and Nate, our characters, our sonas and our boat.
And it would be like the way that a complicated battle part of an arc on Skype or Water 7 or whatever,
they'd have the little faces on a map and they'd show where they're going and be like,
oh, Nate's doing this over here with his sword and then Gibbs over here shooting.
And then there's a battle going on.
It's like, what if I just made One Piece but for the Potycast?
It would never happen in a million years.
You're not fighting battles on the Potycast.
No, we're just sailing.
We're just talking about the comic.
I always like the idea of having the big epic battle scene or implying that and the big epic stuff,
but not having to build it up.
I don't want to write the beginning.
I want to write the middle.
I just want to write the big thing where they're like, oh, that's so fucking, so much blood.
He punched him so hard that he's dead.
That's so fucking cool.
I've been working on the big final moment of Phantom's Revenge this past week.
I've been making assets for the final form of the final boss.
And it's taken me a long time, but it's really coming together.
I'm finally at the state.
It's not all drawn, but I started putting sprites into the game and making objects out of them and programming them so that they move.
The final boss is a big object with a bunch.
It has a couple of little parts that move.
I've animated a little sequence where one part slots into place and then another part slots into place and then another part slots into place.
It's not timed for anything.
It needs a little bit of finesse, but it's moving in the right general way.
And I'm like, yeah, that's pretty good.
Yeah, it's looking pretty good.
That's very cool.
It's very exciting.
I was describing the plot of Phantom's Revenge to my mom in the car on the way to the train station.
Oh my god.
How could you possibly have done that?
Well, I can't say it because it would spoil it.
Oh, right.
I thought you meant from the beginning of life.
So there's this internet, I guess a LOL cow.
Well, a LOL cow is that you would explain Chris Chan and everything.
That would be a very difficult thing to do.
No, I just kept it to the plot of the game itself.
She asked me like, wait, is this about your pony?
And I'm like, yes, yes, he's back.
It's this big moment.
Yes, mom, he must have his revenge.
It's the only way.
And then I described your pony.
This is funny.
Say what?
No, it's just funny.
This is the idea of your mother knowing about Phantom Horn.
She does.
She knows about Phantom Horn.
And I had to explain to her why it was necessary for him to take his revenge
and how he intends to do it.
You see, all this blood.
You needed it to be on the floor.
There's so much blood, yes.
I told her, I was like, yeah, at some point in development,
I decided to make it really gruesome.
And I told her about cutting the enemies in half
and like the bloods playing everywhere and splattering
and dripping down the walls and stuff.
And maybe this is stupid.
Maybe this is the stupid thing to feel anything about.
Maybe this is just obvious, but there's something really satisfying
that the game is called Phantom's Revenge.
And it is like, literally that's what it is.
Like the process of playing the game is Phantom taking his revenge,
step bit by bit, and there's something about the name of the thing
is also the thing itself that I'm like, I don't know,
it's something really satisfying thinking about it.
Man, I'm building the scene.
I'm building the scene right now that I've been envisioning
for more than a year.
Maybe not more than a year, just about a year.
Wait, no, almost two years.
Phantom 4 was like a year and three quarters ago.
2020 March or 2020, I mean.
So yeah, almost two years.
Going on two years, I've had this scene in my head.
Man, I've been working on, shit,
I've been working on Phantom's Revenge longer
than I was ever drawing Slime and Punishment.
That sucks.
What a nightmare.
It's a whole different level of work to make the game.
It is, but it's still just one moment.
Well, that's not one moment.
I would say that the story of Phantom's Revenge
comprises what I probably would have called
an arc of Slime and Punishment.
And I'm sure I could have drawn it much faster
than I have made it a video game.
But I mean, as I'm saying this out loud, like duh,
like of course I could have, right?
So it's fine, never mind.
I talk myself out of being upset.
Yeah.
What the hell?
That's going pretty good.
If it's called Revenge, can you Venge?
Let's check out our old friend UrbanDictionary.com.
Urban, Urban Dictionary.
Let's look up Revenge.
Okay, Revenge.
One of the best Minecraft parodies of all time.
Man, I just listened to Revenge by Captain Sparkles
for 10 hours straight.
Best 10 hours ever.
Second definition.
The sweetest joy next to getting pussy.
I see.
So, okay, let's try a real dictionary.
Venge or Avenge, from the old French,
vengir, revenge, avenge, punish.
So to, so to, so to Venge means to get revenge.
And so revenge is re-revenge.
Yeah, but what's...
Is to give revenge back.
Revenge and Avenge are the same.
To get revenge against somebody and to avenge somebody.
Just avenge is just the verb, right?
No, you can revenge as a verb.
You can revenge yourself on someone,
but you avenge someone else.
Like you can avenge yourself or you can avenge your father on a guy.
But you take revenge for your father on the guy.
Oh, okay.
So, vengir is old French and that comes from the Latin vindicare.
Is this like...
Venge comes from...
Yes, it has to be.
It's damn it.
The same Latin root, if parallel evolved,
one way to become English and then another way through Greek
to become a different English word.
Lamal.
Well, I mean, English is just borrowing all sorts of things from Latin.
This is just like...
Was it F and P?
I think there's a Jan Measley video about how F and P are the same letter.
They came from the same Greek letter.
But they went through two different evolutionary paths.
And one stayed in the English dictionary,
English language and the other one didn't,
but then we needed a new sound,
so we borrowed it back from a different language that evolved it in a different way.
Great, great shit.
Wacky.
Wacky as hell.
I type in vindicare and I get Warhammer 40k.
They looked up some funny words.
Some funny words?
They didn't name...
They were thesaurus-ing?
They were thesaurus-ing.
We need our thing that is a guy who kills
to have a very good name that is historical.
I mean, that's...
Let's us do some googling.
That's the imperial aesthetic right there.
Yeah.
I found this image.
I found this helpful diagram.
Avenge or revenge?
To avenge is to get payback for the inflicted party.
To revenge.
To get payback as the inflicted party.
This is for killing my brother versus this is for ruining my life.
So in case you're...
In case you were wondering...
Yeah, fuck you.
Fuck.
I wonder if you could build a different word
that has vengeance on the end of it.
It means to get payback for no reason.
This is to...
To avenge is to kill yourself for harming somebody else.
Prevenge is when you fight...
You throw the first punch.
They didn't even do anything.
Mmm.
To avenge is to kill yourself for something you did to yourself.
You flip it.
You flip it turnways, right?
I'm about to open one right now.
Yeah.
Good fucking job, English speakers of the past.
You have served us well.
I had something...
Oh, I had...
Let me tell you about a little bit of a crisis that I had.
I went home for Thanksgiving.
The TV was on.
We watched...
Shit, it's not the Colbert Report.
Colbert is on The Daily Show now?
Or The Late Show?
Colbert is Good Morning America?
I don't know.
Colbert does a talk show now, just like a normal talk show.
And he said stuff, right?
I was listening to Colbert do this, you know,
do this broad liberal comedy.
And I felt a bash for a moment.
I felt a bash for a moment because I realized
that all the opinions he was espousing
were very similar to mine.
He had the similar takes on all of the things,
on many things that I do.
I was a bit surprised to see that he was just openly like
I disagree with the Rittenhouse, you know,
verdict and all that.
I thought that was more...
I thought that was something that more liberals
were like, yeah, I kind of get it.
But no.
So I guess the mainstream liberal opinion
is that Rittenhouse bad.
I guess in other things, vaccines good.
He said Elon Musk bad.
And I was like, okay, okay.
Anyway, I felt a...
I felt a pang of like, oh no, am I a lib?
Am I a lib?
Am I a fucking Democrat?
And then I said no.
And I said no, no, no, no, no, it's okay, it's okay.
Maybe Steven Colbert has like a based writer or something.
I may agree with the mainstream media on certain things,
but the difference between me and them is that
they are annoyed about things.
They're annoyed about some things.
But I want beheadings.
That's what separates me from the animals.
What separates you from the Democrats
is that you are phantom horn
and you're gonna get your revenge.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly.
Speaking of exactly,
someone mentioned in the comments that
I think last week we nominated Rod Serling
for the voice grail.
And someone wrote it in the comments like,
you guys nominated Applejack?
They didn't say Applejack, they said some funny character.
And I think they were talking about Applejack.
They were like, you nominated some other funny character
for the voice grail.
And you have not updated the spreadsheet.
You have not updated the spreadsheet.
There's a spreadsheet?
Well, they mentioned, here, the comment is,
yeah, this is Prince Isolation,
who I happen to know just bought a copy of Road to Radcon
with you can too, listener.
DM me on Discord.
Follow my pinned tweet on Twitter
to buy your own copy of Road to Radcon.
I've got more than 50 copies left.
Anyway, they got theirs.
They said, speaking of the voice grail,
wasn't there some funny character that was supposed to be
added to that some episodes ago, like a Kirby or Yoshi voice
or something? I'm pretty sure it was Applejack.
I feel like I never saw them get added to the Google doc
in the description.
Yeah, I remember there is a Google doc.
I didn't... Oh, no, here it is.
Yeah, under the voice mail link.
Yeah, voice grail, voice jail.
Yes, here it is.
Am I logged in?
Can I edit this?
No, I would have to log in as the procrastinators.
So I will.
I'm going to do this right now.
Who updates that, though?
I didn't even know we had it.
Nobody has updated it in a while.
But like who did?
Were you making it?
At some point, I definitely did.
Okay.
Here's the list, the list right now.
Well, I'll just...
I'm going to add Applejack.
I don't even remember the last time I actually updated those.
I feel like we went a long time without adding anyone
to voice grail or voice jail.
There might have been someone
who we did put in jail,
but that I forgot.
So if I forgot anyone...
Let me know in the comments if I'm missing anyone
who should be in voice grail or voice jail.
We need to hire a jailer and a grailer.
A jailer and a grailer.
Keep track.
Well, MarinPan already does...
He's already basically
that for the Minecraft server.
So maybe he could take up
PCP Gailer,
I guess it pronounced jailer.
Duties as well.
Alright, so here is the list
as it currently stands.
Although, some of these...
Okay.
Oh no, no, no.
There were some people who got freed from voice jail
ages and ages ago
as part of the...
The Bail.
The Bail Fund.
Was it the George Floyd thing
or was it before that?
No, it was the riots.
It was that time.
Yes, it was the Voice Bail Fund.
The Voice Bail Fund did get a few of them out,
but it didn't get everyone out.
I'm pretty sure that Lost Tape Archive
and Loll Pussies But Here Eating With Spoons,
who I believe was
an alias of Teen CP,
and maybe a few...
Maybe all of these, actually.
I think all of these were on the Bail list,
but they didn't all get bailed.
Only a few of them did, so...
There we go.
In case you were wondering...
Good ol' racist forestgump.
Just sitting pretty,
anointed in the realm of the voice grail,
as he deserves.
Classic character.
Yes.
I remember Margar.
What have they been doing?
Well, not making voice mails.
And good riddance, because apparently,
they ended up in jail, so they must've done some...
I remember them just being kind of boring.
I remember...
Was it just that they were making too many
and they were too long? Did we just complain about that?
Something like that.
We snapped.
I think Margar made pretty decent voice mails,
and I thought they were good,
but then I think...
I think they got too big for their britches.
And I was like, I've had enough.
I've had enough of you die.
Wait.
Yeah.
What about
Errorari with the
Prepare for the Bear and all that?
Were they never grailed?
I don't think...
I mean, they might've been and I could've forgotten.
I don't think we...
I think they should get a voice grail at this point.
Those were really fun.
You know, that's fair.
Yeah, I...
They started to get a little weird and, like, confusing,
but I really liked the first one.
I didn't think they were weird and confusing.
Well, but I thought that they...
I thought that they had...
She had done everything you could do with them, basically.
They were kind of starting to get repetitive,
but, okay, I'm okay with, like, a retroactive voice grailing
for...
Well, I mean, I know that they're Errorari,
but did they make the voice calls under a different name?
Did they make the voice calls under...
They had a poetic title.
Prepare for the Bear.
I think it's...
The Bear Minimum?
All right.
Should I just... Should I put her in as Errorari
or prepare for Bear?
Prepare for Bear, because that's what it started as.
Prepare for Bear.
Okay, here we go.
All right, that makes sense.
A retroactive grailing.
Because I think we just forgot about the grail for a while,
but, you know, it's an integral part of PCP lore.
Yes.
Yeah, commenters, if there's anyone missing
who should be here, let me know.
But that's all I can remember at the moment.
All right. Well, I'm glad that sorted out.
Yeah.
Well, I guess I got nothing else to talk about.
Speaking of voicemails, do you want to get to voicemails?
I had two things on my Talk About list,
and both of these are things that I forgot to talk about
last week, and that just stayed on the list since then,
so I got to mention them, because they're on my list.
I have to do it.
Grilling cheese.
There's cheese you can grill.
It's great.
Wow. That's it.
It's called halloumi.
It's Greek, I think.
Oh, is that like the white, like, rubbery...
not rubbery, but like wobbly sort of...
It's a bit rubbery.
I mean, it's a very firm cheese.
Yeah, I think I've had some of that before.
You grill it?
It's really good to have like a halloumi salami.
Halloumi salami.
Halloumi salami, what a wonderful phrase.
Like, you could have that as like a thing with like a,
I don't know, a bread stick.
I'm trying to think of when I've eaten it before.
I think I've seen it where my dad had like a Italian,
like he had the Italian flag.
Halloumi made up the white part,
and then there was like pepperoni,
or salami is the red part, and then,
oh no, tomatoes is the red part,
and then something else is the green part,
and I forget what that was.
Basil?
No, it was something that you could pick up a piece of it
and eat it.
Gosh, could be so many things.
Cucumber?
I don't know.
No, it would be Italian.
I can't remember.
What do they have that's green in Italy?
Halloumi's is like...
Marijuana, oh, marijuana.
Yes, marijuana pizza.
A huge flag of marijuana, yes.
Do you imagine fucking a marijuana pizza?
There's no doubt at all that people have done it,
100%.
I've never had it cold.
I've only ever eaten it pan-fried,
and it gets stringy and chewy,
much like a mozzarella stick, almost.
It gets a little soft, but doesn't fall apart.
You can eat it with your fingers.
It's so good.
It's one of my new favorites
that I've been buying from Aldi.
My other thing is I bought a bunch of...
I was looking at other stores.
I've talked about Seltzer,
buying every different brand of Seltzer water I can find.
I was looking at Hannaford,
and they had a bunch of Keto ice creams.
They have different brands of Keto ice creams
than I usually get.
I usually get the Aldi kind.
It's called Sunday Shop is the brand.
This one had a more recognizable brand
called Halo Top,
and I was like, base.
So I ordered a bunch.
I ordered five pints of different flavors
of Keto ice cream from Halo Top.
And they all suck.
They're all bad.
Five pints, you say.
Five pints.
They're all bad.
The thing about the Halo Top Keto
is that they're all very fluffy
in a way that I dislike.
It sort of is like eating...
It's a little bit more like eating
like a cool whip
than it is like ice cream.
Fluffy.
My first thought is that it's like...
when you go to make a snowball
and it's powdery instead of sticky,
it's not...
It's just sort of unsatisfying.
Yeah, it just doesn't...
It's not...
It's fluffy.
It's not creamy.
It's not creamy like you want ice cream to be.
It's just kind of...
airy, spongy.
Like it's okay.
Like cool whip is fine,
but it's not the optimal ice cream experience.
It's not indulgent.
It's not like...
Yeah.
Like...
It's hard.
It's like a...
It's not sloppy enough.
I mean fluffy is fine.
Like fluffy is fine for what it is.
It's just not the consistency I'm looking for
when I dig into a pint.
So I was like...
It has better macros.
Like it has less...
It has even fewer carbs
and more fat
than the Sunday Shop reign.
Which is good.
Which is what you want.
But it just doesn't taste good
and I don't want to eat it.
So what's the point?
Nothing.
Okay.
Yeah.
I had to touch on my groceries list here
so everybody knows what I've been snacking on.
Although I'm not keto right now
because I mean, you know,
I had to do Thanksgiving
and now I got friendsgiving today.
So like...
I was like, fuck it.
Fuck it for the weekend.
Whatever.
I'll get back on it.
I'll get back on it until Christmas after this.
Okay.
That's all I got.
You want to do voicemails?
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
I think the last one last week
was Rod Surling the crypto zone.
So I think the first one this week
is called Trixie?
Question mark, question mark?
You ready?
I am getting to the thing.
Yes.
I'm ready.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
Who is this Trixie you keep it happening about?
Surely you're not talking about me.
The great and powerful Trixie.
I trained all my life to earn that title.
What did she ever do to become a witch?
Golden witch.
What does that even mean?
What's so gold about her?
You've got to be kidding.
Trixie the pony is getting uppity.
Gold.
Oh, demon souls.
It's corrupt.
It's evil.
Trixie the golden witch.
She spins gold into whatever else she's selling.
She spins gold into what is it?
Into Yip Studio.
Lol.
It's the opposite.
It's not Cinderella.
Who is it that spins flax into gold?
I'm thinking of not Rapunzel.
Sleeping Beauty who could spin her hair
into gold or something.
It's the girl in the Rumpelstiltskin.
What is her...
I think she doesn't have a name.
She's just the miller's daughter
who can spin flax into gold.
Or straw.
And a straw into gold?
Okay, Wikipedia says it's straw.
Whatever.
Some versions make the miller's daughter blonde
and describe the straw into gold claim as a careless boast.
The miller makes it but the way his daughter's straw-like blonde hair
takes on a gold-like luster when sunshine strikes it.
Uh, okay.
Whatever.
Weird thing to say about your daughter.
Yes.
I guess it makes sense.
I guess it's not that weird.
Yes, but Trixie the golden witch.
Her magical spell is that she turns gold
into something that is not valuable.
Yeah, yeah.
Into Rap.
Into Bitcoin.
Into...
Yes, she spins gold into NFTs.
Have you been seeing her NFT takes?
I've seen a few of them.
They are predictably embarrassing, but whatever.
She is very...
She said as much in that one tweet where she was like,
What if I minted the asterisk war sucks series as an NFT and sold it?
What would happen?
What would be the consequences of such a thing?
Well, someone would...
You might, in theory, get a bit of money if you sold it
and someone else would get a digital receipt on the Ethereum blockchain
saying you bought the asterisk war series
and that is the end of what would happen.
She's clearly thinking.
She's clearly thinking, hmm, how can I monetize this?
This NFT thing.
Yeah, yeah.
Stone toss made two and a half million dollars
or whatever, selling flurks.
Hmm.
How can I pull a...
How can I, Trixie the Golden Witch, pull a stone toss
and make $200,000 to buy an RV or a truck
or whatever it was that she wants these days?
Always thinking.
Okay.
Next one is called Virgin Crypto vs Chad's Stocks.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, why don't you just, like, buy fucking stocks or something?
Like, you can literally get dividends from them.
You don't even have to sell them.
Like, you'll get paid for owning a stock.
It's fucking awesome.
That is true.
I find that people have told me this before
and I...
Am I just stupid for not doing that?
I mean, the stocks can devalue,
but, like, you still just get dividends for having them.
I've had, like, a few stocks on this trading app that I got.
And I'm like, oh, wow.
Fucking Green Energy UK.
They're Wind Farm Energy.
And, like, I believe in that.
I'll put some money in.
And it has consistently gone down in value.
I put in 20 pounds.
It's nothing.
I was just sort of, like, interested in trying it out.
But I still get dividends of, like, 25 cents every so often.
Minerva double-cast when she was on.
She said, fuck, what was the kind of stock that she...
Was it, like, a market index fund?
I think she said was, like, the most stable stock that, like, only go up.
I think that was it.
And I don't know.
At least I have the moral high ground for investing stocks into Green Energy.
I feel good about that, even though it's not really worth much.
But that's kind of the point of it, is, like, if you believe in a thing,
you buy stocks and so that they have money or something.
The money you put in becomes, like, some sort of a...
It's some sort of a good thing for the Green Energy.
And that's all that matters.
Or, I mean, you could make money doing it, I mean, optimally.
Well, sure.
One would hope. One would hope.
Yeah.
But, like, the way to make money is, like, to put it into Tesla or something.
Well, yeah, something you think will go up.
Chicken nuggets.
I mean, like Bitcoin, Tesla go up, but it can also go down.
Bitcoin has been going down a bit recently,
although it could just be what they call consolidation before another spike.
Who knows?
I feel like the Bitcoin really is, like, a chump thing.
It's just stocks, but worse.
Yeah.
Because you could lose all your money with a stock, I don't know.
It's the same, but you still get paid.
You get paid, like, interest for having it, kind of.
You know, like, the ideal investor who bought Bitcoin early, I mean, indeed,
they have their investment has grown a lot, and they've made a lot of money doing it.
I mean, it's kind of the same as buying a stock before it blows up.
If you invested in Disney before Disney was big or whatever strange thing it would be.
I'm saying, yeah, people definitely have made money buying, for instance, Bitcoin.
But, you know, that doesn't guarantee, that does not guarantee this is the critical error
that some people make in assessing the value of crypto.
That does not guarantee that it will continue to be the case that, like, an investment in
Bitcoin will, you know, quintuple in the course of, like, two years or whatever.
But, and I was, I talked a bit about, like, crypto and NFTs.
Oh, yeah, another coal bearer.
Just, like, I guess it's just standard liberal normal opinion to just think NFTs bad.
Good for them, I guess.
Yes, I mean, it's definitely good that it's laughable on a somewhat mass appeal way.
I was a bit gutted, not gutted.
I was a bit like, hmm, to be like, hmm, I do share a lot of opinions with this mainstream media democrat.
So, I guess I kind of see, I guess I kind of see where the far right psychopaths are coming from
when they call people like me, you know, libs and democrats and don't distinguish any further than that.
Yes, from a skewed enough perspective, I could see why I'm the same to them.
And I'll just have to reckon with that.
Anyway, were we talking about stocks?
I am a fool.
This voicemailer, yes, I actually am a fool for not having my money invested in something.
I have been, in the last year or two, I have been thinking about where to invest my money,
and I just haven't come to any final conclusions about it.
I should have probably, it should be in something, instead of just sitting in fucking Bank of America
making fucking 0.5 APY or whatever dog shit they give me.
So, maybe I should just get something.
I want it to be liquid, I want it to be somewhat liquid, but also I want it to be making at least some returns.
This is the conundrum, I guess.
It's confusing, I definitely need to look into it a lot more, because at the moment I know barely anything.
Like they say that one of the most secure assets you can buy is government debt, government bonds.
I mean, nothing is ever 100% certain in life, but it is as virtual a certainty as anything is in investing
that the United States dollar will continue to be roughly as valuable as it is.
The United States will not default on their debts.
I looked into bonds, and I was like, okay, maybe I could put some of my money, maybe a fifth of my money into bonds.
I wouldn't have it for five years, but five years down the line I would get it back.
And I was gutted to see that the return on that is only a few percent.
I was like, really? I basically just give you my money and I don't have it for years, and I get it back and the gain is like three percent?
I was expecting it to be like ten, at least. This doesn't seem like a lot.
I mean, I suppose it's better than it's slowly losing value by just sitting in a bank.
Right?
Yeah, yeah, that's true. Yeah, that is true.
It may be worth that just to offset if you're not planning on spending that large amount of money all at once or in the near future.
I thought I could get better than that, but I don't know, maybe that's the best I can get.
I was disappointed with those figures, but I don't know.
I've looked into it a bit. I should have looked into it more, because I should have figured out something to do with my money by now, and I haven't, because I'm stupid.
Okay, next voicemail is also called Trixie, this time with no question marks.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey Ben, Trixie posted her, what's your favorite videos on my shitty channel?
And the top vote of comment said, oh, you mean all the ones you, you private it, you fucking idiot, lol.
By the way, you're gay.
Lol.
Yeah, I think I saw that she posted that.
Yeah, it's like, which of my videos, which of my videos do you wish I didn't deprive it?
And I guess the idea is she wants to deprive it, the private ones.
Which like, fucking duh, of course you should do that. Of course you shouldn't have privated those videos in the first place.
Obviously it fucked your channel. Obviously it was always going to fuck your channel, and everyone could have told you that, which I did tell you that, but you did it anyway.
So like, obviously yes, but also like, man, fuck the people that like, fuck people like Tarbuck Transom or someone who, the people that worked on the archive to archive, when, you know, when she was like, yeah, I'm de-listing all my videos, they're all going private.
And then people spent like months, like, you know, finding everything and making sure it was all archived, so it wouldn't be lost as she was like, destroying it.
And then to, you know, six months later be like, just kidding, actually, that cost me some money, so I know I made you guys do all that, but like, I'm just, I'll probably start putting it back.
What do you guys want me to put back? All the stuff that I arbitrarily like took from you and like destroyed, like, which ones do you want me to just like, hit the cancel button and just undo that on?
Just let me know in the comments. Okay, bye.
Man, you factured goodwill.
Oh, it's such a good thing that you're doing, you're bringing us back all of these things that you took away.
Thank you for giving those videos that I like that you took away for us for no reason.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Artificial scarcity. This is the NFT thing. I've realized, okay, people have all these weird claims about NFTs and like the power, right?
People say, oh, environmental concerns. Oh, it's hurting the environment. Oh, it uses too much power. And then NFT bros go, no, it doesn't. It just doesn't.
And I'm like, okay, if you say so. So, I don't know. I don't know. I can't really argue the environmental point. People that don't like NFTs say it uses tons of energy.
People that like NFTs say it doesn't. So, I don't know. But it doesn't matter because what I really hate about NFTs is not that.
That is an incidental reason that I hate them. I hate them just for what they are and for what they represent, which is, yeah, they're artificial scarcity imposed on the digital realm.
Tom had a tweet recently where he said like, he said like, he said like blockchain tech technology is good, but just NFTs as they currently exist are bad.
And I was like, no, I don't think so. I think the blockchain is just inherently bad. The blockchain just exists to create digital scarcity where none existed before.
The blockchain is just a tool for, yeah, for that. It's just a new way to create digital records that are more indelible than ever before.
And I genuinely think that's nothing but bad. I generally don't think anything good can come from it.
I think people when they say that they're only talking about the currency side of it. I don't really know too much about what the blockchain literally is.
The fact that it can prove that a certain IP address or person owns a thingy, which is allowed NFTs to exist, that's stupid because NFTs are like art trading, but in a way that is not necessary because it's digital.
But currency is a little different, I guess, if that's the technology it's using to prove that somebody has currency so that you can't just copy paste money and pay for it.
It's necessary for the digital currency to have legitimacy of any level.
I still think it's bad. I think cryptocurrency is just bad. It's just a more...
I like the idea.
It's money, which is bad, but it's a more concrete, it's an even less malleable concept of money. It's a more rigid, indelible, concrete form of money, which is just worse.
The people, I think, the sentiment I understand of government and freedom, and what if we had a currency that was separate from the wins of the government, who sometimes are people we try to elect the other person and we got this piece of shit.
So I get the sentiment behind it, but it's sort of like the root cause of the problem is money as a concept itself rather than who controls what the currency is valued at or whatever.
People think that by having Bitcoin, problems that are money related will be solved, but that's not really how the problems come from.
It's still just money. It's just money, but more... it's just money, but less fluid as a concept and less evenly distributed, and just worse.
It's just money again, and worse in some ways, in my opinion.
I've yet to see anything good that the blockchain can do at all, and I don't think there is anything, but maybe...
The blockchain is a... I've yet to see a very solid argument for the technology of the blockchain in the digital space, or in life in general.
Here's what I think. I feel like the blockchain is a solution. It's not a solution to anything. It's a solution to its own problems.
There was no... I guess if the problem is like, how can I get in on the ground floor of owning a new currency that will perhaps become the dominant currency one day?
Blockchain is a great solution to that, or Bitcoin may have been a great solution to that, and it has worked out pretty well.
If your problem is how can I avoid paying taxes, then yeah, I guess the blockchain is a solution to that, but it's not a solution to any real problem.
It's an individual solution to a problem that is global, I guess, in many countries.
People sometimes, particularly brain dead evangelists, talk about Bitcoin as though, literally as though, if only every person in the world had just invested in some Bitcoin, you know, 10 years ago,
then now everyone would be rich because everyone would have, because Bitcoin went up, number go up, and so everyone would have more money and be wealthier.
They talk about it as though that were the case. Bitcoin solves poverty by allowing anyone to buy it and number go up and become rich, and if you didn't do that, it's your own fault.
So yes, there are still poor people, but all of those people who are poor, now they deserve it because they didn't buy in, so now it's actually good.
Yeah, it's just the same again.
Yes, it is.
What if we could become the kings? What if we could become the royals instead of the ones that are already in power?
What if Biden had a little accident?
What if, fuck you, I got mine? What about that?
That is, that is attempting off, that does merit further consideration.
Hmm, haven't thought about getting mine, whether anyone else does or not, but it's, that's, there's a theory.
Okay, next voicemail is Son of Marowak. Are you ready?
Yep.
Three, two, one, go.
So I'm just going to throw out an idea for a guest.
How about try getting the Gaming Brit, Shea May, and or B-mask.
I know you've had the Gaming Brit on once before, and I know that the three of them are pretty damn good friends, so I figure if you can get one, maybe you can get the other two.
I know that Gaming Brit is a pretty busy guy, so maybe you wouldn't be able to get him, but maybe just throw it out as a, as an ask.
Like, can any of them make it to the podcast?
Like, it'd be pretty cool to hear all three of them on one podcast.
If not, just throwing it out there.
You can call me a super, super, pooper, scooper for even suggesting it, but I just thought I'd throw it out there.
Did we have, did we have the Gaming Brit on?
The Gaming Brit was on because Nate was, like, kind of associates, like associating with him or something.
They were talking, because Nate's not on.
I don't think the Gaming Brit would pay attention or say yes to anything like that.
I don't know, I don't really know much about the Gaming Brit.
I do like Shea May.
I'm in Shea's...
Is Shea May the Scottish guy?
Uh, yes, yes.
The Seven Hour Pokemon.
Yeah, yeah, that guy.
Okay.
I like him.
I'm in his Discord server.
I've barely talked in there, but I'm in there.
I probably could ask him.
I don't know if he'd be interested.
But I would like to have him on if he wanted to come on, for sure.
Yeah, man.
And I don't know who Beemask is.
I've never heard of that person.
Sorry, Beemask.
It's good.
Shea May's a good suggestion.
I'd like to maybe talk to him.
I mean, he seems cool.
Next voicemail is called VVV321GO.
They're conditioning our kids with Pokemon.
I was playing the game, minding my own business,
and I found Shellos, Gastryjohn, the Slug Pokemon,
and the Underground Yerks, the Slugs in the Underground.
They're conditioning our kids to think it's okay for these Slugs to be in the Underground.
They'll think they're friendly.
Put their balls on them, let them inside them.
We're not safe.
They're already among us.
Slugs are just Yerk propaganda.
Sluggo.
It's just like Karl Pilkington said.
We've already got snails.
What do we need Slugs for?
They're just redundant.
They're homeless, Ben.
They're just Yerk propaganda.
They shouldn't be here.
Yeah, they're homeless.
They're homeless.
They deserve it.
We need to eradicate them.
We need to offer up our bodies as hosts.
No, not in my backyard.
Not in my backyard.
That's not in my brain hole.
Gotta kick them out.
Gotta send them on their way.
Gotta put down benches that they can't sleep on.
Gotta put spikes under the underpass.
Don't let them set up shops.
Salt the earth.
Salt the benches.
Salt everywhere.
I eat salted every meal just for this reason.
They can't get in me.
They can't get in me because I'm too salty.
VVV, thanks for the warning.
Everyone needs to be aware.
This is a growing problem in our society.
Slug awareness.
Raise it.
Next question is which former PCP member do you miss the most?
What do you think?
None of them.
None of them?
Define miss.
Chris still speak to Munchy.
Yeah, I wouldn't pick Munchy because I still speak to him pretty regularly.
So for me, if that weren't the case, I would probably say Munchy.
But since it's not, I don't miss him.
I guess I would say Nate because it makes me sad
that he doesn't seem to care about stuff that me and him used to care about.
Yeah.
He's the one.
Yeah, that makes me the saddest.
Obviously I don't miss Trixie.
Tom is sort of around, I guess.
Yeah, I'd like Tom to be around more.
I wouldn't mind it if Tom were around more.
But you know, he's so busy with Saber Spark 64.
It's just so...
It was just the fact that he's doing that.
I don't know.
I mean, I guess he was already not very around.
Yeah, Nate makes me sad.
I don't understand what happens with him.
I don't know.
I guess that's my answer.
Okay, next one is a YouTube link with a timestamp Kotaku One Piece Worldseeker with Tim Rogers.
How old is this video?
So I'm a cop killer now.
Oh, he said it.
My mom told me I would never be a cop killer.
She was wrong.
Why would your mom tell you you'd never be a cop killer?
What a terrible thing to say to your son.
Son, you'll never be a cop killer.
You'll be a juvie for life.
You'll never get enough slime to enlist.
No, mom.
Fuck slime core.
I don't want to live in the rat race anymore.
I'm going to study the blade just like my hero Phantom Horn.
That's what people will say after they see him coolly take his revenge.
Like a fucking sick fuck.
Okay, well, I guess thanks for the...
Can we play that?
Will we get copyright struck if we put that clip in the episode?
It's just Tim Rogers playing a One Piece Worldseeker and saying,
I'm a cop killer now because he killed a Marine.
Yeah, that's fine.
Yeah.
Put the link in the description.
People can watch for themselves.
Link in the description with the timestamp.
1007.
Next one.
The PCP is now the dick show, except good.
Let's go.
Three, two, one, go.
Yeah, welcome to drama.
You want drama, you need drama.
You got it.
It's the Dick Cressinator Showcast.
Where Trixie is the new Maddux.
Coming live from whatever apartment I happened to have found myself in.
I'm your host, Ben Sainte.
The 905-patreon-dollar-man.
And he was always my actual wholesome counterpart, Gib.
Yeah.
Is he just like me?
He's just like me for real.
This guy should take over the podcast.
He's doing a better job.
He's a better us than we are.
Yeah, the Maddux parallel is there.
She made that...
She made that sub-stack post that was like...
The way she phrased it was...
The way she phrased it is like,
I'm through being a bitch online.
Like, I'm gonna be nice.
I've decided to be nice.
I don't really talk about that.
I think we talked about it a little.
But the real meaning of it was,
I got owned,
I tried to attack the PCP,
and I just got ridiculed and made them a bunch of money doing it,
and I'm humiliated.
So I'm not going to do that anymore.
So I feel like she may...
She has probably learned her lesson
and will probably avoid drama,
which is too bad.
But I would suggest harassing her online
and goading her into some sort of response.
I said this before.
I'll say it again.
I don't care.
I don't fucking care.
God, could you imagine
if there was a lawsuit,
a libel, or whatever?
Okay, well, I mean...
I don't even deal with that.
I mean harassment in the way that is like...
Just like...
You call it harassment if you're like a pussy,
and it's just like someone says something mean to you on Twitter
and you cry about it instead of just blocking them.
That's what kind of harassment I'm talking about.
Also, the illegal kind.
That I can't say that I'm talking about.
No.
The cool kind.
I feel like Trixie is not dumb enough
to do exactly what Maddox did.
But at this point, it's getting closer to possible.
Yeah.
Yeah, like...
I mean, Maddox really did take it to a new level.
It was unbelievable.
Yeah, Trixie has not been quite that stupid.
But like...
I mean, she's made some pretty...
I mean, the Who Are These podcast was a huge backfire.
So, I mean, the parallel is there, for sure,
if you want it.
Does that make me the Dick Masterson in this situation?
Well, I...
Well, I hope not.
But whatever.
Leftist Dick Masterson.
Can we...
Oh man, I don't know.
I don't want to talk too much about it.
Can we just talk about how...
Can we...
It just really stands out to me that Dick
and everyone in the Dick sphere now
is just all about Stone Toss.
Like, they all love Stone Toss.
And they like pay him money.
Yeah, they love Stone Toss.
They pay him money.
They buy his flerks.
They think he's great.
They think he's a free speech worker.
Even the one...
Man, I know I didn't really like Vito.
But like...
Yeah, Vito is also...
He calls himself a liberal.
But he's all about Stone Toss.
He's got the Stone Toss NFT.
He loves Ethan Ralph's got one.
Dick's got one.
Ricky Burrick's got one.
Everyone in that fucking scene.
They're just...
They're just all about this Nazi.
And Trixie is like, I want one.
He's not Trixie begging for one, right?
Oh, no, I did see that.
Trixie wants a flerk too.
It's like prose.
Come on.
It wasn't obvious enough already, right?
They obviously wouldn't believe somebody saying that
Stone Toss is a Nazi or has like...
They would say, nah, it's just a joke.
They would say no, it's just a joke.
And it's like...
Because of that, they see no problem with anything at all
associated with Stone Toss.
I don't know.
I don't have to sit here and explain.
Sure, yeah, it's a joke.
It's a joke.
It's a comic.
And the punchline is you laugh at it because like,
oh, yeah, it's true.
The Jews really are, you know,
subverting Western civilization
by encouraging miscegenation between blacks and whites.
Yeah.
So it is funny, actually.
But it's just...
Because it's just a joke.
The punchline is that it's true, but it's just a joke.
I saw someone...
It was not that comic.
It was a...
I think it was one about trans-suicide rates or something.
And it was a...
A 23rd...
Someone was saying to Ricky Berwick,
like, don't you know Stone Toss is a Nazi?
And Ricky Berwick was like, this is a joke.
And he made a weird face.
And then...
He said, bro, it's a comic.
You're just a joke.
He said...
No, he said, bro, that's a comic.
It's satire.
Like, bro, it's three panels.
It's three panels.
Anything you think...
Therefore, it's satire.
Anything you think it's saying,
it's automatically saying the opposite.
Because it's three images in a sequence.
That's just how it works.
And then...
And then Stone Toss replies.
And he replies to Ricky.
And he's like, yeah, exactly.
And also...
And the reason...
The proof that it's satire...
Is that these people are doing...
You know, the people complaining about me...
The people complaining that I say this
are just proving the point, right?
So, like, yeah.
And they're just...
He agrees.
Yes, it is satire.
And see, here's proof that what I'm saying is literally true.
And not a joke.
So...
Yeah, there's...
Yeah, I don't think they know what satire is.
I think it's just...
They think it means comedy,
but like a different way of saying it.
Yeah.
It's...
There's...
I mean, I don't know.
As far as I'm concerned, there's no defending it.
The it's satire defences doesn't make any sense.
It falls apart immediately if you think about it.
It's just cope.
They just...
They just want...
This Nazi is popular,
and they just want to...
They just want to be his friend.
That's literally it.
That's literally all there is to it.
And it's disgusting.
It's really disgusting.
People you might think would know better.
Like, I didn't think...
Like, I didn't like Vito.
I didn't think of him...
I didn't think of him as a Nazi,
but like, he's a super pro stone toss.
So like, what am I to...
What am I to make of this?
Trixie, you would think, you know, sucks,
but not a Nazi,
but she really wants a flirk.
She really wants a stone-tough NFT.
I don't like it.
I really don't like it.
I'm not surprised in the slightest,
but yeah, it sucks as well.
Yeah, it's particularly obnoxious,
even more so than usual.
Yeah.
Next voicemail?
Yep.
The next one is called,
I'm very behind of the podcast,
but your conversation for like a month ago about 60s anime
reminded me of a really cool part of anime history.
So there's a huge influx of foreign films in Japan
after World War II through the end of the 1950s,
bolstered by the backlog of films
that didn't make it over previously due to the war.
Many of these were Disney classics
and they set the expectation
for what animation should be in Japan,
but made it hard for domestic animation to compete.
That's part of why Tesco was so important,
because while Toya was trying to be the Disney of Japan,
like with the film Gibwatched,
Tesco pioneered the opposite approach
and found every single shortcut
you could possibly take to make it feasible
to produce a weekly TV series like Astro Boy,
which set the stage for TV anime in general going forward.
Director Kisaburo Sugi criticized him
for taking so many shortcuts
by telling him that it wasn't even animation,
to which Tesco literally responded,
yeah, it's not animation, it's anime.
I knew this.
Did he coin the phrase anime?
Like to shorten it,
because it's not fully animation?
I didn't, I don't know, maybe.
Or is that literally just the word that he had for it?
I don't know, that's interesting.
Yeah, you know, that's a good question.
It's kind of like Tesco was the Hanna-Barbera,
or the fucking, the less animated shows
of like Top Cat and Yogi Bear
that reused backgrounds
and were very cheap to make.
Yeah.
They're completely contrasted with the Disney stuff
and the Tom and Jerry to an extent,
which were doing a lot more lavish
on ones and stuff like that.
Yeah, I've said before that like, yeah,
Tesco's big innovation was like,
yeah, we want to make animation,
but like how can we make the most animation
the cheapest we possibly can?
How can we do it?
What's the easiest way we can do it?
And it worked.
And I mean, that's cool.
That's cool and valid, and I respect it.
I've always wanted to go and read all of Tesco's manga.
There's a lot of it.
But there's so much.
There's so much.
I've gotten through quite a bit of Astro Boy,
which is really good, really fun to read.
Very expressive and like cutesy,
but also like subject matters
does not match the cuteness of it whatsoever,
so it's great.
I have not read any Tesco.
I don't think I've seen any of his stuff.
He's great at like setting a panel up,
like filling a panel with interesting bits
and comedy stuff.
He's what you might call a mangaka.
Whoa, really?
In this day and age?
Well, of the 60s?
Yeah, I see, I see.
All right, next voicemail is a preti patel?
Preti patel?
Three, two, one, go.
How much longer do you think the PCP is going to last?
Well, I see no reason why it can't continue indefinitely
in its current state.
It'll end when I'm dead and buried
unless Ben decides to continue it alone.
If I would...
I would hope I wouldn't have to continue it alone.
I probably would continue it alone if I had to.
I would just make it the Ben podcast.
That's why I live, that's why I stay alive.
To prevent that.
This is my one reason.
Yeah, I mean, that's my answer.
I'm not stopping.
Why would I stop?
Yes.
You can't fucking stop me.
I know you all want to.
You're all just listening to the day where I finally give up,
but it's not happening.
Next voice...
I've got to pay spin.
Let me just try and...
Have you considered changing the episode release frequency?
It feels like you're struggling to come up with stuff to talk about every week.
Yeah, I've considered it,
but we still talk for two hours a week.
We're not that thin.
People complain about mere two-hour podcasts.
They want the four hours, they want the five hours.
It's not that easy to do all the time.
I think it's just like...
It's been a run of a few weeks of us not having much to talk about,
mostly because, for me, on my side,
is that I'm hard working on a single thing that I can't talk about.
So much of my time is devoted to that.
It's the same for me.
Yeah, I think I am in a bit of a spell where I'm not doing very much other than that.
And yet, we still talk for hours a week about it.
I think that if...
I have thought about it, like, in theory,
it's like, hmm, is there really that much to talk about?
Do we really have to do it for every week?
But in practice, I think if we did it bi-weekly,
I think there would just be less podcast.
I don't think we would get...
I don't think it would be more densely populated with, I don't know, ideas or whatever.
I think there would just be less of it.
So, I mean, you know, if that's what you want, is that what you want?
You sick fuck?
Yeah, I don't know.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Next one is an image.
What do we got?
Okay.
Gipcore.
And I'm looking.
We got Batman and Pyraman.
We got Berserk.
We got the red and blue Pokemon Manga, I assume.
Is that... that's what that is?
I'm not sure which...
The one piece?
I'm not sure which one that is.
The Pokemon Adventure...
Pokemon Adventures Manga,
which I've talked about loving before.
I think that's what that is.
That's different.
The one that I read was the one that's like Pikachu Boogaloo?
No.
This is a different one.
The one that I had was the one with the really monstrous Pokemon, which is awesome.
Yeah, this one came out with the game before the anime, before Ash Ketchum or anything.
So, the character's name is red.
Is this the one?
His rival is blue.
Is there a Clefairy?
Sure, in Pokemon.
Okay, I feel like there was an early Manga.
Because Clefairy was going to be the starter at some point in development,
and then they changed it to Pikachu.
And I think I read that there was some early Manga
that still has a prominent Clefairy.
I don't know about that, maybe.
The one I read was like his main boy was Poliwirl,
and he got a Pikachu at some point.
Yeah, I think that is the one I'm thinking of.
Okay, so yeah, I think it is.
Yeah, I understand.
We got One Piece, we got Vriska from Homestuck.
Not Homestuck, just Vriska.
Just Vriska.
We got Dark Cloud, we got Scott Pilgrim, and we got Adventure Time.
And I would like to say that this is exactly right.
This is all a gift core.
I have not made this image.
Somebody just remembers things I have said I liked and put them in a thing.
True, absolutely true, very true indeed.
Good job.
I love all of this.
You know, Bayman and Pyraman?
I don't even remember you ever talking about those guys.
I know who they are.
I think I may have talked about it because I got into,
I rewatched it sort of recently.
It's like a little animated show on YouTube with Batman and Pyraman.
And they're just sort of like, well, what are we going to do, Batman?
I come over to the house with best friends.
It's like silly.
They befriend a pumpkin.
And it's just a pumpkin, but it actually is a person.
It's turned into a whole lot of Adventure Time-esque shenanigans that grow.
Like every stupid thing that happens in every episode stays as a thing that is canon to the world.
And then it sort of builds over at times to things that can exist in this world.
Portals that open up to different places or places that exist that they can go back to and things can come from.
It's great.
Go watch the entirety of Batman and Pyraman.
So on YouTube.
I didn't know that it had continuity.
Yeah, it's really good.
I wouldn't have put, I know you like Berserk.
I wouldn't have picked it as a give-core thing.
Well, it's my edgy side.
It's the, you know, I love Berserk.
Almost more than one piece, I think.
Fair.
Something, I mean, I've read the entirety of it.
And I will read any new parts drawn by the assistance of Kentaro Mura.
I wouldn't have picked Scott Pilgrim for you.
I don't remember you talking that much about Scott Pilgrim or Adventure Time for that matter.
I mean, maybe they guessed, but it's very true.
I love Scott Pilgrim.
I have the little black and white comic on my shelf.
I always wanted to get the physical books.
I never got them.
Maybe I should at some point when I have a nicer room to put books in.
Next one is called Just Jacking It.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben.
Have you ever, or I guess give two.
Have y'all ever tried semen retention?
No.
Next question.
What does that mean, just not coming?
Yeah, is that no, not?
It might be semen retention.
A way to, like, minimize ejaculation.
Okay, it is the practice of avoiding ejaculation.
So it's just no fat.
Or you can learn how to orgasm without ejaculating.
Oh.
Why?
That sounds awful.
I mean, there's less mess, I suppose, but that seems like a weird thing to do to your body.
I found an article on Healthline about semen retention, and it's like, okay, what are the purported benefits?
And then it gives a list of mental, physical, and spiritual benefits.
Thanks, healthline.com.
And then the very next one.
Is there any research to support this?
It's a complicated, multifaceted topic, and research is lacking.
Not having enough research doesn't mean all claims are false, though.
So, like, just because we don't know that it does any of these things doesn't mean that it necessarily doesn't give spiritual benefit.
It's not evidence of lack.
Yeah, yeah.
That's dumb.
Healthline.com, what the fuck?
Thanks, healthline.
Someone, you should be ashamed of yourself.
Next voicemail is called Hot Take.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, I got a hot, hot, hot take for you.
Go on.
It's bad to say the n-word.
Yeah, yeah, I probably shouldn't have said it that one time.
And all those other times also.
I'm sorry.
I'm being, oh, oh, so you, oh, what, you're going to cancel me?
Oh, oh, so now I'm being canceled?
Oh, what about my free speech?
I'm being censored.
I'm being censored by the woke mob.
What am I being?
Tucker, Tucker Carlson, please save me.
Please have me on your show.
Just because I'm white.
Just, they hate me just because I'm white.
And I said the n-word.
But just because I'm white, they don't like me anymore.
And that's racism.
I go around to the high school and I say to the children,
I'm okay.
I'm cool.
I'm on a podcast.
What are you doing?
I can't be canceled.
I can't be in the wrong because I got a podcast.
I got, I got a comic.
I got things.
The, the, I'm better than you at everything.
The, all I'm saying, all I'm saying is that this voicemail telling me
that it's bad to say the n-word just because I'm white is the real racism.
And some, and some, and something must be done.
We need a solution, a final solution for people like this.
No.
For people like this voicemail.
This antifa, this antifa, this antifa thug that sent me this voicemail,
that threatened my life implicitly with this voicemail.
I know that they would kill me in a second.
They would, they would, they would, they would, they would,
they would Rosenbaum my ass.
They would pull a knife on me and then pull a gun on me
and start killing me in the middle of the street.
Just because I showed up to a place of, to defend a place of business
with my legally acquired firearm.
And that's fucked up.
Okay.
I think we're mixing things.
Yes.
We're sorry.
We lost, we lost the plot.
Next voicemail is another fucking external link.
So let's go, let's go see it.
Okay.
It's called.
Asking the real questions.
Yes.
Three, two, one, go.
Everybody asks, how can you have a rad con without Conrad?
But nobody asks, how can you have a procrastinate or is podcast without Nate?
Oh, true.
True.
That's a real, that's a real dunk.
Did you know that procrastinators is actually Nate Bestman spelled backwards?
Think about it.
I will not.
And I will just assume you're correct.
Yeah.
I'd rather not.
It's better this way.
Next voicemail is called Infinite Jest and Orville the Duck.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
Two things.
One, Ben, you mentioned how reading Infinite Jest for you was an annoying experience
because I have to keep looking at the full notes.
I argued that the procrastinators podcast is the Infinite Jest of podcasts because
they're always mentioning some drama from 100 episodes back.
Yeah.
Or some episode from Golden Girls or something in the description or the comments.
And it's an active listening experience.
Exactly.
Give you a British.
I just found out about Orville the Duck.
And they were talking about puppets in the last episode.
What the fuck's up with Orville the Duck?
Orville.
Why does the duck have depression?
And why does the duck want to kill himself so much?
And why does it wear diapers?
It's a baby.
Why does the baby have depression?
It's like Gafford.
Why does Gafford read Mondays?
He doesn't have to walk.
Why does a baby wants to put a bullet in his head so fucking much?
It's a baby.
Why do people hate Orville so much?
What is it?
Are you familiar with Orville the Duck?
I think I have seen...
This is not Ring of Bell.
I've seen him before.
But I don't think it was on the internet.
It's like look at this fucked up duck.
Oh Keith Harris dead at 67.
Ventriloquist who gave the world Orville the Duck dies of cancer.
I guess he's a depressed baby duck.
He does have a big diaper.
Damn.
I bet he could fit a lot of doodoo in that diaper.
Just think about it.
Just think of all the possibilities.
That's a big ass diaper.
A lot of high capacity.
And it's doubly fucked because Keith Harris puts his hand up there.
Oh yeah.
All day.
Oh god.
You can't do that with an underage dummy.
They're not old enough to consent to be puppeted.
I've never heard of Orville the Duck as an English thing.
I thought it was something else.
I've heard the name.
But I've never seen him before.
So I don't know what the fuck is up with this.
Cuddles the monkey.
Bubbles?
Cuddles.
Let me google that.
Okay.
There's no images on Wikipedia.
Cuddles the monkey.
Okay.
It's the same dude, different character.
Was it Keith Harris?
Yeah.
I've never heard of Keith Harris.
Is he any relation to Kamala?
Yes.
Man.
Ventriloquist.
Ventriloquist is sort of strange.
It is strange.
That duck is so weird.
He's got like a huge head.
He's puffy cheeks.
Real dump.
Dumpass.
Real dump of a duck.
Real dump.
The dump truck baby ass.
Imagine twerking with an ass like that with a huge diaper.
Full of huge duck doo doo.
Just think about it.
I don't want to think about it.
Just keep thinking.
Picture it.
Imagine it.
Clear your mind of all thoughts.
All sensation.
Breathe in.
I can't.
There's the duck there.
Focus on your breathing.
And then if something, your mind is like a still, your mind is like a still pool of water.
If any thought disturbs it, take that thought and throw it away.
Pluck it out and throw it out of your mind.
Your mind is still.
Focus on your breathing.
Now, imagine Orville the duck's huge dump truck ass.
His diaper overflowing with liquid duck shit.
Just do it.
Do it.
We brought it back to slopp in the final inning.
Okay.
Meditation over.
Back to reality.
When I snap my fingers, you will come back to reality and stop imagining the duck.
But I can't.
Oh, but I didn't snap him.
I'm not going to snap him.
Oh no.
Fuck you.
It's just on loop.
You're trapped in the mind dungeon.
Next voicemail is called hang on. You gotta get back to the old speed pipe.
I just gotta put the thing on there. There we go. What? It's the Among Us twerk. Oh,
yes. That's the one. That's the one. Next voicemail is called, oh man, look at them go.
Woo. Next voicemail is called member grpj. You know? I do. Well, you know what?
I'll answer this. Okay, three, two, one, go. Do you both have green screens? Because if you
both have green screens, you guys could record an episode of grpj. A good reason to play
grpj. I'm sure a lot of people favorite ever PCP content.
You know, funny, I guess, yeah, two people with green screens could
do it, record themselves separately and then pretend they were in the same room.
Yeah. I actually did just randomly decide to rewatch or listen to in the background. The,
yeah, the Lisa grpj that I was on that we did at Radcon too.
There was a pretty good video. I guess the one thing that I spend most of the time,
I take every opportunity that I can to just gush about how much I love
the story. We tried breaking down the topics into like, we talk about the graphics, we talk
about the gameplay, we talk about the story, but I keep coming back to how much I love Brad
as a character and just the arc. And I can't, I just can't resist, I can't help myself, but just
keep going back to that well. I mean, it is really good. What a great game. That's a pretty good
video. That's a good, that's a good, that's a good video. Check that out on the Hippocrite channel
if you haven't seen it viewers. Yeah, check out all of my gaming reviewer backlog if you've never
heard of that somehow. Imagine being like someone who found the PCP in like 2020 and like has never
heard of Hippocrite. That, I mean, it's not that unlikely. There might be like super popular,
except for a few videos that got like, like hundreds of thousands of views, which is pretty epic.
Yeah. The old, I don't know, I feel like you'd have to, I feel like there's not that many like
new PCP heads. Might be a handful though. That's definitely a few. Yeah. Okay, next one. I think
this is the last one is NNN week zero. Three, two, one, go. Damn it. I'm sorry, everyone. I feel like
I let you all down. I thought I was free of temptation, but then Nate made an announcement
in the pod to use cord. And I was back in. Oh, no, no, no, no, yes, watch. No. It was so close.
I only had only had two days left. This is this is why this is why I have to carry the torch. You
couldn't, you couldn't, this is why you shouldn't end the podcast. This is why you were, this is why
you don't understand. This is why for almost a year, you pretended that the podcast wasn't
canceled. It was so that this guy wouldn't kill himself during No Nate November this month.
I did the ultimate No Nate November and canceled the podcast. Yeah, true. From now on. I was sticking
too hard to it. You were like, man, No Nate November has so many physical, mental, and
spiritual benefits. Why don't I, why don't I do this all year long? Hmm. It's the, it's the only way.
The only solution. The only way. No more podcasts. Pull that plug. Gotta shoot that bridge. Pull that
trigger. Yeah. You know, death is the ultimate No Nate November. When do you think about it?
No more. Never see Nate again. No more anything again. No more Nate.
Okay. That's all the voicemails. Yeah, that's it. We did it. Hooray. Hooray.
I will briefly mention that my secret project is I mentioned on Twitter weeks away, weeks away. So
maybe second or third week of December, it should be something I can say, hey, look at this.
Wow, really? I definitely want it. I definitely want it out before the end of the year. And I
think it's possible. I wish I could say that mine was that Phantom's Revenge was two weeks away,
but I just, yeah. I don't know how close you are, but you have been talking occasionally about like,
oh, it's going to take longer than I thought. Again. I always, it has felt like it's been almost
done for like eight months. So I don't know. Yeah. I mean, I might be wrong as well, but
hopefully not. Hopefully not. Fuck. And then I can finally pretend, stop pretending not to know
what it is. Yes. I have seen very little of it. So I'm, it's mostly theoretical in my mind. I've seen
a little bit. Yeah. But yeah, that's very hype. That's very exciting. I can't wait. Looking forward
to it. Send us a message at speakpipe.com slash PCB voicemail if you want to potentially get
a send to the voice grail or get thrown in voice jail depending on how well you perform.
And patron us. Give us money at patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Not for any reason, just because it's the right thing to do. Yes. Anything else?
Nope. I think that's it. And you know what? We, I'm in good time. I'm in good time to make it over
to cook my brussel sprouts. Yeah. That, that time to spare. Okay. See you next week, everybody.
Thanks for listening and stay out of trouble. Bye. Bye. You can stay in trouble. Don't worry about
them.