Take a deep breath. Come on, Ben. You can do this. You have the fortitude. You have the emotional stability to make it through another one of these solo Ben casts. You can do it, buddy. Okay, don't let him hear you cry.
Hello, it is me, the baby boy. I have a question for Ben Saint. Will you abort me? I am only two years old. My brain is not fully developed. A chimpanzee can outthink me. Put me in a blender.
You know you need to. Put the baby in a blender. Put the baby in a blender.
All by my lonesome. In like a cool way. Gibb, well, you know, I guess she didn't say she was coming. I said PCP in 15 minutes and she said she it.
Which seems like confirmation to me. I waited for a while and we're pretty much, we're past the time, the starting time, so I'm going.
Anyway, that's the story. So how are you all doing? I'm doing okay. I feel okay this morning, this Sunday, January 23rd. I felt very angry yesterday. Well, I felt very annoyed yesterday and the day before.
I had an annoyed weekend, but whatever. I'm good now and it's time and I'm going to get back into, all right, this brings me, so what I'm going to do now that I'm feeling rational again.
Oh my God, Gibb. I was just about to launch into the first of my topics, but what's up?
I'm sorry, I don't know what happened. I was like, oh shit, PCP in 15 minutes. My mind wandered. I don't even know what happened. I find myself looking at a video of an orangutan driving a golf cart and I look over and I'm like, wait, oh shit.
The procrastinators podcast is recording.
You know what? That it could happen to anybody. Tail as old as time.
It's a good video.
I'm sure it was he flanged? Was he flanged?
I don't think he's flanged. I think he's big. He's a big boy, big fat boy.
What good is it?
An orangutan is nothing if he don't have a flange orangy hold that flange.
New theme song? Okay. No, maybe. I don't know. Vote in the comments.
I don't even know what happened. I just got out in the shower when it was like PCP in 15. I was like, oh shit.
I guess I looked at videos for a while.
I guess you did. It's okay.
Oh, my brain's so small.
Uh-oh, COVID brain fog.
No, no, I need that COVID. I need that COVID to speed up my neurons, to shrink my brain.
Yeah, your brain's too big. You're saying you're in desperate need of some shrinkage.
To this day, I have not gotten COVID. It's my one floor.
You're living in the past. We're living in a post-COVID, efficient brain world.
You're in that old big brain modality.
It's true.
You know, when things shrink and wither up, like a prune, they get wrinklier. Your brain gets wrinklier too.
Your brain is the same.
Uh, sure.
Obviously.
Um, yeah.
Other than that, how's your week? How was your week this week?
Uh, my week is good. I think, yes, it is good.
I purchased envelopes and boxes.
I also purchased envelopes.
Yes, I have everything with me.
Um, I can't remember where I was, what state things were at.
I think I had the stuff last week, but I'm ready to ship it in the next few days.
Yeah.
I'm ready to ship a bunch of the stuff.
So, you're going to ship the book, the pen, the red man, side zine, and the plush also?
Um, or the plush later.
Plush later. I still need to, to like make, I have fabric.
I just need to make the little Lord of Ghost costumes.
Right, right.
So those will take a little longer, but hey.
Yeah.
Make sense to me.
Yeah, I'm going to, I'm going to get like the, the labels sent to me and I'm going to stick them on.
I'm going to fucking, they're going to be posted.
A bunch of them, not all of them, but a bunch of them.
No.
That's great.
No fucking way.
Uh, cool.
Uh, I can, again, I cannot wait to have mine.
Um, I, um, I should really, okay, I always meant to do this and I, and I guess I still could and I probably still should.
There's no reason.
I never showed off my copy of the, of the Kato anthology.
I never like tweeted with a picture of the Kato anthology.
I think, or did, or did I, I don't think I did.
Um, and, and same with, um, yeah, the Kato anthology.
I have that and I never showed it.
Um, and also, uh, the latest, uh, villain verse cheeses, the last, the last villain verse chapter that he, you know, uh, published.
Uh, I have that and I never showed that off.
And the most recent addition to thing that I got that I should show off and I haven't is, um, I got a, I haven't opened, even opened it yet, but I got like card and like some pins.
A Tyler from Animorph in Time made some, like exclusive Animorph in Time pins that, uh, were just for, for people that guessed it on the show, uh, which is pretty cool.
So I have that in a package here.
I haven't even seen it yet, but I've, I've seen what they look like.
They look really good.
They look like the Animorphs logo.
They're shiny gold.
Uh, like, I want to show those off.
Uh, and I will put, I'll be sure to put your Lord of Ghost stuff on the pile of things that I mean to show off and never do.
You should, you should do your, you should do like a, an unboxing video.
Make a series of it.
Look, look what I got on my, my gamer wall on my, on my things that you see and are impressed by.
I love the gamer wall.
I love, I put anything, I, anything I like, I put on the gamer wall.
Um, I, uh, uh, oh shit, I was going to say something.
Oh yeah.
I, I also, I got envelopes or I ordered envelopes because I'm out of the right size envelopes for the, the plebe and we blue rays.
I think I sold like 80 of them or 70 something of them and I ran out of envelopes.
So I had to, I have like, I think I have, so I went, I went to the post office, but I got there like too late because they, for the international shipping, they gave me, like I had to, even though I had the address on the envelopes, they gave me slips that I had to, for each international one, I had to fill out all the address info again.
Uh, and that took me a while.
And then by the time I got back in line, it was late enough that the guy was like, it took them for, it takes them forever.
I have to like enter all the fucking information by hand.
Like I had to write the shit on the envelope.
Then I had to copy the shit onto a slip.
Then I had to show them the slip and they had to manually enter the address info.
Like why, why do I, why do I not just show them, why not just show them the envelope?
I don't know, whatever.
Uh, so it got so late in the day that they were like, I can't do anymore today.
We've got, I've got to finish up taking people in the line.
So I, I, I didn't get to send all of the international ones.
So I have like, and then I got a few more new orders.
So I think I have like 20 here that I still have to send out.
Um, and I, and then there's like 10 more that don't have an envelope because I ran out and I need to, those are in the mail.
I ordered them from envelopes.com.
It'd be a beautiful service.
I can't recommend envelopes.com enough.
Uh, and they've, they've started arriving.
Uh, Roro Chan showed, tweeted a picture of one plebe and wee blu-ray in the wild,
uh, sitting in his slime light with his monster energy cans.
Uh, it looks great.
Uh, that's very exciting.
I hope I see a lot more of those.
It's cool that it exists.
I kind of imagine like watching it though, at this point.
You know, you know, uh, I, I kind of agree, but I actually disagree about, uh, um,
well, there's two things that I think make the plebe and the weeb stuff that people would actually, would, would actually want.
I think the Radcon, the documentary, like, I don't think that was like published anywhere.
Right?
No, I don't remember.
I don't think I've ever seen like the final cut of that.
I think it was Victor filming it.
I was like, I don't want to say the...
I think he, I think it was only, um, uh, it was, it was only shown to backers in like a Google Drive folder,
and it was, and it was gonna be on the Blu-rays, but then, you know, the Blu-rays were never made.
But it's on, it's on the Vs, because Tectonic Improv shared the bonus, uh, content with me.
So, uh, Radcon 2, it's, it's just called Radcon the documentary, but it's about Radcon 2, and it's like, it's like a 45 minute,
like, interviews, and like, behind the scenes stuff, and like, it's really well shot and edited and stuff.
Uh, I think Victor edited it, too.
Yeah.
And it's good, like, it's cool.
It's real.
Like, the, like, the procrastinators was like something worth filming properly.
Uh, things looked different back then.
It's, it, yeah, I remember it being like, oh, this is like the beginning of a, of an amazing something or other.
I don't know what it is.
Right.
It's like, oh, collaborative creative minds.
Yeah, it was.
I mean, we went on to have two very successful Radcons after that.
Well, Radcon 4 is not technically successful yet, but, um, it is, it is slowly.
I mean, yeah, it was like good at the time.
It was just sort of like.
Yeah.
I know it.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
At least I'm still creative.
That's true.
I'm still smart.
True.
Um, oh, you're still, you're still smart.
You're still smart, little creative type, aren't you?
No, don't, it does weird when you say it to me.
Creating a little content for the internet, aren't you?
Oh, look at her.
Post a little tweet.
Yeah, I'm posting, I'm posting my fucking comic to people.
True.
Uh, um, what else is it going to say?
And of course, you know, the thing, the thing that no imitator can possibly, uh, uh, duplicate.
Of course, the most, the choices and most exclusive of the bonus content is, of course,
the message from Ben St.
Uh, uh, available only on Ben St's plebe and weeb, blue rays, uh, except, except no imitations.
The message, and of course the, uh, the box art and stuff.
There's a, there's a, the, the, the message from Ben St is on there.
That's the watermark.
It's just the seal of quality.
So you know.
It's Ben St in, in the, uh, in the, in the, what is that thing called?
Like the lion that roars before a movie.
Oh, the MGM.
MGM, but like it's you going rare or something.
I'm vaping and.
I haven't, I haven't vaped in a while, but it's still funny.
It's, it's integral to your brand, to your, to your, uh, for it.
And I felt when I stopped, when I realized that I had not vaped in a long, long time,
I was like, Oh no, my, my brand.
Um, it's okay.
You don't even have the pink hair anymore.
What happened?
I don't have the pink hair anymore.
I don't have the pink hair and I lost my pronouns.
So like, what am I?
Nothing.
The fur to Ben so easily forgotten.
Yeah.
Um, and, um,
I was going to say, did you?
Okay.
Did you see before we move on from the, that's all I have really have to say about the blue
was except buy one, uh, uh, Twitter DM me or discord DM me, uh, info down below, uh,
buy more blue rays.
Um, um, uh, wait.
Oh shit.
Oh no.
Oh, I should set up a storefront.
Okay.
I should really set up like an actual storefront.
There's probably people who would buy one, but they're just a little bit like uneasy with
the idea of just like sending money through PayPal and then like just like, you know,
there's probably people who that is like an ask.
So I should set up some kind of storefront.
I don't really know how to do it.
Um, there's got to be a service for that.
Right.
There's got to be some website that you can just create buttons.
Uh, a service.
I guess I'm trying to think.
It's surely it would be quite easy to just set up like a PayPal button on your own website.
Um, some sort of a thing like that because you already have a website.
I guess it's not about Trixie blue rays, but there probably is a way.
I think you can create like a custom invoice.
Maybe there's a way to like create a, maybe there's a way to make a button that has like
a pre-assigned amount.
Uh, people sell things on there.
Like making websites for like business is like a huge thing.
I'm sure of course there are tutorials for all that.
Uh, yeah, I just thought I could make like an Etsy account.
I could sell, I could sell my shit through Etsy.
I don't know.
It seems like that's what most people do that like have stuff that they made that they're
selling themselves.
I'd like to cut out the middleman, but whatever.
Uh, this is Ben St. from the future from about 10, about 10 hours into the future, 12 hours
into the future when I recorded this.
I just, I just went ahead and did that.
I made the storefront.
Uh, you can buy the Pleven that We Blue Rays and Road to Radcon, the book on there right now.
Uh, it is stcomics.com slash store.html.
Um, it was, um, seems like something I probably should have done before.
It wasn't even that hard.
Actually, I just, I looked into, I had looked for how to like make a buy something button
on PayPal before and I just hadn't found it.
This time I looked again and it was just right there.
I was like, oh, okay.
So it wasn't even hard.
Uh, yes, stcomics.com slash store.store.html.
Link in the description if you need it, I guess.
Uh, for, right, Pleven with Blue Rays and Road to Radcon.
And I will, I might add other stuff to there in the future, but, but for now that's what's there.
Uh, uh, yeah.
Okay, back to the, back to the podcast.
Um, but before we move on from the topic of the Blue Rays.
Did you see that, did you see that Trixie says she's, she's making them?
Uh, no.
I saw you talking about a video she made.
I haven't seen it.
Well, you know, I'm, I'm, I, I envy you.
I envy you.
Yeah, there was a, there was a video, uh, which really annoyed me for many reasons.
One notable thing in it that stuck out is that she does offhandedly mention that she's,
that she's, that she's, all of a sudden she's making the Blue Rays.
And then in the chat, she said, like, yes, I'm making the Blue Rays.
I'm burning them right now.
Very weird.
Very weird thing to do.
Like, I'm burning them right now.
Like, like she had a Blue Ray burner or she hardly purchased one.
Well, I mean, she told Dis send her a Blue Ray burner, which we never found out what happened to.
Yeah.
Um, I, but like, if she did, if she didn't have like the Blue Ray discs, or maybe she did.
She had, um, well in the, you know, I was, in the, like Kickstarter update video, she did show a box of Blue Ray cases.
And I'm not sure if they had discs in them, but that was like, that was like six years ago, or five years ago.
So like, I'd be shocked if she still had those.
Yeah.
That she would have got rid of them when she sold like all of her stuff.
In that yard sale.
So it's like, if she had the materials there the whole time, like she's telling the truth that she's burning them.
Yeah.
And she had the materials there, then that's like terrible.
It's very weird.
I mean, I mean, it's terrible no matter what.
It sucks no matter what.
It's terrible no matter what.
It's like, I don't know.
It's very, I was very like, what?
To see that like, first of all, why?
Like, why, what's even the point?
Like, what's even the point now that I have literally fulfilled the demand?
Like, what is the point of being like, Oh, well now I'll do it.
Like, do you, like, do you think it makes you look better or something?
Of course not.
All right.
I don't get it.
What I want to think of is that there was supposed to be like commentary tracks that she would do.
Commentary tracks.
I remember looking at like the original Kickstarter and be like, Oh, there'll be commentary from Jesse and myself and all that about like the plebe and the weeb.
And I don't know whether those exist.
I don't know whether she ever recorded them.
That would be the only thing.
Wait, like commentary tracks for the episodes?
Yeah.
Hmm.
Oh, okay.
I don't even remember any mention of those, but maybe.
I think they were on that.
Imagine her trying to record that with like Bird.
Imagine what that would be like to listen to.
Like trying to go back and make that happen.
Bird would have no interest whatsoever.
No.
Of course not.
I don't know.
Yeah, maybe.
But just, I was very baffled.
I was very baffled to see her say that.
And I thought about it.
And I think, in my opinion, the most likely scenario, and there was a time when I wouldn't have thought this, but like, remember the RV, like she just she just told a bunch of lies about the RV about like having it and like going to get it and stuff.
Totally going to do it.
So I think the most like scenario is that she's just lying.
She's not actually doing it.
She's just saying she is.
Yeah.
If she, if on the off chance she is doing it, I can't wait.
I actually hope she is because it would be really funny to compare mine against hers because mine will obviously be better because like I put, I put actual effort into them and they made them look nice.
And hers are going to be hers are going to be.
Yeah, it's they won't have a label printed on the on the disc.
They might not even have like, like a case art or anything.
If they do, they'll have like, like mint, mint salad shit.
Imagine, imagine having like mint salad art on the cover of your plebeian wee blu-ray.
It would be if they if two exist, it would be pretty funny to have one of each if you were a backer to have one of each.
Jess in my server said that if Trixie makes them, she is going to do a side by side like review and comparison of the two versions, which would be really a treat.
So, yeah, so that's the so that was up with that monitoring the situation very carefully.
That video was really irritating.
For one, because it's like it's it's yet another video where she just sits there and explains her whole life story and expects you to come away with it like, oh, I get it.
I do like I do like void gazers now. Oh, I like I like the direction of the channel now.
Like that explains everything.
Yeah, this clears up all my misconceptions about thinking that the channel sucks.
No, it's good, actually, for some reason.
She sits there and explains that she tells she tells a bunch of like outright lies in it.
Like she she she doubles down on the on the story that like Digibro was just a character she was playing.
Not not true. Simply false.
I know I lived with her. I know there was no there was no like, I mean, I mean, it's ridiculous on the face of it.
Like it's obvious if you think about it for even a second that it was not a character.
She like recorded herself saying off the cuff stuff she talked about her real opinions.
Obviously, it's not a character.
I don't know how you can even say that, but she really does.
She really says it and expects people to believe it.
I mean, it's it's weird because like even if it was a character, the character did bad things and stole money from people by not doing stuff that the character said they would do.
That's a shitty character.
And if you like money, it's like, I don't know, but it's not a character. It's just not it's just it just never was it.
And like if you if you if you were even paying attention, it should be obvious to you.
And yet and yet and yet the comments are all like fawning.
The comments are all like, oh, you've grown so much.
Oh, I'm so happy you made this video.
Oh, like I like I love to see whatever this is.
Like, oh, I support you so much.
Like you're right.
Oh, OK, OK.
The thing the thing that like the thesis of the video is like, you know, my new content is because I'm happy now.
And people only don't like my new they only want my old style of content because I was miserable.
They all want me to be miserable so they can relate to me.
It's like a weird like cope like humble brag like you're like you the audience are just miserable and you just want me to be miserable like you.
So you can relate to me, but I'm happy now.
So if you don't like my new style of content, it just means you're like abusive and you hate me and you want me to suffer.
And that's fucked up.
I don't know.
Just just really annoying to hear.
I mean, like a deranged person say this stuff and like more deranged people in the comments be like, yes.
It's the same old shit.
It is the same.
I felt like it was like, oh, shit, the new Trixie video, people talking about it.
And maybe saying it was like that sounds like everything she does.
There's no reason.
It's so like whatever.
It's weird.
It's just it's it's weird to have people being so emphatic about like how like important it was to them to hear this in the comments.
But like if they'd been paying attention at all, if they were invested at all, they would have heard it already because she said it over and over and over again.
Like they simply must not care.
And yet they're there in the comments to be like, I just shaking and crying, shaking and crying, listening, listening to you say that Ben St.
Ben St. is a holy warrior defending the people from all from me who who stole their money and didn't deliver on stuff.
Direct quote.
Direct quote from that clip.
That was great.
It was weird out of context.
It seems like she wasn't even saying it as a bad thing about you.
Um, I mean, it's funny.
She said she says it in a way that like it's supposed to be like derisive.
Like, huh, they're acting like he's they're acting like he's like some kind of holy warrior.
They're acting like he's like doing something good just because he's, you know, protecting people from the fact that I stole money from them.
She says it like dismissively, but then doesn't doesn't elaborate on like why that's not true.
There's no like there's no like, but there's no but after it.
It's that parasocial relationship thing.
Yeah.
It's always been that like they they view.
I mean, whether or not like people believe the character, they view internet people.
Everybody does to a certain extent.
If you don't know a person and you watch their content, you see them as like an internet character and the internet is the show you're watching.
And drama they have is like like is drama for a TV show.
And it's like, whoa, interesting.
And a character that has like hit rock bottom.
And it's like says, I've learned from my mistakes.
Oh, cool.
Yeah.
They're getting their redemption arc.
People love redemption.
And they forget that it's a real person and they may never actually do anything good.
They just like the idea of it.
And they see it in themselves like, well, if this character of this TV show called the internet can have a bad moment and get out of it and feel happy, then maybe I can do that as well.
Oh, Digi, you're so smart and I love you and here's money.
Yeah.
It's embarrassing.
I'm Jen.
I feel sorry.
I feel sorry for people in the comments like falling for it.
Like I know more than them and I know that they're like just wrong and being duped.
Okay, whatever.
Oh wait, I was going to say one more thing about that.
Oh, oh, she says, she says that like when she's in the part that she's talking about me.
She says that she doesn't know like why I don't like her.
She says that like, okay, there was the Brony lecture and Ben was mad that I didn't release the Brony lecture.
And then, and then she gets like confused and then she's like, I don't know.
I don't know what happened.
I don't know why it went from Ben being mad about the Brony lecture to whatever she said.
However, I forget how she describes the current situation, but like she says, she doesn't know how it progressed.
And like she has to be lying because like she must remember.
I mean, there's more, there's more stuff that she probably doesn't remember or doesn't understand what she did wrong.
I could imagine that like she has to remember at least the argument in the PCP where she had a fucking freak out and rage quit because I said that like Yig is bad and Riley is bad.
So she has to know.
I could imagine it's it's like if somebody is attacking her and she defends herself.
Right.
Then that was her being correct because she was defending herself.
Sure.
And it doesn't matter how she does that defending or what she does in the defense of herself because she's always right.
And then, you know, like she doesn't understand why Ben St would say all these mean things and force her to leave the PCP.
Yeah.
She didn't do anything.
She was just being the best person ever.
It was the only way it was there.
Sure.
Her hand was forced.
I just I just thought it was strange for her to claim that she doesn't know like she definitely knows she she probably doesn't understand everything.
Like she probably doesn't understand why getting why defending why defending may saying that George Floyd deserved it by DMing me to tell me that I'm just jealous.
That's that Trixie gets pussy.
She probably doesn't understand why that's a bad thing to do and why that would make someone not like her.
What was the other one?
She might not understand that like telling the backers that like just because you paid me money for a thing doesn't mean I owe you that thing.
She might not understand that that was bad and would make someone not like her, but she must know even if she doesn't know why I did it.
She must remember the argument about Yig that made her leave the PCP.
So for her to claim like complete ignorance is it can't be true.
It's not true.
I kind of forget like what happened in that argument.
Sure.
Well, I was like if the thing was like you said Yig was bad, but for her Yig is good.
Yes.
And so she doesn't understand why you think it's bad.
And then she said she doesn't she said she said like Ben, you're just being you're being negative.
You know, you're hating.
I don't remember I'm paraphrasing, but it was basically like Ben, you're hating Ben.
I you can't talk about you can't talk about me that way.
You can't talk about Yig that way.
You can't talk about Riley that way.
Riley gives me big money connections.
Riley's given me big money connections.
Big money connections that you'll never have anymore because now you're not my friend and I'm quitting the podcast.
And that was literally it.
That was literally like like like it.
So anyway, my point is just that when she says she doesn't know it's a lie and and that's that's the kind of thing that that that the new like I hate Digiber video is filled with.
It's like just things that I know aren't true and it makes me really mad to hear someone say them and and people believe it, you know, really bugs me.
But so that's really that really bothered me.
The the Blu-ray situation.
Continue only continues to get funnier.
However, by by Blu-rays, I'm almost sold out of my second batch.
I have like 10.
No, I think I have nine that are unsold right now.
If more than nine people buy one, I mean, I can simply like buy more discs and produce some more.
It's not like I'm not going to run out and be like, oh, no more.
Can't sell anymore.
Like I can.
I have the equipment.
But it would be cool to be funny to sell out of a second a second batch.
I love money.
Yeah.
Let's see.
I guess.
I guess I guess that's all I have to say about the Blu-rays and also about the the the the Digiber video.
I mean, there's more I could say that was like weird about that.
But yeah, whatever.
I mean, personally, I agree.
It's just sort of like annoying to think about her and anything she's doing.
Sure.
So I just ignore it as much as I can.
I know what she talks about me.
When someone talks about me, I have to be like, oh, sure.
Sure.
But like, I know what she would say if she talked about me and she doesn't have anything to say.
She just doesn't like me because of you.
That's true.
That's literally what she said.
She said she doesn't.
I'm paraphrasing again, but it was literally like, give a bad because give on podcast with Ben and Ben bad.
And that's literally the reason.
Yeah.
And then she doesn't say that about Tom.
She doesn't know that Tom is still on the PCP and she didn't even.
Oh, and she was talking about like members of the PCP that she had wanted to work with and that she worked well with.
And she says Nate and Jess and she doesn't mention Tom and she doesn't mention I am games at all.
It's very weird.
Yeah.
She likes people who can give her things.
And she doesn't like people who can't or don't want to give her free shit.
That's OK.
That's the that was the other thing I'll touch on it.
Yeah.
That was the other thing is the way that she does the way that she describes people.
It's her new friends in the video.
It's very much like she talks about how, you know, may she liked may because she could just basically groom may into a second version of herself.
Honestly, it was creepy back then and it's creepy to hear her talk about it now.
And then she talks.
Yeah.
She talks about Mint and Riley and she basically says, I like Riley because Riley is my servant.
Riley shows up and says, like, I will do things for you.
I will I will do work for you.
I will I will be your quote unquote producer.
And she's like, yeah, so he's my good friend and Mint draws stuff for me for free and I don't have to pay her.
So she's so she's a good friend.
And it's and she talks about how like she wants what she wants in life.
Her dream is just to live in a truck and go around with with friends and collaborate with people and work on projects.
And then like when she talks about those people, the impression I get is that like really just what she wants is she wants a bunch of yes men around her that will tell her she's great and will do her work for her.
She wants Riley to make her big money connections or whatever, set up gigs or whatever for her.
And she wants Mint to draw stuff for her and and and and whatever other shit she can get.
She wants Asher to edit videos for free for her, you know, dot dot dot.
I'm extrapolating, you know, the list goes on.
She just wants whatever people will give her.
I mean, what does she want to give to other people?
Is there anything that's an excellent question?
She never talks about that.
She never she never talked about like what she could like when she was with May, she never talked about like what she could do for May or like how what May wanted.
It was all about like what do I want?
What am I doing to May to make her do what I want?
And this is and with Bird.
I mean, she barely even talks about Bird.
She I don't think she even mentions Bird in the video, but like she doesn't talk.
She, you know, in the same when she has, she just talks about, oh, he likes me.
He makes me feel good, which I mean, I guess it's fine.
If your partner makes you feel good or whatever.
The point is that it's just a pattern.
It's never about like, it's never about what am I doing for them or like, what are they even like?
It's just about what do they give me always, always has been.
She compares, she compares me to Mint and she says, you know, Mint draws faster and Mint draws stuff for me.
Ben draw slow and I had to pay Ben to draw something for me.
So Ben bad mint good.
Like that's like that's directly what she says is a direct comparison.
She talks about when she wanted me to draw her banner and her icons and I didn't do it for a few months.
And then she had to pay me for it.
And she says and like that annoyed her, I guess.
I don't know.
She doesn't mention that she didn't pay me.
She does not meant she neglects to mention that she did not pay me in advance.
She didn't pay me until after I had given it to her.
So like, I don't know what the complaint is there, but you're right.
Mint draws me for free.
Ben, not do that.
Ben bad.
Ben bad man.
Mint good.
Like everybody acts selfishly most of the time.
Like you do things like I'm trying to make my life the best I can.
But like the disconnect of like expecting people to do things for her without thinking that they would want something in return.
Right.
Like an exchange for a skill and a craft of someone else and money is like a pretty normal thing.
Yeah.
It doesn't make someone like a good friend.
It's just such a weird mixing of like like.
It's really weird.
I like it when people do things for free for me.
Sure.
Of course.
But I wouldn't expect it of a person and I wouldn't think badly of someone if they ask for money because that's normal.
The way it's just the way she talks about people is very, it's very, it's very creepy.
It's creepy.
I don't know what else to say about it.
Okay.
And with that, I with that, I think I actually have exhausted anything I might have wanted to say about that.
What about what else I have on my list here?
Yeah.
You got anything?
You got any topics?
I don't know.
Aside from getting the things ready to ship, I've mostly been working on the secret project and that's cool.
Yeah.
But I don't want to talk too much about that.
Sure.
I'll announce it when I'm ready to.
Other than that, I've been watching Game of Thrones still.
I'm up to the end.
I just finished season six.
So, okay.
So, yeah, you're past where I ever made it to, I think.
I've been looking at a lot of clips and a lot of reviews.
I rewatched Lindsay Ellis' Game of Thrones two-part review thing, which is, I remember, pretty extensive.
Yeah.
It gets to the root of what the actual problem of the show was.
And I was like, okay, yeah.
Yeah, all these people, all these things, there's bad stuff.
And I picked up on it in the show, like, hmm, bad stuff.
I see it.
I see the beginnings of bad stuff.
But I still think season six has got some really good stuff in it.
I feel like you could have easily turned that show into a perfect ending.
That's when it went off the books, right?
It was season six is when we're no longer in book territory at all.
Yeah, I could imagine they had season six wrap up a few plot threads and then start their own things ready for the ending of the show.
But the things they started were just sort of shit, and they sucked.
Oh, okay.
Darn.
So, you have one more season to go, right?
Two more.
They're like smaller seasons, but with longer episodes.
Season seven has seven episodes.
Season eight has six.
But each episode is like a feature length film.
Really?
Like 90 minutes?
It's something like, yeah, 90 minutes.
Wow.
Okay.
So they're big, but like comparatively less happens in them.
It's just sort of like, and then this stuff, the stuff that was been building up through the whole season, and we took care of it.
Oh, and we kill, and this person who was smart, now they're dumb, and they're dead.
Get rid of like most of the characters.
The ending of the show has like three people, and there were no new people introduced to replace the ones that died.
People just kept dying until there was no one left on screen.
And it was like, there's not much to work with when you get rid of everybody.
No.
It's not good.
But season six, I think is good.
It's a good one.
You could salvage season six onwards.
I heard the ending was bad.
I know vaguely how it ends, but you know how it ends, right?
Yes.
Well, obviously.
I've seen it before.
Wait, you've seen it before?
You've watched it through before?
Yeah, I watched it when it was coming out.
Oh, I didn't know it was a rewatch.
Didn't I explain it was a rewatch?
You probably did.
But I had COVID, and that was just one of the parts of my brain that had to go for the sake of efficiency.
I see.
I forgot.
All right.
I got you.
It's been getting me in a world building mood as well.
Yeah.
I'm looking at videos on how to design a world map for your fantasy world.
I'm like, oh, yeah.
Think about mountain ranges and elevation and the ocean currents and how that would
affect the temperature of the places and what would grow there.
And then if you know what grows there, what people, what would they eat and where would
they farm and who would they fight and this and that.
Think of all these things.
I'm like, yeah, I'll think of all those things.
Oh boy.
I still haven't drawn a shitty map, but I love maps right now.
I'm brilliant at maps.
Drawing a shitty map is the first step towards drawing a good map.
True.
I guess paraphrase Jake the dog.
He probably didn't come up with that, which is fine.
Have you seen the Game of Thrones full map?
Yeah.
It looks funny as an image because it's just like a upright rectangle next to a sideways
rectangle.
Yeah.
That's Westeros and Essos.
Well, it's England and Europe, right?
It's kind of just basically England is way bigger.
Because it's like more important.
Yeah.
They don't, the map doesn't, the map extends sort of into like an unknown area, right?
Like doesn't the land just sort of continue off the east side?
Yeah, up the north and like southeast is just sort of like not on the map, which is cool.
When I was looking into world building and maps, I was like, how do I draw it so that
it's the whole globe and it fits on like a projection of the globe, the Makata projection
or the whatever projection?
And there's like a lot of maps don't bother with that.
Yeah.
If you were to like take the Game of Thrones map and wrap it around a globe, it would look
weird because it's not full.
It's not like actually the whole planet, which I think is a better way to do it honestly
because people use maps and they don't know the entire planet unless they're like futuristic
or like present day.
Yeah.
If it's a fantasy like ancient times, they probably would not have cartographers that
have completely mapped out the entire world.
Yeah.
In like the time, in like the real world historical time, the Game of Thrones is like sort of
based on, yeah, they probably just wouldn't have maps beyond like the Balkans or whatever
mountain.
What's the mountain?
Is there a mountain range between like Europe and Russia?
Not Russia.
Well, there probably is.
Yeah.
I'm thinking of the Alps, which is like in the middle of Europe.
They probably just wouldn't have great maps.
It's been like, yeah, and then there's just like China is over there somewhere, you know.
I've seen like maps where like America was only just beginning to be understood.
Yeah.
And they would have like, oh, Europe and all that big Africa, huge.
And then on the left side, there'll be like a really thin sliver, which is South America
and another tiny little dot, which is like North America.
They didn't really understand how big it was or how far across it went.
That's awesome.
Yeah.
Well, why would they?
What?
It's so weird.
Because like they didn't they like they miss like they kind of miscalculated the like the
size of the globe.
Right.
Like they just like that's isn't that why like Columbus thought he could know he didn't
somebody thought they could get they could sail all the way across the ocean.
And it was because they had like miscalculated the size and they just thought it was like
a lot smaller.
I thought it was a smaller distance.
Yeah.
I don't know.
North America was in the way like North America was blocking the way, obviously, but even
if North America hadn't been there, like it still wouldn't have made it because they
just like it was like would have been just way farther.
I think.
Yeah.
I think the first the first one of the first guys to go West was like an Italian called
Americo.
Yeah.
Which America is like named after.
That's funny.
Good.
Good for him.
Proud of him.
And then Columbus called Columbia.
You know, you know, I can't believe the woke agenda.
They changed Americo to America.
They made it.
They put a girl's name in my continent.
Why do they have to woke a fire like that?
Fucking America X.
Yes.
I mean, no.
I mean, no, good old fashioned Americo.
Please.
I'm just going to start calling it the United States of America now because that's how it
returned to the return.
Yeah.
It's yet to Europa and America like this, the moon and the sun, the man and female, the
dragon of chaos, if the theory of the chaos feminine and the law order masculine, Jordan
Peterson.
I don't know anything about this bullshit.
I don't.
I've heard like once before and it's like a book and it was filled with insane like illustrations
and nonsense.
There's some really bizarre diagrams and like weird illusions to like young and archetypes
in a way that sounds like he's just describing like like a mythology dragons and shit.
I don't know.
Yeah.
So.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I remember chaos.
The dragon or a Boris chaos dragon.
Oh, that's all my my Yu-Gi-Oh my family Yu-Gi-Oh deck is a dragon or a Boris chaos dragon.
Play it.
It's got so many life points.
Oh, hell yeah.
You know, maybe this isn't Jordan Peterson.
Wait, no, this one is the dragon of chaos, the king of order.
It's just like it sounds like him.
Yeah.
Sounds like his his work.
Very funny.
Very.
It's very.
Yes.
Yeah.
The walled garden.
Descent and disintegration anomalous information.
You look at this and you're like, oh, okay.
Yeah.
I'm looking at it.
Sure.
So anomalous information comes from the chaos dragon into the walled garden.
Of course.
And I assume that's a good thing.
I think this is a stable system and it's fine actually.
This looks it looks balanced.
Yeah.
It looks it looks about right.
So I've been working on I have also been working on my project Phantom's Revenge.
I hit Phantom's Revenge.
I hit an unexpected snag with it this week.
I hit a really annoying roadblock that made me kind of throw up my hands and like leave
it for a while or for a few days.
And that was that I I tried to X.
Okay.
My plan was, you know, I had the game as an executable file and my plan was I'm going
to have it a downloadable executable on itch right itch.io and and then I was going to
have an HTML version that would be hosted on my website.
And it would also be I would put it I would put that I would also put that on itch and
I would also put it on new grounds because it would be nice if I could like, I don't
know, maybe hit the front page of new grounds or something that would be cool.
Tom did that with a zoomie and it seems to have worked out fine.
So but anyway, I went to first I was like, wait, there's no option to just create as
an HTML file.
Why?
And then I realized that like my license had expired, like my user license for GameMaker
Studio had expired.
And so it just took that option away from me.
It was like, it was like, okay.
So I had to renew my subscription, which didn't end up being that much.
I think they actually gave me like a free trial year or something.
So it didn't actually cost me much or anything.
So that was good.
But it took me a while to figure out that that was what I had to do.
So I did that and then I had it and then I, I exported it as an HTML to find that like
a bunch of shit is broken.
A bunch of shit just doesn't work in the HTML version, like a bunch of things that were
supposed to like fade in or fade out were instead like flashing.
There was a part, hold on, I'll show you, I'll show you this.
Look at this fucking GIF.
Hold on.
How do I, how do I, how do I get it?
Copy direct link.
No download GIF.
Look at this GIF of the, of the starting menu.
Yeah, this, this is what the opening menu looked like.
Like it's supposed to have like the titles not supposed to be flashing the cur, there's
like a weird little like spot appearing at the bottom next to the quit option.
And then the arrow icon is like this weird like spazzing out thing.
It's like cycling through a bunch of sprites for something.
Yeah.
It's cycling through a bunch of like similarly sized sprites and I have no fucking clue why
it would do that.
It's insane.
And, and even, and I tried to go in and I tried to like, okay, let me see if I can fix
it and I go in and I, this, this blows, this, this is like the worst thing ever.
Like I sound, I, I'm going to sound insane to myself saying this, but I went in and I,
I saw the, the, the object that, that defines this behavior and I changed some things to
try to make it work and it sort of worked.
Like it, it half fixed the problem.
It was displaying the correct sprite, but it was like at the wrong speed and I was like,
hmm, okay.
So then I reverted my changes.
I reverted them all back to exactly how it was before I started changing anything.
And then it worked and then it worked.
And then it worked normally.
So like, like you, like the same, the same export, same exact, well different export,
but with, with all my changes reverted.
So the code was exactly the same, but it just worked.
Yeah, I don't know.
So like this kind of thing was all over the HTML version.
Like, there were just things, like the reason why things are flashing, like the title was
because it like, it like understood alpha values, like, like opacity values.
It read the numbers differently in the executable version.
The number, like the number out, the, the, the opacity value varies from zero to one.
One is fully opaque.
And if you go above that, it just is like, okay, well, you can't go over one.
So it just one, but in the HTML version, if you go over one, if you do like 1.1, it's
like, well, that doesn't make any sense.
Let me just drop the, the integer and read it as a point one.
So you know, one 10th opacity.
So it was like interpreting that differently.
And there were other things were like, whereas in the one version, two things drawn on the
same layer, one would draw on top of the other in the HTML version, it would reverse
and like the other thing would draw on top.
So the game had all these weird little like quirks in it that I like, I don't know why
they're there, but I had to try and fix them.
And so I started working on it and I was making progress and I was like, okay, I can fix most
of these issues, but I kind of think that maybe it's not worth it.
Maybe it's not worth doing this right now.
I kind of think that, I think maybe my new plan is that I won't make the HTML version
right away.
I'll just take what I've got with the executable version that works and just release that
on itch.
Like instead of, instead of hosting the game on my website, I'll just have, when you get
to that part in the comic of slime and punishment, I'll just have a splash page that leads you
to the itch page that lets you download the game, right?
And then later, later I can make an HTML version.
And if I feel like it, I can update my website to be that, I can, I'll put it on, I eventually
want to have it on Newgrounds.
I want to see how it does there.
So I think I might just do that later, because like ...
So yeah, it's definitely the right thing to do is to get it out first.
Getting it out all, like it's like, it's a port.
If the code is read differently, there's going to be loads of things that you're going to
have to figure out what, how they're changed and why.
I don't know.
It's a whole like months long, many months of like tinkering.
Possibly.
I hope it doesn't take that long, but yeah, the executable version just works.
So I think I just got to do that, like whatever.
And then if, oh shit, I was going to say HTML executable.
Oh, I don't know, like, I hope that maybe a side effect of that might be that more people
might be inclined to like donate, because like, it prompts you to like donate something
to the creator when you download the file, not when you play an HTML version.
So I kind of think that maybe it's sort of has a side benefit as well of like, well now
people that want to play it will have to, you know, the way to play it is the downloadable
version.
One, it works better.
It will not have any glitches that were introduced with like the switch.
And two, you know, just get that little prompt, like do you want to donate something to this
creator?
I think a lot of people don't have a problem donating, would like, would donate, but just,
you know, they just need to be asked.
They just need to have the request made, and then they'll be like, yeah, sure, toss you
five bucks or whatever.
So maybe it will help me in that way as well.
So I think that's what I'm going to do.
Yeah.
But now I have to, I realized with a bit of like a sinking heart that now that the game
is like done, the game is like done, done, if I'm just going to release the executable
versions.
And now I have to actually do the thing where I go and I draw the end of slime and punishment.
And like, that's cool, I guess.
But I'm also like, that's actually going to be like, I hope how many little pages will
that be?
I don't know.
I hope it won't be too many.
I think it will probably be, I'm going to ballpark it, maybe like 20, 24 ish.
Some of them I want to like take care and make them look a bit, a bit, no, probably maybe
like 36 or something.
So that's, that's, that's not insubstantial thing, you know, I try to, I try to slime
and punishment.
I like I'm okay if the artwork is a little sloppy.
So like some of them, maybe it will, maybe it won't be that many.
I don't know.
I haven't, I haven't like blocked it out or anything.
So I'm really just guessing I will, I'm going to try to keep it as minimal as possible.
But there is like, there is a non insubstantial amount of story left to tell.
I mean, yeah, he, Phantom has to go to the place where the game happens.
And then there's the conclusion after the game, the, the aftermath of the game.
I added, I did something that I might regret, but I think I want to do it.
I made a change to the game and this affects like everything where I think I'm going to
make it.
Oh my God.
Phantom horn.
So girl.
I think I'm going to make it so that the website, because like you read slime and punishment
on my website, I think I'm going to make it so that the website does not let you read
the ending.
The only way to find the link to the ending is to beat the game and the game will give
you like the link at the end.
I think I'm going to do it.
That is, um, well, surely the link, if somebody just had the link, they could copy paste it
and give it some match.
Sure.
It could be, it could be worked around.
I remember when I did like the, the punk run away from snakes page of Balejape, that like
the idea is that you beat that little endless runner, get to the end and then you get the
next page and click on that.
Yeah.
But I realized that one, people might not want to play it all the way through like on
a second read and two, it was kind of hard to get working on the website and it was like
buggy and like, it was probably like a bad idea to like force people to, to play it.
So I had like, after a few seconds, a little bit of the text on the website says, you can
just go to the next page if you want.
Oh, because like, like if it's like, if it's like glitching or whatever.
If it's like glitching or it's too hard, it's just like, it's not that important to like
play that.
It's just fun.
Like the idea of it is fun.
Yeah.
I, that, I, you're right, like, I did, I did think about this and I might, I might still
change my mind.
But like, um, maybe for like the initial release, you can have it like that.
But first, there are some people, there will inevitably be some people who like, maybe
they, they, they're playing on a Mac or something and like the game doesn't work for them.
And like, that's, that's a bummer.
Yeah.
Stuff like that as well.
If the game just doesn't play.
Yeah.
Or it might just not, or that computer can't handle it.
That would be a really shitty computer.
Um, but yeah, like really, they just, uh, can't play games.
Maybe they don't have hands.
I mean, there's, I mean, the thing is, uh, I mean, the game is hard, like the game
is not easy.
So like, there's, there definitely will be people who just can't beat it.
Uh,
I'll try to beat it on stream.
I think that'll be fun and fail terribly.
It's actually, I made it, I made it so that, um, I mentioned last time there, there's a,
there's a bad ending.
Like if you're, if you're bad, if you're bad at the game, you can win, but it's the bad
ending.
So I made it so that like at the end, you see the, the victory screen and then you get
the option to, um, the way it is right now, it's like you get to read, you can replay,
like do another run, or you can go back to the main menu or the third option is like,
you know, continue the story, like read the rest of the comic and that will, that will
link you.
That will open up a webpage that links you to does the secret URL to the, the conclusion
Uh, so yeah, the other separate endings for good and bad.
Like if you play badly, you get a link to a shitty ending.
No, the way it is right now is that if you, if you get the bad ending, the continue the
story option is grayed out.
And if you try to select it, endless war pops up and he goes like, no, that's not canon.
Do it right this time.
I think that's pretty funny.
You need to get over 9,000 points.
I think, okay, I mean, here, here's the thing.
I think that then probably the number of people who have actually like red slime and punishment
is pretty low.
I think that that will be pretty low compared to the people who have, who might end up like
playing the game in an, in an optimistic scenario, the game might get a little bit of the game
might get seen around a little bit.
And so in that case, and most of those people probably don't care about the comic.
They might just be playing the game because it's a game.
And so I think it's like, like numbers wise in terms of like engagement audience retention,
I don't think it really matters that like, you don't get the real ending unless you beat
the game.
Uh, but I kind of think, I don't know, I want to just like punish my, my true fans.
I don't want to make them, I want to make them earn it.
I don't know.
It just feels, it feels valuable.
It feels valuable to me that like, no, you don't, you don't just get to see the ending.
You have to earn the ending.
You have to take, you have to be phantom and you have to, as phantom, you must, you know,
best this, this deadly gauntlet and only then can do you and phantom together as one earn
the, the, the catharsis that comes of the conclusion.
I can see myself, I can see myself like playing phantom's revenge, trying to like it and being
like, I hate this, this sucks so much.
I hate this game.
It's a piece of shit.
I'd rage and it'd be like uncomfortable.
It wouldn't even be funny.
Yeah.
And then I'd eventually maybe beat it and I'll be like, I get the bad ending or something.
Here's, here's the thing.
Here's, here's what I, I'll scream really loudly.
Here's what I hope would happen because the game is solvable.
There is a strategy that if you employ, if you employ, you can, you can just win.
And if you know that strategy, it's merely a matter, if you, if you figure it out, it's
merely just a matter of executing it.
So I mean, you could just, somebody could just like tell you, like two or more people
could just commiserate on like, oh, I can't figure out how to do it.
And the other person was like, oh, well you just, you just got to do this.
Like, oh, in, in this room, you know, the optimal strategy is, is this.
You gotta do the backwards long jump.
Yeah.
Or somebody, or somebody might just like write up a guide or something.
So like if, if people were like, if people were like frustrated by the game, I would
hope that that would maybe lead for some people to be like, okay, well here's how you beat
it.
And maybe, I don't know, I think maybe it would get people talking about it a little
bit more.
Maybe it would lead to some greater engagement.
These people are like, wow, there's this game that I can't beat.
This game seems cool.
It looks good.
It's kind of fun.
It's kind of funny.
But I can't beat it.
What the fuck?
Yeah.
So I think that's what I got to do.
And if people, and if people really want to see the ending and they want to be, and they
want to, and they want to cheat and not beat the game, well, they can, they can just, they
can just do that on their own time.
They're, they're, as Tim Rogers might say, under no circumstances are they allowed to
tell me that they did that.
Uh, yeah.
So, uh, anyway, that's what I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, I'm just looking forward to it.
I wish it were out.
I kind of expected it to be out already.
I have, I worked on it for a lot of January.
I sort of expected it to not be being worked on anymore.
I kind of expected to be well underway drawing the pages by now, and I'm not, uh, but I will
have to get started on that soon and I don't know.
We'll see.
Um, shouldn't, it shouldn't be that long.
Climate punishment used to, I used to bang out like four or eight panels in a day, some,
not every day, but some days.
So like maybe if I really banged it out, I could do, I could draw it all in a week.
Maybe that's not a guarantee.
It might take long.
It might take longer because I might want to be a little more fussy about the, uh, you
know, the ending, want to make it look, want to make it look good.
Don't want, don't want it to be sloppy.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
Um, but the ending I have been, I think the ending, I don't know.
It's hard when I think about the ending, the ending I have envisioned, it really makes
me feel something.
I'm not going to say what emotion it is, but it really makes me feel it.
And so I, I guess I would hope that other people would feel it, but I always find that
like, I always feel like maybe it's just inevitable when you make something that like when other
people read it, they, they don't have the same reaction.
Like a lot of times you might make something that you, you find like, oh, this is disgusting
or like this is, this is like horrifying, but maybe people might read it and they, and
they laugh.
And that's okay.
Yeah.
But I wonder, I wonder maybe if it will be some, if maybe people will read the ending
and they will feel differently about it than I do.
And it's okay if that's the case, but I'm, I'm curious, I'm curious.
It's definitely okay.
It's one of those, those things where it's like you make art for yourself.
Yeah.
You don't make art so that other people can feel emotions while you just have nothing.
And if you do, you better be getting paid for it at least.
Hell yeah.
You better hit that donate button on itch.io.
It worked on, it worked on this game for a year.
I hope, I hope I make a, it would be nice to make at least a little something from it.
I'm not going to, I'm not going to, I'm not going to charge money upfront for it, but
I hope, I hope that the, I hope maybe people will throw some, some, some coins in my coffer.
Not that like I need money or anything, not that I'm like hurting for money, but still
it worked really, I worked really hard, worked really fucking hard on this thing.
I guess maybe even nobody donates, only a year, only a year, uh, uh, uh, fucking, uh.
When, what month did you start?
I started, well, I officially started working on it in December of 2020.
I had done a little bit of work on like some sprites kind of before that.
Okay, so it's a little over a year.
A little bit over a year, yeah.
Um, even, even, I guess even if, even if it doesn't make any money and like realistically
I don't expect it to make more than like maybe a few hundred dollars, that's, that's optimistic.
I'd be, it would be optimistic to think that like a hundred, a hundred people might hit
that donate button.
Um, but, uh, even if, if they, if they don't, and they won't, I guess I hope to monetize
it in a way with the, with the eventual slime and punishment Kickstarter, uh, for a book
which maybe, maybe I'll do it later this year.
Uh, so, you know, the returns, the returns are ephemeral, the returns are nebulous.
They have, they have yet, they have to be forcibly materialized later through Guile
and, uh, Chicanery, uh, I added a new option on the starting menu, uh, that says it's
read the comic.
It just brings you to the first page of, uh, slime and punishment on stcomics.com.
I already, I already had the, what is this option explaining like what slime and punishment
is, but like, it's probably good to have an actual link and they're like, okay, well,
if you want to actually read it, here it is, um, and, and, and so, and so there it is.
Um, I don't know.
I hope people like the game.
I'm very excited.
I'm very excited about it.
I'm really, I hope, I hope it does.
I hope it's, I hope it gets seen.
I hope people like it.
I hope people talk about it.
I hope, uh, it generates a little bit of interest that'd be very, make me very happy.
Um, mif, mif, ah, yeah, I don't, I, I've also been working out on my secret project,
but I, I, it's just, it's just not right yet.
Not quite right.
Not quite.
To, to, to mention it.
To, to, to, to.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
You said, um, you said you thought maybe January or February, is it, or is it still on?
February is still like quite possible.
Yeah.
Um, yeah.
Yes.
Right.
The second, the, my first thought is like Lord of Ghosts, back around those, just get
them sent.
That's fair.
Um, so I'll be working on that while I'm sending those out.
I ha, I do ha, I have to admit that the Blu-rays have taken a bit of my attention away from,
uh, I think that's kind of maybe why I'm, the Blu-rays are probably why I have not, uh,
gotten further along with the actual drawing of it because they've taken, they've taken
time.
You know, I've had to produce the discs and I've had to, you know, address the envelopes
and get them in the mail and stuff, which takes, uh, you know, I've had to devote some,
some mental energy to that, but it's okay.
It's worthwhile.
It's worth, it's worth doing.
So I don't regret it, but you gotta split your, you gotta split your attention sometimes.
Um, yeah, I guess, I guess that's all I have to say about that this week.
Um, fuck, fuck HTML.
Why doesn't it just work?
Why doesn't it just work like the executable file?
Can't, can't fucking believe all this undefined behavior bullshit I have to deal with.
And blood splatters drawing underneath the floor and shit.
Give me a, give me a fucking break.
Um, speaking of give me a fucking break, I, I don't, I don't have to go on at great length
about this, but I kind of do want to mention something that made me mad this week and I've
been mad about it for a while, which was, uh, the artist for the Radcon dojin.
Oh yeah.
Uh, so I announced this on Twitter, you know, we had a guy, I'm not, I'm not sure if it's
like cruel.
I'm not sure if it's like cruel to say who I've mentioned who it is before.
I kind of feel like saying it might drive like negative.
I don't, I don't know if anyone cares enough that they would go and like harass him about
it, but they might maybe and like, I don't want him, I don't want him harassed.
There's no reason to say is no.
Even though I'm angry, even though I'm angry at him, um, but yeah, the, we had an artist
working on the dojin and they had done sketches and they had done like a few like some of
the pages were, were drawn or like mostly drawn.
They looked really good, which was the annoying thing.
They did.
That is annoying because I like his art and I thought his style was a good fit for the
project, which is like, he had, I wouldn't, I wouldn't say he just draws, he doesn't
draw like a generic, it's not generic anime, but it's, it's a, it's a very anime look.
It's a very old school kind of anime look, but it's cute too.
It worked really well for what I thought the dojin would look like.
And this guy was not a guy with a ton of followers, he didn't have a big account or anything.
And I, and he had done, um, years ago, he had done a piece of Brunswick fan art.
He had just sent me a drawing of, of me and Brunswick from the Brunswick comic and I liked
it and this is how I found this guy.
I thought it was good.
So I wanted to give him, we had a couple artists in mind and I thought he was the best fit
and also I wanted to give him the chance.
So I, I pushed for this guy and everyone seemed to be fine with it.
So we're like, okay.
So we talked to him and he, he, we agreed that like, okay, the manga would be 24 pages,
the PC, not all of them, but some of the PCP dating sim people had written the script.
I had, I had commissioned them for the script.
So we gave it to him and was like, okay, it's 24 pages.
I'll pay you half up, half upfront and half on completion, right?
So he, and, and we said, do you think you can have it in a month?
And I think he agreed to, it was either like a month or, or maybe a little over a month,
maybe like five weeks or something.
And I was like, okay.
So a month goes by, he sends me like one, shortly after he sends me like one page and
I'm like, it looks good.
Keep it up.
So then a month goes by and I ask him like, Hey, you know, what's up?
Now I didn't expect it to be done.
Like I kind of expected him to be like, it took longer than I thought.
And I was, and I was going to be like, okay, that's fine.
I don't care.
It doesn't bother me, but I send him after a month and he doesn't get back to me.
It takes him like a week or like two weeks or something to get back to me.
It takes him a while.
And I start to wonder like, did this guy disappear?
Is this guy gone?
But he eventually gets back to me and he's like, Hey, sorry, you know, oh, my notifications
don't work.
You know, my, my discord notifications just don't work and Twitter too, all my notifications
It's weird.
And I'm like, okay, fine.
And he shows me what he had and it was good.
And he was like, sorry, it's late.
You can dock my pay if you want.
And I'm like, no, no, I don't need to dock your pay.
It's, I don't care about that.
Just, just, you know, just keep at it.
And then, and then I'm like, and then a month later, I asked him like, Hey, what, what's
the, Hey, what's the update?
How's it going?
Haven't heard from you in a while.
And then I don't know, man.
The point is like three or four months go by.
It's been like three months at this point.
We agreed to one month initially, it's been three and it's been a full month since I've
been messaging him and asking and even adding him on Twitter, being like, can you talk to
me?
And he's just gone.
He's just nowhere.
And it's so ghosting, complete ghosting.
He didn't on the one, he did accept money.
He did.
He, he did basically take my money and run, but it's not a complete that because he did
turn in something, you know, I paid him half.
He turned in, I think like nine or 10 pages.
So he didn't do nothing, but he didn't quite earn his money either.
So he semi took the money and ran and like worse than that is just that he didn't tell
me if he was, if he wanted to quit, if he wanted to like, Hey, I don't want to do the
project anymore.
Just fucking tell me, don't fucking ghost me.
It's, it's upsetting.
It's really upsetting.
It's like, I don't know, I don't commission a lot of art.
So maybe this kind of thing is more common than I thought, but I'm like mad.
I'm like disgusted.
Like I can't believe that a person would do this.
Like it's so, it's beyond unprofessional.
It's beyond unprofessional.
It's despicable.
I'm fucking getting riled up.
Like why would you treat another human being this way, let alone someone who's fucking
paying you money for a service?
My God.
Yeah.
I, I, I've commissioned artists before and I, you know, things often take longer than
you expect.
Sure.
I don't really know how to like, to, to gauge like deadlines.
I'm just happy that they stay in contact.
It doesn't actually happen that often that they, they ghost me though.
No.
I don't think it's ever really happened.
Maybe it's just been a while and I've been like, maybe I shouldn't press it too much.
Right.
So like complete, like abandonment, like no response at all on anything has not happened.
It, there's a, there's a few more wrinkles to it.
When I had, when I came, realized that like DMing him on Twitter and Discord was not working.
I went on, I went on Twitter and I, because I saw him like, you know, he would occasionally
post some art on Twitter.
He would, he would, he would like, he was like stuff on Twitter.
Like he had liked something on Twitter like that day.
And so I went on Twitter and I added him publicly and I was like, Hey, can anyone get in contact
with this guy?
And that was the last time he ever liked anything on Twitter.
He just stopped going on Twitter after that.
So that was funny.
And the final like insult is that like, you know, I went to his link tree to try to find,
because he had said, he had made up some shit about like how his notifications weren't working.
So I went to his link tree to try to find other ways to contact him just in case.
And I found his email.
I think, I think you looked at the link tree actually.
I, yeah, I, I Googled his name.
I found his link tree.
Yeah.
So, and he, and he had, so he was, he was, he was gone off all social media.
The one thing he was still using was any list, which is basically like my anime list where
you list shows that you've seen.
The only thing he was still posting on was, was any list.
And like, like three, it was before I made the post, like three hours ago, he had like,
he had finished watching like some Gundam anime.
Like he's still, he's off all regular social media, but he's still, he's watching anime
and he's like, and he's updating his like anime's watch list.
And I'm like, guy, you didn't die.
I was, I, ooh, I was really hoping to find out you had died in a tragic accident.
And that was why.
Unfortunately, that's not the case.
So now I have to be very cross with you.
It's like, I don't know what, why are people, I get why people are scared of confrontation.
Like, oh no, I didn't do my homework.
The teacher's going to kill me.
Yeah.
But like, it's always worse if you don't ever say anything.
Like that every show, every piece of media where a character could tell the truth and
get scolded or instead chooses to tell a lie and get found out later.
It's always worse when they do that.
I mean, on the one hand, I guess it comes down to his values, right?
Cause like, he doesn't actually have to face any consequences of this.
Like there's nothing I can do about it.
If he is, if he is okay with this situation, then like, I guess more power to him.
He, he, he, he did, he did what he wanted to do.
He's living his best life and, and, and, and, you know, happy for him.
But I, but I feel like he shouldn't be happy with it.
And I feel like it, a rational person would see this outcome as a problem.
And, and that problem did not exist before when he, when he was, whatever problem he
might have imagined that like it was late or like it was like, you know, it was more
work than he thought or something like that.
Whatever problem may have been there was not, was not that big a deal, but like now it is
a big deal now.
Like what he, what he ended, the way he handled it is, is a, I don't know, to me, to me, it's
like, it's bad.
It's really fucking bad.
It created a problem where basically none existed.
The way that, the way that he chose to respond to whatever was stressing him out about it.
Right.
It's not rational.
It's, it's, yeah.
I, because I think of like, if I was in that situation where I knew I could see that the
person was trying to get in contact with me, adding me on Twitter publicly.
He definitely saw.
He definitely saw it.
There's no, there's no way he didn't.
Like being aware of that, I would just feel bad all the time.
I hope he does.
He should, he should feel bad.
He should feel bad about himself.
This is not something that's like, okay, this is not something that, okay, I'm gonna, I'm
gonna overstate it.
I'm gonna overstate it.
I was gonna say, this is not something a good person would do.
I'm not saying this guy is like a terrible person in general, but this is, this is not
a good thing to do.
You should feel ashamed of yourself.
In my opinion.
Yeah.
So I hope he feels bad about it.
I don't know.
I was tempted to, I was tempted to file like a PayPal complaint and like claw back the,
the money, the like, you know, the first half that I had already paid him.
Maybe I could have gotten it back.
In the end, I decided that probably the best thing to do is like, just forget it.
You know, he did, he did most of half of the work.
So just whatever, just keep it, we'll just take what you got.
So it's, and then we got, we got Kaijukun.
I asked Kaijukun if he would like to complete the project.
And he said, he said he would, he said he'd have it in six weeks.
So we'll see about that.
So yeah, I'm just out of out of spite, out of hurt feelings.
I kind of wanted to like, no, give me my money back.
Your page is going to trash.
You're not on the project anymore.
But like practically consideration, it's like, well, but why, but like, that's such
a waste though.
Like, like whatever, whatever is where his drawings were good.
The pages were good.
I wish I wish he'd completed it because it would have looked really good.
I'm sure Kaiju will also do a great job.
But you know, whatever, whatever.
So I'm mad.
So a lot of things, so a lot of things made me mad this week, I guess, is the, is the
theme.
Yeah.
One thing that didn't make me mad though was the crypto crash.
That was pretty funny.
Was there a crash?
Yeah.
Big one.
Bitcoin dropped like 10% Ethereum dropped even more.
Um, hold, actually, uh, something, uh, Milu in my discord, he messaged me today before
I was awake.
He said like, Ben, you've got that USDT and USDC in your, in your, in your Bitcoin wallet
wallet.
Uh, the gas fees are low.
The gas fees are only $4 right now.
You can transfer it out.
I didn't see it until a few hours later.
That was what I had to check before the PCP started.
I didn't see it till a few hours later.
And then he, and I checked, and by the time I checked, it was, it was like $30, which
is lower than it's ever been.
I've never seen it lower than like 60.
So I was, I was tempted to go $30, but this, he said it was going to be like four.
I may have just missed the window on that.
So I don't know.
Such a scam.
I mean, the whole thing is a scam, but like the gas fees, it can never work.
The aspect of it is just so stupid.
It's useless.
Like it will never, it can never see wide adoption because it's so cumbersome.
It's terrible.
Did you, did you see the, um, the video by Dan Olson?
I did.
I watched it yesterday.
Okay.
That's a good, I had been following his thread about, um, NFT discord servers on Twitter
for a while.
So I knew he was going to make a video.
I've been looking forward to it.
It's a great video.
It made me afraid.
Like maybe genuinely afraid of the future, uh, 10 out of 10, I just really appreciate
like the, the things that like lots of people learning about NFTs, they see as somebody
tweeting about the bad effects and they link to an article and then there's like a bunch
of articles and it's like, it's hard to like remember all of the different facts and like
to know whether what is, what is really the deal with all of this?
Put all of the information all in a row that you could experience from one to the, to the,
you know, from the beginning to the end, you're like, okay, now I get it.
I get it.
And even, you know, my hunches, my, my inklings, my, my thoughts based on some evidence, uh,
have been shown to be true with all the evidence.
They stink.
Right.
Yeah.
Um, they're bad, they're bad in, they're just like a whole stack.
They're bad in like every way and there's just like a whole stack of reasons with it.
They're bad on top of bad.
Like they're not only bad at what they set out to do, but also what they set out to do
is horrifying.
Um, it's, it's multi-layered.
And what they actually end up doing is also horrifying.
Right.
And there's, they're bad.
Yeah.
Like people, people talk about like how they look really bad and like true.
And also the environmental effects, yeah, true, but also like, you know, even more important
than that is like, you know, the, you know, blockchain supremacy would be like a privacy
nightmare.
You know, it's consolidates power more effectively than traditional money does even.
So that's really a nightmarish dystopian, uh, yeah, it's, it's, it was really interesting.
This basically how it's the same system we have now where the rich get richer and the
poor are like mistreated and taken advantage of and shoved around.
But it's, it's the same, but in the digital realm and just sort of worse and worse and
worse.
Like people, people who need money, who, who, who are struggling, uh, get hit the hardest
and it's sad that like, like they're made the butt of jokes, not like it's, I get, they
should be made fun of for, for like the reasons of, of making NFTs look bad by, by exposing
the bad stuff that they do.
But a lot, but at the end of the day, a lot of them are just dupes, right?
A lot of them are just, you know, unfortunate dupes who've like, they, they just, they're
desperate and they're hoping that this is their big break and it isn't and they get
fucked over and they have no money and they lost all of their savings and that's it.
They're fucked and nothing can be done about it, at least in terms of like getting the
money back because it's all blockchain stuff.
It's all legal for that to be stolen from them.
He was not the first one to express this sentiment, but I think Dan, at some point in the video,
he, I'm paraphrasing, but he says like something like, like, like the vision of the vision
of crypto is like the pitch for crypto and NFTs is like, get it on the ground floor.
Like it's basically just like we can re remake capitalism, but like, but you get to be the
boot, right?
If you buy, if you buy in early, we'll still have a system wherein like, you know, inequality
exists and is reinforced and, and boot stamping on a human face forever.
But if you buy in, you can be the boot.
You can be, you can be the boot stamping on other people.
And it's like, well, sign, sign me up, I guess.
If you've been stamped on, I get why you'd rather be the boot, of course.
Uh, sure.
So actually it's funny, funny timing.
The crypto crash was happening as, uh, the I hate digi bro video was, was, was premiering.
And, and, and, and wanted to, well, I saw one or two people in the live chat being like
crypto crash, Bitcoin crash.
And then I looked over to, and then I looked over at Kikko or whatever.
And I saw like, yeah, line go down, line go down.
It's like the biggest drop in like months, actually.
Uh, so that was.
Were she talking about Bitcoin in the, no, but I, but I was like, oh my God, Trixie.
No, you gotta bring digi bro back.
You gotta bring the market doesn't like this.
You're killing Bitcoin.
Uh, yeah.
Very funny.
Um, uh, yeah, I hope it, I hope it keeps going down.
Obviously.
Uh, who knows?
I, obviously there's that nagging voice in my mind that's like, no, Ben, you gotta buy
the dip.
You gotta buy the dip, Ben.
You can't do it.
Ben.
Well, listen, I'll, I'll repeat what I've said.
You've said before, even if it was the worst thing to do, but it was beneficial.
If I knew, if I knew that it's going to bounce and it's going to go up and it's going to
go to the moon, I'm sorry, I would buy in.
I'm sorry.
I would do it.
And I would cringe at you.
I know.
Like I currently do.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Uh, but there's, you know, people, I've seen some predictions that are like, oh no, it's
going in a zigzag pattern.
You ever see, okay.
Can we just up, down, up, down?
Yeah.
Cause it did a big spike and then it went down and then it did a big spike and then
it went down and, um, people draw.
Let me show you an image.
People draw shit like this here.
This is, this is a good example.
Uh, let me see.
Okay.
Website uses cookies.
That's fine.
They'll take the graph, they'll take the graph, let me post, uh, the image here and they'll,
and they'll, they'll isolate some points on the graph and then they'll draw some lines
between them and then they'll be like, oh, see here, it's a pattern.
Oh, it's forming a zigzag pattern, right?
But like, and some, and some, like when you look at this, it, it looks like, oh yeah,
you know, uh, it, it, oh, it went up and then it went down and then it went up and then
it went down and they drew lines around it.
So you can see where it's going to bounce like, oh, it's, it's going to bounce at wherever.
But like, consider the, okay, just in this example, the bottom out, yeah, well, yeah,
zoom out, but also the, the bottom line, like where did they decide to put the left end
of the bottom line?
Could they not have put the bottom, the, the left end of the bottom line lower, right?
And have the angle be steeper and still intersect the bounce point in the middle and then their
prediction point for the bounce.
Oh, well, no, I guess it's, I guess cause the top, the top angles line up too.
Okay.
So I mean, this, this looks pretty, this looks pretty clean, but the point is at the end
of the day, it is arbitrary and people do this all the time and they're like, they, they
isolate a little part of the graph and they draw lines and they're like, see, it's a trend.
See, we can see where it's going to bounce and it's all, it's all just fucking drawing,
drawing targets around arrows that you already shot.
You know?
Yes.
And it like sometime and it, and it, and it proves true about as often as it proves
not true.
And it's like a stupid exercise in nothing, basically, it's, it's like, you can't predict
the future with like, Oh, well, it's been doing this in the current state of the world
for this amount of time.
So all we need to do is make sure that the current state of the world is exactly the
same and it'll happen again.
I look at this graph.
Like that could, like that it could ever happen that all these things are going to change
randomly and you're not going to be able to know.
Yes, exactly.
That's exactly right.
Things, things will never happen the exact same way twice.
It just, it just doesn't happen.
So it's, it's foolish to be like, look, it bounced.
It's going to bounce again.
I look, I look at this graph and it gives me FOMO like, Oh my God, it's going to hit
the bounce point soon.
If, if I don't buy it, I'm going to miss that.
I'm going to miss the gains.
But it's just not that simple.
You can't, you just, you can't actually know these things.
It could, it could just continue to go down and down and down below 20, below 10, maybe.
You just don't know.
You don't know until, until you have hindsight.
I hate, I hate this shit.
I hate looking at this shit because it's so confident.
It's so like, no, look, I drew the line.
No, you, you got to, you got to, you got to obey the line.
And I'm like, maybe I should obey the line, but no, I'm just going to look at the, the
same thing in content, like zoom out over a longer period of time.
This could be like one bump in a different pattern that says it's, it's going to go down
forever or like, or it's going to go down for like a hundred years and it's going to
come up again.
It's like, there's no, there's no metric, there's no way to decide what metric to use.
It's just sort of what you hope will happen.
I hope it'll start going up around here.
I wonder if there's a patent that says it will.
The market did not account for, uh, uh, Trixie denouncing Digi Bro and, and pot and bursting
and bursting the crypto bubble with that announcement.
It wasn't ready for it.
They've thrown off all the models.
Um, what else?
What else?
Do I have any, uh, I guess that's everything on my, on my stupid list of things I wanted
to say today.
Yeah, I didn't have much to say today.
I was too stupid.
Okay.
Watching videos.
Sure.
Got the beginning of the podcast.
Um, I guess one thing, not really a topic, but I would like to do another heckles for
shekels.
Yeah.
You know, I, I've been meaning to bring that up.
I think we should do undertale too.
Undertale too?
Oh, that.
Yeah.
I think we should, I think we should actually do a heckles for shekels of undertale too.
Maybe this week?
Uh, yeah.
You want to do it on this?
I don't know when exactly.
I'll be busy.
You'll be busy.
Okay.
I'll be sort of busy.
I mean, I, I'll have time for like a stream on one of the nights.
Do you want to let me know when you want to do it?
When you know?
Um.
I mean, you don't have to let me know right now.
Yeah, I'll, I'll let you know.
Okay.
But yeah, I also want to do, we haven't done it.
We haven't done one all month, uh, bit, bit cringe.
Um, so you, I don't know, you want to do voicemails?
Yeah.
Sweet.
You got them, you got them open?
I will get them open.
One thing I've been thinking about, and I probably have not acted on it this episode
because I have not been thinking about it during this episode.
But uh, I have been thinking, I have thought this before, but I think I would like to act
on it sooner rather than later and actually do something about it this time.
Uh, I don't like how often I say like, people have pointed it out before and it's true that
many times when I'm speaking, I go, oh, it's like, like, you know, like, like, and uh,
I think it's a bit excessive and I think I would maybe like to tone it down and I might
have said this before.
No, you just said it then.
I know, I know.
I know.
Ugh.
Yeah.
Um, I don't know.
I would like to turn it down.
I would.
Shut up.
Prefer it to turn it down.
Die, die, die, die.
It would be, uh, in my best interests, it would be, uh, beneficial.
I, I, it just, it, read a dictionary every now and, every now and then it occurs to me.
I don't really like how much I say, like, and so I don't know, um, I, I don't really
enjoy how much I shut up, um, so I don't know.
I'm not saying, I'm not saying I'm gonna fix the problem.
I am saying.
I'm just saying it's another on the long list of things that make me mad.
That's true.
I am saying that I would like to not be like that anymore and, uh, maybe I'll, I, I don't
know.
I don't know if I can fix myself at this point.
I mean, is it really a problem?
I, I, in my opinion, if you, I don't like it, I don't like it is why it's, you don't
like it.
You don't enjoy it.
How many times, um, yeah, I don't know, I don't know, whatever, um, like, it's okay.
I just didn't think it's fine.
It's, it's okay to do sometimes in moderation.
I don't think it's something that I need to never do, but there, I've definitely heard
myself speaking at times and been like, that's too many likes.
It's, it's, uh, it's a verbal tick.
You just need to think of something to replace it with.
Um, yeah, like what, what I just did there, I go, um, lots of people do that.
Some people just have nothing.
They have like a silence.
They, they, they leave silence when they don't have a word to say, which is something I've
done sometimes and it means people think I've finished talking when I haven't.
So I don't know, you, you, you could replace it with something you could, you could force
yourself to like add nothing.
I guess I could, I could make a conscious effort to replace it with something that I
find more agreeable.
I guess maybe that's one way to do it.
I would have to think about what that would, like squash.
No, no, um, all right.
Do you want to, the first, the first voicemail is called fatty tuna.
You got it?
Yep.
Okay.
Uh, well three, two, one, let's jam.
Speaking of stupid racist shit on the internet, the English cast for the dub of Nagatorosan
got released and there was a shit storm because it turns out cast a black woman voice actors
was gonna be black and people were saying stupid shit like Edward Toro, which I guess
was actually kind of funny, but still, it fits a little too well, but then people were
like, oh, she's not actually black.
You didn't have to voice her with a black person.
You idiots.
Right.
And it's like, does that mean Darth Vader's not black anymore?
Darth Vader's not black.
I mean, he is actually.
These exact people will make some stupid excuse because of boomer bullshit, but I saw this.
I saw this being posted.
I've never seen Nagatoro, but I've seen the character.
She's like tan.
I don't, I think she's just kind of supposed to be a little bit darker skinned.
Not, I don't think she's supposed to be like tan, like she's a beach bunny or anything
like that.
Uh, that's, yeah.
You know, I cast a black woman and I saw one response that was like, you know, no, nobody
gets mad when white people voice the male anime characters who are Japanese.
So why is it a problem if a black voice is this girl is also Japanese?
Oh, we only only only Japanese actors.
No.
I just hate black people.
I'm sorry.
I'm not sorry.
It's true.
It's not good.
Yeah.
I was with anime fans.
What is it with Japan?
I'm a fan.
Well, it's not just them, but I mean, it's not just them.
But like, why is that?
Like it's gamers too.
It's gamers, Jerry.
It's a, it's a certain type of disillusioned young, uh, internet like cracker.
Just say it.
Just say cracker.
Uh, yeah, leads to those things.
I don't know.
Like a whole like cycle of analysts, but I can see it happening and that's really bad.
It sucks.
I don't like it.
Next voicemail is an image.
Here it is.
What is this?
What's this?
Oh, the father of the son, the Holy Spirit.
Jesse.
It's not yellow.
Nate.
Common as glasses aren't orange.
Uh, this is Chris Chan.
No, they are orange.
Uh, they're not red.
People draw them as red.
No, no, people draw them as orange.
Wait, because of that one scene where he's like points to the heavens and there, it's
like the orange light is makes them look orange, but other places they're red.
You're right.
People misunderstand.
You are correct.
I got missed.
What, I don't know what, what, what can I say about this image, but I agree.
It's true.
It's just, it's just true.
Um, you know, maybe we should like, maybe we should like retweet some of these like on
the two, on the PCP account.
It occurred to me the other day, like we could, I could like post some of these like funny
voice mail parts like on the Twitter.
Yeah, yeah.
Like why not?
Why haven't, so maybe I'll do something with that.
Yeah, maybe make a tweet and then like which episodes it's featured in or something.
Yeah.
Yeah, maybe.
Um, okay.
Another image.
Oh God.
This could be you.
If you go keto.
Got all the girls looking at you.
Yeah.
Meanwhile.
You're completely butt naked.
Sure.
Meanwhile at big carb.
Unfortunately, this is not me because, uh, I haven't worked out in almost a month because
first I got COVID and then after I recovered, uh, the, um, there were, there were people
at the, um, at the, the, the Munchie house.
They were busy and we didn't, we didn't work out like all through January.
So, uh, this is not me, but it could still perhaps one day.
What, what is going on in big carb?
There's a person crying.
There's a person carrying a box.
Line go down.
In the background.
Like their businesses, their businesses, uh, they've lost everything.
They're just like unreasonably upset or like reasonably upset because carbohydrates rule
their lives.
Yeah.
They, they've got more than enough reason to be.
I would be doing the exact same thing if I were, they're seething.
You ask what they're doing.
They're seething and molding and coping.
This guy's mouth is disgusting.
His flat gums with his little nub teeth.
That's what happens when you eat bread.
That is.
That's true.
Man, I gotta go to the dentist.
I told myself, I told, shit, I told, I told myself, uh, okay, it's, it's new year.
I'm going to finish up a Phantom's Revenge and then I'll finally make a dentist appointment.
Uh, and it's, it's been a whole.
It's your, your, your victory lap.
Kinda.
I thought it would be like two weeks, but it's been three weeks.
January is almost over and I'm still like, oh, gotta actually draw the shit.
So, uh, I gotta, I gotta actually do it.
Uh, I like these cute girls.
I like these cute girls.
They're not even all looking at you.
The one on the top left is looking at the pink one.
That's okay.
That's true.
Well, that's fine.
That's fine.
Um, I don't like the drooling one actually.
She can, she can leave.
The other ones are good.
Uh, okay.
This is like that panel of the Vapors.
This is like that panel of the Vapors where Vincent is imagining himself holding infinite
jests and all the girls are gazing at him in awe.
I was just imagining if Vincent was doing this pose naked.
This could be.
Imagination.
Uh, Vincent would never go keto.
Maybe he would.
I don't know.
Um, anyway, uh, which was that, um, uh, shit.
Which image was this?
This was, okay.
So the next page.
The next one is, the next one is called the new, it's called New DeVoo.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, you see that New DeVoo video?
Yeah.
We talked about it.
It was pretty good.
Whatever.
Who cares?
Shut up.
We talked about it last time.
It was pretty good.
Oh my God.
It was a video.
Shut up.
Fuck you.
I don't want to hear about the New DeVoo video.
Um, uh, there was too much of a fucking coward to call Trixie out for like fucking, uh,
mistreating her.
So she's dead to me.
She's fucking dead to me.
I talked about this last episode.
I don't have to go into it again.
Um, that's it.
Okay.
Next one is called, uh, for Jess fans out of the loop.
Three, two, one, go.
So with all the recent bleep in the weeb talk, uh, I've seen a lot of people just like talking
about Jesse and like asking like, oh, what's Jesse doing?
Like, uh, Jesse kind of just left.
Um, Jesse is still making content.
He's just like patron exclusive now.
Okay.
Has been for like, uh, like a year or two now, like two years now.
I heard he does Let's Plays.
I heard he plays video games and posts videos of it.
He makes like three to five like videos a month.
Amazing.
Releases them at the end of the month on Patreon.
It's incredible.
So, uh, if you want to support Jesse, uh, you know, throw a dollar his way.
Patreon.com slash, unless Jess.
Sam, fuck off.
Don't call us a patron for a little while.
And he does do the Let's Plays like live stream super cuts where he like cuts down a live
stream he did, um, makes it easier to watch.
And then there's like a few like weirdo like vlogs.
He did one where he like had a bunch of alcohol and he went into the middle of the woods during
COVID because that's the only place that's safe where no one can get him.
Some of that stuff's quite good, but I, uh, ultimately felt like it wasn't worth my money.
I don't.
Maybe he's made some really good videos though.
I'm not sure.
I don't.
I'll believe it when I see it.
I don't want to be advertised to you on my show.
Fuck off, voicemailer.
Um, next one is, uh, a vocaru link.
Yep.
Uh, okay.
All right.
Here we go.
Uh, this is called Rand, Rand, Rand in, okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Ugh, you ever go back and, uh, listen to old PCP episodes?
No.
Here Nate, go on weird, I know, Rand, Rand, and like, just say a whole bunch of like
cringy, notarian, while simultaneous.
He dreaming of living in, uh, you know, post scarcity.
Communism was like, I don't know.
What?
I'm gonna be like Jordan, your solution.
I'm like, still think this is the smoke I ever...
What a fucking door.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, true.
That was pretty groovy.
Uh, true also?
I would say it's true.
Because he was talking about things that literally happened.
I would agree with that assessment.
Uh, cool.
Um, next one is called, old unused voicemail, haha.
Uh, that's another vocaru.
All right.
Uh, all right.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, it is me, the baby boy.
I have a question for Ben St.
Will you abort me?
I am only two years old.
My brain is not fully developed.
A chimpanzee can outthink me.
Put me in a blender.
Put the baby in a blender.
You know you want to.
You know you need to.
Put the baby in a blender.
What does this remind me of?
Um, is it that song we just heard in the last voicemail?
No, no, no.
I mean, it's probably the same guy.
But it's like some, something about that, that vocal,
would the baby in the blender in that sort of crunched,
distorted voice.
But I think that should probably be this week's intro music.
I liked it a lot.
That was quality.
Very, very drool.
And I mean, I would definitely kill a chimpanzee with no hesitation.
So a two-year-old child would be no problem.
No sweat.
Yeah.
All right.
Next, next one is Janess.
Three, two, one, go.
If you haven't heard the announcement yet,
Scott Pilgrim is gaining anime adaptation.
And the author is going to be the executive producer on the project.
I heard about.
It's made me wonder,
since Ben, your comic style was mainly influenced by Scott Pilgrim.
Oh, mainly.
How would you feel if your comics were adapted into an anime format?
And how would you feel about Japanese voice actors
dubbing the creative characters?
I would be excited because it would make me a lot of money.
That's my answer to both of those questions.
It would be cool.
It would be awesome.
I'd make a lot of money.
I'd get a lot of exposure.
It would be great.
When they say anime adaptation,
do they mean like anime, like Japan?
Or do they mean like a cartoon show?
Air in Japan.
I don't know.
I did see it was getting a cartoon or whatever.
Scott Pilgrim anime.
Okay, a Scott Pilgrim anime series is coming to Netflix.
Netflix is turning Scott Pilgrim into an anime.
I'm not seeing any promotional images.
They have to mean.
There's no way they're going to make it look like an anime.
It has to have the style, the recognizable style.
It has to.
It would be funny if it was exclusively in Japanese.
Like a weeb move.
Because Scott Pilgrim is kind of a nerd and that would be a funny joke.
It would be kind of funny.
I don't know.
Whatever.
Okay, next voicemail is banana.
3, 2, 1, go.
Why isn't Eleazar a guest?
Because they're too busy editing.
Well, I don't know.
There's no reason they couldn't be.
What would he want to talk about?
If he asked and he wanted to, I wouldn't be against it.
But like, you know.
Better question.
Why do you want him to be a guest?
What's your problem?
Yeah, fuck you.
Next voicemail is called go on the Dug Zone.
3, 2, 1, go.
Go on the Dug Zone.
I think it would be neat.
The Dug Zone is the podcast where they...
something, something, Dug Walker.
Okay.
What do they do there?
Do they say Dug Walker's...
I'll go on the Dug Zone.
Are they big?
I don't think they're that big.
Dug Zone podcast.
I mean, I have some...
The Dug Zone cast on Twitter.
They have 38 followers on Twitter.
That's fine.
I'd go on the Dug Zone, I guess.
If they wanted me to.
I'm not against it.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called Plans for Episode 300.
And I just got to say,
I see that this voicemail is a minute and 13 seconds long.
And from the title, I feel like maybe I've got the gist of what the question is.
Right.
But I'll give it a chance.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
So with Episode 300 on the way, are you like planning anything?
Like getting any like special guests?
That took five seconds.
Or is it just going to be like a normal episode?
Because I think it'd be cool if some like new member or something was like announced.
I don't know.
Gamer's Tavern as a member would be pretty cool.
I mean, he's already been on the podcast more times than Jeff too.
I can't tell if this is a joke or something.
No, having other like previous guests on like Minerva or Cybershell would be pretty cool.
I think it'd be neat if Davoo ever got on.
At least one more time.
I think Davoo has quite a lot in common with the current PCP lineup as it is right now.
Seeing as both Ben and Davoo are game devs right now and Davoo and Gibbo are women.
Got to have them women on the show.
Okay, bye.
No, short answer, no, I don't have any plans for 300.
What are we on like 270, 298?
Remember like 290 something.
It's very close.
Right?
I don't know.
I don't know what to do for 300.
We'll just say to all the guests, hey, as many guests are interested, we're doing the episode 300.
Wanna come?
And then they'll be like, no, it'll just be us.
You know what?
Yeah, maybe we should do a get like a former guest extravaganza.
I don't know.
I don't know who...
I mean, I'd like it to be a larger affair than just the two of us and we have regulars that like coming on.
I think Cybershell, it would be fun to have Cybershell on.
To Snaker was pretty fun, maybe we could have him back on.
Yeah.
Who did you just say?
Simsie.
Simsie, yeah, Simsie's cool.
We'd get Kazi, maybe.
Sure.
Can we get Kazi?
Can we afford them?
I'm trying to think, I mean, who else?
I mean, if we could have like 100 people on, but like that wouldn't work.
We just send out like, oh, it's a big episode and like see if anyone's interested.
If there's too many people interested, we'll have to like start saying no.
Or like stagger it out.
Like people come in for a bit.
I don't know.
I don't expect it to be like an overwhelming too many guests moment.
Probably not.
I mean, I'm looking through the past guests list right now.
Does anyone stand out to me?
Jim Storm Dancer.
He unfollowed me on Twitter.
I'm assuming it was not for any like reason.
He probably was just like, what do I need to follow this guy for?
That made me a little sad.
I guess I can ask Mary.
I don't know.
Can I ask Mary whether to be on again?
Haven't had him on.
Dude, you know who'd be a good guest?
Tom?
No.
Can we get Tom?
Honestly, if Devu wanted to come on as a guest, I guess for episode 300, it would be fine.
Like I'm not actually like that opposed to it or whatever.
I don't actually care that much.
I might have sounded a little too serious before.
I don't know.
I guess we could ask Minerva.
I don't know if she'd be interested.
Remember low art?
We had low art on one time.
I haven't talked to him in a long time.
I don't know.
FitMC.
FitMC, I mean, he was more of an eight friend.
I never really spoke to him on my own time.
So I don't know if it would be weird to invite him back on.
What a fucking nightmare.
What a hassle.
Oh god.
Headphones fell out again.
There's nothing worse than running a podcast.
Yeah.
We should stop immediately.
I stop at 299.
I mean, whatever.
It's a podcast.
It doesn't have to be special.
But 300 is like a lot of episodes.
That's too many fucking episodes.
All right.
Next one is called X2 321 Go.
He will be here in two weeks.
Oh, it's counting down to 300.
I just put it together.
This must be counting down to 200.
Oh my god.
Maybe it's X minus 2.
Oh, I've been pronouncing it as like X2.
But maybe it's like X minus 2.
Like it's minus.
Okay.
Well, oh boy.
I wonder what it's going to be.
Or who it's going to be.
Next one is called Benz trans takes 321 Go.
Benz is a trans woman because she identifies as one.
And I agree.
Okay.
Thank you for the voice.
Yeah.
Okay.
Next one.
Oh god.
It's called Kyle.
It's Kyle and funny man.
Episode three parentheses.
Actually dramatic and emotional.
Three, two, one, go.
One man's Kyle.
The other is a funny man's Kyle and funny man in space.
Okay.
Enough fucking jokes.
This show has been going on for a while.
There are a bunch of iconic characters.
But now this is like the series episode.
We're going to show that we can do fucking funny,
referential funny humors as well.
But now we're doing fucking sweet dramatic shit.
You're going to literally fucking cry at this episode.
Finally emotional.
These characters you've come to love over the crazy adventures
they've had.
They're going to do some fucking hard shit right now.
Okay.
Get fucking ready.
Funny man.
What are you doing?
You stopped the guard.
Now you just got a...
Why are you putting a gun in his head?
I don't understand.
Kyle.
This man.
He killed my wife.
My tragic backstory.
Funny man.
No.
Revenge and hate just leads to more revenge and hate.
Somebody will come to avenge him.
No funny man.
Spite and revenge are good.
I must avenge my wife and all my village that got killed by this man.
Funny man.
Oh my God.
I can't believe you did a holy shit.
But guys, this series can do fucking everything.
Funny.
We do series.
You literally cry that holy shit.
Oh my God.
This series is the best because we can do literally everything.
Get excited for more.
I'm already there.
You have me.
You have a captive audience.
I'm on the edge of my seat.
That was...
I don't know.
Too beautiful for words.
I didn't cry enough.
It should have been more...
I think I'm...
More crying.
More screaming.
I think I'm still processing.
I'm still processing what happened.
The tears will come later after the shock wears off, I think.
Next voicemail.
Hold on.
Did I download that one?
No, I didn't.
Okay.
I'm trying to download these as I go.
Next one is called Yeah.
Three, two, one, go.
I have some steam issues.
I think it stems from my childhood.
Growing up and normal reading from my parents would be like...
Be like your siblings more.
I'm an only child.
One time someone shot up my car on my way home.
My parents just said good.
Went to the DMV the other day.
When they asked me if I liked my picture.
I was like, oh, it's kind of bad, isn't it?
And she just looked at me and said, that's what you look like.
I was just like, yeah.
I'm really sorry to hear that.
So your car got shot for the holes?
Yeah.
Was that the second part?
Yeah, just bullets.
And then they kind of said good.
Good.
I'm glad that happened.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
I like how understated it is.
If you want to crank it even harder, it'd be like, I hoped you...
That sucks because I hoped a bullet would have killed you.
But no, they just like the bullets.
There were bullets flying at them.
They nodded.
That's just average slide.
It's just good.
That's good.
I like this is happening.
Next one.
The download I did.
Next one is called testing one, two, three.
Oh, like that My Little Pony episode.
Three, two, one, go.
Yeah.
Damn.
That is what they do.
Test successful.
It's so funny because it's true.
Now you can send a voicemail.
Okay.
Next one is called Ben St.
Three, two, one, go.
Yeah.
True.
Next one is called comrade Nikolia.
Three two one, go.
Nikolai looked for vodka.
Nikolai had a lot of vodka.
No.
You know, don't feel too good.
I think he spelled Nikolai wrong.
If you might die without vodka,
Nikolai here comrade Ben St. had vodka.
I do enjoy the occasional, uh, the occasional, uh, nip of, uh, of, uh, potato spirits.
It's true.
Uh, my Slavic heritage, uh, just to blame, I suppose.
Uh, I don't have any on me, man.
I'm sorry.
What if you could have, like, vodka-flavoured potato chips?
God.
Jesus.
Can I, can I met?
Ugh.
No, thank you.
Uh, you just dip him, why not just dip him in rubbing alcohol, if you want.
Uh, that, that's what you're looking for.
Okay, next one is called Wong Chan.
Three, two, one, go.
Doing great.
Uh, man.
I'm, I'm alright.
Doing good.
How are you?
Look forward to hearing your next voicemail when you tell me how, how you are.
I'm gonna have a little backing for it.
Let's be pen pals.
Be voicemail pen pals.
One, one sentence at a time.
Uh, alright, uh, gotta check my numbers.
Okay, uh, next one is Hi Ben.
From Ben is not a saint for 2069 at hotmail.com.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, where the fuck is Tom?
Is he gonna come back on the channel sometime soon?
I don't know.
If he's not, I'm gonna dislike every video you guys have.
Alright.
Also Ben, you're kidding.
Oh my God.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, you got me.
Um, next, uh, Tom said, okay, talking about the, the, the, the, the, the Trixie vid, the
I hate digipro vid, uh, Tom commented on Twitter.
He mentioned that like, he mentioned the fact that like she seems to have forgotten that
I am games ever happened.
And he said something about whatever, whatever.
The point was it came up that like he's rarely on the PCP.
And he said, uh, oh, the time change because we record earlier in the mornings now.
And I said, well, you, you know, you approved the change.
Like I asked everyone if we were okay with the change and he was like, he said, I underestimated
my abilities.
So I don't know, maybe he would want, I'm not sure.
Cause he, I think if he wanted to be on the show, he could, he could just, he could just
say like, can we do it later?
I think, I mean, I think he's just doing other stuff and it's not his priority right now.
I don't think it's actually like, oh, if we just, we need to change the, the schedule
back so he can be on more.
Although if he wanted to, we could totally do that.
Uh, you know, yeah, that's the, that's the situation.
That's why he says, but like, I don't know if he actually wants us to do anything about
it.
It seems like not.
If you didn't say he wanted anything to happen with that.
So I don't know.
Let me know in the comments, uh, what you think about that.
Next voicemail.
YouTube swearing arc to everybody's favorite storyline.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello.
Justy dumps here here to update you on everybody's favorite PCP voicemail storyline, which is
YouTube censorship arc that is happening to me, uh, IRL.
So last week I sent a voicemail being all like, yeah, uh, why are my lyrics getting censored
in the comments?
Why can't I use that?
Oh, you posted a comment saying you, you'll reply to yourself with a swear.
I swear in the comments again, it's going to be freaking cool.
I'm going to write a comment and then in the reply, I'm going to just write like fuck.
Yeah.
That comment got, uh, deleted and censored.
And I was like, okay, uh, justification to my worldview, but then right above me, some
guy just simply named Jonathan writes the comment, test fuck.
Huh.
What?
Why, why is he allowed to swear?
And believe me, I tried like using multiple different accounts on my fucking sock puppets
that I used to hack Hillary Clinton.
I used them all.
I made a new account, a new Google plus account just to fucking do a comment on multiple different
videos, not just PCP, just writing a simple, uh, swear word like fuck or shit.
And every single time the YouTube would get deleted, but some, for some reason, somebody
has the privilege to swear.
Uh, and what's the deal with that?
That sucks.
Now I gotta pee.
Okay.
Bye.
Um, okay.
Yeah.
There was the, the, the comment that he left, uh, saying in replies to this, I will swear.
And if there are no replies, that means YouTube is censoring me and there are no replies.
I didn't see any.
This is, um, uh, hold on, uh, pro crass news pot.
I'm googling our own podcasts.
Uh, where is, no, I wanted to check the latest episode.
This is the, this is the same, this is the same guy who did a bunch of the songs.
Yes.
Songs.
His name is Mutu, Mutu Sandu Mutu Sandu.
Um, yeah.
I saw the comment.
I, I faved it, uh, last night, I think.
And okay.
Well, I was going to say maybe the problem is that your accounts are too new.
Like maybe, maybe even your main account is like too new that like YouTube doesn't give
it, like, doesn't trust it or something.
That, but that's probably only the case if like your main account was like recently made,
which it probably wasn't.
So I don't know.
Yeah.
It's very weird.
I, it's not only that one Jonathan comment that said test.
Fuck.
I saw other people who said like shit and stuff in their comments.
I don't see Jonathan.
I don't see.
I forget what it was called, but he said, he said it was Jonathan, but I don't, I mean,
I'm sure it was there.
I just don't see it at the moment.
Maybe it was taken down.
Yeah.
I don't see.
I, I don't see a comment from Jonathan.
Also, uh, new commented, um, that the Imgur links keep breaking.
And then Tony replies, you got to add dot JPEG to the URL manually.
Uh, I think, I guess like when it's, when it's in link form, the, okay.
This is so, yeah, the link has JPEG in it.
But when you click it, it brings you to a version of the link that does not have the dot JPEG.
So you have to manually add the dot JPEG to see the image.
And, and I just don't, and I just don't understand.
Weird.
I just don't like, what the fuck?
Um, yeah.
And, and also like why, also like why does it not know where the image, like, like the,
like the file extension is the same.
Like the Imgur.com slash and then the numbered letter hash is the same.
So why, why doesn't that work?
What the hell?
Man, I don't get it.
I don't, I don't get it at all.
Okay, well, I don't know.
Anyway, yeah.
Uh, the swearing thing?
Man, I don't know.
It's mysterious to me too.
Let me, commenters, I mean, if you got any theories about what's...
Yeah, I don't, I don't see Jonathan either.
I think he might have also been removed, perhaps?
And I'm logged into the PCP account.
So if anyone would be able to see it, it would be me.
It's hard to know what's happening because like, it seems like comments can and do exist with swears in them.
Yeah.
I need to like be thinking about it to see, to notice if there are none.
But I know I saw that one that he's referring to.
Okay.
Let me slip.
No, there, there are none.
None of them are in the, like, comments held for review.
I'm looking at the YouTube studio right now.
Someone, one got flagged for spam that said like, like this comment if you, if you passed NoNate, NoNate November.
That sucks.
Hmm.
And then...
What the hell?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
There's just another comment here.
And this is a very strange exchange.
This was a month ago.
This one got flagged as potentially inappropriate.
And, okay, commenter Radodon.
This was not a hidden comment.
He commented, I really don't, this was on the, the, the Tisnaker episode.
I really don't like that the dead YouTuber list sourced by subscriber count.
It feels like it's placing the value of their life on big number.
And then playmaker responds at Radodon.
This isn't up for debate.
You were wrong and I'm correct in.
You delete you comment now and apologize.
You're a butt, you're just a butthurt loser who works some lower management job and is mad.
I called you out for your life being less value than mine.
I think it's a joke.
But I don't get it.
I don't get it.
That was like, were they, were they like referencing the subscriber number that the user has compared to their own?
I don't, I think it's a joke about like, you know, ranking people of a value.
Your life is worth less than mine.
But like, you're wrong.
I'm correcting.
Delete your comment.
You lower management job.
What?
Maybe there was some other, maybe there were other context or maybe there were other comments in the thread that I made.
That I missed.
I don't know.
This just seems, this is a little bit confused.
Anyway, anyway, obviously that comment gets approved and is going back up.
We don't, we wouldn't want people to miss out on that in the future.
Okay.
Next, next voicemail.
This is the looks like it might be the final one.
If you can believe it is YouTube swearing arc three final three, two, one, go.
Okay.
I'm back from peeing now.
So I looked at the comments, like I counted all the comments and I saw that there are,
it says there are more comments than actually showed up.
Yeah.
Five or six missing comments or something.
Sometimes if you, if you sort by new or them appear fucking their comments are deleted by doing epic freaking swear.
So it's not just me.
I'm not crazy.
I just don't believe that there should be this crazy fucking swearing disparity where the
comments gets the freaking swear in the comments, but those fucking lower class peons don't even get to say the word fucking sucks.
It's, it's the displayed number of comments sometimes just seems totally random.
Like, okay, sometimes there will be comments that you can't see, but they're not hidden because if you sort by new, they appear and you can see them.
And I don't know why that happens.
I think like the comments, they try to do like most good comments, like, oh, the ones that you probably want to read the algorithm said so.
So they get like the comments with loads of likes, loads of replies, stuff like that.
But some of them are just not there.
And then comments that have no engagement just don't appear in that format.
So you need to click new to find them all.
Sometimes.
So yeah, a lot of times I see, yeah, like it will display a higher number than I see.
And then I sort by new and then I go, ah, there they are.
Other times I've seen the number be less than the number of comments.
Like this was on a, someone was, someone pointed out on a, on a branches of Yig video, a bunch of people posted like comments about the blue rays, the plebeian blue rays, and they were being deleted.
All those comments were being deleted.
But the weird thing was that like, there were like three, there were like four, there eventually came to be like four visible comments on that video.
But the number of comments it said it had was two.
It was like two comments and then there were like four comments down below.
And in fact, I know there were more because there were more of what had been there that had been hidden.
So I don't know why that was happening.
The point is that the YouTube comment thing is bizarre.
YouTube is crazy.
Can I, I'm going to complain about something also this is not YouTube related but on Reddit.
Okay, I might be crazy, but when I am looking for something on Reddit, I can be on a subreddit and I can go to the search bar and I can search for a word that I know is in the subreddit.
I can search for a word that I can literally see posts in the subreddit that have the word in it.
And I will search in the subreddit for that word that is there.
I can see it and it returns no results.
The like the Reddit search function like simply doesn't work.
And I am and I can't understand it.
I'm like am I I don't know if anyone else has knows what I'm talking about.
Like am I crazy is my computer broke.
I don't think so.
I think Reddit just like why have a search bar?
Take away the search if you take the search bar away.
Oh, yeah.
If it simply doesn't work.
Searching with the search bar on Reddit almost always returns nothing.
So why?
Why?
I don't know.
Why would that happen?
Like symbols maybe to put it in like brackets or.
I hate that.
Marks.
It really pisses me off.
Really pisses me off.
How hard is it to make your website work, bros?
It's your job.
Well, they don't need to do that.
They go all the traffic anyway.
I guess.
Well, they don't have my traffic because their fucking website doesn't work.
Yeah, that was the last voicemail.
Wait, what did he say?
What was that last what did he even say about that?
I don't even remember what the content of the last one was.
It was just sort of continuation of people being like not swear allowed and they're
censored and it sucks.
Okay.
Good.
Well, I also noticed their name is wet piss January at dusty dumps.com.
Yep.
Oh, I know.
Oh, I saw.
Is it wet piss January?
It's quite, it's nearly over.
I think every January is wet piss January.
I'm going to go ahead and say it.
Is it possible to do a dusty piss?
I think you have to be a professional.
I think that's for professionals only.
Dang.
You have to be like Christian Bale getting skinny enough to play the machinist.
You know, you have to be a you have to be an expert at that sort of thing to get like
that without risking your health.
Lamal.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's it.
A pathetic two hour episode this week.
But I think.
Yeah.
Sorry.
We're sorry.
Go men this side.
Oh, forgive me.
There's just, I just not a lot to talk about right now for me.
No, not really.
Just doing.
I hope to have more to talk about soon because I am.
Well, no, I can't put anything out because I got to like finish the pages.
So, so no, the content right will continue.
Nothing interesting will ever happen.
Bye.
The end.