Hello everyone and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
the best guy ever. Today we've got Tom Oliver.
The time has come and so have I. I need to change my pants now.
Gibbontake is here.
Hello.
Goodbye.
There's Ben Saint.
Woo, slime, slime.
And Mage, lethal of Aurora version.
Take a sip of tea and chillax.
Yes, yes.
That sounds excellent. Hello everyone. How has your week been going so far? Have you voted in the Minecraft poll from last week?
If not, do so. Tell us what you think about these potential server ideas. We would love to know.
I hope your current message is not going to be outdated by the time the episode comes out.
Current message? Will we have made up a different plan?
Maybe we'll decide in the week and then this episode comes out.
They can vote. It's not going to hurt anything to keep voting even after we've decided, but maybe we'll have a plan in place by the time that's done.
Your vote may be in vain.
The people, the peasants have a vote, but this is still a dictatorship at the end of the day.
We have a vote. We just don't do anything about it.
Just like real life.
Yeah, yeah. Electoral college and whatnot.
What do they call them? Those special voters? The super delegates? That's the one that killed my boy Bernie last time.
We gotta end them.
What's going on in your life, Gib? How's things?
Well, there's a few things I've been doing. I've been watching MLP Season 8 trying to catch up to the end of the show.
So far, the verdict on Season 8 is that I don't care about anything that happens with the characters I know and love.
I only care about the new characters that I know and love.
That's the opposite of what I was expecting you to say.
I mean, it's just so boring. They're oxa-over and every time they have a friendship problem, this doesn't make any sense based on the years of you learning this over and over again.
It's stupid.
No, it's okay. Fluttershy is about baby steps. It's okay. She can learn the same lesson over and over.
I'm having more flashbacks. Don't go there.
It's not just Fluttershy. It's everyone. It's like, Applejack, why are you fucking stupid? Oh, it's just because of convenience for the episode. Whatever. Fine. It's a shit show.
The real moral of My Little Pony is that you're destiny set in stone and no matter how much personal improvement you make, you cannot change your decision to ever be taught in your own problems.
The thing that happens in the beginning of Season 8 is that Twilight decides to open a school of friendship and invites this after the movie, Season 8.
So like the Hippogriffs, the Griffins, the Yaks, the Dragons, they're all allied kingdoms now and the changelings and all that.
And the students from all those respective kingdoms are cool. They have it a lot of episodes together.
And the Crystal Map sends them to far-flung places like Saddle Arabia.
It's like, yeah, all the new stuff, all the Starlight Glimmer is now my favorite pony of the main seven.
What? She's the only irrational one happening.
She's literally the only rational one, the one who will say, that's a fucking stupid idea, everyone.
Well, that's good.
This spicy take is making me want to watch the show right now.
If somebody, maybe I could go through and cross off all the ones that are bad, because it's mostly filler.
If only someone could review these episodes and let me know.
If only someone did that.
What a shame. What a shame that fandom's dead.
Yeah, well, I'm glad.
If only my boy drowning in horseshoes was still around to give me some guidance.
Yeah, he let us know.
Rest in peace.
But yeah, season eight, I'm finished at, yeah, I'm near the end.
It's fine. It's bad and it's good and it's, I like Starlight Glimmer and Trixie episodes.
That's right, Trixie is a main character now.
Yeah, she's Starlight Glimmer's best friend. The two of them together are very good.
Discord loves Dungeons and Dragons and he's best friends and he has guys nights out with Spike and Big Mac.
Oh my God.
Dude, you're hard selling me right now. You're hard selling me right now.
There's lots of little things that are new and interesting, but anything that is like well-trodden ground, I'm like, shut up.
Shut up.
Yeah, it makes sense.
You said season eight, there's nine seasons, right?
Yes, yes, I was getting through season eight and nine, I haven't seen.
Big Mac gets a girlfriend, I'm not sure if it's in season eight.
Oh yeah, Big Mac got a girlfriend, I think in season six.
What about Cherily, God damn it?
She's cucked for life.
I haven't seen Cherily in two or three seasons. Where is she?
She doesn't exist anymore because in season eight, the school, the main six run is the most important one.
And even the CMC are like, fuck, I hate Cherily's lessons, it's so fucking boring.
I'm gonna go into this new school and they have a whole episode about that.
Oh, this is Cherily erasure.
They put her out of business.
What is a teacher gonna do when her competition is like the princess friendship?
Big magic coming in and crushing the Mod Pod institutions of education.
Yeah, no kidding.
Oh, also.
The people need to rise up against these fucking monarchs.
Spike had a teenager episode and grew wings and now he has wings.
Yes, I remember that. Shocking, but also good.
Yeah, it was pretty good.
A lot of things that I had seen hearsay of, like the grotesque image of the ponies, the fake main six melting in their faces,
like dropping, like falling to pieces and like, fuck you, chrysalis or whatever they said.
Directly out.
Like those things were in context.
They're like, oh, that's not as ridiculous or stupid as I thought.
Like Spike getting wings, I thought that's gonna be fucking stupid, but it was alright.
Yeah, alright.
I always was sad that he didn't have wings.
I thought, wow, what a sad, retarded little dragon who'll never be one of the cool guys.
But I guess you just need to grow up.
Jonah the yak is my favorite of the creatures.
Oh, they say every creature now.
That was the thing.
They can't say every pony.
They have to say every creature in front of the creatures.
That's fucking weird.
I mean, it makes sense, but it is silly.
You know what the worst part is, is that all these other people come in and they finally change their language,
but our boy Spike had to endure it for six goddamn years of being a race.
That's so true.
Spike sort of thought of himself as a pony to be quite...
Yeah, because he's been brainwashed by the suppressed culture.
This is fucking like cultural pony hegemony.
This is fucking like all dragons are assumed to be ponies until proven otherwise.
Everyone's assumed default.
No minorities, please.
It's okay, Spike, you're one of the good ones.
Spike definitely has dragon guilt.
He does.
This is fucked up.
I don't like it.
He must have said every pony referring to everyone including himself many times.
He definitely did.
That's straight up.
It just makes you wonder, so up till recently, look, the other kingdoms were nearby.
They weren't unknown.
Was a pony land or whatever so close, Equestria so closed off from these other countries?
Basically, yes.
I think whenever the map was introduced, they went to all these different kingdoms.
Up until that point, everyone was closed off from one another.
Equestria was the pony place, the yaks, the dragons.
Why did it open up?
Because of various friendship envoys to make friends with everyone.
Was it the magic table that sent the main six to go around the world and solve everyone's friendship problems?
Is that what opened up the borders?
Thank you for making friends with the yaks.
I remember that one.
I remember the yak kingdom and the griffin kingdom and I assume there were probably others.
Why hadn't Celestia opened up these trade routes?
Because she's a fucking stupid character and every time she's on screen, I'm like, you ruined everything.
Oh, she was busy managing the sun and the moon.
I don't know.
It tastes like a minute in the morning.
Do you think that Celestia demands that the other kingdoms pay tribute for having soul power and control over the sun and moon?
I mean, that would be the wise thing to do.
You gotta bring in those six dollars somehow.
Exactly.
Well, I don't think you can...
You don't even have to charge them for it.
You can just hold the hostage over their heads.
I mean, no, I'll do this.
If you don't do what I want, I won't do it anymore and I'll plunge you into eternal life.
Is Pony world or whatever? Do we know that that's a globe world or could it be some sort of flat earth?
Where just like in the flat earth, the orbs just sort of move around in like concentric circles or whatever and then they...
I'm pretty sure we don't know that it's an orb world.
It could definitely be a flat land.
You guys had your chance. You were in the same area with Lauren Faust and you didn't ask the important questions.
That would have been agreed.
Yeah, no, 100%. I wonder if maybe someone has asked the question and there is an answer and we just don't know it.
That's probably, I bet it somewhere.
For the future, if anyone ever gets somewhere near Lauren Faust, the first question you ask is the Pony world around or flat?
Yeah, that'd be helpful.
We need to know.
I do. I really do.
Where are the ice walls and where are they in Equestria? I need to go there.
The world is very much unexplored, I guess, in other directions.
Was there any reverence of Pony?
Oh wait, they came from Ponyland originally, right?
That's the lore in Heart Swarming Eve and then they came to Equestria.
They came from someplace that it was too cold.
Or do we assume it's Ponyland?
Did it even have a name?
No.
I don't think a name was said. I think we assumed and we don't actually know.
The ancient Pony places where the kings and everyone's...
And then they went and they left and they went to form Equestria or whatever.
Yeah.
Twilight and Celestia and Luna did.
Shit.
Well, there you go.
We've learned a lot, I guess.
We've learned a valuable lesson about friendship today.
Dear Twilight Sparkle, I learned...
Nothing.
Speaking of learning a valuable lesson about friendship.
I learned I was racist against my dragon friend for six years.
Yeah.
It's pernicious, not overt anti-dragon racism.
Just subtle anti-dragon erasure.
That reminds me of this one episode that made me so sad for a spike.
Yeah.
So Twilight and...
What's her brother's name?
Shining Armor.
They used to apparently have this brother-sister competition sort of thing.
Shining Armor I think used to win, but Twilight would really try.
And like Spike, poor baby Spike, he was a baby dragon.
He really wanted to participate, but no one acknowledged him as part of the family even.
Well, he was a baby, I guess.
So we see the flashbacks, like they got stars or something, I think, for completing a task.
And Spike, he tried, he wanted a star too, but no one cared.
Spike is gonna grow up, become a full-size dragon and fucking murder these people.
He's gonna be completely justified.
In the episode they do acknowledge that he's like,
I think the competition was like he had the best sibling or something.
Best sibling?
Yeah.
So in the episode, they finally, after like six years or however long they lived for,
they finally gave him his star or something.
I don't remember.
Yeah, finally acknowledged him as a sibling.
Okay, okay, but speaking of learning a valuable lesson about friendship,
are you guys following the Adventures of Phantom Horn in New Los Angeles City,
aka Neil Milwaukee?
I love it.
This has been a fantastic journey, because I have to know,
and I have to, I'm gonna give you the credit,
I'm gonna give you the benefit that I doubt,
and saying that this was the plan all along.
This was a slow burn fucking way of indoctrinating an entirely new group of people into your project
via Chris Chan.
That's exactly right.
Exactly right.
The scheme slowly started to reveal itself,
and I was like, this is fucking devious as shit,
and I'm all about it.
Yeah, I mean I got the links in there.
It's all good.
No, this was the plan ever since Phantom and Keg recorded that very first podcast
with the still images.
It was all leading to this.
Okay, okay, well like, fuck.
Like, fucking, I just, there's the part,
in Sonichu episode 12-9, nobody knows why it's numbered that way,
but in Sonichu episode 12-9, you meet Nightstar, Chris's pony Sona,
and she says, because Chris has heterochromia, or thinks she does,
you know, the green eye and the blue eye.
Does Chris not actually have that?
It's like so subtle that it's not, it's kind of bullshit,
but it's part of her self-image,
and Nightstar also has it,
but she explains that during a science experiment,
she got some slime in her eye, and it turned one of her eyes green.
That's absolutely canon, right?
That's 100% canon.
That's in the comic, she says it.
The exact word slime is used.
Yeah, she got slime in her eye during a science experiment.
So I drew her getting slime in her eye, you know, ha ha,
it turns her eye green, and then she sees New Los Angeles City,
and then I drew a couple more stuff that was drew her sending
phantom and strawberry milk to New Los Angeles City,
and then Chris at some point later acknowledged it,
you know, like retweeted it, like she said she wanted to use
the pictures of Nightstar as,
Chris is using those pictures of Nightstar going,
hmm, I get it, you're lying.
She's using those as reaction images on Twitter at people.
Oh wow.
Yeah, she's doing it.
Like when she says someone says something she doesn't agree with.
So I'm like, well, I gotta continue the story now.
So I've drawn like 70 or 80 panels of it now.
Yeah, I just checked out the thread yesterday fully.
So not only did when Chris like retweeted,
it said like, not only is this canon,
it's actually canon to real life because of the dimensional merge.
This has been decreed as I understand it.
Yeah, I mean, it's, yes, but with the caveat that like
literally everything is canon to real life,
because Chris believes that basically all fiction occurs
in this other dimension called C197,
but it occurs all in one dimension,
not even in different dimensions.
Well, there might be, there are other dimensions,
but like the world where like cartoons live is C197.
And it is, our dimension is dimension 1218
that is merging with C197.
So this is why all cartoons are going to become real.
Does anime live in the same world as cartoons,
or does it have a separate anime dimension?
I would assume, yeah, I think it all happens in C197.
Well, you have a direct line to Chris now.
You can just ask these questions and get to you.
Yeah, like she followed me and she's,
okay, yeah, she's retweeting, okay.
She was retweeting the bits and pieces of the comic
and she was making comments about it.
She made a fucking huge 40 tweet long essay
about the comic, talking about why Nightstar did all that.
I talked to her a little bit and we discussed
why did Nightstar send the New Los Angeles City
and I said, oh, well, it's so they could learn
a valuable lesson about it.
She contacts me and she's like, this is the story.
I want to tell this in the show.
She contacts me and she's like, okay.
So fan, love the comic.
Love the comic, Ben.
Big fan of your work.
Definitely going to tell everyone to patron you
at patreon.com slash ben saint.
Nice.
But, Nightstar would never be so cruel
as to banish them to New Los Angeles.
She would never throw them through the portal,
but it's okay.
Oh boy, here comes the editorial comments
from the peanut gallery.
But it's okay.
We can explain it as a nightmare that they had.
And I'm like, all right, Chris, that's fine.
But consider this, she actually did them a favor
because she sent them through the portal
to learn a valuable lesson about friendship.
And she's like, oh my God, you're absolutely right.
Yep, no, you're right.
You're right.
That is what literally happened in real life.
She said, listen, this is true.
This is true.
I'm going to scroll back.
I want to quote her directly.
All right.
She says, oh, well, she was thrilled to meet
the creator of Phantom Horn.
Did she know Phantom Horn specifically?
Yes, she did.
I think she knows Phantom Horn and give and take
from TF2 analysis anarchy.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Okay.
Here we go.
Quote.
And keep in your mind, heart.
Wait, what?
Wait, hold on.
Keep your mind, heart, and mind's eye open.
You will personally meet Phantom Horn
and everyone else very soon in good tidings
and combined working efforts against our foes.
I sense the magic in you.
You shall do well for yourself, Ben.
Is that a private message?
This is a private message, she said to me.
So Christian can sense the magic in me.
Damn.
You have possibly like the first extreme,
like first party direct line of contact with Chris
for your part two of the Christian lecture.
I know.
Nothing has to be left of the speculation anymore.
I can get around the phone like during the lecture.
Yeah.
You know, I've been wondering,
you're a Christian guru.
A Christian historian, yeah.
How much like saying like,
oh, the dimensional merge is real life and stuff,
but then also coming to you,
the artist of a comic and explaining
like how what you wrote is like not true,
but then when you have told her
how it could be true, she has made it real,
but like here's how much of it is actually like,
like she's just being like a performer,
sort of like creating this fake,
you know, this idea of the dimensional mode,
like how much of it is actually real?
Here's what I think.
I think that to Chris,
an artist, someone who's creating a story
is basically like a prophet
and that they are basically receiving visions
from another world.
They have their glimpsing into another world
and seeing what is transpiring there.
So like...
Quick question on that front.
So I mean, you can debate the legitimacy of prophecy, right?
So it's not that like everything that everyone writes
is necessarily true, they can be wrong
and Chris can debate and say,
oh no, that can't be what actually happened, right?
If I were to come up with an OC right now on the spot
that did not exist before,
does that make that creation real by doing such?
Or was it already real?
I'm merely tapping into this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was already real.
You're just like realizing them.
You're communing with things beyond us.
You know, it's not even like this is a stupid idea.
Like I've had...
I mean, not that it's literally real,
but the idea that like everything fictional exists,
it's just like you have to tap into,
like when you have a great idea,
you know, your brain is like linked to this real character.
I mean, this isn't like a far out concept.
Yeah, it's like a cool, like a world connecting thing.
I know people who function with this mentality,
not like taking it seriously, but just for the sake of...
Yeah, what I'm curious about is how much of it is taken seriously.
And I guess you could never know, truly.
That's a good question.
Okay, what was the name for that?
Like there was the other kin,
and then there was like a faction of other kin
that believed that they were fictional characters.
And the idea was that...
Fiction kin?
Fiction kin, I think.
Is that right?
Okay, well, yeah, and the idea there was the same.
It's that like, you know, in an infinite multiverse,
all possibilities are true.
Therefore, every fictional idea you could possibly have
must have occurred in some alternate reality,
just by like matter of probability.
Therefore, every fictional character you know
does exist in some other timeline.
And therefore, it is possible for me
to be the reincarnation of Ty from Digimon.
Right, even granting all that is true.
To then go on and say, the dimensional merge is happening
with the cartoon world, and we will soon meet Sonichu and Mario,
and we will be best friends.
That's another step forward in the calculus.
That is a...that's kind of a new...
That's a relatively new development.
It's a bold new idea, yeah.
Some guys called the idea guys, I think,
put that idea into her head.
I mean, I think she probably wanted to...
The idea guys are a big thing.
This is something I need to research more,
because understanding modern Chris,
you cannot understand it without the idea...
And the idea guys are shrouded in mystery
because they are literally criminals
who fucking like embezzled and stole money from her.
They're not cool at all.
It's some of the stuff that they made her think is funny,
and they are bad guys who I hate.
You know, Ben, you've long claimed to be an idea guy yourself,
as I recall.
I'm an ideas man, not the idea guy,
not even the same.
I understand.
I'm going to feed this file, not a profile.
I think we're ignoring, though, a very important question.
I think we're wearing a very important question.
Nate, I recall a few scant years ago,
you sat in the very seat I'm sitting right now,
and turned down the opportunity to be in TF2 Analysis Anarchy.
How does it feel to know that that decision
closed the door on Chris Chan, recognizing you...
Chris will never know keg standard.
Well, we'll tell him how upset can I be,
being that I am merely a vessel through which we perceive
the events of the fictional universe that would happen
regardless of our interference.
Because we're just low immortals at the end of the day.
It was only the illusion of choice, Tom.
It was only the illusion of choice.
You have to tell yourself to let you sleep at night, Nate.
That's fine.
Oh, y'all know.
That's exactly what I will hear tonight.
No.
Okay.
In like Chris's first DMs, she says like,
you know, she says like,
oh, it's great to meet the creator of Phantom Horn.
I love Phantom Horn.
He's a pretty unicorn.
He's a great unicorn.
He's an inspiration.
I think the implication is that he's like a trans inspiration.
Although I didn't...
I wish I'd asked more about that,
but I didn't press her on it, but it doesn't matter.
Okay.
But she says like...
She's like, you know,
I loved you in...
You know what?
I'll just...
I'll just fucking find it.
She said something about like the lore.
There's like lore about Phantom Horn in an Alice's Anarchy.
I didn't even know.
Really?
Something shenanigans.
She says memes can be funny with a laughing emoji.
So that's great.
Agreed.
Hard agree.
Y'all have some common ground there.
That's great.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
I am a fan of blah, blah, blah, blah.
Dr. Wolfe does awesome work.
And getting into Anarchy during BronyCon in 18 and after,
I got to show and got to know and appreciate everyone else in that group as well.
Shame Phantom Horn was outside of the Respawn Generator range.
Oh, no.
Just working his oats and asserting his magical identity.
And I looked on everyone else's channels.
So I guess the idea is that Phantom was killed in Team Fortress 2
and Alice's Anarchy because he died,
but he was outside the range of the Respawn Generator or something.
Who came up with that?
Did it come up with that?
I don't know.
That was not addressed in the official videos.
Unless they mentioned it later.
Somebody needs to get in contact with Dr. Wolfe.
We got to nail down the details.
I wonder if people asked them like,
hey, what happened to that guy who was in the first episode and never came back
and someone had to be like,
oh, when he died, he was outside the Respawn Generator.
I know for a fact that they have done that with my character when I was replaced.
Really?
That same sort of thing.
They explained what happened to me.
Was it the same explanation?
What happened again?
No, no.
The thing with mine was like, when I left, I said,
tell them I left to become a pirate because I was doing the Pony Coast.
Oh, that's right.
So I was trying to make it all canon, all slot together neatly.
So I think they just reiterated that.
That I became a pirate.
Okay.
That's what I know.
Well, Phantom Horn is canonically dead.
He'll be like, everyone else died.
He's the...
No, literally, they fucking Zuckerberged him.
He got fucking Zuckerberged.
Do you guys know this terminology?
No.
I don't.
In Slime City, you can perm a kill somebody by Zuckerberging them
and you just have to make really sure that their body and slime don't get into the sewers
and they don't come back.
Okay, so you bury them in filthy dirt.
That's what Slime Corp did to Mark Zuckerberg
when they legally acquired Facebook and all social media.
You know, I criticized them, but it was probably the right move.
Yeah, I think so.
The amounts of capital generated really justify any eggs that needed to be broken.
They speak for themselves.
So yeah, I've been fucking drawing this Phantom Horn and Strawberry Milk
in New Los Angeles City Comic.
It's fucking great.
I'm cranking it out.
I'm very, very excited.
I've been very prolific.
Check it out on Twitter.
I'm cataloging it all in a big Imgir thread.
That's pretty cool.
My concern over the manipulation of Chris is at a low to medium, so that's not a big deal.
Low to medium?
Oh, what am I doing?
Oh, come on.
I don't know.
Telling it funny.
I'm having a goof.
I'm writing a comic.
I'm telling a story.
Yeah, literally the only thing that could be conceived of as bad is that you're shilling
and that's not even that bad because endless war is not like a paid thing.
You just jump in a discord.
Yeah.
I just want to fucking get the word out there and also it would be really cool if Chris
were to draw Phantom Horn or even better New Los Angeles City in the comic, which I
don't think is outside the realm of possibility because, oh, oh, sure.
Okay.
So Chris, okay, this is my final note on the subject if you want to move on, but Chris
was a little, okay, Chris did not disavow.
She didn't be like, okay, this is a troll.
It's never mind, right?
It wasn't like that.
She was still defending it even after the 9-11, right?
9-11, but she was clearly a little uncomfortable with the 9-11 thing, but she didn't say like,
this is not, she literally said in her responses, like, this is what Ben said.
She added me on Twitter.
She's like, this is what Ben saw happening in the timeline.
This is what he saw in C1 to 9-7, like this is canon, you know, and remember, this isn't
New York.
This isn't a real 9-11.
This is fake 9-11.
This isn't, this isn't the buildings.
It's all fine.
It's fine, guys.
It's fine.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, she went out of her way to establish that it's fine because no one was in the buildings,
but this event did happen and fucking Paradox Crocs and Sweet Mouse did these incredible
spiral pirouettes off the, oh my, you know, I got a huge laugh out of that moment.
I did not know where that was going when I saw that they performed yet.
This might be the best 9-11 yet.
That was tremendous.
A record-breaking 9-11.
That was a tremendous laugh.
Are you going to explain how the reviving system works so that minds can be said at
ease?
Ooh, no, I'm not going to spoil it.
Not going to spoil anything.
Ooh.
Okay, okay.
But what I wanted to say about that was, um, fuck.
Oh, no.
Where was it going with that?
Oh, no, no.
Dude, just describing the comic, you were talking about how Chris was talking about the 9-11
and saying that that was Canon still.
It was Canon, but she was a little uncomfortable with it.
Can't imagine why.
But, um, oh, no.
She said it was Canon anyway.
Yeah, but I was going somewhere.
Okay, you know what?
If you want to move on.
Well, you take a minute.
I have a question or two about this.
Yeah, sure.
Because one of the things that I had, me and Michelle were looking at the comic.
Here, think about it while I ask, yeah, we'll have a minute.
I was curious because it seems like the friendly folks over at Kiwi Farms seems to have taken
an interest in the comic and the Chris involvement here.
I'm just wondering, is that, what's going on with that?
Anything of note happening there?
Oh, wait, I remember.
Wait, I remember what I was going to say.
And that is that Chris said in one of her tweets that, don't worry guys, Phantom and
Strawberry are protected by fate because they still have big things ahead of them in, like,
back in their home, which makes me think that she might incorporate them.
And I don't know this for sure, but I want to believe that they might make a canonical
appearance.
And this is the most exciting thing.
Well, I mean, I mean, and when I say canonical, technically this is already canon because
Chris has canonized it.
But I mean, like, Chris might.
If Chris could actually draw them or draw, like, that would be so fucking happy.
Okay.
Phantom and Keg, I know, live in Ponyville.
Yes.
Maybe Strawberry Milk does as well.
Yeah, yeah, Strawberry Milk.
Does Chris's ponies live in Ponyville as well?
Who?
Are they there?
You know, Nightstar and whoever else?
Yeah, Nightstar lives in Ponyville, I think.
Okay, so they're from the same town.
Okay.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, they must be.
I'm almost positive that Nightstar.
I mean, Nightstar is kind of a dimension-hopping jet-setter fucking Rick type.
She's a Rick type.
She just goes all over the fucking place.
But I'm pretty sure she lives in Ponyville.
Yes.
Okay, so my question was, I noticed...
Oh, yeah, go on.
Yeah, that's all I was saying.
Yeah, Kiwi Farms.
Kiwi Farms is just noticing some of it because, like, because Chris was retweeting it, which
is pretty...
It's kind of funny.
I gotta say, I mean, I like...
I don't...
They did some fine work over at Kiwi Farms.
Okay.
They kind of do...
Like, I kind of appreciate that, like, you know, they document all of it.
And, you know, I can appreciate having a healthy interest in all that.
But I gotta say, the caliber of discussion on Kiwi Farms is poor.
They are...
Okay.
The guys on there are, like...
They're making literally decade-old observations and, like, acting like it's still funny, guys.
Like, they are behind the fucking curve on this Chris subject.
They really are...
Well, not everybody's an expert like you, Ben.
Maybe they're just getting up to speed.
Maybe.
It's kind of funny sometimes.
Largely, I'm not impressed with what they're doing over there.
I mean, whatever.
Keep on keeping on, guys.
But try to do better.
I don't know.
They're like...
Remember that time with...
Remember that time Chris hit that guy with her car?
Well, they all stalwartly stick to using he-him, which really annoys me, but whatever.
I'm sure I'm not gonna convince anyone over there to do anything about that, so...
Unlikely.
I don't know.
Do better, guys.
Do better Kiwi Farms.
I believe in you.
Okay.
That's interesting.
Anyway, that's what I have to say about that.
I was wondering if they were causing some any issues or...
They were talking a bit...
No, no, it's fine.
We're talking a little...
I checked the Chris thread in there.
We're talking a little bit about...
Okay, Chris keeps misnaming it New Milwaukee.
Yeah, I saw that.
Even over and over again, I say Neo Milwaukee.
I saw other people being like,
I don't know what the fuck this New Milwaukee is.
I was like,
No, you have to say the full name.
Neo Milwaukee, A-K-A.
Yes, I know, but that's not what it's called.
That's not what it's called.
It's unacceptable.
New York.
That's how we should...
The Los Angeles City, A-K-A, Neo Milwaukee.
God damn it.
Get it right.
Put some respect on the name.
Chris, come on.
I'm a little concerned...
I mean, it's too early to...
I'm a little concerned that maybe Chris might have been put off by the 9-11 thing,
because it's been like a whole day,
and she hasn't liked any of my tweets or retweeted anything I said.
And I'm freaking out over here, guys.
It's been like a solid 24 hours.
That's what happens when you fly too close to the sun.
You're nervous at all times about that melting wax.
Yeah, you gotta put some more content out.
I guess I gotta put some more content out, and I will.
I've told a couple of people I have the entire arc of...
Basically, this is like chapter one.
I have basically the entire rest of the chapter plotted out.
I know exactly what's gonna happen.
It might even be done by the time this episode comes out,
but not necessarily,
because we're probably more than halfway through it,
or close to it anyway.
But I'm really fucking on this hype train.
It's very exciting to me.
It is very interesting.
I'm having a lot of fun with it.
I don't mean to say this in a critical way,
but it strikes me that I think you'll have very little problem
continuing to have Chris's attention,
because it really does strike me that anybody who made...
Obviously, I like your art a lot,
but anybody who made favorable artwork of Chris's OCs,
he's going to love it.
I love it when people make art centered around the things I do.
Yeah, you're right.
That's a positive prospect.
You know what I think it might be?
It's not that she was upset about the 9-11 thing.
Maybe it's just that Nightstar herself
has not been in any panels in a while.
That is definitely going to be an issue.
Nightstar is more of a background presence right now.
At the very end, we'll see Nightstar again.
Because for anyone that's not aware,
the framing that I have set up for this
is that this is basically...
Phantom Horn is the Twilight Sparkle to Nightstar's Celestia,
and that Nightstar has tasked him with writing her letters,
telling him about the friendship lessons
that he learns along the way.
His adventure is in New Los Angeles City.
Here's a quick screenwriting lesson here.
What if you got two characters at some point in the discussion,
Nightstar should be mentioned at least once.
Whenever Nightstar is in the room,
the subject of the matter should be about Nightstar,
and whenever Nightstar is not present,
everyone should be asking,
Where's Nightstar?
This is the wrap to success.
Okay, no, unironically,
I should find any excuse to depict Nightstar.
Whenever anyone talks about her,
I should put a little face of her in the corner.
Ben, have her dimension hop in.
She can do this shit.
Have her pull at Chris and pop into the narrative
and lecture at length about...
Whatever, I don't know.
She can pop out of the dimensional rift
just like Chris would pop out of a time void.
To punch that guy in Four Cent Garbage Towers.
You gotta have a legendary moment.
Try and have a fake friendship lesson.
Try and get back to Ponyville quickly
and just dimension hop in.
Give him a lecture.
I can tell that you're faking,
and then pop back out.
That'll get Chris's attention again.
It will.
Just having Nightstar in the panel
is like, that's what it's gonna take.
We all know narratively,
the way you're writing it is better and good
to have these guys go do things.
Nightstar is like the omniscient god
organizing all this stuff to happen.
The Rick, exactly as you said.
Doing things and opting much more important things
and really shouldn't waste your time on this.
But you have to pay that cost.
You have to pay the piper to keep Chris's ear.
I mean, my purpose here is twofold, right?
There's the tie-in with Chris and Sonichu
and that cannon, right?
So that's the Nightstar angle.
But also, I want this to be a showcase
of New Los Angeles City and RFCK.
Of course.
So right now, I'm focusing on the RFCK.
You should have Nightstar in, like doing a tour.
Being like, wow, look at all these wondrous sights
and sounds of Neo Milwaukee.
Well, did you see the part with Discord?
Yes.
Yeah, we're Discord.
I think it's a lovely little town.
That's true.
It's pure chaos.
I'm thinking of getting a summer home there.
Ah.
And great Discord impression.
Okay, one more thing about the Kiwi Farms, right?
This is the level of Kiwi Farms discussion.
Like, they'll literally just make posts
like, they'll literally just post something
to be like, boy, Chris sure is stupid.
Like, boy, Chris sure is delusional.
Like, huh, Chris?
Boy, he sure is delusional.
And it's like, yeah, great, great observation.
Like, I'm so, I'm really impressed
that you were able to make this trenching point
about like the nature of Chris
and what's going on with that.
Like, okay, fuck off, right?
Like, yeah, we can move past this.
We can move past, I have moved past this
to more fruitful ground, all right?
I'm doing something with my life, right?
I'm actually doing something about it, right?
Okay.
This is what separates the casual trolls
from the true Christians,
is being able to move past the surface and dig deep.
Like, I get it.
It's wacky.
It's funny, all right?
We can all see that.
We can agree that that's true
and then move on to like, okay, what now?
What's next after we've all acknowledged this?
You guys are acting straight like level five crooks
when you need to be acting like level 100 bosses.
This is your main issue.
Exactly right.
Couldn't have said it better myself.
Well, there's that.
There's the scoop, I guess.
There's the story.
Not to monopolize the conversation or anything,
but the Kickstarter, the Vapors 2 Kickstarter
is going like gangbusters.
We're over, it's over 6,000.
At 666, we're doing communism.
Everybody gets a dollar.
Everyone who, well, and then I'm thinking,
I'm thinking that the next stretch goal,
and I don't know when this is going to be,
it'll probably be a couple thousand beyond,
maybe eight or nine or 10, I don't know.
The next one, the next stretch goal will be,
you know, my St. Hart logo,
a little St. Hart in the circle.
I'm just going to make that a pin,
but I'm just going to give it to everyone for free.
Like, if we hit whatever the goal, the next goal is,
I think like,
Oh, that reminds me.
New pin and everyone gets one.
Everyone, yep, and that's just going to be a backer word
for everyone who backed the Kickstarter,
is just a new pin and everyone gets it,
and that's going to be a cool one.
I've been thinking about making that pin anyway,
but I didn't have any,
I didn't like where the fuck would I sell it under what,
this is it, this is the time.
So that's what we're going to do after the next stretch goal.
I saw comments on our latest piece of the episode,
someone said like,
it's illegal to send money through the mail
because remember the plan you had with sending...
I don't give a shit.
I don't care about that.
I read that, I can't possibly believe that that's the case.
I think it is like frowned upon,
if not outright illegal, but who cares?
Nobody, yeah, I'm sure nobody sends like $1 bills
to send money for family,
for happy birthday, here's $20.
Maybe they do gift cards.
Sending money in the mail is like
making money off a Minecraft server.
It might be looked down upon, but nobody cares.
You're not supposed to do it.
But you're going to do it anyway.
I did look at the terms of service,
because I was worried about this,
as like a Kickstarter terms of service thing.
Did I talk about this last episode?
I hope I'm not repeating myself.
No, I don't think so.
Well, okay, I'll tell you.
I'm interested.
Okay, I thought maybe it might be
against Kickstarter terms of service, but it's not.
The things that are prohibited,
you're not allowed to build a Kickstarter
in such a way that backers will profit, right?
Sure, sure.
You're not allowed to do a Kickstarter
where backing the project gives you
future equity in a business, you know what I'm saying?
But that's not what the...
And you're not allowed to structure
so that backers make a profit.
But that's not what I'm doing.
I'm basically just giving a $1 refund.
And it's only to people who actually get a physical thing.
So you had to spend $15 and more.
So that's not what this is.
It's just a $1 discount in the form of a physical dollar bill.
I don't think you're fine.
You might see it as.
So I'm pretty sure...
So there's nothing in the terms of service
that says that this is not okay.
You would have to like...
You would have to interpret it pretty...
You would have to do some acts of...
some pretty active reinterpretation to get there.
If you wanted to fucking fan me
and cancel me off this project.
Maybe it's worth reaching out to them
just to make sure.
But I mean, it sounds fine to me.
I don't fucking know.
All right, Ben.
Here's the important question.
This is like everything we've been talking about
so far is leading up to this.
Vapors 3 Kickstarter.
Chris Chan, Vaporette, make it happen?
Yes or yes?
Dude.
Now, can Chris really be expected
to generate something of this nature
to someone else's script?
I feel like...
I'm skeptical.
I mean, Chris did do that one crossover page.
You know, she was doing the crossover
with like Planet Dolan.
But she did like one page
and then it fell apart.
So, you know...
I feel like it would be an uphill battle
to get that to happen.
You got at least a year
to figure it all out.
I think I just got another backer.
Did I?
Yes.
Yes, I fucking did.
Who is it?
Okay, it's a real name.
I'm not going to say the real name.
Their name's Chris, but it's not that Chris.
Oh, man.
Thank you.
Excellent.
Dab.
Looking...
I'm very much looking forward to my rewards.
What was it?
Oh, yeah, Planet Dolan.
Okay, I mean, I'm going to try it.
I'm really excited that, like, Chris wants to talk to me.
Even if it's just because she thinks that I'm her...
Oh, she messaged you too, Hippo, right?
Hippo?
Oh, Hippo's...
Oh, there it is.
Okay.
Like, even if it's just because she thinks we're her in
with the analysis anarchy crowd, I don't care.
I'm excited to have this relationship.
I want to nurture it, right?
I want to water it.
Like the Truffula Tree.
Like the Truffula Tree in Needville.
Let it grow.
And so, I don't know.
Yes.
Crossovers is Chris Chan.
Definitely happening.
Dab.
That's what's up.
Okay, I've talked for a long time about my shit.
Well, that's cool stuff.
Hey, I've got an update to an ongoing...
Kickstarted.com.
Slash.
Project.
Ben Slane.
Slash.
Vapors2.
No spaces, no underscores.
Type it in your URL bar right now.
Link in the description.
Link to charity and that charity is me.
There you go.
All right.
Be me.
Nate.
Best person on the planet.
I'm at the movies yesterday.
Me and Michelle, we went to see It Part 2.
Pretty decent.
Not terrible.
It was okay.
So we're watching it.
As we're watching, having a good time and the nice comfy chairs they got.
I hear some loud voices like talking in the theater.
I've had very few experiences with people being loud in the theater before.
But in this case, it was happening.
It was like a seat directly behind us.
It was like a few people.
It was a few women making noise.
And I was like, oh man, what are these?
I'm not going to turn around and look at them.
It wasn't enough to be particularly distracting.
But it was a horror movie.
And I heard him saying things like, oh lord, don't go in there.
I wouldn't go in there.
You're going to die and things of this nature.
And I had a flashback.
I had a flashback to a few PCP episodes ago.
Where when Jesse, the man, Endless Jess was saying, black people be yelling at the screens.
It's not racist.
You know it's true.
And I had a brain blast.
I thought to myself, could it be true?
Could this possibly be the experience that Jesse had described previously on this very
podcast?
Wait, were they of the black persuasion?
I had no idea.
I was just sitting there in my theater watching a movie.
You had no idea.
I didn't turn around.
I didn't turn around and look.
I didn't want to be, I don't know, weird.
I thought you were going to bring up Jesse saying when he punched somebody in the face
in the movie theaters.
I thought you were going to fucking deck that.
Some people were making noise throughout the whole movie.
I thought you were going to earn your name for a change, best guy ever.
These people were making a bunch of noise.
There was a bunch of women all together.
The end of the movie, I finally trampled, turned around.
And indeed it do be like that sometimes.
Black people do be yelling at the screen.
And I just want to let everybody know.
You've just set our culture back decades.
It's true.
It might have been the case, but you shouldn't say it.
Look, Emerson, it do be like that sometimes, of course.
We can't make any generalizations here.
Cool.
But I grew up a little bit that time.
What a fascinating experience.
Jesse, I stand with you, brother.
But that's it.
That's my whole story.
And I'm using anecdote from the life of one great best man.
Pre-conceptions confirmed.
Established for the first and very first time.
Yes.
I was like a virgin, untainted, but now I know.
Sad.
All right.
What else is going on?
Mage, Tom, what's new in your life?
All I've been doing for the past week and three days is the stupid Minecraft server.
I wake up at 6 a.m.
How dare you call it stupid?
It's a great Minecraft server.
Stupidly brilliant.
It's going to be a wonderful time.
Okay.
Yeah.
I can tell you've been working.
These screenshots you post, I'm amazed.
I'm amazed by what I'm seeing.
You will see it one day soon.
It's so cool.
I mean, you will be blown away.
I'm glad.
Really excited about it.
The thing is, I haven't even just been building because there's like, I've never really hosted
a server before.
I didn't even know much about Minecraft hosting servers before I took on this thing.
I thought it would be a bit faster or a bit easier.
Don't get me wrong.
Now that I know these things that I know, it is quite not as difficult.
But when I just jumped into this and I was just like, and I don't know how to swim.
I'm just like, oh my God, I'm drowning in this.
Me and Mage have been, she's been doing all the heavy lifting.
I've been her test dummy on occasion.
Obviously she's worked 10 times as much as me, probably more so.
When you see what she's done, I built myself a little house out to the south of spawn point.
I'm going to build a road out to it.
Finally established.
Come pay me a visit.
Am I a wonderful little house I've got?
I said in the comments of the last episode that we would never abandon Bufalantopia.
Oh my God.
Why would you lie to people like that?
Okay.
Well, you know, we will build a new and better Bufalantopia.
Bufalantopolis.
I like Bufalantopia with the number two in there.
We'll vote on it.
And then I will fucking seize the means and ignore the results of the elections.
One of the first things I did when I got into the new server for testing, I caught a Bufalant.
I'm riding my Bufalant around.
Very good.
Keep it going.
Okay.
All right.
We can make it work.
And just for those who are crying about Bufalantopia, it's going to be obliterated in eight months,
no matter what we do.
Less than eight months right now.
So less than eight months now.
That's server.
That server is like closing.
It's a ticking time bomb.
Okay.
Why would we live there?
That's better to get out sooner.
Yeah.
So part of the reason, a very small part of the reason why we are making the server is
just because I didn't particularly want to work on the Bufalantopia server, not the server
of the town.
Just because I know it's coming.
I knew the militia is coming.
So why?
It's a black cloud over our heads.
I was going to make the coolest house, but why am I doing this?
By the time I'm done, it's just going to be erased.
So Mage did indeed seize the means of production from the authority and has established her
own kingdom now and it is a glorious one.
One day, I spent one entire day just trying to program shopkeepers into the game that could
sell the vanilla blocks and buy the vanilla minecraft blocks and it almost nuked the whole
server.
That's how bad it was.
Thankfully, I was graced by the presence of one kind stranger because I am in the server
for the Pixelmon.
Sometimes I ask for help and don't always receive the help, but yeah, this one person
was like, hey, I wouldn't mind looking at the logs.
I have a minute.
Oh, that's nice.
Yeah, and that minute turned into several hours and he didn't know why my server was
breaking down and oh, that was so much trouble.
I had to completely, thankfully, I made backups of the server before messing with it.
So I made the backup, I started messing with it and it just kept going to shit.
Every time I restarted the server, just more and more errors popped up.
I was like, what is this?
This is spreading this curse.
I had to completely reset the server to the previous state I had saved, thankfully.
I didn't do anything other than trying to mess with the NPC.
It's like, how difficult can it be to just program a stupid NPC to stand there and sell
blocks to you and buy blocks from you?
And I told the guys, I'm going to scream if the error is literally just one misplaced
comma or something.
Okay, and I was wrong.
It was three misplaced commas.
It was slightly more than that, but very slightly.
Just a few syntax errors, something like that.
Like three commas, then one apostrophe or something like that.
I don't remember exactly.
Syntax errors are the worst because you're just like, how am I so dumb?
Why is this not working?
And it's just like, oh, I hit the wrong key.
I was so tired.
My vision was blurry.
I was scrolling through like hundreds of lines of code trying to find the one misplaced
comma.
Damn.
It was awful.
I'd like to take a look at this sometime, just for fun, if it's available.
Listen to all this pain that Mage has gone through, and you're going to sit there and
not give us money on whatever we end up deciding to use to find this.
Fuck you, buddy.
I mean, are we allowed to talk about what I'm seeing in these screenshots?
Yeah, but they're kind of the episodes that we're probably going to have a video posted
showing off the server, so go ahead.
I mean, I'm seeing.
I mean, okay, I just, there's a fucking, there's a big ol' like battle arena.
There's the saloon.
There's an endless war made out of slime.
The arena, there's the Royal Rumble Arena of PCP.
Okay, I don't know if this is like a mod thing or if they have this in vanilla.
There are like light blocks, right, that are illuminated.
I want to go in.
I want to make his eye out of light blocks.
I could, but the light blocks are yellow.
I can make them as light as they can.
What's the eye color of the pupil, the very center?
I think it's black.
You know, it's kind of open to it.
The pupil's black, but like, it's open to interpretation, really.
Just as long as it looks like an eye.
Okay, I'll do that.
You won't be able to mess with stuff at the spawn, so all these buildings,
you won't be able to break blocks or anything.
Actually, no, the eye is green.
I did make it like, actually, it is kind of like a green glass
that has like black borders around it.
It's a fancy new block, so I nailed it both on both fronts.
I mean, I might fuck with it.
I might go in and just fuck around with it.
You won't be able to.
I don't know, but I can't.
You can't.
You won't be able to.
No one can get in except me and Mage until they get whitelisted.
But even after that, other than me, no one will have any sort of extra privileges.
Not even if you're an ACP.
Oh, that's true.
Everyone's equal then.
Everyone's equal.
Except for Mage.
I am God.
I have privileges.
You can't.
If I wanted to make some minor cosmetic modifications,
you couldn't just give me some temporary modifications or something?
No, I can't.
There's only two roles.
The admin role and the default role.
And making a new role is like too much trouble, honestly.
I don't want to bother.
I can't.
Let me know what you want changed and I'll do it.
I don't mind.
I mean, that's fine.
One spawn is done.
You've made it a lot of work.
These should be the whole start of the spawn point area with all our buildings that we've got.
Basically, this should be a thing where we modified at the very beginning.
We can probably give Mage notes if things need to change.
Actually, she and I changed a couple of little things here and there.
But once that's done, this is done forever.
The rest of the world can be modified at our pleasure.
I actually spent a bit of today outlining the spawn area, so to speak.
If you press J and open up the map, you'll see white dots outlining the area you cannot build in.
That's very helpful.
Yeah, directly outside of it, you'll be able to build.
Okay, well, I might give you a couple of minor design notes.
Okay, but each floor is a themed floor based on the gym leader that is inside the floor.
That sounds incredible.
That sounds so cool.
It is incredible.
Mage has been an amazing amount of work detailing all the spawn area things with dope-ass items.
I'm legitimately excited, and I fucking hate my friends.
You all should feel excited.
This is just the tip of the iceberg.
Go watch the video that's either up already or coming out soon.
You will be excited.
You will brain blast your fucking dick.
Suck on that.
I can't wait to build my mud hut.
My mud hut metropolis.
Wait a minute.
Mage, you said you were building a place, a hole in the ground for PvP.
What about the mud puddle?
That's a hole in the ground.
I could.
How should it look like?
The mud puddle is basically just swampy.
If you've ever seen a Dark Souls swamp, it's basically that, but with Germans in it.
With who?
Count me out.
What's the reference?
The reference is like the mud puddle.
My Discord server is filled with Germans for some reason, and that's funny.
That's funny.
Mage, you just got to look up a German flag somewhere.
And you'll get some aesthetic reference.
I guess I'll have to tell the Spaniards as well.
It's a very EU server.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to theme it properly.
Okay, I'll consider mudpull it, but I'm also considering the theming it RFCK because it is PvP sort of thing.
We don't want everything to be all RFCK.
That was how fucking I wanted the RFCK.
They get all wrapped up in their little gang wars.
No, it's thematically makes sense.
If it's PvP, RFCK is PvP.
I get it.
I mean, we already have the Royal Rumble Arena.
That seems like a good place for PvP.
No, that's Pokemon.
And that's not PvP.
No, that's Pokemon battles.
I mean, that's not RFCK.
I was considering thinking maybe every now and then we can host Pokemon tournaments,
and then I gift a Legendary or something to the winner.
Yeah, it sounds great.
Actually, while I was building, Legendaries kept spawning around me from time to time,
so I would capture them and they're going to be in my gift reservoir.
I'm not going to keep any of them.
I see you've got a Xerneas and a Varisian here.
I have such dreams.
Listen to all this work you just done.
Listen to all the slaving away she's done for this project, and it's barely even like two weeks in.
If you guys don't give money and join this project, it's clear that you just hate women.
So if you don't want to.
Yeah, that's, you know, it's hard to dispute.
I just think, you know, the fact that the economy values this work at $0 is unacceptable.
This is why we need Yang.
This is why we need UBI, you know.
That's not true.
This is why we need UBI.
Vote Bernie.
We, you know, talk of coding.
I've been, I've been like half-heartedly doing a coding thing.
And it relates to the mud puddle.
I was using Java just because I don't know anything and I was sort of like fucking around.
But I wanted to make a discord bot for my server called Endless Mud.
And the only thing in my discord at the moment is that there's tears.
There's rolls, which are just like burgundy blood, like all the bloods from the Hemo Spectrum from Homestuck.
Red Man Me has all the blood.
And I can bestow blood upon others if they ask.
But I kind of want like an endless mud bot to like give people the rolls.
And just that in itself was like a gargantuan task because discord is not that easy to work with.
There was a lot of tutorials and I burnt myself out.
But I got this thing working where in my own personal server, if I run the bot on my computer, I have it open.
Then I can type, exclamation point, get blood.
And then Endless Mud will respond with, you get blood.
And that's as far as I got.
Nothing actually changes.
There's no currency or anything.
But that's, it's hard.
God coding is hard.
I couldn't even imagine like making something like Endless War.
Yeah, um, crack.
You know, I try, I was like, I was like, I was like, I know, I'll open up a like a beginner Python tutorial and start from absolute scratch and try and make this spot.
I can make this spot.
It would have been so much harder than I thought.
And then crack just came along and was like, I can make it.
And like, I could never have done the stuff.
Like, like, I didn't know anything about databases, right?
It's all like database.
It's database based and it's based.
And um, I don't know.
He fuck crack fucking made it happen.
I don't know.
I don't know if anyone else.
I mean, I don't know.
It's fucking the point.
What I'm saying is how it actually works like, like the nuts and bolts of it.
That's like its baseline level, how RFCK works.
It's like completely beyond my understanding.
Like, like getting it to, to work with discord is the hardest part.
And it's the first step.
Do you know that took like three or four days of like dying at the computer?
Like, I just want to, you ever feel like when you're working on something that's
stressing you out, it's like really difficult that you just sort of like heat up.
And then the back, your back sort of feels prickly.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
I know that in a way that you're getting frustrated.
That's like, yeah.
I think just doesn't work.
You don't know like, oh my God.
I know the, the hot.
I know the heat, the heat of rage.
Yeah.
I want to, I got that a lot.
I don't, my back doesn't get prickly, but I'm sure I have other physical symptoms.
Oh, it's so annoying.
And my back or like, like below the stomach as well.
I just get so frustrated because of the, I feel like it more frustrated because of
the heat rather than whatever upset me.
Yeah.
It's like, oh, this is happening again on top of all this stress.
I need to go outside and jump in a ice bath like.
Yeah.
I just want to.
It's all that blood you have boiling over.
I just want to quickly say to the editor of this episode, I'm, my audio might have
distinct at least two times so far.
I'm not sure.
So just check in on that.
Okey dokey.
We'll sync at the end.
Hopefully.
Sorry.
My oblivion has had to deal with it as well.
Frile by fire.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
All right.
It just like starts lagging and like HIPAA was lagging out really bad for me, but the,
so I couldn't, I couldn't hear it most times.
It should like reorient.
I think it's mostly discord.
Yeah.
Unless you're looking at the, the play head and it's sort of lagging itself.
Well, this, this is why we sync.
This is why we sync at the beginning and end now.
It helps.
Yeah.
I think I might have been partly responsible because of that because of the.
It was me.
It was, for some reason, my audio was, it would always like get like a second out of sync
by the end of most episodes.
I think some of it is to do with like the bit rate of the recording.
Like if our, if an audacity is like 40,000 something something.
We should, we should all have like a hundred versus 48,000.
Okay.
After this episode, we should all like set the project rate, whatever, to a certain rate.
So we're all on the same rate.
I'm recording it.
I mean, I don't know.
This is inside baseball.
This is, this is extreme inside baseball right now.
They're not supposed to see this.
Okay.
Instead of this.
It's just literally speaking out of the computer.
I, when I look at these Minecraft images, I want to build, I've already got a house
that's okay.
It needs a lot more, but I want to build some sort of BGE face floating in the sky, smugly
smiling down and everyone like a new son.
That's one thing I want.
And then also I would love to build a slime corp HQ skyscraper building somewhere.
Yeah.
I would hope that I can lie with the degenerates of the RFCK server and we can team up and
construct this, this office building.
It was extremely cold clinical, you know, no soul only calculated numbers.
It's just a cube, just a cold steel cube.
Oh, that reminds me with that little logo on top.
There are, there'll be like places in the spawn that you can buy within game currency.
Literally just in game, you won't be able to buy it with any other currency.
Just making it clear.
Can we sell in game currency for real currency?
No.
You can sell it for slime corp.
Oh, but maybe we should make the server free and just fill it with Minecraft.
That sounds like a great business plan.
No.
And ironically, it's whatever business is doing, right?
No, no.
I have such a grand vision of like, okay, let's say we buy like a little plot near the spawn.
We build slime corp HQ there.
But the thing is, you can make permission set so that only, like I was already testing this.
Like you can have like pressure plates or switches that only activate with people you've given permission to.
So we could give specifically access to slime corp HQ only to employees of slime corp and everybody else just gets kept out and they cannot even enter the building.
There are slightly different sizes of the plot you can get and like the prices reflect that.
So, you know, you gotta get a big one.
Yeah.
There's like fellow executives team up with me.
Like the bigger ones and like the large ones are just for you to flex there.
They are the most expensive ones and they're by the crew layer by the horseshoe crew layer.
I haven't posted a screenshot of that horseshoe crew layer.
I can't wait to buy the smallest plot I can get and just build like the tiniest little castle.
Just like the most minuscule little like just little purple stone tower or something.
Speaking of Tiny Ben.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
My gun girl, the one of my cop killer OC.
In Endless War you can create slimeoid pets and I made Tiny Baby Ben Saint.
I love it.
I loved it so much.
Tiny Baby Ben Saint's first day of slimeoid school.
Make sure to kill anyone who fucks with you.
Have fun.
Let me read the description of Tiny Baby Ben Saint.
Gun girl, you are accompanied by Tiny Baby Ben Saint, a one foot tall slimeoid.
It is vaguely humanoid.
It sounds just like me so far.
Its face is a single huge eye.
It walks on legs.
It crackles with stored electrical energy.
It is covered in a coating of slippery oil, again just like me.
It can generate harmful frequencies with its brain waves.
It is usually staring off into space.
Its dark purple hue gives it a brooding edgy appearance.
It will huff and groan when given orders, like a teenage, like a teenage,
rebelling against his mom in the most flaccid way possible.
It has just a little bit of moxie, almost no grit, and almost no chutzpah.
A pitiable baby, this slimeoid has no clout whatsoever.
It has overalls adorned.
That's the in-game description of Tiny Baby.
It's adorable, please protect him.
I love him.
I'm honored.
He's just such a perfect little guy.
I always walk, exclamation point walks slimeoid.
I would have to agree.
And with the whole apartment things, I've got an apartment,
and you can change the apartment description.
Something about him just makes me trust him.
I have Gun Girl's apartment description.
She's got a gun workbench and Tony Hawk Pro Skater and a PS1.
Yes, we have real estate. There is real estate in RFC Canaan.
Also, just outside the kitchen is a playpen covered in oil.
Tiny Baby Benzane gets brought home after a long day of fishing and stuff,
and she puts him in the playpen while she plays Tony Hawk.
That's the law, and I really love it.
Speaking of real estate, I didn't get to finish about the Minecraft server.
Sorry for going back to it.
I'm just really excited because I said that people will be able to make claims
and they'll be able to sell claims and buy claims and stuff,
hence the little towns.
I'm really excited, or at least hopeful.
This is going to turn into a capitalist night.
It's already going down there.
I really hope that people will buy those plots and build really neat things
and have a little town.
Are they pre-existing plots that are set up ahead of time,
or can you define your own plot and buy them?
No, I set up because there's limited space in these spawns,
so I set them up.
Smaller ones are cheaper, bigger ones are more expensive,
and they're like the flex plots that I call them because they're super expensive.
In all directions out, take a fucking step beyond spawn,
and there's tons of space in there.
I went south quite a ways to build my house.
Okay, I just don't know how this works.
In the server right now, you can basically just go anywhere
and just set up a plot for yourself.
Can you still do that?
Yep, this is just like...
Oh, this is like crime re-existing.
Yeah, basically if you want your structure to be in your spawn
where everyone starts and stuff.
Okay, I get it.
Is the map going to be endlessly spawning, or is there a cap?
Because a map that keeps going will inevitably...
There should be some cap.
It should be really big, but there should be some cap
because people like to travel forever in a server without a cap,
and it lacks the server however many chunks have been created.
I'll look into that, if you have a point to have and consider that.
Just to reduce processing demands,
putting a limit on the rendering distance.
I have no idea how Minecraft works.
Does that render stuff?
But also, if people are so spread out, they won't interact as much,
and we want them to be players in the game world.
But it's part of the fun of Minecraft is exploring
and finding your own little corner.
Okay, alright, so we'll figure it out.
We'll optimize.
This server is going to be ribbed for your pleasure, dear viewer.
It's happening. It's coming, so you better get ready for it.
I'm kind of high for it, honestly.
I'm looking in the Patreon chat here and there.
I see people being like, you know,
suddenly I'm getting that craving.
I'm getting that craving to mine, and to craft,
and to explore, and to spelunk, and to soar in the skies.
Can we set up a military police state
that will punish anyone who mines at night?
I think a faction should exist and be formed in this Minecraft world,
specifically to do so.
Yeah, like, there's a team that goes out mining at night,
and then there's another team that goes out,
like, specifically to just, like, fight.
You know, I was going to say,
alright, the sun's going down, everyone,
get your weapons ready.
Okay, quickly, PvP is disabled for the overall,
but the PvP is enabled for the nether.
So, like, so be careful in the nether.
It's okay, though.
These cops can still enforce the business.
For example, if you catch someone mining at night,
and you're an agent of the law,
then, oh, I don't know,
maybe drop a couple of stacks of TNT
at important places in their mine,
and just let loose, you know?
Let God do its justice.
What's the thing with, like, in 2B2T,
that people would, like, fight with beds?
Oh, because they explode in the nether or something.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you could fall asleep on the bed,
like, yeah, you explode.
I don't know how you fight with that.
Like, that's the only way to, like, kill someone through.
They're, like, fully upgraded diamond armor.
It's, like, the, like, I don't know.
It's a massive explosion.
Something about that, yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
So, we'll work on that.
We'll get that going.
It'll be exciting for everybody.
It's gonna be great, everybody.
We've been working on it a long time.
I've been playing around, goofing around in there quite a bit.
Very, very happy.
Very excited.
All right.
Well, any, what else is going on?
We could just go to the voicemails.
I mean, I got them ready to go.
Hippo is, I don't know, he's got any shit to raise.
Yeah, any developments, developments in anyone's life, huh?
Any juicy, juicy drama?
No drama.
I made soup today.
That's the only drama.
I did, I have been marathoning the Angry Video Game Note again.
He has those, the seasons of his show, which consolidate an entire year's worth of episodes,
like season one to ten, I think.
He's got more years than that.
He's been doing it.
Season four and five, I think, is the peak.
But watching all of those again really puts me, puts you in the mood to do the video game review thing.
I've been thinking about it a little bit.
Oh, man.
I've been thinking about, like, it's not like I'm secretly, desperately wanting to come back and making videos,
because I often have ideas that I'm like, well, too bad I don't like doing the video thing.
I'll just, you know, think about it, and that'll be the thing I think about.
But I do want, like, I would like a good reason to come back.
I just can't think of one.
Dark Cloud 3 comes out.
The dream.
Because, like, I was thinking about, like, the point of the reviews initially.
It was because I wanted to tell people about certain games that I like,
and so that they know about them, and explain why they're good.
And I just feel like that, like, ran its course, and I don't feel like I need to explain that,
because so many games are completely covered by thousands of people.
And there's, like, the only thing that's, like, could be unique is to do, like, obscure games.
But I don't really give a shit about obscure things, if I don't know them.
It was, like, a very limited thing from the beginning.
Sure.
And then there's, like, oh, well, do it for fame.
Like, YouTube fame is stupid. Do it for money.
You'll never make money on YouTube. That's a stupid idea.
Like, there's a lot of, and, like, content that is, it's just the reason.
Like, I don't know. I don't know what reason I could have to make videos again.
But it would be nice if I could find one.
So you have the general desire, but no specific plan at the moment.
I like the idea of having a legacy like AVGN that's, like, ah, remember Hippocrates.
I mean, people do, like, occasionally, somebody references one of my videos, and I'm like,
ah, you remember. I don't even remember.
And it's, it's nice.
I remember.
And it's, like, I clearly don't have the same sort of clean record, because I stopped and started so many times,
and it took such a long time for so few videos, and not all of them are, like, that great.
I did a whole, like, tier list video of my reviews at one point on Give and Take.
Right.
But, like, if I came back and I keep making videos and they're good, and it's, like, really cool,
then I, people would, it would be good, and it would be like,
maybe you could get money and patrons from it, and I'm like, I don't know.
I mean, yeah, you obviously did them because you enjoyed doing them, at least at a part.
And I doubt that urge will ever completely go away.
So, yeah, I mean, I eagerly await the next video, if and when, do you ever make one?
Well, yeah, there's no plans, really.
It's just sort of, if I ever do it again, I want to be sure that I know what I'm doing.
Like, I could say, oh, yes, I'm making a show, and it's called Hippocrite,
and this is the conceit of the show, and this is how many episode ideas I have.
Like, if I was pitching it to, like, a TV studio or something,
what is the purpose of this? I need to answer those questions.
That's a very good point, and I think a lot of people, yeah, like,
when everybody starts their YouTube with, like, a good idea,
but as you keep going and you get into the thing of, like, I'm a guy who does YouTube now,
then you're like, ooh, I gotta make something now.
Gotta, like, find something, and then that spark can definitely go away.
I certainly know what that is like, but, yeah, I mean, ultimately,
you want to be in a place where, like, you're doing YouTube
and you're purely doing the things that you love and you're passionate about,
and I would say probably because you know that you'll be fine no matter what.
And, like, if you've got, like, a great other career
that, like, allows you to just do YouTube as a hobby
and you don't need to make it successful, you can just do exactly what you want to do,
that's a pretty great place to be.
That's definitely the thing, like, it's in a hobby territory at the moment.
It's just, if I, like, making something as long or as intense
as, like, one of those skit heavy, like, YouTube reviews of stuff,
then it would take a lot of time, and I would need a very good reason to spend that sort of time.
And I feel like spending not so much time on it, making it, like, less of an interesting product,
is, like, completely a waste of time.
I'd rather, like, have a good idea and find the time to put it together
than, like, come back half-heartedly and say,
I'm just sort of, like, reviewing neurogames and with no visuals,
like, or something stupid.
I mean, having it be a hobby is always a good idea,
just because you get that extra freedom.
So, there's no pressure at this point.
I mean, because you're already, you know, you're doing your professional quote-unquote work,
so there's not any pressing need to, like, have a strict upload schedule or anything like that.
So, you know, if you get the itch again, just throw something out and just let it be that.
I've often thought about, I've never done this,
but I've often thought about the concept of, we all have this urge,
when we make a project, we want it to be, like, big and impressive,
largely because we feel that, like, we've only got one shot to make our video on thing.
But, like, well, let's say I wanted to make a video on, I don't know,
uh, like, Fooly-Cooly the Sequels,
which is something I've wanted to talk about at some point.
What if I could make, like, I don't know, let's just say theoretically,
I made, like, a wee-ag-wa on them or something,
and then I'm like, those are okay, but I actually want to make a big video,
and also make a big video that's actually good later.
You know? That's, that's, like, allowed.
You're allowed to do these things.
But I guess you just don't want your initial work to go to waste or something.
I don't know.
Yeah.
It's like, um, I don't know.
You feel like, you feel like you have these precious feelings about your work,
like, oh, I gotta make my, gotta make my thing and it's gotta be perfect.
But, like, you know, I have that instinct too,
but it's not a good instinct because, like, creativity is a river, right?
It's not, it's not a, it's not a one single squirt.
It's a, it's a, it's a continuous flow, right?
And if you're, and you gotta be, if you're making stuff,
if you're making stuff, making stuff, making stuff,
that's how you make something good, right?
The way that you make something good is that you're just making stuff,
making stuff, making stuff, and sometimes some of it's good.
It's not that you, like, stop everything and you just work on one thing,
and you just make, and you do all this work into one thing.
And then, and then because you worked on it so much, it comes out really good.
That's just not how it works.
My estimation of, like, the heights of human genius have become so low,
like, in that way, that, like, a genius just stands up and does amazing thing.
It seems like it's almost always extremely busy people
or extremely prolific people who are just continually producing.
It's someone who's been doing stuff for, like, a long, long time.
And then, one day, they happen to do it in a certain way.
That is, like, whoa.
This is what's happening.
I think, as we go on, that's gonna start becoming more apparent.
I think the meme of, like, the genius is gonna die
just because social media allows everyone to document what they're doing
and everyone has, like, a history.
So you can't just be, like, a flesh-in-the-pan guy
because you'll have, like, you know, five years' worth of tweets
of trying to do things before your big breakout success.
Every fucking famous artist has, like, their embarrassing old deviant art
of, like, where they drew fucking Ed Ed and Eddie Heddy.
Ty, you go back up.
There's this little person over here.
Yeah, you all know who I'm fucking talking about, but you get it.
And then some of those people continue to do that
and make their career in that.
Yeah.
Ed Ed and Eddie Heddy, yeah.
There's nothing wrong with that.
The brave, the few.
The blue-haired girl.
Uh, Lapis Luzuli.
You know, the canker sister.
I don't remember.
I've seen those.
I never actually watched much Ed Ed and Eddie.
Oh, her. Yeah, I don't know her name. Lucy, I think? Lucy?
No, I don't think so.
Wait, maybe.
Okay, whatever.
It doesn't matter.
Blue canker sister.
I like the Johnny Test sisters.
They're cuties.
It's literally Dexter.
Just two of them and a female.
The one with the straight hair.
Canonically in Johnny Test.
Straight hair one is hotter because the other one's like a tomboy.
And who would like that?
It's just shrug shoulders.
Dab sweat off brow.
Rings, you know, sweat out of blanket.
Whip crack sound.
Well, I'm glad we have that figured out.
That's it.
You're welcome.
I was going to just, I was just going to say like,
the reason AVGN got me on this puff of thinking is because...
Mary, is that the motherfucking PCP?
Is that the motherfucking...
Yes, Munchy.
Hello.
Hey, Munchy.
In my America, with the Republican in the White House,
progress is podcast in this generation.
I don't think so, buddy.
You came to the wrong neighborhood.
Oh, no.
They don't make them like they used to.
Hey, hang on.
Gibb was finishing a point.
Let him finish that.
Yeah.
All right.
You interrupted me.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Okay.
The reason it was AVGN that got me on this sort of train of thought
was because his videos, the subject matter never matters to him, really.
Like it's either a game he remembers renting and it's bad,
or it's just a game he's been brought attention to and it's bad.
And he's always thought of it as like he's making short films
of him playing a character called the Angry Video Game Nerd.
And with a lot of other people, myself included,
I came into it with like,
these are my actual opinions about video games and all that.
And like the character stuff was sort of like,
I'll throw that in there because it's funny or it was never really the focus.
The fact that AVGN has like this focus as this was a character he created
and he's continued to, you know, to use that as like the basis of the show,
he has a very clear understanding of what he is doing.
And I think when an if I ever make anything like that again,
it would only be because I have like an idea for a character,
for a show, for it to be like an entertaining thing.
And the video game stuff should like take a backseat.
Otherwise, I mean, it's not impossible to like have it be the other way,
but you'd need to be like very good at talking about video games
like a Mathematosis or whatever.
And I'm not actually that analytically minded.
I'm more of a funny minded person.
So like the entertainment, you know, it's just sort of cool
because like the way he talks about the video games, the videos themselves
are just very casual.
It's just like he's a guy and he's saying this game sucks.
Look at this bullshit. Fuck.
Angry video game nerd is an artismo, you know, he makes shit by hand
and he has an idea of what he wants to make
instead of it being like a sequence of like,
what childhood game can I mine the experiences of in my brain?
Like what can I like break out that I have like a sentimentality towards
which is where all the heart and gold comes out from stuff like you and maybe John Tron.
If nothing else, that approach is going to help with longevity
which is exactly why he's been doing it for, I believe, 80 years at this point.
Because as long as you're being a character, that character can react to anything.
You personally, human being, have only had so many experiences
that are worthy of mining for anything.
I think that separation is really good.
Not only for that content sort of thing,
because it kind of divorces you personally from the work to a certain degree.
Yeah, it's smart.
It gives you more flexibility.
It's easier to get hung up on a certain video when it's your own opinions being broadcast.
It's like, I got to get this video about my favorite game, perfect.
But if you're just a character, then it's like, you know, it's not the same thing.
You can sort of think of it as a product.
It's also easier to dismiss criticism that are just like, you know, bullshit in the comments.
You're saying you're retarded.
You're like, yeah, the character is supposed to be retarded.
Like, I'm not going to care about this anymore.
Okay, that's all well and good.
And I can understand like the pros of that, right?
I understand that like, yeah, like his Nate said that that's great for longevity.
You know, it can be way more stable a thing to do if, you know, it's more versatile like that.
But isn't like the best videos ones where it's like a person really cares about what they're talking about
and it's like a really like personal or even just interesting sort of thing like that.
I can imagine that being way more filling and creating like artistically just inherently.
Well, yeah, I mean, it's not that I want to emulate AVG and exactly, but it's just that aspect of like the videos are they're not all great.
And there's certainly like an element of nostalgia there.
Like I really like the older ones that I remember.
But it's that that that ability for it to remain good to me after all this time and still be like entertaining.
The fact that people like and it's just sort of like a nice thing and people react that way to my videos.
And I'm like, maybe I don't agree.
But I sometimes sometimes like if I had a good idea, it would be nice to make another video.
And if I didn't have a good idea, like I don't at the moment, then I will just never say it just it just got me thinking about the whole thing.
I haven't watched the Angry Video Game Nerd since I was in fifth grade and I remember not really liking it.
So I think that like the idea of a character really just relies on like it being something that you're into.
Whereas like if it's like someone who's talking about something that they like really care about and really enjoy it, right?
I feel like I can basically listen to any of that.
Even if I hate the thing that they're talking about, their passion can often just come through and it doesn't really matter what it's about.
As long as they're interested and I can watch anything.
But if it's like a character, it's like it can go on for like a thousand episodes.
But if I don't like it, then I'm just not going to watch it no matter what.
I think that regardless of all of these like different things, the main thing that I want to make clear is that if I ever make anything in the future,
it won't be to make a money out of it.
It would just be if I have a cool idea and I really want to make one.
Like longevity or like relativity or big money.
Like it's not going to sway me more than like having a really burning passion for making a video.
Well, good.
I don't know.
That's the reason.
Makes sense.
Hey, that's my thought.
It's me, Munchie.
Munchie wears tiny hats.
I'm recording you live.
Cool guy.
On my dormitory.
I'm the scenic boss in Massachusetts.
It's me.
I'm in college.
Remember how we used to have those long episodes where it's like.
Yikes.
Yeah.
We're still doing it.
And the evil, evil one.
The evil one.
Yes.
Agreed.
Well, now I'm here and now I'm going to, I'm going to get really loud and everyone's going to like bang on my door.
It's going to be like that.
Yeah.
That's why I did that.
That's why.
Okay.
All right.
I don't remember that being the case, but all right.
Yeah, it is.
It is a joke.
Fucking fake Nate fan.
Anyway, I made that as a joke and you took it.
You took like a hook line and sinker, Munchie, but whatever.
Anyway, hey guys.
Well, with hippos talking about creating, you know, thinking about the stuff that you're
going to make.
Oh, you know, I'm going to think really hard about the like, the, the, the, the, the, the
artistic process of this one here.
I'm really going to put a lot of thought in that.
Listen, that's all like fake.
And you know what?
That's not even like just like, nah, bro.
Nah, dude.
Listen, guys, I've been on just like, I've just been coming.
I'm going to love with you guys right now.
My door room is just flooded with semen because I've just been having a fucking gay old time.
Oh God.
Someone's calling.
Let's see.
Let's get the speaker on.
Yeah.
Hey, what is it?
Hello.
Oh God.
Jesus Christ.
I love that guy.
Yeah.
Fuck that guy.
Anyway, the point is, is that after coming to art school and interacting with all the
people I have so far, I just come to agree that just to say that it's all been great.
You know, I'm only like three weeks in, you know, I can't all describe what the experience
will be like in like a month or maybe even tomorrow.
But just, just so far, I've just, the synapses have been firing my friends.
My heart has been beating.
My mind has been just completely altered, like completely addled by all the substances
and people that I've known so far.
And it's great.
And I'm on the other side of the line.
I'm on the other side of paradise right now.
I'm letting you guys know that I'm in heaven.
Like I finally figured it out what it was like.
And it's great.
It's great.
Well, that's great.
That extended adolescence of college is a hell of a time.
You know, it's a great, it's a great experience.
Literally.
What, what is your, your projects, your, your work?
What's, what's you're doing?
So some of it is.
I mean, he's like a, he's like a freshman.
Yeah.
It's like a second week.
It's not, it's not, it's not.
I mean, like, you know, I want those pictures of Spider-Man.
I want those pictures of Spider-Man, Munchie.
Get them on my desk now.
I'm just, I'm just curious to see like what, like the, the experience of the learning,
like how they teach you and what they're teaching you and stuff.
So, well, it depends like a lot on like what the class is.
There's no, it's sort of like, so the thing at this school, right, is that everyone starts
out with the same freshman year.
And there's like very selective that you can take to figure out what you want to major
in down the road.
And then once you get to your second year, then things really start to like get super
niche and super specialized based on like what you want to do.
But right now it's pretty general.
So I'm taking stuff that may not like directly apply to any of your students.
May not like directly apply to anything that I'm doing in the future, but will just be
like sort of general skills that like I can, I can, um, not, not so, let me re, let me
rephrase that.
Not so much that won't be beneficial to what I do down the line, but more so is just a
sort of generic thing that anyone can benefit from in any way.
So I'm studying really basic things like, you know, I'm studying 2D space, how to do
composition.
I'm doing like sculptures and I'm doing stuff like that.
That's like, you know, these are the sort of things that you can really take to anything
and apply them in various different ways.
So if you want to know very specifics, uh, I just bought a bunch of cardboard and I'm
making like a cardboard, fucking mechanical, like weird, like, like utilitarian sculpture
thing.
Uh, so I'm going to be making tubes and shit right now and boxes.
Sick.
Yeah.
It's cool.
It's, I feel like I'm two years old again.
But it was like, it was like, uh, my, my, my roommate, um, Lorenz does architecture
school and he's always like, he's always like building weird shit out of cardboard.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I don't like it.
You're not into it.
I'm against it.
Yeah.
I mean, I understand.
I've never, I had like worked with colored pencils for the first time since like, you
know, second grade.
Um, that was cool.
It's, it's cool.
It's cool to have to, oh, you know what?
Okay.
Here's something that really just struck me.
It was very, it was very interesting.
So there's like a very clear divide and it's really interesting when you're able to like
just see the amount of faces in my freshman class that I know I won't see like by the
end of this year, meaning that I can clearly make out like the weeds.
I can separate like the cream from the chaff so easily.
And it's not like I have like a really, I'm like really like better than those guys.
Like I'm like a really perceptive, but it's illustrated in the fact that like all the
seniors and all the upperclassmen, right?
They are like, you know, cool and, and really like, you know, interesting and kind of weird
and kind of off being kind of the people that I imagined that I would see.
And in my like dorm room, like my roommates and all my people in my floor, all of them
are, and this struck me, they're all like Snapchat normies.
They're all like, like really just like the most like generic human being I can imagine
like in my life.
And you know, like kudos to them, man, I'm not, it's just like, you know, it's just what
I didn't expect.
I thought people are going to be more well adjusted.
I don't know.
Yeah, they're just like, they go out to parties and things and like, you drugs and stuff.
Oh, man.
So fucking that's, that's bizarre, man.
Who would have guessed?
Yeah, I know.
I know.
What the fuck?
Um, no, freshmen suck, dude.
No, freshmen suck.
No, fuck it.
You should haze them.
You should start hazing all the other freshmen.
You should start hosing them.
Yeah.
I basically take a note that anyone who does weed, I won't see by the end of sophomore
year.
That's, that's false.
But okay.
Yeah.
There's, there's some people, but many, many, I agree.
Many will, you know, those, those are the types who are likely to wash out.
I'd say.
Well, you know, it probably, you know what?
It probably does make it more likely.
It more likely.
It probably doesn't make it more likely that they will because they don't have their,
they don't have their, they don't have their eyes on the prize.
I don't know.
We weeds, weeds bad for your focus.
Now the kids are doing Adderall.
Those are the top of the class.
The ones that are popping all the way.
Well, you're speaking to yours truly.
Oh yeah.
How do you think I get by?
Yeah.
Anyway, I don't need to make this the school episode, but that's just obviously the most
interesting thing about me that's happened.
No, I talk for like three hours about Phantom Horn in New Los Angeles City.
So have you been following that by the way?
We shouldn't go on a whole other diversion of, I just want to know if you're, if you're
keeping up with that.
Yeah.
Well, okay.
So it's hard, right?
Cause they don't go on Twitter.
Yeah.
So you just have to like ask Kazzie every day, like, is there a new page now?
And she'll tell me yes or no.
But there is a, there is a post that I keep retweeting that is just all the images collected
into one Imgur album.
Oh, okay.
I've been snagging the link for that too, so we can put it in the show notes and shit.
Yes, I will snag the link.
I'll just bookmark that then, I guess.
Yes.
Yeah, do that.
I mean, good idea.
I can't wait for the Kickstarter for that comic.
Oh my God, Munchy.
I'll fucking print a book of it.
Why not?
Munchy, have you seen, are you up to date with Ben's comic there?
Have you seen like the very last page that's been produced?
Is it the one?
Well, the last I left off.
Let's just say it's an explosive page.
Oh, yes.
I've seen that.
There's actually been two more since then.
Oh, okay.
I guess I missed those.
Okay.
I want to make sure you saw 9-11.
Yeah, no.
I definitely saw 9-11.
Spoiler.
Oh, sorry.
Oops.
It was the best one yet.
Oh, by the way guys, sorry, let me just, on the 7-9-11, did you guys see the arch that
someone made for us on Twitter of our character 9-11 in full green screen?
No.
It was sent to us on 9-11.
Yeah, you posted it on 9-11.
And then you in some chat was like, I don't know if we should have refweeted this today.
I did not.
Look, on 9-11, people are actually sad and like, you know, grieving.
Yeah, fuck them, dude.
After that, it's fine, but I just didn't want to, you know, it's actually a day of grieving
for real people, which I'm not one of.
For babies.
For baby people.
It's over.
It's old.
I get it.
I just don't care.
It's funny.
I mean, I agree.
It's hilarious.
But, you know.
But by the way, I just wanted to say that Ben, about that comic, I, this is something I've
been thinking about a lot lately, but first of all, Endless War, as I do every single
day of my fucking life, just thinking about it.
But in relation to like an Endless War comic and stuff, it's just so like, Endless War
is the best like inspirational tool ever.
Like you can just like think about it for a second and then just ideas just start to
flow from your fingertips and your mind and your cock.
Like there's just so many different ways that you could take it that it's just like, I think
like the, like, I'm going to describe like the quickest from like thought to creation
that I think can happen.
Like as soon as I get it in this war idea of any kind, like an update for it or an extra
curricular thing, I just like immediately like, okay, this is just like completely taken
over my mind.
Like I can't think about anything else.
I'm just going to do this because it's like the best idea anyone's ever had.
Yeah.
That's the plan.
That's the plan, baby.
Munchy, Munchy, have you had that moment at school yet?
I'm wondering if this has happened yet.
Have you had that moment where the, your contemporaries have realized just how much better you are
than them yet at, you know, doing stuff in real life?
Well, I mean, I mean, you're a freshman, so you're surrounded by other freshmen.
So I have no doubt in my mind that plenty of your contemporaries are just complete hacks
who do not belong there and will drop out when they realize that it is not for them.
I saw the funny fucking cartoon, Pro-Mare, and I went to a premiere or just a showing
in Boston and it was great and we can talk about that maybe.
But the point of that is I went with three classmates and I went there just to have fun,
you know, hang out.
And I, after the movie, I was stopped not once, but twice by two separate fans who
asked me to take pictures with them in front of my classmates.
And by the way, I had been trying to keep my, like, all of my art online, like a secret
from all of them.
Like, I went intentionally trying to not let anyone know my power level.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
And so, like, I was intentionally dodgy, like, as much as I could be.
And so, then, like, they see, like, all these, like, people, like, like, line up for photos
with me.
Munchy, you were both lording that club and holding court simultaneously.
Yeah.
They were dripping wet after seeing this spectacle.
I have no doubt about it.
Did your classmates ask him up?
Yeah, they were like, what?
It is that.
I was like, I just make stuff online.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, play a coy boy.
That's the way.
Keep him guessing.
Yeah.
You know, they think you're the coolest guy, as of that.
Well, that's how you get hired by, like, Heart to Network.
Yeah.
By lording the club.
Anyway, so I basically, like, have, yeah, tried to keep everything a secret.
Oh, oh, hey, actually, so speaking of endless war and school, actually, so I have, I came
to the school knowing that, like, the first, like, month or two is just gonna be me trying
to pan for gold as fast and as hard as I fucking can, like, I'm fucking a cat or something.
So I'm just, I've been going to, like, every single club and extracurricular activity in
every class and everything that I possibly can to, like, analyze the situation, look
at everyone that's, you know, in the club or just around me, like, rapid fire, like,
hey, what's up?
They respond in two words.
I can tell if I'm gonna like them or not.
Yeah.
Obviously, that's the latest, you know, obviously, there are gonna be people that are gonna be
lost through cracks right there.
People are gonna say something, you know, weird or awkward, and I would have liked
them a lot, but I just didn't give them the time of day because I'm a fucking asshole.
Yeah, listen, I understand, I know, that's, that's what the rest of the years are for.
Right now, I'm trying to build a solid base for which I can jump off from, like, listen,
you know, it's, you know, am I an asshole?
Sure, whatever.
Fuck you, it doesn't matter.
The point of this is that I've been going to a bunch of clubs and in order to get a bigger,
you know, like, just as many people in front of me and get to know as many people as possible,
I have made a Discord server, and you know what this is?
It is an endless war clone themed after my school, so I've, like, I have, like, coded
my own, like, personal, like, weird, like, offshoot spinoff of endless war, and I've
just made it in this thing so I can, like, introduce all the people in my school to not
only endless war, but also me, and then we can, I can, like, lord over to them the fact
that I've made something cool and that they'll have to cry.
This is just for, like, people you know from school and...
No, I'm posting up flyers and posters and stuff like that.
Oh, okay.
Oh, also, wait.
Are they supposed to kill each other?
Yeah, no, they kill each other.
Oh, thank god.
Well, technically, they make each other drop out.
There is slime, though.
Okay, okay.
Well, also, wait, wait.
How long is there slime?
Quick aside, quick aside, by the way, I went to a socialist club, and I went to a place
called...
Wait, a socialist club?
Yeah, I went to a thing called the Finway Socialists.
Very nice.
Oh, okay.
Media.
And you should come with me next time.
Should I actually?
Yeah, I was allowed.
I mean, it was basically...
It was boilerplate shit that, like, I've heard a thousand times before, and they didn't really
care.
But you know what?
Okay, great.
Cool.
Sign me up.
I mean, maybe I'll...
Your friends have been for so long before it all becomes boilerplate.
That's right.
You know, I was just scrolling through the mentions on the PCP and my personal Twitter,
because I think he sent it to both of us.
I cannot find this 9-11 image.
I'm worried that this person felt the need to, like, delete it, because they felt, like,
uncomfortable about it.
Bro, please don't.
Just bring it back if you did.
I don't even remember who it was who made that.
But I'm mildly concerned that they felt like they shouldn't have done it or something.
But no, it's hilarious.
Don't apologize.
Don't delete...
Unless I'm wrong.
Do what makes sense.
Please link it to me.
I want to retweet it.
It's hilarious.
Oh.
You probably didn't see this since you're not on Twitter, but I made a really funny drawing
yesterday, and I want to tell you about it.
Was it the church where you were?
Yeah, yeah.
I saw that one.
Listen, okay, that's a fine image and all.
But you gave Tirstworthy a shirt.
And that's just...
That implies that he's, like, a furry.
That implies that he wears clothes, and I'm, like, really not about that.
I'm really upset about that.
You're right.
No, you're right.
No, this is not canon.
Hopefully that can be retconned immediately.
And Tirstworthy, actually, he wears a headband, right?
Yeah, yeah.
He wears, like, a Ryu headband.
Yeah.
This was...
I mean, I just had to communicate that he's a rowdy, and that he wasn't a fucking tie-wearing
Republican.
He's not a GOP, remember?
Yeah.
I mean, those get mixed up all the time.
Dimension C197 is the cop killer shooting Tirstworthy.
Dimension 1218 is Ben St., killing the GOP.
The joke is that they're both elephants.
Get it?
Because Grand Old Party, the Republicans, elephants.
Very funny.
Yes.
I had to...
I had a fucking brain blast, right?
I was like, I have to make this connection in a new way that makes people make a new
realization about the world and makes them go, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Tirstworthy picture in the show notes is Tirstworthy with his mother back in Africa.
That's great.
Why is it giving me this...
Oh, it's...
Okay.
He's shooting fucking guns.
Oh, I see.
By the way, Munchie, Munchie, tell me you've been to the Promised Land.
Tell me you've been to the Anime Club.
Please, I need to hear these words.
Okay.
There isn't one.
What?
You need to found the Anime Club then, Munchie.
No, no, me.
This is your job.
The reason why there isn't one is because Anime Club is just the school name.
Literally everyone is that person that you would see at Anime Club.
I'm just curious.
In my school, there was an Anime Club and it was a Japanese culture club.
Does that exist?
I'm just curious.
No, there's nothing like that.
All the clubs are very...
So they hate Japanese.
They're racist.
They want to re-enact World War II, Hirasaki, Nagashima.
I got it.
There's a weird preponderance of Chinese people at the school, not really ethnic.
I'm saying literally like from China, like they are from the country.
Like their English and stuff.
Don't they say that America's chief export is education or something?
Is Chinese people?
Yeah.
We might have them, we ship them off.
I don't know.
So I've been to a few clubs.
Chief among them is the Game Design Club, the Game Jam Club, which was cool, fine, maybe,
whatever.
I went to a comic club and the comic club was like, okay, I'm going to make like a really
like fucking like funny ass, like lame ass, normie comparison to an anime that I've seen.
I think you guys have seen Mob Psycho 100 probably.
You know that?
I don't even know what it's called.
The club that like does nothing, you just waste time.
That's the comic club.
I tell them to use this club or whatever it's called.
The Psychic Club.
Yeah.
Yeah, that.
Okay, it's that.
So it's just like people like show up and they're like, yeah, so like I've been working
on like this characters for like 10 years and like I like I like written down something
but I was hoping someone else here could draw it for me.
Like I'm thinking that we could like collaborate and like that's that's what it's like.
That's what people that's my heart.
That's what it's my one call for a wish.
That's what people who want to get into comics are like, they are script writers who need
an artist to draw their shit for them for exposure.
This is that it's an it's an epidemic.
It was like it was like that at my school.
I mean, we didn't have a comic club, but there were there were people like that.
But I have this great idea for a comic.
I just need someone to draw it for me.
There you go.
I need something to do all the work for me.
Pretty much.
You're sizing them up much so you know these people can be thrown directly into the trash
and moved on.
Yeah.
It's also all okay.
Listen.
All right.
Also this is an art school.
So why the fuck are they doing that there?
They should know how to fucking draw.
People think art school is fucking easy.
Maybe they're in the writing program.
That's the reason.
Yeah.
They say you have to go to a college and it's like, I guess drawing's easy.
I'll go to art college and then a bunch of people come to an art college.
They realize it's hard and then they leave.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let me go to art school.
If I did, I did the exact same thing.
The thing with like freshman year, like there was a bunch of like normal people in there
who did not give a shit and they they just enjoyed like acting as if they were still in school
and like enjoyed, enjoyed posting about how much they're not doing their homeworks.
Like I haven't even done it yet.
Yeah.
And it had a lesson shit.
Oh, it's terrible.
It's horrible.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's so weird because it's such like a weird paradigm, right?
Where I talk to the people and they're like, oh, my fucking teacher sucks.
I have to do homework.
I have to draw an art school.
What the fuck?
Oh, damn.
And I'm like, I am like, my mom didn't make me come here.
Like this was my parents decision to come to this school.
Like I like came here of my own accord to like, you know, participate.
How do those people?
I mean, this is why when we like, when we would always talk about college, we're always like,
we have a goal.
Don't just go for no reason.
Yeah.
And so it's like, it's so literally who just like mindlessly went there.
There are other decisions in life and rack up dead.
Yeah.
All that business.
Okay.
Let me know if this is like bad of me to get annoyed at.
So I'm at the comic club, right?
And I'm talking to people and one of the girls there is like, dude, she like, she just like
doesn't want to do comics.
You know, she's just there to like hang out and talk about like fucking cartoons or whatever.
And she's like, guys, you know what?
I love Samurai Jack.
Somehow the talk of Samurai Jack comes up and she just talks about how much she loves it
and about how it's like her favorite thing about how she just, oh, she's such a Samurai
Jack fan.
Fuck yeah.
It's finna fleek, bro.
And then, and then it's, and then someone else asked like, oh, have you seen season five?
And they're like, I've only seen season five and adult swim.
I've only seen like the newest, latest, most mainstream version of this thing.
Is I, is it okay for me to want to kill that person?
Absolutely.
I mean, the elitist about your media is one of the fine joys of life.
It's one of the most wonderful experiences that you and me can have.
I feel like Samurai Jack is old enough and I assume it's not on TV in the rotation anymore.
And it's been like that for long enough that it's like, I don't, I don't think it's like
that fair to like shit on them immediately.
Like you can, you can tell them.
I mean, they can Google search, watch Samurai Jack online.
Maybe you should watch the old ones.
Yeah.
And you can feel superior to them because they haven't thought of it.
You know what?
I'm going to, I agree.
I think it would be the real crime would be if you were like, if they, if they were like,
I haven't watched the old ones and I never will like fuck that.
Right.
But probably like if they liked season five and they're just excited about it and maybe
they'd want to see the first and they just haven't gotten around to it yet.
I mean, that would be fair.
That would be fair enough.
Well, I feel like I don't begrudge anyone for not starting Samurai Jack at the beginning.
And then this, you know, this isn't just Samurai Jack.
This can be anything again.
I don't have any religious Samurai Jack, but like it's not the fact that like they just
watched that season and not the rest and they aren't a real fan.
It's the fact that they like go, they went on and on about how they are a real fan.
Yeah.
That's what I like.
This is safe.
But no one heard me say anything.
Lol.
Get wrecked.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Sure.
I mean, I mean, you know, I guess it would depend, right?
There.
Yeah.
I guess it would have to depend on like, I would have to been there and heard her spiel
to be like, this is weird.
It's weird that you're talking about yourself this way when you haven't even seen four fifths
of the show.
Uh, was it like, was it like people were saying, are you, you're not a real fan?
If you've only seen the fifth one, she's like, no, I am a real fan.
Or is it she just talked about how she's a real fan out of nowhere?
There's definitely would be a weird way to do it.
Someone was like, like they were listing off the things that they like about themselves
and they're like, oh, I used to watch Samurai Jack as a kid and the other person was like,
oh, do I fucking love Samurai Jack?
And then they went off.
Oh, that reminds me of a thing that happened like, back when Final Fantasy had been children
released.
I watched it and I loved it.
I loved it.
You're the only one.
At the time.
To be, I've never played any Final Fantasy games, still haven't, sadly.
I've only seen that one movie and I just absolutely fell in love with Vincent Velland.
Oh my God.
Jesus.
That's such an amazing thing to do.
I remember I talked to people just about how much I loved Vincent Velland.
I knew his height.
I knew everything about him.
I'm played and I feel like I might be the only person in the world who played Final Fantasy
7, Durage of Cerberus, which was the, oh yeah, I knew about this game solely because I liked
Vincent Velland.
It is just a very polished, very pretty shooting gallery, but it is the fucking side story about
Vincent Valentine, who is the edgiest boy in this, even in the post-Cyberpocalypse of
the Final Fantasy 7, Vincent Valentine is the edgiest boy.
Yeah, pretty much.
I love him so much.
I mean, he's pretty cool.
I still do.
I still like him too.
Yeah, Durage of Cerberus is not a great game, but whatever.
I still enjoyed it, so I guess I can understand.
Quote on quote, the edgiest boy is very magecore.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
It's kind of mecore too, in a way.
I mean, yeah, no, I really liked Vincent too.
Nate liked him so much that he caused feelings.
One of these feelings of superiority, I mean, you know what it's going to be.
Just to use the loaded example, it's like in a couple years or whatever, when someone
plays the Final Fantasy 7 remake, and then I'm talking to them, and they just say, like,
we just met each other, and they're like, oh yeah, I love Final Fantasy 7, and I'm like,
oh my god, and then I go on my spiel about, you know, and then they're like, no, no, no,
stop, stop, idiot.
I'm talking about the remake, and then I'm like, oh god, no, it can't be.
And before it was cool, even in 2019, before the game was even released, I was a huge fan
of the trailers.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Epic.
So look, it's not wrong for them to feel that way, but I absolutely give myself permission
to simply feel superior to them, because I do know more.
But if you want to be a real fan, you need to at least have an opinion about the original
versus the remake.
You probably should.
I think that's very criteria.
The thing about these sorts of conversations, where somebody shows that they're just a little
baby about some media, and then there's that one guy who does the deep sigh and lets them
know, like, you aren't cool guy, you're not a real fan, that guy as well.
No, I love that guy, that's me.
You're right.
Because here's the thing, right, fandom is all about commodification, right?
It's all about, it's all capitalist nightmare, we're playing right into the, we're all playing
right into the big corporation's hand when we have these conversations, oh, you're not
a real fan, because you haven't seen the spin-off, you're not.
Because you have consumed product XYZ.
You're saying you don't own, you don't own all the figurines, but you're not a real
fan.
Wait, you don't have the Chewbacca figure with, like, the extra bandolier that only
costs like $22.99 extra, you have to custom order it?
Idiot.
Yeah, so this is what we're doing, we're playing right into Disney's hand, right?
And as, you know, as soon as, first, here's how it's gonna go, first Google buys Facebook,
then Google buys Twitter, then Disney buys Google, then they own us, then they've got
us by the balls, right, then they form the one world government, right, then there's
the tribulation, right, the tribulation, the thousand years of tribulation, then the Antichrist
appears, then Jesus comes back, right, but it's too late, because we've all given up
our faith, right, we don't believe in Jesus anymore, we just believe in-
And they're like, you're not a real fan of the Bible, you don't even know that hell
isn't real, it was never even in the original text, dude.
Yeah, exactly.
Wait, you didn't read, wait, you didn't even read Dante's Inferno, you're not a fucking
real fan, alright?
You didn't, that's fucking fan fiction.
You're not a fucking goddammit.
Goddammit, it's not, yeah, no, you're not, for that example, bad example.
And after all that, endless wars to our heart happens, it's like, under Disney, slime is
invented, and then everything goes to shit.
Well, under Jesus, slime is invented.
I just wanna say, like, you know, like how people get keepin', like, get annoyed, it's
like, oh, you've only consumed this media, and it's kinda sad, because like, I find
it really cool that people get interested in the media, and then like, you have something
to talk about with them.
I think the most annoying thing is if they get a big head about like, oh, I watched the
remake of this thing, and then like, they talk down to you as if they know better than
you, I think that's the most annoying thing people do.
That can be annoying.
Yeah, but like, in general, I really like it when people get into it, even if it's not,
you know, the OG or only part of the thing, like, I think Never Paint recently started
like, their first Pokemon game ever, and I'm like, yes, you're playing Pokemon, that's
so cool.
You're experiencing the things, and that's really neat, and I like that, and I'm happy
for them.
Look, I agree, gatekeeping can be a bad thing, but I believe in benevolent gatekeeping in
a big way, which, namely, like, okay, remember in Hunter Hunter, remember in Hunter Hunter,
and they go to save Killua from that house, and there's literally a big gate in the way.
There's a big gate, and in order to go rescue Killua, they had to do a sick shonen montage
to get strong so they could push open the gate to get through.
This is exactly how I think about, not even like fandom, but like, like the game Sekiro.
So many people got filtered by Sekiro because it was too fucking hard, and they couldn't
summon Solare to save their pansy ass, and they weren't willing to put in the dozens
of hours of work to get good at that fucking game, and good!
They don't deserve to get through because they didn't work for it.
These things should exist so that we have some filtration system, so that we know.
I don't see the connection between skilgating in a video game and fandom of, like, Samurai
Jack.
Okay, if you're in a Discord server that's about, like, deep-level discussion of, let's
just say, anime, like, you're like a Ukrainian Zagok, or you're like an econ, or a Digibro.
You're one of these people who has deep-level knowledge.
The three-level knowledge.
The three-level apocalypse right there.
Yeah, exactly.
These guys, they know shit, alright, they know shit.
Like sure, could a newcomer come in who has barely seen any anime and like engage in discussion?
Sure, they could do that.
They probably wouldn't have been able to contribute to that kind of conversation.
What they should do is, what I would want that person to do is be like, okay, I can
see the conversation is above my pay grade, I could participate, but really I should
just go and, like, learn some of these examples that are being discussed before, like, you
know, like, annoying people by trying to interject myself into situations where I just am at
operating at a way lower intellectual level of information than, like, the other people
here.
That's what I'm saying, which seems like a perfectly reasonable way to look.
Here's my, well, here's my take, right?
You don't, you do not need, you do not need to have, to be an expert to have an opinion
on something, right?
Like you don't need, you don't need to have seen everything to have an opinion about a
movie, for example.
But I mean, you should know, you should just know that, like, I mean, you should, you know,
you should just fucking be reasonable about it and be like, okay, well, I only know, I
only know about the things I've seen.
And if there are things that I haven't seen, then I don't know about them, right?
Just keep, keep that guideline in mind and you'll, you'll be okay, dear, dear.
But specifically when it comes to video games, it's a little different where, because the,
the amount of the game you end up playing can differ from person to person.
If you see a movie, most people finish the movie, not everybody like skips a scene or
like starts halfway through and thinks they've seen the movie.
Maybe some people do, but like, they're quickly shot down with bullets.
If somebody plays Sekiro, for example, and they can't get past a certain boss, but they
say they're, they like the game and they try to participate in certain conversations,
it's difficult because on the one hand, they are a fan of the game because they've played
it, but they aren't a person who has completely completed it like some of the other people.
Okay, but what if they watched the Let's Play and they saw how it ended?
Okay, there's things they can and can say.
There's a visual feeling of like playing the game is different from Let's Playing.
I think everyone understands that.
The person can say they enjoy the game, they like playing it, they love the lore, they
can say all those things.
What they can't say is that I beat the game if they didn't beat the game and that's perfectly
fine, a distinction to make.
It's just, you know, depends on what the conversation is.
Well, it just makes it a little more complicated because like, say for example, somebody has
beaten 90% of the game or, and having a conversation with somebody who's just started, like a game
takes a long time to complete, and a movie or an anime, it's like a start and stop.
You watch the thing from the beginning to the end, and if you haven't done that, then
it's very clear that you're not, you know, you can't participate.
I think it really depends on what the topic of discussion is and what exactly they're
discussing.
If they're just, you know, talking about the things they liked and liked so far and stuff,
you know, just naming things, sharing experiences, I think both a starter and an expert can find
things to talk about, but, you know, like if they talk about some sort of in-depth lore
or future spoilers or something, or like the feeling of defeating the boss, then, you know,
the newbie wouldn't be able to necessarily relate.
I want to make a new OC, possibly an endless war.
They're called the Gatekeeper.
This is all they do.
They know all the lore, and if you ever reveal that you don't know every single thing about
a mechanic or the lore or a character or anything, you will be sought out and destroyed if you
reveal this about yourself.
The mate of the time reaper.
Ooh, that's a good one, too.
Yes.
Well, Munchie, is there anything else interesting going on at school in your life?
Because it seems like a fascinating new change.
It is.
I mean, you know, I'm really early in.
There's probably one person who I've really pissed off with the series of, like, haha,
I'm having so much fun.
Ooh, I feel like, oh, wow, some people are going to not make it through the freshman
year.
Haha, I say naively.
Ooh, I am upset that someone didn't watch Office Emerit Jack.
So I can imagine there's one person really upset about that.
That's really just boiling in their seats or sorry to them.
They're not going to make it anyway.
Yeah, you know what?
That's fine.
Anyway, in school, I mean, there's like a lot of things, there's so many things that
have happened over the past couple of weeks, you know, that it's hard to really pick apart
all the things.
I mean, I'm just having a lot of fun.
I'm really enjoying it.
Are your roommates all right?
How's the roommate situation?
Well, you see, well, you've seen it.
I'm in my dorm right now.
I don't know how the walls are.
And I do know, I do know that one of my roommates is possibly listening to this very show right
now.
Oh my God.
So, listen, I can't talk about any one of them because I don't know how secure it is.
Fuck you, David.
You crazy shit.
No, no, no.
Go back to Scandinavia.
Listen, I can't really speak too much about that, but I will say that I thoroughly enjoy
my dorm.
Well, that's great.
There's no problems there.
But I will refrain from specifics.
I will say that today and for the past couple of days, I have been like just fucking like
in my own eyes slaying, slaying like a queen because I've really gotten a hold of the routine
because, you know, it's somewhat hard to adjust going from, especially like me, like, you
know, living off the chain, you know, you know, fucking sick nasty without having basically
any like actual routine in place.
Obviously, I've talked many times on the show about having like a set in place routine
that I impose upon myself, but how different is it from a self-imposed to like an outside
impose routine?
I mean, that's crazy.
But anyway, the point is, is that I have a school schedule now, so I've had to like
work around my life around that as opposed to, you know, work my like art around myself.
And so it's been a really, you know, hasn't been like, you know, agonizing, but I finally
now actually just put it away and finally been able, I've woken up at seven for the
past couple of days, like how I want, and I'm just in a routine.
I'm writing my journal way more than I used to, and I'm cooking on myself.
I just, I feel great.
I feel a master of my own demand.
I'm getting work done as soon as I get it.
And it's just, I earlier today, right?
The reason I'm all jazzed up about this.
Earlier today, I took a long walk to art supply school, art supply store to get stuff for
my homework.
And just on that, like I just got an idea for something that I want to create, like
an art project I want to make.
And so I just got off of the road and I just stopped in a cafe and I just spent like two
hours in a cafe.
And then while I was in there, it wasn't like the usual, like, you know, I sit down to write
and like, oh God, what am I going to do?
Like I have an idea that I kind of want to eke out of my brain, but like it's so ill
to find a way.
It's like, I just have to sit down like make like, oh, the characters of this character
is this.
No, it just so easily transferred from my brain to the page to the point where it's like,
I have something that I can like just do.
I've never felt like I always feel like no matter how much of the art that I've made
online, no matter how easy it gets, how much of a process I work out, it always feels when
I start a new thing that I'm doing, it always feels like, oh God, there's so much to do.
I have so many things that I have to like, oh, I have to write so much for this project.
I have to do so much for this.
I don't feel that way at all.
I feel, I think it's a large part due to like me being in a new environment and me feeling
kind of fresh.
I feel spry, guys.
I feel like, I feel like I'm alive again.
I feel like I'm just so brimming with things that I want to do and like it's weird, right?
Because I've had so much time before and now that I have less time to do things that I
want, I'm more, you know, incentivized, or not incentivized, but I'm more inspired to
do it.
Life works out like that, but it's just like, I feel good.
I feel really creative.
I feel really like, like I'm making things and like I'm not working hard, but it's
stupid.
I feel like I'm working smart and also hard and it's great and I'm alive right now.
I feel so good.
I like that romantic idea of just sitting at a cafe, like, you know, just doing that
was like, hmm, I'm gonna be like a creative, I'm gonna sit at a cafe and I'm gonna like
write on it in a little book.
Oh, dude.
Okay.
Based on what you just said right there, I've actually made a vow.
This is a scary thing for me, but I'm now officially saving up for an iPad.
I've made the decision.
I'm gonna get an iPad because I want, because my laptop is like really terrible and really
bad and like sucks and I need something that I can go around and write with.
So I was writing and as I just said, it worked out great and I got a lot of stuff down on
the page that I think is like really valuable and it was great, but I was just like texting
on my phone basically and it was like kind of a nightmare with that interface and I've
just been teeter on the edge of being an iPad for a while because I really like the pencil
or like the idea of I can just like go out on the go and I can just draw whatever I want
to.
So yeah, it was romantic hippo, but it was offset by the fact that it was on a, I'm just
like on my fucking phone and it was really annoying and stupid and I looked really lame
and dumb.
iPads are pretty sick.
iPads are dope, man.
I like them.
I like them a lot.
There's so many apps.
The apps, man.
Gotta get that procreate going.
That's like the old standard.
Munchie, you mentioned something in there.
I just had to touch on briefly.
You said that you've been cooking.
That's great.
Okay, but forget you.
Let's talk about me, which is that, okay, so recently, me and Michelle have gotten our
hands on some of these Amazon meal kits.
Oh God, not this shit again.
You must have horse shit.
Don't do Hello Fresh.
Don't do these prepared meal kits like they're bad.
It just keeps coming back.
You think you slayed it?
You think you slayed the Hydra.
You don't want to die.
You think you slayed the Hydra, but two heads grow back.
Ben, I'm under no, I'm under no illusion, but let me tell you, friend.
Let me tell you, when I was chowing down on my 30 minute prepared Amazon meal kit seared
salmon with fennel and pea risotto, it was, I'm not lying, I'm not lying, making this
meal as exactly instructed with all the ingredients prepared right there was so easy to make.
This was one of the most delicious meals I've had my entire life.
These Amazon meal kits.
This is not an exaggeration, I'm 100% serious, and you know what, I'm sure a large part of
it is the satisfaction of having it cooked at home.
It's incredible.
I'm disgusted with you right now.
I'm so fucking disgusted.
I made this fucking, I made this amazing couscous Amazon meal kit deal.
I don't know what fucking couscous is.
You're so spineless.
I just made it according to the meal kit.
You're such a spineless fucking coward, Nate.
You're so fucking terrible.
Why are you arguing again?
You used to be on his side.
Easy to make.
No, no.
What?
Okay, because Nate, Nate used to always, you know, flip flop between, oh yeah, ha ha,
fucking hello fresh, but then also, oh, but I see the appeal, he would flip flop between
them, he would be like, you know, a reasonable person, fuck you.
And so now he goes from, you know, sort of downplaying hello fresh, now going with evil
hello fresh, which is Amazon meal kits.
It just is hello fresh, but now it's owned by Amazon and they're like any evil version.
I mean, I just say that, okay, we, we got them for free.
These were, these were literally free.
So like we didn't pay for them, so that's the big reason why we got them.
I forget if it was hello fresh or blue apron, but I got a, a free, I got like a free like
week's worth of it, which one time, which is why I know.
Yeah, you might as well.
There's no, yeah.
Sure, sure, sure.
That's fine.
That's cool at all.
Okay.
If you, if you didn't roll with me from the start, you don't need to roll with me now.
I want to quickly talk about food since we're talking about food.
Wait, mate.
Let me finish my point.
Then you can talk about food.
It's just that, well, this is, why would I ever want to not do this when it's, it's
so easy.
It's so delicious.
It's, I don't know.
The calorie counts are right there.
They're reasonably healthy.
Because you can literally do it yourself for less money.
You can do the same exact thing.
I don't know how to put together, by salmon, by couscous, by fucking, any recipe that fucking
cares and shit, any recipe that fucking Garfield eats or whatever fucking service this is when
send you in the mail, you can just, you can figure it, you can Google it.
Oh, you're right.
Look, guys, just entertain this for a second, Ben.
Have you ever thought for a second that some of the meals that are being, look, by, you
buy the box, it has the exact meal that you're going to get and exact instructions that you
will get, that whatever you're going to do.
We have made through these, food that I did not envision myself being able to easily make
at home.
I've now learned that it is easy to make, but it can be done.
You know, fine, I just, I'm just saying, I'm just saying that there are ways to expand
your culinary horizons that does not involve prostrating yourself on the capitalist altar
of fucking Jeff Bezos, his offshore bank accounts, or whatever the fuck.
What, are you going to stop using Amazon, Ben?
Are you going to stop ordering from Amazon?
It's not that I think you shouldn't use Amazon.
It's that, it's that you could, it's just that you could do the exact same thing without
using Amazon.
That's a, well, look, it's fine, look, it's fine.
I don't want to overstate, I don't want to overstate how much of a crime I think this
is, but I just like, you don't need this fucking service to do this for you.
I have more faith in you than that.
This is kind of the exact same thing we were just talking about with like the gatekeeping
and like the plague who doesn't, you know, he, he's still like, you are to cooking as
somebody who hasn't beaten a single boss in Sekiro is to you.
Who?
Who's who in this analogy?
Huh?
It's clearly me.
I mean, I'm the, I'm the new guy.
I'm the scrub.
Or he's the gatekeeper.
No.
I thought this would be very simple.
The whole thing with cooking is that you're doing like an easy loser baby stupid thing
and everyone else around you is, is like laughing at you.
Like they're doing the deep side.
You're such a fake food fan.
I can't believe you would do this.
Okay.
Yeah.
Kind of a little bit.
I just, like, if you put the hard work in, like in Sekiro, if you put the hard work in,
you can make these, these things like, like easily over time, you will gain skills.
You will gain like a library of ingredients that you know work well together and you can
make stuff up.
Yeah.
You know, in Sekiro, in Sekiro actually, you can get your hands on rice through after
a while, there's a lady gives you rice, but you eat it raw.
Cannot, the character eats it raw.
It's a life hack, like advanced, like one of the secret ending strats where like Kuro,
your little Lord guy, he actually is like, you've been eating it raw.
Let me, let me like cook it for you.
And then he makes delicious rice balls.
So he does up his cooking game, Cannotically in Sekiro, when you dive deep and do some
of the like harder to access endings.
It's a metaphor.
How fascinating.
Forget, forget, forget and good.
And I agree.
Get, but I'm not good.
Okay.
Good, good.
Wait, okay.
You know what?
I shouldn't be, you know what?
The fact, I'm, I'm reassured by the fact that you got it for free.
This makes me feel.
It was free.
This makes me feel so much better about the whole thing.
Okay.
Listen, we've had the final Hello Fresh conversation like 12 times now on this show.
I'll say what I've said a thousand times before, you know, you don't need it, but it's just
convenient and convenience may matter to you.
You know, if you, if you can spare it, you know, convenience, it's nice and all, but
you know, you don't need it.
Yeah.
But the satisfaction of being like a chef who knows how to do it is way better.
Is way better than summoning in.
That's too big.
I need dinner tonight.
It's way better than summoning.
I guess all I would say, I guess all I would say is if, if you're, if you're like, okay,
I don't know how to cook.
Oh, but like, you know, something like Hello Fresh or Amazon eats or Garfield eats or whatever
the fuck.
If they, they, you know, through, through this, I can, I can expand my horizon and learn how
to do it.
I would say cool, but guess what?
You don't need that.
You can, you can, you can, you can, you can learn on your own.
You can learn, you can just fucking Google the recipe and make it.
I do it sometimes.
It's pretty all right.
All right.
I'm going to make a value judgment right now, but Nate, I don't think that you will ever
Google search how to make a specific type of food.
I don't think you'll ever do that in your life and like try to like expand your horizons
that way.
Am I wrong?
Okay.
Yeah.
Life's a long time.
We'll see.
So I think this is an extremely unlikely scenario.
Well, that's dumb.
If you'll satisfied me, if you'll gave me a hundred percent of my nutritional value and
I had no problems that I could just drink it, I would just do that.
I don't care.
It's not important to me, but these meals, they are pretty great.
They are delicious and they're better than you.
So I'm sure they're better than you.
Nothing's better than you.
They don't blast.
This is Nate's glowing review of Amazon eats better than you.
But I love you.
He was great.
That's a high recommendation.
I got, I ordered the chocolate, you'll in the bottles.
It was pretty good.
Oh yeah.
See, see, yeah.
The biggest problem is that they're not filling and I find myself pretty hungry before too
long after.
The biggest problem is that they're too fucking expensive.
There's that too.
They're like three to four dollars or something when you have to eat.
It's unacceptably expensive.
I have a solution.
Powder is a much better deal.
I have a solution, Nate.
This is like in sort of in relation to what I wanted earlier to say.
So I went out today to the shop and I bought like a bunch of ingredients, like a lot of
like vegetables and whatnot.
I made soup and it was like with a little flavor, soup cubes or whatever.
I threw a bunch of stuff in.
I didn't know who was going to taste good or not.
And just like the cherry on top, I put everything into a blender and I put this in a blender
because I was too lazy to like chop everything into small bits.
Hold on.
Hold the fucking phone.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
How was it?
That is not what a blender is for.
Wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
Are you saying that you put all the ingredients into a blender, blended it in the blender
and then put it in a pot and cooked it?
No, no, no.
I cooked it first.
Like I chopped it into like reasonable cubes.
So did it just end up as like a soup smoothie?
Yes.
Jesus Christ.
Was it good?
It was perfect.
It was great.
You know what I'm saying.
It was like a very like normal.
This would strike me as just like normal.
This doesn't seem weird or bad at all.
This is like tired of having to chew every bite of food.
We've got the solution.
This is not normal, but I don't think it sounds too bad because like when you cook it all
in a soup, it all kind of like the flavors all kind of run together.
Yeah.
So I can sort of imagine you just kind of blend it and it just becomes like a smooth puree
that has that soup flavor.
Yeah, basically.
And it's like, it feels a lot more filling.
It depends on how much water you put.
It might be like thicker or thinner.
What did you put in it?
I want to imagine this experience.
Okay.
It was slightly experimental, so I wasn't sure if it was going to turn out great or not.
No kidding.
Okay.
So a bit of, I think like two small red peppers, which didn't turn out that spicy this time
because I previously had made a similar soup, but that I was following a recipe, but this
time I was just like, just doing my own thing.
So like two red peppers, a handful of like tiny bell peppers, like these orange ones,
like baby bell peppers or something.
Okay.
So just a whole lot of peppers so far.
Just peppers too.
Oh, the red peppers.
Okay.
The red peppers are meant to be spicy, but bell peppers are kind of sweet.
Yeah.
And then I got like a pack of carrots, diced carrots, and something else, something yellow,
not yams, something I don't remember what they're called.
A squash maybe?
Some kind of squash.
Not squash.
It was a very short word.
It doesn't matter.
It's mostly carrots.
Yeah, we got it.
Yeah.
Then some onions, this time red onions.
Okay.
I got some chives and what else did I put?
Like two different flavor cubes, one, like, I don't remember what they're called, like
stock or something.
Bullion.
Right?
Yeah.
So like one is vegetable flavor, the other is mushroom flavor because I freaking love
mushrooms.
Bullion cube.
Ah.
What?
Bullion?
I don't like this.
What?
What are you talking about?
Yeah.
Bullion cubes.
Like all soups do that.
Otherwise, they're super heck of a blend.
Yeah.
Curry too uses like curry stuff.
Okay.
So you put bullion cubes, peppers, something yellow, carrots, and red onions in a pot, boiled
it, and chives, boiled it for a while, and then you put it in a blender, blend it.
There's a little bit of, what's it called, a little bit of butter, a little bit of oil.
Yeah.
Then like, yeah, then I basically cooked it, a little bit of salt, actually a lot of
bit of salt.
Yeah.
I cooked all of it nice and cooked, and then I chucked it in the blender.
This is the kind of thing.
I don't, I condone this.
This is the kind of thing that my friends would say that I do, but actually, no, even
I'm not.
It's disgusting.
That's a totally Bencore move.
It's just like cook it all in a pot and then blend it and drink it.
I like it.
I think that's cool.
I actually think that's really cool.
Isn't it just baby food?
Yeah.
Yes.
It is.
Yeah.
It could be.
Exactly.
That's, if you had a baby and you wanted to feed it some food.
To be quite honest, I sort of had the idea because during the summer, I went to visit
my grandma and she was unwell, and I had to cook food for her like soups and stuff, but
she couldn't chew at that time, so I had to blend it in for her.
And it tasted fucking amazing, you know?
So I just remember.
I believe it.
I believe it's good.
This reminds me of the time I was trying to make mashed cauliflower, which if you do
it right can be very similar to mashed potatoes in flavor and consistency.
But I tried to do, I didn't have a food processor, so I put it in a blender and I blended it
way too much and it reduced itself so much that it became like a slime.
It became a pure, smooth, textureless cauliflower slime and it was absolutely disgusting.
You made slime.
You know, I would think that like, oh, well, sure, it doesn't have, it's not a, it's a
slime now, but it would still have that good cauliflower flavor.
No.
The change in texture made it totally disgusting and inedible, and I had to, even I wouldn't
eat it, is what I'm saying.
And just for future reference, if anyone tries to make what I just made, go easy on the carrots,
because I ate too much carrots and those other stuff, whatever they were, it kind of killed
the spiciness of the peppers, which I was a little disappointed in, I was hoping for
a tiny kick.
I don't particularly like spicy things, but the last time I made something like that,
I kind of lifed a little bit of spiciness to it, but this time it got absolutely murdered
by cats.
Murdered.
Okay, this chapter of PCP Kitchen is officially closed.
I think we're ready to move on.
Let's move on.
Wait, Ben, speaking of Ben Saint things, I have, I finally understand what it's like
to be you, Ben.
Oh no.
And that's to do things that are personally, that are perfectly reasonable and everyone
thinks that it's weird or that it's bad.
That's my life.
I'm just doing the most logical thing.
I'm just following my perfectly reasonable ideas, their logical conclusions, and everyone's
giving me the side I like, what the fuck, bro?
Yeah.
Such as.
I, so, okay, so I get to college, right, and you know, there's nothing in here anywhere,
and I have to decide what furniture I want, and I think, okay, I want no furniture, and
I want nothing on my walls.
I don't want to have anything in my room, and that's fine.
And then, and then I get to the point where, you know, I need, like, you know, I need pillows
and blankets and stuff, and I make the apparently huge, like, social faux pas of not getting
sheets for my bed.
So I just have a pillow and a blanket on my bed, and I have no sheets, and everyone's
just like fucking going crazy.
All my roommates are like, oh my God, what, you don't have sheets on?
People have come into my room like, oh, you're the no sheets guy.
People like, that's the thing that she'll know about me.
You know what?
I'm gonna, I'm gonna agree with that, because I just think it would be really uncomfortable
to sleep on a bed with no sheets.
It's not, though.
I don't think it is.
I wouldn't like it.
Munchy.
Well, okay, whatever, but that's not the point.
The point is that why are people going insane over this?
I was in an elevator, and someone was like, ooh, you don't sleep with, oh, you're the
person who doesn't sleep with sheets on.
Someone literally identified me as a person who doesn't have sheets on their bed because
it's a big fucking secret.
You would think you would be the pizza guy.
Yeah, no.
Okay, no, Munchy.
There's a reason.
The no sheets guy.
Mr. No Sheets.
Okay.
If I'm understanding correctly what the sheets are in this situation, there's a reason why
sheets are put on blankets and pillows and stuff, and it's something to do a little bit
with hygiene, and I think that's why people are kind of weirded out by you.
Yeah, you're gonna have a smelly ass bed, Munchy, if you don't use sheets.
You're gonna be a smelly guy.
You don't want that.
You know, you use sheets, you can wash them, but how are you gonna wash a mattress?
Okay, I mean.
That's the idea.
That's the point, yep.
That doesn't, that has, that you've phased me not even one night.
You used to when you sleep, Munchy, and if you have sheets, you can wash the sheets,
but if it goes straight to the mattress, you'll just kind of have a stanky ass mattress forever.
I wrapped, I'm wrapped up in a blanket, and I have my pillow, which is like my face sweats,
and I get a lot of pillow.
What about when it's too, what about when it's too hot, what about when it's too hot for
a blanket?
I mean, like, it's ultimately up to you, Munchy.
I'm just explaining why people are so shocked about it.
Yes, they think it's a hygiene violation, Munchy.
This is what they think of when they see you now.
I think that the idea that people are referring to you as the no sheets guy is why it's crazy.
Like, I can understand the concerns.
I just don't see why this would be like a big deal.
Like word, word really gets around about this one guy who doesn't have sheets on his bed.
Not a shame that Munchy was trying to keep his power level hidden, but unfortunately he's
now going in the opposite direction, becoming infamous instead of legendary.
I can't believe that you guys are siding with the people who call me no sheets guy.
I can't believe this is the thing.
I literally started this moment when I heard people saying, you know, me and your boys,
your roommates got together and we founded the organization of Munchy No Sheets.
She was like, I just wear sheets on his bed.
Yeah, it was disgusting.
I wanted to kill myself and you when I heard it.
I mean, I'm happy to announce, I guess, to all you fucking cultural, like, vultures
out there that I've caved and gotten sheets now.
So now I have sheets.
Oh, now you've broken your will.
I was going to say you should get a t-shirt printed like I'm the no sheet, like no sheets
for me.
Ask me about my no sheet.
You know, you know, you know, no fat, this is no sheets.
Hashtag no sheets.
You could just not use the trend.
Yeah, the no sheet gang.
Maybe we've all been bamboozled, you know, I don't know.
So here's the thinking is just that I don't like, I didn't want to have this thing like
I've always hated all the bedwear that that, you know, is accompanied with beds.
I hate the fact there's like a billion sheets and there's like different names for all of
them.
And there's like, all I all I want to think about is my pillow, my blanket.
And I don't like the fact that I have to like rustle through a bunch of like sheets like
get through to like the real sheet to get like, you know, all coaxed up in my cocoon
that is my bed.
I don't have to deal with all the complexities of that.
I don't.
I just want to have a very simple bed, but I guess that's just too much.
I can sort of relate with my sheet.
Like I hate the bothering with sheets, but I'll never stop bothering with sheets because
I know how smelly they can get.
And I know the feeling of fresh sheets and like how nicely smell and how relaxed and
how relaxed I feel after I put on some fresh sheets and I just like, yes, I will sleep
well tonight.
I'm going.
Okay.
I don't even.
I completely don't buy any of this.
I'm going to like, okay.
I'm going to wait.
I'm going to wait a year.
I'm like paying people money to smell my bed because I do not believe that they will have
any noticeable smell whatsoever.
I don't believe it.
You don't have the courage.
You don't have the stones to pull off a maneuver like that.
I mean, it doesn't matter because you're sleeping on a dorm bed, so you're just going to leave
it for the sucker who's going to take it next year.
So it's not like you're going to have to live with the consequences.
The potential fear, the potential issue you have is your roommates finding your bed smelly
and just making their life worse.
That's the risk.
I don't know if that's going to happen, but that's the thing to be avoided.
Wait.
Did the bed.
So I don't know.
Was there a bed there to begin with?
Did it have a sheet?
Yeah.
No, it didn't.
Okay.
So it was just a mattress on a frame.
Yeah.
And I had to go out and I had to buy everything myself and you know, I decided, okay, you
know what?
I don't want to spend the money.
I don't really need a sheet.
I don't really want one.
You know, I don't see the need for it.
I still don't.
And so I didn't get one.
But no, but now I'm a pariah.
Now I'm the fucking Jesus Christ, too.
A fucking boss who hasn't used it.
And everyone in the city, like I'm walking down the street and people are like, like,
he's chattering and like chugging themselves.
Oh, did you see that guy?
That guy's the one without the bed sheet.
Well, they're chucking stones at you and raining hellfire down on you.
Just tell them I don't need sheets because I am the sheet, man.
That's my motto in life.
There you go.
And when I try and pick up girls and be like, hey, babe, why don't you come into my sheets
and they're like, you don't have any.
This game was an expression.
Yeah, exactly.
Let's go on a voicemail.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
It's time.
All right.
We got a voicemail here.
Speakpipe people link in the description down below.
It's like speakpipe.com slash PCP.
I don't know what it is, but there's a link down below and leave us voicemails such as
the one we're about to hear.
This one is from a well researched thesis.
Don't at me.
Okay.
Go.
So the first human core thing is to send a two part voicemail because you think you're
riddle my ass Batman.
So confident about what human core is without even knowing what human core is to begin with.
And then you say some dumb shit about bathrooms called out.
All right.
So now that I'm in a voice grail, I'd like to murder my spot to let voices Mozilla Fennekin
out of the voice jail.
He doesn't deserve to be there.
What?
You're presumptuous.
You fucking you think you're in the voice shell.
Why would you be there?
Wait, who?
Who sent this?
A well researched thesis was their only name.
I don't know.
Maybe it's Mozilla under someone else who apparently we put into the grail and now they want to
I think you're saying that this message was so good they expect to have been put into the
grail as a result of the quality of this very message.
That's a grave miscalculation.
It's a really funny joke because this guy's going to jail.
This guy was good enough for the voice grail.
It's a really funny joke.
This guy needs to go to voice jail for his presumption.
Yeah, this guy's going to voice jail.
Absolutely.
I like hate this person.
You're so like cocksure of this message getting in the voice grail.
I agree.
Unforgivable.
Are you joking me?
It's unforgivable.
Yeah.
Well there you go buddy.
You're in jail for what?
Wait.
What is this?
I'm getting an update.
There's another message coming in.
I agree.
It's definitely a trap, but whatever.
There's another message coming in.
What is this?
A part two well researched thesis.
Okay.
What?
Go.
I'm so sorry.
Please let me out of the voice jail.
I smell like peace and calm here.
This is the worst.
I'm so fed again.
Oh, fuck you.
That's what you get.
That's what you get for trying to help somebody.
He plays like a fiddle and allowed us to destroy him.
He tricked us into making his life worse.
He's in shackles.
He's emaciated.
He's a skeleton hanging from the castle wall.
He's all according to plan.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
What he may have actually meant by that was like, he did say like, I want to like give
up my spot for Mozilla Fennekin to get out.
So maybe what he's saying is I'm in grails, but I'm going to give this up and go to jail
to release Mozilla Fennekin.
Well, that didn't happen.
That's not even how the system works.
You just leave the grail to get someone out of jail.
I think if you get the grail, you can.
It's like matter and antimatter, right?
You can add decay grail and it just becomes nothing.
You're both back to being poor.
I want to place a Mozilla Fennekin and well research thesis in the same room, you know,
hanging them up by chains on the wall and give the key to both of their things.
You just place in the middle between them and see who gets to it first.
That's a good idea.
Let's see how loyalty serves them in that situation.
And then the key out leads into like a bottomless pit and then they fall.
And then they fall.
So at this point, hippos communication screwed up.
It was unsupportable by editing.
Let's continue with the program.
Next one is from Di-N word trapped in commie hell, but it's spelled E-N-W-O-R-D.
So it's totally cool.
Oh, and it's also classified.
Okay.
So here's a classified call.
HQ, come and HQ.
This is Agent 1488 requesting evac.
Do you copy?
HQ, do you copy?
No answer.
Those godless commies must have come up with a new method of blocking the transflogestennial transmitter.
I need to get back.
This intel is too important.
The price of failure too high.
I promise sensei that I'd never use this, but I may have no other choice.
I need to do it.
I need to say the N word to hell with the consequences.
No.
Forgive me sensei.
This isn't PC.
This isn't.
Desperate times.
What does this have to do with?
Neoliberals.
Oh, thank god.
These are close.
It's all a bunch of filthy neoliberals.
There it is.
He said he was going to say it.
I don't know.
You've clearly missed the lore, but commie hell has been.
We've been in communication with communist hell and we've been making friends.
It sounds like a better place than normal hell, I guess.
Yeah, absolutely.
It's way more.
Everyone gets the same amount of brimstone in five.
There's no disparity there.
It's a beautiful utopian fantasy.
Next one.
This is from Ototo.
Okay, just get on with it.
Go.
When I was 12, I had a crush on my older step sister.
I once got close to telling her what her parents were out over the weekend, but I pussied out.
Her parents?
Are they also your parents?
And she's getting married and I'm still a virgin.
It would have gotten horribly if I told her, but I still think about it to this day.
Is that it?
All right.
Well, you're a freak.
I understand.
I'm so sorry, dude.
You know, if only, you know, it could have, you fucked up, dude.
No, I would have gone, it would have been so fucking hot if you'd just been like, hey.
Yeah.
If you just opened up, if you just told her, you'd be, you'd be nailing that.
You'd be hitting that right now.
To this day, you'd be getting married.
You'd be ankle deep right now, this very moment.
You fucking beefed it.
This is on you, my dude.
What is there to say about a situation like that?
Can we like ban all virgins from like doing voicemails?
But then much of them never hear from another.
Our entire audience, yeah.
Do you want to permanently ban the Teen CP from ever calling in again?
That's not true.
I would say that.
No, listen.
Teen CP is great.
Are they fucking?
Well, I mean the whole organization.
I mean, every last one of you.
Okay.
Here's the plan.
We ban all virgins.
We ban virgins from voicemails, but if they want them to voicemail, they gotta fuck us, dude.
They gotta fucking beat our meat up in real life and fuck.
Damn.
That's a good plan.
That's the loophole.
Official canonized.
There it is.
Okay.
Next voicemail.
This is simply called musings from prison.
Let's see what we have here.
Go.
And now musings from prison from the wisest man in voice jail, former CEO of Aldi Corp.
Aldi.
Oh, great.
Welcome home.
A few weeks ago, the video on the egg was brought up, posted by Kurzgesagt, and it's
basically just telling a story for anyone who doesn't know about there being one human
soul.
It gets reincarnated to all humans.
And at the end, when it remembers every human experience, it becomes a god.
Now, the point of this isn't to be a comforting tale of reincarnation.
It proposes some values and some questions, like equating effectively universal human knowledge
to godhood.
Other people might say that that level of knowledge would drive you mad, and those come
from different perspectives on life, whether you should pursue as much knowledge as possible
or stay within the confines of your own life.
There's also the question of, would it be worth experiencing all human trauma, which
far outweighs the human pleasure in order to become a god?
Your response to that says a lot about the perspective you come at life from.
In any case, I find it a very interesting story and a good reminder that when it comes
down to it, all humans are ultimately just kind of the same thing, shaped by our different
experiences that lead us into conflict, that can really be resolved if we understood where
the other person is coming.
That's all from me.
Thanks for listening to Musings from Prison.
Royalty Free Music from BenSound.com.
Um, gay!
Okay, I've never heard of the story of the egg, but I had the same idea in college and
I made a Facebook group about a phony religion, about a religion based on it.
We all talked about it, it's been a thousand times, this was a bad voicemail.
We already know this has been the same story.
Okay, well I just wanted to remind anyone who didn't know about that, but okay.
I'll die, fuck you, kill yourself, next voice out.
I had a similar idea, I had an egg today.
I just want to say, I was excited about the reincarnation, not necessarily that everyone
becomes one at the end, but what if you're incarnate, but you exist as your incarnation
at the same time, so maybe a person you walk by the street could be you as a different
incarnation.
That's what the egg is, it mentions that.
He said in the end, everyone is actually one person, I'm just thinking about, there's
several souls, but they can exist, I don't know.
Maybe it's just Adam and Eve, that's two egg theory, multiple egg theory.
It's a minority scholarly opinion.
There's the egg theory, and the major's proposing the egg carton theory.
There's exactly a dozen of them.
Alright, okay, next one, we've got, this is from, oh yeah, here we go.
Another message from, not even Cluster Punk can save me now.
Let's see how he's doing, go.
I gotta make this quick, this is the one call I get.
If they find out I'm in direct contact with the PCP, they'll send me straight to the
firing squad for target practice, I need your help, they're charging me for everything
they found in my car, which included a where the reason people are dying t-shirt, they
located in my damn trunk, so now I have a pending homicide charge, and they're trying
to put me away for good in PC prison.
They also tested me and found out that I have AIDS, that they traced back to that slut action
draft, so that isn't helping my case either.
It's awful, all the inmates are PCP head zoomers, and none of them patron the PCP, they've used
their Jedi mind tricks on the retarded boomer jail security to give them all the bonus episodes
for free.
It's impossible to sleep as the zoomers zoom around their cells in a flamboyant tribal
dance chanting, don't mind at night, don't mind at night, in the morning they engage
in a variety of ritualistic flash mobs to honor their teen CP gods in hopes of one day
ascending to a higher point of existence.
I don't know how much more of this I could take, my chakra levels are on the steep decline
and my Christ consciousness is evaporating, my power levels are so low, sleep evades me,
but when sleep does come, I'm so desperate to escape, I dream I'm rescued, my cold Corona
princess carrying me as he awkwardly bipedal gallops into the sunset, whispering sweet
nothings to me, only to wake up to find I'm still in prison by these simple-minded boomer
overlords and surrounded by zoomic remelans and goblins, please send help, forget voice
jail, I need voice bail.
We should start, okay, yeah, people in voice grail should start a voice bail fund for the
voice jail, what more can I, I mean, I'm certainly not going to do anything to help
this individual, but maybe you can.
Looks like this guy needs to voice jail, B.A.P.
That's so true, current occupants of the voice grail, we've got them snakes riddle my ass,
Batman, OneSpar, John Oreimo, Hell No Fresh, Lost Tape Archive, Racist Forest Gump, and
apparently Lost Tape Archive is on here twice, let me delete that, if one of you wishes to
step down and free this man from his prison, perhaps, wait, he's not even in PCB voicemail
jail, he's just in regular prison, yeah, he's in regular jail, we can't reach him there,
isn't PC prison, so it's technically still PC prison, yeah, but we don't manage the
PC prison, they're opposed to our existence, it's managed by our enemies, oh yes, yes,
probably the pizza party boys, if I had to guess, all right, let's go on, okay, we've
got, this is the PCPFC of the PCR of communist hell, is what this is, okay, why, just listen
to it, go.
Hello, this is the comrade Mao, party secretary to state cancer of procrastinator's podcast
fan club of the people's communist republic of communist hell, here's my understanding
that you have been contacted by a decanter revolutionary dissident, J. Graver was a ghost,
you have been spreading anti-PCPFCPCRCH propaganda throughout the communist hell,
yeah, I remember that, we have the PCPFCPCRCH want to make very clear that we are the only
valid recognized PCP fan club in the communist hell, and this uncertainty will be cross beneath
our iron fist, ex-comrade Graver, we will find you and you'll be spending a very wrong time
in the cosmo fraud to go good, oh, hello comrade Stalin, I just called PCP voicemail, you want
to say anything, okay, here you go, hello, this is general secretary Stalin of the PCPFCPCRCH,
they have composed poem for the PCP, I am very excited to recite it for you, all right,
yet or miss, perhaps it is they do not miss, you have boyfriend, perhaps it is he not give
kiss, he will leave you and find that nothing is amiss, he will do like with Khalifa and give
kiss, thank you, and they say and they say that communism doesn't create great art,
yeah, yeah, something about those voices make me think of it as like a Muppet show thing,
no, no, I'll tell you why, because of Team America, the guy said I exactly like the
rendition of the communist leader from North Korea and that, exactly like it,
that's, I don't know why, those are so funny, the chairman Mao one is so fucking funny, all
right, can we send them to voicemail? Yeah, you know what, you're absolutely right there, Ben,
let me see, I'm just going to send, okay, so these guys are on the same team, now that Che Guevara
rascal, he is operating on a separate organization, now we respect him as well, but so this is the,
let me see if I get this right, that we of course bear respects to Che Guevara,
of course, the PCPCRHK, what the fuck, it's the PCPFCPCRCH, there it is, yep,
that's what I said, okay, I'm adding that to the voice grail, so that's our boys chairman Mao
and the other guy, Stan, okay, great, fantastic, good work everyone, let me just clear the form,
okay, there we go, all right, we got another one here, this is from, let me see,
oh, Cam Smithical, Cam Smithical, I can't remember that name from somewhere,
I know that name, he helped, he helped on the Minecraft server, he helped people,
yes, that's right, back in those days, Bufalantopia, okay, well it's the bygone era, Bufalantopia,
the bygone era, we shall rebuild, go, hey guys, it's Cam Smithical, the Catechery Will
or Minecraft guy, it's been a pretty good month so far, I played Minecraft with a few,
got added to Mage's Discord, the thing that got me into the PCP three years ago,
Steven Universe, came to a head with its movie, I genuinely enjoyed the movie,
and Miss Squish and Stretch herself, Spinel, reminds me a lot of myself, pink hair,
wants you guys to have fun at Bufalantopia, waiting for you to come back to play with me again,
speaking of which, what's the next stream guys, it's been about six days, that's like 6,000 years,
is it me, did I do something wrong, in Minecraft time, I'm here,
oh Cam buddy, don't do it, this is definitely, oh, Cam buddy, that's it, that's it, that's
is this the end of Cam Smithical, uh, voice jail, will we ever go back, no I can't do it,
I can't do it, I will put a good voice grail, he's a good man, he didn't do anything wrong,
he put music to it, I won't cotton to this emotional terrorism,
let's give him one more chance, just like Spinel, he's just been horribly abused by his evil
creators who left him alone with no love and no hope for his future, and it was epic, he's still
doing 360s on his way lord waiting for us, oh, Cam buddy, Cam you gotta come with that sick kata
curry skin to the new server whenever we get it going on, I, you know, I don't know if any of us
are like, actually I'm not even gonna entertain the idea of letting people in for free, let's not
even go there, here's what I'm gonna do, I'm gonna say okay, biggest mistake, and I won't do this
again in the Minecraft server was evolving my, um, vibrava, because the way vibrava flies is so
funny, because when you, yeah, yeah, because when you, um, when you have a fly gun, you just sit on
the flygun's back, but the vibrava just, he just uses its little fire, or a dragonfly arms, it just
holds you by the head underneath it, and just like flies you around, it's way cooler, that is way
cooler, yeah, uh, that's good, oh man, just playing that song made me a little bit
uncomfortably emotional, uh, during this little camp, that was his plan all along, he's just trying
to fuck with you, he's trying to get you, don't let him, yeah, yeah, and, and he's literally dressed
as kata curry, like the most character for one piece, I love, beyond all others, this guy's
really trying to get, and riding way lord, the most emotional pokemon of all, I cry every time I think
about way lord, it's so big, I want one, I really want one, yeah, uh, okay, all right, we got, we got
one last voicemail, um, and this is, oh, coming out from the dirt, it's, it's mozilla fennekin,
he's managed to smell the loud, one more take from the voice jail, all right, this is the last
one, I wonder how many cigarettes did he have to trade to a guard to get him to bring this to us,
oh boy, all right, let's, how many bottles of jankum did he have to produce and trade?
all right, let's, let's roll it out, mozilla, go
Here I cause the Japanese colloquialist.
Brass.
Tail.
Who the fuck is calling me?
It's 6.53 in the morning.
What?
I got a call asking to break out the teen C.P.
At least take me to dinner first!
3, 2, 1...
2, 1...
Take the feed.
That, that, answering the voicemail, what?
Oh god
The power and that performance
We try to do is he's trying to try to like endear himself to us
So we get him out of voice gray or jail
That's what he's trying to do is trying to get us to make him in voice grail instead
We can't let him have a phone
Who let him have a phone and down again jankum comes at a high price. He gets to trade that
Well, so so is that is that no he's still in voice jail one jokes, you know pretty good
All right, you got to keep working in voice debt that that's definitely true
Maybe one day you'll join them
exactly like
You guys seen fucking up
Ultimate survivor Kaiji
Remember jail when he's in fucking he's in slave jail, and he's got a fucking bias way out. It's it's literally like that so fucked up
Yeah, you know, you know, that's a that's a great metaphor. That's exactly what it's like go watch Kaiji
If you haven't seen people that you'll have an idea. I know it's unbelievably good. It's like one of the greatest
Ten years or so. Okay. Anyway, that's it. Keep trying everybody
Oh, we're we are seeing some higher quality voicemails. I'm noticing. Don't think I'm not noticing. I'm noticing people keep them coming
I love it. That's the best part of the show for me
I love to hear the creativity the Mozilla the the remix stuff you're doing Chairman Mao
I really appreciate you calling in that was a that was a pretty good batch. I gotta say it was a good batch
So keep coming speak pipe link down below people love them. Love. Yeah, other than that
We have run.com slash the procrastinators people give us money support the show one dollar discord five dollars bonus episode
Some a possibly attached possibly separate nebulous amount of money minecraft one of these days
We'll keep you updated
They support the Vapors to Kickstarter get that dollar
For a while those pins. Where's where I get my script bed? Where am I getting my?
Doing this fucking phantom or in common specifically to procrastinate and put off finishing those fucking
If you gave us a script we could be working while you're working on that
Oh
Sucks
What else is going on? Oh follow us at TP procrastinators on Twitter for all the things going on with that and that's about it
Don't forget to give us money if you like the draw cast click on the link in the description to go to the quick draw
We just released another episode like a week ago. Yeah, there you go everybody. It's not dead
It's alive and over there and uh
And when you get permanently emotionally attached to the quick draw saloon come and check out the physical quick draw saloon
In the minecraft server that mage made painstakingly
We get you coming and going everybody
All right. See you next week everybody
It's true
Exactly
Bye