You're actually sitting here and you are your own human life size meme. Tell me who you are. Well, I'm
here to tell you what it is. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use. It's no use.
You know the rules! And so do I!
I need scissors. 61!
As I'm a digital cyberte-
An-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an-an
No.
Hello and welcome to this week's episode of the Procrastinators podcast.
I am your host for the week, the best guy ever, and I'm here with my panel of American
heroes once again.
First is Digi Bro.
Hey, what's up motherfuckers?
We have a true Blue American Gibbentake.
I'm...
I mean Hippocrite.
I'm a large water dwelling mammal.
The DeVoo.
Yo.
And our special guest for the week is our good friend Munchy.
It's about time.
Munchy is a guy who worked with Digi way back in the day doing art for him and is an eccentric
character we met.
He still does all of that.
He does all of that.
He does my avatars.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, his avatars have always been Munchy.
I forgot about that.
Yeah, that's awesome.
So his influence is felt to this very day.
And he's here to just talk about whatever.
So the subject of this week's, yeah, that brings us to the topic of this week's discussion
which is memes that need to die.
So yeah, you know, I've had a problem with the use of the term meme.
It's been really bastardized these days to mean funny image macros has become the definition
of meme.
And frankly, it's official now.
Like everyone uses it that way including me.
But the real definition is like an idea, it's like a little nugget thing that's like a consistent
joke or whatever.
And so we're going to talk about once the guy I go.
They are no longer welcome in this world.
So yeah.
So anybody who's got one to start us off.
Okay, I got a powerful one.
Munchy I believe has the big list.
Okay, shoot, shoot.
The one that I have highlighted and underlined and circled is the meme that Pizza Hut is
bad.
People who think that Pizza Hut is bad need to fucking kill themselves.
Pizza Hut is a great bargain.
You can get delicious stuffed crust, cheese crust, and it's just there's like one right
next to my house.
It's fucking great.
And if you don't think so, then you need to leave.
You know what?
I'm kind of with you on this.
I'm sure I'm not surprised at all by that.
Now is that in comparison to other pizza places, other speedy pizza places or just
No, no, just in general, we find it.
If you think that Pizza Hut is bad, bad food, then I think there's a problem with you.
And I think we need to take out your brain and put in a frog's brain.
Yeah, I can buy that.
I'm with you, man, because like, you know, I love pizza.
I would consider myself on some level a pizza like a fish and natto and stuff.
I go around, I eat pizza from all over the place and I don't, I don't like there are
pizza places I've been to that are legitimately disgusting where it's like I don't want to
eat this pizza ever again.
Pizza Hut does not fall into that category.
Sometimes I've gotten them and it hasn't been great.
They've got, you know, the pan pizza, that shit can start to like, if you eat enough
of those, it just starts like eating away at your throat.
I don't know what it is.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
They're very like, greasy, spongy stuff.
I mean, it tastes great, but it will eventually start to erode your.
Just after watching so much of H3H3 videos at their whole Papa John's thing, I had Papa
John's the other week and did not enjoy it very much.
Papa John's is not any better than the pizza.
I actually like Papa John's, but it's probably different.
Did they have those in England?
Yeah, they have them.
I didn't know that.
Yeah, but they're really good at it.
I just came back and I feel like talking about food.
Yeah, they got, I'm starving as well.
I just came back.
Well, I've been to, I just had to say I wanted to talk, I want to talk about Pizza Hut a little
bit more because I've been to Pizza Hut in the Philippines and it's a pretty interesting
experience because it's treated like a classy restaurant there because pizza is so expensive,
like comparatively, because it costs the same amount there as it does here, but their money
is worth like far less than ours.
So you know, trying to pay the same amount for a pizza is like going to a high-class
restaurant.
So like, I was going to say, getting them in Japan, like not only are they super expensive,
they're fucking tiny, they're tiny little things, they're not an American-sized pizza
for sure.
Because I ordered a medium one time and I was able to eat the entire thing by myself.
That's not something I can normally say of a medium-sized pizza.
That's because Asias are small though and we're big eats.
That's true.
Okay, Gib, you got one.
Oh, I do.
Get good.
G-I-T-G-U-D.
I actually consider this a my list as well.
Oh, really?
This is a Gib classic.
Well, I've always had a problem with this ever since it's really become a thing because
it sort of promotes the idea that if someone's having trouble, you should ridicule them for
it because it's not really used as, it's like the most aggravating way to say you can do
it, you know, which is what people would be saying, but it just makes everyone angry.
For example, I believe in the game that shall not be named when you were facing that really
hard boss at the end.
I believe I used the phrase get good numerous times and you were getting extremely angry.
Yes, I had a big rent at you for that.
Well, I remember.
My biggest problem with the phrase get good is when it's used as a defense of criticism
because anytime you were to say like, man, this game sucks, everyone will say, you just
suck at it.
You're just not good.
Like people, it's a defense mechanism for people who don't want to admit that there
might be like that other people even might find there to be a flaw in a game you like.
You just say, well, you're not, you're just not good at it, which I mean, in fairness,
if what you're saying is I'm not good at enjoying the game, then maybe you're right.
If that could be considered a skill, you know, I will come and say I'm bullshit.
And then the thing about that is, is just that like those people have almost always
like really immersed themselves in that game and they've invested the time in when it comes
to like games, you really get out of it when you put into it in terms of enjoyment.
So like you could play a game like Ground Zeroes, like for hundreds of hours, even though
you can beat it in like an hour and you're done, but like it's all about what do you
want to do.
So I'm with you though.
I'm with in general itself.
I just think it's a matter of like, I appreciate that those people can have fun with the game
that much, but it's like, it's like they're denying that there's other ways to play it.
You know, like.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
How could you like, oh, you didn't enjoy it.
It just means you suck and your opinion is now invalid.
You know, I hear it more often when it's just like somebody's getting frustrated because
I get frustrated at games.
Everybody says it would like Dark Souls, for example, it's a Souls thing for me because
whenever I get annoyed at a thing and I, you know, I don't usually publicly say, I hate
this game because I suck at it because that's stupid.
Why would you do that?
But, you know, if I ever see someone else getting told to get good, I'm just like,
it's just, it's really annoys me because yeah, it's pretty counterproductive.
I mean, it doesn't like mean anything.
It's yeah, it's just, I don't know.
I don't know how to explain.
It's like, what do you, what do you expect me to do after you told me to get good?
Am I supposed to just now like, oh, okay, thanks.
I didn't realize I had to get good.
It's equivalent to you mad, bro.
It's just right.
It is, you know, I disagree a little bit because I'm a big believer in trial by fire
and I want people to get mad at games and get, and get, I want, I want them to experience
the, the Jesse Wood Demon Souls experience of like, no, I'm not going to let this game
fucking beat me.
And I like to think that get good is just one way, you know, there's different styles
of learning and stuff.
Like I, I think hippo, like myself, I think is effective on me for example.
I think it does fuel me in the right way.
I know hippo is in particular, hippo is very like contrarian in mindset like that of like,
like that kind of reverse psychology doesn't work on hippo because he's just going to get
mad at you and doubly not want to play the game.
And as for me, I'm more like, I just am so unaffected, like for me, a game has to appeal
to me and I don't feel any like narrative self with the game, you know, I guess with
Dark Souls a little bit because I love the game so much that I was willing to put myself
through learning it, you know, like, and that's why with Dark Souls three, I'm like,
trying to go in blind for once and like, be able to actually have like that experience,
but only because I'm already so invested in it that there's no way I'd ever not play
the game, you know, like there's, there's no convict.
Like if I complained that it was too hard and you said get good, like it wouldn't change
the fact that I was already playing.
And I just like to point out to everyone listening that this is proof that Digi's
stance on spoilers is not always the case.
He is now proving himself wrong.
Please don't go back this.
I believe me.
I suffer through that a lot.
Like I've watched that video multiple times.
I'm glad Munchie's around because Munchie's watched like every podcast I've ever been
in so he can anytime there's a topic he knows we've talked about too much.
He can step in and I guess we could say that.
Yeah, Munchie's wanted to be in one of these for a while.
So it's good.
Munchie has been in one of these.
It just hasn't come out yet.
Oh yeah, that's true.
That's true.
Maybe one day Ben will finish editing that thing.
He said he's working on it.
Yeah, he said he's fine with it.
OK, who's next?
I like all of you.
You got one?
Any of them should die.
I'm just here to be a contrarian.
I see.
That's glad to have that on board.
Who did you?
Do you got one?
She's completely skip over him.
Yeah, I guess if you're going to say good.
I like it in regards to when someone doesn't realize that there that skill is
even a relevant variable of the situation, you know, something like that.
Like, why the heck do girls like me something like that?
Do you think it's not their fault?
Hey, get good.
Like, oh, really?
It's me. OK.
Well, the view, you know, I suppose in that way that is true, I suppose.
The view, I think I think you're going to.
I think you're going to come back on your stance when I say the mean.
Yeah, I'm also I'm also here.
You're going to be open mind thinking, well, I can't think of any means
that needs to die, but now I'm here.
I think you're going to be really on my side.
Oh, the meme view.
There's a few and we're not.
We don't need to get too deep into this, because I've talked about it before.
But the meme of objective criticism, I guess if that's a mean,
I don't really.
Yeah, that's a good one.
Well, it's a cultural idea that we're going to use the traditional
definition and yeah, lots of them need to die.
But if we're talking about internet memes, that's a bait and switch.
You we're using we're using memes in the sense of how Jesse constantly
uses the phrase X is a meme that needs to die about literally.
Well, I thought that I trained him in those ways.
That was only so I kind of had the mindset this was just going to be like,
I mean, like the Pizza Hut not being good food.
Like that's not really like a meme meme, but it's like an idea.
It's an idea.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's something that a lot of people seem to agree with on the basis
that it's something other people have said a lot.
Let's let's make that our definition of room for this.
Something that an idea that has been proliferated through culture
because of the fact that people keep saying it when it's not necessarily
that everyone like has come.
Like, I don't think most of the people saying Pizza Hut is bad
are like everyone individually coming to the conclusion that Pizza Hut is bad.
I think it's more of like, you know, that I think you guys would agree with.
It's it's something that I would like bring in as a problem
if I was ever a guest on the biggest problem, but it's kind of a big one.
So we can come back to me whenever you want.
I don't know, but I guess I'll just go and then we can do you after.
I could finish up my objective criticism.
Yeah, please. Go ahead. Go ahead.
And it's the reason I consider it a meme is that it's one of those things
that people throw at you, especially if you are a critic.
You get it in your comments.
You get it in your messages all the time.
And people use it like like that's just how it is.
Like people say this review is not very objective or like a good review
is supposed to be objective or just anything like any use of the phrase
objective in my comments.
I'm like, why? Why do you assume that's what I'm going for?
Or that that's what all criticism is or that that's even what the world is?
You know, well, I'm not prejudiced.
You know, I don't objectify games.
I think all games should be equal.
So my reviews, yeah, it's really problematic to have any kind of standard.
You know what I said in a comment or games?
They're all I said, just recently, he was like, you criticize roller coaster
three with your own subjective opinions.
And I was like, I think it's objectively true that this game annoys me.
There. Boom. That's all you have to say.
That is true. I cracked the code.
You see, you know, because did you just want to touch on this real quick?
Sometimes when we that's true.
Well, sometimes when we, you and I argue about subjectivity and objectivity,
I think the thing gets lost is that there really are some things that are objective
and they're kind of what Davoo was saying.
And they're sort of well, according to your subjective human observation
that now see that's not that's not true, because it is it is an undisputable fact
that I am thinking the thing that I'm thinking right now that that can't be
how do I know that?
Well, how can you know that I do know that I exist?
I know that for a fact.
You can't prove that I guess I sort of having the same thing that you normally
have that I know in regards to what is it?
Determinism, you guys have the opposite philosophy when it comes to that issue
about how if something can't be objectively proven, then it doesn't exist.
We actually we've sort of a new agreement on that, I think.
My position is that I am a fragment of Munchie's imagination.
You're welcome to that. You can do that.
I think my favorite hippo quote is the figment talks how I am thinking.
That's what he said about me one time for him.
No, I'm for him.
When did I say that?
He said it said it at Brodycon.
You're like, you talk how I think.
Oh, yeah, I don't wear that on my shirt.
It was cool. Oh, oh, I get it.
Because Munchie will just like smunch it out.
Oh, he's like, you know, he's like, you know, he's like, you know, the same thing.
Yeah. Well, he's the voice in his head.
That's brilliant.
All right, so let me let me throw one out there.
OK, here's a classic traditional meme
that that really needs to die.
OK, it's it's the overuse of the term Sempai.
It has been with you for rated to the point of absolute.
I hate every time I say and I really blame PewDiePie.
Not really not PewDiePie, but PewDiePie's audience, I think,
is the ones that made it happen because he's been using it for a while now.
And it's like it's like fucking like kids.
Use that explains me.
God, that explains so much
because I was really wondering how that became such a thing.
And if it's PewDiePie, I believe that really makes sense.
Because like it might have come directly through a yandere simulator.
I think was like the the thing that started it off.
Yeah, it's I mean, it's too recent, dude.
Senpai obviously is just a Japanese word.
It's just a word. It's a word.
So what's weird about it is that, like, notice me, Senpai,
like people now talk about it like it's this unbelievably prolific
Jap like anime cliche and it never really has been like it's not a thing.
You hear a lot in anime.
Usually most characters are in the same grade.
There's not a ton of shows where like it's girls pining after their Senpai.
That's like like I can't even think off the top of my head of a good example
of a notice me Senpai show.
So like that's why it kind of got weird to me because people kept saying like,
haha, is this like one of those notice me Senpai anime?
Well, like what is that?
That's not a thing.
That's like, yeah, I'm sure there's one anime has, but it's not true.
I don't even care.
I don't even care how specific it is.
The problem isn't how specific it is.
The problem is the overuse and the way that like it's been
God, it's been completely ruined.
I cannot hear the word Senpai in anime anymore.
I'm thinking of like the PewDiePie comments section.
It's a nice thing.
Notice me. Senpai is something that I you could possibly hear at like E3
by some really by some fucking.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
That's what it's totally like when like the marketing department
of a games company starts using that phrase like in their marketing.
That's when you know, you've got a dead meme on your hands.
And it's or there was a hot topic that said it as Maddox.
See, OK, that is right there.
Proof that is 100.
No, I didn't say that there was one.
I said if there was one, because that's Maddox.
That whole article about how when anything that makes it a hot topic
is officially a dead like yeah, yeah.
But yeah, I think with the Senpai thing, it's also weird because,
like you said, it's been used so much that it doesn't mean anything now.
And I think a lot of people use it to mean like like person
who is more popular than me.
Yeah, I do.
People on YouTube all the time that refer to like YouTube content creators
as their senpai, see it in my comments.
And I'm always like, do that shit.
I don't understand how I am your Senpai.
Like, where is the logical thread just that more people know who I am?
Does that make me an upperclassman?
Like, is it that I've been?
I think that makes enough sense.
Am I older than you?
What does it mean?
Where what makes me your Senpai?
You're better than no one did you, so it can't be that one.
That's true. That's true.
It's just I mean, it's understandable more when like
because we were making fun of Jeff for messaging
Demolition D and saying, yeah, right, which is something that people say
to Demolition D all the time and especially content creators.
And I see why he made himself look like a total scrub.
Right. I get why content creators do it because we're like,
well, Demo has more subs than us and we kind of do the same thing as him.
So he's kind of like our Senpai.
I get that.
But there's people who will leave comments on his videos,
like, notice me, Senpai.
And it's like, in what way is he your Senpai?
What class are you in together?
You know, like, what school are you going to?
I don't know. All right.
Yeah, it's it's your body on a slightly different level about this than me.
But OK, we can both agree.
It's well, I'm annoyed on the level you are, too, that it's just everywhere.
But like, I also just I hate when there's memes
that don't have like a strong logical thread behind them.
Like when people start using it in context where it doesn't make sense anymore.
Yeah, like, hey, would you like a muffin?
For instance, Jesse, like Jesse keeps using the phrase
like you can't teach that.
And I still I still find it funny because he always uses it in a situation
where it's like, and you can't teach that.
And you're like, ah, because it's something that comes natural, you know.
But like, yeah, when if you started saying like everything you do,
you're like, oh, I just got a headshot.
You can't teach that.
And it's like, what the fuck?
No, you can teach that. You can teach that.
Now, see, I kind of like that one.
I just got an A on my test.
And you can't that's why it's still pure.
You still like it because you haven't heard it that much
because Jesse's the only one really doing it all the time.
That's true.
In fact, the mere discussion of these would have any small meme
is only going to make it worse.
So perhaps we're doing a disservice to the world by just coming to rules, too, by the way.
Yeah, don't I.
Well, we already covered ironic comments or commenting things we don't want to hear
is a banable offense, so don't do it.
I want to go for a shadow man.
Shitposting. Oh, by the way, just to alleviate
maybe some of the concerns of our audience, I think we've only banned
like one guy on this channel.
And it's like, I'm pretty sure the only person who's been banned
was the guy who said that Jesse should be removed.
Now that they know if no one responds to them, they might be shadow banned.
They're living in fear all the time.
They just don't know what I would do is I would have a friend of mine
comment on one of my comments just to know if it was happening.
So if you're living in that fear, I mean, you should you should be afraid from now on.
But I think people were worried that we were already banning people
before like warning them about the comment to rules.
And it's like, no, we gave you some leeway for now.
But when that guy said, why can't you like, why don't you ban Jesse from the podcast?
That was when we I think that's the only guy we ban.
That's no good because because he didn't seem to understand
that Jesse also has access to the channel.
He broke so many rules with that one comment.
Yeah, it's it's no good.
Well, that's it for mine. Who's got another one?
Oh, Munchy, I'm sure you've got more.
I have a ton of more. OK, let me pick.
OK, OK, SJW slash Tumblr.
Core, I wanted Jesse to be here for this.
This also was on my potential list.
Yeah. OK, all right.
Go on. If you see a show that has a cal arts
art style and any like when I say that something comes in your head,
if you like Steven Universe is what you're talking about.
Yeah. Yeah.
If you see in public, a disgusting Steven Universe.
Yeah, being public cat shit.
And your first reaction is to just collect Tumblr core.
Then I think I need to put you down on the ground.
I need to put you into space.
I think your head needs to come off your shoulders.
I think I need to do some bodily harm to you.
That's so that's fair.
That's very fair, Munchy, because I also am extremely angry
when people dismiss a show like that just for its art style
without giving it a fair shake.
And it doesn't fucking mean anything. It's nothing.
Yeah, it doesn't mean anything.
I mean, the thing about Tumblr is that like it's a social media on
if you look at it on a broad enough scale, everything is Tumblr core
because there's there's Tumblr fans of literally everything.
You know, there's blogs for anything.
Most porn could easily be considered Tumblr core
because there's so much porn tumblers out there that like,
you know, Jesse is apparently here.
Bring him in. Oh, good.
Let's let's invite him in.
He needs to be a part of this particular problem.
Agreed. I need to brush my teeth.
OK, but, you know, just to clarify, I think when people say this,
I think they're mostly talking about the intersection between
like the SJW core and the Tumblr core.
I think that's the thing that comes to Jesse, Jesse, we're talking about
memes that we do die.
And the current meme is people calling stuff Tumblr core based on its art style.
Yeah, so I got a meme for you.
I got I got a meme that needs to die.
Yeah, us doing these at four in the fucking afternoon.
Oh, yeah, because four in the afternoon is such an inconvenient time.
It's the most inconvenient time. Who would be awake if you do it at a respectable hour?
Like four in the morning when I'm awake.
Jesse, you're recording, right?
Cool. Can I point out that memes that need to die
is itself now a meme is being more than wanting it to non-internet memes.
We're just applying it to society in general.
No, no. No, no.
This means works.
Me and Jesse have been using it back and forth for a while.
And that's been a great meme.
And that's why I already accused X meme needs to die of being a meme
that needs to die on a previous podcast.
And then I made a comment, I think in the chat.
I think you said that in the chat as well.
I made a comment that that was a meme that needed to die.
And then what I said you did, but those are all funny goofs
because I love this meme and I don't want it to die.
I made this podcast and it might become one.
I need this meme to die because of the fact that Jesse says it so much
that now it's like it's in my head all the time.
Every time I get mad at anything on the internet, I'm like,
just fucking this meme needs to die.
Or like, I've been walking around my house.
I've like opened the fridge and there's no milk.
And I'm like, this whole not having any look at your page to die.
You passed it by a car.
Well, we'll get into that.
It isn't me that needs to die.
Having higher patronage than me.
I just surpassed you by a dollar.
Four videos you've made.
Oh, I'm I'm raking up the page around, baby.
Oh, yeah, come slash Ben, saying yeah.
Yeah, it's my catch.
Actually, Ben just made a great catchphrase and no one should steal it.
It's mine. It's the best meme.
It's the name.
It's a meme I need to list for a hundred years.
We do need to talk about Ben Saints,
Patreon, though, because he just made this amazing Brunswick comic
and has no new patrons.
Oh, well, it's Pokemon.
Everyone go to Ben, no, SaintComics.com,
patreon.com, Ben, Saint, go read it, go watch it.
It's another story.
It's really cool.
If you like Pokemon, if you people like Pokemon,
which I know you do, if you're watching this,
go to Ben, SaintComics.com, read this comic.
It's a really touching and emotional short story
that is really cool and well drawn.
And he gained he gained more views on it
than anything he's made ever, but no patrons at all.
So who even gives a shit?
Right. No one.
I start the comic as the right.
So the meme that we're on is Tumblr for.
Munchy and SJW.
Good old Munchwick.
Yes. OK.
But we can let's we can move on.
I think we all get the gist.
Yeah, I got all right.
Here's that one.
Neutrality worship.
Ding, applause, applause, applause.
Neutrality worship. All right.
No, no, you fuck you get right out of here.
Oh, because that's that's pure Jesse.
That's pure Jesse right there.
Oh, it's cool to not give a shit about anything.
Neutrality is the best light.
It's the it's the one true path in life.
It's the only thing that makes sense.
I don't think Davoo's talking about
neutrality as in like, I don't care about anything.
He's talking about when when people
when there's two opposite two opposing sides on an issue
and everyone's like, oh, shouldn't we just meet somewhere in the middle?
That's obviously where the answer is when sometimes it's obviously where the answer is.
To say anything else is fucking retarded.
Oh, Jesse.
So you're you're you're if I say the two plus two is
you say to the problem with society is the other guys, right?
It's always the other team.
We got it. They're the ones making everything bad for everyone.
That's so fucking childish and stupid.
It's such baby logic.
Oh, we got it. No, you're wrong, Jesse.
You're dead wrong on this.
You've been for a while. Can I ask you guys a question?
Hey, Jesse, what's your stance on spoilers?
Don't don't don't.
What? I don't give a shit about spoilers.
Oh, that's so big of you.
That's so big of you to not give a shit, Jesse.
You're really the better man here.
No.
These fucking idiots, all 10 of them tried ganging up on me about
neutrality warship and not letting me explain what my actual point was,
not letting me get a word in.
And I was arguing with these morons for like 20 minutes before I realized
the recording had fucked up and none of it was even recorded.
So screw you.
I'm editing this and now you're going to listen to me, motherfucker.
These stupid fucking jackoffs.
They're all circle jerking about.
Neutrality warship is bad.
What about you have a stance on spoilers?
You obviously have a stance on something.
Yeah, great point, Digi.
That's not what I was fucking saying at all.
Has nothing to fucking do with my point.
Nobody is actually fucking listening to my point because they're all fucking
circle jerking and talking over each other and not letting me get a word
in edgewise.
This podcast is fucking terrible.
I hate these idiots.
They're not my friends.
They were never my friends.
I fucking quit the band forever.
I hate them.
They're fucking...
Oh my God.
It's so fucking impossible to even communicate in this stupid podcast
that we've created, that we've birthed through some vile satanic fucking ritual.
It never should have been created in the first place.
The PCP was a mistake.
It's nothing but trash, okay?
You put like eight of us in these fucking podcasts, which makes us all have
to fucking talk over each other and nobody can get a fucking word in edgewise.
It's finally you're talking.
When you're finally talking, you're fucking no.
You know that you're going to be interrupted.
So you have no choice but to get all...
You get all muddled up and you fucking have to scream your point.
And it just turns into a goddamn screaming clusterfuck.
I hate these idiots.
Oh my God.
They're sitting there.
They're not listening to what I was actually fucking saying about neutrality, okay?
DeVu brings in neutrality worship as a problem, as a meme that needs to die.
Oh, people.
Neutrality worship is not a fucking problem, and this is my fucking point.
Neutrality demonization is a fucking problem, okay?
Everybody thinks that you fucking have to have an opinion on everything.
Everybody thinks that you have to go out and vote for a rigged system that doesn't represent you.
If you don't vote, then you can't complain.
You're either a liberal or a conservative.
You're either a feminist social justice warrior, or you're an MRA neckbeard.
You're either one thing or the other thing.
You can't be anywhere in between.
There's no such thing as a nuanced issue anymore.
Everything has to be black and white.
That's how much discourse has devolved.
That's how much people have fucking devolved.
Because they shame you for not picking a fucking side on everything.
They shame you for neutrality.
They shame you for apathy.
They shame you for being rational and seeing both sides of an issue.
And you know what that does?
It just folds over in on itself, and it compounds the issue and makes everything worse.
Because what it does is it encourages people who don't really have an interest in the topic,
or don't really understand the topic.
Well, they can't just sit on the sidelines.
They can't just, you know, think about it.
They have to pick a fucking side.
So you have all these uneducated fucking people who don't really know anything about the issue at hand,
who just need to pick a fucking side because that's what society expects of you now.
They'll fucking shame you if you don't have a fucking team behind you backing you up
with a big fucking foam finger that says,
Yeah, we're number one.
Fuck the other guys.
The other guys are at fault.
Kill the opposing team.
And it just encourages stupid people to start shouting each other down.
And it rewards that.
And it pedestalizes stupid people.
It pedestalizes idiocy.
And it shames intelligence because the intelligent people,
nine times out of ten, are the ones who aren't picking a fucking side.
They're the ones thinking critically,
but God forbid anyone think critically about anything
before jumping head first into the current socio-political debate.
We gotta get that fucking debate live and televised for everyone
with their fucking popcorn and their fat-gaping maws
while we watch the country tear itself apart from the inside out
because nobody can fucking be neutral anymore.
It's not politically correct to be neutral anymore.
You have to pick a fucking side.
Pick it now.
You fucking maggots.
You brainwashed, simple-minded, knee-jerking shitlords.
Fucking demonized rationality.
Demonized intelligence.
Pedestalized ignorance.
Pedestalized knee-jerking.
What are you fucking doing when you boo-hoo and whine and cry
about neutrality worship?
You know, every time there's a fucking issue in this country,
every time there's a fucking debate, what inevitably happens?
It ends up boiling down into two opposing, warring tribes of fucking shit-slinging apes
with nothing to fucking say.
Two screaming tribes of extremists on either side
drowning out the rational, logical, cool-headed people in the fucking middle.
Every single time, that's the fucking problem.
That's the meme that needs to die.
And you go, well, wait a minute.
Maybe we can sort of see where both sides are coming from
and kind of come to like a rational compromise.
Maybe the solution is more in the middle.
Maybe it's not on one of these two opposites.
Oh, no, that's neutrality worship.
Oh, God forbid someone be too neutral.
God forbid anyone not be a fucking extremist.
The whole fucking world has turned into a bunch of idiotic zealots
who can't wait to shove their bullshit down each other's throats
and shout each other down.
Oh, but apathy is somehow the problem, right?
You stupid fucking swine.
You make me sick.
You're fucking perpetuating this problem with your bullshit neutrality worship.
It's a meme that needs to die.
God damn it!
Bunch of fucking idiots.
Oh, you don't think neutrality worship is a problem?
So that means that you just think that you have to be neutral on everything
and not care about anything.
Would you stand on spoilers then, huh?
You obviously have a stance that...
God damn it, you fucking idiots.
Fuck you, Davoo.
Fuck your shitty problem.
It's not a meme that needs to die.
It's a meme that there needs to be more of.
Neutrality demonization is a meme that needs to die, buddy.
You're a meme that needs to die.
You all need to die because you're stupid.
This whole thing is stupid.
This whole podcast, all of you, all of my friends are stupid.
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Anyways, now back to the podcast.
I got the meme.
Okay, what's the meme?
It's the meme, Gib.
No, no, no, Davoo, no, Dave.
Dude, how big is Bernie Sanders' dick, dude?
Yeah.
Go on, Gib, Gib, please.
The meme that needs to die the most is conflict.
I'm sick of it.
I understand all of this.
You fucking idiots.
Okay, you know what?
Alright, let me spin off this into one thing that's not really...
Guys, wait, my recording stopped like 10 minutes ago.
No, no!
Just start it now, just start it now, whatever.
We'll figure something out.
We'll just cut that entire obnoxious argument out of the episode.
We can do that, we can do that.
No, that wasn't obnoxious.
We can do it over and over again.
What do you want, Jesse? What are we supposed to do?
The meme that now needs to die is mistakes.
We have to fucking...
This podcast needs to die.
No, we can't. We're not doing that.
My name's Endless Jess and I hate all people who don't...
Alright, Jesse, Jesse, are you recording now?
Are you recording now?
I was recording. It wasn't my fault.
It stopped itself. My computer, all computers.
Computers are a meme.
Alright, we're not hearing any of this because I don't know if you're recording or not yet.
Are you recording now?
Yeah, probably.
Computers are a meme.
Okay, let's just sync it up real quick. Let's say one, two, three, fuck.
Okay, one, two, three, fuck.
We're gonna just cut out my...
Alright, we're good.
Well, what else can we do?
Anything else? The whole argument was predicated on everyone arguing and Jesse's part is gone.
We have to cut that entire probably 20-minute section.
Well, my board was the only part that matters, so I'll just re-record it myself.
Re-record it yourself and then add it in.
You'll be able to say whatever you want. You'll be able to make me look retarded.
It'll be funny. Go for it. Who cares? That sounds funny.
Okay, let me move on from that. Let's spin off to this because I got one that's related.
I got a big meme that needs to die, and it's the meme that children are people, okay?
The children are people. That is a total meme. It's not true.
You are not a human being until you're like 25.
And that's why I think that the abortion should be extended until 18.
I would have bought an 18-year-old who is not working outright.
I think that's totally fine.
I don't see any problem with that because they're not people and they don't matter.
It's just like putting down a dog, you know?
It's a job that you just had to do.
I know. It's a sad name for you, my friend, but that's just the way that cookie crumbles.
Exactly. You guys just got to restart this whole operation.
You're not managing the crowd here very well. You're not really doing well on getting people on your side.
Now, Sam, I'm trying to create a discussion here because I think you guys can agree that children aren't people and they don't matter.
I think...
Oh, here's neutrality worship again.
Forget the whole abortion thing.
Forget the abortion thing.
When I do it, it's matter.
It's the right of all society, but everyone else can do it.
And it's just a solution, right?
I told you from the beginning it was a solution.
Jesse's ranting about stuff that we had to cut from the podcast.
The only point that I wanted to make is the crux of this issue.
The reason that...
You wanted to cut out my part because you knew that I was right.
The reason why I'm not laughing at your whole position about 25 being the age that you can't get murdered is because I just know that we're just...
That's going to be an actual debate 15 years from now.
Oh, it's not murder. It's abortion.
And I can't wait for it.
I'll be an old man, and so it will matter to me.
And children, we all know children don't matter.
Because you're over 50.
That's fine. I'm not really opposed to the idea that...
If you really become a burden on everyone...
Actual societies in our world actually do approve of this kind of thing.
It's different periods of time, and I just know it's probably going to be a thing.
It's probably going to be a real thing here in America in like 100 years or something.
And so it's an actual thing that happens for some reason, even though it should be,
even though I'm the person with that kind of humor, it's just not funny to me.
Dang it.
Well, let me tell...
My real argument...
The real point I'm making here is the meme of children's opinions mattering.
Because there is nothing I give less of a shit about than what someone under
probably 21 at the earliest thinks about anything.
I agree with that. They don't matter.
Everyone under 25 is...
In my opinion, anyone over a day or under 120 who's not me,
I don't give a shit about their opinions. How about that?
Just listen to their opinion, and if it's retarded, dismiss it.
This is a real position. I want to legislate based on this.
I want it to be so parents are always right. Children's are always wrong.
I don't care. You got a kid crying like,
Oh, mommy, mommy, beat me up last night.
I'm covered in bruises like, shut the fuck up kid. Nobody gives a shit.
And we all reiterate the fact that Munchie is like 16, by the way.
No.
I forgot.
Yes, we can. Munchie, how old are you now? You're 15?
You're 15? You fucking liar.
That's no way that's true. You're like 7 feet tall.
He's got his repeater files.
Oh, shit. Oh, I'm sorry.
No, it's because Munchie is fucking Steven Universe,
so he's not aging properly. That's true.
He's the problem. He's 25, at least.
You gem things are all out of wave.
Except that...
Except that Munchie actually looks 25,
whereas Steven Universe... He really does.
...the idea is that he looks like a child.
What is Steven Universe?
I don't even fucking know. He's me.
Nobody knows. He's him.
I'm somewhat...
I'm somewhat with you on this, Nate,
but I don't know where you're hearing this idea
that children need to be listened to.
I came up with it.
I have not heard people...
People listen to what children say about anything.
I think that's a mistake.
When do people do that?
When parents do what their children ask.
That's a problem.
I have a weird...
I feel uncomfortable talking to younger people
unless they like...
I can talk to Munchie, because Munchie...
Oh, God, my fucking window farting.
What the fuck was that shit?
It was my window farting.
Well, yeah, window farting.
Yeah.
Anyway...
Fuckin' dirty Sanders just came in here
and got a fucking...
He got a quick promo on that.
Got a fresh political fart.
I can talk to someone like Munchie,
because Munchie has expressed himself in a way
that is similar enough to an adult
and understands where his limitations are
in terms of how much he knows.
I've talked to Munchie and had the impression
that you understand that maybe there's some things
you don't know about the world
and don't have an opinion on,
but there's other things you do,
and you tend to talk about things you know,
and I think that's cool.
I talk to some teenagers sometimes
who act like they believe they are already adults,
and it really feels weird to me,
because I can see all the gaps.
I can see...
When a teenager talks to me, I know it's a teenager.
There's no disconnect where I'm like,
oh, wow, you really sound like an adult,
but they'll talk about issues and stuff
like they're an adult, and I'm like,
how do you even talk about this?
You have not experienced this yet.
People thinking they know more than they do.
Regardless of their age, just make that the rule.
Like, hey, only say stuff that you actually know about.
Don't pretend to know what you don't know.
Just be fine with being ignorant.
Or at least admit that you don't...
Say something like, hey...
Look, I have seen people who are 90 million years old
and are ignorant about things, but they don't realize it.
This is something that applies to all ages.
Maybe it's just not equally,
but there's plenty of old people who just get really set in their ways.
It's more so when it's...
When it's a young person,
it's more usually that they don't realize that
reading about it and hearing about it
doesn't mean that they know as much as everyone else.
Well, also just that like...
I've seen a lot of head ties, so I know how to pick up girls.
Alright, good man.
The thing about teenagers to me...
You trip over a stick, you crash a rounder into a corner,
your penis enters the vagina as it happens, you know?
That's just how it goes down.
You take responsibility.
I know the thing that makes me...
God damn it.
The thing that makes it harder for me to listen to teenagers
talk particularly about their problems
and thoughts on the world, like broader stuff.
Well, not that they don't matter,
but that they're gonna change not too long from now.
I know that for me,
graduating high school,
I considerably changed my mindset about the world,
because once you have freedom
to do whatever the fuck you want,
even if you just go to college,
as soon as you get that freedom,
it immediately starts changing the way you think about stuff,
because you just have such different concerns,
and it broadens your scope of what things matter to you.
As a teenager, politically,
you might be interested in a lot of social issues
and have no interest in economic issues, for instance.
Whereas once you're an adult,
economic issues immediately affect you.
And I think DeVu would agree
that he would love to hear more people concerned
about economic issues.
But I think as a teenager,
I hear them talk about stuff that's like,
I just don't understand why people act this way,
and I'm like, once you're out of high school,
nobody acts that way.
People are so phony, dude.
People are so phony all the time.
I'm the only one who's real.
I'm not bad that often,
but when people talk about their issues,
I'm like, there's so many problems that you can have
that you will just simply grow out of,
especially artistically.
People not knowing what they want to do artistically.
Once you turn 20,
and you've been out of school for a little while,
then it becomes a pressing issue.
I don't know. I think that may not be the case.
I know people who are 20-something
and still are stuck in that mindset.
Dude, when I was 22,
I had no idea what I wanted to do.
It wasn't a matter of your development
as much as a situation that arose
or just certain things that happened to you.
What was the band that did that song?
High school never ends.
The whole point of that song is actually,
I can't wait to be out of these problems
and these stupid issues and these stupid people,
but then I graduate high school and everything's still the same.
So I guess it's bullshit.
It really depends on what stuff you're referring to.
Because I have a friend who's in the military
and he's always like, this is just high school all over again.
Yeah, the people might be like high school
and I remind you of that,
but your concerns are not the same.
Your monetary concerns,
when you're in the military,
are not the same as high school.
You're not thinking about,
let's say you get really emotional
because a girl dumped you.
In high school,
that's the most important thing going on in your life
because everything else is just happening automatically.
When you're in high school,
unless you're really bad at school
and you do lots of extra stuff to even make it through,
or if you're really someone who takes school so seriously
and you're getting the straight A's
and doing all the extracurricular stuff
and then you're kind of an overachiever,
for most people high school is autopilot
because the next day will always come
and you'll always know what you have to do.
You always go in,
you're always there for seven hours,
for most people they have a home to come back to.
So the things that matter the most to you
are the things outside of everyday life upkeep.
Whereas as soon as you're out of high school
that's the most important thing
is how the fuck am I going to make enough money
to pay my rent this month
and everything else is secondary.
Getting broken up with a girl,
it sucks but it's not nearly as important
as going to work.
All that is true, I just want to clarify
that my point initially was just that
their opinions on bigger ideas
and when they think that those matter
I think that this ties into it because
they're educated.
Because once you're an adult and you have
this grounded worldview
then that means a little bit.
I think the meme that needs to die is anyone
thinking that their opinion matters
or that they should give a shit.
Anyone who hasn't lived
my exact amazing life
is a fucking moron
and should go away.
If you want to see an example,
just go watch Manshild Marsh.
If you're not actually me
then you have no real experience
with anything.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I love giving disappointment.
Oh, oh no.
Hi Hippo, you got another meme.
I'm not Jesse.
Hey everybody, I'm interrupting the podcast again
because I was thinking about what I said
that last time I interrupted the podcast
with my little rant about neutrality demonization
and I realized maybe I was a bit too hard
on the DeVoo.
I mean, we're all friends here,
there's no reason for me to speak so harshly
and so I decided to bring the DeVoo
on here for a special
one-on-one segment
wherein he will
explain more about what he means by neutrality
worship.
Of course it was nobody's fault that the recording stopped
and the world did not get
to hear our exciting debate the first time
but no matter because I feel it's better
to present these kinds of nuanced issues
one at a time anyways.
It's a much better forum than
having five or six of us all yelling over each other
at once so hello DeVoo
and welcome to the
special interrupting the podcast
podcast.
Hello.
I am the DeVoo.
Let me tell you
about roller coasters
and
Ted Cruz.
I actually heard that Ted Cruz
dropped out of the presidential race
recently.
What are your thoughts on that?
Yes.
Ted Cruz was weak.
He was
incompetent.
A dullard.
He could not have won the election
on his own.
And so I devoured him
to gain his powers
and now
we
are Ted Cruz.
We
are Venom.
Interesting choice of words there
referring to yourself as Venom. Are you saying
that you are an alien symbiote?
Yes.
I am
black
goo
sentient goo
with teeth.
DeVoo
is goo
goo draw.
Well that's all the time we have
for in today's edition of the
interrupting the podcast podcast.
Thank you to my guest DeVoo
for taking the time out of his day to be here
but wait I did not get to
talk about neutrality
warship.
That's okay DeVoo neutrality warship was
a stupid thing to bring in in the first place.
It's not a real thing it doesn't make sense
nobody actually worships neutrality
you're complete retard
and the mean that I brought in
neutrality demonization
is actually a
much bigger issue facing society today.
As opposed to neutrality warship
which is not an issue at all
and does not actually even exist.
Yes
when you put it that way
I can see the wisdom in your
words
how could I have been so blind
I return now
to the stars
goodbye
okay that's how I would feel too
alright let's move on
I want one
alright
so
the word cringe worthy
oh yes that was on mine
fucking burns
in the depths of hell
the word cringe in general
is just not good
I have to fucking
this guy's being happy let's get on him
okay cringe
is like
an empathetic thing
if you see someone
doing something awkward
who has no self awareness about it
you feel
embarrassment for that person
that's what people mean when they say cringe
but the key word there is no self awareness
if somebody is doing an act
or doing something and knows what they're fucking doing
it's not fucking cringe
you idiots stop
you nailed it
if you fucking
if you go on
I enjoy cringe worthy stuff
but only when it's actually cringy
it's just like
it's so annoying
cringe now
here's an example
there used to be a famous comedian
called Gallagher
and Gallagher was this dorky looking bald guy
with a mustache and bright suspenders
and he came out on stage and he would smash fruit
with a giant hammer
and people would go to his shows
and they'd wear big plastic sheets
if they were in the splash zone
and everyone loved Gallagher
if Gallagher was just starting out today
he would be on our cringe
look at this goofy idiot in suspenders
smashing fruit isn't he an idiot
no motherfuckers it's his act
he knows what the fuck he's doing
he knows it's silly, he knows it's ridiculous
yeah that's actually the number one mean it needs to die
it's lack of empathy
and lack of understanding other people
or attempting to understand other people
yeah I see a lot of these
like cringe compilations
because my friends will get together
everyone gets bored and we just watch like
fail videos and cringe compilations
and there's always like
some stuff in there
like you said what makes it cringe
is that you feel bad for them
at least for me
I'm like oh man this guy has no idea
what a fucking idiot he's being
but then there's ones in there always
that are like just really fun videos
it's just people having a good time
it's just people dressing up
in funny costumes and doing something fun
and wanting to share it with other people
and sometimes I'm like
this guy clearly knew
this was a goofy thing to do
there's this one video
this guy paint
it's like a sonic video
and this guy is painted blue
like sonic
and he's like running through this insane looking backdrop
and it clearly is supposed to be funny
and like
it's hilarious
it's not cringy at all
it's a joke, it's a fully formulated joke
about running around as sonic
with a couple of this compilation
with like 12 year old screaming
leave sonic alone
like that's cringe
the biggest meaning to die is
there's a lack of empathy for other people
and lack of thinking about what someone really does
and thinks and is
and just making passive judgments without knowing
so you hate autistic people
is that what you're saying
they all need to die huh
should we reopen the first one
that actually brings up a point
it brings up another point
autistic is another buzz word
that needs to fucking die
because people have ruined it
autism
describes like a specific set of behaviors
and people use it just like cringe
oh this is autistic
if they just mean that they didn't like something
no motherfucker you sound like a stupid jackass
go on Wikipedia for 5 minutes
look up the actual symptoms and behaviors
that define autism
and use the fucking word directly
you could use that for like
that complaint with like so many things
like retarded
people using
buzz words and using words incorrectly
is a mean that needs to die
it drives me crazy
it makes me mad and I don't like it
but jesse language is an objective
it means whatever we want it to mean
I got something
it means that needs to die based on what you're saying
ok you need to shut the fuck up for just one fucking second
alright
listen buddy
why does this 15 year old
think that his opinion matters
listen buddy
he's got an old soul
that video I sent you
Nate earlier
oh yeah
listen buddy
is a Chinese language
a Chinese language
I got something
tell me do you
know what this is
like in your mind
this is the one
this is
listen
there we get a knife
we have
a true blue American give and take
this is the one
Utilizer
This podcast is SPARED!
Yeah, so going to my name, which is a super set of this.
Wait, I was going to go next before you.
Who didn't finish it?
When you're on the internet and people...
This whole fucking podcast is a meme that needs to die.
And they'll post a thing like,
oh, look at this thing happening over here in this place.
Look at those people. They are such and such adjective.
And people are like, yeah, this, yeah, this.
Like being in the video game community on the internet.
They'll post some link and be like, hey, look at this.
Those people are, you know, I come on,
I get on to the internet like in 2007, 2008, and 2009.
People are like, oh, look at that. That thing is racist.
That thing is sexist. That thing is racist.
I'm like, that's not racist. That's not sexist.
You guys are seeing it out of context.
Then 2012 rolls around,
and a bunch of feminists go,
oh, you gamers are racist and sexist.
And they're all like, you're presenting us wrong.
And I'm like, ah, you deserve it.
You idiots.
That's how I felt about the whole situation.
Gamers are doing things to die.
Hey, that's, that's misogynistic.
That is pretty annoying.
The whole standard label.
I won't stand to have my female brothers and sisters slandered.
I wanted to say, I think it's funny,
that like up until Jesse joined this call,
we were like, this was like a really, really peaceful
memes that need to die.
And then Jesse came in and he got really contentious.
But then Jesse's also the one who's most annoyed by it.
And like, it's like, I need to go back to bed.
I just think that's hilarious.
But um...
But anyway...
The problem is you, Jesse.
No!
You isolated the X factor.
To extend on what Jesse was saying
about words being used wrong and stuff,
some memes that I think need to die
are, um,
pretentious.
Oh, yeah.
Forced drama.
This is a new one. Have you guys heard this?
Forced drama?
I've heard it.
It's a meme that's gotten big on 4chan.
Oh, so you know it's intelligent.
Basically, any time there's any drama,
it is now forced drama.
Because there's no such thing...
Because I didn't like it.
Right, there's no such thing anymore of just like,
you know, like,
characters might get upset about something.
No, it's all forced drama now.
Well, the artist did choose to
have them react the way normal humans would,
and that was an artistic choice they made,
so obviously they're forcing that upon the situation.
There's no way
to justify this word,
because you're writing a story.
Everything is forced.
You're writing it. You're making it happen.
So, like,
where is the line where drama
becomes forced drama?
It's totally arbitrary.
Are you talking about fiction? I thought you were talking about YouTube drama.
No, I'm talking about fiction.
Yeah, that's also a meme that needs to die.
Yeah, YouTube drama is a meme that needs to die.
And the fact that so many people are, like,
getting big off of the back of that guy,
it pisses me off, but whatever.
My meme that needs to die
is people blaming me for the contentiousness
of this podcast.
If you go back and listen to it,
you'll see that as soon as I joined the call,
DeVu started talking about politics.
That's what fucking did it. Not me.
It wasn't a political thing, by the way.
It was a societal thing about...
It was a completely non-partisan thing
about how people interpret politics.
Go ahead.
Lay it all on me.
Blame me for all your fucking trouble.
Blame me for your people's inability to communicate properly.
I just think it's really funny,
because right up until, like,
our first memes were, like,
Pizza Hut not tasting good.
I'll be your fucking martyr.
Everyone fucking put me up on the cross
for ruining the...
You know, you're just like that guy the other day.
The podcast was worse because you made it contentious.
You know what?
I just thought it was funny because you said...
I wanted to give a shout out to that guy
who said that I should be kicked off the podcast.
You know, it's funny.
I was actually considering quitting the podcast
and retiring from it entirely,
but now I'm going to stay on forever
just to piss that guy off.
That one guy I'll never miss another...
I was in bed and I got up to come
and join this because I thought about that guy
and how much it would ruin his day
and everyone fight and working my satanic magic
and just bringing chaos into this conversation,
just for that motherfucker
and I hope he's listening and I hope he jokes on it.
I love that you brought that guy up
because we were talking about him before you came on
and how he's probably the only person
we've actually banned for the podcast comments.
But anyway, I wasn't saying
that you were making the podcast worse.
I just thought it was funny because you were the one going,
I should go back to bed.
This podcast needs to die.
It was so peaceful up until you showed up.
Not necessarily that it's your fault.
I got a real one.
I got a real meme that needs to die.
People bitching about movies.
It's a cultural fucking cancer.
It's choking America.
It's choking all of modern society.
People are cynical.
You just did that for like two hours, though.
No, no, no, no.
I knew that someone would say that.
But guess what, motherfucker?
If you actually watched my Batman v Superman review,
that was a positive review.
Yes, I approached my audience.
I analyzed that movie from every possible angle.
And that's why it's the best review.
I said all the positive things.
I said all the negatives.
And I recommended that movie.
I recommended it to everyone.
I said, everyone needs to see this movie.
And ultimately, Jesse, you weren't doing all the things
I hate about people bitching about.
All the things I hate about it, you didn't do.
You weren't being like a little twerp about it.
Like, I've always had a problem.
When I was like a teenager, especially,
I was a little bit more...
If anyone got mad at something,
if I just noticed that everyone hated something,
I would be like, you know what, fuck society.
I'm going to try my hardest to like it.
Because people just came in,
took some jabs,
and didn't really elaborate.
It's just, ha, ha, ha.
Wow, I've had a really bad day.
Almost as bad as Transformers 2.
Stuff like that.
Every joke will be...
Well, you know what it's from.
I want to see that review.
Who would do anything around that does that?
It coincides with the rise of
like, humorous criticism
or like the review as like a funny thing.
Yeah, I was going to say.
Because everyone wants to be...
Everyone is so wrapped up in their witty little
sarcastic, sardonic little cynicism
that they end up missing the forest
for the trees.
And it's like Star Wars, The Force Awakens.
It's, you know,
oh, it's too much like the original
Star Wars.
Why is Rey so good in The Force?
When the fact is, here's the real thing
that they're missing.
That fucking Chewie scene when Han dies
and Chewie goes ape shit.
That was the greatest fucking thing ever.
All those fucking scenes with Kylo when he was
like, throwing fits. That was fucking awesome.
Okay, here's a quick meme that needs to die.
The fact that that movie was good.
Just going to...
It was a 10.
It was fine.
It was a fucking fantastic movie.
That's my point.
It was a fucking, you know, it's a miracle
that that movie was as good as it was.
Star Wars was a ruined franchise, Nate.
It was ruined.
Those three prequel movies ruined the entire
fucking franchise forever.
And miraculously...
They made a good movie.
They made a great fucking movie.
They made a perfect Star Wars film.
People can't see the forest for the trees.
Mine only picks. And these meta fucking issues.
Like, why were there no B-wings?
Why was it so much like the old ones?
It has nothing to do with the actual story told in the movie.
No one cares about the B-wings.
You always say that, but I've never heard anyone...
I mean, tons of people complaining about B-wings.
Why the fuck would they complain about
there being no B-wings?
That made sense. It's not a real complaint.
Oh, but...
I feel the same way about Star Wars 7 that I do about it.
That is a real complaint.
It's not a real complaint. You can't just mind control people instantly.
It takes training.
Look, couldn't do shit.
She's had training!
She had a flashback that she clearly showed
that she's had some fucking training.
What, when she was like three before she could do anything?
No, it's retired. No.
It's not true. Who trained her?
Did Luke train her? Did Luke teach her how to mic?
Maybe.
It was pretty fucking...
Alright, please.
Someone else. Munchy. Beams.
My big old butt.
Anyone who fucking complains about
any movie sounds very deep and needs to die.
I can't tell who apart from Munchy sometimes.
Yeah.
Who's got another meme to lay on the table?
Oh, I've got one.
Okay.
People who think that fart is funny are stupid
when poo is literally like way better.
Poop is the fucking funniest thing ever.
Farts aren't funny at all.
Dude, I'm so with you.
They're fucking unclean and they're terrible.
What is a fart?
But just the smell of poo.
You know?
You just remind me of a meme.
I don't know.
I think farts are pretty funny,
but only in person and when there's a victim
and when that victim is not me.
Those are the requirements.
I fart on people all the time
and I find it pretty funny.
They usually don't fart.
I despise poop.
I hate everything involving an asshole.
It's all wrong.
Jesse, we just made like four songs
about assholes.
Yeah, you're a bit...
They were all hilarious and awesome.
That definitely needs to be killed
and raped and molested and embarrassed.
It's being offended by anything ever.
Yeah, what's that?
Especially being offended
by like toilet humor or bad language.
Those are the ones that annoy me the most.
Yeah, I'm pretty offended by that though.
I can't deal with it.
Oh, yeah.
Mostly it's the tone of
this bad language is bad
and you should feel bad
and I'm all superior.
Can we...
Both with Jesse's
movie bitchy thing and with your
offense thing,
I think it's really more sanctimonious
attitudes about those things
that bother me.
Bitching about movies can be fun
and you can present it in a fun way,
but it's when you're like
in a movie as though
you are above that movie,
that's when it's annoying.
When movie Bob writes his fucking
negative reviews where he makes it out
like this movie somehow killed his family
or like it's ruined cinema forever
or like he had...
It was so problematic that he had to
watch it.
His Batman V Superman video, he said,
I was literally twitching.
I was literally spazzing out when watching it.
Dude, is he serious?
Is he in the theater?
Dude, call the fuck down.
Dude, you have actual problems.
Tourettes or something.
If I'm watching a movie knowing that I'm
going to write a review of it
and that that review is going to make me
probably hundreds if not
thousands of dollars, then I'd be sitting there
like, huh, this movie's not very good.
Awesome. That means I get to write
this kind of video and it'll be a fun time.
Let me just picture yourself.
Hang on Deville, picture yourself.
In this movie theater, there's a giant fat man
sitting there watching a movie twitching
spazzing out like little words.
I can't believe it. I'm going to write a review about this.
I hate this movie. Just picture that.
This is a rancid future file of shit.
You know?
The problem is with you, my friend.
It's so obvious that he can actually get offended
by bad language because I can see him
like he thinks he's supposed to be
and I can watch him
decide his level of offense
and it's all about what words are said,
partially they're said, and what speed they come.
Like someone can go, ah, fuck,
shit ass, and you'll see like his
offense start to go up. His
offense towards bad language is like the
stamina bar in a souls game. It's very complicated
in advance, and I can
calculate it like someone goes, sure.
I showed him like a video and he was
like, ah, Jesus, God.
And then I was like, okay, if he says fuck and then
God, one more time he'll stop watching
the video. So I hope he says like shit
and ass instead. That'll be better.
It's so arbitrary and I hate it.
I tried to show them the resist series,
resist bro, because I knew they'd agree
with like most of the points, but
they denied it of themselves because he said
fuck twice and shit once and he
shouted it so that they're not allowed to watch it.
I was so mad about that. I was
so mad, like it was
so stupid, but you know, I can respect
my dad's opinions
towards other things, right, because like he doesn't
want to watch things that are like really disturbing
or like... Oh, DeVoo, you were so right.
You were so right about this point. I'm so
with you. Listen, there's nothing
wrong with not wanting to engage
with something. Right, I don't know if
my dad has the same sort of
same attitude towards other things, but
I remember when Daybreakers came out
and I'm like, oh sweet, let's watch that movie. My dad was like,
I don't want to watch stuff with vampires in it.
I'm like, why? And he's like, they're
disturbing to me. Okay, I'm just asked, does this man
think that vampires are real? Is that the issue?
No, but he just seems like
they bug him and also that movie
buried. I wanted to watch that and he's like, I'm
not going to watch a movie about a guy getting
buried. And my dad had a
really intense upbringing.
He's not like a guy who's been
privileged or anything. I mean, like
Jesse, never you described
like your life in a
drug crack. He's actually a train.
Poverty, bullcrap,
drugs stuff. My dad had that kind
of upbringing, although worse because it was the
60s and there was no internet to distract yourself
from all the misery. So he has earned
being able to
Well, you know, dads are really...
The reason why I brought that up is because I want to
say, like, there are things you can be disturbing.
No, dads are a great thing. If anything, the world
needs more dads. I love dads. I want to make
a quick, quick shout out to all dads.
I love dads. I want to be a dad someday.
I want to give an anti-shout out to all dads.
Dads are cool.
There's nothing cooler than a cool dad.
I love cool dads.
I also have a friend.
Munchie would make a strangely cool dad.
I want to kill all the dads
and I want to keep the dad of all the guys.
I have a friend who gets offended by things easily
but she doesn't have this attitude of her being
right about it. Or, like, you know, it's her
objective truth. Or at least she hides it
really well. She's very, very respectful
about it and I don't mind that. I just mind
the arbitrariness.
And that's my meme.
I agree. Though I kind of
hate people with bad reasons for doing
whatever they do. So I don't think
being offended by swears is a cool thing
at all, but whatever. Let's move on.
Resist, bro. So that reminds me
of a meme that needs to die.
Veganism. And veganism.
Veganism, yeah.
These fucking morons who think that cows
contain the matter.
I know. I know. Who gives a shit when an animal
thinks it's just shooting in the head to devour
its meat? It's delicious meat that was put
on this earth by Jesus and God for us to
consume. So, you know, frankly,
we're just doing what we want to do.
I'm so sorry that I have these
things in my mouth called
canines, these incisors
that I look in the mirror and it tells me
that I was created to eat meat.
You know, I'm so sorry that we take dumb
stupid, brainless,
zombie animal at cows.
Resist, bro.
Stand around and chew cut all day.
The meme at the core
of the issue is the meme that animal
killings matter and they don't.
They absolutely don't. I don't care.
Cows are particularly stupid animals.
They don't do anything. They don't even know
that alive.
We showed the clip of the cow getting its
throat slit and the blood coming out.
I was just like, I didn't even
eat that. I didn't eat that.
I don't know. Maybe it depends
on whether or not you've grown up
around cows sometimes.
I've spent a fair share
of...
I was grossed out by that.
I was grossed out by that, but on the level of...
Can we, by the way,
establish, because
if you were to look for Resist, bro,
you will find nothing.
We're talking about the Resist Capitalism
videos by Anthony Fankano
on his channel, That Is The Plan.
He created this character
Yeah, we created this.
He created this character who was in response to
the Resist Capitalism thing going around
on Twitter and he's just this weird...
until I stopped agreeing with this.
It was really great until he
decided to make his character into
like this...
He did this whole thing commenting on veganism
and basically trying to paint anybody who's not a vegan
as a lazy idiot.
He fucked up.
I can respect the veganism position.
I understand your feelings and I know that Paul McCartney's
line was
if slaughterhouses had glass walls,
everyone would be a vegetarian.
My rebuttal is
everyone had a cow in their backyard.
Everyone would not give a shit anymore.
I listened to Africa for a couple of months
when I was like a kid and
we had a cow in their backyard.
When you spend a lot of time around a cow,
you realize something.
You just want to eat that motherfucker.
They don't leave any more of an impression on you
than a tree.
That's the fact.
I don't know, I think cows are cute.
Gibbs got a descending opinion.
In the 1876 anime series
Nobody's Boy Remy,
the main character's only friend was a cow
and they had to sell it off because they got poor
and it was sad.
Vegans, I know that you won't have this movement.
Not for the person, not for the cow.
Vegans, I know you want to have this movement.
Vegans is just a third elitist and that's really the ultimate
meat that needs to die is fucking elitism.
I know you want to bring society in a direction that you wanted
but it's over now.
Drink your big black cow and get out of here.
Animals are tools
to be used by humans.
They can be cute, they can be funny
but they only matter to us.
The moment we want to kill them we should be able to
because we're the dominant species on the planet.
I agree.
I think we worked all this.
I think that our species worked so hard
to get here.
Not so that we could just go back
on everything we've accomplished
and fucking, and then
assume just because we don't
understand plants that well
does not feel anything
and that killing them is totally okay.
It doesn't fucking matter.
That kind of shoots our whole argument
when you start talking about plants having souls.
You guys are over thinking this.
Vegans are just annoying fucking elitists.
Elitism is a mean that needs to die.
It's the ultimate mean that needs to die.
It's really what it all comes down to.
Anyone who thinks that your stupid little belief
or your stupid little agenda
or what you like
or what someone else likes makes you better
get off my planet.
I'll give you one thing real quick though
and it's just that if we could just have
all the things that we have now
and also let the animals live
then okay sure they can live.
Since we can't I'm totally fine with eating them.
My meme that needs to die is
give us something.
What are you saying?
Okay.
I was just going to say I disagree
with the idea that
farm animals are inherently less interesting
than household pets.
It completely depends on
because they're just animals.
If you live with them they can be cool.
They can play.
Are you claiming that household pets are interesting?
I like my dog.
I like my pet.
Dog haters like Digi that's a mean thing.
I'm just saying.
I hate all animals.
Animals are cool.
I have three dogs
but if I wanted to eat
a dog burger I would totally
fucking break out my hammer
and I would smash that shit
and I would fucking eat it.
I just hate chickens and cows and shit
because they're fucking stupid and they don't do anything.
Chickens and cows are cool as shit.
They're cool as shit and they could be your friends.
Right?
Chickens are my friends.
I would hug a chicken.
I would have a chicken on my shoulder.
I'd be the pirate chicken.
I would never eat a raven or crow.
Because I've never been wrong about anything.
Oh, well done.
Give us another meme.
Munchy, you gotta have more, right?
Yeah.
I have a ton.
The meme that Sonic 2 is bad
and all 2D Sonics are bad.
Sonic 1 is worse.
The first Sonic 2 or the Sonic Adventure 2.
Sonic the Hedgehog 2 is a 10 out of 10 game.
Hang on.
I thought the consensus with the Sonic 1
was kind of the weakest in the whole series.
Sonic 1 either, but I still think it's a good game.
In the whole series, that's kind of...
I'm not saying any of them are bad.
I'm just saying that I thought people actually like Sonic 2.
I haven't heard this argument that...
I've heard the argument that all the old
Sonics are bad, but I think
where that really comes from.
I don't like any of the Sonic games,
but I don't think Sonic 2 is a bad game.
Play Sonic Advance.
What you'll realize is that
the people who are saying that, they've played all the new games,
which all suck.
I'm going to try out the old ones.
And then they play Sonic 1, and they go,
well, all the old ones are like Sonic 1,
and Sonic 1's not fun, so fuck old Sonic.
When really, Sonic 2 is
way better than Sonic 1.
So I think that there's...
I think that people who say all the old Sonic suck
have probably only played Sonic 1
and don't realize that 2 and 3
are much improved.
Not to say that I think they're great...
Okay, I'm not going to say they're not great games.
I just don't like them.
When I played Sonic 2 on the Blue Glow,
I was like, I appreciate what's good,
why this game is fun.
Sonic 1 is tedious
and has too many levels,
but Sonic 2 is like, yeah,
this looks like it's a tight, fun experience.
If you'd played it enough as a kid
to know how to play it,
then it would be extremely satisfying.
It's got great music and great visuals.
It's a solid game.
I'm going to go watch my video.
We've got to talk about wisdom teeth.
They're a meme that needs to die.
I'm sick and tired of these fucking things.
You should get them out too.
No, because my second meme was dentist.
I can't get them out because I don't want to
look at one of those motherfuckers
who want to go in your mouth.
They're expensive too.
I have 30 fillings in my mouth,
so the dentist
is like a second home to me.
I actually have 3 wisdom teeth
grown in, but they haven't bothered me enough
to want to take them out.
That's fine.
The meme that needs to die
is the idea that
English people have bad teeth and Americans don't.
No, that one's true.
I'm going to confirm that one right now.
I'm already cracking it.
They don't have the best...
Let's hear Gibb out on this one.
Go ahead. Convince us.
I don't know how to convince you.
I can just say fuck you.
It's not true.
I will say that when I...
I don't think it's that Americans have
better teeth. I think it's that we
put better teeth on television.
I actually want to disagree because
when I was in Japan, I distinctly noticed
a ton of fucked up teeth.
You can see that on Japanese TV.
I feel most at home.
Because the Japanese are just genetically inferior.
Let's be honest.
I think we need to take out the Japanese braces.
I need to speak as a man.
Speaking as a man with awful teeth.
We can treat the Japanese like cows and chickens.
You've all seen my teeth.
You all know that I've got the most...
God damn it!
Let me finish my fucking sentence.
Everyone knows I got the most...
When I watch
British and Japanese shows,
I feel much more comfortable
and less self-conscious about myself
because I realize that the stigma...
Because people make fun of my teeth
offline all the time.
My friends give me shit about it.
My mom's like 50 and she's got braces.
Because her teeth...
Genetically, I got my fucked up teeth
from my mom.
But she's embarrassed about them and wants to fix it.
I'm like, I don't give a fuck.
The fact that they're in disarray
doesn't really change anything.
It doesn't really matter.
It's just a weird aesthetic thing that people are obsessed with.
And only really in the US.
When I watch shows from other countries, they clearly don't care.
They've got pop stars with fucking teeth.
I was watching baby metal videos yesterday
to prepare for
my podcast with the Needle Drop.
The lead singer girl has pretty fucked up teeth.
And I was like,
they're internationally successful band
known for how adorable the girls are
and the girls got fucked up teeth like me.
So, you know,
I am asking for more fucked up teeth representation.
I had a hard time talking.
You can go listen to my videos from 2008
and try not to keep your eyes from watering.
So that raises
that straight into my teeth.
Although the day I got my braces off,
I was like, great, a retainer.
Awesome. I put that on.
How long do I have to have this retainer on?
The rest of your life. The rest of your life.
You put it on when you go to sleep permanently.
Every night. I'm like, uh, no.
I'm still doing that, dude. I'm still doing that.
As soon as I found out about that, I was like,
I would never get pregnant.
After your whole orthodontist shit's done,
you're given a retainer and said
use this for the rest of your life.
That's awful.
When I heard that, I would flip my shit.
With you, Jesse, this whole thing needs to go.
This whole thing needs to go.
So, like, only a week ago,
I'm like, alright, I'm not putting this thing on anymore.
I would rather have a good life and slightly messed up teeth.
Hopefully they won't.
Teeth shaming is a meme that needs to die.
Big problem. Go vote it up.
You know what?
Star Wars is a meme that needs to die.
I fucking...
That's what you like to...
No, no.
Okay, I guess I have a complicated stance
on this issue.
The Force Awakens
is by far the best Star Wars movie.
But I fucking hate Star Wars,
and it needs to go away forever.
I agree there.
I don't like what Star Wars does to people.
I don't like what it does to my country.
I don't like the obsession that everyone
in the fucking world has with Star Wars.
Star Wars isn't that special.
Whenever anyone is a super fan of Star Wars,
and I just think about how these people
could have been watching Star Trek this whole time
they've been wasting their lives.
Now that this is pretty much just turned
into the biggest problem in the universe,
I'm going to say franchise worship
is a meme that needs to die.
I think it's really cool.
That one is a serious problem that causes people to be stupid.
Yeah, I think that it's really cool
when we have a continuing story
or a continuing narrative that can go on for like...
Star Trek is a great franchise
because it makes sense
why they keep doing more.
They're always like a sequel to the last one,
except for those new movies
which just tried to reboot the original characters,
which doesn't make any sense
because Star Trek should just be always new people.
It should always be updated
to match the current technology.
So the Star Trek TV shows have always made sense.
Even if there's one that's not good,
it doesn't really affect the overall nature
of the franchise because that's the kind of show it is.
It's something that should come back every 10 years.
Right, and like in Star Wars,
that's what makes the next generation worse.
Right, and Star Wars reflected
where our culture was back in the 70s
in regards to storytelling
and it reflected upon the hero's journey.
More than that, it's been a progressive version
of that day in time.
Just having that black chick on Star Trek
back in the day was like...
Everyone was like, oh damn, Martin Luther King
called her up at one point and was like,
hey, just want to let you know, you're making us proud.
You're just being a black face on TV
and that's just helping our cause.
It evolved that way because like I said,
it reflected the hero's journey stuff
and it reflected the way that the world
saw warfare and evil empires after World War II
and all that stuff.
That's why I ultimately didn't like
Episode 7 that much because it was
still the same stuff.
I feel like the logical evolution would be
to tell a story that's all about
the way that storytelling is today
and reflected stuff like...
Star Wars has never been an intellectual series
from the beginning.
To be intellectualism, I just think that
Star Wars was fine being what it was
and it didn't need to be...
If you want to make another movie like Star Wars...
Just make a new sci-fi franchise.
To this day, you'll still see
New Star Wars merchandise and the commercial
on TV will show up and you'll get the music.
I'm like, dude, this was like
three movies and then three shitty movies
and I guess we're going to have more, but
why are we still on about this one franchise?
There's other ones that have better character designs,
better ship designs, more interesting stuff going on.
I don't want any of it repeated.
Right now we've got all the
superhero movies coming out and everything
and I think it's cool
for a little bit, but then when we get these
we've got to this point
where stuff will succeed
just because it's in a franchise and that
makes it so all anyone cares about
is franchises anymore.
What I was going to say is
it's not just franchise
worship, but franchise enabling
with people who don't like the franchise
but they will still buy it like Final Fantasy.
People like you, Jesse and Nate
you're going to buy Final Fantasy 15.
I'm only going to buy it to show the world
how fucked up it is.
And you're going to hate it.
That brings me to an even better point.
Just generally enabling
there's so many fucking
reviews out there that are like
why do people keep buying
these games from the perspective of
someone who bought the game
so they could review it.
You're a part of the problem.
Or exempt from this because they do it
they actually make something out of it.
But that's the thing, everyone's doing it now.
Not to buy the game, they're making a difference.
You can fucking, you can make a game
and you can like
probably make like back
like if it's a relatively cheap game you can probably
make back your money just on the number of reviewers
buying the thing so they can bitch about it.
That's not true. No it is true.
Because think about it, there's hundreds of
YouTube reviewers and I'm not just talking about big people
I'm talking about everyone on Twitter
who wants to fucking buy a game
so they can tell everybody else not to buy the game
even though their opinion doesn't matter and nobody listens to them.
You only, like, if you think
something looks, like, if you're mad
at the bad business decisions that a company
is making then tell people
I'm not buying this game and you shouldn't either
because I'm upset by their business decision.
That's why I parroted everything. I'm not a part of the problem.
I parroted millions of lives. I don't think that would happen.
Well Digi you have warped and perverted
to the point about Star Wars.
No this is a different thing.
This is nothing to do with Star Wars.
Because Hippo changed it and I
wanted to leap off of that into a different
meme which is people
enabling bad business decisions
for the sake
of, like, criticizing them
by way of supporting them
which doesn't make any sense.
I don't know how much that would make.
I might make like $2,000, $3,000
from that sort of stuff.
I agree there's some
Digi must be talking about
the larger environment we're in now
where people want to talk about the new topical thing
because they know there's going to be a desire for it.
Digi that whole scenario you said
about how the reviewers are the ones
enabling it because just them would be enough
to make sales for something low budget.
Well let's say there's a franchise that needs to die.
Episode, you know,
the first movie comes out in the franchise
everyone sees it and it sucks.
The second one comes out and it sucks harder
like stop watching it.
You're describing Final Fantasy XIII right now.
And then no one
watches the third one except for the reviewers
but apparently the reviewers watching it
allows it to make his money back.
People say don't watch it and then the audience says
oh we didn't and so then the reviewers are like
that doesn't happen though, that will never happen
because when the reviewers see it
they say oh guys
this movie's terrible
you should not see it and then everyone's going to go
oh well now I got to know how my opinion
is going to be a review and then they're going to go see it
because people are reviewing it.
I'm saying that we should
if you think a movie is going to be terrible
and you don't want people to see it
don't add to the hype, don't make it
there's so many things.
I'm wondering if our negative review
is inherently counterproductive
like because you made your asterisk war thing
that probably got more people to watch it
than who already would have.
Is it a destructive force to do something like that?
That's a good point and in fact criticism
is a meme that needs to die.
I hate reviews, I hate reviewers
it serves no functional purpose in the world
we have to separate down
it's only destructive
there's no such thing as constructive criticism
nothing good can ever come from a bunch of cynical idiots
patting themselves in the back
about how cleverly they can dismantle something
and try to shit on someone else's art
all criticism needs to be abolished
it's all a fucking disease
I disagree with that because my asterisk war series
is perfect and
everyone should watch it and give me 100 million dollars
and anyone who
doesn't think it's perfect is objectively wrong
but the point of it
Reviewers and critics can also make videos
like what is the appeal of anime
where it's all about go buy
spend money at all this stuff because it has
really interesting and diverse stories
we're talking about the negative review itself right now
however much
Digi is able to empower the asterisk war
by making his video about it
he also makes videos saying hey everyone
anime is really interesting
so go watch it
the whole point of the asterisk war thing was
to just use that show as an example
that's a meme that needs to die
the point of the asterisk war series
was not about
the asterisk war itself
and while I do in the end say
I wish people wouldn't watch this show
even though I did in fact incentivize
tons of people to watch it
it wasn't so much about this one show
it was about this genre
that I haven't covered any other shows
in that genre since
and I don't intend to because people keep asking me
are you going to talk about asterisk war season 2
and I'm like no because
that defeats the point
here's this type of show don't watch it
the reason that I don't consider
your asterisk review
in line with what I'm talking about
is because you kind of approached it
with a purpose and it was more analytical
a lot of people would make that case
my problem with
with the world and with criticism
popular criticism nowadays
and it goes back to Star Wars
goes back to everything I'm talking about it's all connected baby
my problem is that people nowadays
are more in love
with having the funniest negative review
than they are with actually understanding
the art in front of them
I think we're all really just mad at movie bob
can we all just like is that really what's happening
is that we all just really hate what movie bob
is doing
talking about every fucking smarmy
wise ass on the internet
well I don't watch a lot of those
so like I don't know the guys you're talking about
that's when that started with me as transformers
too because people would go
I didn't think it was a good movie
I just thought it was mildly entertaining whatever
but people were like oh it's so terrible
it sucks so much
no I think it's the worst movie ever
oh man you know oh jeez
this pizza slice was really terrible
it's almost as bad as transformers too
it's so annoyed me because
and even the star wars prequel stuff
before I saw the plinket reviews
I was very annoyed by those people
because they would always just be like oh man
I just got a freaking gallstone
and it hurt like hell
it was almost as bad as jar jar binks
but those movies really aren't that bad
I hated those people so bad
I hated that so much it made me want to like the prequels
because I hated those people about it
because they weren't being constructed
I felt similar
the plinket reviews are analytical
and have something to say
so you're making a decision
between substantive critiques
and just shitting on something
although you did say
constructive criticism doesn't exist
like five minutes ago
yeah well that was a lie
no wait wait wait
that doesn't mean it needs to die
everybody shut up I have to go back
it wasn't a lie I was right then
I actually agree
I agree that constructive criticism is the truth
even when he lies
because as I said in a previous podcast
it's only really constructive
if you know what the person intends
so like you know me ragging on Astros for
has nothing to do with whether the author
did what he intended to do
it has to do with me wanting people to stop
gratifying the author
I don't know dude maybe his intention was to make the worst thing of all times
that people would realize that he should be supporting these particular
yeah he succeeded
yeah like a meme that needs to die
is saying that you need to
make your criticism constructive
even if really what they mean
is just don't use exclamation marks
well this is getting too close to our
comment or rules and reviewer rules
so Munchy give us another meme to go
yeah Munchy go
new pokemon aren't cool
the fucking ice cream pokemon is
fucking amazing he's so cool
I'm not joking he's awesome
he's literally very cool
one of them is a ring of keys
he's the ring of keys dude
I know it's awesome
yeah but have you played Kingdom Hearts
Kingdom Hearts has keys in it
Kingdom Hearts uh no it doesn't
who's the keys in Kingdom Hearts there's no keys
the key blade you fucking idiot
it's not a ring of keys it's one key
I know that big pokemon are inherently cool
cause you put them in the lock and you go
yeah but this guy you just give him your keys
those keys don't come with him you use him
as your key holding device
he is a pokemon that is
literally a key blade monster
enough about the damn keys
so about these pokemon
a lot of people rag on
like uh
a garbodor and the uh
what's the one that calls into garbodor
it's fucking garbage
I appreciate that complaint
and garbodor
and jesse's video is fucking hilarious
with that part cause it's literal garbage
but if you
I'm feeling
god damn it
I had this song in my head all day the other day because of you
you son of a bitch
let me finish my point
you might break my heart
oh why'd you do anything so easy
ever be so hard to do
I wanna tell you
how I'm feeling and to say
I love you
yeah look
continue my point
do not try to co-op the fact that chaos happened
to interrupt the point I was barely into
god damn it
so back in generation one
there was this pokemon called
grimer that evolved into muck
and if you read the description of grimer
which is literally just a purple puddle
the darkness of warnings the future doesn't
scare me at all
nothing's like before
if you read the description
for grimer and muck they are literally
sewage
it actually says
literally sewage in the description of muck
muck is well known to be made out of cum
so the idea
of a pokemon that are just a blob of garbage
has always been a thing
and generation one had
volt orb that evolved into
electrum
muck is like
garbador is just this fucking
snaggletooth gay fag
I agree that garbador looks like shit
eggs? that one is pretty stupid isn't it
execute rules
execute rules are awesome
execute tour
I just think that
I don't think that garbador is
conceptually bad
the meme that
executor is not the best pokemon
is it's gotta die
I think
stop! tofu I'm not done
taking this point
why do you keep trying to come up to the chaos
to cut me off goddammit
anyways
the latest generation of pokemon
when x and y came out
I looked at all the pokemon from all the generations
and I tried to give them all
ratings
and I actually thought x and y had
by density
the coolest pokemon
there's a ton of really awesome ones
how lucha
dore bird it looks amazing
you've got
the whole sligeun slugdra family
that was one of my favorites
fucking
gujra
gujra should be an all female
should be an all female
gujra turns me on
gujra is like my main for that game
there's
the fucking one that's like a ghost sword
that one's pretty cool
I like ghost slag
there's a ton of awesome pokemon
and I'll say that
there are some shitty ones in there
that one that's like a barnacle
attached to a rock that one looks fucking terrible
that one sucks, that one's horrible
somebody just said that gujra turns you on
so I looked up
gujra to see what it looks like
and what the fuck is wrong with you
it's a goo monster
it's adorable
this thing is a filthy
fucking
it's an abomination
it's a big pink goo
that's what it is
it looks like it's got a mucusy chin
it's covered in jizz
it's covered in jizz, it's gross
aren't you not into like slime girls
and stuff
I mean I like slime girls but this dude's just covered in jizz
I don't want to touch that guy
he's pink and goo, I like it
he's pink and goo
I like it
let's say no slime girls
are you telling your thingamajig?
yes I'm done with my story
I actually had a very similar thingamajig
but a friend of mine
had gotten to pokemon a number of years ago
and she wanted to do a pokemon mystery dungeon
story with me
where we would each write our characters
sort of like a roleplay but not in order
and so we'd do a run of mystery dungeon
or we'd just tell a story
we'd just write a story
we never did it but we spent weeks preparing it
so in that time I had to decide what pokemon I was going to be
I thought that the entire list
and I concluded that by density
X and Y had the most consistently good designs
I had the exact same conclusion
and then when Digi came out with his pokemon X and Y videos
and said that this generation has the most
consistently excellent designs
I was like yeah, that one had the least amount
of unique pokemon
quality over quantity
I ultimately decided to be litwick
I believe that's a gen X and Y roleplay
well I like gen 3 because it's
if I had to be a pokemon
I'd be a litwick, that'd be pretty awesome
Shandalura is my favorite pokemon ever
yeah that's right but munchie was right
that wasn't X and Y, that was before
I think me and munchie can both agree
that munchlax is possibly
the greatest pokemon ever
not possibly, are you joking?
gen 3 or 4 right?
gen 3 I think
gen 4 is the best pokemon generation
if you think so you're literally fucking retarded
I think this whole thing about pokemon
designs happened with
all the best evolutions for the prior pokemon
all the best items, all the hottest
pokemon girls
munchlax, alright sucks
I believe the whole meme about pokemon generations
thinking that pokemon, the new generations
are good just because he wasn't
with it in the real old days
he doesn't understand the real pokemon
he doesn't know
I wasn't there in the real old days
Misty isn't even cool dude
Misty isn't good
wait what are you saying
I don't know
I didn't hear
I didn't hear what he said
should I be out of breath
he said misty is not cool
oh well
alright new meme
that's somebody new meme
munchie go, next one
4chan
everyone who goes on 4chan, I want to fucking strangle
it's not cool
get the fuck out of here
he's got it figured out
you guys are a bunch of babies
you can't handle the man's game
4chan is a force ultimately for good
I love 4chan because all I do
is look at the pictures
and I don't read anything
I don't like 4chan because I can't understand
the least terrible
message board on the internet
that I've ever seen
you haven't been on MLP board
that one is easily the most terrible
oh it's fine
that's not how we got into 4chan at first
I'm very shitty now
but at the time it was like
every third thread
has a post that makes me laugh
wow way better than anywhere else
on the internet because I'm on the internet
and I hear about how 4chan is this terrible awful place
where everything just sucks
all the time daily constantly
I go there and it just seems like people are
consistently more funny than anywhere else
and they're more real than anywhere else
4chaners who are proud
to be 4chaners
4chan pride
because I'm a little proud
I identify as a 4chan guy
I think being proud to be a 4chaner is antipathical to 4chan
culture
4chan is good
it breeds this 4chan pride attitude of
we're in a secret club and us 4chaners
we're cool we know what's really real and what's going on
I do hate elitism
you know what really annoys me is when there's
a war between tumblr and 4chan
I'm reddit and I'm like
I go to waller sites they're fine
who cares
I don't really post on 4chan much
because I just am not good at writing in their personality
when I make a post it just sounds like
people always go go fuck back to reddit
anytime I post on 4chan
that's the real problem with 4chan
and for most group think it's just another fucking
who's fucking Skype is going off
is that me I'll kill me
who the fuck is doing it
what is that noise
it's fine
best guy ever you are
you're an amalgamation of all the
worst traits of humans
I'm an amalgamation of all the best traits of 4chan
is what I am I took it all
which means you're the worst of all humans
is exactly what I just said
what's the next meme munchie
okay this is the big one
well I need to go last
I'll come up with another one
okay water bottles literally just
like fucking tap water
I bought it in an outrageous price
I don't want to pay like one dollar
for a bottle of water when I could just drink it
on my tap
hey munchie
every comedian from the year
2000 called
shit
but it's true
their message didn't seem to have an impact
it is a little sad that people are still
drinking it after so many comedians
made the point that they
I didn't even know that anyone else thought about it
oh man you clearly don't watch it
up comedy
or even biggest problem in the universe
what's going on
I've been using
the same water bottle for about a year
I've just been refilling it
wow
you're getting a little bit of the plastic shit
in your body if you keep using that
I know I'm probably going to die
but it's pretty good
I'm just saying if you're using one water bottle
do what I do and just get a really big one
I don't drink water
I hate the meme that foldable chairs
are not comfortable
I'm seeing a foldable chart now
literally the most comfortable I've ever been in my entire fucking life
you just remind me of a meme
I don't know how to feel about it
it's the meme that whenever I listen to stand up comedy
or listen to cultural criticism stuff
all the things I do make me a poor
fat midwestern American
going to Walmart, I used to eat at McDonald's
everything about my lifestyle
I'm with you on that
but then when I have an opinion
about some societal issue
I'm a privileged elitist
coddled, silver spoon, born
person who's never known anything about struggles
or not having tons of money
I don't know
and this has been the airing of grievances
by the DeVoo
we'll see you next week for more
I agree
I'm a little annoyed when people
make it out like
Walmart, middle America
literally everyone goes to Walmart
there are things that you can only
get at Walmart
where Walmart's the only convenient place to go
it's like
you go on the internet and you hear about how
we're
regular people and there's all these rich fat cats
and they look down on people and then you can go to
peopleofwalmart.com
look at how poor they are
I'm like, oh come on people
well, the joke with people of Walmart isn't better
it's just a joke
it's just offended by that joke
as you feel like you need to
oh man, that doesn't mean it needs to die
if a joke offends you, that means it's true
my rebuttal to that is always
I'll say, hey you know
I went up to some black people at a diner last week
and said, you being black means you have
less intellectual fortitude
but that's true
it's like, you know
no, you're doing it wrong
so that's a stupid thing
by the way, plenty of things can piss you off
even if they're completely not true
like, accusing, um, you know
nerd culture or whatever of being sexist
oh, it pisses them off, they're being defensive
that's because, you know, it's been a big
controversial issue that people have
obviously it's not always true
hey everybody, you destroy all nerds
get out!
Ben, are you recording?
you're a whole hour and twenty minutes into this
we already did that
I am recording and I'm ready to go, let's continue
don't mind me
hey Ben, since you're here, we're doing memes
that need to die, do you have a meme that needs
to die?
nope
okay, moving on
amazing contribution you've made
I'm glad I came
Munchy?
I have the biggest one
okay, I have this written down
memes are fucking funny
stop talking about them all the fucking time
ironically slash dank meme lovers
I hate you, memes are fucking great
yeah, I like memes
so the idea of memes being overused
I'm with you on this side too
I had the problem with the word memes
I love how as soon as Ben came back to this podcast
we went back to the original
topic
when Jesse got here, it all went crazy
when Ben gets here
I'm here to enforce the rules
of this podcast
Ben is a stern authoritarian
nobody talk over each other, nobody interrupt
each other, given
we need that bell
you know what Ben, rules
are a meme that needs to die
I had it with your rules
Jesse Wood is a meme that needs to die
okay
these memes need to kill each other
my meme is a meme that needs to die
I'm with Munchy's meme that
people who haven't seen Highlander
is a meme that needs to die
Highlander is the most important meme
in American cinema history
anyway
I think memes can be pretty funny
I still think Dam Daniel
is pretty fucking funny
someone said Dam Daniel to me
someone said Dam Daniel to me the other day
and I didn't know what it meant
it was a funny phrase
this guy made a ton of vines
of him observing his friend
Dam Daniel
back at it again with the white vans
it's pretty funny
you said that
reminded me of a meme that needs to die
a youtube channel called I hate everything
is a meme that needs to die
this fucking guy is not funny
he's not funny
he's not interesting
he never says anything remotely original or unique
he just jumps on every fucking bandwagon he can
all of his videos are monotonous
droning bullshit
he fucking hops on fucking e-drum of bandwagons
he hops on meme bandwagons
every fucking video he does gets up
forward to the front of Reddit because
oh man it's a channel and he rants and he hates things
he's not even fucking funny
that guy is fucking trash
he's
his whole career is built on e-drama
and on the fact that he has a funny face
and everyone wants to draw his cartoon avatar
everyone wants to suck his stupid dick
the thing I hate about I hate everything
oh and if anyone's wondering
the thing I hate most
that guy had a video about hating Dam Daniel
by the way
just want to throw this out there
my series fuck everything
by about two years
and is much better
the thing I hate about I hate everything
is that his name is very generic
so every time I think to myself
oh I'm feeling really bad
I hate everything I think of his channel
and I don't want to
he has ruined the phrase
I hate everything
he's made it unfun to say
I say we just ignore him
because hopefully he can become less
that's a meme that needs to die
actually is people thinking that
not commenting on something will make it go away
I don't think that usually works most of the time
no I think it will
it reminds me of another meme
of like
if someone is criticizing you about something
and you go well if I just don't acknowledge it
then it will go away I think a lot of times
that just doesn't work because I remember at one point
the irate gamer coming out with a video
saying that I was always fully aware
of the fact that
it's a much more complicated situation
ripping off AVGN
for context the irate gamer was a guy who came out in 2007
who obviously ripped off AVGN
oh no he was an irate gamer dude
oh I bet there's plenty of people who don't
because lots of people haven't been on that one
I have no idea who the irate gamer is
he has 157,000 subscribers
which is, you know, marginal
anyway the point is he came out with a video saying
I never wanted to comment on the fact that
my videos were so similar to AVGN
I never really wanted to stand up for myself
and then he had this 30 minute video
you know, if you had said all that
when it happened you probably would have
defused a lot of the video
and it does sort of help you see his side of it
but I don't know if it
defends him from the fact that he's not funny
and has like shitty wooden acting
and a terrible show
the whole point was that he was
not creative enough to make it seem
like he wasn't ripping him off
ripping off AVGN
so earlier on someone said I'm glad you came
and that reminded me of a meme
I realized, the lack of boy bands
there need to be boy bands because they're funny
to have in our culture, you know
they say so much in our culture
I've been listening to some Beatles
I listened to the first Beatles out of the way
Are you considering the Beatles a boy band?
I mean they didn't
DeVoo
come to America
DeVoo, a traditional boy band
We are going to try to classify
the type of thing we do
we just do what we like
yeah, that's the thing
cause those boy bands do
just worry about trust
cause imma give mine a baby can't you see
it doesn't matter
Backstreet Boys are infinitely superior
to NSYNC, I'll just throw that one out there
right now so everyone knows
that's a whole other podcast
no strings attached
I know the Beatles became more interesting
and I am much more interested in that stuff
but their first album especially kinda sucks
it's 100%
because one direction is today
like one direction is amazing
one direction fucking rules
because of
I've never had
the Beatles were really
artistically influence
make an analysis that explains
why
let me tell you right now
why the Beatles are a terrible example
of a boy band, it's because
they made their own music the entire time
they evolved through that process
they weren't figure heads the way the typical boy bands are these days
I don't care
all my definition of boy bands is a bunch of guys
who make songs about how they're all gonna
well that's their shitty definition but okay fine
because I like it because it represents
where our culture is at that time
and it's really funny that
it's a nice thing to be able to gently make fun of
it's so cheesy haha
we got one direction I guess
there was this sudden wave of boy bands
or at least there was supposed to be one
boy band who did the song I'm glad you came
that song which has double entendre
in the lyric that I love
but then one direction was the only one that stuck
around
it kind of sucks because the whole point
is to have lots of them
the whole point is to have lots of them
because they can all compete
like we had back in the 60's
like we had in the 90's
but now we have a boy band monopoly
today and that's just not nearly
as interesting
when you said I'm glad you came
and all that it reminded me of a meme
that I think maybe needs to die
which is the meme that women
are like really hard to please
sexually and men just
get off constantly at all times
there's like this huge disparity
in the way that women and men
have sex and everything
I think it's like way
blown out of proportion by like comedians
like you know where it
it can be funny but I think it's
affected the way people actually think about
these things where like
I think women are just as sexually
open and like into weird shit
and able to like be stimulated
as men are
that's a meme that women care about sex
or want at all they don't I can confirm that
they're not interested at all
most of the women I've talked to are pretty
fucking promiscuous
they say that but they're just trying to impress you
it's all a big fugazi
it's not real don't be fooled
when I had sex with my ex
girlfriend she was coming all the time
and I was coming rarely so I felt like
it was a reversal of everything
have you considered that she might have been a man originally
there's this girl who I've talked to for a long time
on the internet and
she shares a lot of the stuff I'm into
she's more intensely into
those things but I am
into other things that are also more
intense than she is into
so I don't know I think it's kind of a mixed
my point is that there's no
there's this idea that
all women are harder to please
and that is not the case
it's highly independent on the person
that's fair
yeah whatever
let me bring it back
a second let me talk about an actual
thing relating to memes that need to die
here's what I hate
okay
the whole modern
slash poll alt-right movement
the political spectrum there
it all couches itself in fucking memes
and makes itself like funny
and approachable
as part of its like marketing
like Hitler was right and shit
and I hate it yes the whole
every meme that comes out of poll
is nothing but like a funny sort of
packaging method for these terrible
alt-right ideas about how we need to create
a fucking ethno-state
and it drives me up the fucking wall
wow Ben you know a fucking white
thanks for ruining this hilarious podcast
with that deeply insightful fucking social
commentary
you're welcome
I have to realize
that most of those people are just being ironic
shit posters and they aren't funny and I still hate them
no that's how it starts
they start by ironically shit posting
that Hitler was right
at this point there is no way
to tell the difference between the people who made it
sincerely and the people who were joking
it's kinda like the
gamergate thing people start out agreeing
with like the funny meme part of it
but then they kinda get something
I got in the poll
and I was like wow finally
a place on the internet where people agree with me
on something
but then as I continued to be on it
I could no longer tell
if the anti-semitism was a joke or not
it's like gamergate
some of them are serious
I saw this big graphic that was like
here's all the things that Auschwitz really was
exactly it was like what
you hate neutrality worship so much
but you know what you get when you don't have neutrality
worship you get poll and gamergate
and you get fucking channels like
something out of a car that do nothing but keep saying
don't get involved people
we're in a bad place
we're gonna be here
let's get out
over and over again
that's what you get when you don't appreciate
and respect neutrality
neutrality is to be expected
I don't want to be appreciated
there's a bunch of fucking ideologues
pushing their agenda
two teams of monkeys
oh god
oh god this is the worst
there's no man left in the middle
you have no neutrality
these cacophonies are in the neutrality
podcast
okay okay okay everybody
shut the fuck up
here's my meme that needs to die
is the idea that people aren't going to take
everything to its logical extreme
if it proposes something to be done in society
people will go well
we're gonna do that today but in 50 years
it's gonna be like the super extreme version
you're like what no it's not
and I go yeah probably is
every single thing that humans ever do is extreme
I believe completely in the slippery slope
and that's my meme that needs to think
is the idea that the slippery slope is a fallacy
I think it's a 100% real thing
I think fallacies are a meme that needs to die
thanks for bringing that up
anytime some stupid asshole brings up like debate fallacies
and like in like a conversation
I'm with you here
holy shit that's annoying
you insulted me so that means you're wrong
you know Jesse I gotta say
I don't get people saying that
accusing me of fallacies but
I will say that while I think your style
of arguing makes people think you are
committing fallacies when you aren't
I was arguing with a commenter the other day
and he said
you're not responding to my questions
you're just using adhamanim
you're insulting me
listen up motherfucker
this is not a debate
debate fallacies do not apply
outside of a debate when you come to me
and try to insult me
I don't have to play friendly by the rules
of fucking courteous debate with you
I can call you a stupid asshole
if you're acting like a stupid asshole
it's not a fallacy it's the truth
the whole reason that adhamanim is a fallacy
is because an adhamanim is when you think
that attacking someone is
for your ideas
but usually you're just trying to make
the point is you suck ass in your dipshit
if the point you're trying to argue
is that someone is an asshole
calling them an asshole is very much
in service of that and is not a fallacy
I want to extend this a little bit
out to just copy paste arguments
in general which are all memes
if you're copying and pasting
some argument that is like
the rhetoric that everyone else is using
because like it's just
it's very much with all the fallacies
and everything
I think the point of knowing the fallacies
is understanding them
it's not winning an argument by going
you did adhamanim you lose
it's like if you understand
that kind of fallacy
then maybe you can make an argument
from the perspective of knowing that
that's three times you said fallacy instead of fallacy
I don't give a fuck
I think fallacy sounds cooler
let it go the first two times with the third one
okay let's move on
my point is that you don't need to
just copy it
I think probably one of the worst things
that ever happened
now that I'm thinking about it
was Idea Channel made these little videos
explaining fallacies
and they encouraged people
to take those and when someone
makes that fallacy to link them to video
and that is the
total opposite of what you should be doing
because every conversation is its own scenario
knowing those things
can help you to argue
but in each individual scenario
you don't go you broke the
code of conduct
there's a reason that rules are supposed to be flexible
to that situation
on the internet
people are smarter than they are
in your life
comparatively speaking
in terms of arguing
people
offline or at least around where I live
people do ad hominems
and red herrings all that kind of stuff
it's because when you're doing it in a text medium
you have time to think about your responses
that's exactly what I mean
I've almost never seen an ad hominem
I see your point of view
but I have the exact opposite conclusion
people are smarter
in real life when it comes to arguing
because in real life they fight
and they punch each other
which I respect way more
you know I might respect that more
cherry picking
debate fallacies out of a list that he found somewhere
I respect
cherry picking is a fallacy
are you accusing him of a cherry picking fallacy
I'm just going to bring up
I'm accusing him of being dumb dipshits
I'm going to bring up briefly
ad hominem
I don't want to focus on this too much
but this whole copy paste argument thing
I think this is exactly
if I were to try to get to the heart
of what bothers me about SJW
what I think it actually is
when it's a problem
is when it's this
it's when it's people who have read
an argument on tumblr
and they've decided it's true
and they just keep repeating it all the time
to every situation
without actually
the proliferation of toxic and problematic
because those are the words
if one of us makes a rape joke
in this video and then someone comes in
and they're not making an argument
they're just pasting an argument for why it's wrong
in all contexts that they got from tumblr
and they'll copy paste their response
right in there
I've seen so many times where it's like word for word
something someone read somewhere
and they've had that idea
like when we talked about
like Tom just the other day
got some shit for saying rape in the video
even though rape is defined
in the way that he was intending to use it
so it's completely wrong
and that's what happens when you're following
the use of different words instead of actually
looking into it
the idea channel thing about link to anyone
if they use a straw man or an ad hominem
it's like I almost never see ad hominems
I never see it online anyway
so I don't know what the point of that video is
you never see anyone call someone a fucking idiot online
I just never see it used as a substitute
for an actual argument except in the procrastinator's chat
not even there really
really not even there to be honest
but what I see as fallacies
it's a whole lot of really advanced versions
of straw man
or red herrings
it's way more advanced stuff
what the fuck is red herring
a literary device
no red herring was the bully on a pup named
scooby-doo
they always talk about it
it's usually like more
specific more detailed fallacies
that are more complicated
you're being a real red herring right now
this name was for red herring
and fucking freddy
freddy always thought it was red herring
because he was a bully
but then velma would always prove him wrong
I've never heard of red herring
you know really fred was the bully
because red herring never did anything
yeah
yeah that's true
I've also never seen a pup named scooby-doo
munchie give us another meme that needs to die
I'm not a fucking endless well of these things
I ran out
you said that you had like a hundred at the start
you said you had a notebook
no backlights
on your fucking nintendo
systems this happened like a
million years ago but it's still relevant
because I bought a gameboy sp and the backlight
still isn't even good the best backlight
is on the nintendo ds in fact the nintendo ds
is the best gaming console ever
well munchie handheld consoles
in general are a meme that needs to die
because it's gonna be worthless
no no no
please let's not have this argument again
we have like 20 minutes on this last part
for no reason
I just want to say that coming into this
chat late I just
I don't know if I love or hate that memes that
need to die is basically just things we don't
like
it's not so much
things we don't like as cultural
ideas we don't like like things that a lot
of people seem to believe in
tomato tamada
that's what memes are
isn't there a whole part
in metalgear solid about how like they hate memes
because it's changing like wasn't that
what metalgear 2 is about
and then in rising they're all like we need to increase the memes
which I wholeheartedly support
wait what
the plot of metalgear solid is
the plot of metalgear solid is that memes will
overtake everyone's minds
it's very comfortable nobody has individual thought
it's amazing because it's slow
the Kirby games aren't supposed to be fast
it's supposed to be enjoyable experience
that's why Kirby 64 is the best game ever
that I'm gonna come to your house and rip your balls off
and have the best power the power combined thing is
the meme that needs to come back to Kirby
the meme that Kirby 64 doesn't rule
I don't like that meme
is that a meme who says that Kirby 64 is amazing
everyone says it's too slow
it's too slow
it is too slow
it's too much like the old ones
when
all you gotta do is click
harder on your stick and you'll run faster
you can dash
or you can just be a pro
and just get firepower and use it for max speed
harder on your stick
how about the meme
the meme that needs to die
is the meme that Nintendo has never brought back
the power combining from Kirby 64
that's what Guy just said
it's totally right
it's a nightmare that they haven't
and it's sheer laziness
what I do like is that they make up new powers
but the combining was the best thing ever
that ever happened in my life
Kirby game I played
and every game that I play that doesn't have it
it feels incomplete
in the one with the mice
they had a thing
where you could combine powers
but they didn't become new powers
there were like four unique powers
one was like fire sword or something
but that's so weak
it's super weak
what they all need to do is make a new one
first Kirby game too and I was also disappointed
is somebody now playing Kirby 64
sounds like it
what? oh sorry
well guys
I think we should move on to the
what I know for a fact you will all agree
let's move on to our final
we need to have the final place
which is the fact that we don't all have
7 million subscribers
each
that's just the general idea
and they have to be different subscribers
that's a huge meme so everyone go to all of my patron
go to patreon.com
you'll find it on my page
give me all your money
make me do shit because people
one day we can all work together
and make projects together
imagine how great that will be folks
and I'll be the professional advertiser
it hasn't heard the term that we use
analysis HQ
that's what we're going to call it
it's going to be analysis HQ
it's going to be where we're all teamed together
okay fine
that is the working title
I want to call it the best buddies bungalow
I like that
the BBB
the BBB I like it
it'll be like the BBC
I'm telling you guys if this ever happens
over our office I'm going to make a wooden plaque
and get mounted over the front door
what about the procrastinator's pro tier
paradise
DCPTP
that could work
I want you all to move
into my house in Medford, Massachusetts
I want you all to kill my
downstairs neighbors
and move into their apartment
and I'll have the best time
I'm serious everyone come live with me
I know that DG is like pretty attached to his current lifestyle
I'm not
and then I'm going to live with Victor and you guys have to come into Victor's house
like um
I don't know I don't think most people know this
but my internet really sucks because I live in a rural neighborhood
so I can only upload youtube videos
like in the middle of the night
it sucks I can't
it's a shame that DG has a family
and I don't
but you have a family
Jesus
my family is a disappointment
your family exists though
you don't not have a family
they just aren't very great
well
I think it's only fair
to make it fair that we make DG's family
as shitty as Jesse's is
to equal everybody out
it's the only way to be fair
let's put fluoride
in Vic's drinking water
hey my family is awesome
they just can't deal with bad words
that's the only reason I need to get out of here
fair enough that's a fair reason
I just can't
man I can't deal with this slow internet bullshit
it's bad I can't deal with it
I gotta move I'll live in a freaking bunker
in like a triple bunk bed
with nine people on it if I have to
whatever it takes
to have a new life
I'm with you dude
so everyone shake things up man
shake it off like Taylor Swift
okay that's gonna do it
no no no no no
it's a me
alright munchie go
one final meme to rule them all
oh no that's the game that she'll not be mentioned
the worst meme ever
Undertale
it's the best game ever
and the worst meme ever
that's true and if you want to prove it
watch the new video that I just came out with the other day
it is the by far the best Undertale video ever made
and I hope you'll watch it
and see that I am the best
give me all your money
okay we've covered that point
we've covered that point thoroughly previously
so now we are officially done
we're wrapping it up okay
say goodbye
goodbye
before anybody stops your recording
just sync with them
and jessie too
no we just subscribed
to the channel
don't you know that we're all idiots
oh jesus christ
we're all idiots
no I'm not editing
I'm not editing
okay
okay well everybody will do the sync
now okay ready
I'll count three say uh
munch
one more time
the point is
jessie's stopped recording
right after the end of the podcast
we can all stop recording now
alright I'm done recording
whoever edits this is gonna be a fucking nightmare
don't even miss this video
hey Marcy
hey Marcy by the way
I did go and edit the
the nuclear throne cast
let me sing you the song
of my people
I hate this fucking podcast
I hate editing this
fucking podcast
I hate editing it
I hate recording it
I hate it
these fucking
jabronis
made this shit
at four in the afternoon
I'm in bed
they make me wait
they don't ever let me
go to sleep
they work me to the bone
they keep me locked up
in the basement
and I never fuck about my friends
about my rights
the time of the radiator
all night
I have to eat worms
and cockroaches
they don't feed me food
they feed me gruel and a bowl
ew
I
I hate it
and I'll put it together
that's fun
fuck it
fuck em
Jesse Wood is a meme that needs to die