Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I am the best
guy ever and let's see who else is here. We got Ben Saint. Minimum wage. Illegal band.
We've got Tom Oliver. I was really upset at the death of Steve Jobs. It ruined Apple
and it's cost him thousands of dollars in revenue from me personally because I will
not buy their products anymore because they're so fucking bad. Well, how unfortunate. We've
got Munchy. Hi guys, it's me, Prisoner308. Welcome back to day 238 of my let's play of
Breaking Out of Jail. The Warner hasn't found me yet but he just might. Stay tuned. I really
wish you'd said Prisoner358 because that's Casey Neistat's new company 358 and you would
have been the one political prisoner of Casey Neistat. But anyway, the one political prisoner.
Have you fucking seen that guy? Maybe I'm just the first prisoner. Okay, fair enough.
And welcome to Thew. Hey buddy. In the land of Ooze, there was a man whose name was Job.
This man was blameless and upright. He feared God and shunned evil. Nice. Thew, I just need
to let it sink in. How many, like, fangirls just squeed and glomped themselves because
Thew is on this episode. It needs to sink in for you. I'm very happy. I'm very happy
to have the legendary cryptid Thew break weir's head once more. Let's just know cousin of
Slimmer Man, Thew underscore thes here for another round of the Procrastiners podcast.
Yeah. Welcome. Welcome. Nate, you're the person. You're the guy who started it. What are we
doing? What are we doing? Why are we here? Listen up, everybody. Here's what we're doing.
We're talking about jobs. We're talking about jobs. What is a job? Where is a job? Please
give me a job. I deserve a job for free. I don't have to work. I deserve a job. Just
give it to me. Let's get into it. All right. So here we go, everybody. A definition of
a job according to Urban Dictionary. Here's what we got. Job means by which at least 30%
of your life is stolen from you. Here we go. To enrich the owners of a company making useless
shit that some other poor idiot in a job will buy. Wow. Are we going to have to fight Nate?
Tom over here. That sounds right. I'm with Tom. We need to seize the means of production,
you motherfuckers. I think I wrote that definition myself. Edited by Ben St. It says. There you
go. Ben has had an allergy to jobs. Why would you edit my perfect entry, Ben? God damn it.
Now that we're past the re-perselection podcast, let me just lay down the law here and say
that I am post-job. I am post-job. My generation is post-job. We do not need jobs anymore. We
are past the point of jobs and now we can just do things on the internet and that can be where we
make money. Well, I mean, yeah, we're in the crowdsourcing crowdfunding era. At least we're
starting out. We can't all do that. And I'm saying my generation is post-job. Well, okay. The reality
of the situation is most people get jobs. What? In America, at least. In America. What are you
saying? I am one of them. I have a job. I have a job that subsidizes, at the moment,
like my internet activities because I, you know, work at it and devote my time to it and stuff.
But listen to the second definition of job, by the way, because this is also incredible,
just in a different way. Job, something that's impossible to find because everyone only wants
to hire experienced people even though you can't get experience if no one will hire you and they're
too damn lazy, you're too damn selfish to train you. And then there's a quote,
finding a job is such a pain. I'm imagining like a guy, I'm imagining a guy in like a
rumpled up, you know, business shirt and like his tie is all pulled loose and stuff and he's like
hungover. He's all scruffy and five o'clock shadow and he's just been out pounding the pavement.
He's been out pounding the pavement trying to, you know, trying to work to get his life on.
Yeah, it's not at all that this person was actually sitting at their computer refreshing
Craigslist for one hour a day and deciding that was enough work. Thank you very much.
And then going back to play Hexbox, damn that Hexbox for the rest of the day.
There are definitely people like that, but the job market is pretty retarded, especially in
Craigslist. Well, don't get me wrong, it took me like three years to find a job that I now have
and it's a great job. It's a very good job. Well, it's funny, you said that and I was immediately
reminded of a tweet I saw on like the, you know, how like Twitter has like recommended things.
They had like the UX Twitter for some reason, it like knows that I went to school for design
and like always recommends me all these things. And one of them was a terrifying a job posting
for a programmer and it's like required 10 years of experience in Swift, which is like
Apple's programming language. And I just like posted a screenshot of that. And he's just like,
Swift has only been around for three years. Oh my God. It's just like LeMau. Oh no. So yeah,
it's pretty dumb. It's pretty stupid. Well, there's a lot to say about jobs. I mean, these are
actually really good jumping off points, these two definitions, because they're really, they really
showcase what the current generation thinks of jobs. And you know what? Well, wait, the last
generation, we are in the Gen X is represented right here. The last generation, we are not going to be,
you know, degraded with your disgusting millennial tendencies. We are, we are post job. We are,
I don't have a bite in this. Millennials, millennials failed to get jobs. And then Gen X is post
jobs. They get off scot free. They win. They want to take credit for, but really they had no choice
because jobs just don't exist anymore. Clearly. Yeah. That's, that's, they're for baby boomers only.
Hate the tale. The game has changed in a lot of ways. It really has. Because like in the old days,
you know, everybody says it, but like in the fifties, you know, you'd go to fucking elementary
school, you go to middle school, you'd maybe finish high school, and then you could get a job at a
factory like one guy and provide for you, your wife and your nine hot children. You could do that
back in those days. You could pay, you could pay your way through college where flipping burgers
over the summer. It's true. That's true. That is generally true. I do think that what has happened
is it's, it's fucking machine learning. Basically, as long as there's anyone who knows how to do
something, it'll only take some developer about a couple of months to create a program that can do
it as well. We're seeing this happen with like analysis videos on YouTube. I'm pretty sure over
the summer, someone's going to make an algorithm that can produce a nerd writer video. There's
already top 10s, dude. Nerd writer's not that far above a top 10. The last thing you want to see
is someone standing in your lettuce at Burger King. This person posted themselves on Burger King
standing on lettuce and posted it on 4jack. Yeah, so like this thing is basically the only way to be
a... There's so many cryptids. The only fucking way... Why did we do cryptids for the topics?
Next time, next episode. Sorry, dude. Sorry. No, no. The only way to fucking make money and have a job
is to outthink all humans and all robots in the world, right? And that's what basically all of us
do. We all talk about things, but it's certain things. I mean, that's created with the people that
had to figure it out slightly. The scale floor is so high for this game. Yeah. No, it's the only
fucking way. It's the only fucking way. The only thing you can do is to be ahead of trends,
and that's the only way to make money now. I mean, just the way that it is, like, and this is the way
that's technically always been. It's just that technology is advancing so fast now. Like the
only thing that anyone will pay someone to do is that they can't do on their own, or they can't,
like, hire a machine to do at a much lower cost than it would take to hire a human. So, for example,
you got, like, a janitor. Like, yes, you could get a robot to be a janitor in theory, but that would
probably be really expensive, so it's cheaper to just, like, hire a guy to push a group around.
The fact that we have every job listing for entry-level jobs requires 25,000 years of experience,
I think it's probably because of, you know, the legal system and employee protection system is
kind of being outdated at this point. Like, we don't have the frameworks, both legal and colloquial,
or unofficial, that we have as expectations for what an employee-employer relationship should be
is kind of dated at this point. At this point, having a job is just sort of filling in the
cracks that robots can't quite fulfill yet, you know what I mean? Like, and yeah, like, all the
friends I know who have, like, regular-ass jobs at, like, stores, they're always worked part-time,
but given as many hours as you can possibly make someone do without it being full-time.
Yeah. Right?
That's like 39 hours a week or whatever.
The worst.
Should be illegal.
It's like...
Yeah, I mean, it's just in the nature that, like, as long as it's not technically illegal,
these giant organizations are gonna do whatever they can to maximize profit and minimize expense.
So, you know?
But yeah, employee protection, like, I'm not trying to sound all fucking randy in here,
but it does make humans more expensive to take care of because robots, you can kick them around,
and abuse them all day long, and be a cheese gate with them, and I think that that is part of why,
uh, yeah, entry-level jobs require five years of experience now.
You know what? Guys, the PCP podcast is probably repetitive enough to us to get
AI versions of ourselves, and the people won't know the difference,
so we can just rake in the cash by putting our AIs up to battle week after week.
I have no doubt. There is a formula. There's an algorithm we could assemble.
You know, you start off the podcast, you got, like, uh, you know,
like, you get a percentage chance of, like, 90% I do an intro,
then there's, like, a 10% chance it's one of the other random people who'll do it.
Then after that, you've got, like, Urban Dictionary.
Like, literally just have a bot read the definition from UrbanDictionary.com,
and then you just move on, you just, you go to Wikipedia, you look up the entries there,
and you just make a random, you select random words from that page,
and you insert them into a thing. You have it cut from person to person every,
like, 20 seconds or something, maybe less than that.
And then at one point, you have a giant section of weird utilitarianism just stuck in there.
You just insert that awkwardly and arbitrarily, and then you just go to the questions.
Uh, it's, it's, it's baby shit.
We gotta get, we gotta get people on this. We, we gotta, we gotta calm up.
We gotta calm up. We need, we, this needs to be real.
Bonus episode, the, come on with the next bonus episode, the PCPAI episode.
Oh, that'd be a great idea. The next bonus is the bot episode.
Okay, we gotta get working on that.
Yeah.
Yeah, PBSA News channel made an algorithm up to themselves.
Please email me Steve Jobs.
Uh,
Nate, it seems like you're pretty, you're coming down hard on the jobs are good,
and everyone, and if you don't have a job, well, then my, like, time to perish.
Well, okay, listen, I, I'm just very hard on the personal responsibility front, you know?
And like, if you don't have a job, like, I, I get it.
There are all these challenges that you face in our, you know,
like my generation is at all these issues.
I was pretty lucky because right from the start, I was interested in technology
and like computer science stuff.
And now I'm a programmer, professional programmer now.
And like, it's, it's a great place to be.
That is, it's pretty much one of the best places to be to get a job.
And I'm really, really sorry to everybody out there who has an intrinsic interest
in to use the old cliche lesbian dance theory or like just what it doesn't matter,
you know, art history, whatever it is.
I'm really sorry that no one wants to fucking hire your ass once you get a degree in that shit.
But it, it like, it's your life.
It's your life to run.
And the world doesn't give a shit if you get a job or not.
Only you can carve out your place in the world.
So it's your responsibility.
Once you're fucking 18, 17, 20, whatever it is, figure your shit out.
Don't get into massive debt.
Don't be stupid.
Find a place where you can get a job or, I mean, or be an entrepreneur, you know,
go outside the system that's easier than ever now.
It's just, I, I don't, whenever I hear people complain about the job market, I think like,
I, what I hear is, it sure is unfair that people will not give me shit.
That's really upsetting to me.
And I, again, I acknowledge all the challenges involved in this,
but no one owes you anything and normal that attitude help you to get the things you want.
I'm interested in helping people get what they want in life and be better people.
And that means, you know, not just sitting around and wishing you had a job, but like
literally going out and like, if you go to school for five years and you get your art degree or
whatever, and then you find yourself flipping burgers and like, because that's the only job
that's around, I get it.
That's going to kill you.
It's going to be crippling.
But here's what you do.
You don't cry about it on your fucking blog.
You go and you assess your situation and you determine a path to get what you do want in life.
You know, a better job, you know, whatever it is you want, you make a fucking strategy
and it's just completely useless to sit around and complain about it.
If you're like interested in politics, you could perhaps address what you consider to be
like issues.
Like I'm not a hundred percent on either side of like the minimum wage debate,
but there is real stuff there.
So I could understand someone like committing themselves to fighting on some side of that argument.
But again, don't let politics distract you from the shit you should be doing to run
your life better.
That's the most important thing.
We are all responsible for our own shit.
So when it comes to jobs, you know, like my mentality is projected onto like,
you know, if someone else has a job they could or could not offer you,
you have to make them want to give it to you by providing value.
That's, you know, that's the long term of it.
I gotta tell you, this is one of the only weird totalitarian rants that I would a hundred
percent agree with and I don't have any problem with.
Well, there you go.
Fantastic.
I think we might be venturing into the realm of non weird utilitarian.
I think this might be the realm of normal, normal discussion.
Yeah, that seems like a pretty normal to me.
Well, okay, wait, my, my, my, my mother obviously would like me to go to college
and she is always like, you know, you're such a good artist.
You're drawn the computer and I can't even believe it to me.
I don't even get it.
How can you do that?
You should go to art college.
But I, this kid, this kid's able to go to yahoo.com.
I know an email account.
He's got computer skills.
How does he do it?
I just can't never know.
I can't even turn my computer on.
I don't know what the fuck's going on.
But, but if I, if I were to go to college,
I would go like hard in to like, like, like a STEM field, like like engineering,
like my go to is engineering and my mom's always like, well, well, why do you,
like you don't have an interest in engineering.
You don't like engineering.
Why, why wouldn't you go to something that you like?
Because what I'm not fucking stupid is why because I'm not,
I don't want to get a degree that won't help me get a job.
If I'm going to invest in going to college,
then my investment should be returned as fast and as quickly as possible.
You know, I know we've said this a million times,
but like what is the point of college?
What is the point of college?
It is to eventually prepare you for a job.
It is not adult baby camp, you know, where you can just go around and fuck around.
It is that, but that's not, that's not ideal.
It's not, it's not helpful that it is that we should strive against that.
Yeah.
I recently found out, like I didn't realize that this was a thing about, about courses like,
like that are just like, you can just like buy a college course.
Buy a college course that like just is a course for like a semester.
Like you can just do that.
You can just buy an art like, like course.
If you're like, oh, you know, I really want to be taught anatomy by like a teacher.
So like, you can just buy a course for anatomy at an art school.
Oh, well, dude, you know, I'm sure that's true.
And I'm sure like some, some schools do this differently than I was.
I've literally, I've literally seen that I'm going to do that.
So I mean, that's cool and all.
And like, if you think it's worth your money and like it's something that you're really interested in,
then great, you know, it's just, it's just, you know, you shouldn't expect.
Like there's no reason you can't like go to like engineering school, make that sweet dash
and then just put in the fucking work when you're doing your sick ass engineering job
and also do art.
That's not, you are not prohibited from that.
You don't have an excuse.
If you come home from work every day fucking tiring, you're like,
you know what, I have this passion for doing, I really want to draw or do whatever,
then you should try, then you should do or whatever.
If you don't like, if you don't do the thing that you want to do,
then you got to wonder like how much, how much you care.
I don't, I don't want to suck my own dick too hard here.
But like that's exactly what I did.
You're the best about this.
Yeah.
I mean, that this is what I did.
I, you know, I took the long, you know, I didn't do a digit and I respect digit for what he did,
but I took a much safer route with my career path where I slowly but surely kept working on my college,
kept doing myself, worked my shitty part time jobs, but the entire time I would do exactly that.
Come home exhausted from like building furniture at peer one or, you know,
stand on my feet doing just a bunch of stupid bullshit that everybody does.
It was like a shitty job.
And then come home and it's like, okay, time to work for like five hours making a video now.
I'm going to do that now because that's what I want to do.
And like, if you don't do that, I question how committed you really are to this thing.
Yeah.
I, what I love about you, Nate, this is going to turn into Circle of the Jerk episode two.
Yes, go.
It is, is, is that you like, like, like your base stats are like fine, but your true talent,
your, your talent is that you just will go forever and never stop.
You just like, you will just never cease your, your, your tiring advance.
No matter how like, like it hurts your body or soul, you will just never give up.
That, that's your one, that's your one true, like, like special unique ability.
And you know, again, I don't want to suck my dick either here,
but it's really nice that like other people have started to kind of emulate that with that,
like a bunch of people have done like their own we Aguiz now, or not we Aguiz, but, but
their own me a math of us.
Like, like I just copied guys like Digi and other people who have done like a month of solid content,
but it's the branding man.
It's that Huey's law that makes people see like, wow, this guy really sells me on how cool it is
to work hard on stuff.
And then other people do it.
And it's like, and then every, everyone is glad they did it.
They feel better.
They feel like heroes.
Ask them all, ask, ask math whiz, ask man mode.
Ask any of those other fucking guys who did it.
Uh, you will be a better person if you just tie yourself to a standard into the legendary
munchy W tiny hats vlog, watery advice.
This was vlogger accord at rad con three, where I took a shower after like 20 minutes
of debating if I want to take a shower.
Because you know, like, oh, you know, I, I, I want to just go downstairs and just hang out.
You know, I don't know if I really want to put in the effort to take a shower.
It's too much.
But then I fucking did it.
I forced myself to, and it was great.
Immediately the water hits me and I feel like a new fucking man.
And I, and this is the same thing that goes as I say in the video for like working out
or, you know, like, like, like exercising anyway, taking a shower, doing the normal people stuff.
You might not want to put in the effort into doing work.
But once you do, it'll feel so good.
It's just like, it's just, it's always like that.
It's always like that in every way.
And every way.
It'll feel good.
It'll be good when you do it.
And you'll get the experience, obviously, of doing it.
And if you don't, you will feel bad.
You didn't do the thing you know you need to do.
So you're even preventing yourself from feeling bad.
And that all becomes a good thing that you feel about yourself.
That's how like I feel when I work out and when I come out and do work or any of that shit.
Ben, this is what you're saying.
Oh, I was, I was going to say, yeah, you've got to, you've got to step outside yourself
and be like, I am, you know, I feel averse to doing this thing that is good for me.
But, you know, I know that even though it doesn't feel like it now, objectively,
I know that I will feel good once I do it.
And you have to like, you have to like kind of go on faith.
You have to kind of operate on faith that that is what will happen,
that you will be glad you did it.
Well, you know, the thing is, the problem is that everyone is like,
Oh, what's the point of life to be happy?
And that's not the truth.
That's wrong.
That's false.
The real meaning of life is to find something that gives you meaning.
You have to do something that makes you feel fulfilled.
And fulfillment is totally different than happiness.
Happiness is eating an entire pizza.
Fulfillment is like doing something that like 10 years from now,
you'll look back and think that was fucking amazing.
So I agree.
I think most people delaying gratification.
Delaying gratification is the most important skill anyone can have.
Look, it's called life edging.
All right, get into it.
That's it, man.
That's exactly it.
Like, I don't know.
Like I remember so well that full year,
it took me one year to make both of my Gurren login videos.
And I remember coming home after my fucking shitty job building furniture,
and I would grab my fucking laptop, get in my car, drive to that.
My parents had like loaned me.
It wasn't actually my car and that a drive to the fucking library.
So I'd have privacy and be able to focus and sit there on my terrible
fucking laptop that couldn't even play a preview image.
So I had to render out footage and then play it back.
If I want to see if the edit had worked properly and just do that.
And again, you know, six months, just like month after month after month,
working on the shit, coming home, recording, whatever I need to do.
I'm not interested in like making myself sound cool.
When I'm interested in having people understand why this is important
and why it matters that this is how you orient your life,
you got to know that the best things in life take work
and you should not sit around and be like, why are people giving me shit?
I care about you, everybody listening to this.
I want you to have the best life possible.
And the way you can do that is by empowering yourself
and take responsibility for your life.
I just want everyone to be happy.
God damn it.
And this is how you do it.
Nate, you're literally Caliburn.
You literally are Caliburn in every way, in every way.
Yeah, you're playing a game that's supposed to be unwinnable to play.
And you're just fucking cranking shit out
and you're abusing women every step of the way
and getting your shit done to its fullest extent.
And you'll know the taste of my lash.
The PCP is just the felt that Nate has amassed
over his years grinding out this fucking shit.
As I conquer planet to planet,
I'm like, dissented to that black hole in the sky.
Yeah, sick.
God, X6 was so good.
Remember that part?
Oh, it was really good.
Hey, this is all cool and all.
I feel like we've gone through a little bit of the philosophy.
Believe it or not, whenever we talk too much about how cool I am,
I don't want to do it for that long.
I would rather hear about some specific stories of jobs
that we've each had that are there that I've had a blot in my life.
This is the Nate redemption episode,
where I take back everything that I felt for the past three years.
And Nate comes around to be normal.
He'd be like, you know, guys, let's not get too into the philosophy.
Let's try and transfer into some standard stories here
and get back to the roots here.
Ever since Radcon, I've just had two phrases
ringing in my mind the whole time.
It's, where are the memes?
And give me the memes.
And by Christ, I know that's what the people crave.
So that's what we got to do.
All right, you were talking.
So you're barred from entry to talk about stories now.
Tom, you haven't said anything, basically this entire podcast.
You're basically not worthy of existence.
What else is new?
No, fuck.
I mean, I agree with everything that's been said so far.
Is that like, yeah, you got to like fucking make your shit happen.
And that's just the, you got to grind if you want to.
Where are the memes?
Give me the stories.
That's the memes.
Well, Munchy, you were horrified at my story.
I told you about how my job got fucked over out of college.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
So I, the reason like my whole life went to shit
is because I had, I had everything set up and lined up after school
and then it all was cruelly robbed from me at the last second
for no fault of my own.
So when I,
That's what they all say.
What?
Yeah.
I mean, I'm just going to like turn this all around
and take all responsibility off of my clothes.
Well.
But no, so when I was going to school, like during the summer
and the winter, I would work doing like, I sort of an internship.
It was like a college program at where my dad works.
He works as a contractor at Hanscom Air Force Base.
So he's like, he does like businessy sort of things.
He balances like a billion dollar budget and stuff.
He's a smart guy.
Cool.
And so he's like, hey, you're poor as fuck.
Come work here at this program thing.
If they accept you, you can go do that.
I'm like, okay.
So I just started going there, just like doing a like paperwork
and filing things away.
And then I got an email and they were like, hey,
we need this thing designed.
Does anybody know how to do art things?
And I'm just like, hey, this is what I've been waiting for.
So I designed them this whole like thing just in my spare time.
And like it wasn't open for like people in my position,
but I'm just like, I'll just do it anyway.
Because I have a bunch of downtime in the middle of like the things
they're giving me to do.
So I did it.
And they're like, whoa, this is fucking great.
We're going to use it.
So like it's all over the place at the base now and stuff, I guess.
And they still use it.
And I was like, oh, that's sick.
And they're like, you need to come back again
and do like design work for us this time.
Like, all right, sick.
And then I started doing that.
And then they were like, yeah, you're great.
We like you a lot.
We're going to hire you doing design here at the design team
once you're done with school.
And like six months at this point, I'm like, yes, I'm fucking sick.
This is great.
I'm going to get like a big cushy paid job right out of the gate.
It's going to be great.
And then fucking Obama cut the funds.
And they killed my fucking position literally two weeks
before I was set to graduate.
So when I graduated, I'm like, well, I have no backup plan.
Because I literally have been working where I was supposed
to get hired in two weeks.
And they fucked me.
And then I was a sad boy.
Winner of the Nobel Peace Prize, Barack Hussein Obama.
Where's Tom's piece, Obama?
Where is it?
I put in the hours.
I put in the effort.
What?
What was the thing you worked for?
I just worked for it.
It's a hands come air force base.
It's an acquisition base.
Yeah.
Any, are you commenting there to do anything to say
on the matter?
Well, military spending still increased every year.
Yeah.
Well, not for me.
I know, right?
Yeah, I guess it was bullshit.
They can spend a trillion dollars on like the F-35,
but they can't throw me like 30 grand a year, those fucks.
Now I understand why Tom's a communist.
It's not to rebel against the citizen himself.
It's to spite Obama himself.
It's to get back at the man.
The ultimate cracker of capitalists.
Yeah, yeah.
Tom is looking at Obama up on Capitol Hill
with his fucking fist clutch.
I was ready to make the man rock over there.
I was ready and bushy-tailed.
I remember going into college and I was like,
Dad, I know this is expensive, right?
How much is it going to cost me per month when I graduate?
And straight up, everybody has debt.
Don't worry about it.
And I was like, okay, Dad, I'll believe you.
I don't mean this to be mean or anything,
but your father failed you in this one small thing.
Small, small thing.
Well, okay, that's true.
I'm not trying to say the guy's evil or anything,
but so much of the generation above us has underestimated
and wasn't fully abreast of the situation
that we found ourselves in.
And it is fair to criticize.
It's fair to criticize for that.
Because out of school.
It was a different system when they grew up.
Out of school.
It was a system when they did this.
I really struggle.
My spills were $500 a month in student loans.
If he had said son,
you're going to have to pay $500 a month,
I'd have been like, well, I'm not going to school.
He probably didn't actually know,
because none of our parents grew up
in the same economy that we're in right now.
If you look at the charts about how, I'm sure you have,
but the charts of the increases in enrollment costs
of colleges and housing and boarding
and all the stuff that people used to do themselves.
But now, because it's all rolled into that,
you can just fucking take a big out federal loan
and just push all, delay the fucking, delay the pain.
As opposed to the growth which causes the cost
to constantly increase for future generations.
And I'll tell you, I'll tell you why.
This isn't really a conspiracy, because this is just true.
But it's the fact that we do this.
It's the fact that we just have this magic wand
we can wave and say, I get into college now.
All my problems get delayed for four or eight years.
The fact that that exists is why it's so easy for the colleges
to just keep blowing up their fucking prices
that they charge for enrollment and shit.
And the government just like magically creates more money.
Like, okay, sure, we'll just give you our money.
It's a huge fucking evil cycle,
and we all get ground up in it.
It's more or less the same thing
as what happens to healthcare prices and housing prices.
Sounds right to me.
I don't trust big corporations on any of this shit.
I trust big corporations to make my shoes
and make my iPhones and stuff.
I don't protect them to protect my fucking data or anything.
But that's why I would much rather any fucking time,
like just like deal with individual people
and have like a small little business that I run one-on-one,
as opposed to these giant corporations
that literally are more powerful than the governments
that theoretically control them.
But actually, they have massive sway over
through fucking funding them politically
through super PACs and all this bullshit.
Oh, it's a mad world.
What are we to do?
Is there anything that we could do about the system?
How can we change the system?
Is there any way to do that?
Or is it so off the rails now
that there's no point in even acknowledging
that there's a problem?
I really think the only thing to do
is stop relying on the government.
The solution is clearly to seize the means of production.
Yeah!
Well, it sort of is only in the sense of by seizing it,
we stop relying on the government to do shit for us
because it allows them to do this stuff.
Listen, guys, I'm not,
I'm no fucking hardcore,
like all government is inherently bad or any of that shit.
But I'm telling you right now,
like who the fuck wants your government
to control like every aspect of your life?
Do you trust these fucking bureaucrats
to control every minute detail?
They've got 300 million people to control it.
Don't be a didgy bro and let the civil system come to pass.
You gotta be more woke than that.
I'm with you and I am on your side,
but I want to be Del's advocate
because there are people who are a dirt pour
like white trash like trailer parks
and they are just in the cycle
where everyone around them.
How dare you talk about talking like that?
They're in the cycle where like
their dad relied on the government
and his dad relied on the government
and now like they are just so entrenched in that culture.
Like what can they do to break through?
Because it's not like they have any money to begin with.
It's totally, that's a totally fair point,
but here's the real deal.
Fuck them.
That's my answer to this question.
At some point, someone's gotta pay
and it's gonna be these people.
I'm really sorry.
I wish it wouldn't happen.
Wait, wait, they have to pay for what?
Well, they went when we, like just for example,
they were one crazy example.
If we just, for example, cut welfare 100%,
just say it was gone,
because let's just say America had a revolution
where everyone realized that like taxation is theft
just crossed the board.
Let's just say that happened.
Then like, then man,
that sucks for all the people
who really relied on welfare to live and shit.
That's like, and that's gonna cause huge problems.
Like all those people will probably
not be able to pay their fucking rent,
get kicked out with a massive homeless population.
You know, the housing market will crash
because people can't afford the things
that were being subsidized by the government.
Don't get me wrong.
There's gonna be huge problems.
But long term, long term,
I like to think things would go better.
You know, if there was less reliance
and less government control and all this shit,
but I'm not fucking economy.
The solution is something even more socialist,
but it's secretly better for economics, which is-
Bring back Obama!
Is he the universal guaranteed income?
Yeah.
Yeah!
Okay.
That's not a bad plan.
Well, yeah, because the thing is-
That's the opposite of what you just proposed, Nate.
I know, but like DeVoo said,
it's technically more socialist,
but it gets us more towards an egalitarian system.
Right, because it's-
The thing about welfare-
Does it, though?
Well, security-
Well, here's my-
Wait, wait, wait, let DeVoo finish.
Okay, go.
The thing about all the government spending shit,
and let's just go on the record here.
The government spends way the fuck more money
on entitlements than it does on the military.
People don't-
Just spend more, that's true.
Yeah, it's true.
It's like significantly fucking more.
You could kill the entire military.
I thought it was something like two-
Two-thirds is like entitlements,
then one-third is the military.
It's like a half.
Like, you could actually-
Okay.
The military is like a quarter,
and entitlements is like half
of all the money the government spends.
And let's not-
Let's not be-
You know, like, that's a lot of money on both fronts.
I know, I know.
It's a lot of money saving both fronts.
It just pisses me off because people
always count social security, welfare,
blah, blah, blah, all as separate slices of the pie.
Right, right.
But they don't separate the fucking navy
from the fucking, you know, Air Force.
Anyway, irrelevant.
So the thing is that the government gets
to decide how you use your money,
what you can spend your money on.
It gives you all these rules.
The idea of UBI is simply that everyone,
everyone gets a certain amount of money,
the same amount of money in their bank account,
attach their social securities every month.
And that's it.
Doesn't matter how much or how little money you make.
That way you don't have to worry about losing money
by making more money in the form
of different tax brackets, for instance, right?
You'd make the same money every single month.
Well, Taboo, here is why.
Here is why that plan is evil,
and I'm coming to your house to kill you.
It's because that system is prejudiced
against the less competent.
That's the problem with that system.
And how can we discriminate against people
on the basis of competency?
How can you make that case?
Didn't you just make the case that we need
to fuck those people and let them die completely?
I am, I mean, I'm being...
He's making a joke.
He's trying to...
Where are the memes?
Did you like that joke?
Yeah.
No, I was fucking gay.
There's the memes.
But dude, no, like, the idea of UBI
is that you don't have any excuses.
There's nothing in UBI
that incentivizes you to work less, you know?
I love it.
I think plenty of people know,
like have some Republican uncle
who is still on disability
and totally could fucking work but doesn't.
I have one, you know?
So it's just like, yeah.
People, you know,
as long as they're fair economics people,
they talk about how when you have the government
spend money on shit,
not only does it cost a lot of money,
it also results in all this fucking red tape
and it makes the law too complicated.
And I mean, complicated laws in general
are the secret way in which the poor get fucked over
because we have a lawyer society
where basically the better lawyers you have,
the more you can get away with shit and vice versa.
No one ever talks about that shit.
No one ever talks about simplifying the law.
That would help out a lot of people.
It's because who's gonna fucking report on that?
Fucking Rachel Maddow,
who's like one of the elite class, you know?
Right, exactly.
Of course not, you know?
So simplified law,
the thing is that you can't politically get away
with having less fucking entitlements.
People don't really talk about this,
but Republicans almost never even propose that shit.
It's mostly libertarian think tanks
talking about cutting funding for shit.
No one even suggests it actually.
No one even suggests it because it's too political.
I'm suggesting the right fucking now.
I'm doing it.
So my point is with UBI,
you sort of cheat the system
because everyone basically gets what they want
regarding helping out the poor, right?
But without all the red tape.
And I think that's probably the best compromise
that you can come to.
But even fucking the socialist paradise is like Sweden,
can't make that shit happen
because obviously the government wants all that control.
That's why they use the whole
veneer of generosity with other people's tax money
in order to get by with that shit.
But yeah, UBI, that's the closest I think we can get
in this generation.
That system is so attractive to me in many ways.
And everyone's gonna,
Tom, if you want to cut in, yeah, feel free to answer.
Well, I was going to say like,
just to play devil's advocate on it,
is that I think personally, I would love that.
I think it's a great idea.
My only concern with a system like that
is like we just talked about how like government,
intrusion into things like the healthcare market
and college drove the prices up.
Like wouldn't the market eventually adjust the fact
that, oh, everyone has X amount of money
so we can price everything up slowly but steadily
until it just doesn't matter anymore?
Oh, you might be right.
I don't actually understand economics,
so I don't know exactly how.
I got it, price controls.
That's always worked out.
Oh, I found the solution.
I'm gonna sound, Munchie, I do want to say something.
No, no, no, you go on, I'm gonna shift gears.
Okay, I might go on a little bit long.
Sure, sure, sure.
But it's just, so there's just a story that I want to tell
about me as a young man that might make people think
I was always evil, but here's just one.
If you don't need any help with that, Nate,
that's not a thing that we will now think.
Here's how you know that I'm not pretending anything
that I say now.
It's because when I was a kid,
I was like, you know, I was like,
it's because when I was a kid,
my mom is a special education teacher.
And so when I was in school, and I was doing well,
and I felt whatever, things were going fine.
I was in elementary school at this point.
And my mom was telling me about her day.
She worked with a kid one-on-one.
You know, she spends her days just with one kid,
at least with this particular job she was in
at the school that she worked at.
And I just said to my mom, okay, mom, I get it,
but here's my question.
Why are you paying so much attention to this kid
who will never be an amazing shining star?
Why not spend your time to help a kid who's really good,
and could be even better with one-on-one attention?
And she was just like, well, he doesn't need it as much.
I gotta help the people who are lacking
and need more of a boost to get up to help them.
And that has always confused me.
I've never been on board with that system.
Like, what is gained?
We feel good.
Yeah, like, what is gained helping someone
who is never gonna make significant progress?
Well, I guess if you wanna talk purely...
We feel good.
No, I think there's a utilitarian fact of that.
You know, the low achievers, they form the backbone
of the service industry and stuff.
There are people who can't really climb higher.
So there needs to be a minimum level of competency
in any sort of employed positions.
Yeah, you're not wrong, Tom.
I'm talking about people who are not even capable of speech,
for example, as some of these students.
So there's...
Like, we got issues.
I think you're severely alienating most of our audience.
I'm not trying to say people who are more lower functioning
don't deserve care or attention or appreciation.
It's a matter of distribution of resources
is what I am focusing on.
And I'm interested...
And let's be real.
If we invented robot butlers that could one-on-one
tend to all the people who needed this kind of extra care,
and I'll tell you right now, the way that we get there
is by helping people be really smart science boys
who are at the top level of achievement
so that we can invent that.
And right now, isn't it great that when...
This is just one example, but you got a girl
who's got some disability, she gets lost or something,
she pulls out what?
Her fucking cell phone that she couldn't have made
that was made by a really smart science boy
that science fucking developed,
and she calls home so someone can come pick her up
so she's not, you know, scared or in danger or any of that shit.
Like, that...
To me, it makes all the sense in the world
to focus our resources on the high achievement.
Oh, God.
On the high achievement.
That's what I'm saying.
Let it be known that I...
And as a baby, I detected that.
As a baby, I detected that shit.
Yeah.
Let it be known that I've hit the eject button
on this train that we've all been steaming, powering down.
And I am now outside.
I just want to gas the retarded munchie.
That's all I'm saying.
I think the reason you knew that
is exactly what your mom has said.
I don't think this is necessarily true.
Like, objective fact, this is what should happen.
Again, I'm not...
But the people want to...
The reason people want to do that
is because they feel like the people who are well off
are well off and they want to help the people who are not.
Whether that's morally objectionable or not,
I'm not here to discuss.
A lot of people have an instinct.
But people want to do it.
People want to help people.
But see, I think this is a major issue
of human nature itself.
Like, we see people who are rich
and I see it every fucking day.
I did it today.
Me and my girlfriend were talking about...
I forget who.
Let's just say like Nicki Minaj.
And it was like Nicki Minaj tweeted something
about being unhappy.
And my response was,
okay, but you're rich, so fuck you.
That's wrong.
That's incorrect.
That does not...
Just because someone is rich or successful
does not invalidate, you know, like...
Yeah.
They're part of this.
Well, there's a connection here.
There's a connection here.
On the rich.
I made the connection to those with versus those that...
We have such strong instincts
to just want to help those without.
And on a practical matter,
it is not always beneficial.
And this is why people love communism and socialism
to begin with.
They love the idea of just giving stuff
to people who are without.
But that might not necessarily be the best way
to help those people.
That's the point I'm trying to make here.
Stuff is not just something you can give.
When people talk about like,
oh, let's fucking...
Let's bridge that fucking wage gap
by giving some money over to those other people.
Ask yourself why the hell does handing
and throwing a shitload of money at Africa
not necessarily fix it, right?
There's more than just...
I think...
Okay, let me put this away.
When it comes to institutionalized
those in power versus those in not,
those who are not in power,
incomes, wealth,
is actually kind of a distraction.
It doesn't actually have all to do
with why certain people remain successful
and others don't.
When we just look at the wealth gap
or the income gap and we're like,
oh, if we could just fix that,
we fix the actual underlying reason
why these people are making
different amounts of money.
It doesn't make any sense.
Like if we make it to where it's illegal
to pay a CEO more than say $250,000 a year,
all they're gonna do
companies will just give CEOs
a shitload of free stuff to incentivize them
because there's a reason why CEOs get paid so much.
They'll work around it.
That actually...
And then we just get in the semantics game
of trying to criminalize each of these little things
and that's a huge waste of time.
Right.
Okay, I think we're conflating certain subjects
because I'm not talking about the rich
or people who just don't have the backbone
in order to get a job.
I'm talking about mentally birth defect people.
I'm talking about birth defect people
who I feel like their existence is suffering.
And I feel like...
That's not necessarily true.
I mean, it depends.
It depends on what you do in your stuff.
It might be content.
Like there's a lot of people who are retarded,
who are just perfectly happy,
it's just that they're not gonna fucking make Apple too
or whatever.
They're just...
I know...
Okay, what I'm saying is that I'm not saying
that we should just have all of our teachers focus
on the people who are just underachievers,
who are just able-bodied and fine
and can do whatever.
They just don't have the fortitude and willpower to do it.
Those people can fucking die and they don't matter.
At some point, somebody has to start looking out
for those people because if we say,
if we do what you say,
we should just focus on all of the successful people,
who are going far so they can create things
to make the robot butlers or whatever,
they have to care about those people
to want to make the robot butlers.
If they don't, then they'll never get made
and they'll just all die.
The way I see it, there should be a skill floor
that we should be trying to elevate everyone to.
And then once they are at that floor,
we should leave them alone until...
It depends on in what way, but yes.
I mean, that's the general idea.
We should try and elevate the people
who need our help on a physical or mental level.
Maybe not, I don't know how much money
we are dedicating to this in our society.
I don't know what our priorities are,
but I think that it's just a humanitarian
and just not entirely against our interests
or burning money or anything.
I think it's just a nice thing to do
in order to help our general society
be more on level with one another
and be able to achieve the same things as one another.
You're not wrong and I would never say anyone
who wants to do that shouldn't do it.
For example, my mom chose to go
into the special education field.
She knew exactly what she was getting into
and I salute her and I'm proud of her and I love her.
And of course, I respect her decisions, of course.
The problem is when you conflate,
or not not conflate, but we're mixing
between individual specific choices people make
and then just broad policy issues.
I don't believe that men are biologically equal
to women in every single way.
But I know women who are stronger than men.
I mean, of course, that's true
and it happens plenty of times.
It's just, whatever, it doesn't matter.
I'm getting lost in the woods here.
A bunchy...
You're saying different topics here.
I want to talk about something.
I want to shift gears to something
that we were kind of talking before.
DeVu reminded me of, about simplifying the law.
I think one of the major problems
in the United States government
is that it's so fucking old
and all the people in it are so fucking old.
Very, very sure.
The government, like the way I...
That's why I'm voting for Bernie Sanders.
Exactly, this is the youngest person,
the hippest guy in the crowd.
I'm voting Bernie in 2020.
I don't know about you guys.
Bernie's a good man.
Yeah, yeah, when he's six feet fucking under,
we're going to lift him up to the O-locks.
Why the fuck not?
At this point...
I mean, he's what, he's like 74 now,
something like that?
Oh, he's already dead.
No, no, all we got to do,
we just got a weekend at Bernie's, Sanders him.
The entire fucking presidency.
The entire, the entire 2016 election
was just a buildup to that punchline.
Remember everybody out there,
when they start telling you to vote for Joe Biden
instead of Bernie Sanders,
remember Joe Biden is 75,
Bernie Sanders is 76.
Not a big difference there.
Why does Bernie Sanders look so fucking old?
He just looks like an old ass man.
He just, well, Joe Biden is one year younger.
He just happens to look more photogenic and stuff.
Okay, okay, well, it fucking doesn't matter.
I'm an old ass Jew, Bernie Sanders.
Uh, I'm from Brooklyn, motherfuckers.
The way I see the government is like a bunch of bricks,
like tacked on top of one another,
who like, like, like each layer of bricks
is from like a different time period
and like looks completely aesthetically different
to the bricks before,
but they're all laid upon the same foundation.
So when you step back and look at it,
it's just like a hodgepodge, different ideas.
Munchy, I hear you do tear up the Constitution.
We've got to start.
Destroy it, dude.
We've got to start with the service agreement to Minecraft
is the template we should be using.
All right, all right, all right.
Rule number one, all people who are created work equal.
Rule number two, do not mine at nine.
This is broken by the United States of America.
Okay, so like, bro, see the thing about like society,
and I assume basically every culture,
but America is definitely no different,
is that the average person really views the government
as like a magic MacGuffin in like a movie,
but it's like whoever can grab the magic lamp
and then like rub their wish into it in the third act,
like everything will be fine.
Like at the end of fucking Return of the King,
where like, you know, the ground collapses
and conveniently only collapses the bad people, you know?
But that's what we always want.
That's how it's always talked about.
Like I remember like when Obamacare was like very slightly
approved of by the Supreme Court,
people were like, okay, cool, healthcare is free right now, right?
Like, yeah, or like when conversely,
if Obamacare gets obstructed by like one month,
people are like, oh good, healthcare
has improved the capitalist now, right?
Fucking no, I think it's-
You know, Tavu, you're totally right.
Like remember that argument I made a long time ago
about like, shit, what was it?
It was like that we should like,
we want to get on the suicide episode when I said like,
I want like people to like review people
and like approve people before committing suicide.
Like to institute that,
I recognize takes like a magical level of like bureaucracy
that does not exist and can't be relied upon,
but like if it existed and worked perfectly as I envisioned it,
that would be nice, but it's not real.
And I think that this mentality comes from sort of childhood
where you see police officers as just like objective enforcers
of the law, which is this objective power or like,
you know, you go to school and like,
the school is this objective force of knowledge
and teachers just know things, right?
So I think that if we saw not having laws as,
not necessarily a problem, but possibly a solution,
if we always just think of the way to solve problems
as more laws, why can't it ever be-
You know the problem is here?
What?
The problem is we got all these goddamn gamer girls
who think of the goddamn American government as like the,
it's like the code base that was made by the creators
of their favorite game Minecraft, you know, Notch.
They think that like, of course it was crafted perfectly,
to be the most impartial.
You know what it's like?
There's this one scene in I Shield 21.
Okay, this is a great example.
In I Shield 21, there is an exact, there is a moment.
It's a football manga.
It's one of my favorites, it's a sports manga.
The only time, okay, so whatever.
Like in real, like these days,
football is called ref ball in the United States of America
because the refs like interfere with like every fucking play
and throw a million flags and like control the whole game
because of like safety and other shit.
In I Shield 21, every, like the whole game is played,
the whole manga is laid out that people just like do things
and then like a touchdown happened, yay.
And like everyone understands it immediately.
There's never any question.
There was only one moment in the manga
where the issue of the refs is addressed.
And it's this one moment where like the character looks
like he was out of bounds,
but he had actually grabbed some dirt to be in bounds
or something like that.
And like there's a dramatic reveal
as he like looks into the eyes of the ref.
And the left, like stone faced and perfect,
perfectly mechanical and robotic,
looks back into the eyes of Manta,
the guy who had made the play.
All right, he was like trying to get out of bounds
or whatever to stop the clock.
And like they do zooms on face to face to face
and the ref raises his hand
and in perfect recognition of all the facts says,
yes, it was out of bounds.
You are safe to do another play.
You can still win this game, my heroes.
And then he overturns Roe v. Wade.
Like perfect.
Yeah, exactly.
And they think of the government as like perfect
and impartial and always has your best games and minds.
They're constantly complaining
about how bad the government is.
Right, yeah.
Oh, that's, that's true.
No, like I remember, okay, in 2012 or 2011,
it was the 112th Congress or whatever the fuck.
It was the one where Democrats and Republicans
were like half and half.
So like nothing was getting done.
It was obstructionist central,
north, south walking, Zach, fuck, Tobias.
And one of the, I would read articles of like the top 10
reasons why this Congress is the worst Congress ever.
And one of the reasons that they brought up was
this Congress has passed the fewest laws
of any Congress in like 80 years or something.
And I'm like, you know, I hear people talk about, you know,
deregulation, like it's really cool.
But then other people are like,
Oh, deregulation sounds scary.
Like we don't want corporations to do whatever.
But like why not just actually look at the regulations
and look at this on a case by case basis
and consider which ones are reasonable.
I actually, for unrelated reasons, happened to check.
December 2017, the US government had 61,950 pages
of regulations, the federal government,
which apparently is a 25 year low
because of the Trump administration's net negative
on regulations.
But yeah, 61,000 pages, like.
Have you seen the shit they do?
Where like they'll get like a new law
and that they're voting on like an hour
and like all the senators get a copy of it,
like one hour before.
And it's like literally 2000 pages long.
That happens every fucking day that shit's happening.
It's a world.
I mean, I remember some people I've heard people who've said
that they've heard people who've said
that every US citizen breaks three felonies a year.
And there you go.
We live in a world where it's really just all about
selective enforcement.
Lawyers are really the ones who control the control freedom
in the society.
So there you go.
You know what really sucks?
What really fucking sucks?
Working a job.
Let's talk about how fucking gay it is to have a job.
Let's talk about how gay it is to fucking.
We should have an entire episode about that.
I've woken up.
I've woken up for my stupid.
I have a big news for everyone.
That I'm.
Make news change.
I already know this.
Yeah, I got a fucking job.
Oh, right.
Oh, no.
I can imagine it.
I know.
What a nightmare.
Oh.
That he's betrayed us all.
Life is over.
Well, do you want to talk about what it is?
The neat life continues because it's a work from home thing.
I'm basically just answering calls.
And the reason why I did it.
OK, I used to do online tutoring.
And I would just be hanging out on this tutoring website
waiting for notifications come up that people needed help
with math problems.
And then I would go and walk them through a math problem.
And I would just have that open while I was working on stuff.
And also the physics, right?
So I would kind of split my attention between
doing my art and doing my job.
So I got this job in the hopes that I can kind of do that
and just be like drawing while I'm waiting for calls
and then take a call and do a whole thing
and then go back to doing my shit.
In the hopes that I can have money
but also be working at the same time.
But time will tell.
Time will tell if that pans out.
Yeah, but I'm not just asking you about physics.
Why nothing can go faster than light?
And your answers sounded like a shitty sci-fi novel.
Wait, are you?
When?
It's like a last year or something.
We just were real.
Because real physics is bizarre.
Real physics is a shitty sci-fi novel.
I know, right?
Isn't that fucking weird?
That's God, man.
There he is.
There he is right there, my dude.
How is your production of the only thing
that really matters?
Endless war.
Beast capades.
No, endless war.
Endless war.
I was in training this past week.
And in training, I was like tuning out
and just trying my best to throw together some shitty makeshift code
out of cracks like source code.
Endless war will continue forever.
Endless war is the new hotness.
What is this, an episode of the Rowdy Fuckers Cop Killers?
Get the fuck out of here, guys.
God, the people wish.
The people wish, they.
The people wish.
They will.
I have banned Rowdy Fuckers Cop Killers.
Slime will flow forever.
I have today achieved the dream, the impossible dream.
I now command two mega slime.
Whoa.
Compared to your pitiful one, Munchy.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
The Rowdy's will fucking rise.
We were catching up to you right and quick.
And this, and that was like, that was only like three people.
Those are only three training sessions that I had
to destroy your pitiful army.
They have no resolve.
Once I put my immense wit and intellect onto the scene,
and I command my troops, like they've been desperately asking me to,
then I will achieve victory in no less than 30 minutes.
I guarantee.
Rowdy Fuckers Cop Killers are banned from now on forever on the PCP.
It's over.
Listen, listen.
All I'm saying is that not yet, this is just a stopgap measure
from when I can make my full-time job developing Endless War,
by which I mean thinking of things to do with Endless War,
trying to do it, failing, and then asking Crack to do it for me.
Endless War, that's your job.
Who are you?
Donald Trump?
Syria?
Am I right or wrong?
Yeah!
There's each other on the back.
Got him.
The actual serious question is, of course,
like I assume you plan to still do comics and stuff.
Yeah, yeah, that's the whole point.
I'm going to be like, my goal is that I can make money
while I like do art kind of intermittently, you know?
Okay, now we're talking about job shit.
You know, trying to shape my life in such a way
that I can get my shit done without, you know,
without neglecting, you know, my stuff.
You're packed.
Ladies and gentlemen, there you have it right there.
Ben taking responsibility for his life,
recognizing he has to make a change, I'm assuming,
in order to reach some financial goal or whatever,
and here he is doing it, all right?
So I don't want to hear no fucking excuses.
If even Ben can do it, anybody can do it.
He needed the second Oculus Rift.
One wasn't enough.
Any one for each eye.
HTC Vive Saint.
Now that would be the one for the modern age.
Guys, that's too advanced.
Let me ask you this.
It's time to Max Revive.
It's me.
Oh, yes.
It's me, Munchy, tripping of the plebs,
the Procrastinator Senate we had before us.
Everyone wants to hear stories.
People want to see the personal raw experiences
about the stories that we've had doing our selective jobs.
And we want to hear Nate groan about,
I don't know, furniture or some shit.
We don't even know about that.
I'm talking about people right now.
Wait a second.
Why have we been talking about philosophy and governments?
None of that matters.
Let's get into where are the memes?
We need the memes.
He's right.
Was Davoo saying something there?
Nate, I was just thinking, you already
have such a messianic complex.
Does that have anything to do with making furniture out of wood,
being like a carpenter or some shit?
Well, you know, it's like, so I guess the job I was referring to there
was, like I said before, working at Pier 1,
worked at Pier 1 for a year or two.
My job was, I did some of that up front,
just people buying shit.
Your job was basically like push sales of all kinds of bullshit.
But what I much prefer to do, my favorite thing to do there,
which was sort of my main responsibility was,
Pier 1 is to some degree a furniture store.
So we would get these big boxes of furniture in,
and it would be my job.
And then there were other guys who would come in.
It was all women who worked there.
But then the guys who worked there were the ones
who would build the furniture, just because we were bigger, I guess.
And so I would just sit in the back.
I would open up box after box after box and assemble,
like Ikea style, extremely simple furniture pieces to put together.
And I would sit there, and I would commune with God,
and my halo would appear, and I would invent the table.
I am Jesus, is what I'm saying.
Guys, remember in fucking Passion of the Christ at the beginning
when Jesus literally invents the long legged table?
Yes.
Is that true?
Did that happen in that movie?
It starts out, someone is like...
Gibson.
Someone is like, wow, what is this weird table you're making, Jesus?
He's like, oh, see, it's got long legs, but you sit at taller chairs.
And the guy's like, oh, it'll never catch on.
Did I talk with you guys, I don't think I did.
Just so happened a week ago, I was just sitting in the back of the car,
I think, yeah, with my parents, this was a few weeks ago,
my parents are in the car, like my sister's in the car,
and I'm just sort of sitting in the back seat,
and just randomly accessing memories in my brain.
And I remember having seen the beginning of the Passion of the Christ,
which I hadn't seen since I was like a kid.
So I didn't really, at the time I took that scene for granted,
but now I'm like, what the fuck?
It's like one of those like time travel movies
where like someone bumps into Ben Franklin, you know,
and it's like, oh man, you know, you should put a key in a bottle or some shit.
But it's like a Jesus movie, you know?
Like, it's a fucking Jesus movie where like,
it's not only that he died for our sins,
but he also invented the long-legged table.
Is there any evidence that there is a connection there?
That Jesus didn't invent the long-legged table.
Yeah, it's not the fuck up haters, I want to hear it.
We just seem to sit a little bit closer to heaven,
and Jesus was there.
There you go!
Yeah!
Woo-hoo!
Oh, god damn.
So guys, what do you say?
Radcon 4, we have the last supper.
We make long-legged tables!
We invent the even longer-legged table.
So we can get closer to Jesus!
Yes!
It's the PCP, the Pro Carpenters podcast.
Whoa, soon, soon.
The Pro Christenators podcast.
I don't personally have much more to say about that job,
but that was the job that I worked while I was making
Gern-Loggin video, part one and part two.
So like, I would buy day, I'd be fucking building furniture
and selling people shit at Pier 1,
and I'd come home, and I would work on-
And you'd be building mines.
I'd be mining.
What fucking motivates you?
What is it inside of you that makes you go building furniture?
Before you answer that, I want to say to Javu,
Radcon 4, Jesus lecture,
where you explain the history and life of Jesus Christ.
I don't know.
I think I probably could have my dad do that lecture, but...
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
Wait, what's the fire that's lit under your ass that makes you go,
I'm gonna make this whole video on this shitty laptop?
You know what it is?
It's fear.
For me, it's fear.
A lot of things are motivated by fear,
a lot of things are motivated by fear,
and there's probably some degree of that,
like fear of like being unworthy in life,
and like allowing myself to...
Fear of looking back and regretting all the things you didn't do.
Yeah.
That's what motivates me.
That's a fair, it's a fair thing.
It's a fair thing, and I think that's kind of helpful.
I don't fear that, I'm living that.
That's my life.
Well, there you go.
I guess, like, I don't know,
a lot of it really does come from, like,
when I was growing up, I just felt shitty about myself,
and just like I wasn't doing it.
Like, I don't know, like it really,
I know it's weird as I come back to a lot,
but a lot of it comes back to, I think, my issues with women,
and like how I felt like such a failure,
and that I was completely failing when all my friends were like,
superior to me, and then I realized I didn't want to be,
nor did I have to be inferior anymore.
Like, I could fix myself, and then I did.
And then once I did that, I was like,
well, let's keep this train rolling, I think.
Like, and like, I don't want to take all credit.
Like, Ben is the one who suggested
we even make videos in the first place.
So he's the one who like turned me on to even the possibility
of doing this kind of stuff.
Nailed it.
It was good, I'm sure glad it happened.
And then, just when I was in it,
I discovered how much I enjoyed doing it,
and then, I don't know, man.
Like, it's like that particular video series or whatever.
I just really liked that show.
I was mad that people were explaining it poorly,
and I like wanted to correct the record.
But the real thing at the root of it.
That particular show whose name must not be mentioned.
Indeed, indeed.
The Bolton Mortyve anime.
That's what they call it.
I guess I just really have things I want to achieve in life.
Like, these days, I spend a pretty large amount of time
thinking about how I admire Cenk Juger of the Young Turks.
And I know that's a weird guy to pick out of a hat.
But apart from the political issues I strongly disagree with him on,
I look at this guy who was some fat, virgin, 25-year-old asshole
who was a super political nerd.
But now, he's got a huge network and a huge successful business
where he works with all these fascinating people.
He gets to meet all these amazing people
and do all these cool things.
He's not in as good of shape as he could be,
so I'm gonna be working on that.
But I really spend a lot of my time thinking about
the male role models in my life I want to be like.
And just try to live the way they would, I guess.
I spend a lot of my time thinking about how the Penny Arcade guys live
and how I want to live like them.
And how I'm closer than I ever thought I would be.
But there's still a long way to go.
I mean, and I think about Red Letter Media too,
just whatever, I know we talk about them a lot, but that's...
The Penny Arcade guys, they fucking built an intellectual property
that now has turned, and they expanded their operations
and they turned into these media juggernauts.
And what the end result of that is that now,
they can spend like literally one hundred, well not one hundred,
like so much of their time can be devoted to them
just pursuing whatever they want to do.
Like Tyco can just go and fucking make raps with that other guy.
And that's fine, and they can fucking bullshit around
with their stupid Boy Scouts in the Woods D&D setting
that nobody cares about, but it's totally fine
and I'm sure they have a great time with it.
And that's how I want to live, just fucking around and doing whatever I want.
These guys have added a ton of value to the world
and now they get to enjoy the benefits.
Like they fucking...
The first thing I was real, like I was always aware of...
What's the name of their comic?
Penny Arcade, it's called Penny Arcade, right?
It's just like you showed me, what was that show?
Strip Search.
Yeah, that's the kind of thing they can just do on a whim.
And like if they hadn't spent like a decade or decades or whatever it was,
like building up themselves to the point where they had the resources
to like create that show that they probably never even imagined
they'd be making like at the start.
It's because they gave themselves power.
I'll say it man, I'm in it for power.
I want the power to control my life and do fun things I want to do.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, that's what I'm in for, that's what I'm doing.
For me, it's really like a holy war in the name of proliferating the art and society,
but mostly just art that I want there to be.
But in my honor, right?
Like when I hear, whenever I read up or watch YouTube videos
about the fucking Roman warriors, I'm like, they have my mentality.
Maybe we're the same number of skirts, probably.
And like...
You know what they called, if I remember correctly,
the Roman soldiers, DeVu?
Legionnaires.
DeVu is Legion, is the joke I'm trying to make.
Yes, I am.
All right.
Forgot about that one.
Discrystallize to my mind.
Where are the memes?
Where have all the memes gone?
I'm doing my best.
They have, they have, no, they have, yeah, they've fallen into obscurity.
They need to be max-revived.
You know what they called, you know what they called Roman soldiers back in the day?
They called them DeVus.
That's what we're doing right now.
Did you know?
So fucking like, I mean, I think it's pretty appropriate.
My fucking fiance, she's always complaining about her sister, whose name is Sam,
and one of her ex-friends, whose name is Sam.
And I'm like, you're in the Samnite Wars.
The first and second Samnite Wars.
And it's like, do you think of in any language that isn't Roman history?
And I'm like, no.
Wait, is that a real word?
Samnite?
Yeah, the fucking Romans kick the show of the Samnites.
Oh, did the Samnites have jobs?
Any fucking fucking antiquity history buffs laugh at that joke, you see?
I'm sure they did.
I mean, I'm sure they did.
You have to cast a shitload of stupid miniature nets to get random people in the audience,
you see.
You know, the PCB has splintered into minuscule individualized memes for different groups
to appreciate.
Yeah, it's fucking literally going around.
That's what we're going to press the groups for to toilet.
Yes.
Like the history buffs.
Every audience member is sitting waiting.
When will my memes come?
Yeah.
All right.
I'm going to sit through all these.
All these bargain memes.
It's the Disney princess mentality.
Like your group isn't real and doesn't really exist or no one gives a shit unless you have
a Disney princess associated with your ethnic or religious group.
That's how it works.
We're never going to get into the Muslim Disney princess.
I'm waiting.
Well, there's Jasmine.
There's Jasmine.
Yeah.
She's not.
She's not a good Christian wife.
Look at what she's wearing, Nate.
Come on.
Well, okay, goddamn.
Back to the topic here.
This mentality in myself was finally I understood.
Jasmine is Islamic.
That's the topic of the podcast.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
We could debate whether or not Jasmine is a Muslim for ages.
We could never reach a consensus.
Jasmine versus Islam, the new bonus episode.
That's a good one.
When Hippo was saying in the chat earlier that, you know,
when I really think about it, creating a cult around myself like developing hardcore fans
is really just exactly the same as getting the algorithms.
You're basically just doing a humiliating rain dance
and tooling your content and persona to get a certain specific result.
Neither one of them is doing what you want to do as an artist.
Right?
It's kind of the way he was putting it.
But you get, if you've got a following that gives you power
and having power lets you do the things that you want to do.
And doing what you want will lead to success
if you just do it consistently and you work hard.
Guys, can I, I'm sorry, I'm sorry to cut in.
Can I just bring you a brief moment of joy
that just happened in real time in my life while I was on this podcast?
I get a message from Michelle that who just says-
Thanks, a father-in-law.
Let's go to the board.
It's just that she says, someone, she's at work right now.
I picked her up yesterday.
She just sent me by saying, hey, Nate, just thought you should know.
Someone just asked me, hey, Michelle,
were you here with the big muscular bodybuilder last night?
And they literally asked if I was a bodybuilder.
I know I don't deserve it, but it makes me feel good, okay?
Fuck off.
All right, I'm sorry.
Nate, I really like this idea of Nate having a kid.
And the moment I thought of Nate having a kid,
I was reminded of this YouTube Barats and Barretta skit
where there's this guy who's training his year and a half old daughter
to be a world-class Olympian and giving her weights
and throwing her all around.
That's what I will do with all my children.
That sounds like Nate.
That's what I will do.
Yes.
No, I'll do it.
I will show you that score.
You played that explicitly, the horrific regimen you have planned out.
To make sure your kids can be all they can be.
Well, listen, Ben, exactly as you said, delay gratification.
I will delay all gratification for my children until they are 18.
They will not know an ounce of happiness or joy in their life
until they reach the age of 18.
My children will have the ultimate coom when they leave the nest
and they realize they are so much better than all these scum out there
in the fucking world who did not wear fucking training masks
and weights for this time they were one fucking day old.
They'll know no pleasure until they rip the still beating heart
from your enemy's breasts.
That's right.
A.K. me.
I will be their adversary.
The joy and rage and the soul of weird utilitarianism.
When they conquer me, they go to be transcended.
That's the end goal.
Every weird utilitarianism is doomed to be killed by his own children.
Who lives in permanent antagonism with.
That would be the final challenge.
The day they reach 18, you'll stand in front of the door
and you'll have your back turned to them
and you'll slowly turn around and be like,
your final challenge is to defeat me in hand to hand combat.
And they'll be like, what, dad?
And meanwhile, while they're stuttering,
you make your first move and stab your son through his heart.
You should have acted sooner.
You slow pussy, too fucking slow.
Luckily, I've got several clones of you lined up in 2016
where you fucking failed.
Number 27, get the fuck dead.
That's what I'll say.
It'll be great.
You'll say, get in the ground, you fucking nigger.
There, that's what it'll be.
That's what it'll be.
Because this is my wife's son, just to clarify.
Um, you know.
This is not yet.
That's what it is.
All right.
Where were, well, jobs, right?
Yeah, I was talking to you.
My wife's full-time job is to stay at home, dad,
to my wife's son.
Is my full-time job is what I'm doing every day.
Please don't bully me.
This is a real job.
Someone has to do it.
God damn it, I deserve respect.
I'm a human being.
That's it.
Someone has to do it.
We all know, we all know that Tarone can't do it.
We, yeah, I just got to take up,
I just got to take up the main tool.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
Ben, you've done jobs before.
You were just talking about jobs.
Yeah.
Should I list them?
Yes.
Yeah, that sounds fun.
Let's all list our jobs.
Okay, let's list our jobs.
I like that.
Well, let's see.
When I was in high school,
I worked at Mrs. Fields Cookies in the mall.
Yeah, yeah.
I worked.
You drew fancy designs on them.
I remember that.
Yeah, it was really fun, actually.
It was like way fun when I had to decorate cakes.
I was a counselor at Astro Camp for like six months there.
I worked at, I was a food runner.
After that was over, I was a food runner
at this restaurant called the Chateau
that actually we just went to when we were in Boston.
Oh yeah, it was nice.
Yeah, yeah, I worked at that restaurant.
And I actually, this was like eight years ago
or like seven years ago.
And I saw people there that I barely recognized
out of the corner of my mind.
I was like, oh my God, they're still here.
Oh no.
They escaped, but they're still here.
So that was harrowing.
God, what the fuck?
I don't know.
I was a, I don't know.
I had a bunch of shitty little jobs.
Fucking Poland, fucking Poland, job.
I was like a, I did like document editing
for some company.
I was just like editing,
that I would, I did that from home for the most.
I had a cubicle in an office,
but I almost never went to it.
I mostly just worked it from home.
They would send me assignments,
I would do them, send it back,
but a bing, but a boom.
I was like sort of an engineer,
but mostly I just like,
mostly I just like took readings
off of an electron microscope
at this place called Integris in Bilarica,
Bilarica, whatever.
I never learned how to say the town's name.
And I think there's more.
Oh, I was.
The Poland one.
What about Poland?
Oh yeah, yeah.
And then I taught,
I taught physics to, to Arab kids in Poland.
Several months.
Yes.
Nice, nice.
I think that's a pretty exhaustive list of my jobs.
Ben, the real mental powerhouse behind 9-11,
you can thank him for its success.
Yeah.
This was post 9-11.
Of course.
Oh, okay.
They were all in very high spirits.
I can't imagine what it must have been like
to be alive during 9-11
and like being able to like,
like perceive it as being true.
That's incredible.
Yeah, I would say that for me is the dividing line
between like millennials and then millennial 2.0s.
If you don't remember distinctly 9-11 happening,
then you're.
I'll tell you right now, Munchie,
you missed a hell of a party.
You missed a hell of a good time.
I know, I know.
I wish I had been there.
I was, I was just in the plane.
I was having too, I was dead when I go to attend to.
Hey, I'll just run through my jobs real fast
because we're all doing it.
My first job was I worked for our next door neighbor Ralph
and I worked, like he had like a big party,
like he had a big fucking bit of land
in front of his house.
Or like he would hold like events.
So people would like have weddings there
and they'd like do stuff like that.
I worked there as like a caterer
and just like a guy who would stand around
and like watch and like make sure and clean up stuff.
And I worked there for like a couple months.
That was on and off.
I got a job at Papa Gino's Pizzeria.
That's the good shit.
That's my favorite kind of pizza.
To this day.
So in your dad's man, that's pretty.
Oh yeah, there will be a stealing your dad on Papa Gino's.
I'm very excited.
I want to watch that.
I want to know, I want to know an in-depth review
of this Papa Gino's pizza, which I'm sure you will do.
Oh, we get deeper in depth than you have ever
dwelled before.
Let me see.
In, I think that was the last job I did before college.
In college, I worked as a librarian
at our award-winning school library
at the College of New Jersey where I went.
That's my alma mater.
Also while I was working there,
I got like a small little gig
to like make a program for a guy that he paid me for.
I just didn't do it though.
That's really the long and short of it.
What was the program supposed to be?
You know, I can't even remember what the point of it was,
but like I basically, this is my first quote-unquote job
as a programmer.
The guy, like I met him through my job at the library.
He just was like, hey, I want to like this thing to do this.
And we had a couple meetings
and then like a couple months passed
when I was supposed to be working on it.
And I just presented him like the fuck all that I'd done.
He was like, wow, this is like terrible.
This is not, you did not do the work.
And I'm just like, no, I did a good job.
I'm really good.
I deeply ashamed of it to this day.
Beyond that, I think after college,
I just got a job at,
I worked at a pizza place for a little while,
making some shitty ass pizzas for this like mom and pop place.
They were, they were a,
Hoptic Christian Egyptians.
They were cool.
They loved Jesus.
They loved-
I'm the only one who thinks Hoptic is.
That might be the wrong word.
Whatever.
They were just like super Christ-faggy Egyptians.
They had haptic technology.
They didn't have a brain uncontrollably.
Yeah, like touch.
I would feel them and they would, you know,
respond to my touch in real time.
That's not the pizza's homemade.
I asked the man to tell me the secret recipe for his secret sauce
and he would not tell me.
He would not tell me.
He started to unbuckle his pants.
And you're like, actually, I don't need to know that bad.
Yeah, that's how it went.
So I worked there.
Then I worked at Best Buy for like a year or two.
That was okay.
I had some amazing fucking stories
about the things that happened in that fucking place.
That's where I met the guy who I had literally the moment
that made me realize all weed was bad and evil forever at that job.
I was just around these people who were just big weed guys
and recognized I never wanted to be around them ever again
or anyone like them.
ParkourDude91 was such an unbelievable good experience for me
to see in real time this person hopped up
on weed doing bad things.
It doesn't matter that it was all fake and not real.
That doesn't matter.
That's not a problem.
It's your only reason to imagine it.
As long as...
It instilled in me the knowledge, the knowledge,
the objective true fact that weed makes you retarded.
And I'm so stretched this day.
Thank you so fucking much, ParkourDude.
You've done a real solid for me.
You saved one from that green hell known as the M life.
That was one of the reasons why he wanted to do it.
Was to portray gamer weed culture as terrible.
And in literal hopes to inspire people to not be the person he was presenting.
Is he on record just saying that?
Is that true?
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
Dude, right after we recorded that lecture,
Munchie took us upstairs and showed us the video
where he reveals himself as a fake.
And then he goes on his diatribe explaining his motivations.
And I'm like, oh, ParkourDude's mission was born out of hatred and contempt.
It wasn't just lighthearted poking fun at.
He's like really seriously despises the kind of thing he was parodying.
And he was just going full tilt propaganda against it.
Holy shit.
Nate, I feel like you would really like Yann Rinkowski.
I mean, because he is, he's like, I feel like both him and Sam Hyde
are like, like, like, like they moonlight in philosophy.
But I think Yann is really like, Yann really has a principle that I really enjoy.
And I try and do, but I'm not very good at it.
And I need, I've been thinking about it and I want to do it more.
Where your comedy is rooted in the things that you believe.
And like your, your comedy is rooted in like, like how you want to perceive reality.
That is 100% true.
And I think about that a lot when I'm, when I'm trying to do stuff.
Yeah.
When I, I, I kind of think that comedy without that is just inherently less valuable.
But, you know, whatever, I can just say just goof for the sake of a goof.
Hey, let me just finish my last jobs here.
All I did, I worked at peer one and now I got my current programming job.
And that's it.
So I'm, I'm, I'm done.
I'm out.
It's all my jobs.
Um, um, David, you, you, you clone some Wondos, right?
What?
Yeah, that's all I've done.
I've never actually had a real job.
I just fucking worked with my dad on cleaning windows and cleaning out gutters.
Yeah.
Really interesting because looking back, I think I,
the, the, the way in which I ran at YouTube clearly reflects that job because that job was
totally unfulfilling, but like totally not stressful.
Cause when it's just, you know, you, you're there and your fucking dad and your brother,
it's not like you have to like put on a huge.
When you're there and you're fucking your dad and your brother understood.
I'm with you, dude.
I'm with you.
I only gotta be professional.
I only gotta like be professional attitude when there's a fucking customer there.
You know, that's fine.
Yeah.
But it was, it was pretty low pressure, right?
And it's a pretty easy job to do.
Like the thing about the reason why my dad has a successful business doing that is that
no one wants to clean the windows, which is why you can never get a consistent employee.
Like, you know when you can never get a decent window cleaner,
but if it's someone who's in your family, then they have to give a shit.
Like it was weird watching like familial bonds for sweet actually do a good job,
even though I openly didn't give a shit.
The point is, despite being very like physically draining, it wasn't that draining.
And it wasn't like emotionally or psychologically draining because
you can just be like, oh, hey, I have 20 windows to clean right here.
Pops into your buds, listens to entire podcasts.
So it's pretty easy.
So I had plenty of time to like think all day.
So it was actually a pretty easy, a pretty great job to then transition into being an internet person.
But also it took my very specific mentality of absolutely hating it.
If I'm spending any time not doing what I want to do and thinking that I'm making something
important that I actually give a shit about.
If I spend any time not doing that, I want to die.
So, you know, I feel you on that.
But incidentally, speaking of family jobs, I totally forgot about this.
I was the guy who filed my dad's paperwork for a long time.
I totally forgot about it.
But yeah, I remember filing dad's paperwork.
Yeah, I actually kind of loved it because I get to watch Star Trek while I do it.
And I did that all day.
I would listen to podcasts while doing it.
I hated doing it because I was like, man, I could be spending my time so much better
because he would pay like $8 an hour.
Yeah, my dad would do that kind of stuff too, even before he did that business.
He'd be like, hey.
Honestly, I would not have done it even though he was paying me.
But like he kind of like insisted that we do it.
Yeah, well, hey, we were living with his house rent-free.
So yeah, yeah.
I guess it was pretty good of him to pay anything.
True.
Tom.
Okay, so my first job was in high school and I went to Papageno's just like Nate did.
I worked there just to buy a computer because I didn't have.
Tom, let's literally open a Papageno's franchise, just you and me.
We should.
We're old school employees.
My mom and dad, their first job was both Sonic.
They both worked at the Sonic restaurant as their first job.
Oh, yeah?
Is that how they met?
No, they met each other like decades later or like 15 years later,
but they still like that was that just coincidence, right?
But they still worked at Sonic.
No.
All right.
So sorry, Tom, didn't mean that.
It's all good.
Papageno's the first job.
Then I went to college and I worked at the cafeteria at the school for a while making sandwiches.
And then I also did like the desk thing like where you like sign people into like the dorms
and stuff.
I did that for a while.
And then I got a job at Apple while I was in school.
So I would go down the street to the mall and I'd work as the guy who like you talked to
you about computers and shit.
And I did that for like almost all the Apple geniuses.
That's pretty cool.
You were an Apple genius.
I was like the specialist.
That was the one who like sold you stuff.
I wanted to be a genius, but they're like, you got to work your way up to that.
But yeah, I did that.
It was it's funny because like to this day, everything that I've done, like when I've gone
in to talk to people about jobs, everyone's like floored that I work for Apple.
They're like, what the fuck?
Did you design the Galaxy S5?
God, I wish.
Dude, look at my iPhone.
Was this you?
Was this you, Tom?
Just tell me.
Yeah.
When you see the jobs died, I go.
Put it together.
Yeah, that was me.
Okay.
So I did that.
Then I worked during the summers at Handsome Air Force Base.
My dad, we're not with him.
I was like in a totally different building doing something completely unrelated.
But I did that for a while.
Then when I got out of school, I worked at Best Buy for the season.
And it was.
Hey, are we the same guy?
Yes.
We are the best and worst guy ever.
That's the dynamic.
This runs so deep.
It's so deep, dude.
We need to do our best guy, worst guy podcast.
That'll be great.
That's a great.
That's a fun truth.
Oh my God, literally.
That should be what happens.
I agree.
The communists on the capitalist finally clash.
Oh, no.
Those two ideologies finally get compared to each other after all these years.
I don't think the universe could handle it, but.
Cold War II begins.
By the way, oh, continue, Tom.
I was just going to say after that, I went to Staples for a little bit and that sucked.
Then I went to Whole Foods and I was like a sign maker.
I did like graphic design and stuff there.
And that was nice.
I worked there.
We got our legendary groceries for Radcon.
No, no, no, no, no, no, the first, the first place that me and Tom went to.
No, I don't think we went to Whole Foods.
We went to Star Market, which is like the total opposite of Whole Foods.
Whole Foods is like a high organic food place.
And that was like the healthiest I'd ever been when I worked at Whole Foods.
I had to do nothing but eat food there.
But the only thing I got afforded to eat was Caesar salads because it was so expensive.
So I ate nothing but Caesar salad for like a year and I lost a ton of weight and it was great.
But I lost that job because I was like too...
Retarded.
Yeah, retarded.
No, I was like, I was trying to do too much.
Like I'd try and like solve problems and maybe like get fucked.
And eventually we're just like, we're tired of you trying to solve problems.
Get out here.
We want to be shit.
Uh, that sounds slightly like a simplification.
You were, you were too...
Maybe you overextended yourself and then got not enough done or something.
No, like the problem was that like I would
suggest ways of making things better.
And they didn't want anybody to rock the boat, I guess.
Oh.
And we shoveled this, Tom?
Whole Foods.
I see.
Trying to make things better.
Like what if we had some fucking unhealthy things here so that people would actually power shit?
Because I worked, I worked up, I didn't work on the floor.
There was like an upstairs where they made all the signage and stuff.
Because all the signs of Whole Foods are done by hand.
So I'd have to like write, I had to like do a bunch of classes to learn how to do the Whole Foods
handwritten font.
There's like classes you had to take on how to do that.
So I'd learn how to do that.
And then like you just write these big signs and you have to like draw and cut out on like
phone board and stuff like illustrations to like...
They must be losing so much money by using that system.
Absolutely.
To train people to make a handwriting font.
It's their goddamn branding though.
They gots to do it.
I love that they have this corporate fucking pipeline to artificially induce that homemade aesthetic.
It's so fucking fake.
Like do they like, hey we need to go and pick out the individual coffee beans,
but first we need to put you in baggy shitty like overalls and then like make you look ethnic?
Probably.
Yeah, so that was dumb.
But I was like, I was trying to like...
We had these two computers to do all the work on.
And one of them was like a really really old Power Mac G5 and it was a piece of shit.
And they had files on both computers.
So if you were...
There were three people in the office including me.
They would be on the computers.
I'd be doing all the bitch work because I was the newest person.
And if they needed to get a file off the other computer, they have to stop what they're doing,
get off, go on the other computer, get the file and bring it over.
And I was like, I can network these.
Like give me some time and I can network them together.
So you can access the files from each other's system so you don't have to keep stopping.
And they like, give me like an hour to do it.
I'm like, it's gonna take more than this.
And they're like, well forget it, you suck.
We hate you.
And there's like just tons of like little things about how like the signs were made.
They're like, we could do this faster, but they like refuse and eventually they're just like get out.
So that's how I lost that job.
Okay.
And then I started doing Patreon for a while.
Never try and fix the world ever, is the moral.
That was the moral of the story.
Never give up.
Sometimes corporate systems can be too rigid and we clash with them.
It's true, but never give up on fixing the world even if some people.
If embargo and boycott whole foods, that is the moral of this message.
And then the last job I had, I had a job for, I think a week doing at a racquetball office,
doing like paperwork for them.
And it was like the most dumb job in the world because I originally,
one of my mom's friends told me about it because she works like a hiring agency
who's trying to get people to fill the slot and I need a job.
She's like, do this.
It's work from home.
It's like $15 an hour and you'll be doing like social media stuff,
like getting your social media brand account set up.
And I was like, oh yeah, I can do that in my sleep.
Sure.
So I like go through all these like ridiculous bullshit,
like trying to talk to people to get the job signed up.
And during that time, it changed from work from home to come into our office an hour away
and from $15 to $10.
So, and I was just like, I was already signed the paperwork at that point,
but day before I went into work, they're like, by the way,
you were only giving you a two thirds of what we said that the price was going to be.
So I'd go in there and I just like, it's not social media branding anymore.
They just want me to like do data entry.
So the entire job was a lie.
And I was like, okay, so I was there for a week and then a week,
the next week, I got an email when I woke up before I was going to go into work saying,
we actually decided we don't want anyone to have this position because it's too expensive.
So you're fired.
And it was, you know what, your stories about all this,
everyone just seems to fuck you over all the time.
And it reminds me of the opposite.
Are you starting to understand why my life is awful?
No, let's, and like next PCP episode, the PCP fucks over Tom.
Then we kick him out and we take his money.
I just remembered the greatest thing that ever happened to me.
And it was when I got fired.
Well, I didn't get fired.
They just like stopped the hire, they just stopped paying me from that job where I was
like doing document editing for whatever company.
I did not know, I had no idea that this is how it worked,
but you know, I did that job for maybe six months.
This was like kind of during the TBAP days or maybe a little before.
So it turned out afterwards that I didn't know about unemployment insurance,
but apparently if you work like a real job or a real enough job,
you know, they just bank a bunch of money with the government.
And then if you lose the job under like the right circumstances,
like if they lay you off or whatever, whatever, you just get more money,
like even though you're not working.
And so like for like several months or maybe like two months or more after that,
I was getting like $200 a week in the mail.
And I was like, or no, it was like $150 a week.
And I was like, oh my God, it's, this is all like,
like I was living in a shitty little side room of some guys apartment.
I was like, I can basically live off this.
Like I don't, I'm not working, but I can live and it's like America.
And you know, that's that, that's that emotion, you know, that,
and then I hatched a plan to live that way for the rest of my life.
Right. Yeah.
So it was this unfortunate series of events that led to your current mindset
about lowering your standards to adjust to whatever,
whatever you're currently being given out of the, out of the pity of people's hearts.
It's funny, it's funny you mentioned that.
That's the origin story.
Like this job, the racket ball job was actually like amazing because like,
what a racket am I right?
It was, it was, it was incredible.
Like I made negative money working for this job because,
because of the driving or something.
Because, because they, I had initially gone there to get a work from home
because I didn't, my car was broken and I didn't have the money to fix it.
So, so I got the job because there was supposed to be a work at home position.
So then they said, well, it's actually a driving in position.
So I had to get my car fixed, which was $600.
And then I only got $150 where I was fired.
So I made negative $450 working for this.
Which was amazing.
First of all, Nate, I can understand why you're so fucking utilitarian and
objectivist sometimes when like, I hear people all the time go,
Oh, it's a full stereotype that there's all these people who just wouldn't work at all
if they didn't have to.
But like your older brother kind of is like that.
So I guess Ben did it, everyone.
It's Ben mentality.
I did it.
You just like, you're one of these guys who doesn't want to have to work any harder.
And if someone just gave you money, of course you'd take it, you know.
Well, why not?
Who wouldn't?
Because you're not, I'll tell you why Ben.
And it's because you will not have real power over your life.
You'll always be dependent on people.
And that's not fun.
That's very stressful.
Listen, the only thing that I want power for is to be able to do whatever I want.
But what if they take it away one day?
And if I have that, if I can have that, you know, without, you know, working for it,
like, like if I can have that on like relatively little, you know, resources,
then it like, what would more resources even gain me?
Really, the only thing that the greater number of resources gain you,
which I would understand if people didn't put as a priority,
but it's just a bigger safety net if things go wrong or change.
That's really what it comes down to.
I like a big safety net.
I do.
I admit it.
Sure, sure.
That's all.
It's just if I'm all, if I'm managing to do everything that I want with relatively little,
you know, it's not, I don't have much motivation to strive for more.
I have big goals for my life.
Because I already, because in that situation, I've already achieved the goal.
I, it is, it has come to my attention.
But a safety net is true.
And you know, I mean, it's not like I, you know,
I put off a lot of responsibilities for a lot of time and like,
I put off paying off my student loans for a long time and that was irresponsible.
So.
Sure, sure.
I'm not, that was not the optimal solution.
Well, there you go.
That's great.
I'm glad to hear that.
I guys, I know it's off topic, but I just need to say,
like that came into my life in real time.
This little bundle of joy that just appeared right now.
I need to share with you guys here today.
This will be in the show notes.
Oh, what's, what's this about?
Just, just, just look and see who you see in this crowd shot of this My Little Pony episode.
Just, just go through and tell me who you see.
I see the Breaking Bad guy.
I see Heisenberg.
It's Rick and Morty.
Yeah.
Wait, this isn't it.
Oh, there it is.
There they are.
This is not real.
Well, I mean, they've already done Dr. Hooves.
No, look at, look at, like, look at the pixels on Morty's eyebrow.
It's real.
How do we know this is real?
Where's the confirmation?
That looks, that looks fake to me.
I saw it posted somewhere.
Oh, is that Heisenberg?
And I choose to believe it.
Is that Heisenberg in the back?
I think so.
Probably.
Disgusting.
Okay, but hang on.
His cutie mark is a pickle.
Like would Rick's cutie mark really be?
No, no, it's a test.
It's not.
It's a test too.
Oh, oh, okay.
My screen is fucked up.
Yeah, yeah, I see it.
Okay.
The bottom looks like a pickle.
All right.
Uh, I don't, I don't know.
I can't even speculate.
Right, dude.
Like Tom, whenever you talk about how people were just like,
Hey, we, you know, that job we decided to give you,
we decided to not give you that job.
It reminded me of the inverse of this one window cleaning customer I had,
which was like a fucking modern castle, but a house,
which is to say a really big house that has lots of stone,
like siding and shit.
And I was just like, damn, this house is amazing.
And my dad told me that he had talked with, you know,
the customers and like had a conversation and like
somewhere or another, how they made all this money came up.
Cause these people were fucking young, like mid thirties, maybe early, no, no.
I think like late twenties and with like, like some baby kids, right?
So here's what it was.
The guy, the husband, the dad, he's like a legal document writer thing or something.
He like was doing negotiations for a thing regarding a casino.
And basically his company had him write up a list of terms and agreements and
usually they're going to like reject half of it and you're going to be negotiating for a while.
But they just accepted all of their terms.
I don't know exactly the cause and effect chain reaction here,
but basically it just meant that they all made shit billion dollars of money.
Right.
And it's just like, wow.
Yeah.
That's like a total like out of nowhere windfall.
Crazy.
Right.
And like the mom was saying that like it's crazy when I'm taking my kids to the grocery store
and they basically want everything off the shelf.
And I don't know what to do because I could buy everything on the shelf.
Right.
I'm like, damn bro.
Damn.
Yeah.
It's just like, I feel damned when fucking how when like YouTubers are all like,
I can't believe it.
I have 500,000 subscribers.
I never thought I'd have that many.
Really?
You actually got more subscribers than you imagined yourself having.
Does anyone ever actually done that?
Or am I just, I don't know.
You know what I'm talking about guys?
Yeah.
Well, I suppose I'm lost.
I know.
I'm gay.
I haven't gone through my list.
Yeah.
Please, please.
As I said before, I am post job.
The only jobs I have have been like a back room deals.
Like like no like official salary or you know,
you know, what's the word like regular earnings.
You know, I did not have like a schedule or anything.
I would just do odd jobs throughout society and mostly commissions on the internet.
So I am post.
What's that again?
It's called the gig economy, right?
Right.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
I am post job.
I have lived my entire life, including now where I guess you could say that the PCP is a job,
but like it's more fluid.
It's more fluid.
It's entirely like individual.
Like it's basically commission based more or less for everyone, including me.
Yeah.
So on the only jobs, like if I like the main thing that I've done with my life,
like the main salary earner, I would say is probably commissions followed by the PCP
in terms of how much I've made.
You're also a lawn mower, ain't you?
Well, I used to.
I don't really do that as much anymore, but that's what I'm saying.
I remember you saying that that's how you paid for your flight to Radcon too,
if I remember correctly.
Well, it was mostly commissions, but like.
Okay, no shade on it obviously.
I think it's cool.
No, no, no, no, no.
I know that it's cool.
That's why I say what I mean, like do odd jobs through society,
where I'll just like go a neighbor or someone who just needs me to do something for them.
Who just needs me to perform some miscellaneous sexual act?
I understood.
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
Yeah, okay.
I don't like to do that much anymore because I don't, like most of the people who would be
that are like not here and like I don't live in an area that pertains to,
what I'm saying is I live in a shit ghetto place and I'm not really in demand anymore.
So most of it is online stuff, but I've never like, I didn't have like a summer job or anything.
I've never had like, you know, I need to flip burgers in a high score or anything.
My flipping burgers was flipping minds and creating psychological revolutions on this podcast.
I mean, because you know, that's definitely true.
And it's like, I got my first job at Papa Geno's, or you know, it works for my neighbor,
whatever, like the first one I think it was Papa Geno's that I did when I was like 16 and a half
or like 17 or something.
Yeah, that's exactly, yeah.
And that's like, that's exactly like when you were doing like this stuff, this online stuff and
Mohan Lawson, you know, but more importantly, like the commission.
So like you totally, just like your generation in general, at least like the artists out there
now have like the ability to do this like online commission work when guys like, you know,
my generation was the transitional one where we were going toward this,
but everybody still got like shitty meme jobs out there.
I know, that's what I'm trying to hammer home.
We are folks job.
We have evolved past the need for jobs.
We can just do like, like, like, like, like young artists can just do commission work
and they can get fucking mad dash.
By mad dash, I mean barely more than like a quarter of what you need to live.
Well, you know, this is the fascinating thing though.
Like maybe I'm not really sure it's a quote unquote good thing for like the people
I guess just like for the worker class of society that things are going this way
because things used to be much more cushy and like comfortable and you didn't really need
to worry about it.
And like the economy has just gotten so much more demanding, I guess you have to have like
two parents working to support a family and stuff.
I'm not saying there's nothing to be done except rise to the challenge, obviously.
But I'm just saying that like people really seem to be like lowering their standards across
the board and maybe at a necessity.
Like I don't know if it's just, you know, not everyone's a Ben out here.
It's just, you know, like I was reading like something recently about how like,
or you know what it was?
It was that article that came out pretty recently about how like your average YouTuber
is like barely escaping poverty.
I mean, not your average YouTuber, like your successful mainstream YouTuber,
like I don't know, like your super bunny hops maybe or, you know, one of those tier of guys.
Like those guys like are barely making what like, you know, like a livable minimum class wage,
or minimum class, middle class wage.
And there's just like, like where's the growth opportunity here?
Like there is some if you become like a media mogul or something and you really like
take the internet by storm, you know, you're a fucking PewDiePie or you're, you know,
like the young Turks have a huge network of stuff.
But like, man, it's tough out there in the commission world of being an artiste on the internet.
It is tough out there.
But I think what you lose in like wealth and money, you make up for in time doing what you like.
That's valuable.
Which is the most valuable thing.
That is the highest good that there is.
Agreed.
I'm sort of on board because like, what do you want to do with the money?
Do things that you want to do.
Yeah, that's right.
If you're doing what you want to do, then I said this time and time again,
where I don't particularly want to be super rich or anything.
I just want to be able to do what I want to do, which is just to draw forever.
And so as long as I'm not dead and I'm drawing forever, that's ideal for me.
Yeah, Munchie, what you're tapping into is the fact that we're in this transitionary period,
like hypothetically, well, it won't be that long before robots actually do actually everything.
Like they could even make novels better than people could.
And at that point, we're just crossing our fingers that we continue to be the masters
of this planetary domain.
That will be the final issue.
But at that point, you know, we won't even have money.
I mean, I don't know, this is this is really high minded shit.
But like, we're sort of moving into an area where like,
if everything is automated, hypothetically, then you don't even need to pay money for
anything because everything is automated, right?
So we're sort of hypothetically transitioning away from a life from a world where money is
even relevant.
And the transitionary side effects is it feels like we're fucking up and failing
because we're making less money.
But like money is becoming less relevant.
You know, like, think about, yeah, that's kind of the awkward transitional,
if we're talking like the baby boomer era, we're talking about like the 60s and 70s,
we're thinking about like, it's all about making lots of money and spending that money
to have a good life.
But nowadays, you can sort of have a lot of the same things for a lot less money.
How much money did you have to spend back in the 70s to have a level of entertainment that
you can now have with Netflix?
You know?
Yeah, infinitely more, obviously.
So like, I feel like we've sort of developed our lives.
Like the capitalism develops in our minds, this idea of like this fucking MMO that we're all
playing where like the score that you judge yourself by is your point, which is to say
your money, right?
But there are other ways to feel valuable.
And yeah, I think that like your KD ratio or something, right?
So yeah, yeah, let's we need to gamify real life.
The only problem is I don't trust anyone to make a system where like you allocate points
for the right things, because you're just going to get a bunch of like spawn camping
pieces of shit who just, you know, that's endless war.
Endless war is the gamification of real life.
Yeah, you're right.
The only thing is to make endless war real, aka incite gang violence across all the major
cities in the United States of America.
And then we'll have our ideal society.
We have to irradiate the seas and turn it all to slime.
We need to flood the Grand Canyon with slime to make that slime river flow.
Yes.
And the violence should follow naturally from there.
That's true, but also forbidden.
Deleted.
I I I've been having doubts myself about about how the upward momentum of Internet
content creation and how it will be good for like like me personally.
And I've been thinking about, you know, like I really admire and I and I respect the security
that you have, Nate, of, you know, just doing a job, having that safety net and also doing
what you love, you know, make videos and stuff.
And I have not fully formulated and you'll hard set my opinion.
I used to be super into like, you know, obviously content creation is just a way for me in lines
with all of my beliefs and like what I want to do and it will allow me to do what I want.
But the more I think about the more I think, well, you know, like, like having more money
will be having more money and I will be able to do more of what I want.
You know what I'm saying?
If I, yeah, yeah, wealthy, I will be able to go and go more places and do more things,
which will tie back into my heart.
Yeah, I mean, it does serve the goal of, you know, freedom.
Yeah, it gives you the freedom.
You just it is important to balance your your time that you dedicate to this thing to give
you the safety net so you can do the fun things that you really are passionate about versus
you know, about those two things, making sure that they don't, one doesn't consume the other.
And, you know, like you have to be pragmatic.
Like if you can't pay your rent unless you spend, you know, 12 hours a day at a normie job,
you know, because then you have to do that or else you'll just die and then you won't get to
spend any time doing the fun stuff.
So, you know, you got to be pragmatic about the stuff.
But yeah, that's that's the most important thing I'd want people to take away.
I think that's really important.
If you can make it work full time doing the thing you want to do.
Fantastic. I recommend you do so immediately.
But, you know, being aware of where future trends are going.
And I mean, these days there's a lot of there's a lot of cracking down on some of the more out there.
The only future trend that matters is your trend into the fucking grave.
So there's no time.
There's no time.
Which is 100%.
There's no time to be like, oh, I wonder if I should like wait or not.
No, just fucking do your shit because time's the most important thing.
Money's stupid.
Just fucking waiting waiting in general is almost always a mistake.
But it's important to take smart action.
So like it just like like there's this guy like Uncle Adams.
I know I think I talked about it before, but that guy just said like fuck it.
I'm going to spend whatever amount of money it takes work full time on being a musician.
And I will drive myself into the fucking ground until I get there.
Like in my personal opinion, he is a little bit naive about his chances.
And I think a much smarter move would be to like get a job work on your music in the side.
And because frankly, his music is like, isn't that great?
It's like, what if you never get good and you never get the money back?
Like which will happen to most people who try probably, you know, worrisome.
So you have a motivational crack.com article talking about success.
And like it's point number six to be successful or to get anywhere in life.
You have to start now, which is pretty basic sentiment.
But my favorite my favorite sentence on probably anything cracks ever written
was I would come home every day, I would be at work all day not liking my job,
thinking about all the things I'd like to do writing my novels and shit.
But then I'd get home and then file the rest of my time under the fuck this day folder.
And then just get ready to do it all again tomorrow.
That's what people do.
It's really easy to do that.
I did that for a long time myself.
I always I did that my a lot of my life and hated myself intensely for it.
And I was just so delighted to look back one day after I'd gone through doing all this Tbap
and you know best guy ever in PCP stuff.
And now I'm just like I'm so happy every day when I realize I'm not that guy anymore.
I'm like still that 50% of the time it's like a coin toss whether I'll actually like burn a day or not.
And it's okay be wrong.
Yesterday I should have been working on finishing all the paperwork for like who gets what for the
for the rad kind of it.
Instead I played Stardew Valley.
So you know every day you have a lot of money writing on that.
So I feel free to criticize me everybody.
That's totally fair.
But I'm working on it.
I'm by the time you hear this it'll be done.
So I will say like I have figured out I have cured myself of the most base form of procrastination.
But there's other forms like a crop.
He has to leave the podcast now.
Well I'm supposed to be working on the next Digi video right now.
And I'm kind of doing it.
But I was also kind of just working on selecting dozens of different colors for mannequins in a
level in a video game.
And I'm like I don't want to make the video.
I want to make more colors for my mannequins.
So I'm like oh um anyway the point is.
D-d-divu.
What's up?
Oh continue continue I'll do it after you.
Yeah so I tend to procrastinate by doing something else.
But isn't the thing I'm supposed to do.
A lot of people do that as a way to trick themselves into thinking they're doing what
they should be doing.
Like for example when it's time to do your taxes I will like clean my room.
Because one is like less objectionable than the other.
You know we do that kind of stuff.
Don't fall for that trap people.
You got to be aware of that stuff.
You got to be aware.
So like here's the thing about all these motivational speeches that you've been cutting Nate.
It's like I give all these I mean you're better you're a better hype man than me.
So I guess this is the difference.
But all these people in my life who I've known.
Who have who still struggle with the same problems I had before I started working hard.
And I just feel like none of my motivational fucking speeches like help them at all.
Like for me I look back at myself and it was just all it took was I had I was forced to
start doing a full-time job.
And then like nine months later it was literally just something in me snapped.
And I just didn't stop working ever.
And I don't know maybe it's just not everyone is cut out for this.
Maybe some people ultimately don't mind having a stupid job that much.
They just think that all these cool internet people are cool.
So I want to be like that.
It's like you know I think it might only be for you if not being that is literal psychological torture.
You know as the world famous show Grounded for Life once eloquently put it somebody's
got to make the sandwiches.
Yes.
And that's a perfectly reasonable thing to say.
When the robots make the sandwiches there is a there is an AI burger flipper.
I don't really put a lot of stock personally in like willpower or like people's like inner
strength coming out.
I really think you're just either predisposed to hear a certain message and then like do stuff
or you won't be.
So yeah you know I just think like some people will just get that.
But what I will say is though like because I am a guy who cares about this kind of stuff.
I think that the more messages that are out there though the higher likelihood that someone
might hear it and then be inspired to do these sorts of things which I would argue is a good
thing.
Motivational speeches didn't work on me but it might work on someone else.
Yeah exactly exactly.
I okay this is slightly off topic but I but there needs to be a topic about self-help
culture slash like spirituality because my mom my mom is so hopped up on like feeling the
good vibrations and like thought it was within you and like self-help and like trying to
like like like like do all these like weird like bell and whistles like like fucking fake
snake oil bullshit in order to make herself feel better after coming home from work instead
of just trying like to do normal like I'm going to take a walk or exercise.
See that stuff that stuff comes off.
That stuff comes off is so like I don't know like not not like you're talking down to people
and like it's just so like self masturbatory and like not actually fixing the problem.
That's why I always do and I always go for like the blackpilled like self-help like listen
literally no one cares about your life.
You are worthless in the eyes of everyone else only you can like fix your shit.
So listen do you want to show your life do you want to be sad forever you know if that's
the situation you're in if the answer is no literally no one else will help you you have
to do it yourself.
That's the kind of message that I respond to at least and so it seems more sincere.
Whenever I fucking get in my mom's car and we go anywhere she always is playing some
fucking bullshit like someone lying through their fucking teeth making mad dosh praying
on fucking naive like like like like like mentally exhausted middle-aged single moms
sure it was like he like like self-help like how to be happy in 10 steps here's what you do
or like a thousand steps and it's all fucking not like it's all like like nebulous fucking
not actually like practical like not actually like just take these steps it's all fucking
bullshit number one remember to love yourself oh my god that's it right that's the shit what
this is and when you have to self-help it's not like you shouldn't do that no of course not
of course not I know I can quantify the issue with this mentality that all these that so many
people have that it's a focus on the methods and not a focus on the results you see the
thing about all those books first helping you with any walk in life whether it be money or
confidence or sex they they spend so much time complicating the procedures and like adding more
and more things to remember and you just spend more and more time thinking about all the improvements
you can do then it distracts you from the fact that it's actually it's pretty easy to know whether
or not things are changing you just look and see the results you know yeah like you just gotta be
honest about your situation books to like get you laid with women you know that I feel like they
kind of distract you from a very simple a very simple test are you getting laid or not right
all you got to do is just keep examining that fact and then change your behavior accordingly
you know a great way I look at great example of this I think is like like working out and
like being in the gym the work is the ultimate example of that like you could read it is it
is perfect for this because if you aren't tracking your numbers and your reps and your like if you
you're smart you should measure like your waist size if you're trying to lose weight and you know
check your weight like you should be writing it all down if you're not you're fucking up right
off the gate but most people I think do who are serious about this by doing that you have
uncontroversial like 100 factual results right in front of you every time you go in so you know
if you're doing it right and if you're not progressing you are doing something wrong and it's just
up to you if you're gonna fix or not or if you just don't care I know I've seen like fitness videos
about this being like you can spend forever researching fitness and never like dipping your
fucking toes into it get yourself addicted to the feeling of actually having accomplished something
you know that's the way that's the way exercise is good for you and will make you feel good go
back yeah like watch water advice watch water it just takes effort it takes more effort than
not doing it so the default is to not do it of course for I just realized a way I can describe
what's happening here these these books want to say that it's all mental like it's all in your head
the reason why why your life sucks and you're and you feel bad because you don't do anything it's
all mental it's not about your physical habits that you do it's not about what you do with your life
and like who you hang out with or the way that you spend your time it's all just like just like
readjust how like it's like just think about you know when you put in your debit card to pay for
something and it makes the no it's just thinking about like an 8-bit video game just making like an
8-bit video game yeah I can see that seems like that mentality is a little bit liberating but
really it's binding it's basically putting all misfortune onto you like it's all within you
nothing about your environment is limiting you see that's where like like someone might be tempted
to like really gravitate to that because it allows them to like quote-unquote like be responsible
for everything but that's not actually the case it makes your challenge insurmountable in some
cases yeah well it just it's just you're not fully assessing the problem because like just for example
if you want to lose weight and like your whole family is fat and all your friends are fat like
like yes you could theoretically just completely change your habits but realistically we have
to recognize we are weak impressionable foolish creatures and the best thing to do is start hanging
around people who eat the way you want to eat and who exercise and to get friends like that you know
that's the that's that's a huge way to change our environment yeah yeah yeah I'm just saying and
I'll just share my mom because she's a great lady and I like her but like she'll listen to all of
these books and and she's listening to like like unbelievable like hundreds of books and hasn't
given her a single extra number in her kd ratio has increased at all exactly exactly because
she'll just do like like she'll just try and like think about the world differently but she doesn't
do anything differently she still does the exact same things that she's always done for years this
much his mom is the ultimate nemesis of the pcp she is our art ethicist of
if Nate were to encounter her as like a child he would have smothered her like
well listen I got a lot of respect for for people who raise a kid but but you know still we can still
make criticism it is totally back easy to fall into the trap of like listening to and like indulging
in things that like tell you that like tell you how to feel better that like that like that like
tell you how to think you know yeah yeah like like like it's easy to fall down the self-help
rabbit hole and and think and think that it is doing something for you even listening to this
podcast fair viewer you may be pushing off responsibilities maybe you should be applying
for that job you want right now instead of listening to this podcast about jobs for a bunch of assholes
who don't know shit like one quote from welcome to the nhk that did you always fucking quotes where
the guy says I have read all the self-help books I could write a self-help book just based on my
knowledge of all the other self-help books and none of it has helped me yeah but like to jump back
to what you said about um about uh you know getting yourself into an environment of say
people who eat right or eat the way you want to eat I guess one thing to keep in mind
is that we here on youtube telling people about getting success on youtube we exist in this void
without considering any of the other values and variables or things that you want to have or
maintain in your life i.e if the people if all the fat fucks if all the fucking grease slurping
slobs in your life are people who matter to you maybe that's simply your fate if you can't turn
your if you can't turn your fucking there's no such thing as fate fucking bean burger
knows away from them then maybe not your fate but ultimately maybe you should give up you should
give up the bacon of giving up bacon right well it's it's just you're making a calculation that
you know your proximity to these people is more important to you than whatever the goal is and
you can do that a lot of people do that it's actually pretty psychologically easy for me
in like 2012 to decide I should start working on youtube or game design stuff because I had
nothing else going on in my life right I had like two friends who I would see once a week
and that's all I had to live for I had nothing to lose right whereas so you were liberated in a way
if you're someone who has anything to lose it becomes a much more difficult like my first
experience with actually having to make a hard decision was deciding how much effort I should
put into my channel versus the digi bro channel that was the first time I ever had an actual fucking
trade-off so just keep that in mind folks that a lot of people are held back like you might be held
back by other things you already have in your life you know and don't let our single-minded
explanations of how to fucking get youtube success like dictate your decisions because you have my
approach here I want people to insert whatever thing it is that they care about into the slot
of like just for example like if you want to lose weight or something surround yourself with
like-minded people you know whatever it is you're interested in whether you have passion for pursue
it with as much gusto as you can muster right like if doing yeah if doing an actual job like
being a dentist or some shit interests you like genuinely interests you and like doing painting
or some art thing doesn't interest you to a significant degree stronger I don't think there's
any reason to do that like the only reason I do art is because there's nothing else I am interested
in doing so it's actually a very easy decision for me sure yeah what are you gonna do when digi
bleeds all of his money for making an avant-garde content that no one understands or what are you
gonna do when he bleeds all this money fair fair question yeah I mean I'm right now I'm working
on going down and downloading shitloads of porn that's related to the video and gonna have to figure
out how to censor that yeah what are you gonna do when he bleeds away all of his money well I don't
know make uh he fucking he's gonna get a job there we go back on top there we go bringing it back
no I'm working I'm working on video games something even more okay quick question quick
question to do here's a real okay how much money have you invested in making this game and how much
have you seen on returns uh maybe both are maybe both are zero maybe I am well I am well
beyond well I mean that's my point it's you know what I think it's so bullshit to everyone now you
guys are jumping on this whole like oh you're in a patreon that someone else's patreon is y'all are
all living your life no no no I'm just asking dude I'm not giving you shit no
the fact that you were doing this for digi is not a problem at all the fact is that digi is
bleeding money and exactly as I would say for anyone who works for a corporation like you should
be aware of if that corporation is like currently going through bankruptcy proceedings just like
my friend digi but no I'm just kidding that's not the sound but like theoretically let's just say digi
dies I mean you never know like just what if he dies you know and I'm just saying anyone in any
situation should be aware of the realities of how things could change and have a backup plan that's
on the right the reality I want to live in is where where where divu becomes unshackled exclamation
point divu well I will say I will say I deeply I deeply miss divu's videos I would love those
back yeah I forgot that would be that I forgot divu used to make video in a perfect world in a
perfect world uh but you know hey man okay digi's patreon did decrease over the winter
by a huge margin I've actually continued to get paid the same amount of money like digi also
makes lots of money from agrev that he just keeps sure I've actually been continued to be paid the
same amount of money so I'm not actually I don't want to criticize you you don't need to get into
if you don't want to I'm not trying to like examine your financial situation uh you know
if you don't want to that's perfectly perfectly fine but a bunch of started this munchie what the
hell do you need my money I mean that is actually why I'm on the pcp right now I decided yeah I'm
just gonna sure it's gonna fucking bite the bullet and be on this show where we go completely
off topic and I'm as bad as anyone else at that because I will make a bit of money I do need that
money uh so there you go good I didn't know where your priorities are the barrels was to your head
you just had to pull that trigger and he's done it last thank god like talking about what we said
earlier about the irrelevance of money in the face of like just being happy actually I basically
already have that like I felt like I fucking broke through the heavens of actually becoming
someone who makes stuff that people find relevant and useful to them that's really hard to accomplish
you know to like actually be someone who can make things that people give a shit that's really
hard to do so once I accomplish that I basically felt like I've been set for life you know now
that we found the goldmine that is water park vlogs there's no going back we've cracked we've
opened Pandora's box this is a bubble that will never burst
there's two there's two major forms of currency in 2018 and going forward there is two major
source of income across the world water park vlogs and endless war these are the two driving
force of the economy everything depends on them what if there is gang violence at Disneyland
oh christ it'll be a slime park instead of a water park oh my god that would be we have to make
that we have to we have to build yeah we have to build a new room we have to build a new room in
endless war the slime park oh maybe you can maybe you can pay you can like pay a little bit of
slime to like go on one of the rides or something you have to pay for admission yeah yeah okay okay
bin no okay okay you do like like like exclamation point ride name of ride and and then like like
and then you and then you pay amount of slime and then we have like six or seven like like like uh uh
text walls that we will type out describing your experience with the ride oh oh and here's a quick
thought yeah both both ben and munchy can make competing rides at the slime water park and of
course whoever makes the better ride will get the more money because they get paid for the experience
oh my god like right like we're like tycoons like we like this business we're like your rollers coaster
tycoons in real life and it'll be a race to see who can make more rides and like who can make more
like designs for rides like more like running like running this water park racket in the background
we're just like making slime hand over fists you know how there's like like like like in normal
means there's always like okay who can make the biggest roller coaster we can like who has like
the biggest wall effects describing this person's yeah exactly all right and this war has infinite
growth potential there we go straight from the mines to the water parks to the tycoons yeah we gotta
close this pcp because we have to work on endless war right the fuck we gotta get to the questions
these are the questions let's let's shift over to anyone want to make any final points on jobs
jobs suck i hate them that's fair correct same i am post jobs me and my me and my fellow
2000 millennial children are all post job hashtag post job you indigo children yeah we have no need
for for your for your dirt all you know why hashtag post your jobs because we're poor because the
robots have taken over jobs because um you know the other thing that's appetizing about this kind
of job is that you're your own boss you know you don't have to call in all the time but but just
remember people who want to have a job with their their own boss you really do you have to be your
own boss and you might end up hating yourself as your own boss and that's me i can talk about this
you know how like you get you blame your boss for making you go to work even though going to work is
like like what you're supposed to do with a job if you force yourself to do your job you might have
people blaming you for working like it can't it might even be you you might have contempt for
yourself for forcing yourself to work and if you can't have that then you probably cannot be your
own boss makes sense to me i mean dude it's fucking it's fucking hard like every every success you
get to revel in but every failure you have to realize it was totally your fault you know
so like it sucks realizing that oh i only make 10 percent of the money i used to
and that's my fault so hooray yeah uh well there you go all right let's let's get some questions
jobs are gay question time uh here we go here we go here is a pity question over on the twitter
hashtag sbcp follow us at tbcrasnators uh here here we go uh eskimo bob two asks do any of you
give to charities why are why not no anybody does any no because i'm a charity at this point
i don't give to charities simply because i don't have the money to i don't think i don't think
charities are like evil or anything i get the impression that people are in the chat are gonna
be like come down like oh fucking any don't you all know that charities are evil well well i don't
i don't really i'm sure nate's gonna throw some weird utilitarianism but no i would donate to charity
if i had the money to do so as long as i believe in the cause yeah i i don't have enough money that's
an excuse like if you did have the money you would is what munchie and tom are saying i don't really
trust charities but it's it's not even in the equate it's it's not even a question because i'm
you know because like i'm in debt and stuff i'm like i can't be i can't be doing that with like
that's not what i'm gonna do with money if i get it if it's a hard yes i would get a charity but i
don't it's it's not off the table for me in any way i was a charity that i trusted then maybe i
i i could make excuses personally all day about like oh my finances aren't in as good a shape as i
would like before being to me to start giving money but i'll tell you right now philosophically i
dislike charities not across the board but like the idea that i could give money to a charity and
like any of that money gets absorbed in like administrative costs i do and who knows who
knows what percentage that is i okay i get exactly that has to be there has to be some mechanism like
there has to be some red tape there for like anything to get done like okay i know again like
i'm a little biased here but like i think about like the fucking the pink ribbons the nfl players
who are like the pink shoes are like the it's like breast cancer awareness and like of course we
all want to fight breast cancer it's evil let's kill it but the if you look into the finances like
less than like 10 percent of the revenue from that shit goes to the goddamn charity and fucking
nike keeps the rest and the fucking nfl gets their cut of course like it sickens me i think of
charities as sort of like a modern day what was it like catholic church uh where you just give the
catholic church money in order to get into heaven for free i think of charities and basically like
well even if the money socially that's what they are even if the money didn't actually go to a good
cause i intended for it to be a good cause therefore it's a good thing to do i'll tell you what if i had
lots of money like millions of dollars billion if i had fucking you know notch money i would be like
notch but way stronger like i would just pay people to do art all the time strong like i would
like nobody's stronger than notch if i had a billion dollars i would go on youtube look at all
the people who obviously want to have full-time jobs doing your videos and i'd be like yo close
your patreon that has a sad like seven dollars a month on it i will pay you a full-time wage to
make this on a contract basis right that's what i would do you know that's nice because i believe
in art i don't believe in disease free third world nations leave that shit to bill gates you
see that's the thing the only way the fallacy of spending money is that it doesn't necessarily
get you exactly what you want you can spend a billion dollars to have something happen but if
you're not there making sure the money's being spent correctly it doesn't make shit that's why
the bill and melinda gates foundation does do legitimate good in the world yeah yeah gates is
full-time fucking job it doesn't just take all his money it takes all of his fucking time
and if bill gates didn't do it he would be considered like evil by the world just by virtue
of having that money so he gets something out of it but i just assumed if he had spent the same
amount of money on charity but just threw the money to like the most honest earnest sounding bitter
you wouldn't vaccinate shit well yeah agreed uh probably it's like that that's that's my point
like okay when i think about like it like yeah exactly as you were saying debu there's like
people out there who just aren't making enough money doing what they want to do and you know i have
a little bit of conflicting feelings because i think to myself like okay i value what this person
is doing but if they're so unpopular that like they haven't been able to like capitalize on this
and like make it a successful business like i know not everyone's a great businessman but like will
this even succeed long term if i subsidize it so there's like concerns about that it's not about
me it's not about trying to push stuff out the boat that is going to be successful it's about me
wanting certain art to exist okay sure i remember there's this documentary i only have seen the
commercials all this relay the commercials information about the guy who made five-hour energy
he became a god damn billionaire and spent 99 percent of it on just charity and fucking like
uh philanthropy he basically built this huge fucking like science lab where he just gives
scientists and engineers free money to build cool shit that can help the poor like a a hand-cranked
water filtration bitch type of thing right like so basically he spends his money on very specific
things that can very specifically help people in specific ways like when um james ralph recently
like a couple years back did a charity where he was auctioning off some old avg and set pieces or
like scripts and the money was going to charity but it was very specifically going to the hospital
this like this like specialty hospital that like saved his daughter's life right well sure okay
basically like his daughter wasn't treated properly when she was born so he took her to this other
medical specialty place and they like basically uh resulted in his daughter not being like
permanently disabled because they knew what the fuck they were doing right so james ralph was like
all right if i ever do a charity it's gonna be these guys right because they're very specific
people who i actually know right mm-hmm so that that's the thing about why i think it's bad to
like not bad but i think it's misguided to think that if you have money you must give the charity
because yes you could have a million times more money than someone else but we all only have 24
hours in the day and doing good takes time not money i mean takes you know and that's very true
and i like i can make another argument here that like okay who's gonna do more with the money for
the world like some like elon musk or like some poor kid in chicago like you know maybe that kid is
like a super genius and like he'll use that money and like get somewhere in life and go really far
but we've got a track record with elon he's doing good work over here with all his money i don't know
if i necessarily agree with the sentimentality of we just have to like put all of our resources into
like like the rich and powerful and and genius well i mean in this particular case it's an argument
to like take elon's money to give to like poor people which of course i am not in favor of uh
but yeah i i i it again it comes down to the individual decision of just i like poor black
kids in chicago let me give the money if i like everybody i just choose to wait there was infinite
money and infinite resources of course we want everybody to have it uh it's just a matter it's
a matter of you know distribution um i don't think i don't think it like like i don't think it needs
to be a matter of of of moral ambiguity to just do to just give money to who you want to give money
to win and if and not what i you choose to do i i disagree i mean to certain degrees because like
if i give so well just like there can be cases where like if i give so much money that i personally
let's just say i give so much money that i starve to death because i can't buy money for myself
just as an edge case obviously that is that is not ideal you don't want to go that far that's
too much even if the people that you're giving money to survive only because you gave money
and maybe more people survive than you die the question is what will they do with their lives
we have to make these calculations now because we're dealing with these sort of like that's
that's what we're talking about we're trafficking in direct human life at this point the human
trafficking and what they'll do with their lives is i'm a human trafficker is that they will be happy
uh correct correct but and that's what people want is for other people i have now completely
forgotten and just now remember this is a question this isn't just a continuation of the topic
yeah that's true just do any of you give to charities why why not i'll make one last point
in favor of munchie basically in this point which is just like if i could for if you think about for
example like in the middle in the middle ages like there were probably like super genius kids born
to just like dirt poor surf families and like they obviously had like no opportunity to like
succeed and we're just like trampled and you know died never getting a chance to succeed
i want all those people to have an opportunity to succeed across the world so like yeah where
charity where charity can do those sorts of things i absolutely wanted to do so though i don't believe
in like extracting money from people if they don't choose to i don't when this when this person said
like would you give charity i i don't like believe in like really like huge big charities or anything
i just want to like analyze like just giving two things that i feel deserve money and slash or
attention yeah i don't have any particular like uh standards or or beliefs like that i
want to give to that i can like think of right now mm-hmm you know i'm saying like like there's no
charity that i that i am like itching to give money to i'm just like like the idea of giving money
to other people does not repulse me i it doesn't repulse me either it just depends on this like
sometimes it does repulse me other times it doesn't you know yeah sometimes repulses me too
yeah there you go there you go we don't anyone else want to win this no tom would you give
it oh tom is the charity case right i forgot i've been ben what do you think just real quick uh
if i had like more money than i knew what to do with than maybe but like i'd have to be really
i'd have to like really know like what the money was going to yeah like i would just have to be
thoroughly convinced that the money was actually making a real difference and not you know that's
it makes sense to me uh one other uh twitter question here from at doombox two favorite
anime okay moving on we're going to be uh to the piece to the patreon lounge questions over here
this is why we have bad comments is because you read them aloud and they think they're really
funny that one is funny it was a joke comment god damn it all right we've had that joke like four
i like it every time all right here's an actual good question yeah an actual good question here
discount gumshoe asks this is a great question for this topic i told everybody that we're doing
the job's topic uh okay will the chad artist or just you know or will the artist ever be free of the
you don't work hard meme that the virgin wage cucks have forced upon us you don't understand what he's
asking here like so so often so often you'll be like an online content creator like a video maker
or like a draw boy and you'll say those you know you'll meet someone out they'll be like hey what do
you do uh so you know i'm i'm a i'm a youtuber i'm an artist you know i do commissions and they're
like oh no what about a real job though what's your oh you know never be free because inherently
being an artist means that what you that you're doing what you you're you're you're choosing your own
work and it's just i think it's just inherently less punishing and it's just it's going to be seen
by those who have to do stuff they don't want to do for a living you know it's going to be seen that
way no matter what and i don't even blame it like i think that's kind of reasonable i don't think
what the work of an artist and the work of a wage cucks virgin wage cucks they they are of the
opinion that work is supposed to be like grueling and hard and bad they the word work has negative
connotation to them because they are virgin wage cuck bitches yeah and so they they feel the need
that like oh like work needs to be hard because i'm because you know it's hard for me because i don't
want to do any work i'm just a worthless piece of shit but like artists are doing work objectively
they're just doing work that they enjoy and that doesn't make them feel bad
yeah man like i don't see like virgin wage cuck comments in my preview much like let's just face
back plenty of artists are pretty damn lazy a lot of people don't realize how i think the real
issue here is discrimination like artists being called inherently like not working hard like some
subset of my experience might be really skewed or wrong but i just see that if you are obviously
working really fucking hard it's gonna show and people are gonna not say that shit right you
know the only reason i disagree with that divu is because of like stuff that like tom will retweet
where like people i i don't even know like i kind of am skeptical as to how often this even happens
but like tom will retweet these like horror stories sometimes of like someone like he's like
hey would you draw my oc and they're like sure it's like a hundred dollars like
you expect to be fucking paid for that piece of shit and you know like that attitude is kind of
inherent here it's like how i'm sorry my body's still fucking high uh it's like how could you
possibly not expect someone to request some form of compensation i feel like that's just that's in
the mix here somewhere you know what i mean that's like me and me and divu me and divu staged one
right yeah and it took seven fucking months to do it you goddamn non-worker yeah i just sat on it
and didn't post it for months and i don't know why yeah so it was a perfect example of lazy
artists ladies and gentlemen there they are yeah all artists don't work you see i can feel why why
munchy would would be so strident fighting back against this because we all know how hard a worker
munchy is and the crazy stuff he's always cooking up uh i could i feel the same way you know like
the content that i make is is generally very high effort i'm currently fighting against that but
was that not sarcasm just now i was sincere just now whoa what do you mean i think i it feels so
weird for someone to have nate compliment me it doesn't i come with people all the time that was
so bizarre i was just waiting for the like like like oh we all we all know what munchy's always
cooking up a fucking faggot let's go ahead dude yeah my answer to that question so people
can't tell i'm sincere my answer to that question is really just fucking if you want those people
to go away i think that if you just work harder people will see it you know like yes you can say
oh it's you know it's not actually easy to draw yeah but i see artists of equal drawing quality
who are like five times more prolific than the other one you know sure you know what i mean like
there's definitely you know what it comes down to the the question is will like the artist ever
be free of this like meme that's you know discrimination or whatever the answer is basically
what ben was saying it's really no like because there's this kind of there's this kind of like
competition between the two yeah because people associate work with like bad unfun stuff as long
as that exists right there will be but there's here but you individually can absolutely rise
above it there's a much stronger reputation uh deriding those who are stuck in entry level jobs
as being underachievers who coast on minimal you know clock in your nine to five every day
and then go home and do nothing right so i think though i think that stigma is probably worse and
more hard to get rid of so i think uh i think everyone in any position is going to be faced with
some sort of prejudice about not being hard enough yeah he's gotta be hard even if you're
successful and rich people are gonna be like oh this guy didn't fucking work to be rich right yeah
yeah and there's the whole like yeah there's the management fallacy where people don't people are
like you don't do fucking work you just tell other people to do work why are you getting paid so much
money kills me that's the fucking capital uh fucking communist mindset in a nutshell yeah those
bitches need to watch winter wrap up where you see the true value of someone whose skill is
organization yeah people need to fucking watch season one winter fucking wrap up organization
matters people get the fucking right the the problems they just don't understand what managers
actually do uh and some are lazy yeah you know what you know what this is actually kind of relevant
to this in general because like i think of a lot of the reason people think art is just easy
and they assume they're lazy is because they don't know how hard artists can actually work
because they don't understand the process yeah of it being made you know idea that like artists are
just talented you know yeah they just have an inability that's true and just for my realm of
experience like when you post a video bam the video just for the viewer it didn't exist now
magically it exists but they don't see the months of work and the editing and the recording and you
know all that shit that that's one of the things mean mean been starting to go back to
reference copulars but but we're trying out streaming and that's like the main thing that I
think like like we're trying to see if we want to do that full time yeah and it's looking pretty
great and like i think it's well suited to our long form content but the satisfaction that the
reference specialist fans get from just waking up on some random day and you are just blessed out
of the blue by by a ravers cop killers video by six seven hours long yeah yes it just it spawns out
of nowhere it's great it's a great feeling it's a great feeling i think that's a large part of why
youtube is so fun you know it's just fun to be subscribed see a huge video drop everybody loves
it plays off that like slot machine mentality where it's just like i wonder if it's gonna be here
today it's the skinner box it's like you know small like random random rewards more or less yeah
youtube subscriptions are loot boxes we need to ban online gambling such as subscribing to anyone on
youtube it's a gamble and we can't allow it we need harsh regulations that that's why there's such a
little Amish population and like demographics on youtube is because it's a form of gambling they
can't do it that's the reason all right two more points before we go on the next question okay first
of all uh just really quick here unrelated uh i just realized the other day that we actually passed
the two-year anniversary of ravers cop killers on uh april 11th so yeah well the debut was on that
first one so right yeah dude the pcp is also passed or not aware yesterday was homestuck day
yeah it was right i know right i wish i hadn't been so sick i would have fucking done something for it
i would have been stuck you were stuck at home and i was so upset you know i was going to make
armors people fan art because i don't want to disrespect homestuck by just like not even
acknowledging that it was there all right but the real thing that actually is related to this
is the one like like like the biggest influence or the biggest positive influence the pcp has had
my life uh that's completely changed the way i perceive something was the insistence and and
me realizing that work is and should be good yes work should have no negative connotations
and it should be a pure positive because you know like i had grown up and my mom would come home
for like oh working this fucking so bad and i hate it so much uh but like when i yesterday yesterday
was or two days i lose track of all time because uh because i don't perceive time the same way other
people do i'm a cryptid uh i i worked for like like six hours on that one feeling closer to death
like vlog video i worked so hard that i had to like get footage of like a range things and then
after it was done i was so fucking happy that i had put in the work to make that and i had gone
like like this guy like like like call me on skype and i had to like do some like green
green screening shit right i had to like arrange a footage like frame by frame for a certain part
it was fucking it was great and i was so happy that i had done it and and and just the fact that
i could sit back and think wow i put in so much work what what a good what a good day this yeah
that's the feeling that i love more than anything else you think real smart and you'll get real
lucky work can be nothing but good when it comes to like editing videos there's lots of parts that
are just constantly creative but then in parts where it's more like grudge work uh then you can
put on a podcast because there's parts of your brain that are being unoccupied because it's
boring but then there's parts where it has to be stupid there's just no two way you cannot be
cognizant while doing this part so then you can get drunk for that part you see if you play your
cards correctly you could smooth over the experience of every part of the production and if you can't
then you're doing something wrong and and furthermore if you are listening to this podcast right now
if you have found your way here and you are you are intelligent enough to be listening to this right
now i guarantee you can have the life that you envision for yourself ideally in i would say
five to ten years of investment no matter how you work right fucking now yeah if you get to it now
and whenever you start like if you want to start for a year that's fine but then there'll be five
to ten years from then so you know whatever you want to do buddy that's that's the sooner you'll
get it to pay off and when you start doing the thing you want to do we're think about how to make
it a like economically viable if it will never be economically viable except the fact that you'll
need to have a side job and then maybe one day you'll be you'll be doing this 20 years later and
you'll realize huh you know what i guess i don't need my side job i really can do this full time
because you never know if the what matters is to just be working towards the things that you want
to do that aren't economically viable that's probably a hobby and hobbies are cool yeah so there you go
that's true hobbies the ladies love hobbies guys the ladies love doing it and what it takes
is working a job to make it possible then you know you got to do that you know what i'll say
about this if it's what you want then it should be worth it i i said before that a lot of this
is motivated by my deep sexual insecurities as a man and uh i feel like that really did motivate me
in in one sense here that was like i once heard advice uh in my in my old days of researching
like how to be attractive and how to be cool and stuff and i i read a thing that just like women
just love men with passion and like it's you got two choices one make your full-time job your passion
so that you're excited to go there every day and you have something to talk about to like the ladies
or whatever so that you you are full of interesting and exciting things that are that like a woman
would want to be a part of there's that option or if it's not your full-time job and if you're if
you don't like your full-time job then you've got to make yourself like your hobby your your purpose
in life you've got to have something in you that's burning inside as like a desire to reach and yeah
so that you have things to share with people that's what it's all about man and and having that inside
me both motivated me to like improve my life so i would like be able you know just like all the
normal stuff of like wanting the things i want having you know control over my life and that
and then also it tied into my you know wanting to like be attractive to women and stuff it was
helpful in two ways yeah i completely agree with everything that you just said but i just hate sex
so much so i'm just going to say do everything nate said but do it for yourself for inner fulfillment
what i'm describing is basically a cheat code it's a cheat code if you attach your desire to get
girls to this that might help you as well it did for me entirely how i've gotten a fucking person
i think like the the the hilarious side effect of that is if you do nate's cheat by the time you
get like so fucking good and like your life is so good you realize you don't even fucking need to
fuck that much because that's yeah that that's a real secret dude the real thing that is more
important and like like there's guys out there was inside you all along there are guys out there
who enjoy a fucking new bitch like every single day but your average guy what they're interested in
is like i i mean this is my experience i think your most average guy just wants a girlfriend
who makes him happy you know he's pretty hot we all want that and even whatever way you define
that as and uh like you just feel contented like that part of your life is satisfied i think that's
a very common thing that a lot of people want and like if personally on my quest that took
fucking a bunch of bitches that's what it took for me to realize that about myself and uh but now i
know now i know and i'm pretty content i would tell my fiance back when we were just like dating
and shit i just asked her like why the fuck do you find me attractive like i don't i don't know
why i'm that hot to you and she said okay well you know quentin tarantino and i was like what and
so she compared me to quentin tarantino and then she's into people like quentin tarantino
the madman himself fucking shrimpy fucking egotistical a guy like that when when billy
mitchell has fallen from grace recently for being a cheater she was really sad about that too because
she really likes billy mitchell for the same reasons and i was like oh wow yeah i went when i
was i totally get that it's a passion man yeah when i was 15 i realized oh i should just like
not care about like trying to impress girls and i will just make myself impressed with myself
and yeah basically ever since then it's been pretty easy you just you just don't even think about it
and you just get pussy jumping on your ass all day you gotta do it we should really have
we should really have an entire episode about relationship so so so we can get into this
but i'm much more far online with the devoo of just improve yourself and obviously people who
like the improved you which is to say the you that you want and should be we'll just naturally
gravitate towards you yeah i mean i told you that's that's the that's the basic uh logic find it
we've been going for almost three hours yeah we gotta start we gotta start rapping
i've been like the last hour we've been talking about getting hype and doing your work i've been
looking at this file that i started before the podcast it's like i really just want to
fucking work on this it's okay you know what i i totally feel i totally feel it for that sake
let's let's just get a question to a little bang them out real fast yeah yeah rap is shit out
here's one that i well i want to answer by one spar bleakly and in the patreon lounge
since shitty questions is a big pcp meme now will there be questioners rules episode uh on the
podcast like like commenter and reviewer rules i think that would be funny and possibly a decent
topic i could see doing it i what i would want to do is i want i would want to like replace the
question section of an episode with questioner rules so we can have like a dual topic kind of
because because i don't know if we have enough to say that will fill like an entire episode
but i don't know about that okay okay to like to like address how bad the questions are i think
we could do that i'm in favor of doing i think that would be cool i think that'd be some idea
such a boner killer to have a whole episode on like questioner rules and then have to take
the shitty questions after laying it all out but they perfect perfect examples of what what how to
do it wrong which i'm sure it will be without a cable out of town maybe um all right well you
know what uh this is okay this is an interesting question grace you asks i got my masters and
and i guess this thing and i'm still struggle oh and i still struggle to get a job how can you
really stand out fancier resume formatting interview tips so okay well if we're the ones
to be asking about this yeah yeah i like there's a million things you could say about this i just
i thought this was a heartfelt question that this person's looking for for information on
a little help so just i don't know my my thoughts on this are damn you already got a masters and
you're struggling to get a job okay here's my here's my real question okay like what's the masters in
i assume there's not a lot of demand for it uh i mean i suppose you could be shit and you could
be like bad that's entirely possible um okay like there's no cheat to like one one weird old tip
to like stand out or anything i would say what what people want is just competency at the at the
end of the day they're gonna take whoever looks like they're best at the job so like how do you
demonstrate that here's what i would do i don't know what your field is for me like one thing
that really impressed people when i was applying for programming jobs was the work i did on my own
outside work just the side programming stuff i had going on so i don't know maybe you're like a
maybe you're a fucking writer or something you're trying to get like some job writing for a magazine
or something like have a blog have written to it try to make it popular you know just you know go
through the motions of doing the thing that they want like nobody wants a college kid who's only
learned a bunch of bullshit that probably isn't practically applicable they want someone who's
in the fucking trenches already and they know can easily plop into a slot so what like resume
formatting interview tips like i don't know if you have like terrible time interviewing and
you're constantly fucking it up then like yeah obviously you should work on that in in whatever
way i'm sure there's lots of resources for that fancier resume formatting man we're just we're
beating around the edges the core issue is have be able to tell them why you're great and how you're
perfect for this and all that shit like you want them to believe that you're worth the job
do you believe that you're worth the job good yeah yeah you gotta you gotta impress him a little
peacocking in terms of what you can do does not hurt you never heard that's right that's right
kstep in the questions bar asks thoughts on the tick with take your dog we were actually playing
on doing i thought we should do that as the topic today nobody wanted to do it because they didn't
want to get into the weeds of the drama i didn't even want to talk about the drama literally just
figured out how we can do well okay tig with a bring it up is inherently linked because it's
popular right now it's a property talk about right now because the drama i mean i know i just figured
it out here's how we can do an episode about the episode will be called internet content creator
group incompetence or maybe somebody shorter that way we can compare and contrast our own
competence or lack thereof to tig with tags because there's a lot of times where i'm thinking
man we sure are a lot less masturbatory here's here's my i mean there are many differences
and i guess there's some similarities but like right out of the gate here here are my thoughts
on the tig with take doc kstep i have not read it and i am not a lawyer i have i don't trust anyone
who just says i had x experience i demand evidence before i think anything about anyone
and to do otherwise anyone in the world is immoral so i hope that like everyone we could what are
you supposed to say right now like oh they're all bad because a lot of people said they were bad
is that true where's the proof like were the police involved like there was like sexual allegations
is any of that substantiated i don't fucking know i have no grounds to make any assessment
whatsoever and frankly it pisses me off that people just take the word of people when they
just assert things without evidence agreed no need to me dude don't you think it's fucked up that
like we think this culture now is just like an allegation can tank an entire business that's the
problem that's the problem but and i read some of that stuff most of it is people being awkward
and just not communicating clearly like some people have sexual crime allegations literally
go to the cops and tell them everything and work it out it's not the court of public opinions job
to judge if you were like abused at your job it's your job to figure it out yeah why are you like
why am i involved i don't care at all about the um the issue of like whether or not they should
like it should be sued or some shit like that or defamation yeah like wait what is tick with tick
actually tanking right now as a result is channel awesome like actually like financially i believe
that as a note like basically none of their fans gave a shit and that it didn't matter right exactly
for me this is like a bunch of people leave the site though like i a bunch of people have been
leaving the site for the reasons that have been explained in a document that it's it's
shit to work for them right but for me what i take away from it is it's an interesting case study in
incompetence and hubris basically imagine if you listening at home have you read it do have you read
i scammed a shitload of it and i read all of lindsay ellis's part because she's the one good
writer in the group so okay so be aware that's what we're working with that's the information
not only have i said reports being referred to by davoo now okay not only have i skimmed most of it
and a lot of it was the same complaints listed over and over again so i saw the gist of it but
also i am the one in this group who's seen the most tick with a with like hippo at a close second i
believe right so i do have a lot of understanding of this group i've been i mean i i've started
following them like ten goddamn years ago right and it totally makes sense to me now imagine if you
as in you the audience listening at home did some weird shit on the internet that somehow got
popular and now suddenly you have all this power your dug walk or you have all this power to get
a bunch of little spurgies flocking to your throne to mooch off of your fame and now you
have the power to coordinate them to do these giant skit movies together if you guys didn't know that
was where most of these complaints come from is is the production of the big tick with tick crossover
movies where they did the anniversary stuff yeah and it was like making a whole movie but like you
know home video style and people were just explaining in depth how dug and his brother rob
and the producer mike mccodd were just totally didn't know the single first fucking thing that
they were doing but because they were in this position of power no one could like question them
and mike mccodd would like you know bat down anyone who did question them so dug always
side as everything is going really well and everybody's really happy but then meanwhile
the people working for them are like why the you didn't think to give us food on this set
what the fuck right like oh that's so that's so retarded that like this is like the major issue
they didn't even give us food or water on the set like this is the big issue this is what you've got
this is the damning evidence oh my god shut the fuck up i don't care about your stupid baby problems
fucking go to starbucks across embarrassing like it's like it's embarrassing that they would make
such an oversight no i think it's absolutely appropriate that most tick with ticks fans don't
care and they continue to watch the videos yes i don't think okay it does sound like mike mccodd
might be kind of a bad person dug and robber just sort of like oh why would he be a bad person
what is he done because he sort of was a fucking creep about like people like being critical of the
website not like damning critical not like defamation critical but like saying problems that they have
that are pretty innocuous mike mccodd would be like shut the fuck up you don't get to say that right
or you're fired right he's a man defending his business whatever i don't know unless it is something
directly more of a criminal on behalf of dug and rob walker they're just they were just fucking
over privileged fucking white boys who don't understand like how to take care of shit and it
pissed a lot of people i don't even agree with that i don't even agree with that shit like what the
hell i didn't read the fucking document i don't deserve to comment on this none of us too i bet
the people who fucking wrote the thing i don't even know half of what the fuck they're talking about
because none of this shit's serious and it's all like little baby complaints if it's more than a
baby complaint it should be with the fucking police it should not be the court of fucking opinion
public opinion i just like this is such a bitch move no they're just trying to ruin the reputation
of a fucking company and what did they really do they didn't give us fucking water on our fucking
coffee break when we were at this big meetup thing bring a fucking water bottle go to the
fuck to shaws and buy one no let me explain yes i do totally agree that this is why they were able
to be kicked around so much and and and i'm no people are gonna get mad at me because i'm sure
there's more serious stuff than what i'm bringing up i'm just focusing on the stuff that i'm biased
toward that's exactly why i know what you'd listen to me either no one should care to anyone on this
issue well please go on actually like kind of have to go so like if we don't wrap up soon i'm
gonna have to leave okay i'll say okay i'll say yeah the thing is the reason why these people were
kicked around is that they're all talentless fucks like almost all of tag is just non-entities right
like there was no formula more boring that was that was brought to prominent popularity on the
internet until the cinemasans fucking plague hit the world right so like they didn't really have
any power they didn't have the ability to like strike out and do their own thing they were completely
leaching off of Doug Doug's popularity so you can see in the article most of them writing their
complaints in this document are too incompetent to make a compelling case i had to sort of unpack
what they're saying detach what they're actually saying from what they think they're saying and
then come out with an accurate explanation they're putting it like we've been mistreated and abused
and hurt and fucked them and there's a little bit of that but again Lindsay Ellis the Nostalgia
Chick the one really talented person who ever graced that website her whole case was presented
much better she simply explained how Doug was not capable of arranging this shit it was disorganized
people were like he was constantly fighting with his brother like in front of people about like
script disappearance it was just embarrassing and wasn't so is that really what it is though
it was just an embarrassing situation is that the crime it was embarrassing and also way too stressful
and stupid and it could have been so much better like she even explained like i went up to Doug
being like yo we're on a set we're not there's their first big movie was like in the middle of
nowhere i think there weren't a whole lot of restaurants around and she said yo what about
food and Doug was like i don't know but then like fucking spoonie came up and said well you know
food is typically provided on a movie set and he was like maybe you're maybe you're right spoonie
maybe i should well lock up the fucking misogynist i guess i know right what men say i know i know
anyway the point is it's just a story of incompetence and hubris and not realizing that like people
aren't having nearly as much fun as you are and i totally believe that happened i believe all of that
i 100% believe every story in there but i just don't give a shit yeah but name because i don't
think these are serious problems except for the sexual allegations take them to the fucking cops
yeah i'm not a dude but dude like when people portray this as the fall of the nostalgia critic
it's like no this is just finally people are pointing fingers when they should have been all
along like finally these i don't even like any of these people i watch this i have some positive
feelings towards the nostalgia critic because i like them i just don't like to see fucking witch
hunts and there's too many fucking witch hunts these days people are fucking cowards fucking
talked i mean whether you know it never mind yeah i love this fiery name but we should leave now
escape my right before i turn it against you okay you gotta get the fuck out of here i have nothing
else to say on this matter anyone else want to comment on this it's gay and i like it uh i
i agree i agree that if the allegations are criminal in nature then they should be taken up with the
police i just really don't think the people like us the viewers have should have like any involvement
in any of this it's like the whatever people can tell their stories if they're fucked up it's just
the way it is presented at a point where you can do more damage to somebody on twitter than through
legal means that's a good point tom that's a damn good point basically what i am saying here is way
back in 2008 when this site was brand fucking new i made a blog post i made a different forum post
saying yo you people like don't know what you're doing this is a giant shit show of talentless
and everyone came down my fucking door being like oh you're being a true old band band band right
but now 10 fucking years later the people who ran the people who consisted of most of the shitty
content on this site are finally calling it like it always was and i always fucking knew it it's a
fucking it was a very good it's always been a total happy shits right devoo wins devoo wins this episode
all right who wins i'm satisfied so devoo wins all right i think we're done everybody please
that's it our questions all right all right so if you like this episode if you didn't un pledge
remember most of those questions we just read it came from our patreon lounge so give us a fucking
dollar at least on the fucking patreon.com slash the procrastinators and we're more likely to your
question there ask discord then you're in you're on in it's it's an active discord you want to be
in on this shit uh you got it we got the feed for all the psb stuff it's great uh beyond that it'll
be pledged five dollars you get all the bonus episodes munchie what was the last bonus episode
the bonus episode that we last recorded was radcon three yeah that's the one that's the one yeah
radcon three there may have been a a snippet explain in depth it may have been a step by step
process i think we i think what we should be have done is put the bonus episode clip at the
beginning of this episode but i don't know i'll figure out later uh that's it uh follow us at
twitter at tbcrastinators everything gets announced all the show that comes out still rolling out
tons of radcon three content so you probably want to be checking the fucking radcon three playlist
accumulated yeah it's it's not anywhere close to done uh so i can't release any of my stuff
ben what the hell is going on the ball but it'll come it's coming okay all right
ethan is editing the spirit science lecture as we fucking speak oh my god now i'm cooming just
thinking of it i know uh what else and i'm a nevratrix cop killers and i've already put out
those two vlogs yeah it's coming it's fucking it's pouring out there's big stuff still on the
horizon here and uh it's gonna be great it's gonna be great uh oh and uh uh everybody who uh all the
backers here's your just update we are still getting together the paperwork to get everybody
their stuff but it is coming don't worry i'm on the case you'll get it pretty soon uh all right i
think that's it we are out of here everybody we will see you next fucking week with another episode
of memes and dreams bye
stupid boy yes yeah
myself i'm
don't want to do it