I'm going to bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Alright, you want to just go?
Yeah.
I guess I want to actually...
Okay, um, yeah.
Hello, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Woooo!
Okay, yeah.
Um, you know what?
Now that this podcast has started, let me write down some notes about things I had to talk about this week.
Wait, we didn't sync, let's sync quick.
Oh, you're right.
Okay, three, two, one, sync.
Sync.
Okay, sorry about that, everyone.
Now that the podcast has started and we've sunk on...
Live on video.
Let me write some notes about what I wanted to talk about this week.
Uh, nothing.
There's nothing that happened.
Nothing has happened except for news of the world.
Oh, god.
I don't really know what to say about that.
Shaving.
It's like, uh, news.
This isn't a politics show.
I just made an angry tweet at JK Rowling just to make myself feel better.
Mm, JK Rowling.
I just thought it was pretty funny.
It's pretty funny how, you know, Roe vs. Wade gets revoked.
What is...
The Shaq meme, uh, uh, trans women exists, you know,
fucking real shit for JK Rowling.
Oh, Roe vs. Wade getting revoked.
She doesn't say anything about it for like three days
until some trans woman says,
I bet JK Rowling is a right wing.
She says, no, I support abortion.
No, this trans woman's attacking me.
I support abortion.
Trans women are at it again.
I'm so under attack right now.
I'm so...
I'm so vulnerable.
Die.
Die, trans.
That's what she said.
That's what she typed.
I saw her.
She's so stupid.
And I said, no.
And I said, no, like the Shaq meme,
like the giga Shaq meme,
and the camera panned across my chiseled jaw
in black and white.
That's what happened.
Yeah.
What else?
Oh, okay.
Well, I have three things on my stupid list now.
So that's three more than I had a minute ago.
Hell yeah.
Content for our viewers.
I hate our viewers,
but I understand that I exist in a constant state
of push and pull with them,
where they always want to pull the content out of me.
And I always want to push the content out of me
like I'm taking a shit all over them.
And so I have arrived here at the toilet
of our podcast to do the deed.
Anyway, I did go to a protest about that yesterday.
And like usual, I left feeling like,
well, if nobody put a brick through any windows,
what was the point?
But, you know, I guess my job was just to be a body
swelling the numbers, which I suppose I did.
So I did my part, I guess.
There's not really any, I mean, you know,
here in Massachusetts, like, you know,
everything's fine for the moment.
I guess it's nice to do a protest here
because they can say, oh yeah, they did one everywhere.
They did one in every major city.
And like, yeah, we did ours.
It wasn't huge.
At least it got like media coverage.
I remember like, there was a lot of like anti-JK rolling
like pro-trans stuff that was going on in London.
And I noticed that the BBC had not made a single article
about them at any point, whatever.
It's whatsoever, not even like a written article.
No mention whatsoever.
It's like nothing.
We needed to smash more windows.
That would have got their attention.
Oh, I thought there was going to, I thought there was going
to be a follow-up like, but then.
No, no, it's just like, if you do a protest
and nobody pays attention, did it even happen?
I was telling, I was there with, I was there with Steve.
And I was telling him like, actually the, you know,
I went to, I was at this thing and I was at,
I was at, I did a BLM march in 2020.
And then I think maybe like the year or the year before that,
I went to the counter protest for that straight pride parade
that they did.
And that was way angrier.
That was like, people were fighting the cops.
People were getting like, cops were like grabbing people
out of the crowd and like hauling them away.
People were blocking the road to like block like the police
like motorcycle, a convoys and stuff.
I got maced.
I mean, I didn't personally get maced.
I got second hand maced because someone near me got maced
and it got into the air and I got some in my, in my face.
That was way, way more hardcore.
You should have won your steampunk goggles.
I know, but I didn't.
Instead, I just looked like a normal fucking idiot.
Someone gave me a bandana while the mace was going
and they were like, here, cover your mouth.
And I was like, thanks.
And I did.
I still have that bandana somewhere.
I saved it.
I thought it was cool.
Anyway, yeah, that was the angriest.
That was way angrier than, than the BLM march.
And it was way angrier than this one by far.
Would you say that angry protests are something you want to go to more of?
I don't know.
It's not that I want.
It's not that I personally want to be the guy putting bricks through windows,
but I do want them to happen.
I don't know.
I don't want to, I don't want to be the guy doing it.
I don't want to put myself in any risk.
I would never, I would never, you know, only in a video game.
I never heard a window.
I would never heard a window.
On the, on the other hand, like, oh, and there was the, there was the mate.
There was also the Mayday march that I think we did like a year ago,
like almost exactly a year ago.
And that was like, that was not that big, but it was angry.
And we didn't really do anything, but it was definitely done without permission.
And we definitely were all like going through the streets and blocking the streets.
This, this time there was sort of like a route that was like planned.
That time we were just out there blocking traffic, just walking in the road.
And that was pretty funny.
This was a little more organized.
It was fine.
What's the point?
What's the point of all this?
Oh, you know who, you know who are heroes though?
Are the ones that are, that are out, the ones that are outside, you know,
city center in front of the town, you know, city library, like whatever.
The ones who are heroes are the ones that are outside fucking Justice Kavanaugh's house,
just like yelling at him all the time.
That's, that's what you should be doing.
The ones that Clarence Thomas is like, you shouldn't bully us.
You shouldn't bully us just because you don't agree with our decision.
You should bully them.
Those people should be throwing bricks and molotovs and stuff.
Those houses should all be burned down.
And I, and I appreciate those people who are there providing cover for me to go
and be the one to do that, I hope.
Um, those are the ones doing the real shit in a video game.
Mmm, based.
Yeah. Um, so solidarity with those dudes, I guess.
Uh, that was, that was for the most noteworthy thing that I did this week.
Yeah.
No, it wasn't yawning at you.
I was just, oh no.
I made a social faux pas.
Okay.
Yawning in your face at whatever you were talking about.
Yeah, whatever.
Civil rights or something.
I live in the UK.
This, this doesn't have anything.
They'll never, they'll never get me.
They'll never give me civil rights.
The Supreme Court will never, yeah, yeah, will never curse me with civil rights.
If I never have them, then they can't be taken.
Exactly.
Uh, what, I saw a bunch of, uh, fucking, uh, Immortan Joe, uh, you know,
do not become addicted to water.
Do not become addicted to civil rights.
You will resent their absence or whatever.
Uh, good stuff, good stuff.
Really trying to think.
I guess I've walked some.
I've walked around because it's nice in spring.
It's nice.
It's warmish.
It is warmish.
The birds are tweeting.
Wow.
Isn't it beautiful?
You said it.
You, you said.
Time passes and another season is here.
What an interesting topic of conversation.
What a, what a concept.
Yes.
Tell me, tell me more.
I said I was going to, I said I was going to start playing Pokemon Go.
When, uh, frickin, I got a new phone.
And then I, and then I didn't, I haven't, I haven't played it yet.
Kind of meant to.
Oh no.
There's nothing to say.
I didn't do anything new this week.
All right.
I was, I was, uh, just doing the same old stuff.
Yeah.
But mostly nothing.
Sure.
Yeah.
It's, it sucks.
Well, it doesn't suck.
I was having fun, but like, nothing to talk about really.
Mm hmm.
I, um, I reached out to that one artist that draws the big boobs.
Oh, I did see you.
I, you made that tweet.
Yeah.
And I got no, I got no response.
I didn't even say what it was.
I just said, could I make a business inquiry?
Which I didn't, didn't get any response from that at all.
Do they not have an email for that?
Uh, I didn't see one.
I didn't see one anywhere.
Uh, maybe if I looked harder, I could find some other contact info.
I mean, I think all they had on their TAPS was just, uh, their Twitter linked, I think.
And then on Twitter, they just had their TAPS linked.
So I was like, well, I guess they got to contact them here, I guess.
Cause they have not actually posted on TAPS in a while, like a year or more.
Um...
Oh, I voted in a thing.
It was a local council election.
Oh, very nice, very nice.
There was a big, um, across the whole UK, the conservatives lost many, many seats.
Really?
So that's good.
The labor, labor isn't really like, it's like a hollow shell of a party.
They only seem to exist to be like, we're not as bad as the conservatives.
So like, there's not that much like interest going on.
Like not enough passion, nobody cares.
Yeah.
Um, but they did win a few seats.
And then the Green Party won a lot of seats.
They like doubled theirs, which is nice.
I voted for Green.
Double, what's double zero?
Double six days, like 120 now.
I think, I think in America, there's like one congress member who has like, who's like a third party at this point.
Yeah, it wasn't like, and members of parliament, it was like council members.
So like, across the whole bunch of councils.
So like, more numbers means more possible peoples.
We had, um, couple, couple months ago, we had, um, yeah, it was like city council or,
and I think city legislature and also I think mayor, I think it was mayor of Boston, not, not governor of Massachusetts.
We, we elected Michelle Wu, who seems fine.
Um, uh, yeah, I think, I don't think there were any third party candidates on the ballot.
I think everyone was a Democrat or Republican, which is whatever.
That's just how it is.
Um, the, uh, the, um, that was, uh, was that like February?
I don't know.
Man, I was looking at, uh, oh, this, this, like this week or very recently, they rescinded all the COVID, like, restrictions and stuff.
Like, uh, you know, masks on, uh, masks on public transit are no longer mandatory and stuff, which I don't like.
Uh, most people that I see on buses are still wearing masks, but it's only like, maybe 70% of people are.
Which is like, okay, great.
Uh, yeah, the masks have been like non compulsory for a while now in London.
I don't really see anybody wearing them.
They were only, they were only compulsory, like on, like on the tee.
Sure.
I mean, that's what I mean.
Like on buses and trains, like they haven't been compulsory for a while.
They had like, uh, signs up saying, uh, we recommend it, but then those were also gone.
So I don't know what's happening now.
I guess everyone, everyone's acting like, yeah, COVID's over.
Yeah, we, we, we just switched, we just switched from compulsory to, uh, recommended.
And, uh, yeah, COVID numbers are kind of going up now, so that's good.
Uh, what is it?
What is it?
It was, um, wait, I was looking at it a second ago.
Damn it.
I just had it up also.
Why do I hear someone talking in my fucking kitchen?
I hate them.
Um, numbers are, numbers are, numbers are, they're, they're climbing.
They're about now where they were in like, in Massachusetts.
They're now about where they were in like April of 2020.
They look like they are rising to like January 2021 levels.
Hopefully they're, they're, hopefully they're not going to go fucking January 2022 levels.
I guess in, I guess in March and April of last year, we did have sort of a little second
spike, uh, around this time after the big spike in like January.
So maybe we're having that.
I hope it's not proportional.
I don't want to get, I don't want to get COVID again.
Heesh.
Is it even possible to get it?
I guess it is possible to get it sometime.
What do you mean?
Duh, duh, dude.
Because like this like vaccine, like I remember hearing like when COVID was new, people could
get it more than once, but I don't know like post vaccine, whether that's likely anymore.
It's, it's, I mean, it's less likely, but I mean, you can still do it.
I, I think they're rolling out the third booster soon.
I think, no, my, my parents already got the third booster.
I don't know if it's like available for me yet.
I don't know.
There was a third one.
Yeah, there is.
Uh, I haven't really heard anything about it.
Uh, man, can't believe I didn't win Vax millions.
Oh, three COVID-19 vaccines are authorized or approved for use in the United States.
Okay.
There are authors for use, but are they authorized for everyone?
Can I get my third?
Who is in my kitchen?
Who is in my fucking kitchen?
It's COVID.
They're in your kitchen.
It's my fucking property manager or something.
Um, there's a booster free, second booster, the fucking mass.gov info details.
Give the details for the first and second boost.
They don't mention the third one.
That's frustrating.
Okay.
I'll have to look into this later.
Whatever.
I should get one point.
I won't want to get it.
Uh, it's, oh, it's Mother's Day today.
Not for me.
That was a few months ago.
Yeah.
For me, it is, uh, I guess, I don't know.
I was thinking yesterday I called home.
I was going to ask, like, should I come like eat dinner or something?
Cause like I can make the trip.
I'm really tired today and I kind of hope maybe they're doing something.
Maybe they're busy and they don't want me to come.
I kind of don't want to.
And I just want to sleep all day.
Um, but, uh, I don't know.
I'll call later and I guess we'll, we'll see what they tell me to do.
I'll just do whatever they fucking tell me to do.
Just like being a kid.
It's what Mother's Day is all about.
That is a lot.
That's exactly right.
Oh my God.
I hear you.
I hear it.
It's the same guy, same guy who yesterday, I think.
The last week you could maybe hear him yelling from the balcony upstairs.
I think he's the guy who's doing some shit in my kitchen right now.
Oh, it makes me so uncomfortable.
Oh, I don't want some fucking townie hearing me podcast.
It's so embarrassing.
That would be the worst.
Not just that they, like, maybe they, maybe you could just say, oh, I'm on a zoom meeting.
Go away.
At least they know what that means.
Zoomers know what zoom is.
God bless them.
I've been, I've been continuing, I've been continuing to refine my gummy experiments.
I had a, yeah, I had a pretty successful batch.
The, the, okay, so far.
I think I would say my most successful recipe here.
Let me, let me tell you what it is so far.
This is two, two tablespoons of water.
To that add three sheets of gelatin.
Melt that in the pan.
Add to that a pack of a cup full of a mixture of two tablespoons corn fiber,
one half of a pack of sure gel pectin mixture,
one eighth of a teaspoon of malic acid,
and two dashes of stevia.
Add, add to that like a small dash of flavoring and some food coloring if you like.
Boil it in the pan for a few minutes and then transfer it to gummy molds and then refrigerate.
That was what I did.
That was, that's the one, that's the one that had the best results thus far.
But I, and then I, then I tried it with, I tried it with half the water and it didn't work at all.
I feel like if I could reduce the water a little bit, it would be better,
but you can't reduce it too much or else it just, it just doesn't work.
I could, I think if I, if I reduce the fiber, that would help, but like the fiber really makes it,
the fiber really like keeps, keeps it like unsolid, which is, which is good and bad.
If it's like, I kind of, I don't like it to be too solid, but if obviously it doesn't hold together if it's not solid enough.
The one, the one with the half, the one with the half water, it was like, it just didn't, it didn't come together with solid.
It was, it remained a paste, but it was like, it was a delicious paste.
It was like a delicious chewy paste with like a great texture to it.
So I'm going to try and do it with like, okay, instead of half the water, I'll do three quarters water.
Like, like a spreadable, like on toast, you could have that.
Yeah, I put it, well, it might just be that I put in, I put my favorite flavor in the half water mixture,
which is passion fruit, by the way.
The passion fruit flavor additive that I have is by far the best one.
Watermelon is pretty good.
Guava is good, but passion fruit, just forget about it.
Rose is also pretty good.
So I've made like, in the last two weeks, I've made like one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
I've done, I've done like 14 different recipes.
That was the one.
I've tried it with corn syrup.
Actually, I tried, a previous recipe I tried included corn syrup and actually that was probably like the second most successful one.
Then I tried duplicating that recipe, but I replaced the corn syrup with white sugar, because there's a type of candy called patefui,
which is just sugar and pectin, basically.
So I was like, okay, what if I tried to do like a half and half between gummy candy and patefui.
And for that, I would basically be like use, it would basically be patefui with gelatin, because patefui doesn't have any gelatin,
but like gummies do, so just add some gelatin.
So I replaced the corn fiber with white sugar, like you would for that.
And I thought, you know, white sugar, oh my God, someone's vacuumed my kitchen.
Oh my God.
Oh, I can hear that.
Jesus.
All right, it's fine.
I'll just, I'll just continue.
So anyway, as I was saying, fucking, what was I saying?
You're combining with the white sugar.
Gelatin, gelatin, the white sugar.
I thought, okay, obviously if I replace the corn fiber, or if I replace the corn syrup with white sugar,
that's replacing a liquid sugar with a solid one.
So like you would think that obviously then the result would be a drier and more solid final product.
But no, it wasn't.
Let me consult my notes here.
Was it the opposite? Was it more liquidy?
It was not, it was, it was, it was not liquid.
It was more, it was more of a gel.
Yeah, it ended up as more of a gel and less of a like solid.
Yeah.
I, you know, you know what?
I wonder if maybe it was because for the same reason that reducing the water made it less of a paste as it didn't hold together as well.
Maybe it's because the corn syrup contained water and that extra water gave it more bind.
And, and replacing it with white sugar meant less water, meant less bind for the gelatin.
I don't know, that's just a theory.
Maybe.
I really thought, man, I really thought, I really thought the corn syrup was going to like give me like a really great consistency,
but it has not really added much.
And, you know, and the white sugar also didn't, I really thought that go using the white sugar and boiling it longer would give more of like a chewy gummy pot if we texture.
But it really hasn't.
And so I'm kind of thinking maybe I should just stop even trying with corn syrup and sugar because my goal here is to have,
if I can have these be lower calorie, lower carb, I would like that.
And if sugar and corn syrup are not even improving the consistency, why am I even bothering with them if I could just leave them out entirely?
It's better.
So I think I'm just going to like not even fuck with them until I get what I, what I consider to be a perfect recipe without them,
which so far, the one I just, the one I described a moment ago, is that I'm going to, I'm going to tweak it a little more.
And then maybe I can take that as a base and start like, you know, add, maybe I can experiment with sugar and corn syrup and see if I can move on from there.
Who comes into my fucking, who comes into my fucking house and vacuums in my kitchen when I'm podcasting?
You should know that I'm podcasting.
Doesn't he listen to the procrastinators podcast?
Doesn't he know that we record at 10 a.m. on Sunday?
Maybe they can't hear because of all the vacuuming they're doing.
They always, they always listen while they're vacuuming at 10 a.m. on Sunday.
What is it with people doing loud things on the weekends?
That's a consistent thing across all society and I don't get it.
Always with the loud gardening, the loud something, the loud cleaning.
Just live in filth.
Nice, quiet filth.
I wish, I wish.
Oh my God.
I'm so mad.
I should probably just get over it.
I feel, I feel, I feel violated.
Yeah, I can imagine.
This has never happened before.
Well, you feel like the sanctity of the procrastinators podcast recording session is being violated.
Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely I do.
This is like church on Sunday morning.
Some people go to church.
I go to discord to record a podcast.
Oh, is our leave all this in?
No, don't leave it in.
Cut out, I mean, cut out, I guess, most of it, some of it, much of it.
Cut out the whole episode.
Yeah.
I'm mostly just perplexed who is coming into my kitchen and vacuuming.
Would it be the landlady?
It's not the landlady.
And it's actually, it's not the property manager, but it might be one of his goons because he has a couple of goons.
Maybe they're trying to get all the bugs.
Well, I hope somebody's got that.
Well, I guess if there is a thing to talk about, I've been dealing with too many projects syndrome.
I've been dealing with having so many potential things I could be doing at any given time that I just don't know what to do, what to spend time on.
There's like, there's like, I mean, you know how it is, you got your things that are to be finished, and then you have new ideas and you want to try those.
No, I don't have new ideas, no.
Wow, what does the new idea I have?
That would be something.
I think I was having ideas for like video things.
Like, you know, those, those video game challenge runs people do is like, can you do X video game?
You know, I've been, I've been seeing a lot of those. Yeah.
They're, they're just sort of really fun, except when they're about like Elden Ring, it's like, can you beat Elden Ring without using a sword?
Yeah, of course you can.
It's like, you can do anything in Elden Ring.
Obviously, sometimes it's like, sometimes the answer is just obviously yes.
Yeah.
And then there's more interesting ones like, you know, can you beat Rayman without using your hover ability?
I saw, I watched that one.
Yeah, this is a pretty good one.
I think I watched every, every challenge run on that guy's channel.
And I feel like I want to do one. I want to do a challenge run. I play video games.
It does, it does seem fun. I don't know.
I think I've even talked about this before.
Like, I just really want to do a challenge run.
But like, wow, what? Huh?
Yeah.
And then I get distracted by all the things that I said I was going to do.
And I was like, I gotta go.
I best do this thing.
Oh, I best do that thing.
And then new idea just fades into the background until I think about it again.
And I'm like, oh, you know, I should do that.
Just a constant cycle of like, oh yeah, maybe I should do this.
Well, I, well, I made myself a little, a little to do list that I've been checking steps off of.
They are all, they are all related to, they are all related to getting the book finished.
I didn't, I didn't do it.
The last two days I should have been working on that stuff.
And I haven't really gotten anything done the last two days,
but I have checked a bunch of things off the list.
For instance, I printed off from my print, my printer.
I printed off physical, like shitty draft, black and white drafts of the pages.
And I put them in a three-ring binder.
I bought a three-ring binder so that I could print pages to put them in
so that I could move them around and arrange them to my satisfaction
to get like a page order and like, you know, where should I insert an extra blank page
because like maybe I want like this page or that page to be on the left or the right side,
you know, when you're actually holding the book in your hands.
I've been doing that.
I've been, I was supposed to write more footnotes,
but I only wrote like one more page of them yesterday, which is disappointing.
I've only got six pages of them, and I'm only on like page 40.
I'm on like page 42 of like 200 or something.
So that's going, so I have to get all that done
before I place orders with like companies that get sample copies made.
So I have not been getting distracted with new ideas.
I just, just the old fucking shit is there's a lot.
There's just a lot of steps involved and it's taken a long time, but it's good.
I think the reason I'm in this state right now is because the major thing,
the things that it was like eating up my time was getting the punk and alley demo out
and sending the Lord of Ghost books, which are now complete on my part.
I've sent them out to everybody who I could get their address from.
And there's a few like returns that I have to like resend because of some bullshit.
Costumes.
I got like a return envelope of the thing and they've really fucked it up.
And it was like, it was like they made an entire other envelope with sellotape,
sellotaping it back up.
Like the original envelope I used just to haunt to shreds.
I was like, God, I wonder how many other ones of those are like in terrible condition when they arrive.
So that's not good, but hopefully people will have those.
And the pumpkin alley demo is like, okay, gaming stuff that's going to be worked on.
It's going to take a while.
Yeah.
And so I'm like, okay, I could spend time on many different other projects,
mostly probably clerse a gun smoke and some other things.
I'm like, I died.
You know, this is good actually.
Actually one of the major, well not one, I mean, one factor that has kind of pushed me to like stay on track
for the whole book thing is that I know that you were planning to kickstart the pumpkin alley.
And I really want to get my book kickstarted before you do that.
So I've been trying to like, I don't know if it's possible,
but I've been kind of hoping that I can get like the book like ready to like ready to print maybe like this month.
I don't know if that's doable, but that's kind of what I'm shooting for.
And maybe like, and maybe launch the Kickstarter like next month.
You know, that's my optimistic hope.
I think a lot of what I'm like struggling with is the fact that I'm flying in like a week.
I'm going to go, I'm going to be in Boston.
Two weeks.
In two weeks.
Well, like in a week, it'll be like three days until I fly or something.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Yeah.
It's really fucking coming up, huh?
So I've got, I'm like, all right, I got to set some things in order to do some stuff,
but not like do too much that is like.
Yeah.
You know how like, I don't want to leave a lot of things hanging when I leave.
I understand.
So I don't want to do nothing for a week either.
So I'm like, I got to choose something.
I got to pick something.
Yeah.
But you don't want to start anything.
You don't want to, you don't want to start anything that you'll leave unfinished for.
You're here for like a week or no.
About a week.
Yeah.
A little over a week.
Shit.
That just makes me, I get a, man, I like actually that guy, that guy, that thing, that thing
that I told you about, I guess what, what some have referred to as my new secret project,
which I hate to call that because it's not going to be a long thing that is a secret
for a long time, like the previous one.
I left that guy hanging for like a, almost a week.
And then I finally got back to him two days ago.
And then he finally got back to me yesterday, but I didn't get back to him.
So I got to get back to him.
I think maybe right after, like maybe right after this, because I actually got to get in
touch with that guy like soon.
And then I got to go see that guy.
Because then, you know, what with you coming to visit the timetable on that is a window,
the walls are closing in.
It should be okay.
I was thinking about that yesterday.
Actually yesterday I was feeling, and this is really stupid.
Yesterday I was feeling like, Oh God, I could record the podcast tomorrow.
Oh, I can't do anything today.
So I just played Noida.
And so I just played Noida and it's, and I hate it.
I hate Noida.
It sucks.
It's a nightmare.
Waste of time.
Wait, you said I have to do the podcast tomorrow.
I can't do anything today, like yesterday.
I mean, it not, I didn't say it like that, but that's kind of how I felt.
Yeah.
Like, like in order to be prepared for a podcast the following morning, I can't even lift a finger.
Well, it wasn't, it wasn't just that the, it was partially that, oh, I got to do the podcast in the morning.
And then it's Mother's Day.
And what if my parents, what if, what if they tell me to come visit in the afternoon and then that's my whole day gone, you know.
So I got to get my noise in right now and see you.
It's like, it's like, I look at, I look at my watch and I'm like, damn, it, I woke up.
It's noon today.
The podcast is at 10am tomorrow.
That's less than 24 hours.
Like, I can't do any, I can't, I can't do any work today.
I can't do any writing.
Fucked.
You know, sometimes I'm, you know, this is a trap that I fall into and I fell into it yesterday and I didn't, I didn't get nothing.
I did, I wrote like a page yesterday, which is not as much as I would look like, but oh well.
Anyway, yeah.
But I was thinking about that thing, the thing that we got to do, the thing I got to do soon that I've been talking to that guy about.
And I was like, you know, there's, I just got to not like worry about being too prepared for it because you know, you, you know how it goes.
And you kind of just got to fly by the cedar pants.
You kind of just got to, you kind of just got to fly and not worry about it.
And when you show up and do it and when, when you do it, it's just kind of, it's going to shake out how it shakes out.
You know what I'm saying?
I do.
Audience, sorry to be vague, but you'll, you'll see.
You'll see in hopefully not even that long because I think, I think, I think the, I think the, the, the unless something catastrophic happens and the whole thing fails for some reason.
If the whole thing fails, shall we just say what it was?
I mean, yeah, if it fails, I'll say, I'll tell people what it was going to be and why it failed.
But I don't think it'll fail and I don't see any reason why it would.
And if it doesn't fail, I feel like probably by next month, probably sometime next month, people would know what it was.
And then I can be like, okay, but I don't want to say, I don't want to say what it is just yet.
Because if I say what it is, then I'll, I don't know.
Nothing, nothing bad will happen.
It's a hardcore pornography.
Literally, literally nothing bad will happen if I, if I, if I say what it is, but I don't want to anyway.
I don't know.
I don't know why I do the things that I do.
You just love being a secret project, Haver.
Yeah, but I told, I told people you, you kept Pumpkin Alley a secret.
I didn't, I did not keep Phantom's Revenge, I kept Phantom's Revenge a secret until it was like halfway done.
And then I told everyone, I guess it was released the demo.
So I mean, I guess I know why I did that, but like, in hindsight, I kind of wish that I had not told anyone about it.
No, I couldn't because I had released it on Patreon.
You know what I should have done is I should have not told anyone about it except for people on Patreon.
I think that probably would have gotten me more patrons.
But oh well, what can you do?
Yeah, I mean, I don't know which was the best way to do it.
I feel like there's, there's pros and cons.
Like if I had been talking about Pumpkin Alley the whole time, maybe more people would have learned about it and been anticipating it.
Maybe.
Or maybe there would have been less of a buzz when you dropped it.
Yeah, potentially, perhaps only.
Yeah, I don't know.
Somebody bought Phantom's Revenge for $5 a couple days ago for the first time in a while. That was nice.
Yeah.
What was I talking about? What?
Okay, well, whatever.
I was talking about like too many projects.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Well, I guess the only other thing is I want to, first of all, I want to come back, do more Elden the Ring streams because those were fun when they were being watched and people were having fun with them.
So I'm going to make a more regular schedule that people can like follow properly.
I also kind of want to do Clarissa Gunsmoke draw streams like I did before.
Those did seem to work out pretty well.
Yeah, it's like I make things on stream and people get to Pog in real time.
That's, that's, that's what you like to see.
So I could do that.
I don't know whether I will, but at the moment I'm just sort of thinking I got to go on a plane and I'm scaled.
Not for like the plane reason, but because it's the first time I'm going to America since COVID and there's new restrictions where I have to prove that I have a negative COVID test within one day before the flight.
Which means I need to do some sort of weird phone thing where I get on a phone call, like a video call with someone and do a COVID test at my house, or I do some other test at a facility and I get a, I don't get it.
I just don't understand.
I read all of these things on like the US customs board of patrol stuff.
I've never, I've never even heard of such a thing.
I've never even heard of such a thing.
What the fuck?
And, and, and like I just don't understand what they mean.
Like proof of a negative test.
Like if I just to the thing.
Like you have to, like you have to do a zoom, like you have to do a zoom call and show yourself taking the tests.
I, yeah, I mean, I don't know what they mean by proof because there was something like that.
And then I assume the only other way to do it is to go to like a hospital and get a test done at a hospital by a doctor, which can then verify it.
Those usually take like more than a day to get the results of.
Yeah.
So like a fucking, like if I could take a self test, a home test, or just do the swab in my nose and back my throat, put in a little thing and it comes up negative.
Do I, can I take a picture of that?
Or is that not enough proof?
I have no idea.
And I'm, I'm confused about the process.
And I think I'm just going to worry about that all week because.
Good idea.
I got to do that.
That's the only thing.
Pack in my suitcase, whatever.
Once I'm in the air, I love being in the air.
It's the most satisfying, calming thing in the world because no longer can somebody say, you're not flying to America because I am.
We're going to land in America and there's nothing you can do about it.
Absolutely true.
Can't get me anymore.
I'm free.
Free as a bird.
But until then, it's the, it's the scariest, most stressful thing ever.
So that's, that's going to be my next week.
I'm going to be like, oh, what?
COVID.
What day?
What day are you flying?
The bleep that at least our bleep that just in case somebody decides to come to the airport and hunt you down.
Yeah.
Oh God.
Okay.
You know what I think?
I think these guys, and I think there are two of them.
I think what they're doing is I think they're fucking around with like the ceiling tiles or something.
I think they're fucking around with like the ceiling tiles and maybe the vacuum is there to suck up like debris that might have like fallen down from the ceiling as they were fucking around with the tiles.
I think that's what's going on out there.
I don't think someone is just vacuuming.
I think there's a,
They're like hiding drugs in the ceiling.
Well, I mean, I, I mean, I don't know.
Little, little step back.
I guess it, I guess, I guess it could be that.
No, I think there was like water damage.
I'm going to see the tiles.
Hiding the body up there.
I'm not, I'm not sure.
I mean, there's water damage in one of my ceiling tiles in my room, but like whatever.
I don't care about that.
Oh, no, I hear, yeah, I hear the guy.
I hear my property manager and his, and one of his goons, one of his more affable goons who I sometimes hear him yelling to out in the parking lot behind my house.
Boston is crazy.
It's a, it's a crazy old mix up world of ours.
You know.
Goons in my house?
No, thanks.
There is at least, there is at least one goon.
Did you know that if you take Boston and you add slime, you get New Los Angeles City?
That's canon.
And you put it on the grand, and you put it on the grand canyon.
Put it on the grand canyon.
How'd it get there?
How did Boston get to the grand canyon, Ben?
Did they fucking drive it down the road like that at one Simpsons episode?
Well, they filled the entire underneath of the ground with trash.
New canon.
New RFCK canon is that Boston exists in RFCK world.
It exists in Massachusetts.
And they just, when they were making New Los Angeles City, they just copied Boston exactly so they didn't have to do any city planning.
They just, they just copied it.
Oh, speaking, speaking of RFCK, I did look, I saw the Alleyoop comic.
I saw Alleyoop, which he's been up to as an independent character in the city.
Wait, there's a comic?
There's a contest villains contest entry.
It's like a seven, eight page comic of Alleyoop and some Lord of Ghost Lore.
Oh, cool.
I haven't looked at the villains contest entries yet.
It's so cool.
Wow.
I'm so proud of her.
Well, that's exciting.
I'm proud of when she's been up to.
Yeah, good for her.
That's cool.
I'm thinking of, of like turning whatever happens in that into like canon somehow for like Belle Jape 2 or whatever.
Oh, wow.
Who, who's, who's doing that?
I have no idea.
It's just a new account called Alleyoop.
They seem to be an old school PCP head.
Because the comic involves like resurrecting of like some classic villains like the Undertale 587.
Wow.
And stuff like that.
It's DeVoo.
I don't know.
No, it's not the same art style as DeVoo.
Why would the hell would it be DeVoo?
I don't know.
Just someone.
DeVoo always hated RFCK.
Did she?
Well, I don't know if she hated it.
I think it was just like being on that show.
Like the first episode, it was you, Munchie and DeVoo.
That is true.
Yeah.
Funnily enough, that is true.
And she was just like, I don't know about this type of show.
Okay.
First, yeah, that's even weirder.
Because at that point, RFCK didn't even really have much of an identity other than the fact that it just was me and Munchie.
So what would...
I kind of remember, now that you mentioned it, I do kind of remember that was true.
Like what was the problem?
Like what did you want?
More intellectual discussion, less funny gamer jokes, I guess.
I hate her.
Fuck you DeVoo if you're listening and I hope you're not dying.
I hate everyone.
I hate everyone who I used to know and don't know anymore.
I hate them.
Now you're just somebody that I used to know.
Oh yeah.
It's a good song.
Goatee.
What else to say?
What else is on my stupid list?
Do you have anything else to say about whatever you were talking about for the last hour or two?
I don't know.
No.
Okay.
Last thing on my list.
Last thing on my list is I don't know if I just need a haircut.
I might just need a haircut.
But I keep thinking about whether I should shave my head.
It might just be that my hair looks bad because I haven't had a cut in a while
and a haircut will make me be like, okay, it's fine.
Both cut?
Been seen?
I keep looking at my hair and thinking like maybe am I bald enough that I need to shave my head yet?
I don't know.
It troubles me.
It troubles me a lot because I look at myself in the mirror and I think I look fine
and then I see myself in like a photograph or like a recording, like a video someone took
and I'm like, I'm genuinely horrified.
I'm not exaggerating.
The feeling is one of horror and I don't know what to do about it.
What's the horror from?
I don't know.
I don't look right.
I don't look the way that I look in the mirror.
Well, that's always how it is.
I flipped.
You flipped your canvas.
I don't know.
I can't even really explain what it is that's different.
Just something about the geometry.
It doesn't match up.
I was lifting.
I had Munchy asked if I wanted him to record me doing bent over rows to check my form.
I said, sure.
I looked at the footage and I was like, oh no.
What's going on with my hair?
Is that what my head looks like?
I look at my head every day.
I look at my face and I know what I look like, but then I see that and I'm like, no, I don't.
No, I clearly have no clue.
I have no clue what's going on.
Is it like in the mirror, like the clown makeup is invisible or something?
You got like a big afro bouncing around.
All I'm saying is I don't know what to think because like,
seeing myself in the mirror, I think my hair looks all right.
I saw myself in the video and I'm like, this guy needs to shave his head right now.
And I don't know which of those is true.
You should do half and half.
You should have one side shaved and then your hair goes down long on the other side.
I thought in the last time I was really on video was the two Radcon 4 lectures and like,
I think my hair looked okay in those.
Did you have the pink?
Yeah, I did have the pink and it looked fine.
A little messy, but like whatever.
I don't think I looked that different, but so I guess I'm a little grayer now.
LeMau.
That's all right.
You know, I always, I always thought, I always thought it would be cool if when I started going gray,
if I would do it like, go gray at like the temples, you know,
swept back like Dr. Orpheus from Venture Bros.
Go gray at the temples.
Looks good.
Well, here I am, years 2020.
It's happening.
And you know what?
I actually don't like it.
I changed my mind.
It's not cool like I thought it was.
You just go to shave everything except the gray hair.
So it looks like they look good.
Yeah.
You should just embrace it and just do a samurai like shave the top of your head thing.
Like why not?
Then no one can criticize you.
Work around with a big old, what do you call it?
Not a kimono, like a robe thing.
It's, it's, it's genuinely, it's genuinely just a feeling of like, I don't know what I look like.
And therefore I don't know how to, how to deal with it.
I don't know how to, I don't know what I need to do to myself to look better because I don't understand
the truth of the situation that I am in with regards to it.
I mean, sometimes, sometimes I look at myself and I'm like, oh, I don't look good.
Oh, and then I'm like outside and I'm like, I probably don't look good.
And again, but I can't check.
I guess I could take a picture if I don't want to.
I'll just, if somebody says I'm like a freak of nature, then then I'll know that it's a problem.
You're a freak of nature.
Until then, until then, I'll just be whatever I am.
And if they have a problem with it, I'll cry.
Yeah.
Nobody says anything.
Nobody has any thoughts until they're like behind those doors.
And then they say, did you notice the Gibb was like a freak of nature today?
Like what the fuck was wrong with her?
I do hear that sometimes.
Yeah.
Dang it.
I just assumed it was fake, but no.
Oh, it's true.
Only behind closed doors, as you say, yes.
Shit.
Comments.
It is just as you say that.
Do you comment nice things and then secretly?
I have not seen.
Like in your head, you comment, what the fuck do you do that?
I mean, I have not seen what you look like in any capacity since Radcon 4.
So that'll be funny.
I sure hope I don't look embarrassing.
I guess you haven't seen me since Radcon 4 either.
I may have seen like one or two photos.
I don't think I look that different.
I gained a bunch of weight and then I lost most of it.
So I might weigh a little bit more now than I did then, but not by that much.
I gained a bunch of weight and I lost all of it in my arms and legs and it stayed in my stomach.
Really?
No, I'm just making a joke.
Oh, I think I was like, I was like, I was like 160 pounds at Radcon 4.
I'm probably like 170 something right now.
So whatever.
Paying care is gone.
I have more gray.
Other than that, I look pretty much the same.
I think.
I don't know.
Maybe not.
Maybe my, maybe my hairline receded more than I know, than I even can tell when I look in the mirror.
And I just, but it was so gradual that I didn't even notice.
I don't know.
Well, when I see you in person, I will scream if I find you upsetting to look at.
Yeah.
And then you will know for sure the truth.
I would hope.
I would hope so.
I just, um, I don't know.
I just wish I, I just kind of just wish I knew like, yes, it is time, it is time to shave your head.
It is time to just go bald.
Although I don't want that because I did shave my head one time in college and I don't think it looked good.
I don't think I really have the head shape for it, but probably I could get used to it if I had to do it.
So if I could just rip the Band-Aid off and just be like, okay, definitively, that's what I got to do.
When I, uh, when I, when I have it like, my hair is kind of longish right now.
And I kind of think it looks all right when I just sort of like brush it to the side, like kind of brush it back.
Like it looks fine.
But then like, I don't know, I saw myself in the video and I like, it's like completely like scraggly.
It was just kind of like one little strand of it kind of like falling down in front of my head.
Well, hey, weren't you lifting in that video?
Surely you'd be a little scraggly.
I was sweaty and scra- yes, that's true.
Working out.
Yes, that's true.
I don't know if it accounts for it completely.
I don't know if, I don't know if it fully explains the anomaly, the anomalies I saw.
You gotta do, you gotta do a vlog, you gotta do a vlog and you gotta look and figure it out.
I don't analyze your own footage.
I don't want to.
Okay, on the other hand, I could take pictures and videos of myself from all kinds of scientific angles.
That would be extremely unflattering, but I feel like that would be exaggerating in the wrong way.
I could convince myself that the situation is arbitrarily bad if I wanted to.
I don't want to do that either.
I don't want to know what the average person sees when they look at me.
And then I can be like, okay, well, how can I adjust that to achieve maximal results?
Munchy?
I don't know.
I don't think, I don't think, what's he gonna tell me?
He doesn't know.
I don't know.
He's not gonna know what I should do.
I honestly feel like I should, I feel like I need to ask a stylist.
I feel like I need to go to a stylist and be like, listen, just tell me.
A couple times I've gone to a hairdresser and I've asked them, hey, what should I do with my hair?
And I've never gotten really any good advice.
I've never had anyone be like, oh, you need to do this and then this is gonna look good on your head.
Yeah, that's not style.
Wow, that's just like hair care, I guess.
Yeah.
I get things like that as well.
I'm like, I'm not sure, like, they have products they want me to buy, I guess.
Like products they prefer, but they don't have like creative decision.
No, I want someone, I just want someone who knows about like style to tell me, like, look at what I look like and just tell me what I should do.
Because I don't fucking know.
I just want to know.
You should model yourself after Phantom Horn.
Okay, done.
You should have the bangs, you should have the poofs, and then like the sort of ponytail thing.
He doesn't have a ponytail, he just got, you know, I mean, a horse's mane just kind of goes down his back like that.
Yeah, go full mane with that.
Phantom's got more hair than I do, so, you know.
Will it into existence?
I don't know, so I don't know, I don't know if I can pull it off.
Phantom hair.
I don't know if I can pull off his look.
Phantom hair, yeah, more like.
Anyways, that's, I don't know, whatever, that's all I have to say.
I'm griping about what I look like.
Sucks.
How annoying.
Oh, that actually only didn't, that actually didn't take that long.
I just, I thought, I feel like I've been complaining about this for like half an hour.
I just looked at the time and it's been like five minutes, so actually it's okay.
Never mind.
I'm not sorry.
I have no idea how I'm supposed to look.
Like it's all I can do to like look sort of fine.
And the rest of the time I'm just like, I don't want to dwell on it.
I don't want to think about it too much.
Yeah, I mean, I also don't like to think about it that much.
And then when I'm confronted with it, I'm like, well, that's just perplexing.
You look in the mirror.
I'm perplexed.
I will say, I did see myself in a different, the mirror in my bathroom,
the mirror in my bathroom is kind of like face height.
So I see my face in it.
I stood in front, I changed in front of like a lower mirror that showed my like body the other day.
And I could tell that I had lost some of most of the weight that I had gained during the worst of COVID.
So that was pretty good.
But that doesn't tell me what I should be doing with my hair though.
Unrelated, unrelated good news.
Yeah.
In other news, another week has gone by that I have not learned how to update the RSS feed.
One of these, one of these days I will do it.
I feel kind of the people that people that listen on the podcast apps must be like,
they must have simply not heard an episode in like three months and I am sorry to those people.
I truly do not mean to put them out.
I want our podcasts available to them, but I just hate work.
Yeah.
I don't want to learn it either.
It's complicated.
It's technical.
Tom said he gave you instructions.
I don't know how useful they were.
Yeah, he did give me instructions.
I did not read them in detail.
I kind of said, okay, I'll figure these out later.
And then I have not, later has not come yet.
Whatever.
I'll do it.
I will do it.
I swear.
I'm supposed to be updating the RSS feed now.
I might, maybe this week I will in between grinding away shit for the book and grinding away at preparing for that thing that I got to do in like two and a half weeks.
I will be so, instead of wasting my time on Noita, the worst game in the world, I maybe will try and tell myself, okay, I instead I will procrastinate by learning to update the RSS feed.
That's because with the procrastinators, that's when you got to work on something, but instead you decided to do something else.
That's when I work on the podcast.
That's thematic.
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
That's right.
You understand.
Okay.
And it's well-known fact that everyone who leaves the podcast, they're productivity skyrockets.
Yeah.
Do we want to talk about that?
Talk about what?
Like everyone?
We could go through the list.
We could go through the list and check off, like, is that true?
I don't know.
I think it sort of speaks for itself.
I haven't heard much from most people.
Yeah.
I mean, I see Tom still doing a little work on Azumi and stuff.
Does he?
Yeah, on Twitter.
I haven't seen.
Mostly seen complaining about Elden Ring.
Elden Ring?
Yeah, okay.
You're right.
It speaks for itself.
The audience is invited to consider whether that statement is true or not.
Oh, and I suppose Mage does stream stuff.
She's a VTuber.
That's great.
That's lovely.
That's lovely for her.
I don't pay attention to it, but it is there.
It sure is.
VTubing seems like a big, I don't know.
VTubing seems like a stupid thing that stupid people do probably.
I don't know.
What's the point?
The point is, I don't have to show my face, but I can draw a little picture.
Here's a question.
Is VTubing a creative exercise?
Can you express yourself by VTubing?
If you're very talented with the model, the animation stuff,
switching expressions to match your voice can be difficult.
I could imagine that if the ring is complex.
There's some creativity in the acting part, I guess.
I don't watch too many of them.
I could imagine that if the ring is complex enough,
maybe there is almost an element of puppetry to it.
Or you are acting through it, I guess.
I think that the vast majority mostly use automated eye and mouth things.
Occasionally, we'll click a button to change their expression,
but that's the extent of it.
But there are some people who can do really elaborate things.
That's kind of...
I saw one that I thought was pretty cool.
It was like an eldritch monster.
It was like a tentacle monster with one big eye in the middle.
He would switch his expression from a big pink heart eye
to a big sparkly yellow eye or an angry red one.
It just looked pretty good.
It looked pretty good.
It was very easy to achieve.
Clearly, he's just using a toggle to switch which of a set expression he wants.
It works.
It's conveying the emotion that is meant to be conveyed there, I guess.
I don't know.
How many streamers?
It's the laziest possible thing.
I didn't really consider what I do v-tubing.
It's just a little PNG that opens their mouth.
Streaming...
I guess on the face of it, streaming is not that much of a...
I guess you could be creative with streaming.
I guess it's not really...
You definitely can be creative with streaming.
I guess anything you can do as a streamer, you can also do as a v-tuber.
Whatever.
The most creative thing for me when I streamed was just choice of game and making the thumbnails.
I enjoyed making custom thumbnails for every different game that I played.
I should do that more.
I was actually drawing an Elden Ring thing.
You know, I don't know if I ever mentioned this.
This was a long time ago.
But I actually put almost a week of work into this.
Maybe not a week, a few days of work into something before I gave up.
I was actually working for a bit there on modding Hollow Knight to...
Modding?
Well, I was just going to edit the sprite.
I was just going to edit the sprite to have my face on it.
The Bensane avatar face.
I started modifying the sprites and then...
That was fine, but then I realized that actually making the game run with a custom sprite sheet is a little more complicated than I assumed it would be.
It's not just a matter of insert one line of code or whatever.
So I was like, oh no, I'm not confident I can easily do this actually.
So I never did it.
But I had edited a bunch of the basic Hollow Knight is walking around sprites.
Although there's actually a lot of sprites for...
Wait, sorry, your character is not the Hollow Knight.
But you know what I mean.
The guy you play as.
Isn't his name...
Does he have a name or a title?
I think there is one.
I can't recall it at the moment.
I want to call him Hollow Knight.
I know Hollow Knight is actually the guy you fight before the sort of last boss.
You can take Hollow Knight's place.
You're a little hollow grub.
Hollow Knight's brother.
I was going to say he's called The Guardian, but no, that's in Petscop.
There's text that sort of suggests that your character's name is The Guardian in Petscop.
That's different game though actually.
Hmm, okay.
Well, talked about Shave My Head, talked about marching for abortions.
What do we want?
Abortions!
When do we want them?
Now!
Wait, I got to complain.
I got to complain because the people with the megaphones at this thing, you know, they were leading chance and whatever and that's cool.
But they did this multiple times and it made me really mad.
They did one chant that was like...
Okay, I remember it was...
I mean, okay.
I'll invite you to think about this.
Complete this for me, right?
Complete the line.
Okay.
The people united will never be...
What's the next word?
Fight it.
I don't know.
Close.
Yeah, okay.
You want a rhyme.
Divided.
The people united will never be divided.
They did that chant, but every time they did it, they said the people united will never be defeated.
The people united will never be defeated and every time I'm like, I can't believe it.
Like, why are you doing this?
You're there.
Like, you're there, but you just...
It's like you're flubbing it on purpose.
Like, you have to be doing this on purpose.
Divided.
Maybe to them it goes without saying that if the people united, they're not divided.
But like...
But it doesn't rhyme.
The people...
I don't know why I said fight it.
I really just...
Will never be fighting.
Okay, but you get the...
It's supposed to rhyme.
Yeah, yeah.
And there's an obvious answer.
And I just...
I just didn't get it.
The people completed will never be defeated.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's still better.
Still...
Still better.
Still better than we got.
Oh.
You know what?
I'll tell a little bit more about that.
One, when the march was like...
You know, a couple of people gave speeches and then we started a little march.
As we were marching away from the library, there was a guy.
He did not follow us.
He was just kind of standing there.
He was holding...
He was wearing a VR headset.
He was wearing like an oculus rift.
And he was holding up a sign for like anti-natalism, like no more babies.
And he was just standing...
And he was like spinning.
He was like standing on the steps and like spinning in place, chanting something.
I guess maybe he was high or something, but he was wearing an oculus rift on his eyes.
And I just wish I knew what he was seeing.
Maybe he's living in the virtual world where babies don't need to exist at all.
I guess he was...
I don't know if he was there to troll or what.
Or if he was just having a good time.
I don't know.
Also, there was some old drunk guy who was there to counter-protest.
I think this guy seemed like he was just going to be there regardless.
He might not have even known there was an event.
But he was there with a sign that was like, no.
People need to have the right not to have abortions.
People need the right not to have abortions.
Whatever happened to freedom of speech?
White lives matter.
I'm black and I'm proud.
He was chanting, yeah, that was it.
He started chanting, white lives matter.
And then he started chanting, I'm black and I'm proud.
And he was.
I think he was mixed race.
But anyway, I don't know.
He followed us.
Freedom.
We walked by him and he followed us like yelling at us because he started talking.
We were looking at the sign.
We were trying to decipher his sign because it didn't make any sense.
We eventually figured out it was an anti-abortion.
And we're like, okay.
And then he started talking to us and we said, no, no, we don't want to hear it.
And he followed us and he yelled at us.
And then eventually he left us alone.
And he was around.
He was just kind of around for the whole thing.
Just messing with people, just being a menace.
And you know what?
His freedom of speech was maintained the whole time.
Nobody silenced him.
God bless.
I want the freedom to have the government choose for me what I can do with my body.
I don't know.
He was kind of hard to understand.
But it seemed like he was saying that he had had a kid that he aborted when he was younger.
And if he had not done that, he would have a grand kid right now.
And it's like, people need the right to live.
People need the right not to have abortions.
We're like, okay.
Sorry.
Thanks.
That's just silly.
You can just choose not to have it.
Yeah, you could have just not done that.
I'm sorry.
You could have just not done that.
No more freedom.
My freedom led me to make a decision that I regret.
Well, bummer.
Man.
I don't know.
Put on a mask.
He wasn't wearing a mask.
I bet he wouldn't like it if people had the right not to get COVID.
I bet he wouldn't be a fan of that.
What a fucking jackass.
Anyway, that's what happened this week.
And that's the way the news goes.
That's right.
Is it voicemail time?
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Okay, we got a lot of YouTube links.
So we're going to skip all of them this week.
If your voicemail is a YouTube link, it will not be listened to.
We told you.
And you're doing this on purpose, obviously.
All right.
The first one is a Pastebin link.
Oh, motherfucker.
Is this just a text question?
Yeah.
Okay, fine.
If you had to rename the show for trademark reasons, for example, what would you call it?
First of all, what trademark reasons?
That is a funny thought that like, oh no, there was actually another procrastinator's podcast.
20 years ago.
I don't know.
I have no idea at all.
The crumbly slime podcast, like it just give it a name.
Yeah, honestly.
It didn't have like a theme to begin with.
Yeah, honestly, it would be any name would be fine.
Ben and Gibbs power hour.
The oatmeal.
The oatmeal eaters podcast.
The one one two oatmeal podcast.
I would call the podcast Kirby's nightmare and dreamland.
Episode one.
Every episode would be named after a Kirby enemy.
First one would be waddle D.
You turn it into like a pretend let's play like we call it let's play Kirby's nightmare and dream and part one.
We just do a podcast.
We don't talk about Kirby.
There's no Kirby footage.
Yeah.
This episode met a met a nightmare.
We'll just call it.
We'll call the podcast.
We'll call the podcast building building of a volcano in Minecraft.
The procrastinators podcast to.
Yeah, for branding purposes, if we had to change it.
Okay, I hope that answers your question.
The next question is called 140.58321 go.
Snakes.
Are you okay?
Oh, I think.
Oh, did.
Did oblivion fall upload that the that reaction video of him and four eyes to the pig thing?
Yes.
I didn't I didn't listen to it yet.
I should.
I think it's just on oblivion's channel.
Okay.
I'll I'll go check that out later.
Listeners should also you should go check that out.
It's supposedly it's a reaction.
It's him and four eyes reacting to me getting upset about big squeals.
Okay, next one is called Yeeg Studios isolation pilot plant.
Yep, for short.
Three, two, one, go.
This place is not a place of honor.
No highly esteemed is coming right here.
Nothing value is here.
What is here is dangerous and repulsive to us.
This message is a warning about danger.
The danger is still present in your time as it was in ours.
The danger is to the body and it can kill.
The form of the danger is by carbonate rain, financial irresponsibility, cringe, burning bridges for no good reason, and bad white person quote unquote rapping.
The danger is unleashed only if you substantially disturb this place physically.
This place is best shun and left uninhabited.
Everyone says everyone accuses me of burning bridges.
But everyone I burned bridges with did something.
I swear it's other people that burn bridges with me.
I'm not a bridge burner.
I value my bridges.
If a bridge gets burned, I didn't do it.
People burn their bridges.
It's not my fault.
Trixie Trixie burned that bridge.
And likewise for everybody else likewise for everybody else that you the viewer are sitting there thinking, ah, but what about this?
No, they did it.
They burned it.
Anyway, what were we talking about?
I don't know.
Okay.
Good, good voice.
Next one is a vocaru link.
Let's let's see about that.
Oh, nice.
Nice.
What?
That's right.
Nice.
I do.
Let's fuck Celestia.
Let's fucking do it.
I'm ready.
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
I don't remember saying this in the show.
This is just how I remember it.
Don't call it that.
Do not trust him.
Do not let him in.
He will read you.
Do not read him.
His voice is ash.
His air is dead.
You must not breathe it in.
You must not comprehend the vapor, his dreadful vapor.
Put Celestia back on, Twilight.
I want to hear more about the wide-milf ass.
Oh, that's over.
It was strangely like, it had like an underlying level of like robotic static in that voice,
but other than that, it was very clear.
It was.
It was, yeah.
It's Princess Melestia.
She's here.
Okay, I'm okay with it.
Next one is called the new wacky voicemail characters all suck ass.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Okay, look, Samurai Sama was funny, like obviously, but the funny part was never the fucking racist voice.
So if we could stop doing racist voices to be funny, that'd be cool.
Yeah, the other, I don't even remember what the other guy's name is, the other Chinese guy.
You know, besides the Samurai, the other Chinese guy besides the Samurai.
I don't remember what his name is.
I don't remember either.
He does not have a good gimmick.
His bit initially was just racism, and then I think the most recent one, he tried to do something extra with it.
I genuinely can't even remember his name.
I don't remember his name off the top of my head.
Okay, I mean, these are, I feel like the subject line and the voicemail had different themes, but sure, okay, yeah, true.
I guess I agree with both.
Next one is, okay, skipping that YouTube link, and then we got a vocaroo link.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
What happens to the old voicemails?
Did he just get deleted? Is there an internet archive?
I hope that's the end. I hope that's the end of the question.
Can you understand it?
Nope.
What?
I think it's backwards, right?
Yeah.
What's the point?
I guess I could download it and, like, reverse it.
Well, I mean, thanks for the incomprehensible voicemail, I guess. Thanks for a minute of noise.
We could download it and reverse it, but we'll leave that up to the viewing public to solve.
Do not trust him. Do not let him in. He will read you. Do not read him. His voice is ash. His hair is dead. You must not breathe at him. You must not comprehend.
The vapor. His dreaded vapor.
A scripture of empty prophecy spewed from the kingdom of sewers.
A waste of moths upon his breath held captive in her orbit.
The fog rolls off his skin to lay the nation light and slips into the grave. The great dead distance.
Okay, next is a YouTube link, and then...
Three or four YouTube links, and then...
Dusty dumps.
One of them says, I think Trixie is re-uploading vids at gmail.com. Yeah, probably.
Yeah, and then next one is Dusty Dumps presents the PCP voicemail album.
Okay. Three, two, one, go.
What's up, PCP nation? It is I, Dusty Dumps, aka Mutusandu, aka Chris.
That's my name. I'm just here to announce that I'm almost done compiling and remixing the tracks for the PCP voicemail album, which is a collection of all the musical voicemails that I've made over the year.
This is the 22 tracks, all in all, with five of those being bonus tracks, and two of them being album-exclusive tracks never heard before by anyone, except me of course, because I made them.
It'll be released on Bandcamp at a pay what you want sort of deal. I'd recommend just getting them for free, because I really just made this for fun. I'm not really looking to make anything up this.
I have but one request, if I may. I'd love to have some sweet frickin' album art. So if there's any artists out there interested in contributing the album arts, I'd be happy to take it.
Just DM me at Mutusandu on Twitter.
Mutusandu.
If nobody's interested, that's fine too. I'll just try to come up with something, I guess.
Alright, that's it. Get excited. Sorry for the long voicemail. Love you. Bye-bye.
If you had a concept in mind for what you would want to see as the album art, that would probably help.
That's exciting. I'll give that a listen. I'll promote Dusty Dumps' PCP voicemail album. That's really cool. I'm looking forward to it. I know he's been the music guy this past year, so that's pretty cool.
Next one is further Dusty announcements. Three, two, one, go.
Okay, one more thing I forgot to mention. I have now created the Dusty Dumps channel on YouTube where I will be slowly but surely uploading my voicemail songs as sort of funny lyric videos.
So you can all sing along at home. I've only made one so far. It's the Life of Ben one.
So if you're interested in all that, just search Dusty Dumps on YouTube.
Okay, that's it. See ya.
I see it. Dusty Dumps 13 days ago. Dusty Dumps presents Life of Ben.
Oh, I clicked on a Dusty Dumps video that's three years old. Where is this?
Yeah, there's an animation called Dusty Dumps that is three years old. I think that's unrelated. Dusty Dumps, Life of Ben.
Alright, I won't listen to it at the moment, but I will subscribe to that channel.
Yeah, Dusty Dumps. Give them a sub and the album coming out. I'm looking forward to it. Very funny.
Next one is, where are we? How much do you pay the editor?
Honestly, there's a formula.
It's a proportion of the month's earnings, although the episode's earnings. I forget what the number is, though.
Okay. YouTube link, no. Next one is Cimo, C-I-M-O, and then a bunch of O's.
Oh, like the Paul McCartney song.
Oh, alright. Three, two, one, go.
Yeah, this seems playable and looking at my hand, I think we made many mistakes.
Main one, I'm going to do a shocking play, buddy. Okay, you ready? I'm going to set one.
Okay, alright.
And I'm going to set another, and that's all.
What's that?
Was that the Nostalgia Critic?
I don't think it's Doug Walker, but I don't know who it is.
I thought it was Doug Walker for a second, but then I wasn't so sure, and now I... I don't know.
Okay, I don't know who it is.
The Paul McCartney song I referenced was Seamoon.
Oh.
It's a good song.
Next one is a vocabruelink. Okay, three, two, one, go.
Just look. What do you see?
Oh, yes, Ben. Harder. Harder.
Keep pounding my pussy.
A man?
Yes.
Fucking a horse.
Ethan, get out of here. I'm busy.
Wow, Ben. You got caught red-handed.
Ethan is a pig that fucks a horse, so what does he have to... how can he judge?
Wow.
Next one.
Next one is Better Call Saul, Season 6 is Wild.
Cock and Balls, Slime and Punishment.
Wait, an HTTP...
Directed by Benjamin... it's your name.
Look at all the bottom.
Part two, Eleazar, Cock and Balls.
Better Call Saul, Season 6.
Okay, I'm a little curious. I'm going to check the Wikipedia page.
It doesn't actually say that. There's no way.
It's a freely editable thing.
I guess I could have edited it and then take a picture. I just assumed they'd like doctored the image.
No.
Okay, I think... yeah, I guess all the episodes in Season 6 are all called Something and Something.
So, okay, I get it.
Unfortunately, Eleazar and Benjamin are not actually credited on the show.
Alas, that would really be something.
Okay, next one is called Ben Cells, 3, 2, 1, go.
This is going to be the whole thing, isn't it?
Yeah.
And this is a pay.
Well, now it sounds like Peter Griffin.
He's right. Okay, next one...
Where's the Vapors?
This is a context once again in the next voicemail.
And it's Alex from Yeek looking at, I don't know, something in space or whatever.
It's looking at the end of Homestuck.
Yeah, that's what it looks like.
Wait, is that what that? No, maybe.
I no played Yeek.
Well, I'll tell you right now, he does not go to Homestuck in Yeek, so...
Oh, it sucks then.
Okay, next one is a Vokeru link, 3, 2, 1, go.
Yes.
I heard that.
At least they didn't before.
Tommy Oliver.
If you know this person, I beg of you.
Don't interact with them.
All universes are made of similar elements but all have different chains of cause and effect as their DNA.
Just like different seeds in Minecraft.
But if you touch this singularity, you will influence all other seeds.
And nobody can predict what will happen then.
Maybe a new Big Bang.
Maybe all worlds will overlay one another.
Maybe causality fundamentally will stop working.
Please, stay away from Tommy Oliver.
Don't miss a final episode, Friendship Magic Dimensions.
Okay.
I won't miss the final episode of Friendship Magic Dimensions.
Thank you, Alex Yeek.
I guess don't touch Tommy Oliver.
You just don't want to touch it.
You just don't want to do that.
Okay, I'm going to download this voicemail.
Okay, next voicemail is another Vokeru.
3, 2, it's 2 whole minutes.
3, 2, 1, go.
You?
Who are you and why are you impersonating me?
You don't recognize me?
Look, does this look like impersonation to you?
What? How?
Oh, I see. You have lost your memory when Tommy Oliver shot you.
Same thing happened to me, actually.
Come inside, it's gonna be a long one.
I requested you to install a voice module in my head, so I could send voicemails?
Correct.
And then you use remote control to record voicemails with it?
Yes.
But why won't you record yourself?
Hug. This is a long story.
Through my life I've never felt any connection to other people.
My family didn't really care about me.
I wasn't interesting enough to make friends at school.
Only times people cared were when they tried to use me.
So I've been listening to your voicemails in case module malfunctions.
When I felt something.
For the first time in my life.
I too wanted to talk to PCP.
But do you really think they would listen to me?
Never.
Well, I listened to you even then.
You could have just asked.
Asked? And you would have agreed to.
Of course.
Wow, friendship really is magic.
So you make voicemails with me?
Sure.
High five.
Wait, who I hoof?
Let's be real.
What happened?
What was that?
It seems that Tommy Oliver's bullets left out bodies and flew away.
But why?
Actually, I don't really care.
Yeah, me neither.
Let's go record voicemails.
And then they have recorded many great voicemails.
But that's a whole another story.
The final episode, friendship magic.
Narrated by Robert Stax.
Laura's antisocial person.
Twilight sparkles herself.
Tommy Oliver is Tommy Oliver.
Google woman is Twilight Saber Spark.
Poojee is ages school.
Oblivion fall is interrupting death pay.
What a journey.
What a journey we've been on together.
I don't remember when Tommy Oliver shot Twilight with a gun.
When they discovered that friendship was magic.
His bullets exploded and flew out of them.
Okay.
They can make voicemails all day long.
That's all they need.
You too, listener.
All you need is the power of friendship and making voicemails.
And we will have to suffer through them.
There's another one.
That was great.
Oh god, there is.
Oh no.
Yeah, okay.
Three, two, one, go.
How?
No!
What is happening?
Is that Tom?
I think it was the bullet.
I'm sorry for being late, Chris-san.
Sunny-chu.
Yes, the dimensional merge has finally happened.
There, there.
Pray your heart out.
Now, we'll put you there.
And how do you want me to punish them?
Oh no.
Social ending. The merge.
Narrated by Robert Stack.
Random people as prison guards.
The odds went out as Christian.
Wolfie-chu is Sunny-chu.
Wait, how did you get there?
Stop.
What do we did now?
Visit your friends and say,
How nice it is to have friends.
Friendship really is magic.
That's what I'm saying.
What a twist.
That was Christian in jail.
Voiced by the odd ones out, I think he said.
Yeah, they did.
Fascinating.
And Sonichu.
Oh, it was, of course.
Of course.
It was Sonichu all along.
It explains everything.
Yes.
Excellent.
Okay.
Next one is called Snakeweed.
Three, two, one, go.
Is it true?
No.
That Simsie is an absolute fucking legend.
Because I've known him for years.
And he's a sexy boy.
Just needed to be conferred by other people.
Because, you know, bias to views and all.
We just need to be with him.
I can't confer.
Just letting him use a sexy boy.
Sexy.
Was there a question?
Oh shit, yeah, a question.
How big is Simsie's penis on a scale of 1 to 10?
It's huge.
He's not on the episode.
This is going to be weird.
Well, if he's not on the episode, that's fine.
Just get him on the episode.
Give us your opinion anyway.
Yeah, just get it, you know?
I want to know.
I want to know what you think.
Has Simsie got a big penis?
I believe so.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, of course.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He shows it.
Every time he comes into the chat, he posts his penis.
I've seen it.
I can't say it the way he says hello.
I've seen it in my mind's eye.
I like to rotate a 3D model of it in my mind.
Simsie told me, Simsie messaged me yesterday to be like,
sorry, my real life friend sent in a voicemail.
I think they sent it in too.
Sounded just like him.
It was like, it sounded pretty similar.
Yeah, a little bit, a little bit.
Next one, it's as though like Simsie's mind had been body swapped into like a different
body.
Pattern.
Next one is called Happy Birthday, Ben.
Thanks.
The one after that is called Do The Bonus Episodes, have voicemails?
No.
The one after that is called Noah Gervais.
Yeah, three, two, one, go.
Hi, I'm Noah Gervais.
It's Noah Gervais.
Hi, Noah Gervais.
I was watching one of your videos yesterday, I think.
I watched the Alan Wake one.
Next one is Ben's Weekly Reminder, Play Gelteroon Chapter Two, okay.
One after that, Hidden Symbolism of Pig and Crabs, three, two, one, go.
So about this, Agent Squill doing Operation Crabita, voicemail.
I think the plot was that pig destroyed most of the crabs which is why Twilight Sparkle
was able to roll through them.
But that's just a theory.
R and also I have that song playing during the fight in my playlist and its metal gear
theme goes metal.
So you have listened to Pig Metal and enjoyed it.
Ah, you know what, wow.
So the pig that thinned the herd in a sense and that's how Twilight Sparkle was able to
roll through the crabs with her miracle build.
Ah, the herd, thinned the herd like horses.
Yeah.
I understand.
I understand everything.
Okay, next one is called My Personal Blog, three, two, one, go.
It's crazy, man.
I'm sitting here on a computer.
I'm sitting here at a digital device like a, there's just little rubber buttons I push
on and they make little electricity connections and shit.
And my point is that the other day, like earlier today, the other yesterday, I was sitting in
front of my computer and I pushed the button and I was like, how did humanity make a computer?
Like how did they do that?
Yeah, they couldn't figure out that the earth was flat.
I mean, they knew it and then they forgot.
But it's like, you know, like, it's like man with little tiny lens looking at little,
looking at little pebbles with a little lens, like a magnifying glass.
But if he looks, if he tries to look up, if he tries to look down, look at a tree, you
can't see it because it's out of focus.
You know, it's like, and my point is, is that he's so right.
Yeah.
Well, to make a computer, you just have to invent the transistor and then just, you just,
you just tie them together in like a chain and you like sort of weave them together in
sort of a, a net.
And then you overlay a bunch of those nets on top of each other and they all connect and
they become a neural network.
Dude.
And you make a.
Friends.
Sys.
Transition.
Every time I hear, every time I hear the word transition, I say that now.
It hasn't happened yet, but one of these days it will.
What were we talking?
Yeah.
Computers.
They're wild.
They're so cool, man.
They're like a bunch of silly cones and you put them in a row.
Do you just take a bunch of cones, a bunch of rods, stick them in your eye?
Colors, man.
All right.
Next one is called Happy Birthday, Ben.
Thank you.
Next one is called Please Update Podcast Playlist on the channel.
They lack epi.
So.
Oh, you know, that's actually probably would be a good thing to do.
Update the podcast, the playlist.
Yeah, I will do that actually.
And maybe before I do the SSR, RSS.
RSS.
SSI.
The Real Special Service.
The SSRI feed, the Super Serotonian Reuptake Inhibitor Feed.
Keep your from being depressed.
Next one is called So Des, starting from around 300, do it while it's not much work.
I think they're referring to which episodes are not on the playlist.
Oh, episodes starting from around 300.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so like a dozen episodes.
Yeah, I'll do that.
Next one, Ben's Weekly Reminder to Upload the Episodes to Spotify.
I will.
Happy birth.
Next one, Happy Birthday, Ben.
Thanks.
Then a bunch of YouTube links.
And then one called Simsie Friend.
Three, two, one, go.
Yes.
Hello, Ben St.
You sound ledgy.
Thanks.
I know Simsie.
He's literally holding the phone right now while I record this.
Oh, I see.
My question is, Tails got trolled.
Is it like legitimate good?
You dingus.
Can we retake this?
You haven't seen.
If you'd seen the lecture, you'd know that it is good, actually.
Or just read the comic, actually.
Take Cybershell's advice.
Don't watch my lecture.
Read the video.
It's legitimately entertaining.
Whether or not it's good doesn't mean anything.
There are qualities of genuine quality to it.
One might say.
I don't want to say it's good.
I would say it can be enjoyed.
It can be very enjoyed.
It can be enjoyed unironically, yeah, for sure.
Yeah, yeah.
Next one is called Jamie.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm at the pub right now.
Simsie is looking at me right now.
He's got quite a lot of judgment.
But I also kind of want to ask Ben St. a question.
I just want to ask, what's your favorite beer?
I don't know.
What do they be drinking over there?
And if you include this in the podcast, I'll be embarrassed.
Sorry.
I guess everything gets included.
Literally, what kind of beer do you guys be drinking over there?
I know you guys like anime and Tails got trolled and stuff.
This is DJ Bro's anime podcast.
It's kind of irrelevant.
But just what kind of beer should be drinking?
That's all I want to know.
I went out to a restaurant the other day.
Usually, when I drink beer, I drink...
I'm on the record as having an unrefined palette.
So I just drink piss water.
I just drink light beer with less calories.
I drink Miller light or Michalab Ultra or whatever.
Usually, Miller light is my default.
I just drink some light beer.
It sucks.
But it's fine.
And then, although if I'm trying to save money, I'll drink Narragansett.
I went out to a restaurant the other day and I had two Narragansetts.
Narragansetts, traditionally, they come in a 16 ounce can.
That's the bigger can.
Tallboy.
And they cost $5, which at a restaurant is a pretty good price for a beer.
This fucking restaurant charged $7 for their Narragansett,
which is like charging a buck 25 for an Arizona iced tea.
So, you know, didn't appreciate that, but oh well.
Man, that's my answer.
Miller light or Narragansett, depending on whether I value lower calories or saving a couple bucks.
I just drink where there's a drink to drink.
I mean, I'm a partial to a Doombar or a hobgoblin or a Corona.
I guess Stella Artois is pretty good.
I like most of the time I drink and I'm like, I'm two beers in.
And that's just nice.
I feel buzzy.
I went to the Stella Artois brewery in fucking Belgium.
I think it's Belgium, right?
I thought it was French, but maybe.
Oh, hold on.
And when I say I went to it, I mean that I like walked by it.
I didn't like go on a tour or anything.
It's in Leuven.
Wait, is that in Belgium?
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, I walked through the town that it's in.
It's in the Netherlands.
It's in Belgium.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Near Brussels, Leuven.
Okay, I don't usually drink beer.
No, I guess I do.
I don't know.
It's a very simple way to just have a drink and alcohol is to be had.
It is a simple way to have a drink and it generally leads to not being that hungover the next day.
So I would say that it's a pretty good thing to drink if you're going to drink.
But the people that I generally drink with these days, none of them like beer.
So usually we do something else.
Are they chugging shots?
Yes, yes, they are.
They're doing shots or they're drinking cider.
Cider's okay.
I like a dry cider instead of a sweet one.
Cider's fine.
I guess it tastes good or whatever.
But it's just beer but more expensive and it tastes like an apple and like whatever.
It's just more expensive and I don't care that much.
It's about, you know, it all comes down to value for dollar for me, honestly.
That's not true, although it is kind of true.
Next one is called In the Car with Dad.
The audio is kind of shit.
Three, two, one, go.
Now don't you go and get me no left about being a baby and being a little ninja or whatever the hell you're being.
You can talk.
I've heard you.
But you know what?
Very don't.
Very don't talk because the next word to come out of your mouth better be God bless America.
Like the American you are.
Ben the Saint is on.
Help me.
You gotta help him.
I, um, how, how, oh, how the turntables.
Oh, how are you?
This is what you get.
This is your punishment for trying to get that scroll back.
You know, Finder's Keepers nerd.
It's expecting something else.
Bummer, man.
Real, real, it's rough.
The next one is challenge three, two, one, go.
No more three, two, one goes.
No more Samurais.
No more pigs.
No more Ben casts.
No more tombstones.
This is the last episode of the PCP.
Say farewell to the listeners and kill this podcast right now.
I'm sorry.
I will fail your challenge.
My friends.
It's, it's too hard.
It's too hard to end the podcast even harder if you can believe it than continuing it.
There's a concept in physics called inertia.
Actually, it's an object in motion will stay in motion unless acted upon by a force.
Look it up.
It's true.
Believe it or not.
I don't believe it.
Well, you're gonna have to, you're gonna have to live with me not believing it.
I can't.
So I'll kill myself.
Okay.
Next one is a comic.
Oh, is it?
Hang on.
There's a voice.
Is there a voicemail tag?
No, it's just garbage.
It's just garbled.
Okay.
A comic.
Let's read this.
This trash.
Oh, um, okay.
Sama lives here.
Sama Slayer.
Evil is here.
I am not a samurai.
I have fought alongside them as a warrior bound by honor.
And before their final hours made an oath to them.
If anyone emerged to besmirch their clan's name or subject them to any shit cannon,
I would strike them down for the clan.
For my friend.
I've come for you foul beast.
Goo Goo Gaga.
Your tricks won't work on me.
Ah, so you can see my spirit inside this vessel.
Shut up.
I'm going to rip your spirit from this cursed children child's body.
You can't just do that.
Just threw them through a wall, I guess.
Now feel the strength of my ultimate attack.
Secret technique.
1000 sword strike.
I just wanted to cube and say of shit cannon destruction.
Oh my god.
Just like that, the imposter is slain.
Such is the fate for all fake samurai who dare to besmirch the order's name and cannon.
Such is the honor bound duty of the Sama Slayer.
Wow.
You ripped out that.
Oh, I mean it's cannon because they made a comic about it.
That is cannon.
That is very cannon.
Yeah.
Comics are very high on the canonical hierarchy.
So there you go.
So the baby samurai, no more.
Seems to have been exercised by the 1000 sword strike.
I mean, I can see it happening in his little very, very, very faint green aura there.
I can see it happening.
He's crying sad little tears, his little beetle helmet.
Just be advised.
I guess I didn't need to help him.
He said help me.
Well, the Sama Slayer, he's killed him.
Sort of.
This is what you want.
Is this what you wanted?
All right.
Next one is an Imgur link, but there's also a voicemail attached.
So three, two, one.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, Imgur.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm sending a message after every episode I see, but I'm running out of funny.
I guess look at my favorite image on the internet.
Thanks.
Look at my favorite image on the internet.
Yeah, it says another old comic.
Like an anime girl coming home from school.
What the hell is this?
It's a group of thugs.
They grab her.
And then the one guy, he takes her arm and he ties a knot on her sleeves.
And they run away and now she has, she can't get her hands out of her sleeves.
Hey, is that me grabbing her from behind with the beanie on?
Yes.
Nice.
Tied up her sleeve.
That's kind of cute, I guess.
Next one is called, it's a Dropbox link.
It's a Dropbox link.
Let's find out what's going to happen.
Oh my God, it's the artist.
It's the artist.
It's new.
There we are.
All right.
Okay, I'm on the first panel.
I'm already liking what I'm seeing.
Yes.
All right.
By new PS, did y'all give anything for free comic book day?
I've not heard of free comic book day, so I guess not.
Oh, maybe it's an American thing.
Yeah, there's a day called free comic book day where just a lot of stores, you can just
walk into a comic shop and they'll just give you a free comic or something.
Oh yeah, we don't have that.
That sounds cool though.
A lot of artists do something for it.
No, I didn't realize that it happened.
Oops.
Next one.
Here we go.
What the hell do you hogs want from us?
Radcon money, the lost tapes, patrons?
We don't have any of that shit.
It's true.
True because we didn't charge for March.
I'm never going to stop.
The rest of my life, I'm going to look at my bank account and I'm going to think there
would be several more hundreds of dollars in there in that number if only things had
been different and it'll never not be true.
I'm cursed.
Anyway, anyway, it's not important right now.
Oh, Benji, my bitter summer child, you know what I'm here for.
Snoop hogs.
Errorare's rap hog from episode 255 Snoop Hogs.
I don't recall a rap hog, yeah?
Before, I really like the way they did the hands on this Snoop Hog.
Oh, yeah.
It's a little bit, a little bit gorillas.
Yeah.
That's his name.
Jamie something.
The tank girl guy.
Yeah.
It's a bit, or a bit, or a little bit Hellboy.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I see what you mean.
Yeah, it looks really good.
The answers.
The answer's Ben St.
What does oblivion fall put in the CPK recipes so they don't taste like shit?
Clusterpunk Kitchen.
How to properly pronounce icy, icy Molotov Ligma Sakurai.
Okay.
The real reason why Nate left the podcast.
The Snoop Hog is being, he's snooping around.
Oh, sure.
I find these, these answers.
God, my tits are so hot.
I can't, you have all the answers in those.
My fat tits.
The Kawasaki scrolls.
The Kawasaki scroll.
They're in your cleavage.
My tits look so sexy.
They're great.
They are great.
They are.
I wish I could see mine more.
They're kind of, you can just kind of see them from behind there.
This, oh my God.
This is so good.
New is a genius.
Why, I have nothing else to add to this.
I can't, I can't improve upon it other than, boy, I don't remember there being a wrap
hog, but I believe it.
I do remember we were listening to a few of Errorari's things.
We couldn't comprehend them.
So maybe there was a wrap hog in one of those and we just didn't get it.
Perhaps.
It does explain where the scrolls have been all along, you know.
Fat tits.
It answers a lot of questions that have been lingering.
What a revelation.
Well, that was the last voicemail.
Oh, is it?
Yeah, I think so.
Right?
Am I crazy?
Oh, no, that's true.
It's, that is the last one.
Yeah.
So, and what a, and what a one to go out on and wow, we've only been recording for two
hours today.
We have, we have robbed these view listeners.
Oh, no.
Of their content.
All right.
Next week.
Their hard iron content.
I will, I will make sure to make have some things to talk about next time.
You should, you should like injure yourself and go to the hospital so you can talk about
that.
Yeah, I'll say, oh, what the fuck?
My legs broken.
Oh, and then we can fuck.
And then I can gripe about American healthcare, private healthcare and all that and we can
have a whole thing go down that rabbit hole, you know, how many, that's an evergreen, not
well, it's an evergreen well.
I pledge that for next week's episode, I will, I will be in, I will have spent, I will be
arrested.
I will be incarcerated in the American prison state.
Nice.
I will deliver my manifesto from through my one phone call through my one phone call
give, I'll call you and I'll say, Hey, listen, I'm just going to like talk into your talk
into your answering machine.
And I just want you to play my message on the podcast.
And that's my one phone call.
What if I can't figure out what if I don't have an answering machine?
I guess I don't need a machine these days.
It just goes on my phone.
I guess the podcast, then I guess the challenge is met and the podcast is dead.
I'll try and carry it.
Oh, no, I'm dying of COVID.
I won't be able to carry the podcast.
Oh, how ironic.
How ironic you would die of disease that everybody fucking has.
I can't do the podcast by myself disease.
What if Usopp did a podcast on the pirate ship?
Well, that would be racist because Usopp is a racist caricature like Aunt Jemima,
and he needs to be canceled.
You know, the real racists are the ones that won't let Usopp have a podcast, in my opinion.
Thanks for listening.
Is there anything else?
Oh, hey, please, please give us some money at patreon.com.
We didn't charge for March and my bank account is a little bit lower than it should be forever.
Forever?
And I will never stop crying about it.
So please console me at patreon.com.
We do have like a bunch of new bonus episodes.
Like four or five new bonus episodes.
A few like a week ago or so.
They were made real.
Before last week, they came out five new five five four or five new bonus new behind the scenes bonus collections.
Access to the Minecraft server.
And five dollars are up access the Minecraft server.
All the previous all the previous bonus episodes.
There's like there's literally like 50 of them.
So if you haven't listened to that.
Why not why not why not take a why not roll the dice on all on the old procrastinators bonus bonus content.
Keep yourself entertained for years to come.
Forever and ever.
Amen.
And I don't know, I guess that's it.
That's it.
Okay.
Bye.