This episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast was brought to you by our bonus episode.
Go to patreon.com slash The Pro Crastinators and pledge $5 or more to get access to all our bonus monthly episodes.
Last month's episode was...
The topic for this episode is New Year's and Old Year's thoughts.
And, uh, here's a blast from the past. You may remember this guy, Munchy, with his diminutive headwear.
Ah, it's time to return to what we all think about when we think about Munchy.
Munchy got a fucking-ticking huge fucking fist at the BCP!
Oh, well, I'm sorry I didn't get ghost of the child this year either.
But next year, for sure, guys, for sure!
Smash cut!
Smash cut to 2021.
Yeah, to 2029.
That's patreon.com slash The Pro Crastinators, giving you a boner every single time.
Hey, everybody, it's another episode of the PCP.
Nate's late, like a bitch, but I'm here.
What a didgy bro.
Way to start the new year, never feel.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Welcome to 2020, to the new decade, even, not just the new year.
But, uh, how you guys feeling, Mage, Ben, in the new year?
Um, um, uh...
It's not the new year for us recording it.
It will be when you hear this.
We haven't suffered through it yet.
Hopeless, uh, doomed.
There's no light at the end of the tunnel.
We're all headed towards oblivion.
I feel grateful.
I am feeling great as well.
I'm excited.
Right on.
Nice.
Happy for you.
At least in a general sense, in the actual moment, I'm tired, um,
fed up with waiting,
because we already waited half an hour for Nate to get home,
but he's still right here.
He did, so here we are.
We really did.
In so many years, he blended up just once.
Yeah, that makes it all the worse.
He's tarnished his perfect record.
Uh, it's painful.
It's like Lisa Simpson getting a B.
The last episode was the last of the year and decade, technically.
But did you guys talk about that at all on that episode?
No.
Did we?
I don't know.
No, I think we just talked about the holidays.
Okay.
Do you want to talk about it being the end of the fucking decade?
Let's do it.
I want to talk about what you, what you did,
what you did during the holidays at some point,
because like you were talking while before the holidays, wasn't it?
I recorded last one.
Who?
This?
Us?
Yeah, last episode was recorded on the 22nd, so it wasn't Christmas yet.
Now it's post-Christmas.
What did you get for presents?
I need to know.
Oh, it's got a bunch of crap.
I didn't even get, I asked my parents for like one thing,
and it wasn't even a big thing.
And I think they just forgot and didn't get it for me.
What was the thing?
I just, I just, it's just a boring, like I wanted like an adjustable like razor,
like for your beard, you know, you put on like the different length attachments
and hair clipper.
I was like, I could use one of those.
They got me like shoes.
I didn't want shoes.
I remember the shoes.
The shoes saga continues.
They got me a couple nice shirts though, so whatever, it's fine.
It balanced it out.
Got me some stuff.
I got random stuff from May's family and a hundred bucks on Amazon.
I mean, I'm an adult.
Christmas is not exciting anymore, nor should it be.
Although it was exciting because I did my own Christmas for the first time
where I had the tree and I had the stuff,
and I had Epstein didn't kill himself written all over the place.
Did you have your family over to your place?
Is that how you did it?
I had, I had Vic in shade over.
Oh, that's pretty good.
That's pretty cool.
But I mean, you could just go,
you can learn all about it by watching the fucking video I made about it.
Epstein didn't Christmas himself.
That was what the video was about.
I watched it.
Didn't really have the time.
What else could it be about?
How should I know?
Things aren't things that they seem to be nowadays.
So, you know, okay, my Christmas, I had fun because I got this gift.
Like my parents said, it's like, oh, there's not going to be any gifts this year,
but I decided to be sent and I got everyone gifts.
Well, rather than like, okay, so for my sister and my mother,
I got, I got the money because they can just buy their own clothes
because I'm not really good at buying clothes and they like clothes.
So, you know, just money.
I got my dad a computer, but like, it got a bit busted during the shipping,
but it's okay.
It's fixable.
It's just going to cost a little bit extra.
But yeah, no computer for that.
Sounds expensive.
It's okay.
I got a new computer for myself and my old computer,
that which is still really good for today's standards.
I got it shipped over to my dad.
It did cost a little bit.
I got it insured.
Thankfully I got it insured.
So maybe I'll get some of the money back of that because they busted my computer.
That should be to get it all back, right?
Isn't that what insurance means?
Kind of like, you have to put in what you think the computer is worth.
Like, you know what, what this, what the shipping item is worth.
I put in 500 quid, though the computer actually cost it like more than twice as much
back when I bought it, but I bought it in 2016.
Well, I didn't buy it.
I got it as a present.
But yeah, 2016.
So it's been a few years on it.
So, you know, I lowered the price just to be fair.
And yeah, they kind of busted it a little bit, but I'm not sure if it's going to be
like, oh, because you didn't pack it properly.
You're going to, you're not going to get your refund or anything.
I mean, they have to like survey the damages.
They asked for pictures.
No, no, they asked for pictures.
I took some pictures.
So I don't know.
We'll see.
Maybe on the next episode, I'll have a reply.
It's been a few days, but it's the holidays.
So, you know.
Anyway, and I got, I got like, like the best give ever.
I, it's not very appealing looking, but I got my very first onesie.
And now I am one with the Gremlin.
I am the Gremlin.
I am wearing the onesie.
I am a Gremlin.
I love it.
It's so good.
What, what is, what onesie?
What Gremlin?
What is this?
I'm wearing a onesie and I feel like a Gremlin wearing it.
I'm just, I'm just a big old, big old onesie.
And it's so weird.
With your footies?
Yeah.
Without, without feet.
It is just with the, yeah.
It's just a one piece for like legs and, and arms.
And, and like, it has a little hood on, on the head.
And it's really great.
And this is what I've been wearing around the house now.
Who needs clothes?
One'sies for life.
I love it.
I'm a Gremlin.
And I'm glad you also thought that she meant an actual Gremlin.
Yeah.
It was imagining like a kid kigarumi, but like with the Gremlins.
Because the Gremlins I have are Totoro and Snorlax.
So.
I wish.
Easily imagined.
I wish I would have got something like that.
But no, my, my families are normies.
They wouldn't have gotten me something as cool as an anime onesie.
But no, this is fine.
It's very soft.
It's very warm and it's very pleasant.
A little short on the legs, but most things are for me.
Too long.
Legs too long.
Amazing.
I, my, I got boots.
I guess I'll wear them in the snow.
I got Copic markers.
That's pretty cool.
I never use those, but you know, there might come a day.
They're good.
They are good.
So it's makes you feel good.
They're good.
So I should probably use them.
But I don't know.
I guess time will tell.
I got new hats.
Got a bunch of new knit hats.
That's pretty cool.
Haven't worn any of them yet.
But what I mean, you know, whatever.
My family has been nagging me about wearing the hat that I wear because they think it's
super ugly.
And I'm like, I don't care for your Christmas with the giant fluffy thing at the end.
I hate those hats.
What hat, what hat do you wear?
It's like, it's just a black like hat.
It's a, it's kind of like a beanie, but it's not a beanie.
I think it's just, it's just like, it's just like fabric.
It's just black fabric with a red triangle on the front and they find it nice.
Yes.
Antifa.
No.
Yes.
I was, I was watching a speed run of Kingdom Hearts two and I cannot believe how fucking
cool Halloween Town Sora looks in that game with his goth Santa.
His got the goth Santa look is so great.
I was like, wait a minute.
Was he always goth Santa and Kingdom Hearts two Halloween Town?
He was amazing.
Great decision.
You gotta Google that.
Agreed.
I want to, I want to have a look.
Some Googling it.
Halloween Town goth Santa, you say.
Halloween Town.
Are you watching this?
Are you watching the speed run right now, Ben?
No, no, I just, this is a thing I've been doing lately, just putting on like GDQ speed
runs just on autoplay.
That's the one.
Look at that.
Oh, it does look cool.
It actually, the 2D drawn art is cooler than the 3D model.
I also like this one.
I like the goth Santa.
It's my shit.
Oh, there's a figurine for the goth Santa.
Look at it.
Yes.
Is that not just the fucking coolest?
I don't even play Kingdom Hearts and I want it.
It's such good aesthetic.
What's the guy's name?
The guy who did, he did the world ends with you.
You ever play the world ends with you?
That game's fucking sick.
I played the elevator back when it came out, but it didn't play too well on the computer
so I never actually got to play it.
No, you got to play that on a dual screen.
It's out on the switch now.
Is it?
Oh, yeah.
I guess that makes sense.
Great.
I'm glad.
I was afraid that maybe would, I was afraid that maybe would never get re-released for
anything because of like, you know, the weird screen setup.
It's great though.
People should buy, people should buy that on the switch.
Classic.
Fuck, what's the guy's name?
What's the character designer?
Do you guys know?
He's a big shoe boy.
He's a big shoe boy, zipper man.
You know.
Trash baby god.
Rob Liefield.
Lots of pockets.
I mean, you're talking about, you're talking about Nomura, right?
I am talking about Nomura.
That's correct.
Yeah.
Got it.
We got there.
Fuck, man.
Nate's turning over in his voicemail grave right now.
He's named Nomura.
He, I'm sure he would have lots of opinions about Goth Santa.
Goth Santa.
So I spent, you know.
God, I hope not.
You know, I spent the holidays.
Mostly, you know, I talk about, you know, I had to suffer the company of my family members.
Same.
Who are all, they're all so much taller than me.
Me and Nate, we're all tiny and everyone else in our family.
Yeah.
Everyone else in our family is like six feet plus.
They're huge.
It's like, it's weird.
I have the exact opposite problem.
You want to trade?
No.
No, wait.
Maybe.
Maybe I do.
Let's do it.
Well, so I had to do that.
Mostly I was just plastered the whole time.
Mostly I just got like roaring drunk and like passed out every single day.
It was great.
It made it go by faster.
You know, I say that like it's a bad thing, like I had a miserable time, but actually
it was fun just getting fucking wasted all through the holiday season.
I try it sometime.
I had.
I have.
Nice.
Tried it every year in fact.
It sounded like I said I had, I had done so, but no, I just wanted to say that I had
done something else to pass the time other than get plastered.
I do not drink.
Damn.
I got this, I got this game on steam.
How do you live?
I survive.
I drink water.
You know, I didn't drink that much until recently and now I drink all the time.
Do not.
It's bad.
I don't know.
I don't think it's good.
I think maybe I'm, I think maybe it's weird.
Let me ask you this, Ben.
Do you like it?
You know, sometimes kind of, I guess.
Good.
You can like a lot of things, but not all the things are good for you even though you
like them.
You know, but it's not about good for you.
It's about whether it's good.
Actually.
I mean, what good for you is a very subjective thing.
Actually, it's interesting.
Yeah.
When I drank less frequently, when I did drink, I would wake up the next day feeling like,
oh no, I got so drunk last night.
Oh, I must have acted like such an asshole.
Oh, everyone hates me now.
Now, I've been, I've been drinking like every night for a while.
I've been, you know, blacking out like all the time.
And everyone loves you now.
And every, well, I don't, well, I don't care anymore is the problem.
Now I wake up and I don't care what I mean.
Maybe you're too cynical if that's the right word nowadays.
Cynical?
I'm not sure if that's the correct word.
Like just.
Oh, I'm just, I just don't give a fuck.
Yeah, basically.
I've just gotten, I've just gotten so used to the feeling of waking up and not remembering
how, how I fell asleep that I'm just like, yeah, that's fine.
That's normal.
Don't worry about it.
I'm highly against that sort of lifestyle, but you do you.
Okay.
Well, I'm highly against your sort of lifestyle, whatever that means.
Now it's just, I don't particularly, I have, I have a few alcoholics in my family and you
know, I don't, I don't like seeing their lives go that way.
So just out of concern for your wellbeing, I just say I don't really approve of that
sort of.
If you start seeing shit, stop drinking.
Um, I'm probably going to cut back pretty soon.
Like why, I don't know.
I think it's just a holiday thing.
Like people all, people all get together and partying.
Then I can't remember, did I ever tell you to read the manga Disappearance Diary?
Oh, another diary.
I don't remember.
Okay.
Well, it's a manga about a guy named Hideo Azuma who recently died, Rest in Peace.
But he, he had this manga he wrote about the three times that he had disappeared, that
he ran away from his family and just became a homeless man.
Well, the first, the first time he ran away, he just became homeless for like 20 days or
so before the police found him and brought him back home because apparently they can
do that.
Um, then the second time he ran away, he just like went to a different town and started
up a different job as like a construction worker or whatever.
This guy's a manga artist.
Um, and then in the third part, he becomes a hardcore alcoholic in the 90s.
And in that part, I truly...
His most lucrative job today.
Yeah.
I, I had never truly understood what alcoholism does to you until reading that.
But it's basically like, you know, if he wasn't sloshed at all times, he would like
hallucinate freaky shit and like just, just vomiting in the streets and like barely knows
where he is most of the time.
Yeah.
I mean like, if you're real deep in it, you get like withdrawal and like you're fucked
and you have to like detox.
Uh.
I mean, I know something about withdrawals.
Let me tell you, because I didn't have no weed yesterday and it was not easy to get
to sleep, but.
Um, no.
No, man.
No, drinking's gay.
Drinking's for the birds.
Uh, I can't, I can't wait to be above the influence again.
I really, I very, very drink anymore.
And it's, it's funny because, uh, people used to like identify me as the guy who drinks.
I mean, your Twitter profile says like getting drunk and ranting about anime.
I, I, one time I almost changed it to say getting high and ranting about anime or whatever,
but, uh, it's just about the way that people respond to those two things.
It's really funny how like how normal it is to people to drink or to say you drink.
Um, but not the same when you say you smoke pot, not yet anyway, but people have a very
different set of assumptions about that.
And like, it was just funny to me how like when I started smoking pot, it started coming
up a lot in my comments, like, oh, did you use high?
That's why this video is like this.
When like, I was like, but I've been, but I used to be drunk in all the videos.
Like what?
Is this the trade off?
Like, how do you tell the difference between a high video and a drunk video?
I wonder.
Yeah.
Both of those things kind of, I don't like.
One is, one is, one is normal.
Equally.
You gotta live a little bit.
I live the way I like to live.
I find, let's, dude, let's peer pressure mage.
No, you will not succeed.
I am a contrarian.
How do you know you don't like it?
If you haven't tried it, don't you know all the cool kids do it?
I have tried alcohol and my, my family likes to sometimes tease me.
Like, at least they used to, and they were like, Hey, try this, try that.
And I hate it.
All alcohol tastes the same to me.
I even smell alcohol in deodorant and I don't like it using the deodorant.
So why didn't you keep drinking it?
Huh?
What are you, pussy?
You some kind of pussy?
Then it's not gonna work.
Um, I mean, wait, there are drinks that don't taste that.
I have to say, I don't think anybody likes alcohol.
Like, I mean, I could probably full stop that, but I don't think anybody likes it at first.
Like, it's, it's a, it is an acquired taste.
I don't try not to acquire that.
You got to start with the drinks that don't taste like it.
Right?
You got to start with like your free, like bullshit.
All drinks tastes like that.
All drinks tastes like alcohol.
No, no, no, no.
You start with my card.
Ever have like a, like a, like a sex on the beach or something, or like some kind of
fucking wine cooler or whatever.
It just tastes like juice.
I've tasted like really weak ass ones that they would even give to minors that had a
little bit of alcohol in them.
I can taste the alcohol in it and I hate it.
Though there were more tolerable than like beer or something like that, at least I'll
say that much because they had the extra flavors to them.
Nobody likes being unconvinced.
Okay.
The only kind of alcohol I like is the one that comes in like chocolate candy.
There you go.
You just got to drink Kahlua then.
That's what you got to do.
No, no, no.
It has to come in candy form and in small doses.
So if I, if I take a, if I take a pot right now and I melt down like half a pot's worth
of candy bars and then I fill the rest with alcohol and then put it in the freezer and
send it to you.
Would you eat my alcoholic chocolate?
No.
All right.
Well.
Boo.
Worth a shot.
I got some.
What if I made you weed candies though and said no.
Hell yeah.
No, weed smells terrible.
I hate it.
Like I can smell.
I hate the smell of weed.
I can smell like in the neighborhood.
Whenever someone smokes.
It smells bad man.
I don't like it.
It's beautiful.
It smells like a.
It's all like a field of flowers.
Field of.
Yeah.
Have I told the story about how one time in my dorm I was trying to like microwave
peanut butter cookies with weed on them to like get the weed in the THC into the fat
of the peanut butter.
And I microwave them to I microwave them too much and I burnt the cookies in the microwave.
This was in college and the fucking dorm or TA or whatever.
The RA was coming down to the hall and we were like shit.
We got us.
We got a stash it.
So we just had to shove these like burnt super heated peanut butter weed cookies into
our mouths and it tasted like ashes and it filled my sinuses with the smell.
The weed smell and it burns.
That sounds like the worst.
Yeah.
It was awful.
I don't like.
That's what I think of every time I smell.
I wouldn't want to smell weed emanating from my own body.
From my own like inside of my mouth which is currently burning.
That's I understand why that would.
Yeah.
That would be traumatic.
The smell of weed.
It was.
It really was.
Also there was a time there was one time in college when I smoked weed and it I must
have had something in it because it made me fucked up.
It like it made me.
Probably did.
Yeah.
It like I remember I smoked some weed and then I went to a party and I was at the party
and I could like it was like a bodily sensation and I could feel the fan like the ceiling
fan was on above me and I could feel that the air blasting down at me on the ceiling fan
like I was in a wind tunnel and it was like drying me out and dehydrating me and I couldn't
move and I thought I would die which doesn't sound like what weed is supposed to do.
I don't know.
Curious what drug.
Yeah.
I would.
I'd be interested.
This was not.
This was not normal.
But anyway.
You know I tried C.B.D. and by tried C.B.D.
I mean that I walked into a store that was giving out tiny little paper cup samples of C.B.D.
lemonade and they don't even ID check.
Lemonade.
Yeah.
Just they don't even ID check.
You don't have to be above 18 to do C.B.D.
I didn't.
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
They gave.
It doesn't have any psychoactive properties.
I guess it makes sense.
And you know what?
It didn't do anything.
So there you go.
I mean it seems like a huge meme to me.
Like I guess Tom has had some good experience with C.B.D.
because it's meant to basically have the physical effects of weed without the mental effects
essentially.
I mean it's already in weed.
Yeah.
But it's you know it's the C.B.D. without the THC.
Tom was taking it as a way of helping with his back.
Although he was also just smoking weed.
So I don't know which he did more of.
Did Tom smoke weed or did he start using it with the C.B.D.
vape?
Was he a smoking weed kind of guy?
No.
It's because of the fact that when he went to New York to hang out with his friends
they had they gave him weed and because he had back problems he realized oh I need this
and started smoking.
Liz in Boston where it's legal so it's not impossible to acquire.
So it's way easier to buy C.B.D. so you can just get it on Amazon so I would assume he
did more of that.
I actually had I actually had everyone I had I had Tom and I had Zen over to my house
the other day for friend's mess.
My roommates we had a feast.
There was antipasto.
There was lasagna.
There was chicken parm.
No pasto allowed.
We were totally antipasto and everyone was like hey Tom you're walking again.
Nice.
And you know what?
It was great.
Honestly the best part of the holiday was friend mess.
It was magical.
That boy completely wasted.
He stays on his feet the rest of his life.
Never sits down again.
Yeah.
And I don't remember going to sleep.
And I never will.
Never will again.
Fuck sleep.
Yeah.
So yeah that's been my holiday season.
I had I worked a lot and then did a crimbus.
So but you know we could we could reflect on the decade that just ended.
Oh my God.
Was it a good one?
Was it a shit one?
We all met this decade.
The whole PCP happened this decade.
Was that a net positive or a net negative?
Yeah.
It was an experience.
If I look at the whole decade I would have to say it's been pretty good.
Yeah overall.
I mean before the PCP before doing any of my shit online I had no direction in life.
Frankly the last 10 years was a third of your life a almost a third of my life.
And it's kind of hard not to like I mean it's the first it's the first third where we were like completely independent adults.
So it's like it's almost not a competition between this and previous decades at least for me.
Yeah it's like before.
I mean for me it's I shouldn't say it's almost it's definitely not a competition for me.
Like the 90s and 2000s don't have fuck at all on the 2010s.
Wait a decade ago yeah a decade ago I was still in college so like I had basically had no life.
I basically had like made no choices in life whatsoever so.
For me for me it started off really really shitty but things have been going up since then
and are continuing to go up I think.
So I'm pretty happy with the decade overall.
Up and away.
Indeed.
Yeah.
Ben's thinking he didn't end this decade on the on the highest point of the decade.
I don't feel like I don't feel like I've ended it that strongly.
I feel like I'm.
It's fine.
No it's a disaster.
No no it's fine.
No it's a huge nightmare.
No no.
I've been feeling very I felt very stagnant.
I felt very stagnant the last maybe in the last couple years I guess.
I feel like I haven't made as much progress in my life as I wanted to.
If you if you're if you're healing blues put a splash of red make purple.
Purple makes things better.
Oh my god.
Yeah I guess I'll give it a shot.
Splash of red huh.
Fucking stab stab stab.
That'll fix it.
I was wondering if you'll come to that conclusion.
Ben turns around to his entirely blue painted room considering maybe a splash of red will.
Holds gun to my head.
No.
Maybe that's just what the doctor ordered.
That is not where I was intending for it to go.
Hey what stinks in here.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Ben was just talking about killing himself.
Oh yeah that sounds good.
Hell yeah.
I was not encouraging this.
Now there's a New Year's resolution we can get behind.
You know Ben what is it form follows function or whatever the fuck because you just died in my nuzlocke just yesterday.
I heard yeah I heard it.
I heard that Ben's.
It was a slaughter Ben.
His hypnosis didn't get the job done.
Okay you know.
Hey Nate what if we did a tribute to the dead Ben saint by on after I count to three we all just say Ben saint and then we'll do the same thing again.
Oh good idea.
So here's our tribute.
One two three.
Ben saint.
Alright great tribute.
Pour one out for my little my little my little man man.
And just that very day I had retweeted some adorable art of the brothers united.
Oh god.
I also retweeted that.
Did you follow my instructions and never switch him out under any circumstances.
You know I actually did switch him out for pure strategic benefit but he died nonetheless.
Well he's probably glad to be dead then.
Better to die than a hero than live a coward.
It's so unfortunate I got into a situation where I switched in sheep over I won't go on about this but like sheep over my Zubat.
I switched in just to die.
It was like a level five Zubat so that I could get that you know you get the turn in with somebody else whatever after it dies.
And if only I had had Russell on my team who's yearning for death.
Who's craving death as a rat attack to be reborn as a ghastly one day but we'll see.
We'll see if that happens.
Anyway tune in on Tuesdays and Saturdays.
Twitch.tv slash definitely best gamer for the Nuzlocke adventure.
Alright anyway.
So Nate we were talking about whether or not we thought the last decade went good.
And I think we all pretty much concluded that it had little competition since it's the first decade where we were like autonomous adults.
That is a totally fair metric and yes there's nothing to compare it to for us.
You know I did happen to hear.
Well except for childhood.
I was saying a decade ago I was in college so I hadn't done anything.
It's such a different experience of like I can take no ownership over how good or bad my life was the previous decade really.
Because I like I guess I did my homework.
So you know life was better than if I hadn't.
But currently I mean yeah we've all been kind of building up careers in one avenue or another.
So we can actually have some autonomy over it.
I'm pretty happy with how things are going.
Life is generally pretty good.
But sounds slightly more optimistic than bad.
But yeah I would think so.
You know that's fine.
That's fine.
It's cool.
Just remember the splash of red and then I'll feel better.
I don't know.
I'm in a stage as everybody knows about trying to do a YouTube thing full time.
I have not gotten where I need to be yet with that.
But I'm making some changes and I think in the bonus episode I talked about this a little bit more.
Yeah because that was our New Year's resolution one.
So if you want to hear more about it you should go listen to that.
Or be pledged to me.
I'm going to do a fucking update on my Patreon too.
Whatever.
I'm making some changes in order to do that for the new year.
So I'm feeling pretty positive.
I think some good things are coming in the future for me.
And for me the worst case scenario is that all this YouTube shit completely falls through.
And then what's the tragedy of my life?
I go find some pretty cushy programming job again.
And I just do that while doing YouTube on the side.
So am I that worried about how things will go?
Not really.
I'm going to still be doing stuff online so I'm not going to go anywhere pretty much no matter what.
And I feel generally secure that financially I'll be okay.
I guess so yeah I'm feeling pretty decent.
I don't mind getting a real job if I have to.
Which I did for a long time before doing YouTube full time.
So that pretty much sums me up.
Yeah well the 2010s for me.
Excellent fucking decade.
The other decades I was miserable and depressed.
So there wasn't much competition from those.
But this was like a honestly just a pretty much clean upswing across the decade for me.
I mean there's rough patches in different areas.
But like the overall experience is like pretty much as good as I've had it right now.
So I'm feeling pretty good about going into 2020.
It's a little like oh man this decade was almost too good.
Could it really be better?
Or will it inevitably get worse?
But who knows.
I'm going to try to make it better.
You know one particular aspect that is a definite decline.
Okay actually you know what this is fascinating because I don't know if you guys talked about like our Christmas time
and visiting the folks or anything.
But me and Ben were back at our parents place for a little bit.
You know Ben gets there I think a little more regularly than I do.
But going back there like my parents live in a wonderful house in excuse me in like I guess you'd call it a suburb
of relatively rural Massachusetts near the Cape.
So it's like a beautiful location.
You know it's cold as Massachusetts is.
But it's a great house.
You know they've been saving up their old lives.
They've been very financially responsible.
So they've got a great little place there.
Very similar to our old house.
But like when I'm there I feel the icy grip of my father's authority
wrapped around my fucking throat.
And it is suffocating.
It is truly suffocating.
Nothing is harder than going back to living under your family in my opinion.
It's so true.
And one example like we've had so many.
Our dog Sessho sleeps with us like in our bed on the end most of the time.
I'm always fucking kicking him because he's leaning against me.
I kick the shit out of that dog every now while I'm sleeping.
But generally it's nice.
But like it was unthinkable that the dogs would even be upstairs.
And like while it was funny we all got we all drank and we were all having a good time.
And like in like on the night of Christmas or whatever.
Grace brings up my parents dog Beanie and like sleeps with her in the bed.
And like it wasn't like a huge deal.
But like that was something unthinkable in our youth.
And I think my dad was at least mildly off put by that reality which is just.
I get it.
You know you understand the reasons for it.
You gotta put you gotta fuck with your parents.
You gotta do it.
Like I mean speaking personally I you know my relationship with my parents is such that I respect them.
But I will also just dig into them if they you know are being annoying or you know or making my life more difficult.
So you know when I'm around my my family like it's not that my my dad's not really a problem.
He's also kind of off in his own world and just a 80 D reading his phone or whatever.
Like everybody else is the ones you have to like snap into into focus and organization.
So you know I try to basically be like all right I'm the man of the house now bitch everybody's gonna listen to me you know.
As much as I can just because like yeah being in a in a being used to being your own you know man of the house I do what I fucking want.
Everything's on my schedule in my terms and then you go to some you know either your parents or you know when I go to May's parents house which is more often by far.
Which she doesn't mind at all because you know she's not usually the one setting all the timetables and everything anyways.
But when I'm at her dad's house it's just like well I am no longer in control so I just kind of like completely let go you know.
I just like achieve a Zen state and I just turn my brain off as best I can and veg veg around.
Yeah right approach.
It's the right approach.
Being at your parents place you just kind of give your permission to just ignore everything just like you know whatever they're taking care of it.
Don't even think.
Not my house.
Not my problem.
Oh you guys can't decide what you want to do.
Well I don't care what we do so I'll be over here.
I'm not going to argue.
I'm not going to sit around and fight with everybody.
I'm not going to try to take any authority.
Y'all figure shit out.
I mean I'm just a kid.
I'm just a baby.
I haven't talked about so many times like when you're a content creator or whatever like all your time could be devoted to that.
But like this is why I noticed like there's a couple of aspects like I rarely think about like how to have fun like actively.
Like sure I'll veg out and watch a movie just to like distract myself.
But when I'm on vacation anywhere that's when I like I exercise more.
I like actively do fun relaxing things more like with intent and therefore I enjoy them more because I'm like I can't even do work even if I fucking want to.
So I have to find enjoyable things to do.
So it's it's good.
I don't know.
It's a good thing to have for me.
It can be hard depending on where you are to find things to do.
I mean like I said if I'm at like a maze house for instance you know yeah first of all it's in Rochester.
It's a frozen tundra.
There's snow everywhere because we went for Thanksgiving and I did drive around a bit.
But like when we were our plan when we went was like oh we're going to go all over town.
We're going to like revisit everywhere we've been.
But it's like when you're trying to also do things with other people it's just like you can't force anything.
You know it's not so simple as like all right everybody in the fam we're all going to go to this place at seven o'clock and that's what we're going to do.
It's like somebody's going to be like I'm not going to show up and say I can do eight and then it's just like you know what we're just going to hang out at your dad's house to let people come and go as they please.
You know like I'm not going to fucking try to do anything.
So I had a good time though.
Yeah I mean I had a great time too.
But like you know we were talking about like I don't know we all gave ourselves each other our little gifts.
I mean I got like my parents like some chocolates and stuff with a whole session of diarrhea sagas famously everyone knows but whatever.
So like the gifts don't really matter anymore.
So we were talking about like maybe for next Christmas just doing like a destination holiday or something.
I mean you know we put out Hawaii or who knows where we could go.
Hold on.
Are you telling me Nate that you told a story about a diarrhea saga on this podcast and it was not the title of one of the episodes.
What are we doing.
I guess that's a fair point.
It's not any of our diarrhea.
That's right.
I mean how long did the story go on for.
I never think it was that long.
I think that's why the story is just that Seshio ate some chocolate and got diarrhea.
Yeah in a nutshell.
Well you can boil any story down to a boring story.
I mean what difference does it make right.
We name the podcast always after one thing in three hour discussion.
Diarrhea Saga.
That's a title.
Perhaps he's right.
Who suggests the titles these days.
Thought that would be off putting.
I don't know.
You know I didn't correct him.
No off putting is what we is on brand for the PCP.
Well that's true.
Anyway Seshio ate chocolate.
Got diarrhea everywhere.
It's a nightmare.
It still haunts this place to this day.
It's a good thing he survived.
Now that I think about it we could easily change the name of our podcast to Diarrhea Saga.
And I don't think it would be a bad idea.
We're already the poop craps denators podcast.
So you know we have a storied history of poop related stories.
We should do the poop episode and just go all in.
I'm definitely down.
That's a great idea.
I can't believe we never did that actually.
Have we done that?
Yeah we've done hygiene and I think that was discussed but not at any length.
So I don't know.
Poop episode is genuinely a great idea and we should do it.
It's a real money maker.
You know what?
You're not wrong.
People in the comments will finally be satiated.
They'll finally stop clamoring.
Easily talk for three hours.
I bet we could rope Jesse into that one too.
I bet we could do it.
Oh I hope.
I mean I don't think we could do it without him.
I think it would be unright.
It would be.
It would be a wrong.
Uncool.
I'm ready.
Every comment would be where's Jesse.
Okay well let's toss that one out and see which fish we can reel in from our little pond here.
Oh I was going to say though.
This is kind of unreliable.
I was just talking about vacations or whatever.
So me and Michelle were talking about we're probably going to take another trip out relatively
soon to see her folks in Hawaii and like generously they are like I don't know like her dad got
some money so like he's willing to pay for the tickets but like because it's like it's
not during the holidays.
We were thinking about like in February sometime that's like the prices are like so discounted.
It's going to be probably like 12 to 1300 or so for like both of us for a round trip
which is way better than it has been previously so that's pretty sick.
But like when I'm there I cannot wait because I can't do work there and I have to relax
and I have to do fun activities.
I don't know and I'm just going to go surfing in the middle of fucking winter when it's
like hell here in Cincinnati and I'll be able to escape the horrible lifestyle that we have
there.
Oh you know what I was making a point about that which was just that like the environment
we live in here is so much shittier than like the house I grew up in in you know back east
with my parents or like obviously when we take a trip to Hawaii or anything like that
and like this is the one way that my life has like gotten worse I would say.
Right now me and Michelle live in a decent apartment in Cincinnati it's fine.
We're in the ghetto which sucks.
This very day I was walking around just walking sesho and like he's just pooping.
He's holding a bag to pick up the poop and like a lady drives by and just yells at me
and says like hey you can't let him poop there like on a neighbor's lawn.
I think she doesn't think that I live here because I'm white and this is like an all black neighborhood
basically.
But I'm just like oh no I have a bag and she's like that's still rude and I just yell why.
Why?
And she just drives off before answering the question.
She had no fucking answer.
No I mean I'm prepared.
I will not leave a mark.
I'm being very responsible.
This is my neighborhood.
But I mean people you know.
What do you recommend doing about the fact.
What do you recommend I do about the fact that our next door neighbor lets their dog
seemingly shit all over our yard.
I'm pretty sure that's illegal.
It may that would probably count as littering.
I think you should you should in a friendly way if you haven't talked to him about it
before I would I would fucking never spoken to them in any way.
Okay.
I think here's what you should do.
You should.
This is what I would do.
I would actually get a like a friend gift kind of thing like a pie just like and go over
and introduce yourself first because you want to get off the right foot and be like hey
we're neighbors never came over just never from the time but like here's a little gift
you know we move into the neighborhood just want to you know be friendly neighbors.
It's been six months.
I think.
It's never too late.
Just do what I did.
Just get high on Molly and go over to your neighbor's house at four in the morning knock on the door.
Easy peasy.
I'm trying to get a solution.
Yeah.
Don't and ruin any.
All right.
Hold on.
What do you think of this idea that I had.
I had an idea of putting a sign in the yard or on the porch.
No.
Don't do it.
Okay.
All right.
No.
Finish your plan.
All right.
Well I was going to have a sign that says if your dog shits in my yard I'm going to
eat your dog.
Okay.
Look that's funny and I like it but what that won't do is make your neighbors like
you more.
I don't want them to like me.
I want them to make their dogs stop shitting in my yard.
I also thought about just putting up an electric fence.
The two problems are one and the same.
I think those two problems are linked because if they, if they, right now you're a faceless
nameless creature who lives in this thing and you're not a human being to them.
But if they know you and they know your name and they don't think about you at all.
What if I took a shit on their porch in the middle of the night.
Well you'll just start a gang war.
You'll start a shit war.
A shit flinging war.
I like where that's going.
Which would be good.
I don't want my speed.
I'm telling you.
This is what you do.
Apple pie shit.
You put on your Sunday, you put on your Sunday best pajama pants and you trot yourself over
there and you knock on the door and you say, hi, I'm, I'm Mr. Digi bro.
You may know me for my wonderful, my little pony reviews.
And you introduce yourself and you say, hey, you know, hey, I'm going to be honest.
There's a little bit of an ulterior motive now that we've met.
I'm just wondering if your dog's pooping lawn.
I just wanted to kindly ask if that's you.
This is, no.
I don't feel like this will even work.
They're going to think you're a fucking little bitch who buys things for people who let their
dog shit in their yard.
They will appreciate the courtesy and the neighborliness.
I guarantee you they're not thinking about the fact that their dog shits in your yard.
They will not, they will not connect those two events and they might, until you explicitly
make a thing out of it.
I mean, I'm just going to burn their house down.
You don't, you don't go in hot saying like, hey, your dog shouldn't hear, stop that,
because it might not even theoretically be their dog.
You phrasing the form of a question, I would say.
I think you should.
But I would, I would talk to them.
And it doesn't have to be, it could be perfectly nice.
You could make a friend in the act.
I, I think.
I don't want to be friends with those people.
I know.
I want to drive a monster truck to their house.
It opposes our generation's, you know, state of mind.
We don't like to do these things, but.
It's not about what I like.
They just seem like, you know, those people.
You know what I mean?
Are they normos?
Disgusting normies?
I don't even know.
Boomers?
I actually have, I can't like picture them well enough to think what, what I think they
are.
Well, fair enough.
You gotta open your heart.
You gotta open your heart, did you?
Well, I live, I live in the fucking city.
I don't know any of my neighbors and we all just have a general animosity towards each
other, which is unfortunate.
That's fucked up.
You know.
That's fucked up, man.
I don't like it.
I, yeah, but I'm not going to do anything about it because I am a loser and I just
stay in my apartment.
And that's, that's life.
That's life.
What a nightmare.
I could knock on these fucking people's doors and introduce, like if I lived in a suburb,
I would do it, but I live in the ghetto.
So I'm going to, I'm going to avoid that.
All right.
Here's non sequitur, but I'm interested in you guys' thoughts on this and the audience's
thoughts on this idea.
I, I brought it up in the chat the other day, but nobody responded.
So I had this, this vision of like what if the PCP was given like a budget to make a
show?
Like if we were given like one million dollars.
Like Sam Hyde was back in the day?
Like even, I was thinking more like when Casey Neistat got funded to make that show that
they sold to HBO for two million bucks.
You know what I mean?
Like just having somebody who was like, who looked at our group of people and said, I
have money.
I'm going to give you guys money to make something and we're going to try to sell it to a network.
Right?
Like if we had a budget of even just like half a million dollars, maybe not even that much.
One, three IRL arena.
That idea alone, I think proves that we've got chops to do cool shit.
Yeah.
Well, here's my idea.
All right.
So if we have a big enough budget, what we're going to do is first we buy a house outright
with the budget, then we just spend like a month near this house.
Like we can either stay in it, around it, wherever we have all this money to fuck with.
So all the money is going to be about keeping everybody in the vicinity of this house for
a month as we just destroy it.
Like just completely demolish this house.
So like we would start the first week would mostly be us like live streaming and taking
behind the scenes footage as we decorate the house.
So first we would just like paint all over the walls, floors everywhere, draw shit all
over the place, fucking just do whatever we want to the place to make it into like a bunch
of sets.
And then we would film a whole bunch of shows on these sets and in the process of course
just destroy them as soon as we're done, get tons of footage of us just breaking this
house until finally when we're done, we just lay it to the fucking ground like we either
burn it down or demolish it.
Bulldoze it.
Yeah.
You know, I like this.
I have a pitch.
I think we should paint a daisy on the front door or on the top of the house and we name
this project Daisy's Destruction 2 and what is that in reference to?
You don't know.
You don't know Daisy's Destruction is this horrible like, like I think it's like a pedophilic
like a snuff film about like the execution.
All right.
Well, let's not name it.
I still think it's a solid idea, but I think we should name it Diarrhea Saga.
Yeah, it's no Daisy's Destruction, but I guess it'll do the job.
Yeah.
Well, it sounds amusing.
I would do it if someone wants to come along and give us, how much you think we have to
get for this?
I think we could do this for 30 grand if we get a small house, maybe 40 grand.
I have no idea.
It depends on how much it costs to outright buy a house that we have no intentions of
reselling.
And we could do that in the middle of nowhere, like cheap real estate.
Right.
That was what I was thinking is it would be because down in, you know, in like Western
Virginia or North Carolina, there's just tons of these houses that are just isolated.
They're just on random plots of land in the middle of fucking nowhere, you know?
So yeah, we could easily find a house that nobody cares about on a plot of land nobody
cares about and just lay waste to it.
I think I'd have to look into the legality of all that, but you know, I think it would
definitely be a hell of a lot of fun.
I mean, I definitely agree.
But you know, that reminds me of, go on.
We would probably risk serious injury if we were actually like, like breaking the house
down to the point that like, to the point that like, anything was like actually falling
apart.
We would be in serious physical danger.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
We just got to be careful about the structural integrity of rooms that we're in from top
to bottom.
We have to go top to bottom.
If the things we break are more like walls and we start on the top floor and then make
our way down, that wouldn't necessarily interfere with the structural integrity like, like, like
you say.
Actually, it would be kind of funny if maybe we were like only allowed in like the attic
for a while and like we had to like destroy it as fast as possible and only when there
was just was no attic left.
Are we allowed to go down?
Yeah.
I mean, I was thinking more like using like the destruction of the house over the course
of the span would be more minor, like more like just wrecking things inside the house.
Wrecking the house itself would come more towards the end because we want the whole house to
be a bunch of sets that we can film shit on, you know, but like just make a huge mess.
Kind of like what we did with the plebe and the weeb, you know, where there's at the end,
it was a fucking just total disaster zone, you know, but just do that except also we
tear down the whole structure of the building at the end.
Yeah.
Depending on the format, maybe we could all wear destructo cams and kind of have it, you
know, Radcon Arena, IRL style.
I imagine like you watch you watch it out of sequence and just like some episodes like
there's a door there and other episodes, there's not.
Sometimes there are more windows than others, you know, something when did the when did
the rug?
Haruhi, Suzumiya release style.
Yeah.
I just I always think back to there's this series from I think vice called thumbs up.
I might have talked about this before about two guys who like hitchhiked their way across
the country and there's one bit in one of the early episodes where they stop off in
like a ghost town because there's all these, you know, there's always like random derelict
buildings and towns on the railroad tracks that aren't used anymore.
So they decided to just like sleep in one of these random derelict buildings.
It's like all covered in graffiti and stuff.
And then the next morning they're like, now let's tear shit up and they just like pull
out a gun and start just like shooting windows out and just like they kick a whole wall over
and it's just like, oh man, you can fucking do whatever you want to a house that nobody
cares about.
Like, that's true.
I don't know about the legality of firing guns randomly inside house, probably fine.
If you own the house, you could definitely do it, depending on the state you live in.
I'm worried about like the bullet travel, but fuck it, whatever.
I'm sure it's fine.
It sounds like a great time to me.
Fucking Hunter Thompson used to fire guns on his property all the fucking time.
That's fair.
As I'm sure many people still do.
You know, this reminds me of a thing I've been thinking about, which is the premise
of this thing.
Which incidentally, if we're doing that show, got to buy some guns.
Probably yes.
Got to buy some real guns.
I was thinking about, you were saying like the rocket launcher, if we can find one.
That would be nice.
The initiating thing that has to be there is like an investment from like some benefactor
or studio or something like that.
I'm all for that.
But what I was thinking about was like, it's interesting to note how most of us are out
here doing our shit and we're trying to survive on Patreon.
At this moment, I mean, let's be real.
The only one who's truly succeeded financially in this model is Digi.
I'm working on it.
I'm hoping to get there.
But, you know, not there yet, but whatever.
We're working on it.
The rest of us are kind of scraping out various degrees of what you call survival in quotation
at, you know, at a lowly state.
But it seems to me like the dream of Patreon and all these things is like the people fund
you because they like your work and they keep you afloat, blah, blah, blah, and we're all
working on that.
That's what I'm trying to do too.
But it seems that like the vast majority of people require like, there are like these
little micro-sponsorships that go around now from like fucking Audible and stuff and that's
fine.
But like there's lots of like big donors necessary for even what seems like like indie businesses.
When you look into it a little bit, you find out that there's like a large, like a billionaire
or like a large corporation like funding the success of this business.
And when I learned that, it's like, oh, I guess they didn't.
I mean, they didn't really make it just on like the strength of their product.
I mean, I don't want to be an asshole because some of these started before Patreon had distanced
stuff.
I think it would be almost unreasonable to expect anybody doing anything that involves
pre-production to not be backed by somebody.
The kind of work that we do has so little pre-production that and even when we have to do it, we do
a whole Kickstarter for it.
We'll do a Kickstarter just to fly people out to a location to do work that doesn't
require any setup.
But I really think that investment is the only way you're going to get like the ability
to do something bigger than what you can just do by yourself with your own money.
And I mean, technically Kickstarter is meant to be an investment platform.
The idea is that the people supporting you are investors in this thing just to some degree.
But even if they're not getting like money back from it, but like I do have to think
that...
I was thinking about this recently that it's baffling to me that there is not more investment
going on like in YouTube, in internet creation.
And maybe it's just because of the fact that it has worked so little in the past.
Like that, you know, previous times they've tried to have YouTubers do that kind of stuff.
It just hasn't worked.
And most YouTubers just think, oh, well, I make way more money just doing my own daily
content instead.
But like I think that what people are missing is that the people who need the investments
are the smaller channels.
Like the big ones who already have millions of subs who already are proven successes,
they don't need to do anything that involves pre-production.
They're already successful.
But like the potential in let's say a group like the PCP, and I don't even know if we
would succeed or if anybody would care about the product we produce.
But like a group like ours will very much conform to what we have, to what we can do.
When we do Radcon, we do basically whatever we can afford and whatever we have the time
for with the people and the place that we have.
So like a group like ours, if we did have an investment from somebody, you know, we
would definitely find a way to use it to make something unique.
And I think it's surprising that there's not more like talent scouts trying to like
search the internet for people who could do things like that.
But I don't know, maybe it would have to be us who would have to approach somebody about
it.
Maybe we could find some fucking freaky billionaire who loves anime and just wants to give us
a million dollars to destroy our house.
I know Baron Trump's a big fan of the animes.
Oh fuck!
I gotta reach out to Baron Trump.
I'm not even joking.
That's my 2020s resolution is to get Baron Trump to bankroll a PCP house destruction project.
I guess I wonder like for them, like how they would get a return on investment with
them.
I mean, when you're a billionaire, your concern is probably at least preserve the money I
currently have, which seems relatively easy if you're investing in smart ways.
Our production would be so cheap, though, like we wouldn't need, all we need is to be
able to buy a house and destroy it and maybe, you know, buy materials that we could use
for it.
But we're not going to want anything crazy, like, I think that as long as they could
sell our show to, like, anywhere, it would be fine, you know, like if they could even
sell the show to a network or an internet network or something for the same price they
spent on doing it, then, you know, profits would be guaranteed.
But see, that's the X factor right there, because of course the thing we haven't really
talked about that I wanted to bring is like, when you do this, there's two separate issues.
One, there's kind of a like, this doesn't matter as much, but like I personally feel
a little squirmy.
I still want to do it.
I still love to get a sponsor for the PCP, and we should actively pursue one, I think,
one that we all like and are comfortable promoting.
There's just no reason not to, in my opinion.
But whatever, it doesn't matter, like, but when you have investments of this kind in
any capacity, like, not morally, but like in terms of like self-esteem, I start to be
like, oh, like, I guess I didn't do it all myself.
I guess I needed a big, big dick to swing in and help me.
Okay, but that doesn't matter.
But even more importantly than that, is this idea of like, like you said, if like a sponsor
is helping you, and is like, involved to any degree, and is helping you like pitch the
product to like a network or something, or even if you just have someone over your head
at all who like, wants to see how production is going, you suddenly get into the murky
realm of like editorial control, and what, of course, what you would want is like some
sort of agreement that the people get to do whatever they want.
What I want is just money.
Just give me a fat slab of money and let me do what I want.
I mean, I just feel like it's inevitable if people put in money, they're going like fucking,
you know, Kickstarter back or whatever.
Of course, it's right on in black and white that like, when you pledge, you're expecting
a product.
And if it like, as long as you deliver what it says, they should be relatively satisfied.
But like, what if the product is just not as good as they wanted, people could get mad.
I mean, I don't, I don't remember the total saga of mighty number nine, but to my mind,
the biggest problem with mighty number nine was that it just wasn't that great a game
and was delayed a lot.
I think.
And also the people who made it were insulting to the fans of the thing.
I don't give a shit about that, but I get why people do care.
That's, I mean, I mean, I understand.
It's like, what, what is their development of this game, a fucking hug box, or you need
to have your, you know, feelings, respect of the whole, you don't want to disrespect
your investors.
These people paid money, you know, to support your thing, and then you turn around and you
shit on them.
They had wrong think they were damn white sis patriarchal mails.
That's not what I'm talking about.
It's just like you don't insult the people who support you, you know, you're not wrong.
You're not wrong.
Okay.
So that's fair.
But like, so even with like a Kickstarter model, you, you still have like a quote unquote
boss over your head.
And when it, let's say you have this billionaire investor, it just seems like inevitably, and
this is the thing that so many like fucking the Pink Floyd song have a cigar or whatever,
you get pulled into the smoke filled room and you sign the contract to get the money
to make your album.
But then when it comes to make the album and you make your song, you're all loved, they
say, ooh, I don't exactly like the message behind this song.
Why don't you tweak this and ooh, you know, I don't like this thing.
I'm just going to shelve all this work.
Bottom line, I would not sign.
First of all, I probably wouldn't sign a contract at all.
But if I did, I would have to be that I really knew exactly what it was, you know, like,
I, like you said, you don't just work with any sponsor.
You work with the ones that you actually think are good.
So it would be difficult.
It wouldn't just be a matter of finding somebody who's willing to throw money at us.
It would be willing.
I mean, just considering this.
I mean, why would anyone throw money at us unless they already knew what we made?
I mean, I mean, currently, currently Googling sponsors that will let me say the N word
and trying to find if we're even, we're even on target for this.
That who, who can say?
I mean, yeah, I guess that's fair.
But I feel like considering like the group and like kind of we make money here on the
show and doing what we do, but like still relative low amounts, digits in the strongest
position to like negotiate because he's making the most.
But like if someone came to me right now and said, hey, Nate, trying to make it as a
contact, don't sign the contract.
Well, I'm just I wouldn't, but I'm just saying that like there sure is a strong
temptation when like your financial problems will go away if you sign this contract.
But now you have a totally new, a new problem of, you know, selling your soul and not be
able to make what you want possibly.
What are they going to do?
But I'm just saying it's tempting.
What happens if you break the contract?
I mean, typically with things like that, you like sometimes you have like, I forget
the name of the clause, but like, like you aren't allowed to do work in that field for
like X number of years.
That's bullshit.
That's not real.
That's not a real.
That's not a real thing.
It's impossible.
How could they stop you?
I mean, I'm pretty sure it exists.
I guess I could be wrong.
But I mean, it could just be the bad man the other day.
I would think that they would blacklist you from getting jobs in that field.
But the very OK.
There's got to be some sort of general repercussions to breaking contracts.
I would assume I think it's mostly you would get blacklisted.
You probably get fined.
You would not be able to work under them.
Isn't yours anymore, probably.
And you don't need money.
They can't find you.
They're not a how would they find?
I don't understand.
I don't I don't get it.
OK, would they just take it out of your next paycheck?
Well, they just stop paying you, right?
That's that's the problem.
So you just get it all up front.
What if you just get it all up front and say, huh, nice job, losers.
OK, but here's just a thought.
If you're responsible, this wouldn't be a problem.
But maybe you've spent some of the money on production costs or whatever.
And if you now decide, oh, well, I'm not going to finish this project.
They're like, OK, give us back the money you spent.
And then it's like.
Let's not even speculate on how this works.
And so none of us fucking idea.
But, you know, generally, I just say, don't sign the contract.
DIY forever.
I haven't signed any contracts ever up to this point doing except,
I guess, the YouTube Partner Program and, I guess,
Patreon's agreements and Kickstarter's for those things.
But those are, I mean, generally pretty good.
And the YouTube.
So yeah, I would definitely consider for all of those.
I've been. And we've all signed in blood.
We all exist only at the whims of Amazon
and Google and only for their for their benefit.
Yeah, that's pretty much true.
Yeah, well, Twitch on Twitch, at least, yeah, to a degree.
Well, I don't know.
I mean, I'm I would love to have a sponsor personally,
but I just hope to find one that is reasonable.
I'm still working on the Nattaku, dude.
New time. Yeah, I mean, you know, I was watching some
county care videos lately, probably right.
I was I was watching Count Dankula videos, his Mad Lad series,
which I find interesting.
I fucking hate that guy.
How dare you?
OK, fair enough.
But I mean, he's he just he didn't want to.
He's awful. He's a monster.
But go on. OK, sure.
Yeah, how dare he make his dog do something funny?
What a nightmare.
How dare he tell a joke?
Hey, hey, fuck you.
He did other things beside that one thing.
OK, so some real shit takes on Twitter the other day.
He's a meme, Lord.
OK, guys, let's not get it.
I don't care about this at all.
The point I was making was that he was shilling
Raid Shadow Legends on his videos.
Oh, boy, I'm ready to sign up.
And I like it just makes me be like, oh, I hate this video now.
As long as that's I mean, I feel that way every day.
And almost like fucking probably 50% of all videos I click on.
I'm just like, if I have to hear about fucking Nord VPN
or Dollar Shave Club, I'm going to kill somebody.
Yeah, yeah, I have the same thing was just like,
I mean, you know, of the app for the phone, right?
Yeah, I think they offered everybody.
Yeah, they even reached out to me.
I politely declined because I don't like Amino
and I don't want to support them.
I've got a fucking VPN guy.
I'm asking me I've never heard of before.
I don't know. Can these people solve my financial problems to any degree?
That'd be nice.
Is their product worth shilling in order to do so?
I don't know.
I mean, I haven't done it.
I just who will save me?
Who will be a good sponsor?
Huel, please, I love your product.
I believe in you. Believe in me.
Let me show for you your new, your new Huel Black product
that has less carbs and more protein is the perfect thing
for the modern lifting man.
Let me let me sell it for you.
I got to fucking reach out to those guys again.
I don't know, whatever. It doesn't matter.
These are complicated, moral quandaries.
I feel one day I will find the solution.
I would love just to make more money,
imagine, on Patreon so I don't feel any desire to do these things.
But that's not happening right now.
So fuck me, I guess.
Well, she well, shit.
I pretty much sums it up.
I don't know. Left turn.
Anybody got anything else they want to discuss?
Christmas times or?
We're ready to have somebody get cool gifts.
We already discussed that.
It's your turn if you want to say something.
I got some wonderful new boots.
I got my Christmas shoes.
I put my money down on the counter and got Christmas shoes.
And it was great.
They are wonderful boots and they have this beautiful zipper on the side.
That's it. I love my boots.
They're my favorite thing I got at Christmas.
My Christmas shoes.
I got a onesie and I feel the same about it.
I love my onesie.
I got Michelle a onesie that you seems to like, which is very nice.
Yes, that's good.
But tragically, it doesn't have a butt flap.
And I was thinking about this.
That probably is really annoying if you have to go to the bathroom
to not have a butt flap.
That is inconvenient.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, that's life, baby.
In the big city, no butt flaps.
It's tragedy strikes constantly.
All right, I'm out of shit to say, I guess.
Anybody else got anything we can do that we got the voicemails.
That's why I spent the beginning of this podcast.
Go for it, dog.
Go for it, dude.
I just want to reiterate.
Fuck you.
It's not about the dog thing.
Count Ankyla's a bad man in many ways.
Oh, no, bad man said.
And there you go.
He's a very bad.
But he looks cool.
I don't understand how he's bad.
Does he look cool?
He's got a commie star in him, Ben.
You should love that.
No, he doesn't.
Yes, he does.
He has a tattoo of the fucking hammer and sickle on a big star.
Yep.
Does. OK.
Is it ironic?
Well, it wasn't at the time, but he's changed his belief since then.
So now it's just, you know, an epic goof on himself.
I don't know.
All right. OK, whatever.
I know you guys don't care.
It's fine.
Go on.
Yeah, that I know I am that's fair, Ben.
I shouldn't have jumped and assumed it was the dog thing.
That's just the thing I know the most.
So fair enough.
You can have other reasons to dislike.
And he wasn't trying to be an asshole here.
There's that.
I haven't seen his tweets, but from what I've seen,
I haven't seen anything too awful.
He's he's real bad.
I know he's a meme, Lord.
He says offensive things.
I hurt.
He he likes fascism.
He really hates.
He really does not like fascism.
He really hates justice.
Oh, my God.
He's definitely he's definitely like conservative ghoul.
Which makes you which makes you a bad person,
which makes you a bad person.
I like how you're like absolutely wrong.
No, I don't really think so.
I really don't.
I think so.
OK, well, I don't fucking care.
I mean, he ran he ran for UKIP, right?
He ran for UKIP.
And then he left because they were stupid.
OK, all right, that's true.
That's fine.
It's all good.
Well, that's luckily for you.
The political discourse is about to be solved.
We've got speak by voice mails.
We need to listen up.
We've got a couple of voice mails
that are all about this issue.
Our first message is from the one and the only
centrist Sam is calling in with everything
we need to know about politics.
Let's hear what he has to say.
Take it away, Sam.
Hey, guys, it's me, centrist Sam.
Yay.
Want to know what I think about politics?
I do.
Please.
What are they?
Great.
Oh, my God.
We're clarifying.
He's right.
What are they?
He's so right.
OK, let's not pause on this.
We've got to keep going because this is followed
by a hero of the people.
Leftist Larry is following up on this message.
Let's see what he has to say.
How many of these fucking guys are there?
Endless.
All right, Larry, what have you got for us?
Hey, guys, it's me.
Leftist Larry.
Want to know what I think about white people?
No, I don't.
What are they?
Oh, damn.
You're saying all the right things, Larry.
You got me, but I didn't expect it somehow.
That's incredible.
All right, and now.
I thought he would never go for it.
It was brave and true.
What a brave take.
We've got a final message from our girls.
I think I've heard enough.
Right wing Richard has to balance the scales here.
Let's hear what our friend Richard
has to say on the other side of the political spectrum.
Rich, Dick, take it away.
Hey, guys, it's me.
Right wing Richard.
Want to know what I think about North Korea?
Thanks, Rich.
No, what are they?
That's it.
No, he did a subversion.
He did a subversion.
I guess he didn't blew up North Korea.
Nobody likes North Korea.
That's something we can all agree on.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
I don't know.
I think he's fine.
Consider the literacy rate.
Consider the hospital system.
I don't know.
Something, something.
They're pretty bad.
Is this a hot take that North Korea is bad?
North Korea?
Not that bad.
I don't think so.
Well, I don't know.
How much can you blame the people of North Korea
as opposed to the leaders of that?
It's not as bad as you imagine, but it's all so bad.
That's what I hear.
It's impossible.
I mean, I don't like the idea of my family being gulagged
if I speak against the state.
And like three generations of my family,
do they breed them in captivity?
Don't they have like a total media blackout
from media outside of North Korea?
That's not as true as it seems.
That's what I mean by like, there's stuff that you hear.
But if you investigate it, it's like halfway between the truth
and not.
But I mean, it is still, you know,
it's still North fucking Korea.
I mean, it is what it is.
You know, I don't remember the details,
but didn't Kim Jong-un like kill his brother who was like
on the run or something?
Didn't that happen?
I have no idea.
You know what?
I will say this, at least in the main city of North Korea,
they have one thing that we need to copy,
which is that their buildings are all like pink and blue
and shit.
That sounds nice.
They paint all their buildings and it looks really good.
Is North Korea saying trans rights?
Guys.
Oh my god.
North Korea just said trans rights.
It's good.
Thank you, North Korea.
You know what?
You wear, huh?
What?
The buildings are pink and blue, man.
The buildings are pink and blue.
So obviously they're saying trans rights.
We need to get a Kim Jong-un bumper sticker.
It's just his face.
It says trans rights under it.
Maybe we can get a nice picture of the city.
Yeah, that sounds great.
That sounds great.
All right, moving over.
OK, here we go.
We've got an open letter to a certain Conrad.
Let's hear a certain magical Conrad.
Who the fuck is Conrad?
To no one knows, but let's hear him out.
Go.
Conrad is either the bravest person alive or the stupidest.
His fucking obsession with trying each and every restaurant
surrounding whatever place he happens to be absolutely
baffles me.
The first Avengers movie came out in 2012, seven years ago.
And the post-credits scene, we find our heroes enjoying
a delicious-looking meal of lukewarmah.
Flash forwards to now, seven years later.
I go into this shop I've been driving past in my town
for 20 years or so, where I pay $9 for an underheated, thin
breaded, autistic taco-looking motherfucker
with crunchy chicken and overbearing cucumber,
which I painfully vomit up that night,
a vomit seven fucking years in the making.
And I just can't fathom how he's
how he can waste his life like this.
And it fills me with inboten rage.
Well, I mean, it sounds like he saw the Avengers
and it incepted him to want a schwarma,
but he did not try it until recently,
and it made him puke his brains out.
First of all, I've never tried a schwarma.
I don't really fuck with Greek food that much.
The word sounds terrible.
I don't want to have one.
It doesn't sound.
I don't like euros.
In general, I don't like that weird sour cream.
Does anyone else associate the word schwarma with swamp ass?
In my mind, the two terms have overlapped completely.
And I think of them at the same time.
OK, maybe just a second.
Well, now I will.
But I mean, OK, I don't think that guy,
it's not that I like literally systematically
start from my house and in a radial motion
go to every restaurant nearby.
I try out all the ones that sound good.
If I'm on Google Maps and it's like two stars,
I'm like, hmm, don't know what you
have to do to get two stars on Google Maps,
but it can't be good.
But I mean, there's hundreds and hundreds of restaurants
in any given city.
Well, I mean, this guy's hot take is, yeah, hot take.
Don't try new things.
Yeah, fair.
I have never had an experience as bad as what
that guy sounds like he had.
So I'm sorry that your one roll of the dice
came up snake eyes.
Me and Michelle, when my parents were in town,
I mean, did you, when you were here,
we went to like that great steak place, the fuck what's
it called, the precinct, right?
So a famous steak place in Cincinnati.
It's fantastic.
It's expensive.
When my parents were here, I upped the ante
to the number one rated fucking place in Cincinnati,
which is the Orchard, it's some fucking,
it's a hotel restaurant and it is amazing.
Like, we all loved our food, but Michelle fucking puked
afterward because something just didn't sit right
at the most expensive fucking restaurant,
the number one rated place.
Like, maybe they undercooked something?
Probably just didn't agree with her.
I do feel like there's no account.
After a certain price point, there's just no real correlation
of quality to price.
That's not true.
Kind of.
It is true.
That is where God.
That is entirely dependent on the individual place
and the food.
I mean, you're playing for atmosphere here to a large,
like they got a live van going, it's the atmosphere.
It depends, cause like, I mean, there's some places where,
yes, everything is overpriced.
And then there's other places where it's not.
And I mean, you just gotta, you just gotta suss it out,
you know, with the, I mean, it's hard to do that
with like really expensive restaurants.
Like take a, you know, take a roll of the dice on that.
But I mean, I absolutely believe that there are,
you know, steak houses that are charging you $70,
where I will not like that steak as much as I'll like,
like, you know, $8 Thai food dish.
Like, I'm sure that's a thing.
Yeah, always possible.
I like all those YouTube videos that compare like the,
it's like the $20 billion Strativarius violin.
The Epicurious videos.
Versus like a $20.
I don't know who does them, but yeah,
anything comparing cheap shit versus expensive shit.
Well Epicurious does a show where it's like,
they'll have an expert in like mustard come on
and like test out cheap versus expensive mustard.
I like those.
Yeah, I watch all those.
It always comes out that like the price difference
does matter.
It's just not that it necessarily matters to you.
It's like, hey, yeah, you could definitely tell
the difference between these two things,
but the cheap one is still good.
You would still enjoy it.
There's no reason to spend $12 on noodles,
you know, like they'll often say shit like that.
But except for the steak episode,
that was the only one where the steak episode was like,
look, when it comes to steak, you know,
there are seven grades of beef.
And if you want to buy the highest grade beef,
it will cost you a fucking lot of money, you know.
Is it worth it at all in that case?
I mean, according to people who eat steaks, yes.
I mean, this was a huge argument on the old
biggest problem in the universe where
Maddox thought that any steak over $30 was not any different.
That like, it was $30 was the cap,
and Dick was like, no, like not at all.
Cause he goes to steak houses and, you know,
I would probably be like,
I probably could tell the difference between
like a $60 steak and a $30 steak,
but like, there's no way,
there's no way that I'd be like, boy,
sure, I'm glad I spent $30 extra on that steak.
Right, that's the rub is that like,
it is diminishing returns no matter what,
cause like, I mean, 80% of the way there
is just having steak at all, you know,
like that's most of the battle.
Consider the situation from the perspective
of a person with infinite money,
and then you have all like, of course,
sure, get the most expensive one.
Yeah, I mean, and not even just the most expensive,
but you could experiment with all the expensive ones
and figure out which one's actually the best, you know,
which is what I would do if I had like,
you know, if I was super rich
and I could just flip on whatever,
I would definitely try like every piece
of expensive cuisine, but I would never just like be,
oh, this one's the most expensive,
so that's where I'm going every time, you know,
or this is the most famous,
which is how a lot of people think.
If I was rich, if I had the money to do it,
I would get a personal chef to prepare me
both delicious and nutritionally,
macronutrient and micronutrient satisfying meals
for every meal of the day.
Oh, that would be, that would be the greatest gift.
That's my Kokoro wish.
Make it happen, people.
Okay, by going to patreon.com slash theprocrastiners,
or better yet, patreon.com slash bestcamer.
Okay, next voicemail we've got, who is this from?
This is, oh yeah, you have to get out Nate.
Okay, go.
Okay, so it's came to my attention
that something needs to be addressed,
so I just wanted to have a little pow out with you guys,
a little sit down if you will, you know, me, your dad.
Good.
Everybody says about how mage grew up
in this dystopian fucking nightmare hellhole,
but no one really mentions the fact
that Nate is living in one right now.
Yeah.
Especially in like Fairfield and like Over the Rhine
and shit like that.
That's true.
As kind of a little example,
just the other day in Coleraine,
a group of I think like 150 to probably like 180 underage teens
decided to have a battle royale at Northgate Mall.
I don't know, I'm not talking about no Fortnite bullshit,
I'm saying like an actual, they went in
and whooped each other's ass just because.
It sounds fucking awesome.
Not only that, but when I lived there,
I think I was like either nine or 10,
I was in Fairfield.
I was just riding my bike down the road,
you know, being a good little fucking boy
and I seen a guy, it was a bad drug deal,
but one guy stabbed another guy in the fucking neck.
Damn.
So yeah, point of me calling in
is just to kind of tell you guys,
get the fuck out of Cincinnati, Nate.
There are nice neighborhoods, but I don't live in them.
You don't have much nice to say about Cincinnati, Nate.
You know?
It's a fucking, first of all, ugly, ugly city, dirty,
grimy.
It looks nice from a distance.
It looks ghetto even in the parts that aren't ghetto.
It's way too spread out.
I thought Virginia Beach was spread out,
fucking Cincinnati is like another level.
Oh, I guess.
Nate drove like what, 25 minutes to the fucking Walmart?
There's one like 15, 20 minutes away, something like that.
It's not the closest in the world.
On average, if you have to drive anywhere,
how long will you be driving for?
I would say 10, 15 minutes, maybe 20 for things.
So for me, it's like 30 seconds.
It's like the average driving time, you know?
Okay, okay.
Well, I mean, you know, I don't like to encourage her
because I think it is bad for both of our psychological help,
but Michelle moved here from fucking Hawaii.
So naturally there was, which I'd like to think,
means she really cares and she really values my presence.
I guess so, she moved to the fucking ghetto.
I guess she was, right?
Yeah, and man, my first apartment, you saw it, Digi,
my first apartment, that's where Michelle moved in with me.
It was a sweltering hell of fucking-
It was a nightmare place,
but we lived there together for like six months
before we moved.
I cannot believe she did that, which again,
I guess she likes me, that's pretty cool.
But I don't like to encourage her,
but Michelle's like, Nate, this place kind of sucks,
and like we should definitely leave.
And now that I don't, my job doesn't tie me here,
but we should, we should in fact.
We're literally planning to do this, right?
Like we're planning to do a Kickstarter.
Yeah, this is the plan.
This is the plan.
Cansheds, move Nate out.
So if anybody heard that voicemail and was like,
wow, we need to get Nate the fuck out of there,
well, there's an easy way to do that.
It's called-
Set aside your pennies.
It's called five grand.
I'm keeping it at four, but yes.
Five would be nice.
It's called four grand.
All we need is four grand, get Nate out.
Somebody could probably fund that by themselves, honestly.
Russell, you're our main benefactor around these areas.
You want to just, somebody wants to drop me.
Just drop 4K on moving Nate out.
Next time I'm streaming, Russell, next time,
we can set aside rules.
You'll be a gasman.
Or anybody, so that we can, you know,
leave this open.
Only 400,000 bits will do it.
Indeed, well, right, 400,000, you're right, you're right.
Sounds good to me.
Mr. Beast, do you like to give people money?
Call in, call into the show.
Okay, anyway, let's move on to the next one.
Oh, okay, we've got speaking of Nate's streams.
We've got a message here from some mysterious individual
just called to the left, to the left.
Let's hear what he has to say.
Take it away.
A, B, C, B.
Sorry if you've heard this one before,
but voicemail god is feeling pretty fucking smug right now.
I just killed four of Nate's Pokemon in his Nuzlocke.
SMH, bro, took one step too far to the left, got fucked,
and I didn't kill a bad saint, so, yeah.
Anyways, get fucked.
Is this Sean?
This is Sean, a.k.a. voicemail god,
and a.k.a. my rival in this game.
I fucking hate that guy.
You know, let me just frame this,
because this is hilarious.
We gotta fucking, we gotta do something about him.
He killed you, Ben.
He killed you.
Yeah, first he stole,
first he stole my status as rival,
and then he killed me on top of it.
You know, it's funny, Ben.
Everyone was saying-
What does he have against me?
Well, he believes in capitalism.
It served him well to be the,
he believes in the free market,
and that's no good.
I guess so.
Well, you know, that lovely art of you and me,
together, my hoot hoot, Ben's saint,
and I, the trainer, going around, having a great time.
Everyone was saying, don't let Ben's saint near you.
He's whispering leftist ideology into your ear, Nate.
He's dragging you to the left.
Well, good thing I died, so.
I said, it's fine, it's fine, but then,
I mean, I don't know if you were actually there,
but literally, literally, in the game of Pokemon,
I was just wandering around the city,
getting ready to do the gym.
I took one step too far to the left.
It triggered, it triggered the fucking voicemail
god, Rival Battle, and I was slaughtered
by a level 18 croc knot,
or the second totodile level, who there is.
I'm glad.
Who's a nightmare.
You know what?
So, I learned my lesson.
I probably meant-
Don't let Ben whisper near.
Don't go too far left.
Even one step too far will kill you.
That sounds like something I would do, so.
I'm glad, yeah.
All right.
I died doing what I loved.
A radicalizing, radicalizing my fellow PCP members
and causing destruction.
Well, you know, he went out of martyr, I would say,
so congratulations, everybody.
We had a great time.
You know, and the good news is, it's now a real nuzlocke.
There has been the first genocide.
Things are getting serious now.
Oh, god, it's a nightmare.
Okay, moving on from that, we got two more left.
This one's from I'll Die on smart goals
for New Year's resolutions.
Okay, I'll Die, take it away.
Hey, Nate, so you were trying to remember an acronym
at the end of last episode for goal setting,
which was smart goals.
Some people may not know about it.
That's right.
I figured it's worth mentioning.
It stands for specific, measurable, attainable,
relevant, and time bound.
So something like I will lose this number of pounds
by this specific date,
which is what you're doing,
it gives you a metric of success.
It's relevant to something that actually benefit your life,
has a deadline to keep you motivated.
As opposed to I will exercise more,
which doesn't establish any point of action.
And once you say it, you're not actually
moving to anything.
If resolutions come up on the podcast,
you probably agree it's worth putting out there
in case it helps anyone out.
You don't even need to play this voicemail.
You can just write down the acronym
and bring it up if you want.
Or not if you don't want to,
or you could play the voicemail
and waste everyone's time.
Don't tell me what to do!
I think it's the end of it.
Or you could just thoroughly and not waste anyone's time.
That's all I'll buy.
I choose to do so.
Yes, it's great.
All right, hey, I put a little image in the thing
he said is like, whatever.
Relevant, as opposed to realistic,
doesn't matter, both are the same thing.
Yeah, smart goal.
That's what I was trying to think of last time.
Just like me, Ben and Digi, our goals are,
okay, my goal I think is good.
Work out three times a week,
for the month of January.
Like, that is attainable, that's specific,
and I don't have like a, it's time-bound.
I think it checks all the boxes.
This nebulous goal of stick to a diet
is perhaps a little vague,
but I think you and Tom know what you're doing,
so I'm not too worried about you.
But for other people who are starting something,
use these, use this as your measure.
It is, I learned, oh, you know what?
I was gonna say about this.
The first place I heard about smart goals
was from my boy, Scooby 1961,
my big, gay fitness god,
who I love like a father and a son,
and he's my favorite person in the world.
He's such a hero.
Did all this fitness shit for free.
And actually, you know what?
He was one of like literally one of the first YouTubers.
We know Nate, we know about Scooby, fuck.
I swear you've given this exact spiel many times before.
I'm not giving a full spiel.
I was just gonna say that,
did you know that this guy before YouTube existed,
he actually paid to host his videos
for people to download,
and when YouTube came out,
he was like, wow, I can't wait to save money
by not having to pay to host my fucking videos on YouTube.
Isn't that what everybody was thinking
when YouTube came out,
who had videos on the internet?
He's the oldest one I know.
Okay, it doesn't matter.
Anyway, there is actually news about Scooby,
I wanted to say, which was just that
it seems he is in fact retiring
from like fitness videos on YouTube,
and he's changing his channel to like,
it's like Scooby's travel vlogs,
which he's been doing for a long time,
and it's the fucking end of an era, it seems,
with like his fitness uploads,
and instead he's just kinda gonna be taking it easy
and relaxing more, and I just wanna give my thanks.
That dude's like, hold his balls, right?
He's in his 60s. He's in his 60s.
He's in his 60s, he's deep in his 60s now,
and he's been doing this for so fucking long,
like at almost no benefit,
and you know, whatever, retire early, he's a great guy.
And I just wanted to say, guys,
here's maybe the last time I'll mention Scooby
on the podcast, but he's created such a wealth
of content on his channel,
and like on his website,
I think it's Scooby Workshop.
Go there, if you're looking for fitness help,
there's so much of good to help you achieve these things.
I learned about smart goals from him.
There you go, he's a great guy.
I'll love him forever.
Thank you, Scooby, for everything you've done.
I'm feeling a lot of like, end of the decade,
end of era stuff going on right now,
and it feels like this is one of them,
so thanks again, Scooby.
All right, anyway, we've got one last voicemail coming
from, who is this?
Oh yeah, it's Whispering ASMR Style,
so mom doesn't hear.
Okay, let's hear what this hat say,
hang on, bear with me.
Gonna get my dick out for this one.
Yeah, it's time, boys, lube up.
All right, here we go, and go.
I have something to get off my chest, that is.
Other than this twink, teensy-beed groupies,
BBC, I'm being tit-fucked by,
and well, that's the problem.
See, I'm a freshman in high school,
and as would be assumed, I'm trying, man,
I'm in the trenches.
It's in full-on Vietnam shit, I've got yellow malaria.
So, here I am, going hard in the taint,
talking to mad girls like a real human being.
That's when it hit me.
After becoming kinda close with a couple of them,
I realized that I'm just the token gay.
It's hurting, I'm pill-battle being shorn,
and a Jewish, but no matter how hard I try,
I'm unavailable, cause they think I'm gay.
Either they treat me like the gay-eye-friend
in a group of girls, or they think I'm gay
and fully off the market.
Please, PCP, as the gayest council of individuals,
I could find, help me swallow my pain,
and find a solution to this AIDS epidemic.
I know the solution.
Yeah, I know the solution.
Yeah, you just tell them you wanna fuck them.
Yeah, just help them make-
Just whip your dick out on the table.
Ask one of them out.
Oh, yeah.
Just like, bro, this is teen CP, I think, calling in.
I just, like, here's,
consider the way that you're framing this.
You're like, after getting close
to a bunch of these girls,
then they started to think I was gay.
So, look, you're a young man, I understand this.
I was far worse than you, probably.
I didn't do anything until I was like,
fucking 20 with any girls.
But like, just consider the fact
that you're not making any moves
until you are already friends with them.
If you are even-
That's a terrible approach.
If you're even speaking to a woman,
you've already made it past every hurdle.
That's the only thing you're supposed to have to do
is speak to them, and then if it either,
you figure out within, like, very quickly
if that's supposed to go anywhere or not.
Like, if you're not figuring out where it's going quick,
you gotta swerve to the next one.
Like, if they're not-
I understand.
If they don't seem interested, gotta move on.
Yes.
We're in a delicate social marketplace right now,
a sexual marketplace.
I understand that I, too, was absolutely confused
and had no fucking idea what I was doing growing up.
But like, get to this, it's not sexual assault
to let a woman know you are attracted to her
or interested in it.
Who said it was sexual assault?
I'm exaggerating for comedic effect, Ben.
This is the point of what I'm saying.
But like, the point is, like, you can say to a girl,
like, hey, I think you're cute, wanna go out sometime?
If you just say that sentence, boom,
they know you're not gay, so you're over that hurdle,
at least.
And if they say no, then you're like, okay.
Let's talk about this,
let's talk about this wanna go out sometime meme.
Okay, sure.
What does that mean?
I feel like-
It's a social dice breaker.
I feel like that's a dumb line.
I feel like that's a shit line.
Cause I feel like-
Well, you gotta get her alone, you know,
to have your way with her.
I think that it's way,
I think you need to have a specific plan.
Sure, sure.
I think that if you're like,
why don't we go out sometime?
Like, what is that?
Oh, no, yeah, it's better if you come in-
Oh, you're right, Ben, you're right.
With already a date and time and a, or a, or a,
you start with a suggestion,
then you follow up with the date and time suggestion.
So like, don't think about it.
I'm gonna do this at this time.
Do you wanna do that with me?
Or, or it could be like, hey, let's go see a movie.
I'm free Thursday at six, how about you?
Then it's like, you know, you've already set up,
you don't, the onus is not on her
to come up with a date and time,
but if she can't do Thursday at six,
then, you know, then she,
maybe she has another time in mind, you know,
but like you gotta start off with a time in mind.
What do you think about doing this?
Here's when I wanna do it.
Are you available?
No?
Well, fuck me.
But like, you know, you gotta, you gotta make it,
you gotta send some kind of clear signal
in the early developmental stages
because I do think that,
I think a lot of guys think of women as like,
oh, I'll befriend a girl and then I know I like her,
so I'll start dating her.
But I don't think that-
Wrong direction, wrong move.
Yeah, I don't think,
I especially don't think girls tend to think that way.
I think they tend to think like,
I'll date a guy and find out if I like him,
because you don't find out what it's like
to date somebody by being friends with them.
It's a totally different experience.
So like, you need to approach it like,
it's not about dating a friend,
it's about dating someone and, you know,
figuring out if that's gonna be good or not.
If you become a platonic friend with someone,
then you have established your relationship
as a platonic one.
Yep.
It's not impossible to break out of.
You know, I guess I'm-
Mage, your advice sounds terrible already
and it's totally wrong.
No, fuck you, Mage.
What does Mage think about it?
It's irrelevant.
I mean, I still wanna know.
No, I think I'm just a little bit different from most people,
but back when I used to like guys
that are not my current boyfriend,
I would, it was usually people I befriended,
like guys that were my friends and I was like,
oh, I get along with him so well
and I kind of would develop a crush
just from being friends with them.
That's a fine perspective, Mage,
but frankly, your position there
is from the female perspective, which I get,
but for a guy who's trying to get a girl,
and you don't have a girl you love right now or whatever.
Mage, Mage, Mage.
Well, I wanna know.
I mean, from that perspective,
what should this guy, what should the caller do?
I don't really wanna give advice because like he said,
I don't feel like I should.
He's been gays-owned, Mage, help.
I mean, if you're friends with her
and you're getting along with her,
I think asking her out is a fine enough advice.
Yeah, I think it should be a new experience.
So we all, even Mage, who is completely
on the exact opposite spectrum, right?
It has the exact opposite perspective.
We all just think, we'll just ask him out.
Just tell him you wanna fuck.
I mean, that's the bottom line,
it's the only way to do it.
There is no beginning of a relationship
until somebody says, let's start a relationship.
Like it doesn't, you will just fall into a groove
of being friends and hanging out until somebody says,
like we have to take this to a new level
or else it's not what I intended it to be.
It will not progress until somebody puts their foot down
and says something.
Stop me if I'm crazy, but I feel like there's a pattern here
wherein like every time someone calls in
to ask a relationship question or a dating question,
the answer is always just fucking tell him
you wanna date.
You're absolutely right.
Just tell him you wanna fuck.
Because the bottom line is that communication is everything.
It's 100% of what a relationship is, is just communication.
So you need to be as clear as possible
in your communication if you want people to understand you
as a just general rule of life.
At all times, if you want anybody to know
what you're thinking, if you want them
to figure out your intention, fucking tell them.
It's not that hard.
And make sure that the person you're asking out
is receptive to communication because there are some
awful people that don't like to talk things out,
are sneaky about it, are not honest.
And he's like, oh, I'm fine.
And then you don't text them
and then they're angry about it.
It's just awful.
Yeah, stop talking to those people.
Just don't hang out with anybody
because you're that level.
As a separate piece of advice, don't talk to those people.
If they play mind games, don't play with them.
You go to another table, play with other people.
Another mind games crap.
Be a person of action and press through these things.
Don't get yourself stuck in the mud,
slaving over some, I don't know.
I mean, obviously you don't want oneitis,
but you also don't want, like I'm not saying be callous,
but like don't waste your time either.
So I don't know.
From the way he told that story,
it sounded like he kind of became friends
with like a group of girls or something
and became, they see him as the token gay.
I mean, step one, break them off from each other.
You can't have them in a group.
You have no, like you will be seen as a token gay
if you're just surrounded by girls.
Isolate them from their social groups, right?
Inflict emotional pain on them
and then establish yourself as the only one
who can provide relief from that same pain, right?
That sounds like a, isn't that something that like,
what's his name would say?
Dennis.
Roosh, Roosh V.
Yeah, yeah, well, yeah.
Ben, I'm curious, how do you feel about Roosh
now that you've turned your,
I know you had met him before and maybe thought he was okay.
I feel, you know, I don't know.
I haven't like read his stuff in a while.
Yeah, I used to.
He's very, very against anal sex.
Okay, okay.
Very not a man.
He thinks that anal sex is a sign of paternosal gay.
Oh God, why did my fucking headphones
have to die right now?
Okay, modern Roosh, I'm sorry if I'm talking over anyone.
I legitimately can't hear anything.
I'm just gonna go for a second
until I get my headphones back working.
Modern Roosh is a fucking mutant.
He is a creep and a monster and I hate him
and detest him and he has become bad and scary
and dark inside.
I think back in the day when I used to read him,
he wasn't, okay, I mean,
he mostly just offered some pretty normal advice.
He would occasionally say some kind of fucked up shit
but he always kind of said it with a wink and a nod.
So it was like, oh, he's just joking about that.
Now there's no winks and nods.
Now it's just fucking weird.
Like as so often happens, later on,
the truth comes out,
he's like, I think some of,
maybe a lot of it wasn't jokes.
Like he maybe wanted me to think.
I mean, it's gotten strange
because he called into the dick show one time
and even within his appearance, it was very strange
because again, he was like railing against anal sex
and talking about how porn is trying to turn us all into-
Is this just like an anti-gay thing
or is this between men and women too?
It's all kinds of shit.
He's one of the, he's like a very traditional values
in terms of-
He didn't really used to be like that.
Not at all, not at all.
He's become like that.
Yeah, I think he's,
I think he might on some level be one of those
like a preserve the white race kind of guys.
I think there's a little bit of that.
Is he white though?
Well, it doesn't matter, I guess.
I think he's, I don't know.
I think he is technically-
I don't know.
I mean, he's very traditional values.
He's very Judeo-Christian values.
But from like a weird robotic place.
Like you read his tweets-
And there's a big overlap,
There's a big overlap between those people
and the ethno-staters.
Well, like you said, Ben,
when you read his stuff,
it feels like weirdly robotic and alien.
It doesn't sound human.
It's like somebody who-
It does.
Who's like extremely concerned about human values
while having no humanity.
I feel that I understand Ruse's progression pretty well,
which was just that, I mean,
I'm sure he would say it as a matter of road.
I've listened to some of his stuff out of interest in this.
I didn't read his books, but I don't know,
I would kind of watch it.
I knew Ben had read them,
so I thought they were in my sphere.
I remember he was a big go around,
like fuck as many women as possible,
but then at a certain point in his life,
he was like, I'm not getting much emotional
or personal fulfillment from this anymore.
Like what I now want is a long-term lasting relationship
with a woman or whatever.
But he's also like-
I guess he's Armenian.
Because I went to his Twitter and the first thing it says
is Armenian Orthodox with one of those little cross-logos on it.
Cool.
Hell yeah.
I guess that's where he's at.
I'm gonna try to scroll to his Twitter
and find some of his anal sex tapes.
I remember there's a bit in like one of his books.
Oh, here's a cheater take right away, so what's that?
Really?
Oh no.
Is he Roushvi on Twitter?
Yeah, just Roushvi, I believe so.
Roushvi.
Looks like him, 64K followers.
Yeah, that's probably him.
Five Orthodox Jews,
you wounded in Hanukkah machete attack
by blackmail in New York.
A certain, Roush says,
a certain tribe is losing control
over their frontline soldiers.
What the fuck does that mean?
Wait, what?
I'm looking at his, I just see anal sex is not natural,
it's disgusting, while linking to an anal sex article.
He's just really against anal sex.
But whatever dude, I don't, fine.
Yeah, and he also thinks you should not have sex
out of wedlock now.
I mean, so true.
Yeah, yeah, and it's not just him thing,
he just thinks people shouldn't do it.
When he spent like his entire life doing it.
So his response to somebody talking
about the conversation on consent is,
you're on the road to hell if you're concerned
about consent, get married if you wanna have sex.
Oh my God.
I mean, the outspoken atheist thirsts for God the most.
He cries out in anger and despair,
please someone help me receive the faith,
help me be humble, help release me
from the thoughts of demons.
Is this for real?
I told you dude, he's gotten really weird.
This is worse than I thought.
I wish I could have, I don't know,
I don't wanna be an asshole about it,
but I wish I could have any respect
for like the argument for religiosity
outside of like a society does better
when it has religion.
Okay, maybe true, fine.
Maybe atheism will lead to death,
but I'm still not fucking convinced
by the argument at all.
There's no reason. Make up a better religion.
That I mean, that's the solution.
Make up a better culture that has some totems.
I mean, there's tons of countries and cultures out there
who really treat like their,
like they treat their own morals as a sort of religion,
like there's this, I was watching this video
about like five extremely small towns
and there's this one extremely small town in Japan
who has become obsessed with recycling
because they decided to have a,
they used to burn all their waste
just like in their fucking yards, I guess,
like they just didn't give a shit.
They found out how bad and dangerous this was.
So their town implemented a zero waste policy.
There is no trash out of this city at all.
Everybody is obsessed with like separating their trash
into like 18 or no,
it was like 30 something different categories of trash,
but like everybody does it and they all like got into it.
You know, like once they realized that like,
hey, as long as I just think about the stuff
I have differently, like I realized
none of this has to be wasted.
Like this can all go back in.
So like everybody in this town treats recycling
like a religion.
That's all people need.
They just need that kind of guidance.
They will turn it into a religion themselves, you know,
by obsessing over it.
You might be right.
If you're gonna make people have some kind of moral compass
to cling to or give them something,
like don't make it some weird random fucking made up
bullshit from 3,000 years ago.
Like, fair enough.
You know who was into zero waste?
Michelle was literally like a vegan and an actual zero waste.
What is zero waste?
Where your whole perspective,
like everything you consume in life
should produce no trash, just recyclables
and you recycle everything such that, you know,
I mean, you can't control what the recycling people do
once you give them the bottles
and they don't recycle everything,
but you can, you know, do your part to get it
as best you can.
And like, here's one thing I never thought of that.
I always thought like, how am I gonna, like, okay, straws.
Straws always confounded me
because there's no way you could recycle the straw, right?
It's too small, but then Michelle fucking moved in
and she brought her, was he, her reusable straws
with their special scrubber that you use to go
into the straws to clean the inside of the straws.
And now half the dishes are straws
that need to be scrubbed out from the inside.
She's not zero waste anymore, but we still have those.
And frankly, I think they're pretty cool.
I like them.
I enjoy scrubbing out those straws.
It's fun to be.
I'm glad.
I see, of course, Roosh had a shitty take about J.K. Rowling.
That's great.
That made me realize.
Are you still scrolling through this?
You should stop.
And you'll just get mad.
You know, I was already mad.
So yeah, this is just, I'm just, okay.
Here's some more Roosh tweet for you.
Porn should be banned.
It serves no purpose, but to destroy the mind, body,
and soul.
I guess freedom is not good or allowed, fair enough.
Okay, I mean, if that's your perspective, then fair.
Oh my God, porn is human trafficking, guys.
Did you know that?
Oh my God, consenting adults can't consent to things.
What a nightmare.
This is the luck that you have run into, Ben,
by not following any right-wing stuff,
because this is what's going on in the right-wing sphere.
No, I'm aware.
I'm aware that the alt-right is anti-porn now.
Yeah, cause like, out.
No, it's not that.
It's that there's a huge war,
and that it's really like,
only five or six fucking insane people
who really hate porn,
who are like, rallying against it,
and everybody else raising an eyebrow and going,
what the fuck, like, why are you guys bringing this up?
I think it's a Psyop.
I think it's an attempt at it.
Well, gab-band porn, right?
That's part of it, right?
Yes, it was at the, well, the guy who runs gab,
went on this like, gigantic anti-porn tear,
and just like-
How can you be a free speech platform,
and then just like, they did Lolliporn a while back,
they did all kinds of fucking shit.
These people don't give a shit about free speech.
No, they do not.
They don't give a fuck.
I mean, just, you can make an argument that like,
oh look, pragmatically, free speech is consequential,
so I'm not ultimately for it like, completely,
like, okay, fine, but then you can't have that as your,
whatever, well, no, no, shit.
You can't make the free speech alternative to Twitter,
and then fucking ban speech off of it.
It's no longer-
It's just-
It's allowed on fucking Twitter!
It's just, it's just-
So in name.
The conservative platform now, you know, that's fine.
You can do that,
but it's great, whatever, fucking.
I'm honestly like, a little mad that even Bitshoot
doesn't have porn on it, honestly.
Like, you can't post explicit sex on there.
Why not?
A fucking medic, or can post like, fucking surgery,
fucked up, but porn is not allowed,
are you fucking kidding me?
Shows dicks.
Shows fucking dicks and stuff.
It just can't be said-
I mean, they have a not-safe-for-life tag
that you can like, you can have your video
be not-safe-for-life, but you cannot show explicit sex.
That's retarded.
It's retarded.
What the fuck, all right, you know what?
Is it maybe there's some sort of law
wherever they're being hosted or something against it?
Not that I know of, but it could be.
Maybe, maybe.
If so, then I guess I understand it pragmatically.
Okay, by the way, just going back,
I was just gonna say one last thing
to our whispering ASMR teen CP guy
about the whole gay girl getting a girl thing.
Have you ever asked a girl out in your life?
Not to be an asshole, but just consider that question.
Have you ever, ever in your whole fucking life
said to a girl anything that made it clear
you were interested in her
and that you wanted to spend time with her?
If not, consider that.
Because I didn't for my whole fucking life
and then I figured out, oh, I'm just not doing anything.
I'll fix that now.
So consider that.
I made the same mistake and I,
well, I can't even call it a mistake
because I still have never asked a girl out
or done any of that shit.
I just got famous.
So that's another method.
It is, don't do that.
That's a retarded method.
No one should do that.
Don't wait your whole fucking life.
Okay, anyway, that's done.
And I think we, oh, that was the last one.
That was our last fucking voicemail.
So there you go.
We're all done.
Here's what I wanna tell you guys about.
One more thing, one more of my revolutionary ideas.
Here's what I think.
This is my big goal going into 2020.
I hope you all will consider it as well.
Which is to go torrent.
Go and torrent.
I like, I like, you know,
I like a little bit of what bidshoots going on.
It's a little slow.
It takes forever to upload on there.
You know, YouTube, obvious dumpster fire.
Where can I post literally whatever the fuck I want?
Torrents, I could just send people torrents.
Did you know that it takes like two seconds
to turn something into a torrent?
I've never done it personally.
All you do is you open up your torrent tracker
and click create torrent and then just select a file
and it's a torrent.
Does it come from your computer,
like hosted in a certain file location or something?
Yeah, it will be, I mean,
if you have that file on your computer,
you turn it into a torrent,
somebody downloads it from you directly,
but now, you know, they are seeding,
assume of Lee if they decide to seed.
But I'm gonna make probably a video about it.
It's just called like, why aren't we torrenting everything?
But like, torrenting has come so far.
It's super fast.
You can actually play torrents.
Like you can set your torrent thing to,
yeah, to download from start to finish
and then play it in the thing while you're downloading it.
So like, it's basically streaming.
The main reason I don't use torrents that much,
even for things I should,
is because it's not as immediate.
I like being able to just like type something in and go.
But now, more and more streaming sites are disappearing.
It's way harder to find illegal sites on Google
and shit like that.
So, you know, torrents are, I mean,
as the internet fucking devolves into a police state,
torrents are the only way you can maintain
your fucking freedom.
And it's all on your servers, your hard drive,
so nobody can do anything about it.
And once it's spread to other peoples,
they'd have to individually take it off
of everyone's fucking computer.
So, you know, if you're backed by something like Patreon,
it's totally reasonable to release shit through torrents
that you can't release through any other platform
because your audience will see it.
And it'll be, it'll stay up.
So, that's what I wanna do.
I wanna buy a server and start fucking
releasing shit through torrents.
It's a good idea.
Uh, I mean, you're gonna have a limited install base.
It's true, but like, the thing is,
I think that we're punking ourselves with YouTube
because you can only really be successful on YouTube
by making formulated content at this point.
I mean, YouTube doesn't even recommend me anything
that's not like the same shit I've seen.
Like, it's all 10 to 20 minute videos
in the same like analytical.
I mean, I know this is partly
because that's just what YouTube recommends me
because I've watched so much of it.
But like, I do not find anything on this platform anymore
that is not heavily steeped
in what YouTube has always been.
Like, it's just whatever, everything that comes out now
as an echo of something that's been on YouTube before.
You could make something wholly new,
wholly unique in the video format.
Put it on YouTube, nobody's gonna care.
What difference does it make
if you just make it a fucking torrent, you know?
Like, and I mean, nothing stopping you
from advertising your torrent.
You know, you can make YouTube videos about your torrents.
So, yeah, I guess so.
I mean, if they find out what they're torrent,
I suppose they could always remove you
for some of these things.
I mean, if you're hosted to the Piles on a server,
the server host could decide this is problematic content.
We are not going to host your fucking files.
I mean, what I would do is probably like,
you know, make a YouTube video being like,
hey, here's a new content I have out.
You can torrent it on my website,
you know, give a link to my website.
Then on the website, you can find the list of torrents,
you know, you're downloading them straight from me
or people who are hosting them.
So, yeah, I don't know.
I don't know what they could do.
I don't know what new forms the world would take
to try to deal with that.
But I really think that's where,
I think that's where people are just gonna end up going.
Like, I think that we've tricked ourselves
into thinking we need a YouTube alternative
because we think the audience is too lazy
to go other places.
And that's partially true,
but I think people are lazy about stuff
because they're consuming the same shit.
Like, if you go to YouTube,
would I leave YouTube for a YouTube video?
No.
Would I leave YouTube for something
that couldn't be posted on YouTube?
Yes.
That's what I think the mindset needs to be,
is like, hey, we don't have to make content
that's for YouTube.
We can make content that's whatever we want
and then figure out how to market it afterwards
once we know what it is.
I suppose that's true.
And by the way, and if you're torrenting folks,
you're gonna want to have a VPN.
So go, if you don't have a VPN, everybody, promo code PCP.
We don't have that, please NordVPN.
Please pay us to show your product.
Or there's a bunch of VPNs, that has to be Nord.
Or any of the other ones.
Not that I use VPNs, but.
Well, it's too late.
We just advertised Nord for free,
so now they don't have to pay us.
Ever since, you know, ever fucking since,
I got like a fucking notice the other day
about torrenting, like, I don't know,
some fucking movie or something.
I torrent everything, I don't give a shit.
I'm gonna torrent until the end of time,
as long as I can.
I don't fucking care.
I just got a VPN.
And you know what?
Since then, I've been torrenting like a madman
and it's been not a problem at all.
What kind of notice did you get?
Like from your ISP or what?
I got a letter from my ISP saying like,
we have detected that you were downloading.
It was actually something I think like a movie
I downloaded on Michelle's computer,
but I didn't mean we were doing it or whatever.
And I mean, look, this is the rub.
What are VPNs for?
So they can't track you when you're downloading shit.
This is what they are fucking for.
They won't tell you that on the other shows,
because they're like, they can't say that.
But that fucking video by Tom Scott or whatever,
he's absolutely right.
This is the point.
Yep.
Anyway, that's it everybody.
So you leave us more voicemails on the speak pipe link
down in the description.
And we got a lot of discussion out of that last one.
We sure did.
It goes in a lot of places.
So yeah, leave us fucking voicemails.
Love to have them.
Make quality.
Everybody was good.
Thanks for leaving them.
I was happy to see.
Oh, you know, a fucking real mass Batman called in,
but it's basically just an advertisement
for his upcoming content.
So we await that happily.
You know, riddle my ass Batman.
Looking forward to that one.
Love you.
Love you buddy.
Happy to have met you.
And other than that, hey, patreon.com slash
the procrastinators $1 discord fucking talk to us
and all fucking shit like that $5 bonus episodes.
When you hear this,
there will be a new bonus episode out about year and review
and about our plans for the upcoming year in detail.
So a bunch of us all talking about that shit
that we touched a little bit on here,
but way more in depth.
And I've got, I make a little announcement in there
that people might be interested in.
So give it a, give it a listen if you care.
What else we got?
At tbcrastinators on Twitter, updates, et cetera, blah, blah,
blah, and that should do it.
Oh, and also if you want to play Minecraft with us,
there'll be another stream coming before too long.
The patreon.com slash piece of Minecraft.
Subscribe to canton.
Canton.
I was happy to see while we were on our little hiatus
that crossed over 7,000.
So it's still, it's gaining pretty steadily as it goes.
So I'll be happy when it keeps growing
and more content is coming on canton.
So keep your eyes peeled.
Anyway.
My day is ruined.
I am going to be, now I'm poised to enter,
to exit the decade at the lowest point of all.
After having, after having a meteoric fall.
Just scrolling through route, route,
let's just talk about it.
Roush's Twitter and just being pissed off.
Is that what you're going to do this year?
Yeah, among other things.
That was the straw that broke the camel's back.
Well, I think social media is a cancer
and guns and destruction is the solution.
So we'll more on that next time, everybody.
We'll see you soon.
Have a wonderful week.
Happy New Year.
And we'll see you next time with another happy,
slappy episode.
See you then.
Bye.
Happy 2020, America.