Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be procrastinators.
Welcome to the Pro Crastinators Podcast. The only Pro Crastinators Podcast starring me, Ben Saint, and Gibbontake.
And we've got, I'm not going to believe who's on the show this week. The one and only. Everyone has missed him. Everyone has been asking for him in the comments for years, for years and years.
His slavering, drooling, brain dead fans have just been ravening in the comments. They say they won't watch if he's not here. Well guess what, suckers? He's back. It's the one. The only. Cheesy Manfredo.
I'm back, baby. Oh my god. Finally, the triumphant return. Finally, after. I look at. The prodigal son. I see all the comments. I see cheese heads in the comments. They'll be like, no cheesy, no watch. No cheese, no watch. No cheese, no watch. It's crazy.
No cheesy, no watch. It's like that Bob Marley.
We're back and we're better than ever. It's March 29th. Oh shit, I just stalked myself.
Oh shit, I stalked the time.
I said what time it is. They know. They know when I am.
A time traveler can come and fucking murder you.
When they listen to this, they can be like, okay, so who was where at exactly 29th of March last week?
They can follow the air trails. They can follow the chem trails.
Did you leave trailing behind you? Everywhere you go.
They can look at the map of all the boats rounding the Horn of Africa and not going through the Suez Canal and be like, fascinating, I see.
They're going to deduce something.
They're going to grab your audio and be like, wait, wait, what's that sound?
Wait, and then they hear the beer chirping and it's like, hold up, is that an East Coast swallow?
I know where Ben's located.
The rarest, the rarest of them all. It only grows at this one address on this one street.
Are you sure you mean the Horn of Africa, like the bit on the edge?
The bottom, right?
No, no, the Horn of Africa, if you look at Africa, there's like a spike on the right side.
It's like where Saudi Arabia is.
Kenya is or...
Is it on the Madagascar side?
It's the thing next to...
Saudi Arabia is the big chunk that's like cloth.
Yeah, next to it, yeah, yeah.
It's like technically Africa.
The Horn of Africa is the Somalia spike. You could stab someone.
Oh, cool.
I see. I meant the Southern tip. I don't know what it's called.
I know it's South Africa.
I guess it's just called South Africa.
That's where Elon Musk was born.
Fun fact.
Lucky him.
Lucky us. Lucky us that South Africa decided to gift us the savior.
Elon Musk, thank God.
Who would have thought it would have been a white guy? That's so crazy.
It's so... I mean...
Can you imagine... God, thank God Elon Musk was born white, right?
Otherwise, who knows what could have happened?
Yeah, yeah, like...
I don't even know what the joke was there.
It's just alluding to race relations in South Africa.
Like, hmm, you know what? Think about that.
Race relations in South Africa? Why? What happened there?
Nothing, actually.
Nothing, nothing, nothing at all.
Don't look it up. Don't worry about it.
They just dug the white people out of the ground, you know.
There's just different kind of rocks down there.
Like the Orcs and Lord of the Rings.
Yeah, that's where white people came from.
It's all in the books.
Yeah, Saruman got the white mud and then that birthed out the white people.
The white mud. Delicious.
The whites.
So what's popping gamers? How have you guys been?
I literally just got to my house like five minutes before the episode was supposed to start.
On the bus.
First time I've ridden a bus in a while, but I had to do it.
I had to risk COVID because I had to see my fucking family again this weekend.
Oh, man.
But my parents are...
Well, my dad's vaccinated. My mom is semi-vaccinated.
So I guess they were like, eh, well, time to risk it all.
They haven't had COVID in a while. I gotta make sure they're topped up.
At least your parents get vaccinated.
I'm pretty sure my parents are not going to get vaccinated at all.
Oh, really? I'm sorry.
It was like at the start. I don't know if I said this before on a previous episode,
but at the start of March, one of my roommates tested positive and everyone else in our house got tested too.
And I was calling my mom. I was telling her that I won't be able to come visit this weekend because I don't know if I have it or not.
Yeah. Yeah. And then I asked her if she got tested.
If anyone in the family got tested and she says, like, no, because we don't live in fear.
Oh, dear.
Oh, is that why? Oh, no.
That's why.
Yeah. And I'm like, I don't... Oh, I can't...
And then I see them on Instagram story and Facebook and they're still going to like parties and shit.
And I'm like...
I...
They're living in fear of the vaccine. That's the funny thing is that they are living in fear.
They're so scared of taking the vaccine. They're not even difficult.
It's fucking annoying. I do not like it.
I think I'm going to be able to get it in like... I might even be able to get it in like a month or two.
That's exciting.
I should probably try and sign on to a list or something. Yeah.
I think here in California, you could... I think everyone could get it on the 15th or something.
They're like giving... they're massively giving it out on the 15th.
I don't know how to do it exactly.
Jealous. Jealous.
You know, it's so... it's funny because I was what...
I heard that there's like a specific Twitter bot for people in California that if you follow them,
they could like tell you where you could get an appointment.
The thing is, the downside is you have to be following the bot and I maxed out my follow so I can't follow the bot.
So unfollow someone?
No, I can't do that.
Okay.
You need all 5,000 of those followers?
Unfollowing someone is like the worst thing you could do to someone, Ben. That's like...
That's true. That's true. That's why I relish the opportunity to do it whenever I get the chance.
That's why I avoid the problem by never following anyone.
I don't... based, based.
Yeah, yeah, people ask me why do I still follow Nick Fuentes and I'm like, I did it on accident years ago
and now I can't go back on my word that...
I just can't find the button.
That's what a coward would do. That's like, yeah, no, you follow things till the very end.
You're not allowed to change your mind, right?
I guess you're right.
Only a coward would undo an accident.
Only a coward would clean up after his messes.
That is so true.
Yeah, my roommates are the ultimate not cowards because they never clean the dishes. It's pretty base.
Good for them. Good for them.
Yeah, it's awesome.
I love spending an extra 30 minutes for every meal that I make. It's fucking awesome.
It's like, yeah, it's a little extra work, but it's worth it to know that your roommates aren't cowards.
You don't live with no coward.
When push comes to shove, at least they're not cowards, am I right?
So I saw a Nate. I hung out with Nate also. He was there, believe it or not, him and Michelle.
Family gathering with Nate?
Yes.
I wonder if your family is related or something.
What was he doing there?
Yeah, we were married for a brief while there.
Yeah, that must have been very weird for Michelle, but you know.
Oh, it was.
It was.
Okay, so funny.
On what was supposed to be the last day, we came into Boston and we got a munchie and Kazi to come out and hang with us.
But it was so gross and rainy and we all hated it.
We just went back to my parents' house and just stayed there and just watched the witch, the Vovic, which I'd never seen before.
It was pretty good.
And then I got an acai bowl because we were saying, bro, you hardly touched your acai bowl and I wanted an acai bowl.
What's wrong?
What's wrong, king? You haven't touched your acai bowl.
It's basically, do you know what, acai is like a berry and it's basically just like a sorbet bowl.
It's like a sorbet bowl and they put granola and fruit and chocolate and shit on it.
It's like frozen yogurt, but a little different, I guess.
Acai?
It's full of antioxidants. It's a super fruit.
It's good to know. Yeah, you're probably immune to the coronavirus at this point.
I should hope so because I had to ride the freaking bus and I don't like doing that.
I tell you what, I really don't like doing that.
Not a big fan of the bus.
Not a big fan of that bus.
Do you get paranoid about touching the handlebars and stuff?
Not so much about touching because I bring a big bottle of hand sanitizer,
of green hand sanitizer that I slapped the Slime Corp logo on.
So I sanitize my hands pretty regularly when I'm out.
On the bus back to my house, there was a, I don't know if he was a homeless guy,
but he looked like he could have been, but he was sitting on, he wasn't sitting,
he was like leaning against a seat that was up, right?
It was like one that you can fold down if you need to, but it was up, but he was leaning on it.
He was technically wearing a mask, but it was like crunched up, so it covered his mouth,
but not his chin or his nose, and it had spots of what may have been blood on it.
And he was just standing there with his like cart or whatever,
and he like talked overly familiarly to the bus driver as he got off calling her sister and stuff
and wishing her family well.
And then he got off and then this girl like got after him and sat like right where he was sitting,
and I'm thinking like, I wouldn't sit there, but she doesn't know.
She doesn't know who was there.
The bloody mask was really like, hmm, what's that about?
There was this one time that that sort of thing happened, but it was much stinkier.
There was a guy on the tube, he was like very homeless, very smelly.
Very homeless.
Extra homeless.
Like he had his shoes were like wet.
I don't know, his shoes had plastic bags taped around them, and he smelled a bit of piss.
It was very unsettling.
Well, I mean, don't judge.
I mean, who among us hasn't smelled of piss?
How dare this man not have a home?
What the fuck is wrong with him?
I know.
Why can't he go to the home store and buy a home?
He bought too much avocados.
What I'm saying is that I came in and I didn't notice this at first because he was on one side of the train
and then most everyone else in that carriage was on the other side of the train.
And I sat down on a free seat and then I was like, oh, no.
Oh, God.
Oh, it's so bad.
I have to move.
And it was so embarrassing.
Like sitting down next to this guy and having to move because he was like, like you would throw up sort of smell.
Yeah.
Fuck.
I hate this.
Everything about this is so unfortunate.
Damn.
All right.
So give imagine that experience.
But almost every day.
Because I know I had no way.
No, no, no.
I'm talking about myself.
Like I lived.
I lived unironically for a situation like that almost every day.
Were you the homeless man?
Yeah, I was the homeless man.
No, it was like, no, it was, it was, it was a, I wrote the public school bus.
And, you know, it was like, it was like, I think the beginning of high school.
And I would just kind of sit in the front because I didn't have too many friends on the bus.
Right.
And I mean, I wouldn't really care too much.
And there's this one, there's one girl who would always sit right next to me.
And no one would want to sit with her.
And I'm going to tell you why because she smelled really awful, like really terrible.
And I don't think she had poor hygiene.
I think it's a medical condition unironically.
Cause it just, it always just was the same kind of like stinky consistency.
And you could actually smell some soap on her.
Like she would maybe try to like kind of rub it off.
But unironically, she would always just smell like terrible.
And I, I think she unironically had a condition.
She just had a condition.
Sham.
Yeah.
And like, but like, I think over time I eventually got like numb to it.
Like I didn't even like notice.
Um, we never even talked at all.
She would just like sit right next to me because she's got a.
Cause.
And now we're married.
Yeah.
Now we're married.
But was she cute though?
Now she's my stinky wife.
Uh, she was okay.
That's good enough for me.
I don't know.
I don't look at people's eyes.
It faces.
Hmm.
What?
I'm too nervous for that.
The beginning of high school was like maybe 10 to eight years ago.
I don't know.
There was only, there was only two Iron Man movies when I went to high school.
No.
Impossible.
Yeah.
True.
I, I, I chronicle time by how many MCU movies existed at the period.
Thank God we live in a more civilized age now.
Yeah.
Thank God.
Thank God there's three Iron Man movies now.
Imagine.
Really in limbo after the second one.
It's, you know, it kind of, yeah, yeah, it's, it's terrible.
That's why I hate Trump cause they never came out with Iron Man 4 under a Trump presidency.
It's really, it really is a shotting example.
The first thing, the first thing Biden said is that we're bringing Iron Man 4.
Iron Man 4 DVDs are going to go out the door immediately as soon as.
I'm still waiting for my Iron Man 4 DVD.
Biden.
Speaking of, speaking of Biden, here's some good news.
Fuck that.
Biden.
Joe Biden?
The Joe Biden.
He's a man himself.
The man of the hour.
He's going to run for president 2024.
Good news.
I saw that.
I saw he said he definitely wouldn't, but now he's just going to do it.
He's going to be dead.
He's going to be fucking dead.
I'm hoping he is in Minecraft.
In Minecraft.
He's going to perish in Minecraft.
So is there, I don't know much about the election stuff.
So can a president, like if Obama, for example, didn't run for his second term,
would he just be able to do that?
I thought it was sort of like a championship belt.
Like Obama has the belt and now all these people are going to try and challenge him.
You don't have to run.
You don't have to run, but you're only allowed to hold off as twice.
Yes.
So Trump's going to run again in 2024.
So it's literally going to be Trump versus Biden again unless they die, which would be
better, but also probably something worse, someone even worse would show up.
So I don't even know what I want.
It's so, it's hard to predict who might be the next Trump 2.0.
I don't think it's going to be, it's not going to be Junior.
That's for a fact.
He's going to be like, no charisma.
What counts as Trump 2.0?
Like someone who's just bad policy or it's just like the same personality sort of thing?
Yeah.
I could see Tucker Carlson running for president eventually, but not like in 2024.
He's making too much money.
Steven Crowder, I think Steven Crowder mentioned something about running for office in his
state.
He did.
God, all fucking mighty.
All every other motherfucker.
Ben Shapiro for 2024.
Fine and finitely a logical president.
Stop just telling me facts about what is going to happen and stop.
Just bring back president by combat.
Trial by stone.
Gladiatorial arena.
We got to go back to the Skeksis and do trial by stone.
I think Joe Biden.
Like getting stoned?
No, it's when you take the sword and you smash the rock with it and you try to make
a big cut in the rock with your big sword.
If I were going to say pull out the sword like Excalibur, right?
Haven't you fuck seen Dark Crystal?
No.
I'm not a virgin.
You...
Got him.
Damn, damn, damn, damn.
Whatever.
Never mind.
Philistines.
No, no, babe.
I'm just, babe.
King, I'm so sorry, King.
Babe, you haven't even, you barely even finished your trial by stone.
Babe.
No, babe.
Keep talking about Dark Crystal.
So sexy, babe.
Did I, did I say that I got the Asaebel?
Did I say that on the show?
Yes.
Did I got the Asaebel?
So now I know.
Yes.
Okay.
I knew about, babe, you've barely even touched your collectible blue Sonic Curry.
And recently I saw, babe, you've barely touched your whale flavored horse meat.
That one was pretty good.
I didn't know about, I didn't heard anyone say, bro, you've barely finished.
You barely touched your Asaebel, but I vibed with it.
And they used to watch, they used to watch that Pokemon Go guy, Nick, on that.
He had that Pokemon Go YouTube channel, and he would always get Asaebel's.
And I always wondered, and now I know.
And that's my story.
Now you know.
And I'm sticking to it.
Do you still play Pokemon Go?
Uh, no, not really since coronavirus.
Even though like, you can.
Oh, did I call it?
Well, you can.
I just realized how dumb that is.
No, it's not dumb because they changed it so you don't really have to walk around anymore.
They made it like a lot easier to find Pokemon.
Yeah.
Like, yeah.
Well, the main thing they did, I think, because I opened it today, they had a nice little walk.
But your buddy gives you like gifts that you can then send to friends and they can open it and get items.
And poker stops spinning distance has been increased.
So you can spin things that are very far away, not that far away, but like.
Further.
It's better.
Yeah.
And they've made other changes that allow you to play at home, which is pretty good.
It's not that great though, because you can't get the real experience.
The real experience is just having a nice walk and occasionally twiddling at your phone.
My phone is just.
A nice walk is kind of important.
I should just get a better phone because that's the coronavirus didn't help.
But the real reason I stopped playing was just because my phone is bad and the game just lagged a lot and it was really annoying.
So I should just get a better phone.
I could just.
Fuck.
Get a fucking phone.
My parents were asking me what I want for my birthday and I literally could not think of anything like all weekend except maybe like a new pair of shoes.
Yeah, I obviously need a new phone.
I'm such an idiot.
It takes me.
It's taken me this long to remember.
You DM your parents saying, actually, I know what I want now for a gift.
And then they say, well, sorry, Ben, too late.
Now Nate is going to get two gifts.
I have.
I realized that like those.
Okay, the shoes, the shoes that used to be Nate's, but that are mine, but that I did not steal.
Of course, they are my shoes legitimately.
I've realized that they just smelled like horrible.
I just I didn't even like notice anymore because they live in my room, but like I wore them out.
I put them on and I went out to like get in the car with the fam and they were like, Ben, you smell terrible.
And I'm like, I don't know what you mean.
I just showered like before I got in the car and they were like, no, you smell really terrible.
And I was like, why?
How could this be?
And I gnashed my teeth and I and I pounded my fist in the air and I said, why God?
Why have you cursed like this?
And then I realized it was just the shoes.
They were they were like, they were just disgusting.
So I washed them and I will probably destroy them soon because they are infected.
They are unclean.
They are cursed.
Nate, Nate did a like a gypsy witch spell.
He definitely did something because it's not it's not natural.
It's not a natural affliction that ails them.
It's not of this earth.
You know, you wonder why Nate hasn't uploaded anything on the best guy ever channel because
he was too busy learning the dark arts so he could curse Ben saying.
Curse the shoes.
To have stinky shoes.
Word.
He shall have stinky shoes.
Next step of his plan is to give Ben a stick.
If I can't have them, no one can have them.
I will give Ben a stinky wife.
That shall be the next step of my plan.
No.
No, please.
Why is this a stinky episode of the PC?
Uh-oh.
Stinky.
Terrible.
Yeah, that's fucking.
That's fucking stupid.
Speaking of speaking of stinky, I've been recently, I've been enlightened.
I found out something about myself and it's due to Ben saying.
He kind of triggered this.
I found out that I've been a fan of Andrew Hussie the whole time.
Oh, because I, yes, I've showed you.
I've showed you the way.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, Ben said cheesy re-cyclonials.
Yep.
Cyclonials.
Yeah.
Have you noticed?
Oh boy.
Seen any Hussie stuff before?
Um, I avoided Homestuck like the plague, um, because I was, guys, I didn't want to read
it.
I was just not interested in reading Homestuck.
And then, um, and then Ben over here was like, adding me saying like, uh, geez, you're going
to like, cyclonew's got to check it out.
And I'm like, yeah, maybe.
And then another friend of mine, uh, shout out to Sporktown Heroine.
Um, she's all like, she, she showed me like a screen shot of it.
She said, I got, I got a bunch of people in my, in my Discord server to give cyclonew's
a chance and they all thanked me profusely and said, Ben, you really are a genius.
And I said, I know, but thank you.
I, I, I was like, wow, I, you know, it used to be best guy ever, but clearly it's, it's
Ben now.
Ben best guy ever is Ben guy ever.
Ben guy ever.
Yeah.
But, um, I, um, also because, uh, Homestuck is just long and I don't know that just kind
of like not, that didn't sure attract me.
Right.
I mean, it was, it was like a comp, it was a combination of the art style and like it
being long and it's like, uh, but, um, but cyclonew's is like only going to be nine
chapters, which is like, okay, cool.
I could, I could live through this.
Well, if you like cyclonew's and you're looking for more hussy, but Homestuck's too long
for you, you should check out a problem sleuth after, afterwards.
Problem sleuth whistles the clown might be something to look into.
I, I keep getting, I keep recommended, um, whistles the clown too.
I mean, I'll, I'll check it out after, I'll check that out after like, colognew's cause
I just, um, I don't know if I would recommend whistles the clown.
It's such an, it's, it's like an incomplete story.
It's damn.
It is.
That is an unfortunate thing.
No, cyclonew's takes place right after whistles the clown.
What are you talking about?
Oh yeah.
It's.
He was, he was the first jubile.
That's, yeah.
Yeah.
That's the plot twist at the end.
It's going to be revealed.
What were you saying, Gibb?
Uh, the, I'm just trying to remember it cause whistles the clown kind of felt like
clowns, Dragon Ball Z style.
Like it's, they're just super powered, like one of them is sort of a Vegeta clown
and the other one is sort of a Goku clown.
I think Andrew Hussie is reading my mind.
Oh my gosh.
I think Andrew Hussie on air on like reading my fucking mind.
It's, it's unfinished, but like, it was just, clowns are funny and, and that, and
but like, not in the way they intended it.
It's always been cool.
I read cyclonew's and it was, it was really freaky how much is kind of like stuff that
I already thought of.
Not like, not the story, like the story exactly was like a story.
No, no.
I mean, like a lot of the ideas and cyclonew's were things I already like had in
mind for stuff.
And I'm like, wait, what the fuck, what the fuck?
And I just kept reading more of it.
And I'm like, this is kind of like spot onto a lot of things that I kind of already
believe about, I guess, I guess spoilers for anyone who hasn't read cyclonew's.
We spoiled the whole thing on the other episode.
Cyclonew's on steam, on Android device.
Yeah, it's just, it's just the one time purchase.
And then every time a new chapter drops, you get it for free.
Yes.
Technically.
Right.
I am to get to get you to get you to read it.
I agreed to, I bought you the game in exchange for you bought me David Boring by Daniel
Klaus, which I read.
I read, by the way, I read it at my parents house this weekend.
What'd you think?
I thought it was based.
Nice.
I thought it was cool.
And I don't know if I want to like talk to, I don't want to spoil it or anything,
but I would recommend it and it makes me, I've never read any other Klaus.
I've seen Ghost World the movie.
I haven't read the Ghost World comics, but I think I might check out some more Klaus
stuff at some point.
This is all I wanted.
Cool.
Cause I would read, I read Vapors and I'm like, is this kind of like Klaus kind of?
A little.
I sort of see it.
Yeah.
And then I'm like, yeah, Ben should like, if Ben wants to upgrade on his, the genre of
David Boring would be like a white guy discovering himself type story, right?
Kind of.
Yeah.
He needs to read more Daniel Klaus.
I would recommend, if you liked David Boring, I'd probably recommend like the Death Ray,
which is like.
The Death Ray.
Yeah.
That's Daniel Klaus.
That one's like a pseudo superhero story.
Like just, just imagine if it, just like how David Boring is written, imagine that, but
apply to like a guy who wants to be a superhero, but it's still kind of like all, all of a
Daniel Klaus's characters, like main characters are usually kind of like low key shitty people.
But, but not like, not like in a, like, like, how do you, how do you describe the character
of David Boring, Ben?
I guess spoilers.
He's, I mean, he's, he's, I don't know, cold, unemotional, obsessive.
He's kind of an ass.
He's not great.
Yeah.
I am.
So all of his characters are kind of like that.
So imagine if that character, but if you like wanted to be a superhero, and it's, it's probably
I was probably unironically the most realistic take on someone trying to be a superhero in real life.
Yeah.
And that, yeah, that one's good.
David, he has a recent one called patience, which is like a time travel story.
And that one's like, was really, that was really good.
I think he, I think he's been doing that one for like, he's been like low key, like writing
that one for like 10 years.
So I would recommend that one.
I should just, I should just buy, I should just buy a couple more on Amazon or something.
A few.
Yeah.
I want, I really, I, yeah, I think it would do you, I think it would do you some good.
I think you would get pretty inspired.
You know, I feel like reading David, David boring was a little bit inspiring for me.
So I think you're right about that base.
I am.
Yeah.
I like to call David boring, my Scott Pilgrim.
Because I'm really.
Yeah.
Cause people always, I always hear people say like, Oh man, I relate to Scott Pilgrim.
And I'm like, like, I don't relate to Scott Pilgrim.
I relate more to David boring.
I think that one hits me.
That's my relatable white boy.
It's not Scott.
Um, yeah, I see, I guess I see what you mean.
You two are, are a freak who wants to fuck his, his cousin.
Yeah.
Of course.
Spoilers.
Spoiler.
That was a big, big, big.
It's a media.
That's a medium size.
The story is more than that.
The story is.
Yeah.
But I, I'm not wrong with you.
Like, I think I mentioned this before when I tried to sell it on you.
I like the whole aspect of like David boring.
He thinks he's falling in love, but really he's just horny.
Like that's just it.
He's just horny.
That's it.
He's not like, he doesn't actually give a shit about the women.
Yeah.
He doesn't give a shit about the women.
He like,
That's true.
He's like, dot, dot is like, you only like her cause she's got a fat ass.
Like, no, no, there's more, there's more to it than that.
But, but there's not.
Right.
There's not.
No, there's not.
And he just can't figure that out.
Like.
Yeah.
And that's all like what I kind of like got on my like second reread when I entered
my twenties.
And I'm like, oh my God, he's just, he's just horny.
He's not like actually fucking falling in love with these women.
I can't, uh, man, I don't know.
I would say there's some things I would point out about it, but they're, they're bigger
spoilers.
Uh, like, I mean, I don't know.
We said spoilers for people every day.
I mean, I don't know.
I mean, I can't believe that he gets shot in the head twice and doesn't care that he gets
shot in the head and finds the guy who did it.
And it's just like, well, all's, I guess all's well that ends well.
No harm done.
And, um, it's, it's, I thought it was like weird that all these things where all these
death was happening and there's like no consequences for it.
But I guess it kind of makes sense because it's sort of set in the apocalypse or something.
So it's, I don't, I'm not sure if like the apocalypse was meant to like thematically
be like a theme of the story or if it is like a convenient way of like, hey, how come you
don't get, go to jail even though like the cops, the cops think you murdered your friend.
Oh, well, it's because Dot just shoots the cops and it's the middle of the apocalypse.
So there are bigger fish to fry.
And so, you know, they don't come after you.
Uh, and, uh, it was really, uh, when it, when like the, when they went to the island
and like the germ, it's like, oh, the world, actually the world has been engulfed in germ
warfare.
I was like, well, this is, this is not where I was expecting the story to go.
Story, it did that a lot.
Didn't expect to be shot in the head the first time.
Didn't expect the apocalypse to happen.
Uh, didn't expect, um, a lot of things.
Did you, um, did you like, did you like all the twists and turns?
I like, I enjoyed all the twists and turns.
Yeah, I did.
It really, really went places.
I, um, what I really also like about the book, and I guess, um, I don't know if you
caught this, but the book kind of low key tells you what like love is.
Like, um, for like, there's that one line that, um, I think it's the, the Judy girl,
the first girl that he like falls in love with.
We have like the fat ass.
Yeah.
Um, he has like a flashback with her where, um, she asked her like, uh, would you kill
for me?
Right.
Yes.
And he's all like, uh, I don't know.
But she says my professor says it's not love if you won't kill for it.
Oh, and that's the guy.
And that's the guy who shoots him.
Right.
Exactly.
Cause he, he's actually like in love with her, but here's the thing that like, um, also
like David, um, I feel like the book might be trying to say something like, um, David
is like love.
Like he does love someone, um, not like in love.
Like he wants to fuck with someone.
Like for, he loves.
Not like unironically, even though he never said like he loves her, he does.
He loves her like, like platonically.
And the big, the big scene that kind of proves that is the part where she's like getting harassed
by that one homophobe and like David goes up, yeah, David goes up to him with a piece of
plywood.
That's like, that's like the only time he ever, that's like the only time he ever like
does anything.
Right.
He goes nuts and he like tries to fucking kill that guy.
Yeah.
He says, I'm going to fucking kill you.
Which is like proof.
That he loves Dot and Dot loves him back.
That's way, that's way more than he ever did for any of the other women or anyone else
at all.
Right.
Exactly.
And Dot loves him back because Dot like shoots those cops at the end.
Yeah.
True.
It's fucking subtle.
It is.
Oh my God.
It's fucking, it's fucking genius.
He's my Zach Snyder, uh, Daniel Klaus.
My Zach Snyder.
Is that a compliment?
I don't know.
Because Zach Snyder is a genius, Ben.
Oh, okay.
All right.
Uh, I will, I will, I'll check out the death ray.
Yeah.
Death ray.
Uh.
What is that?
Is that a comic?
Yeah.
Is that a story?
That's the one he was saying.
It's about the guy who wants to be a superhero.
Yeah.
I don't know anything that you've been talking about.
He was just, he just explained it a mere 15 minutes ago.
No, no, no, no.
What?
I'm just saying, I, I, I'm not, I don't know what it is.
So I haven't had anything to say.
Where do I read it?
Okay, wait, uh, Gib, do you, um, would you-
It's a book.
You go to your local library.
Gib, Gib, hard question right now.
This is the serious question.
You can't, you can't swipe.
You can't swipe it.
These kids these days don't know about books.
They don't know about physical media.
I don't, I don't-
Where's clicking?
I grab a book and I'm like, where's the apps?
Where's the apps store on this thing?
I can't-
I open a book and I control-
Like, I can't-
Wait, I put my finger on the page, but the words don't move.
Where are all the, where are all the Pokemon creatures in this book?
I can't find them.
I try to zoom in to a painting by scraping it with my finger.
Um, Gib, hard question right now.
Um, this is, uh, do or die question right here.
Do you like the comic The Vapors?
Think very carefully.
I don't know if I'd say it.
I like it.
About your answer here.
Okay, well, for everyone in the audience-
I might love it.
Oh my god!
Well, if you love The Vapors, you'll love David Boring.
It's, it's like, imagine if, imagine if Ben was, was older and a boomer.
Yeah.
Uh, hard to imagine.
Hard to imagine.
Imagine if Ben, uh, never discovered Sonichu and he's all like, I'm just, I'm just-
I'm not gonna read Sonichu, I'm just gonna make more comics.
That's-
I'm just gonna be good.
I'm just gonna be good and wholesome instead and live my life to the fullest.
Yeah.
That's where, that's the Sonichu Diversions.
Yeah, I think so.
Oh, and I think, uh, I think, yeah, that phrase is good, uh, Dan Pussy, which is another
book that he wrote.
Dan Pussy?
Dan.
Dan Pussy.
Dan Pussy, okay.
Yeah, which is, which is about like a, a piece of shit nerd who, who's, who's actually
a good comic artist and he like goes up in the industry.
It's like a weird, it's like a commentary on just the comic book industry.
Like there's like a bunch of like proxy characters for guys who, who work in these industries.
Like there's like a Stan Lee guy who's like a piece of shit.
Is it, is it like that, is it like that one like Japanese drama about the guy who like
wants, he's like trying to be an animator and he like goes to school alongside the guy?
Blue Blazes?
Yes.
Um.
Is it anything like that?
Blue Blazes is kind of, Blue Blazes is like hopeful.
Dan Pussy, Dan Pussy is kind of like, kind of like, yeah, sure.
Like kind of like the rise and fall of a character.
I think it's just called Pussy.
Is it called Pussy?
P-U-S-S-E-Y exclamation point.
Oh wait, I think the character's name is Dan Pussy, but yeah, the comic's called Pussy.
Yeah.
Pussy, yeah, yeah.
Pussy.
Amazing.
Yeah, that one's good.
Um, he has a bunch of other stuff.
Uh, that feels very like, I don't know how, how you feel about David Lynch, but um, he
has one book.
Fine, I guess.
He's got one book called, uh, like a Velvet Glove Cast and Iron.
That's like a very, it feels like the most David Lynchian thing Dan Klaus has written.
Um, so, so yeah, if you, if you, if you thought, yeah, David Boring is fine, but what if it
was weird or like you should read, um, like a Velvet Glove Cast and Iron?
Like a Velvet Glove Cast and Iron?
I'm writing all this down.
All right, good.
Taking notes.
That's like, this is, this is what I want to do.
I just want to uplift my kings.
I just want to expand their minds with a good literature.
Right?
First was an acai bowl.
Now this.
Yeah.
You know, yeah.
You, the acai bowl fueled your body and now I'm feeling your mind, right?
It's brain food.
Yeah.
You were eating your acai bowl while reading, uh, uh, Daniel Boring.
You were like, whoa, I'm like, I'm like a hundred percent healthy right now.
It was a triple threat.
Triple.
Triple threat.
Yeah.
So, so if, um, if the next chapter of the Vapors is suddenly more good, um, you know,
it's suddenly good.
Yeah.
You know who to blame.
You know, you know who to point fingers at.
Uh, good.
Apparently there's a, there's a Hong Kong punk band called David Boring.
Really?
What are their fans?
There's also a guy who just seems to be coming up when I type David Boring.
Who is this?
French singer and actor.
Law.
Um, base.
Just like, just like the real David Boring.
Um.
Hmm.
Well, somebody's going to say something to me.
I heard.
I was, I was going to ask, oh, since, since you are not, since you are not, uh, uh, uh,
educated, unlike me in the works, in the works of the, of the, of the Daniel Klaus,
uh, you moved, right?
Oh, I was going to segue into something else.
No, I didn't mean to segue your segue.
Um, well, I guess I didn't actually have much to talk about.
It was, it was just the, the, the, it was the Kato guy, um, that comic thing.
Oh, the, the Kato anthology.
Yeah.
I, I, I want to do something.
Which I, I don't want to do.
I mentioned it last episode.
It's the, it's the, an anthology, this guy, um, Kato and, um, is the, it's a YouTube channel
and it's got the, the, they're looking for submissions.
They're going to do a Kickstarter later this year and they'll, yes, I mentioned this on
the last one and I put the link in the description.
Okay.
So what's up with it?
Well, I, I want to do something and I don't want to just repurpose an old comic mostly
because it's just difficult to like make it fit into 10 pages or however many is like
the maximum.
Yeah.
So I'm thinking, okay, let's do like a short story.
Let's do like a couple pages, maybe two, five pages of just a little story that has a beginning
and middle and an end and it's going to be very easy and it's going to be short and
it's going to be a story and I'm going to write it and why aren't I writing it and what's
going on?
It's so difficult.
Yeah.
Sure.
What's going wrong?
I can't, I can't figure out how to write a small story anymore.
I've, I've spent so long like in my head and on papers, secret papers, like writing huge
world building documents for a grand epic that I can't, I can't figure out how to write
a just a small thing that ends at some point.
Well, you got to think of the ending first, right?
They all blow up.
That's one thing.
Well, boom, easy, easy.
That's a start, right?
They all blow up.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I guess I should have thought of more to talk about.
That was just, I want to do it and I need to get into the like the right mindset, the
right headspace.
I was thinking maybe I should think about it and then I was thinking maybe I shouldn't
think about it.
Maybe I should just draw something.
So that's where I am right now.
I don't know how to think.
You saying that makes me a little bit hungry to maybe just, I don't know, I don't know
what context, but like it makes me want to just, just, I don't know, think of like a
new little, like a little, just a little story or something that has like a beginning, middle
end and just draw it or something.
Instead of, you know, because the thing I've been working on now has been like a big long
thing in there.
Oh God.
Yeah.
Enough.
I feel that.
You should, okay, if you want to, I recommend you do a story about a little goblin character
just running around.
A little goblin?
There's a little goblin guy.
He's a little goblin guy.
They run around and then he gets blown up due to his own actions.
He's hubris.
Right?
Like, yeah.
He's right around getting into little goblin shenanigans and because of all the shenanigans
he pulls, he gets blown up.
It all comes back in his face.
Like, oh no, the consequence is by action.
This, I gotta say, this sounds...
Pulling pins out of grenades because he likes the sound it makes.
Oh, darn.
This is the, this is the, you got a winning formula here.
You should copy, right?
Yeah, every story.
Start with a goblin and then work your way up.
Right, exactly.
Just a little goblin guy just doing little goblin shenanigans and then he faces the consequences
of his actions.
It's a, it's trying, it's trying to...
It sounds so simple when you just say it like that.
You have to...
I think it, I mean, I think the thing is it is simple.
It is just that I haven't, I haven't set aside the time to do any thinking or doing.
I've just thought about, like, in the future, this will be what I do.
Something related to that.
But right now I'm doing something else and I'll, I'll never, I'll like, never actually
properly think about anything.
Don't, don't think.
Just draw.
That's, that's my...
Well, that too.
But like, what, what I mean is like brainstorming.
Like, talking to someone is so much easier to get ideas out than just thinking to yourself.
You ever, um...
You're having a conversation that you can bounce off of someone's, like a word someone says.
You ever thought about having like a partner, um, like a writing partner of sorts?
I'm not, I'm not applying.
I'm not applying.
I'm not applying, but I'm just, um, just wondering if there's someone you, you think you could
like, you could trust.
A writing group or partner, just like a, I don't know, writing room, a creative space
where a lot of people are doing things creative and you can talk to them.
That would be good.
Some sort of thing like that.
Yeah.
It kind of sucks that you have no...
You just walk in.
Yeah, go on.
Like, you walk into a room and you got your, like, your kawafi and you're like, uh, so,
uh, how about there's a guy and he falls over.
How about this little goblin?
A cliff.
And then it's like, ah, yeah.
It's, uh, how about this little goblin, right?
And, uh, due to his hubris, right?
He gets blown up.
Something happened.
It always has to have a goblin and an explosion in it.
Right, exactly.
But how, how do we do it?
He, um, I don't know.
Maybe, uh, he messes with the people and the people are like, you know what?
I had enough of this little goblin character.
We're going to, we're going to trick him.
And, um...
Yeah.
He keeps, he keeps like throwing rocks at the guy who has the bazooka and he's like,
haha, this won't be backfire on me.
And then the guy with the bazooka gets you, shoots him.
He shoots him and then he's like, damn, I should have not poked.
I should have not pissed off the man with the bazooka.
And maybe it could be a metaphor for like property rights and being a libertarian or something.
There'll be like a cute mascot character that holds up a sign that just says the moral at the end.
Yeah, he turns around to like, he turns, after the goblin gets blown up and he's like,
half of his body is laying, he's bleeding out.
He looks at the camera and says, I can't believe capitalism caused this.
Then he dies.
Yeah, see, it's so much better than like, the amount of progress is made in this.
Very cool is so much greater than like the number of hours I've thought about thinking about starting about.
I think, I think a very easy way to kind of like write is like, you ever watch a venture bros?
No.
Well, well, I guess this isn't really a spoiler, but venture bros is only written by two guys.
And you could tell by watching the show because every scene there's always two people like always bouncing off of each other.
And they're foils.
Like every dynamic in the show is like a foil to each other.
Like one character is like selfish, self-absorbed or like stupid and the other character would usually be smart or like centered.
And they bounce back at each other.
And if you can think of like a good dynamic, like the basic one is kind of like, oh, one's the silly guy and the other one's the straight guy, right?
And that's usually like a good starting point.
Okay, the silly guy and the straight guy get into a car accident.
What does the silly guy do?
I don't think gay people are that silly.
I feel like that's a homophobic comment to make.
Yeah.
Oh, my bad.
I forgot.
Silly was a sexuality.
Well, yeah, it's clown gender.
It's clown gender.
Yeah.
LGBTS.
Where's C?
Where's clown in the alphabets?
It's the plus.
That's why the plus is there.
It's LGBT.
It's C-L-O-W-N-G-B-T.
It's C-L-O-W-N.
I am speaking of clowns.
I need to meet Andrew Hussey.
We need to unite forces because he's unironically.
I think I know what his end game is by reading Psycholonia.
I think I know what he's trying to do.
Do you know his Instagram account?
Oh, yeah.
The whole clown boy-y thing.
Yeah.
I started following him on my pasta account with the hopes of that being the first step in stone.
So we could have clown-to-clown communication.
Pure honks.
Nothing real words.
No thoughts, just honks.
A friend of mine showed me screenshots of some sort of private discord with Andrew Hussey.
He was talking stuff about his left-wing beliefs that unironically I agree with too.
I think this guy unironically might be on the same page as me.
I need to meet him.
I need to be as equal.
I need to create some sort of franchise that's unrelated to clowns.
So I could amass the same heights he has.
And then we need to bounce off of each other and convince.
Because unironically, I do kind of have this big grand plan that's kind of like...
There is an end game.
I have an unironic end game to pasta the clown.
That's kind of like what Z is going through in Psycholonia.
I have an end game.
I'll say it after the podcast because I don't want this idea to come out just yet.
But I'll tell you what this crazy end game is like later.
But I do have a clown influencer end game.
That's why when reading Psycholonia, I was tripping out.
Oh my god, what the fuck?
It's fucking...
Did you see the latest chapter?
Yeah, I did.
I love all the designs. They're so funny.
I really like how the clowns look in Psycholonia.
They're all kind of low-key juggalo-based.
I haven't read the latest chapter yet.
I haven't read the latest chapter yet, so no spoilers.
I get my clown...
It's just jubilites, jubilite designs.
Yeah, they're more jubilites.
My clown designs are more like killer clowns from outer space.
That's how I get mine from.
That's my fucking influence.
Have you guys seen that movie?
No, I haven't.
It's just Psycholonia.
It's Psycholonia.
There's a space clown in Psycholonia, right?
It all comes back.
Uh, based...
It's funny that you mentioned the whole like,
Andrew Hussie, I want to make like a big thing so that we can talk.
Because I remember feeling like that once when I read Homestuck
and I'm like, oh, I should become a super famous person
so that I can be friends with Andrew Hussie and talk about stuff.
It's such a visual reaction.
I know as a mere viewer, an audience member,
that I have no sway in this situation.
I have to become like a juggernaut in order to say hello.
I must.
Yeah, it's like a nice thought.
It's that parasocial relationship thing, you know?
I mean, it's like that, but it's like a little...
It's turned to a little more of a good end, I guess,
if it makes you want to do something with your life.
If it motivates you to do...
I mean, I think a lot of the stuff I've ever done
has been motivated partially by feeling like I need to impress people.
Oh my god, that's me.
So if I don't have anything to show, why is anyone going to pay attention to me?
Why is anyone going to say hello or whatever?
I'm not good at the social stuff.
I can't just say hello and it'd be a really cool hello.
No, I need stuff to back it up.
I need images. I need a website with my comics on it.
I can say, hey, look what I do.
Social anxiety is like, you need to compensate for it all the time.
Right. I always fantasize about being invited to special events in different countries.
To countries I wouldn't even go to visit unless I was invited to, you know?
Uh-huh.
There's like a comic festival.
I guess a big example that I would think of is there's this comic creator named Ed Piscor
who got commissioned by a rapper in Japan to do album art for him.
And Ed Piscor says, I'll do it if you pay for a luxury vacation for me to spend a month in Japan.
And he did. He got paid that way, right?
And then when he got to Japan, the creator of Afro Samurai heard that he was in Japan
and he assigned a meeting with him so they could meet.
And that's so fucking rad.
Imagine going to a country and one of the big artists in that country finds out you're there
and they DM you like, yo, let's fucking meet up, dude.
That's so fucking cool.
That sounds so like, I don't know, it's that like, wouldn't it be nice to be famous
so I could do these specific things, you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know whether that would be like a person that I would...
Like, it would be cool if people were interested in what I did.
But like, I don't, I haven't really thought about like,
if this person said, hey, love your stuff, let's meet up and chat.
Even if it was Andrew, I'd say, I wouldn't even know what to do.
It'd be like, oh.
Hi, hello.
I would, I would want, I would want him to say, hey, listen, hey, listen.
I've got, I've got a plan and you, and I want you to be in on it.
And I've got something that we could, we could work together on.
I've got some, I've got a devious, a devious plan for some kind of collaboration.
I want you to show up on my YouTube reviews.
I want you to appear in my move, my nostalgic movie reviews.
Doug Walker.
Yes, please.
Oh, yes.
I always wanted to be in a skit in a...
Andrew Pussy.
That guy with the glasses.
Doug, Doug Walker appears in Homestuck 2 to say, oh, what am I doing here?
I already, what do you do?
I already reviewed this movie.
And then he yells.
He yells really loud.
But Doug, it's not a movie.
That's credit card?
Um, I can't wait, I can't wait for the day Andrew Pussy DMs me.
And he, he, he, he, it's post a picture of him with an AK-47.
And he says like, geez, he strap up.
We're going to make cycloneos in real life.
He says, he says, it says, I've, I've, I've faked a gas attack on the island of Nantucket.
Get on your boat and come out.
We've got to, we've got to fend off the mainland police.
On the, on the island of America.
Yeah.
I like, oh, right, right away, sir.
And then I hop into my clown movie.
Right away, sir, yes.
Sorry, yes, sir.
Yeah, yeah, right away, of course.
Oh, God.
You get into your, your clown boat and there's like 50,000 people stuffed into a tiny little yacht.
It's so...
Tiny little rowboat.
Just all in one boat.
Oh, that's great.
Yeah, give your full will, your filled with ideas.
My name you think of that.
There you go.
But I should write the story about a clown boat where there's so many clowns in the boat.
Look, just, just, just, here's an easy formula.
Just one character is super horny and the other character is not horny.
Boom.
There you go.
There's a formula for you.
Okay, re-reading psychologials.
It's like that meme with the guy shooting the message over the, the cyberpunk guy shoots the message over the head.
You know?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But it's like, but it, but you're reading it and you're like, oh boy.
Uh, the, the, the, I don't know, fucking capitalism is bad and millennials sure do you hate, hate life.
And the shooting the message over your head is wouldn't it be fucked up if there were clowns in a boat?
I wanted to, I, I want to describe psycholonial as it's literally the Joker movie.
If the Joker actually believed in something.
Mmm.
I still haven't, I've never saw the Joker.
I never saw the Joker.
The Joker, I haven't seen it either.
The Joker is just psycholonials, but dumbed down.
But if you, but if you liked, if you liked all the Joker memes you've seen, it's probably worth the watch.
Um, I kind of meant to watch and I just never got around to it.
I, um, I wanted to get a wacky Phoenix.
I wanted to make a wacky Phoenix.
I wanted to get, um, I wanted to get a screenshot from the Joker movie.
The one where it's like, he's on the talk show and it's all like, wait, you actually believe so-and-so.
And then the Joker replies, yes, and I'm tired of pretending.
It's not, I was going to get the guy saying like, wait, you actually think it's funny when cops get shot.
And then it would be Z in the Joker's chair and she'd be like, yes, and I'm tired of pretending.
It's not.
It's a good meme.
If someone wants to beat me to it, just go ahead.
I got, I got, I got, I'm going to scramble.
I'm going to scramble off the podcast and post it.
I'm not even going to at you.
This is a mess.
It's fine.
I still tweet, I still tweet all the time.
But this is a message for Andrew Hussie.
Don't worry, I'm going to, I'm going to get huge.
We're going to clown up pretty soon.
It's going to be great.
I have, I have a couple of clown plans, a couple of plans that might put me on the CIA watchlist.
I can't say more.
And CIA watchlist, as in they follow your like social media.
Oh, yeah.
I like you.
Aren't you, isn't it true?
Isn't it true that you're on trial now?
Is it true that you are the editor for the pizza party podcast now?
Yes.
Yes, I am.
I am the editor for the pizza party podcast.
You're like there.
Eleazar.
Yeah, I'm there.
I'm there.
Eleazar.
That's so fucked up.
That is pretty fucked up.
Can you like, can you like make them, you just sentence mix them to say stupid shit?
Easily.
I don't even have to try.
Got him.
It would be child.
Damn.
Got him.
But I'm, I'm very tempted to, to make like a, like a, like a compilation of all the same
sounds that like pan pizza likes to repeat in like every episode.
Wait, who does pan pizza?
He has like a, he has like a, he has like five sounds that he always makes in every episode
and he likes to play them on repeat.
Or you just like to like say it a lot, right?
Like, uh, like there's the classic like, yeah, yeah, like he'll say, yeah, yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Like every time someone says something like mean or rude, he would be like under his breath
will say like rude or, or, or if it's like, or if there's like a quiet silence, he'd be
like, yeah.
Yeah.
Like he'll, he'll do that.
Like I, it's just something I fucking noticed.
This is a monster.
Wow.
He's such an asshole.
I can't believe it.
He would say such terrible things.
He's not, he's not human.
He's beyond.
Speaking of, and also I kind of like, uh, so, so, so you know, you know, Nolan, right?
He's former member of the peaks of party podcast.
I, I mean, I only knew him because I guess, I guess in the past him and Trixie had some
bad blood, but then I guess that didn't matter at all.
And then I was on that episode with him and I didn't, I don't know.
So I knew that he was a guy on the thing.
Yeah.
Um, he, uh, he recently left the show because, um, I don't know if I don't even know if getting
canceled the right term, but let's say he was, he was pretty sus person.
Like, yeah.
For the longest time, I would always hear rumors about him like emotionally manipulating
like other artists to like get artwork out of them.
I read his letter.
I read his like response.
The Google doc thing.
Yes.
Yeah.
I have a copy of it because he deleted the original.
Good.
Yeah.
I mean that forever.
I still have it.
And he, um, yeah, like the whole he, for people who don't know, um, Nolan is very infamous
for having a very specific fetish.
Like he, uh, he liked it when like characters got wrapped and like, as in like, as in like
tied up and like, uh, yeah.
In, uh, what's the word?
Not entangled.
Uh, just like wrapped up bound up.
Yeah.
And if you, um, and if you like, for example, like if his little avatar on the pizza party
podcast looked like a pill, but this, it isn't actually a pill.
It's actually supposed to be, um, Jake, the dog from adventure time, like wrapped up in
web from one specific episode.
It just like stylized like a pill, right?
Uh, what?
Wait, look, wait, hold up.
I'm going to look for a picture.
Okay.
If you, if you look for a picture of like, Nolan's like avatar, he has like a, he has
like a little yellow and white like pill on his shirt.
Okay.
But it's supposed to be a Jake, the dog, like wrapped up in spider web.
Neat.
I remember that episode.
Right.
Yeah.
That's the episode with the spider.
So weird.
That's so weird.
You would do that.
Make that your logo.
Okay.
Whatever.
I always felt like this guy has like Nutella smear it on his arms.
Yeah.
Um, and he would specifically always like, you know, there's nothing wrong with like having
a fetish and commissioning people to like draw it as long as like the art it consists.
But the weird thing, the two of the weird things he would do is like, he would kind of use
his popularity on the podcast to like emotionally manipulate like art out of people.
To get artists to draw.
Sure.
To draw his fetish.
And also for some reason he would always want the artists to draw like they're so not getting
wrapped.
See what, what I don't really understand is like, I wouldn't, if I had like a fetish at
first, a particular thing, I, I don't really get like wanting a particular person like
to draw it or it seemed, I don't know.
And this kind of thing, it seems like you want all these different artists to like draw
your thing.
I would be like, maybe I have one artist whose style I like and maybe I like to see when
they draw it.
Uh, I don't know.
Like what I'm saying is that it's a very like weirdly, like personal relationship there.
I feel like you could,
Between artist and con commissioner.
Right.
And he would, he would also like, um, still like get commissions from like minors to get
their like little sonas like wrapped in web too, which is so kind of, he was doing this,
he was doing this until like last summer.
It's a little,
It's a little sus.
It's a little weird.
There's, I think there's, I think there's sometimes little like kind of context.
There's like weird thing that people could do that maybe at first don't seem weird.
You could like, you, you could explain like any, any particular instance of that you could
explain like, Oh, well, it's not about the fact that we're underage or maybe he didn't
know the artist was underage or maybe it was like some, but like, if you have like a pattern
of doing that, then it's like, it's then it's big, then it becomes sus.
Right.
Yeah.
Um, it kind of reminds me like, um, uh, do you remember the whole incident with, uh,
John Bob?
I watched, um, I didn't really know what that was about, but I did watch the, the Bernie
video about it.
Yeah.
It's very, um, yeah.
That's a really good video.
I like to rewatch it.
Um, I'm not calling Nolan a groomer.
There's like no evidence that he's a groomer.
I read the letter and like his explanation, it did, it like, it doesn't mean that like
it's okay to be like having this sort of like pseudo relationship over this fetish with
like underage.
It doesn't make it okay, but it did kind of be like, I can see why.
Like he basically says that like basically an older person sort of groomed him when he
was a kid and he like internalized it and sort of told himself that it was okay to like
cope with it, I guess, which is like, I guess I can see why that would happen.
It doesn't sound too outrageous.
So yeah.
Okay.
No, I got that.
I'm just saying that like with John Bob specifically, like he, um, he would like to draw other people's
hands, like beating, beating him up.
Right.
And like at first, at first it's like a fun, at first it's like a funny gag.
But it's kind of like, I don't know.
It's just kind of weird because it later turns out that he might have had like a humiliation
fetish.
Right.
And so he's getting like all these other people's like popular sonos and he's like using that
to beat up his little, oh, I'm just a little guy.
I'm just a little guy getting beat up.
Haha.
Isn't that funny?
Like it is.
It is funny.
I feel like, I feel like, I feel like, um, this is probably something artists should like
look out for is like when people draw other people's sonos, how, what they do that, like,
like for example, let's say like, uh, I don't know, let's say someone.
What was the word?
There's like a particular word for this.
Right.
For when you, when you, when you, when you like get art, when you get fetish art drawn
of yours for you, but and you're like, you try to like hunt down more people and get
more.
There's a particular like verb that I had never heard before that someone said, oh,
Nolan was blanking.
And I said, what?
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, wait.
Fetish mining.
Mining.
Yeah.
That was it.
He's a notorious fetish miner.
It's so crazy.
I remember.
But it's M-I-N-E-R.
Yeah.
I remember when someone, that definition was floating around on Twitter.
There was like several people in the comments who said like, oh yeah, Nolan from the pizza
party podcast.
Like, um, he, he, he was like that.
And it's so funny because if he, like, I've talked to other friends and other like little
art circles and everyone, every other person kind of has like a, yeah, like Nolan commissioned
me to draw my sonna getting wrapped.
Like you, you fucking see that.
Oh my God.
This motherfucker was getting every other person to draw.
Like, it's just so weird.
Like, why, like, I want to see you specifically get wrapped.
Oh my God.
Like, okay.
Like, yeah.
Yeah.
It's so weird.
I don't, I don't, that's not how I relate to pornography.
Yeah.
Personally.
I don't, I don't think I ever commissioned anything NSFW.
Does that remember?
Um, I want to see commission people to draw like Pasta the Clown, but mostly just funky
poses.
Honestly.
Yeah.
I wouldn't, if I were, I wouldn't, I don't think I would do it.
I would feel like a weird, it would be kind of like I was asking them to show me themselves
naked or something.
Or like, do something.
It's like, hey, you do something to make me fucking come, right?
Like it's not.
Yeah.
It's sort of not even, it's, I would feel uncomfortable with it because it sort of makes
it like not just about the content.
Yeah.
Right.
Like, oh, draw Sonic the Hedgehog getting wrapped.
I mean, that's fine.
Cause Sonic's like a fictional character, but like draw, draw Pasta the Clown getting
wrapped.
It's like, uh, I think I'm good.
Yeah.
It.
At least Merlogic has the common courtesy to have cartoon characters by Wonder Bread.
Yeah.
He's got, he's, he's got, he's not here, he's not here for your OC.
He's not interested in your OC unless she's blonde, rich and white.
Right.
Sure.
Which, you know.
And no, no one has that.
No one.
Oh yeah.
But also, um, I'm pseudo, like taking over Nolan's role on the podcast kind of, that's
fucking epic.
That's fucking epic.
That's, that's literally based in red pill.
That's, that's based in rap pills.
Yeah.
I'm kind of taking over his role in the podcast, but like on my, on the previous episode I
showed up on the podcast, uh, let's just say that a lot of people thought I was little
too cringe.
So I don't know how consistently I'm going to be on because, um, the episode actually
was that, was that we, okay, I would, people should, people should go migrate from this
episode and go, wait, people got to start posting no cheesy, no watch on PPP episodes.
That's the only way.
Go and find Cheesy's last episode and say no cheesy, no watch, no cheesy, no watch.
If you go, yeah, yeah.
So once the new episode drops, which is probably going to be probably already dropped by now,
um, or it drops next week, I don't know, pan pizza is weird sometimes with a scheduling
like for sometimes two weeks in a row, he just won't upload anything.
And then he'll just upload something the next, it's so, yeah, it's so weirdly consistent.
But um, the next episode, I'm not on cause they wanted to, I remember pan like first
asking me if I wanted to be on and I'm like, sure.
And then like once everyone was in the call, um, I tried to jump in and I couldn't cause
I didn't have the recording role.
And I'm like, and then I DM pan like saying, like, um, I don't got the recording role.
I can't jump into the call and then pans like, yeah, actually, um, I second thought,
we just kind of want to focus on the guests, which, uh, isn't a, isn't a bad thing.
It's just kind of like, they probably don't really want me to inconsistent.
Also, like I kind of low key pissed them off.
Like the last episode I was on.
Why?
I, so towards the end of the last episode, um, I got them all mad at me because, um, so,
okay, so what happened was that we were on the topic of whether or not like,
like hot girls listen to the pizza party podcast.
And, um, Izzy said that.
Okay.
Izzy said, no, I'm going to say no.
Yeah, that's what, that's what me and Pam were saying.
They're all listening to the PCP.
Yeah.
All the hot girls listen to the PCP, but, um, but, uh, but, but Izzy said that,
yeah, actually there is hot girls that listen to, to the pizza party podcast.
And she linked someone called stripper waifu, right.
And like, I, I guess I, I assume they might have been some sort of sex worker with
that name and with their profile picture that was suggested.
I, I looked for their media tab and I couldn't find any pictures.
And then I'm like, Izzy, this person doesn't got any pictures in the media tabs.
How could I confirm they're hot?
Right.
And then I noticed in their bio, they have an only fans, right?
And, um, so, so I was like, can you, can you, I want to see this person like me.
Okay.
Find me, find me the links.
Show me stripper waifu.
Hold up.
Let's see if I could, let's see if she still has that name.
Um, well, okay.
Okay.
While I look, while I, please, I'm so thirsty.
While I look, while I look for that, um, tell you the rest of what happened.
For sure.
Sure.
So, so basically, um, I see that she has an only fans, right?
Um, yeah.
And I'm like, oh, cool.
Um, let's, let's check her prices live on the podcast, right?
And, and they, and they, and they were all like, they're all like, uh, don't do that.
That's weird.
Don't do that.
Right.
Like, uh, don't do that.
And I'm like, all right.
Okay.
Like they all, they all told me to like, they all told me to stop.
I'm like, okay, right.
Right.
And then I, and then I pretended that I stopped and then I quickly blurt out like her prices.
And then they all like, I'm super fucking mad at me.
Okay.
Well, they told you they didn't want you to.
Yeah, they didn't tell me they didn't.
No, yeah, I mean, I, I get that.
I get, I understand I went too far.
Okay.
I don't really get why it's like a problem, but like, I guess if they didn't want you
to, then whatever.
I don't know.
I guess cause I did like, I guess they didn't want me to think, um, I don't know.
They maybe thought I was going to go into a more misogynistic joke.
I mean, here, okay.
Here's the thing, the stripper waifu, like, um, like she had.
Some really affordable prices.
Oh, okay.
Like, unironically, her prices are really fucking affordable.
What, what a deal.
Yeah.
And I was about to say, like, I think it was like a three point, like, I think it was
three dollars, three, three point 50, like dollars a month.
And I'm like, Oh my God, that's a fucking, that's a fucking steal.
That's nothing.
Right.
Like, yeah, I could afford 10 stripper waifus.
Well, okay.
Well, you got to, we got to, all right.
We got to patch things up.
We got to patch things up between you and the pizza, the pizza party podcast.
So we can have a man on the inside subverting them.
Yeah, I'll be the, I'll be the PCP member on the inside.
You can't, can't stop me.
Um, base.
Show me the lady.
I'm looking for the money.
Please, please.
She's easy.
I'm looking for anything.
I'll even, I'll even pay three pounds or anything.
Please, she needs, she needs my money.
Cheesy.
I can't.
Oh my God, you are literally, you are literally.
Destroying a sex worker's career.
On our right now, I'm, I'm, wait, wait, I'm sorry.
Haha.
Wait, I literally just want to see her and think if I say if I think she's hot.
I just want to see, do I, do I agree with Izzy that a hot girl
watches the pizza party podcast?
Okay, cool.
I found her.
Uh-oh.
Oh, no.
I'm very skeptical.
Okay.
Here's her.
Yeah.
Okay.
I found our only fans is right here.
Oh my God.
This is it.
Oh, no, no, no.
The symbol of truth.
Um.
Hmm.
Well, what is that?
I can only see like a tiny, I can only see her avatar and it's so filtered.
I, I can't really.
Yeah, I just can't tell.
I can't, I can't really even make a determination.
Okay, wait, so it's, oh wait, stripper waifu underscore.
Let's strip her underscore waifu.
All right.
Or wait, this one is stripper underscore waifu.
But do you have like a Twitter or something?
Um, look, I swear she had a Twitter, I mean, she might have nuked it.
Hmm.
Cause of the pizza.
It's cause you talked about it on the pizza party podcast.
She just couldn't take the heat.
I, I killed, I killed her.
Now, now the PC, she's on the PCP.
Oh, hold up, hold up, founder.
Found her.
Here it is.
Mistress Wednesday, stripper waifu.
Uh, okay.
I, I would say, I would say that if someone called this a hot girl, I wouldn't be like,
Nuh-uh.
So this is fine.
No, she's, she's, she's attractive.
She's attractive.
All right, Izzy, you win this round.
You win this time.
I'll get you next, I'll get you next time.
Um, damn, she, she, she cranked up her prices.
No, it's cause you gave her, it's cause you gave her the, the, the signal boost.
Yeah, I, I like, you fucked up the supply demand curve.
I could have, I could have, yeah, exact, exactly.
Yeah.
Once I blur it out, the 3.50 and then everyone in the, everyone was like,
that's so affordable.
What, what a steal.
So they all jumped in, they all jumped in and now it went out.
Damn, I fucked it.
Well, it looks like she's doing good.
Um, does it say like percentage of, doesn't it?
Good for her.
Yeah.
I, I hope, I hope this conversation doesn't backfire on me.
It probably won't.
Who, who listens to, who listens to the PCP?
I can't think of a single.
Yeah, no, yeah, only, only hot girls listen to the PCP.
That's right.
And they like this, and they like this kind of stuff.
I love going into the comments of that episode.
And like, there's like, like the majority of people were like,
saying that I was like, cringed, not funny.
I kept talking over people and there's like three people who really liked
me and said like, I need to, I need to come back.
Hmm.
And I know Cheesy, no watch, no Cheesy.
No, Cheesy, no watch, no.
Cheesy, no watch.
So wait, I want to know what he want to know.
Yeah, but I wanna know about your new place.
Oh, all right.
I'm in a new place of residence.
I never really talk about it because, of course,
it's embarrassing.
I was still living with my parents.
Yeah, that had to go, that had to go.
Yep.
Yeah, it's always been difficult
like trying to figure out where to move if I wanted to
because if I go further into London,
the prices get really expensive.
And if I go further out of London,
if I need to commute into London for work,
then it's just more of an annoyance.
And I got an opportunity, a person I know,
set me up with a room and they've given me
like pretty good rent for it.
And it's really nice.
I'm in a place and I have fucking,
I have a little bathroom to myself.
I have a small kitchen area to myself.
It's all one big room and like a fold out sofa bed.
It's like so much privacy, it's unbelievable.
That actually sounds considerably nicer than where I live.
I'm jealous.
Cool.
It's, yeah, I feel like I can,
that my favorite thing about it, unironically,
is that I am responsible for cleaning up my own messes.
I know that I usually try to clean up my own,
I usually try to clean up my own stuff
when I was at my parents' house just because it's polite.
A lot of the time it's like dirty dishes,
only like two of those are mine, not, there's no space.
Somebody's got to do the washing up.
Do I have to do it?
I didn't put that shit there.
That would always annoy me.
But now, if there's a big pile of crap,
I know that it's me that did that.
And it's my responsibility and it feels fine.
It feels completely guilt-free, no annoyance at all.
I'll scrub those dishes, yes, sir,
and I'll do it with a smile on my face.
And I'm, it's all, I mean,
I'll probably get bored of it eventually.
But I just like that.
No, never.
God, God, I wish that was me.
God, I wish that was me.
It's, it's, it's very good.
I can't, I can't like,
I can't pretend that it wasn't like very fortunate
that this happened.
I just happened to know a person who had the space,
the person they were running with left
and they liked me.
So friendship-
It all works out.
That's the, I mean, that's the best,
that's all the best like deals,
all the best situations you get in life
because like you knew someone and they were like,
oh, hey, I can hook you up.
Yeah, I mean, that's how to do it.
The professional term is connections, right?
Right, right, right, right.
Yeah, what the fuck?
Network.
What the fuck's up with those?
What?
It's just his nepotism.
It's so annoying.
What's the deal with networking?
I mean, I hate it, but like,
I will never say no on principle, you know,
I will never, my principles will never get so large
that I will refuse free shit if it's offered.
Oh my God, as a socialist,
I want nothing but free shit, am I right?
My fellow commies?
Yes, but also, I don't know, you should,
you have to share, you have to share that room
with everyone, with me, with just me, only me.
I'm the only one who gets socialism.
You have to share the room with me
and I love to masturbate.
No.
That's one of the dust, that's,
actually, I'm not going to say that, that's gross.
I masturbate, I masturbate naked, so you just have to.
No, no one can tell me, don't do that.
Nobody can come into the door and say, what are you doing?
No, no.
It's all like, I'm jerking off in here.
Hey, I'm jerking off with the door open.
Hey, I'm jerking off in here.
What are you talking about?
Hey, I'm jerking off over here.
I'm jerking here.
It's actually, you know, this is America.
This is the best thing about it.
This is America and no one can tell you
that you can't jerk off in your own doorway
with the door open, facing out
into the rest of the apartment complex.
Biden didn't say day one, we could jerk off, day one.
And we better, and we better now,
before he force feminizes all of us.
We better get it in while we're still going.
I'm way ahead of him.
Hey, we're first jerking off,
then freeing the kids in cages.
I think that was step two.
Can't wait.
You Europeans are so progressive.
You're so ahead of the curve.
We're, we're cavemen stuck back in America.
Yeah.
Still waiting to be forced feminized by our presence.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I don't know, I feel like,
I feel like in the UK specifically,
we're behind America when it comes
to forced feminization policy.
Yeah, it's kind of.
It's a race.
The race is on.
Yeah, J.K. Rowland saw trans people and be like,
yeah, I don't like that.
Then she used her wand.
No, no, no, no.
Yeah.
No, I don't like that.
She summoned all her, all her, her coven.
She got to, she saw.
Dude, I just realized, you know, you know,
punk, you know, the character I made.
She's a pumpkin.
You know that pumpkin meme where he says,
no, I don't want that.
I wonder where that, where.
No, I don't know.
It's like a pumpkin who says no.
Okay.
Wait, what?
It's like a pumpkin who says no.
I just figured that out.
I don't know what.
That's where it retroactively inspired.
Is this a, is this a, is this a British meme?
No, I don't.
No.
Okay.
Wait, oh yeah.
Oh, it's just like, it's a game.
It's like a, oh, wait, oh, I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, I remember, right?
The hungry pumpkin who said, you say,
give me the french fries.
You click on something else.
He says, no, I don't want that.
That's punk.
No.
Purple sleeves.
Oh my God.
No.
It's punk's dad.
Is this retroactive lore?
This is true.
This is punk's dad.
It's kind of base.
Oh God, he eats the whole mug of coffee.
Give me the salt.
Okay.
He just wants the salt.
Why just the salt?
Why is it just a stick of butter?
Like his,
All right, complete tangent.
So I just had a brain blast about that.
Like his angry eyes.
I don't know.
I think I've seen this.
I can't,
I can't tell if I've ever seen this before or not.
It's too,
my mind is just too much of a swirling miasma of
genius thoughts.
It may have appeared in like a flash
in some sort of meme compilation.
Wasn't it on, it looks like one of those like kids
like flash games you could play at school that didn't.
It was,
it was on a site called pumpkin,
like pumpkin spelled wrong.
Like pump.kin.
I can't remember.
It was like an old site and it was just sort of like
learning games,
but made by like non native English speakers.
So it was kind of like broken English
and didn't really teach English very well.
And it was funny how bad it was.
Like those children videos that like are like generated
by people in India.
Yes.
Something like that.
That's pretty based, pretty based.
Pretty fucking based.
Well, now we know.
All right.
Now we know the pumpkin story.
It's just so weird to me.
Like I made a pumpkin who says no,
and I have had seen this before that.
I just didn't make the connection until right now.
So consciously you were thinking about it.
That's just something pumpkins do, right?
Like they don't like things and reject them.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
No, it's just a normal pumpkin thing.
Pumpkin.
It's like a,
like in Cinderella when they did turns the pumpkin
into a carriage and the pumpkins like,
no, I don't want to be a carriage.
And he doesn't want to be a carriage anymore.
It turns back into a pumpkin.
He got forced carification.
Oh my God.
It's just like,
you know, we all understand that like,
you know, foxes are clever.
Pumpkins, very picky, very cheesy.
They do like to deny things.
Yeah.
It's time to learn.
I'm going to go to wikipedia.pumpkin.
Christ.
No.
I'm going to learn something about pumpkins.
See if they actually are picky.
Yeah.
Let's find out.
Not going to lie.
I was a big fan of the Gibbon monkey talk
in the last episode.
I thought that was really good.
I learned things about baboons,
that episode that I can never unlearn.
And I-
You mean orangutans.
Yes, yes, orangutans.
Whoops.
Is your flange still there?
My flange is,
I have been,
every time I see another male,
now I have been challenging him on the strut
and just beating the shit out of him.
And every time my flange grows bigger and bigger.
Yeah.
You challenged that one homeless guy on the bus.
That's why his mask was all bloody.
That's why his mask was bloody.
Yeah.
That's courtesy of Ben Flange-Saint.
His flange deflated as mine swelled
to ever greater, ever greater size.
And resplendence.
Every male you defeat, your flange gets bigger and bigger
until you're just fucking massive.
I think that's how it works.
I'm still a little bit iffy on how does an orangutan's body
know that it has defeated the alpha orangutan
and must begin to grow, do you emit flange hormones?
Do the-
And yet it happens.
Do the orangutans?
Apparently.
Yes, gone.
No, you could finish your orangutans.
I was just gonna say, do orangutans rip off each other's flange
and that's just like...
And stick it on their own?
And stick it on their own face and sew it in with gorilla glue?
They eat it and they absorb the flange nutrients
and they just get bigger.
It's got that special flange tissue.
There's only so much to go around,
so they have to eat it off of each other and repurpose it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's just like eating penis makes your penis bigger.
Exactly.
There's only so much.
Straight there.
Apparently pumpkins I learn now are easy and fun to grow.
They are not picky when it comes to habitat for growing.
So it actually doesn't happen in the real world.
Pumpkins are actually quite amicable to situations.
I can't believe the media would smear pumpkins.
I can't believe the media would smear pumpkins
saying they're not as crazy.
Well, this is like how the one famous drow
that everyone writes books about is the only good one.
The drow are all villains,
but Drizda Ordon is the good guy who goes against the grain.
These are lone individuals who stand up
against the tyranny of their culture.
They were just sick of how chill and fun and cool
all their pumpkin relatives were,
and they were like, no, not me.
I'll take the road less traveled, thanks.
I will inherit the role of the asshole pumpkin.
There has to be one.
Yeah, pumpkins, like the bottoms of pumpkins
look kind of like assholes, but I think it makes sense.
If you cut a hole in it, you can fuck it like an asshole too.
Yeah.
Did you know?
Guys, don't give me any ideas.
I might draw that.
I might draw it, then I'll become an SFW artist.
You guys better not.
You could do it if you wanted to.
I could do it.
Can I commit?
I'll hold that sort of Damocles over my own head
in a bid to get people interested in my brain.
I'll hold that sort of Damocles over the pumpkin
and think, should I cut a hole in it?
Should I lower the sword and cut the hole?
I'm on a commission you gave to draw your Sona,
fucking a pumpkin.
Nothing weird about that.
Which Sona?
I don't know.
There's so many.
Just pick one, pick one, pick one.
Draw me a pumpkin wrapped up in a spiderweb, please.
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh, stinky.
It all, it all circles back around.
Time to wrap up this section game.
I was gonna say, are we at voicemail time about?
Yeah, it seems like.
It's like, I guess we are.
I don't know.
I didn't have much else to talk about, I don't think.
I guess I'm not really there.
So let's, I made a, I guess I'm making clown adoptables.
Are you really?
Yeah, I am.
This is like the fourth time I'd done it.
Oh wait, I saw,
I saw you made some monster on Instagram.
Yeah, yeah, I made like a,
made a little post about it.
And adoptables are,
adoptables are very interesting now,
cause the whole talk with like NFT,
like people are like,
oh, you could finally own digital art, finally.
And it's like, well, adoptable has been around for like years.
Yeah.
You could already own like.
It's so, I mean, it's so stupid.
It's almost as if the NFT doesn't mean
or do anything.
There's no contract.
So there's no legal liability for anything.
You just say you'll,
you could just sell the adoptables
and then continue to draw the thing
and nobody can stop you.
No.
Same with NFTs.
You can just say, hey, you own it
and then you can just delete it
and then you just do it again.
Then they don't have that specific thing.
With the adoptable,
they like literally give the person the JPEG.
So they like, like, I mean,
it's the JPEG and it's the understanding
between you and them that this is yours.
No, I don't understand anyone.
I'm not an understanding person.
I'm kind of like the goblin who blew up in a way.
Well, I'm just the whole goblin getting into shenanigans.
Yeah, you should have.
Thanks to my own hubris.
I sold too many adoptables.
That's what I should try.
I should try a comic about a little goblin
who gets into shenanigans selling adoptables.
Then he gets blown up at the end.
Oh, wait, the goblin accidentally creates
like an offensive adoptable
and his name is credited as a creator
and he gets attacked by Antifa or something.
Maybe he makes adoptables and he puts them
and he ties them to NFTs and then twist.
What blows up is actually the price of the cryptocurrency
and his NFTs are with a fortune
and he becomes rich beyond his wildest dreams
thanks to his own hubris.
And he buys a bazooka and he doesn't know how to use it.
And then he gets blown up.
Yes, yes, obviously.
He gets rounded up with all the billionaires
and then gunned down by Antifa at the end.
Yeah, that's a good ending.
Oh, good ending.
I hope that's how cycloneo ends.
But with adoptables is kind of like an honor system.
You gotta like, the previous ones I'd be like,
okay, so this is like, you own this character
but every time you use it for anything
you have to credit me as like designer.
And that's about it.
But I think I'm gonna actually create some sort of physical,
not a physical form, but like a digital form
that people can just like put their signature on.
Like you own this character
and you can do whatever you want this character.
You just always gotta credit me as designer, right?
But also I wanna add like,
oh, you can't sell this character as an NFT.
Yeah.
And I think a bunch of just-
I would hate that if somebody did that.
Yeah, and I think artists should just,
now at this point just any artist
if you do any commission,
if you don't want your artwork to ever be NFT,
you should like clarify that,
specifically in your fucking commission
so like it can't be fucking used.
I don't think I have like,
I mean, I've done a few commissions for some people
but very little of my art,
it was like I sold it to someone
or I made it for someone for money.
Like I think I own almost everything, which so,
so that in theory means I don't have to worry
about it getting NFT, right?
Yeah, as long as you know, post the images online
and then some, it's like ha, I yonk
and then sells it, right?
Yeah, but I mean-
That's like anyone could probably do it.
You could do it with any JPEG, right?
Right, right.
I guess if I'm thinking of like,
if I'm thinking of like actual legal consequences,
cause that's where my mind goes
when it comes to adoptables.
It's like, the honor system, I have no honor
and I don't want any.
I will never honor these things.
But like, I suppose if somebody like, say for example,
somebody just draws like Magda or whatever,
just pretends that it's not Magda and sells things.
Like you, I don't think you've like,
like legally gone through like copyright process
for your stuff.
You don't have to like file copyright.
You don't need to do that.
Yeah, it's good.
It's like, you did it and if it came to court,
you could say, I did it.
Here's the proof.
It came out before.
And then they would be like,
oh, I guess you have a case.
But if you had sold something as an adoptable,
I wonder what would happen if that did go to court.
You changed your mind.
You wanted to use that character again.
And their case was you sold it to me as an adoptable.
I mean, there's no precedent for that.
I've heard people, I have not seen this,
but I heard people say specifically in the furry community,
there is like a resale market for adoptables.
I mean, literally, I guess nothing's really stopping me
from going to someone who I sold an adoptable fund.
It's like, hey, I changed my mind.
Can I buy this character back off of you?
Right?
I don't know as in like selling it back
to the original creator.
Yeah, yeah.
But I was thinking was that like in my special contract
that I'm gonna write out,
I'm gonna have like a clause in there where it's like,
so I don't own the character I sell to you, right?
I don't own it, but I am allowed to like use
like similar aspects of that design
for my own personal or commercial products, right?
Or my own pieces, right?
Cause sometimes like, I mean, I don't,
sometimes like recently when I was designing
a one specific like clown character,
I liked the design so much, I decided,
you know what, I'm not gonna sell this design.
I'm just gonna keep that design, right?
But there's like other characters that I've drawn
where it's like, I like this aspect of their design.
I would like, I could see myself reusing
this specific aspect and like with another character,
not that character, but just a piece of that character, right?
But I just kind of want to get that like,
I guess like internet legally bounded, right?
It gets like, yeah.
I mean, I guess at some point you hit a sort of gray area
where it's like, okay, well, how many elements
can a two characters share before they're
the same character, basically?
That means these, I guess it would,
that's gonna depend a whole lot on the details.
I, yeah, like, I think I've probably,
I don't know if I mentioned this before in the podcast,
but I've already told you guys about this comic
called the Capra.
Capra, I don't think so.
Yeah, Capra, a Capra, right?
So in that comic, it's like, if you read it,
it's unironically like a Suicide Squad fan fiction.
It's just that they got all the characters
and they made them like legally distinct, right?
But the thing is that like-
They, 50 Shades of Graded.
Right, exactly.
But it's so, but the thing is that like,
they didn't really like change the designs that much.
Like, all right, like this character,
this character right here with like the white mask
and like the gun wrist.
Like this character is from,
he's supposed to be based on,
he's based on this character from the Suicide Squad, right?
Yeah, dead shot, yeah.
And just look how similar they fucking look, right?
Like they don't even look too different.
Like someone in passing-
It looks like someone just erased details from the-
Right, exactly.
From the original.
Yeah, someone in passing could just like see like,
and also the characters have very similar names.
Like the character of Dead Shot, his name is like Floyd
and the character in Capra, his name is like Lloyd, right?
Yeah, Natch, naturally.
Yeah, it's not even like too, like fucking different.
Like yeah, if you walk by,
if you know anything about Suicide Squad
and you walk by this cover,
you might think it's like a Suicide Squad book, right?
But it's like legally allowed,
like you're allowed to just like do this.
Yeah.
Yeah, and I guess what also helps is that like the book is,
the comic's actually fucking good.
Like it's not a bad comic.
I see.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So that means that-
That's what's weird about,
that's what's weird about Adoptables to me is like,
what's the, if you see a character that you like,
what's to stop you from not buying it
but just making a character that has very similar elements?
I think I'm, I think the vibe that I'm,
the most people who-
Doing this essentially.
I think I'm-
Toppering it.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know, like I don't see that, like I don't,
I mean, I've only recently started doing Adoptables.
Yeah.
I don't know if maybe like the process of just doing that
is like an extra amount of energy
that not that many people have or like care too much.
Maybe like, yeah, I can see that happening,
but as of yet no one has given that much of a shit
to like try, right?
I think to me it's just sort of like,
if you have a good design,
like you said with the specific clown one,
like it's so good you want to keep it,
you don't want to sell it.
So people who are selling Adoptables
aren't selling their best work,
they're selling things that they don't really care about
as much and they can, you know, people can have-
I mean, they might sell something that's like,
just appeals to someone else more than it appeals to them.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure.
But like if I'm like going out,
like if I'm on the hunt for a character
or if I see a character design in use
and I'm like, oh, I want that,
that's not up for adoption
because they've been used already in something.
Yeah, yeah.
Usually an Adoptable is just like a character sheet
and I don't feel anything
when I look at a character sheet usually.
You want to, yeah, yeah.
I noticed the two kinds of people who like buy Adoptables
are people who can't really draw that well.
So they had like a,
so let's say they buy an Adoptable,
it's like, oh, cool, finally, I have an OC.
So I'm going to show this to other people
to commission them to draw this character, right?
Yeah.
That makes sense.
I've heard people say stuff like they don't,
like some people want to do fan art
of other people's Adoptables,
which I think it's fine.
Like that's nothing weird about doing fan art
for someone's OC.
Yeah, I would say fan art is fine.
Yeah, as long as they're not like selling it
or passing it off as an original.
I think also the thing is that like,
everyone in here is like an artist.
So if we don't really need to buy a character,
we just design one, right?
Yeah, I don't really necessarily dislike
the practice, I just think it's so pointless
and I would never use it in any way.
I can, no, if, I mean, I guess I can't really imagine,
I mean, Furries have a whole thing
where they have like a Sona
and like I can't really imagine like having a Sona
that like is me that I, maybe if I did,
I would be like, yeah, please like draw this Sona of mine
doing all these things I want to see.
Maybe that would make it easier to understand.
Actually, I've got like two or three artists
who have like bought Adoptables,
like for example, this Adoptable that I sell,
Panpeekse bought this one from me.
And, oh, really?
Yeah, yeah, and I guess like, oh.
Yeah, yeah, like, yeah, I've got it like friends buying.
It's kind of cool, actually.
I like what I've noticed is that,
what does Panpeekse want to do with it?
I mean, I've gotten like two friends
who have bought like two Adoptables off of me
and what they usually do is they grab it
as like kind of like a base
and then they like kind of redesigned a little bit, right?
Of course that opens the question as like,
well, what if like, let's say they just kind of just looked
at it and then they just designed their own.
Yeah, what if they just did that without buying it?
Without buying it.
Like, I, hmm, I guess you don't.
I mean, it does ultimately come down
to like people willing to spend money
and you just have to hope that they are.
Do you technically lose?
Cause it's kind of like, I don't know, like I,
it's kind of like pirating a movie, I guess.
I guess, I'm sure a lot of it does come down
to just like people want to support an artist
or like just people just don't want to be thieves.
They want to like appreciate something that they like
and support it.
I'm sure that's a big part of it.
I think the.
I would be,
or the, or they just don't want to like get into trouble.
They don't want someone like it best, best just to not
even fuck with like any chance of someone accusing me
of being an art thief.
I mean, if, if the person you the thing,
if the person you like stole, like quote unquote,
stolen and adoptable from is popular,
you'll probably be put on blast.
You're right. Yeah.
I think what I think people don't really care too much
if designs are similar, but they, but they,
I think people don't like tracing more.
I think tracing is like what people don't like more.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hypothetically, what if somebody like came up with
as many character designs as humanly possible,
put them all up for adoptable, you know, you could buy them.
And it's like so many character designs
that basically every character design ever is like.
That sounds plausible.
You couldn't, you couldn't no longer design
your own character without somehow plagiarizing
these adoptables.
And then you know what, you should, you should,
you should try. Excuse me.
You should try to do that.
You should try to design literally every character
that could ever exist.
Yeah, actually, that's a pretty good racket.
I could spring up.
First you start with a stick figure
and then you draw a stick figure with a face.
Then you draw a stick figure with hair
and then you start to stick figure with clothes
and you just keep going down the line
until you get everything down.
Yeah. And then I say,
different face, different face, different combinations.
Excuse me, you have drawn,
you've drawn a character with two hands
and glasses and a hair and I did that.
So please pay up.
I call Marv one say, excuse me, sir,
I think you ripped off my design for Iron Man.
I came up with a robo red and gold guy.
I guess also like, there's like weird specific
kind of like rules.
Like you ever seen the thing where like,
like a show would have the same name
as like an album or a song,
but it's okay since there's both two different pieces
of like properties that like it's fine.
Oh, you mean, you mean like the Vapors
which shares the name with an 80s band?
Yes. Oh, I didn't know that.
Yeah, yeah.
Or how Bongo Luna shares the name with like a DJ.
Does it?
Oh, I think so.
I found like a guy.
Like Bongo and Luna?
No, I think I can find a guy called Bongo.
No, I found a guy called Luna
and I think he made a remix that has the word Bongo in it.
I see.
It's like the most.
Yeah.
I mean, it's kind of like, I mean, the thing is like,
if there's something I've like learned,
this might be like kind of like cynical or unironically,
I'm just built different.
It's like, I don't know.
Like I noticed some shit takes effort
and sometimes if it's even the little bit of effort
people just won't do it.
Right?
Yeah.
So I'm just not too fucking like worried.
Right?
Sure.
Yeah, I get you.
And I guess the thing is like,
I kind of have so much faith in my like,
I guess skill in designing characters
that like I'm not fucking too worried
about selling off a couple of designs.
Right?
Sure.
I mean, that's why like, I mean, yeah.
But if I want to reuse like aspects like of a character,
like why not can I have another character
that also has like a broken heart on an axe, right?
But it has like something else different about them, you know?
Mm-hmm.
Right?
Like it makes perfect sense.
Yeah, I could like still do that again, you know?
Yeah.
I got you.
Right.
Hey, do you want to start voicemails?
We're gonna start voicemails.
Let's start them.
Let's start it.
Bass.
So first one is called, wait, I'll put it in the chat.
There it is.
First one is called, wait, it's loading.
Okay.
More like take a shit on my desk yearly.
Three, two, one, go.
Give shit on my desk yearly five just came out.
And every time that it shows up, I'm like,
oh yes, this existed.
I totally forgot.
And it's a wonderful, fun little time.
And as such, I decided to rewatch all of it
from the beginning and shit on my desk yearly one.
One smug left a comment saying,
in three years after the procrastinators have all died
in the suicide pact of 2020,
I will make sure to keep watching these videos
and keep your legacy alive.
And I have to say, where,
where was the suicide pact of 2020?
Come on.
I would, that would have been so cool.
Swimming bass, swimming bass.
We fucked it up.
I forgot about shit on my desk yearly.
We did a suicide pact with the entire world in 2020.
Bass, bass.
Yeah, nine years,
we're all gonna do the biggest suicide pack
on a global scale.
It's gonna be pretty rad.
Except it's suicide, it's homicide,
and I'll be left alone.
Can you remind me,
can you remind me about the premise of shit
on my desk yearly?
Yeah, so it started like five years ago now.
I think it's episode five.
Yeah, so four or five years ago,
I think it was around the time when I was like,
actually, I don't know.
I think it was just sort of like episodic videos about stuff.
I think Digi, Trixie was doing things of that nature
and I was, I think it was like a joke that was like,
what if I did a scheduled release video
that was like a year?
And I checked and you could do that.
And I wanted to see how many years it could be in the future,
that you could schedule something to appear on YouTube.
So I filmed a bunch of like completely pointless crap,
like me just talking about the shit
that was on my desk at the time.
Okay.
And it's like banal and as tedious and pointless as possible.
But the fact that it came out like once a year,
for who knows how many years, it was the joke.
Is it still coming out?
Yeah, number five just came out.
Oh yeah, we give and take channel.
Oh my God.
Do they come out automatically?
Yeah, I scheduled them all at once
and they are still like, they're like, yeah, you can,
you just, I feel like you could go to like 2040
and schedule something and it will appear
if YouTube still exists.
Damn.
That's interesting.
How many do you have lined up
or do you want to spoil it?
Kaiju comments and says, oh my God, it's still going on.
Yeah, it's funny because it's like everyone's like,
oh no, I'm old, I'm a whole year older.
Because it's such an uneventful video series,
but which means it catches people by surprise
every time it happens.
You're watching Best of the Worst,
Biohazards, Slaughter High and Kill Point.
Oh, that's a good one.
I made sure to.
Maybe I'll go watch that.
Yeah, that was what was out at the time
and it was on trending.
So it was like, oh, that was proof,
proof that it was actually filmed in the past.
Notably, this video has no dislikes and 145 likes,
which is very, very unusual that not a single dislike,
but congratulations on that.
It did again.
Yeah.
I made the best YouTube series in the world.
It's true, it's true.
Um, next voicemail is called,
sorry, let me find my shit here.
Next voicemail is called Put Put Prince.
Let me put it in the chat.
There it is, three, two, one, go.
You're right guys.
So since Radcon, I've wanted to come up with like,
a voicemail to leave something funny or something artistic,
but it's been a year and I've come up with nothing so far.
So I'm going to self-prove myself where I leave a voicemail
every week until I come up with something decent
or something, something all right.
So that's it, that's my plan.
Every week, one voicemail.
And if Tom is here, how does he feel about streaming?
You know, his creative, you know, his projects and stuff.
If Gibby's here, you know, I'd like his closer streams
and if Ben is here, you can fuck off.
Damn.
I predicted that, I predicted that joke.
Did they say that they liked the Clarissa streams
or did they ask a question I didn't hear?
I think he said he liked the Clarissa streams.
That's what I heard.
Tom's not here.
Okay, so the plan is I don't have anything good
to make a voicemail about,
but I'll just keep making one until I make a good one.
All right, we'll get good luck.
It's a good plan.
You start by doing something.
And then you make a terrible voicemails
and then eventually you don't.
That's the first time.
I mean, one of them's gotta eventually be good, right?
It's the law of averages.
Right, one of them guys is eventually the top 10, you know.
You gotta make, you know, you gotta spend 10,000 hours
mastering the art of making voicemails.
So you gotta work through all the first 10,000.
I just hope that I'm a guest on
when we get to the good one, that'll be very eventful.
Years from now.
I'm gonna try to guess it.
The next voicemail is called Rub and Tug.
Three, two, one, go.
So if you wanna have sex,
I know you've never had sex before.
I've found this great website.
It's called rubmaps.ch.
And it's this place you can find like prostitution brothels.
And you walk right in and you say the code word or whatever
and then they'll sucky sucky for five bucky.
And it's pretty legit.
I just found out about this a few days ago
and planning my next visit.
Fuck yeah.
Wait, what was the website called again?
Rubmaps.ch.
Rubmaps.
Where fantasy meets reality.
Oh my God.
Massage parlor review, erotic massage.
I am over 18, yes.
That's America, so not for me, I guess, lol.
Latest reviews around me.
Oh, Jenny over in Worcester.
Only $60.
Jackie is $40, herm.
That's a D, is that cheaper than,
is that cheaper than, oh, what is it, waifu?
Something waifu?
40, I guess $40 for the massage right now.
$7 a month, seven times 12.
That's like, I don't know, wait, wait,
I can do this, I can do this, it's like.
How many handjobs could a month for a stripper waifu?
That's like $85, that's like $85 a month.
40, like, it'd probably be cheaper
to just join a stripper waifu's only fans
than to go to one of these massage parlors.
But that's not the personalized experience, though.
Okay, you know what, maybe like, I don't know,
stripper waifu, maybe do one month of stripper waifu
just to feel it out to see what's the flow
of content being uploaded and give or take
if you don't like that, save your money next month
and go to see Jackie.
This one is.
For $40.
Some of these people, oh, this lady's name is Yo-Yo.
I like that, for some reason.
Does she spin around really fast?
Why is this review near me in Lafayette, Louisiana?
This is fucked up.
Oh, wait, no, I was looking at newest reviews in the US.
Okay, that's, latest reviews, let me find one,
let me find a good review here.
Okay.
It says you can't read a review, it's a premium,
it's fucking kidding me.
Click your little instant access to the review,
go premium, it's fucking lame.
Are you fucking kidding me, I can't read a fucking review.
That's lame.
Jesus, that sucks.
That was gonna be great content.
Yeah, that's lame.
Damn, if anyone can get me a subscription
to rubmaps.ch, strictly for content creation purposes,
obviously, send me a DM.
Oh my God, wait, oh my God, this place is way closer
than I thought, it's like only two blocks away
from my pad, holy shit.
Oh my God.
They say the devil, they say the devil is tempting.
He's a tempting person, right?
I didn't think he was gonna be this tempting.
He's in the details.
Oh, you're terrible.
As tempting as sex, could it be?
I don't think anything could be as,
wait a minute, a hand job, though.
My harm, my harm, my hand job.
Next voicemail is called,
Gidus to it, Gidus to it,
three, two, one, go.
First off, we have a pretty cool, pretty small,
pretty chill, a cycloneal server,
which I will probably link to in the comments.
But anyways, speaking of cycloneals,
remember clown and horse gender?
Of course.
Yes, wait, is that it?
Okay, good, okay, good.
You're welcome in advance, by the way.
But remember when, when, when in KMZ,
just kind of, you know,
just kind of like strangled equestria death?
Yeah.
No.
Yes, I remember that.
No, I don't.
You're welcome.
I don't, that doesn't make any sense.
What is the implication here?
I think the implication is that clown and aqueous
is like horse and is like clown gender,
horse gender, it's not a sexual preference.
It's not misunderstood, I think.
I don't, I don't know.
I mean, it's not about clowns having sex with horses.
This is something else.
If it, I don't, he can't, he can't think that.
He can't think that that's what it is.
But it's like, okay, the clown,
so it would be an allegory for someone with no gender,
killing someone with a lot of gender.
So what's, what am I, what, what does it mean?
Riddle me that, ironmathyatgmail.com.
Riddle me that.
Okay.
Riddle my ass.
Hey, next, next, shout outs, shout outs.
Next one is called Tom's Content Gold Mine.
Three, two, one, go.
Tom always acts like he doesn't have anything to talk about
on the podcast and yet he plays D&D every weekend.
Clearly, as someone can talk about what he did during D&D.
After all, the best thing about D&D is telling people
who really don't want to listen to it
about what you did over the weekend.
That's absolutely true.
And what would fit more on the PCP than that.
That is absolutely correct.
I want 100% agree.
It is a content goal.
I was looking forward to getting my like frog character
campaign more underway.
I was going to talk about it,
but then it kind of evaporated and it never really came
to pass, which was sad.
Tom's got the opportunity to, it would be like,
it would be, imagine it's even worse
than like Maige talking about her dreams
would be Tom talking about D&D.
I was just having a flashback to that.
And ironically, Tom needs to learn
to be more annoying on the PCP.
He doesn't take enough risks.
I actually agree.
I think Tom avoids talking about things
that he thinks no one will be interested in.
And I think as a result,
he ends up not talking about things
that we would genuinely,
we could ring interest out of if we tried.
Tom, you gotta know you're annoying, Tom,
and you should own up to it.
God made you annoying and you shouldn't feel shame for it.
You can't deny it.
It's one of your talents.
You can't just pray the annoying away.
You have to embrace it.
Exactly.
You have to be your true self.
Embrace the cringe, Tom.
Embrace the cringe.
That's right.
Well, Tom does embrace the cringe
because he posts gifts.
He posts reaction gifts, gifts,
which we know is we have the cringe trial.
They truly are a gift.
And he was found guilty.
So we already know this much.
Next voicemail is called,
it's just called Janess.
Three, two, one, go.
What do you recommend for a daily regimen
of learning the drawing fundamentals
to practicing drawing over and over again?
What space of time should I allow for each?
You're asking the wrong people.
Who the fuck says, I don't know how to draw.
I mean, what space of time?
Well, you know how to draw.
What is my time?
I would say,
what is your drawing regimen for learning how?
Did you do that?
Did you do the whole like stuff?
I remember back in middle school
when Tumblr was at the height of its popularity,
I would have a USB where I would just constantly save
like a lot of like photos.
Like photos are real life of people in outfits or scenery
and to a USB and I would call the folder art references.
And during weekends,
I would just go through like every single one of the photos
and just draw as closely as I can to that photo.
Even though it looked bad,
I was still trying to draw realistic
and over a course of the time,
like I would just start,
I would just kind of subconsciously learning like anatomy
and how to make like things look good,
how to draw hands well.
Because I did that,
it's like why I know how to draw hands well now.
That's an interesting, that's a pretty good,
it's a pretty good regimen you get there.
Yeah, yeah.
So if you can just, I don't know when you have free time
like weekends or whatnot.
I know there's certain websites
that just give you random like stock images
to kind of practice with, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I got to start, I got to start like,
I got to go back to the fundamentals a little bit
because I have not drawn humans in fucking forever.
All I'm drawing are little goblins getting blown up
and it's fun, it's fun, it's great, it's awesome.
It's awesome, it's great.
I'm happy for you.
Read Villainverse, of course.
Read Villainverse.
I need to practice more humans.
If you want to see goblins, lots of goblins getting blown up.
Goblins get blown up in Villainverse.
Every chapter, at least one goblin blow up.
One goblin blow up, that's the cheesy guarantee.
Oh, goblins.
I don't know if there's anything funnier than a goblin.
I just don't know, there it is.
I think their question was about like
how to balance drawing for fun
and drawing fundamentals like time-wise.
I don't know if there's like, I guess the balance would be
depending on the person drawing for fun enough
so that you enjoy drawing in general
so that when you're doing the fundamentals,
you don't want to die.
I would say just draw at how much time,
it's just like as much as you can
that you aren't like suffering and you want it
and you are fucking furious and fed up and you hate it.
If you get to that point, it's time to take a break
and maybe come back tomorrow.
I think it'll depend on everyone.
Different like the tolerances for this
because I have, I'm no patience for learning.
I hate learning.
It sucks, except when it's random facts on Wikipedia.
But like studying and like drawing stuff
that isn't like funny stupid shit is difficult for me.
So I can't, I got to do it more.
I just got to, I don't know, learn discipline, I guess.
I think would be good is kind of like
have the fun drawings be like the reward, right?
So like, let's say I'm going to try to draw
three like anatomy pictures for practice.
And then once I finish those three,
my reward is to draw like my fun little anime,
weeaboo, bullshit, whatever the fuck you like.
You know, that'll be your little fucking,
that'll be your little treats.
That'll be your carrot at the stick, at the end of the stick.
I hate carrots.
It would be your ass I eat bull at the end of the stick.
Yeah, bro.
Oh, base?
Oh, fucking love, I say he bulls.
I don't know.
Next voicemail is called,
I have to draw my commissions.
They've waited many months.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP, I haven't actually listened to the podcast
in like several months, probably like six months now.
I'm really behind.
I haven't been listening to anything about it.
Don't worry about it.
I just wanted to tell you that.
Nothing happened.
They gave me a refund on it, but I still got the switch.
Based.
So I got a free switch and I got Mario Kart with it.
Fuck you.
And I can't stop playing Mario Kart.
For like the past four days,
I've done nothing but play Mario Kart.
I got the gold wheels, gold Mario, I got the gold kart.
Good for you.
And I'm getting really close to getting the gold glider.
I'm like ranked 5,000 online.
All right, next game's about to start.
I'll see you.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
The title.
I hope he gets that gold card.
I hope he's got it by now.
I really do.
You said he has a list of the PCPs,
so I guess I'll update him.
So I think you got to,
if you really want to like update yourself on the PCP,
I recommend reading Villainverse.
Just look up Villainverse.
If you want to really understand.
If you want to really understand the PCP,
there's a, it's either a Tumblr link
or a Medibang link, right?
But you know, just their first three chapters
and a prologue, it should keep you up to speed.
And maybe it should,
maybe it'll fix your Mario Kart addiction.
Who knows?
Hmm, anything is possible.
And anything, anything is possible, game.
Next voicemail is called satire.
Three, two, one, go.
Look, look, look, look, look.
The capitalist system, the corporateocracy,
whatever you want to call it,
it's all built with loss in mind.
See, these companies,
they know they're going to be stolen from.
This is going to suck.
And that money is right there,
the being stolen from fund.
And you can, you can reach out and take it.
You know, you can steal from Walmart
and they won't follow you out.
You know what I mean?
Oh, this is about chocolate thing.
That sort of thing exists, but like larger scales.
Or you can get away with like a lot.
I'm not kidding.
Because these companies don't have the resources
to investigate every time they're stolen from
in a petty way.
This goes for other things too.
Like creditors and banks and shit.
And banks, they're actually committing fraud constantly.
And if you know the law, you can fuck them.
And you can take their money basically
and keep your credit score.
I'm not giving advice or anything.
I just think everyone should look into
the opportunities afforded to them by the system.
And we are in the looting phase of capitalism.
So it's okay.
I think it's kind of based.
If the, I don't, I'm sure it's probably true.
It's probably true that banks
are constantly committing fraud.
How do we get it though?
I don't know.
I would like to maybe know more
about how to actually get the money.
I look like, I don't really,
I don't know like really can say anything about this
because you know, Vosh hasn't made a video about it.
So I didn't really know what to think of it.
Yeah, sorry.
We're gonna have to.
Maybe call back next time we are Vosh, my guy, I'm sorry.
We can call in, we can call in on the stream and ask him.
But yeah, I know about like,
it's easy to fucking steal from Walmart
and all these places, it's no crime.
I mean, it's true that like, yeah, I mean,
no corporate entity will like pursue a loss
to an extent that like getting it back
will cost them more than they'll recoup from it.
So like broadly, yeah, you can steal,
you can steal from anyone who doesn't have the resources
to not, yeah, who it's not worth it for them to like
unsteal it, which you know,
you could use that knowledge
in any number of different ways.
Up to you, gamer.
Yes, each gamer, it's up to each individual gamer
to decide which, I don't know, fucking Twitch stream
to dump their bits into or what the fuck does that mean?
It's up to each gamer to decide whether they want
the good or bad ending, a mass effect.
It's all, it's up to you, gamer, it's up to you.
It's the choices you make that matter,
which is the true ending.
The next voicemail is called Based Joker,
three, two, one, go.
Every poo poo is pee-pee time.
But not every pee-pee, it's poo-poo time.
Everything about that one, Mr. Batman.
I had an impression.
I think about that all the time.
What's the deal?
I fucking love all the sort of like heat ledger impressions.
That was a good, that was a pretty good
heat ledger impression.
I'll give him that one and I laughed so.
My father left the voicemail on the BCP on time.
Next voicemail is called.
Do you wanna know how I got these subscribers?
Got these subs.
The next one.
My father ate a S.I.E. bowl on time.
Batman, you barely touched your S.I.E. bowl.
You barely touched your Sonic Curry.
Stupid.
The next voicemail is just called High Ben,
three, two, one, go.
This is the procrastinator's podcast theme of the day
and I'm really gay.
Yes, I wish I had a voice modulator,
but I don't, cause I'm whore.
Say hello to Ben and Gib,
and maybe even Tom Oliver.
But not Fixing Aid, Mumky or Davoo.
Jesse Mage, Mumky Jones or Jeff Foo.
But Ben St. is here with Gib.
And that is pretty okay.
Pretty okay.
The water of the PCP.
I'll take it.
I'll take pretty okay.
He didn't have me at the beginning,
but that finale really like, okay,
he landed it.
Nobody said my name with such gusto before.
He really went for it,
and I have to applaud the enthusiasm.
The next voicemail is
Literal Baby Children,
three, two, one, go.
Hello, PCP.
Where were you when you found out Dan Grumps was a rapist?
Oh my gosh.
He's not a rapist.
There was a whole big thing,
but he's just maybe a scummy guy.
I didn't really look any further into it.
It apparently has a history of like,
I know when I say groomer,
people think by default like minors,
but no, a groomer could also be applied
to someone who just uses their power
to like get people over someone, you know, by...
Yeah.
He used his influence as a popular let's player
to fuck some fans occasionally.
That's what I would assume.
That's what I would assume he would do.
Oh, he didn't call him back.
Oh no, but I want him to keep fucking his girls
who I think he shouldn't be fucking.
Why didn't he call them back and keep fucking them?
That's so evil.
It's...
What a joic.
Hey, I'm joicin' off here.
I'm zirkin' off.
Because it's been a while since that happened.
Yeah, it's been like two weeks.
Yeah, fucking time moves so fucking fast.
Wait, no, it's been one week.
Like, by the time this video drops,
we're all gonna forget about that boat
that like got stuck in the Suez Canal.
I only kind of heard about that second hand in there.
I don't really get what's so funny about it.
I can't believe Dan fucked the Suez Canal.
Yeah, he fucked that.
He dug it, he dug the Suez Canal with his own hands.
You know what?
It's actually a perfect time for me to make this announcement.
I won't just be replacing Nolan on the Pizza Party podcast.
I'll be replacing Dan on Game Grumps.
Congratulations.
Finally, we can have a man on the inside of the Game Grumps.
Yeah, yeah, I'm not so grumpy now.
Hopefully, I don't fall for some horrible controversy
any time soon, ha ha.
Hopefully, you don't fuck any fans,
because that would be a big no-no.
That's why every time I hook up with someone,
I make sure, have you heard of Villainverse?
I would say, no, I'm like, oh, good.
Every time you fuck, every time you,
when you're on Game Grumps, you gotta be like,
hey, you ever heard of Game Grumps?
They're like, ugh, I hate that shit.
That's for babies.
And he goes, yes, yes.
I'm done, I'm done fucking someone.
I'm free.
I'm done fucking someone.
And then afterwards, they tell me, by the way,
I really like Bangalore Luna.
And I'm like, oh, no, what have I done?
No, what have I done?
What have I done?
Next voicemail is called,
next voicemail is called,
it's called doidgazers.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello there.
This is doidgazers.
Hello.
And I'm your host, D.
And today, we're gonna be smoking some weed.
And then after that, we're gonna talk to some guy.
And then we'll go smoke some old weed.
Gripping.
And then I'm gonna do the hippity hop.
And that'll be a remedy wrap.
Is this a people movie I'm watching right now?
Please give me money.
And subscribe to my blog post, Patreon thing.
That's right.
And you can give me money.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Nice, nice baby.
I love the baby in the back.
That added a texture to it.
Is this what it feels like to watch voicemail?
I've never seen episode of voicemail.
Is this what it's like?
It's, I mean, it's way longer.
Where is the baby?
No baby.
And imagine it's like four hours instead of 30 seconds.
Well, there's no baby.
I'm not interested in that because the baby stole the show.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't think I've watched an entire episode of that podcast.
I've heard like a little snippet here and there.
I skimmed through one.
And I watched half of another one.
It's bad.
It's dumb.
It's awful.
And I hate it.
Yeah.
Well.
I'm anti-yig studios.
I'm anti-yig studios until that.
I'm also anti-yig studios.
I'm glad you're here.
I'm glad you'll support me.
I'm sorry, Ben.
Say I'm going to betray you right now.
The last video they dropped, let's say it changed my mind.
It made me feel stronger than ever.
Maybe yig studios isn't so bad if they could beat up Ethan.
I agree that Ethan Ralph is a monster, but I don't think any better of anyone involved over this.
I feel, yeah.
I feel like everyone should be embarrassed.
Emotionally about it as you seem to be.
I think it was, it was a funny moment, but like, LeMau.
Let them fight.
I'm not really like, ooh, thumbs up to whatever this situation is.
It's completely insane.
Let them fight.
I'm so surprised.
I'm so surprised that it was like uploaded and so
That's the problem for me. Yeah public amount about it. There's like wow
That's the issue for me. What a fucking joke. What a what a gross what a what a fucking yucky
group gaggle of goblins. We've got over there
Hopefully not and not funny goblins that get into shenanigans
Uh
Anyway, doid gazers, doid gazers everypony. It was a little based. It was a little based
You know credit was credit is due they punched Ethan Ralph a bit sure pretty good
I guess but I mean who hasn't right who hasn't punched Ethan Ralph
Next next voicemail is called honest requests
There it is, uh, three two one go
Okay, I know this is like entitled fan bullshit
But arm retrieval meant a lot to me and I'm like semi furious that munchie
Privated all of that shit without warning. Uh, I would like to download all of it, please
Because it meant a lot to me
Is there any way you could tell him to like hey
Could you unprivate it for like even 24 hours so I could download all of it real quick?
You could and it could be gone forever, but I just I just want it for for to have personally because I love it so much
Please I love that show
I'm very angry that it's gone with no warning. I just want to download it for personal viewing
I'm not going to re upload it. I promise. I understand that
I think you should just ask him. I think you should just ask munchie. I mean, there's nowhere you can contact him
That's the thing is there not wait wait hold on. No, he doesn't use twitter
He's changed his social media
Hold on. I'm getting his clothes the social media stuff
I'm getting a discord DM from munchie and he says that he'll have it up for for three weeks
You have three weeks to to download it before he before he deletes it
And hopefully he sticks to his word. It doesn't delete it two weeks earlier. Let's see
Um, I don't I mean I can I feel like I didn't expect because like
Certain munchie content was like, oh, yeah, I could see why he wouldn't want any of that up
And like I I could see why he wouldn't want to inform people so that they could re upload it
Um, I didn't know that I didn't know that armless
I didn't know that arm retrieval was gone. And yeah, I'm not entirely sure why it's down. I guess just to complete the
The the mission I suppose
Maybe maybe there's some aspects of it. I forget like he doesn't want to like I feel like his
Decision to not inform people was so that
That was definitely one she are definitely deliberate. Yeah
I'll I'll I mean I kind of want to see them again
I don't know whether I'd watch them but like it is kind of sad that they're gone
If yeah, maybe I could talk to him about like
Something it might be worth asking him about I guess. I don't know if I was munchie. I would really try to like get
Just to
Take down that the plea of in the weave episode where they talk about curvy because that's probably one of the most
most heinous shit involving munchie
Is that right? It's the one where he says like the n-word like a hundred times
Yeah, like I see the case to be made there. I have not watched arm retrieval. I mean, that's why he took down lectures the first two
Yeah, I mean, I don't maybe maybe just doesn't want to take I mean, I don't know
I don't know what what's going on. I don't know if I don't think much even has any contact with jess
So he would have to establish contact first
Is the plea of in the weave on on jesse's channel? It's on my japanese anime
Yeah, okay. Yeah
Yeah, that's a good point and uh
I don't know
Contact jesse about it. Yeah, like there was one thing like, you know, it's how much you like, yeah, you probably should
Try to tell jesse to be like, yeah, he take that down because
Is it much he's trying to actually work in the industry and whatnot?
Or whatever. It's not I think he's it's not necessarily about that exactly. He just
He just made the decision that he wants
the
The life he led online to be like he's embarrassed, but he doesn't like it doesn't like that. It's all public. He wants it gone
so i'm like, yeah
I maybe forgot about that actually. I should probably mention it. That's probably
It would probably maybe bear mentioning like before this episode comes out when we're in we talk about it
Which might provoke people to like
Try and try and archive it
I know probably already someone probably already has it somewhere. I feel like that's viewers
Viewers, I know how you feel. I know you don't like things being gone
But munchies my friend and I care more about him than I do about you
Yeah, whatever whatever munchie says it goes
Pretty much
Uh next voicemail is called
Mentos trio thing
three two one go
I just want to say that i've been
Curious about the mentos trio ever since the things we can't get into podcasts and at the time
You know after learning more about you guys
I just assumed that it was like ben nate and grace, you know, like your sister. No, uh
I assumed that was the trio. It was not. I don't know why that that was my go-to
I'm surprised you remember we have that wasn't the case
um
Cool, thank you. Thank you for finally answering a question that I
Was like intending on making a voicemail to ask about for a while, but I just kept forgetting so
Fucking good on you ben. Thank you. I'm glad I'm glad someone actually remembered and one
It might have been yeah, it might have been before you joined last week. I think I talked about it like at the beginning
I guess I remember and you have mentos
Yes, I told I had in previous episodes
I had I had mentioned a thing I used to be in called the mentos trio and I think last episode was the first time
I actually explained what it was
lol
um
Okay, so the next uh, the next voicemail is a it has an imager link, which I I guess I will post it
Here
Okay bacon bacon busker beatdown
Featuring error are a bear and pig
Okay, okay, this is uh, okay
This is well, this is well drawn actually
Uh, this is could use some color though. Um, okay, so this is album art. I suppose
Uh three two one go
The missiles in my hands and pistols in my eyes won't work against this pig
Because of his thick hat even when the bear uses
Claw attack
It doesn't really work because the pig's too fat
But the pig's got a big honking hog. He go we gotta use our words to burn him. So
He's burning so hard. He can't get back
We gotta beat the pig with a candid rap need to do a rhyme to take him down
What kind of rhyme could make a swine frown?
I don't know
uh
harm
um
fire
Hey
Uh, hey, uh, uh hoe. Let's go. Uh, hey pig. You gotta you fucking blow
My name is cheesy and i'm here to say you're really really gay
A dislike pigs in a mage way
Um
I'll bring home the bacon
Uh by killing you and cutting you up. That's a good one. There's potential there. There's potential there
Don't catch me waking because I never sleep. I pull out the lock and I make this bacon weep
Most embarrassing like a rap like a rap, uh
See, uh, what would you call it? See I can't rap because I can't see me. I can't rap or I uh this
I
Improv I can't I can't rap well because I can't say the n word. Oh if I can say the n word
I would I'd rap so amazing right now. Oh my god. You blow this pig away
Yeah, blow them off of the water, but at last at last. Oh, you just blow his eutrums out with the
The price I pay for being an ally at last
Sad but true god jk jk. You're lucky. I'm an ally. You're lucky. I'm an ally, sir
Yeah, you say squinting
Well, Errorari, I hope I hope we've given you a little bit of ammunition there for
For the rap against this this pig
Hope we helped uh next voicemail is called. Oh fuck. What is this? What is this garbage?
It is called
Pete
Okay, it's called piece. Do you give do you see this it's called pcp opening one
And then there's like a what?
It's like one second it's one second and it's
What is this?
Yeah, uh, there's a link to uh, I don't think this works. I think they fucked this up
Oh, well, it's a file share. Yeah, I don't know what that is
Try again next time buddy better luck next time
Yeah, okay. Okay. Next one is my uh, no, I haven't posted it the next voicemail. Oh, wait. Did you wait?
Did you listen to this the one second one the one second one? Yeah, I did. He just says he just says what what?
Okay, he says what there's double check. What?
Yeah, unfortunate
Uh, the next one is called mine sweeper, but demons three two one go
Someone brought up demon crawl last week and I'm a big fan of it
But they didn't do a great job of selling it. I thought
Mine sweeper is a big part of our functions
But there's so much other shit that if you're just here for mine sweeper, you may not actually enjoy it
You play through a bunch of levels that get bigger and harder, of course
But you've got an inventory to manage you got gold spend health defense armor stage mods to deal with
Metaprogression shit bosses so on so forth the idea is that it's got cruel rng that will gleefully throw
unavoidable guesses at you left and right
So you got to mitigate that with stuff you find like a bow to shoot at hidden cells
Or a familiar to run around and die to monsters for you
Also, maybe you get bad items that fuck up your run like something that makes them pc's never show up or
A hobo cat that makes shop prices higher. I could go on about it forever
But you can just play the android version for free to see if you like it pc version is well worth it
But obviously that costs money. Uh, not a problem for me, but hey, it's cute. It's got a nice pixel art style
It's good. Go try it
Okay, cool. I think a little bit more again
Uh
Oh god, I I forget to wait
Demon crawl demon crawl demon crawl now. I understand it a little better
Demon crawl
Next voicemail is called cute vtuber says hi and nothing else
three two one go
Oh
Hello, this is me beer to reach a phone
You've just been fucked with you just been trolled. I just freaked your fucking mind all only mecha
Which is kind of this are repeated in red
All which is true only metal can thoroughly freak a podcasters minds
If you want your minds unfreaked in your lives
Then this monopoly man would be a tree chase the bands. I won't open you a million dollars by the end of today
For these podcasters who the freaking die. Okay. Goodbye. Thank you to each day. It was nice talking to you. Goodbye
It's nice talking to you, too
Nice hearing from you
Uh
Nice nice I got owned tonight. I think so. How many uh more voicemails is there?
There's only one two three four. There's eight more
Word, we're almost um, you could give me one sec. I'll be right back
Um, you guys to keep playing we're gonna do that. We're gonna do the next one without you
We can't we got to go we can't you when things change you just got to keep moving forward
You can never go back. You can only go forward
Next one is called the bandits have arrived three two one go
Tom deduces that the bird creature is telling what they believe to be the truth
And has no hints of maliciousness about them
Gib also succeeds in tickling the bird creature into laying an egg
And proceeds to eat it in front of him
The bird creature does not like this
And then proceeds to leave without offering any additional information or weaponry
You continue your fortifications for the next few weeks
Finally a band of bandits appear outside for fortress
The bitcoin bandits
They make attempts to penetrate your structure, but then stop
It seems your fortifications have succeeded. They then make the demand
Man
Give us your bitcoins
What do you do
Very simple command
I like the fact that that bird was trying to help and I just tickled it into making an egg
Uh like like how inappropriate and then I ate the child that they made and they're like oh god gross
It's terrible. It's terrible etiquette
um
Oh, it's just chaotic and neutral things
uh, I mean
I actually already I already sold on my bitcoin
So, uh, uh, oh, you know about that. I sold two similar time a little later than you did so I didn't uh
a
It was it was already going down by the time I had sold it
But then it went even lower and I was like it started to come back up and I just reinvested the money the money again
It's gone back up. Uh, so basically I've just I nothing happened actually
Damn, I sold it. It's back. It went back up to it was close to where I sold it before
It's gone back up most of the way, but not quite to where I sold it
So I may still I may still have made the right decision
Uh, although damn it really like shot up earlier today and I don't I don't like that. I don't like to see that
Yeah
So please please die again
It it was like at the lowest point in the last week
And I was like, you know
I don't like the idea that I don't have bitcoin. What if it does go up? I'll feel so stupid
So I just put the money in I basically paid for the transaction fee twice
And I yeah, I mean
But it went up though, so
You just feel more comfortable when you have bitcoin you feel naked without bitcoin
Okay, yeah, I guess
Uh, I need my bitcoin to keep me warm at night. Yeah, I say I say to these bandits. No, you can't have my bitcoin
It's my safety blanket
I say, uh, I say, oh god, they they don't uh, they don't know
I say I say there's no bitcoin. There's no bitcoin. I sold on my bitcoin. Sorry. I sold the bitcoin. No bitcoin here
Goodbye, but ben. I've already told them that I have my bitcoin and I won't no, but I
Oh, well, I mean they can have your bitcoin
You know, I don't care. Oh, no
Uh, I I push ben off of the photo. No, I push you
the fortifications
Oh roll for
Pushing off fortifications. I'm gonna get they can they can take your bitcoin and leave my fuck leave my fortifications in peace
No, we're struggling. This is where we are right now. We're struggling trying to push each other off
We're trying to push the other way. What is what does pushing me even do for you? They're gonna just come to see that I have no bitcoin
Yeah, but if if you're down there
You should just let me put you should just let me push you off because no no no no you do have bitcoin
So it makes more sense. That's why I need you to be pushed off because if you're pushed off you can't push me off
If they if you if I push you off, they'll take your bitcoin. They'll be happy. They'll go
If they if you push me off then I want to have my bitcoin
There's if you if you they're still gonna attack you they're still gonna attack you for those bitcoin
Yeah, but then I'd be in the fortifications. They'd
I don't but I don't want you to be in the fort. I want to be in the fortifications you and your bitcoin can go outside
please
Like I push I push harder
I want to live and I want you to die. No, I want to live and I want you today
Okay, so it seems don't you just understand it seems we're at an impasse here
Okay, oh, oh, oh hang on hang on roll die dot com just go to
It
No, no, no let him roll let him roll
I'll roll. Okay. Yeah, I'll let I'll let them roll let them let them resolve
I don't want to I don't want to roll on the show right now
Okay, so that's so that's where we're at. Uh, I'm gonna win. I'm gonna win for sure
There's no question. Um
Next voicemail, uh is uh, where is it? Where is it? Here we go
Um
Jebediah Prickingson comes to an obvious realization
Three two one go
Hello, this is me Jebediah Prickingson
Also known as the prick for my respectable penis size. Yes, of course
I just gotta say I
I feel I'm pretty silly about
Thinking about killing myself. Yeah
Our social relationship doesn't really exist
Feels stupid kind of you know
Also, it feels stupid to send you guys voicemails
Yeah, maybe they shouldn't
I
That's it. No Jebediah pricksing prick prick prick prickles and you have a voice modulator
That's the absolute bare minimum of what it takes to be the bare maximum to be yeah to be to oh for a worthwhile voicemail
So you're you're already beating. Um
Who was it before who said that they're just gonna send voicemails until one is good
You're already ahead of that guy
You know things things think focus on the positive things we're looking up
Um next voicemail is called
Wait, this one's called an honest request which is the same there was already one called an honest request
But this is a new one three two one go
Okay, okay, okay, where where do I go just show me where just point the way sucky wucky come you want me
Yes, please
Don't don't say that. Yes, please. Don't say for me. Comey's for me
Oh, no more next
More more yes more yes, but have you considered yes more?
Uh next next voicemail is called interesting question three two one go
Did you ever taste stash through your own semen and how did it taste and why did you do it?
What could you understand that did they ask I think you tried semen
Have you tried your own semen?
out of the taste
I think I I tasted a little bit one time just out of curiosity and I thought it tasted kind of
Not very much like anything, but yeah good
I've I've gotten
You guys ever heard of the the technique snowballing
Yeah, yeah, I've seen I've seen clerks
Yeah, so let's say I let's say I have that and I have I've performed the snowballing so
No, I haven't done that I haven't done that but I took a it took a little like
Sniff tasted it and was like ew and that's uh, that's where that's where I'm at with that
Um, babe
Uh, no, I've never done anything. I've never been curious enough. I've never done anything. Okay
I would I would like to know with regards to semen
I see and eating. Okay. No, that's pretty fucking lame
Yeah, come on give live a little
Yeah, please
No, I'd rather die than live. I fucking I'll make you I'll fucking make you
Next thing you're gonna tell me is you didn't eat your boogers when you were a kid
Well, you never know I didn't you've never tried to eat a little of your poop before like just you never been curious
Like what poop tastes like
You never thought like come on. What if I as an adult like like what if I just shit myself and I like didn't go to the toilet
But try that it's like, you know
It just had a curiosity
Just to see what would happen. Do you believe in the lies of society?
Oh
Sheep you're all sheep sheep. She felt like me the enlightened poopy
Next voicemail is called hyben 2 3 2 1 go
Guys
You need to get uh, uh digi's new cohorts
Uh bird and riley on the podcast. I was thinking that they were pretty gay
Uh before but I saw a video of them beating the shit out of digi's enemies. So, um, they seem pretty cool
I just don't want to eat the shit behind me. Uh, ben, you might want to watch out too, buddy
Uh, okay
Thanks for the voicemail. Her name is tricksy. Her name is tricksy. Oh, yes, and her name and her name is tricksy
There's no digi
Uh, that's all I have to say about that. I'm gonna inherit the digi role
I'll be the new digi
I didn't didn't ethan say that he was going to attempt to recast digi
I saw a tweet where he said he was going to find a homeless man
And and uh and make him the new digi pro and in recast and recast her and what?
No, as in as in
The tricksy is no longer digi bro. Therefore find a new person a homeless man and make him the new digi bro
I am I was really which is funny in concept. There must always be a there must always be one
I was uh, I was rewatching before um tricksy deleted the digi after dark content
I was rewatching a couple of them and I realized how wait
Is that channel gone too? It's isn't it like the digi collective now and it just has nothing but the music related stuff
I didn't realize she deleted that stuff. Um, did she okay, whatever?
Um, I was rewatching it doesn't matter. I was rewatching a couple of old, uh
digi
Digi after dark and I and I was amazed how much I I still like
Related to a lot of her older points
Like in in this moment right now and there's more right now in my life
And I realized maybe maybe I should be the new digi bro. I I I relate so hard at this moment right now
That would be pretty ironic then if they replaced uh, no one be with digi bro on the on the
The pizza party podcast
A picture it'll be a picture of tricksy and I'll say digi one
I
Let me see here. I mean it looks like there's still
Oh, yeah, okay. Looks like yeah, it looks like most of the content on the digi collective is gone. Okay. Yeah, lol, whatever
um next voicemail is
Uh, I'll put it right there and it is called
Breaking news
Three two one go
It's just a new thing Ralph. It's a drunk asshole more than 11. Well
Um, yep base base next
God, well, I can't yeah. Yeah, I can't really can't can't really argue. Can't wait till he goes to prison permanently. That'd be awesome
I mean, I don't wish anything good on him
Uh, that's all
That's
That much we can all agree on
Uh, next next
Next voicemail is called board co-op plus boy
boi
so ben's weekly reminder to catch up on one piece and
Boi so three two one go
Not only is it your weekly reminder to catch up on one piece this week ben, but
How about this the binding rizek is getting its
Final dlc
31st. I thought you guys should know if I recall correctly. That's a game you guys enjoyed in the past. It's true
But I know that's something that I am looking forward to
Fair um, I don't need I don't need that in my life right now
I got I went on I got on another noida kick earlier in the week and I
I got so I got so powerful that I was crashing the game
Uh, like my wands were so good
I don't know why they do this but but when I have wands that shoot too many that shoot a single projectile that explodes into many small projectiles
Some that can sometimes crash the game and it was doing that it was crashing my game
It was deleting my wands. It was deleting my spells. It was corrupting my save data. It was so
infuriating
Uh, I I don't
Know what the problem is like like I still could play it but like stuff was gone and I'm like well, that's not fair
I fucking I earned that stuff
My wands my wands. No, it's unfair. It's unfair. Why?
It's unfair and I hate video games now
And uh, I was going for the alt I was going for the 33 orb run
I had everything I I needed like
And I I guess I still could do it that save file is just kind of there
But like I'm just feeling I'm salty about I haven't touched in a while
Uh, and I don't I don't need to start playing a new game like binding if I if I started playing binding vizek again
I'm sure it would sink another 100 200 hours into it easy
Maybe at some point. I'll I'll I'll go back to it
Um
The last the last voicemail is called oopsie. But oopsie bobo. There it is loading it there three two one go
Some pussycald in last episode to warn you about the consequences of shoplifting
Um, buddy, don't express your own insecurities on other people
We very know what the fuck is gonna happen if they catch us
Nothing they're gonna say. Please stay
I've done it. They've caught me nothing happens. Try to get away with it. Just play along
You can um put them in another bag and try not to pay for them
And if someone sees your bag you just go like oh, no, no, no, I just forgot to pay
I'm so dumb
Sorry, sorry. I forgot to pay
Now I gotta go
Bye bye
I think it just walk out of the store in almost every case like the worst they can do is like ban you from the store
And like if they remember you they might they'll tell you like you can't come in here leave
Uh, I think that's the worst that's gonna happen. I can't say for sure
Thank god, like like I said on the last one. They they're not cops. They can't arrest you. Yeah, my uh
My cousin, uh, tried to steal a pants from macy's and they told him he was banned and then he came back to next month
They didn't fucking notice
I'm sure if there's like a change in management then like how would the craig
Craig left the call. It's I guess it's been three hours
um
But I guess that's a good signal for us to end because yeah, we were 10 minutes away from uh, ellie is our three hour limit
All right, okay, I guess any
Yeah, go on. Yeah, any any final any final thoughts before we wrap up
I think I remembered the specific reason why I wanted to come on
I dropped a video recently called how to get your own adult swim show
And I did I didn't want to provide it. I did show it to you. I don't know if you've seen the finished version then or gib
I don't think you showed me the finished version
You showed me a version. Yeah. Yeah, I did. I've been just showing it around to everybody because I'm pretty
proud of how it came out
And I need I need I need more eyes on it and since uh, since daddy pan is not going to put me on every episode
It just every other episode
I and I need I need the views I I savor I'm savor for the views on this video. I need them
Right, so you absolutely. Yeah, so it's on the cheesy manfredo channel. It's how to get your own adult
swim show
I recommend it. It's a funny
Video, I won't spoil it. It's funny. It's informative to spoil it. It's basically
It is informative. I didn't I did not know any of this until you told me about it
I guess like to run it down really quickly. There's there's there's a stream on adult swim
Um called the development meeting where people could actually call in and try to pitch an idea for a show
And they were actually talking to people who are development heads at adult swim
So these guys aren't just like
Host or actors. No, they're actually like development heads
And I've seen enough episodes that I like know the meta game of how to get like a pitch
Like across so this video. Yes. Um, yeah, this video is going to teach you the way to perform the perfect
It's a good idea. It's a good idea for a video. It really is
Um, yeah, check it out. Let's check it out
I will once again remind you that if you're a comic artist
Do you know any comic artists cartoonists who want to maybe get their work published in the kato anthology?
Link down in the description if you want to see see that and then submit your work
For when they do the Kickstarter to publish it, uh, probably in a month or a little more. I'm not exactly sure but soon
Link in the description for that
Um gib anything left
No, no, I guess I guess that's it. I guess that's it for the pro
Crastinators
podcast
Goodbye
Long later
Yeah