I'm gonna bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
That son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch.
Bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch.
Okay, so right now it starts.
Now this is the official beginning of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am Ben Saint and I have to introduce myself because as who are these podcasts tells us
if you do not have a theme song and the hosts do not introduce themselves, that is a Cinema
Sins ding on your podcast because that's what podcasts are supposed to do.
I have with me today a reborn pyro from Shreddit.
Hello.
Hello everyone.
And Advil also from Shreddit?
No.
Advil from Advil.
I'm sorry, excuse me.
Pardon me.
Pardon.
You guys want to introduce yourselves again for anyone who doesn't know?
Yeah, so my name is Reborn Pyro.
I am one of the four hosts of Shredditors along with Aspoy, Lumia, and Kai the Kitty Lewis.
Yes, you were on one other time.
Yes, sir.
A few months ago, I think.
We make fun of Reddit and that's about it.
I mean, we have a new guest every week, a new wacky Zany guest.
It brings a lot of diversity to the table, unique thoughts, unique pallet of cringe,
and every week we tear into a new subreddit.
Yes, I was on the one about the cheating, the r slash cheating subreddit about people
who are like, oh man, ever since I discovered cheating on my wife, my life has just been
so much cooler.
Why didn't anyone think of this before?
The new meta unlocked.
Or that one lady who was like, I put an upside down pie up with my shopping cart.
Why am I not getting laid?
Yeah, it's a universal symbol.
What was the other episode that I was on?
Confessions.
Just confessions in general?
Yeah, where the guy had a dream about calling Obama the n-word.
Oh, yeah.
Wait, actually?
Yeah, that one was like, he's like, hey guys, I'm like liberal, I swear.
But I keep dreaming, having dreams where I call Obama the n-word.
I'm not racist or anything.
What does this mean?
That guy needs to get off cod, I swear.
He needs something for sure.
It sounds like I'm implying something, but I genuinely don't know what it is.
A therapist?
Perhaps, I mean, who among us couldn't use a little therapy once in a while?
That is 100% fair.
Yeah.
Yeah, so the shreddit, funny shit over there.
What's going on? What do we want to talk about?
What do we got on the docket to discuss this week for PCP stuff?
What do you guys want to talk about?
I'll throw the ball to you.
We should let Advil introduce himself.
Oh, did I not? Ah, shit, sorry.
No, you're cool, man.
I'm Advil.
No, it's not okay.
I'm so stupid.
That's what I thought.
That's what I thought, yeah.
No, I'm Advil, I make commentary-esque videos.
I like devolving into a topic that a lot of people have talked about or researched
and then just kind of finding out stuff about people who have a specific image.
Okay, commentary, commentary, gotcha, gotcha.
My next video is about shreddits, so make sure to stay tuned.
Are you going to roast shreddit?
Yeah, A, Reborn Pyro.
Are you going to cancel Reborn Pyro?
Oh no, oh no.
Yes, finally.
Finally, someone's got to take him down a peg.
No.
Pyro said you were like the social media manager?
No, that was Marin.
Marin we were going to have on.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
Yeah, that's right, that's right.
We stole two employees from the PC.
Marin was going to be on, but he couldn't make it.
We have stolen two employees from you.
We stole Nate's editor and we have stolen your Minecraft guy, Gitfuckdab.
Nate's editor is no need, bro, right?
Yes, he is also our editor.
Well, you know, fucking SaberSpark64 also stole Eleazar.
Oh shit.
And the editing scene for YouTube channels that have PCP members on them
sure is just a big incestuous like everybody's fucking editing for everybody clusterfuckdab.
You guys are the mob bus.
You just kind of disperse equally against like every YouTube channel out there.
I think so.
It's like your people.
They had, yeah, the SaberSpark64 was getting edited by, it was Eleazar,
DuneCoon from the Proanon, KaijuCoon of being an artist fame,
and there's one other one.
I think there was another one who I'm forgetting, but it's another person who is in the sphere.
I just thought it was really funny that they poached our editor.
Oh, and I think maybe No Need Bro was the other one.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Sorry.
I lost the thread.
What's happening?
Where am I?
All right.
So one of my shows called the PCP.
Yeah.
So we were talking about this before the episode started, but I just want to bring it back up.
Oh yeah.
Riley is a fucking coward.
I do not give a shit.
I made you delete your tweets, you little fucking rat goblin.
Run to Trixie and tell her about how the big mean shred it made you delete everything.
Fuck you.
You fucking...
So he was...
Let's back up a little bit.
All right.
Let's give a little context for this.
This was in the fallout of Trixie's, I would say, instant classic post about her appearance on
The Who Are These Podcasts, in which she appears on the show to bring up the PCP.
They are very on procrastinator's podcast as a subject of ridicule and mockery, and
spends like 20 minutes, 20 plus minutes or so, trying to convince the hosts that like,
the PCP fucking sucks, man.
The PCP is fucking stupid as hell.
There's a lot of angles to this thing that happened.
There's the angle of the fact that even the hosts who seem to be friendly with her and
seem to know her from outside the show, even they don't seem impressed and at certain times
they just make fun of her and tell her like, you're not being funny, please be funnier.
God fucking imagine being told that.
Complain funnier, quote, complain funnier was what he told her.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
He said, are you zugocking the podcast?
And I think zugock is a reference to some other guests that they had that everyone agreed
wasn't funny and just had an axe to grind.
Are you zugocking the podcast?
Please complain funnier.
And then there's the aspect of what she actually said.
Her complaints were all like, they were all like extremely like minor and like huge reaches.
Like she said like, Ben literally can't speak.
And like, okay.
And then you?
I don't know.
I don't know anymore.
So confused.
Advil, do you watch the PCP?
I mean, are you familiar at all?
Yeah, I'm, I watched.
So I got, I got told that I was going to come on here.
And so I was like, okay, I'll just, I'll watch a few episodes while I'm editing.
Okay.
And I watched, oh fuck, I completely forgot that guy's name, but I'll try to figure it out.
But yeah, I watched a few.
Wait, which guy?
The, um, let me try to find it.
I completely, I think I watched the fit emcee one.
Oh, that's a pretty old one.
Yeah, because I just really like fit.
Oh, sure.
Makes bangers.
But, uh, okay.
I found it.
I watched another one.
I forgot, but yeah.
Fair enough.
Good shit.
Thank you.
Um, it's, uh, uh, what was it?
What was it going to say?
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
The, the other aspect was like that, like so many of the things that Trixie brings up
on who are these podcasts to like call us bad at are things that like notably she is worse
at than us.
For instance, there's a, there's much made about the fact that I joke about only reading
that Henry Kissinger book one page at a time while I'm shitting.
And she's like, Ben doesn't read.
Ben doesn't know how to read books.
And then later on Gibb, we're talking about cowboy towns and like, where do people live
in the cowboy, in, in old Western cowboy towns?
And Trixie makes a big deal of like, why did they bring this up on the podcast without
reading a book?
Why don't they just read a book about it?
Why wouldn't they read a book about it before they say something stupid when, you know,
like anyone who knows Trixie from, from, you know, a while back at least will remember
that like kind of a whole thing about her was that she refused to read books and that
she said like, I'll never read a book.
I just want a YouTube video to summarize it for me.
Oh, she forgot her character.
Oh no.
Like everybody, like everybody knows, everybody who knows her knows that she is like that.
And yet here she is.
She says, okay, she brings up the old like, she brings up the old thing about like, haha,
everybody quit the, everybody quit the show because Ben and Gibb are such insane leftoids.
And like, she knows why she quit the podcast and she knows that it, that's not the reason.
But she's bringing it up as like a, I really think she's bringing that one up just because
she thinks these guys will not like that because these are like Dick show adjacent, like rightoid
libertarians or whatever.
And so, so there's all the, so there's like so many of the things she brings up are hypocritical,
which is very weird.
And then the last thing that's notable is she starts right off the bat with a, with a jab
at like Gibb's voice and how Gibb's voice like doesn't pass.
She says something like, or she, she says it doesn't pass.
She says something like, like, yeah, Gibb is a trans woman, though you'd never know from
her voice.
And she's like, chuckles about it.
And, and this, and that's another like one, why would you say that two, like glass houses,
three, fuck you.
And then on everybody, everybody noticed this on Twitter and everybody called her out and,
and she like, she couldn't keep her story straight.
Once sometimes she would say, oh no, I wasn't trying to be insulting.
No, that wasn't an insult.
That was just me clarifying.
So the host would know.
And then to other people who were like, that's a hurtful thing to say.
She said, no, no, no, I only meant, I only, I meant to hurt Gibb's feelings, but I only
meant to hurt Gibb's feelings.
If you're trans and like you, you were offended by that, like fuck you, like you don't get
to be offended because I didn't mean to hurt your feelings.
I only meant to hurt Gibb's feelings.
So, you know, just lying about it on Twitter.
So basically she posts this, this podcast appearance on Twitter.
Everybody dog piles her ratioed completely.
Gibb says like fuck you on Twitter and gets like 10 times the, the like ratio on her fuck
you reply.
It's a big, it's a big shit show.
So this, then this, this past week we recorded immediately I call an immediate emergency
bonus episode where we do the live, live, like line by line, listen and respond thing
with Simsie.
And we recorded that and we released it right away.
It's up on the, the Patreon right now.
So that was a very funny thing that happened this week.
And that is what sparked a bunch of arguments on Twitter, including the one between you
and Riley.
So that's, that's the background for why Riley and you were having a, a big, oh, because
you, right, because you went on Twitter and you said like, yeah, Trixie is no longer invited
on the, on the, on Treaded, which is very funny.
Very, very funny.
And Riley was very upset.
This really ruffled Riley's feathers because if there's one thing, you know, his, his pride
as a, as a producer does not allow for any of his connections to like fall through upon
each other.
This is, this is, this is a big, a giant, a massive blow to his personal brand.
So for context, there, there is some deep lore here.
Okay.
A few months ago, or actually almost a year ago now, we were approached by somebody with
a me, Barry Coffey company.
And they apparently had, they apparently had already sponsored Riley and YGG on some extent.
I don't know exactly, but they mentioned that, uh, I, yeah, I, um, I just, I just want to
say, I, I, uh, yeah, what could, I, how can I be delicate?
Um, I'm sure that, I'm sure that they said they did that.
Well, okay.
I was going to say that they said that, well, because I asked, you know, if you're sponsoring
them, have they ever heard of our show?
And they said, actually, you guys were one of the ones they suggested I reach out to.
So, okay.
So I was like, oh really?
They were like, yeah, um, uh, I guess you're actually the guys from Shreddit.
Um, cause originally I'd been told by Vale to reach out to them.
They were like, I'm surprised you guys reached out to me because I was going to reach out to you.
Um, that's very, that's very strange, actually.
That's very curious, but share.
Uh, so going by that, we've always kind of joked that, uh, you know, they, if they
suggested, uh, that person reach out to us and they must watch our show.
And so it was a funny meme, like, oh, you know what, Trixie's being a bitch on Twitter.
So, and on this, uh, on this guest appearance.
So, you know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to post on Twitter telling her she's never allowed on Shreddit.
Hmm.
It's, and I really liked it.
The funny, the funny thing about the fact that Riley, like, got really mad and
started, like, complaining at you about it is like, it literally, it had nothing to do with him.
Yeah.
He, he, like, he was not involved at all, but he just had to be like an insult, like
any, an insult against Trixie is, is an insult against him in his mind for some
reason that I genuinely do not understand.
Um, I mean, dear God, it's so weird because he kept, you
know, trying to make it some kind of movement, like every other tweet saying
something like, you guys are all SJWs.
You're trying to censor free speech.
This is a movement.
And he kept going on and on about it.
And so I quote, he kept comparing it to like, like you guys also want to cancel
black comedians.
Yeah, like he kept, that's what you also want to do.
And it's the same thing.
When you say that Trixie making fun of a trans woman's voice and claiming it
doesn't pass and laughing at it is transphobic.
What you're basically doing is saying that like black comedians like Dave
Chappelle shouldn't be allowed to have to be, to work in this town ever again.
Yeah, I mean, what is that comparison?
I don't know.
It's fucking stupid.
That's the biggest leave I've ever heard.
Like, I know what he means, but it's fucking dumb.
And it's, it's dumb.
I think in specific context, that argument can be like good.
But the context of, hey, this, I mean, I'm going to be a little
transphobic and say that this trans person doesn't sound like a woman.
Yeah.
Is, and then when you get called out for it, well, actually you're racist.
So, I mean, it's, it's basic.
I mean, yeah, like it's the fact that he, the fact that he's bringing it.
Like nobody, nobody mentioned that.
Nobody was talking about that.
It's basically a completely separate issue, but he brings it up as like,
you are also responsible for this other thing.
Yeah, it's like his trap card.
No, you found their trap card.
So, so what I ended up doing is I quote, tweeted him saying that it was
a big free speech movement with a screenshot from one punch man where
Satama says, here's a guy with free time and he's holding a letter.
Classic reaction, classic reaction.
And I was like, you know, no one's ever brought up a movement or free speech.
We're a show that makes fun of Reddit.
Trying to make us political with something is a very Reddit thing to do.
Right.
And then after that, he just deleted a lot of the political tweets.
His, yeah, his political takes in that thread were very cringe.
I will say, I will say this.
He seemed very caught up.
He seemed very caught up with the idea that it is like insane, like insane
in his mind to suggest that a trans person could ever be transphobic.
Like the very, the very idea of that like completely defeats itself in his mind.
It's a total contradiction.
Say, you know, same.
I mean, I don't do I have to explain how like that's fucking stupid.
I mean, like, of course, anyone can be anything no matter what, you know,
follow your dreams.
If you want to be a big anyone can do yeah, you can do it.
Hey, if I can do it, anyone can.
You want to make fun of trans people, go for it.
That's going to get me canceled.
Oh, yeah, you're out.
Please, not again.
Yeah.
So that was the that was that story.
That was the big funny drama that happened on Twitter this week.
Stay, stay tuned for more.
We're just just just really funny seeing her post that and just get completely
ratio on Twitter literally just made us money because we turned it into a bonus
episode and a bunch of people pledged.
If you if you pledge to hear that our response to that, thank you very much.
And I hope you enjoyed it was a fun.
It was a fun to record that I went into I went into it.
I deliberately avoided listening to it so that I would not have heard it when we
did the bonus episodes, why but have a fresh reaction.
I'd be hearing everything for the very first time.
I was I was pretty pretty baffled by some of like the weird like the weird
stretches and the weird like she knows this isn't true, but she's saying it
anyway, because she knows these podcast hosts don't know us and she can get away
with like pretending that she thinks it's true about us.
Like set like saying like saying that like I would that like I would like
freeze up and like not be able to function if someone like approached
me in public and talk to me as you know, like that's that's yep.
That's me, I guess.
Anyway, good, good, good times.
Yeah, good times this week.
Great times.
Yeah.
So OK, OK, OK.
The reason why we're on.
Have you seen the Antunes video?
Oh, no, I didn't.
You posted for me.
I didn't get around to watching it.
OK, I do know who Antunes is.
All right, that's that is a perfect jumping off point, though, like knowing who he is.
Let me I talked to a few about the syndiems, but you don't have any
memories about someone named Daft Pina being in the PCP fan community, right?
No, no, I I may have heard the name Daft Pina around somewhere,
but I know that I know I think the first time I heard of him was when you had
some falling out with him or something like that.
That's why.
So the reason why they bring that up, there was a old tweet that I found
it's deleted now, but it was him posting a picture of an airport and saying
I wish I was landing for Radcon and I don't remember who we tagged.
But I know we tagged like two or three members of the PCP in it.
Mm hmm.
And wait, wait, wait, what was the tweet that he tagged some of us in?
He said he took a picture of an airport and he said I was I wish I was landing for Radcon.
You know, like you want to know this.
I think it was multiple years ago, like it wasn't a recent tweet.
OK, so so so Daft Pina is familiar with Radcon.
That's pretty funny.
Um, it's also funny that he used to be a fan of old school PCP back when it was a lot edgier.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, man, do you think he's a do you think he's a Yig head?
Oh, I hope not.
There's no there's no way.
There's like there's no way there's like there's like six.
There's like six real Yig heads and they're all like and they're all like very
like obviously insane and mentally ill on Twitter.
Lamal, that's right for you, but to tell to tell what's going on here.
I got into a little squabble with Mr.
Penis. I'm sorry, Mr. Pina.
I'm sorry, Mr. Pina.
Gotcha. OK.
So basically, he made a video on a theory on art.
And at the time, I thought the video did a good job.
Can you explain who a theory on art is?
A theory on art is a very big Twitter artist.
He is very good art. OK.
He has been on my show, Shreddit, three times, not since the video, of course.
But, you know, at the time there came out of video canceling them for saying,
you know, racial slurs and the F slur and all this.
OK. At the time, I thought, you know, the video was good.
It canceled a bigot.
Um, OK.
But the issue is he used clips from Shreddit three times in a show,
which is fine credit them, right?
Well, the first two, he cut off our names so you couldn't see whose videos it was.
And then and then the third time he called us the r slash podcast.
And that's funny because that's not a very popular podcast.
That feels more like a jab than a credit
because the r slash podcast is just a text to speech robot reading reddit post.
Hmm. Well, why would he do that?
I don't know.
I politely asked in a server and he says,
well, in the third time I show, you know, a clip from your show,
the name is in the bottom.
I don't care that I miscredited it.
I just, you know, if people really want to find you, they can.
OK.
And it's like, well, OK, so I understand what you're saying,
but you've made several videos calling out artists for tracing
and, you know, not crediting their work.
OK. OK.
So you feel you feel you were improperly credited.
Well, I mean, we got called the wrong name.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And I mean, yeah, it sounds like he just he sounds like he just fucked up
and then wouldn't admit it.
Yeah, especially for like a 200 sub channel, you know, show or whatever.
Having someone because he has over 100,000 subscribers on his YouTube channel
and the theory on video got over well over the like amount of
like subscribers he has.
It has like 200,000 now.
And there's like a bunch of videos about a theory on, et cetera.
And having like that, like if he went, by the way,
like if you at least just put in the description,
it would just help at least like a little bit gain a bigger audience.
You know? Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, of course.
No, I think I think there's merit to what you're saying.
He gets worse, though.
Yeah.
So a history of like not not crediting
anyone in his videos.
The most he does is credit the the people that
like voice at like, you know, retweets or whatever at the end of the video.
He like does that, but he doesn't credit any of his sources.
He doesn't like give like full context
interviews to like whenever he interviews someone.
So it's purely just his word against, you know,
it's just his word against the viewers, you know,
it's his word against everyone else's and he goes off like,
you know, his his fans believing whatever it is.
Yeah. I mean, sure.
I don't make sense.
But like I was saying, so, you know, I was very polite.
I was very professional.
I was like, listen, you know, you call artists out for this.
I understand that, you know, you might be busy.
But if you could just, you know, please credit me, right?
And then I get a ban warning from his discord server for that.
Like super nice, super professional.
Um, OK, so then I start talking
because people in a server start reaching out to me.
I start talking with them.
And did I get another warning?
And the second warning reads like a schizo
post and it's full of misspellings.
From from who?
From Pina.
Because he has a he types out messages for a bot to DM people.
And the reason why I know he typed this out
is there are multiple misspellings.
He types out messages for a bot to DM people.
Like, like whenever you do something,
you can get a message in your DMs.
Oh, yeah, you broke rule number one, two, et cetera.
And then it gets like a very vague reasoning.
Gotcha, gotcha.
All right.
OK, and here I'm pulling it up.
OK, yeah.
And the second the first warning
was for asking him a second time in VC, you know,
just trying to have a back and forth conversation about,
hey, you know, it's really not cool of you specifically
to not credit people.
Um, but the second warning was you were warned
in armchair critics for you were warned
because you were persistently in violation of the rules.
You were not threatened with a ban.
Past being warned, you continued to instigate arguments
and use mistrust and attempt to rally members of this server.
And he spelled this wrong.
The feature creator, Daft, address your question in Q&A
and past his response, you have continued to instigate
and falsify the situation.
How is asking to be credited at instigating
and falsifying a situation like it's not complicated?
It sounds like he's just mad.
It's just big mad.
As you stated before, you were simply asking Daft
to credit you, yet you are now claiming Daft
with stealing assets and refusing to credit.
Well, he did play.
I mean, those are the same thing.
Those are the same thing.
Yes, and he did straight up refuse to credit me.
Like...
Yeah.
Yeah, get your story straight.
You say he refused, he took your content without crediting,
but now you're saying that he took your content
without crediting?
Oh, no.
Okay, I see.
And the funny part was before I got this,
I have an app called Better Discord.
I can see hidden voice channels that the public can not.
I can't see into locked text chats,
but I can see who's in calls
and what the chat rooms are called.
Okay.
He had, at the time, a PR manager.
Him and that PR manager were in call for four hours
before I got the second warning,
and then the second I got it, they both left call.
I have confirmed with the old PR agent
that the entire four hours was discussing
how to handle this.
Why does it take four hours to discuss
if you should credit somebody or not?
I see.
To give context, it's not like 100% certain
that it was the PR manager.
It was, well, no, no, it was the head moderator,
but they claimed that the PR manager bit was just a joke,
but also, who knows?
Yeah.
Okay.
Either one works.
All right, so, so.
It's still not good.
All right, so it sounds like a weird stupid shit fit
and he threw a tantrum and gave you some weird
fucking bullshit about some legalese nonsense
because you wanted to be credited,
and he was like, well, actually,
here's why I shouldn't have to do that and fuck you.
Whatever, he flipped out about the fucking stupid shit
that he should just say sorry for and fix.
That was it for my end.
I mean, I made a tweet on Twitter
because I thought it was really messed up.
Yeah.
The reason why I said I used to agree with his video
on Ethereum is Ethereum actually,
he came out as a black gay man,
and he says that he has the right to use those slurs,
how he sees fit.
Wait, wait, wait.
Ethereum did?
Yes, Ethereum is.
Oh, that's right, that's right.
Oh, that was the guy who was like.
Yeah.
Yes, I'm black and gay, so it's okay.
And he said that, and nobody knew that before.
Was he lying about that?
No, no, everyone was like,
he said, by the way, I'm gay and black, Lil.
And everyone was like, cap, cap, you can't be black, cap.
Yeah, Defpina posted the meme of why would someone
go on the internet and just tell lies.
Yeah.
And then Ethereum posted a video of himself.
Being black and having sex with another man.
Well, anyone that's known,
anyone that's known Aether for a very long time knows
that if you bring up feminine men in the call,
he will go off on rants about how much he loves feminine men.
The homosexual part was never in doubt,
but nobody knew that he was black.
Yeah, okay.
He's posted like a lot of videos of him
like going through his old notebooks and stuff,
like where you could just see his hand flipping through pages,
unless he just has like an incredible budget for like,
faking truths, I'm pretty sure he's black.
Jesus.
Okay, all right, understood, understood.
Yeah.
So, okay, I think I understand all of this crap that happens.
So where does it stand now?
Did Defpina eventually just like say fuck you,
get out of my server and that's it?
He actually did because, okay,
so behind the scenes for the last month,
there have been a lot of people collaborating
on anti-pina projects, let's say.
Advil here is one of the ones-
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Defpina, I want to say, okay,
the one thing I did see of Defpina was,
you remember Cheezy's big Twitter artist
who follows you tweets about,
you know, those comics about like,
when big Twitter artists like your tweet
don't give you the retweet boost, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I remember-
Oh, he's had a fuck going, actually.
Defpina was one of the guys,
was one of the big people on Twitter who replied,
this is, actually, nobody owes you a retweet
and you just look petty
and it's just going to ruin your reputation
if you just complain about people not retweeting you.
And it was one of those,
it was one of the loser responses from someone who is big
being like, I hate when people,
I hate when people want anything from me.
I hate when smaller content want a boost.
Just get better at all.
There were many cringe responses to that,
but that particular one of being a big artist
and being like, you shouldn't expect anything from me,
peasants, was like one of the more cringe ones
and he did it, so that did not leave a good impression
in my eyes.
So, okay, that's my context.
Continue.
So, yeah, a lot of people reached out.
Antunes is one of them.
Antunes had a lot of personal beef with Daft.
Oh, well, Antunes is much worse.
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
So, a lot of their beef response comes down to
pettiness, like Daft refusing to give him the recording
he made of Antunes in their interview
and just a bunch of stuff like that
because he was interviewed for the video,
he did know about it, but it's the way Daft handled it.
For which video?
For the Antunes video?
Yeah, he made a video on Antunes.
Okay.
And he recorded-
I mean, fuck it, fuck Antunes.
Nothing, no treatment is too bad for Antunes.
Regardless of how you think of Antunes,
I still think his handling of the whole situation
was not the best because he-
Doubt.
He doubted.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
There's nothing you could do to Antunes
that I'd be like, ooh, he didn't deserve that.
Not on like an Antunes personal level,
like I don't care how you feel about any of the people
I'm making my video with or like on or whatever,
but going like-
Are you making videos?
Are you working with Antunes?
I asked him for an interview and that was really it.
I asked him for information.
Okay, okay, I mean, that's one thing.
But like, is it technically working with?
I can never say that.
Okay.
No, interviewing someone is not working.
No, it's not unless you're like both making money off of it.
Okay, then yeah, I'm not gonna make money off the shit,
but the, I feel like from like a general creator sense,
I don't know if I just have like this self-righteous
like belief on how a commentary YouTuber should handle it,
but it seems like even though Daft tries to stir away
from the commentary spectrum,
even though he's collabed with the right opinion
and Turkey Tom, the way he handles himself,
like online and on his own channel,
even is very unbecoming of a commentary YouTuber.
He's very sensitive.
He doesn't work.
He's very, he's besmirching the good name
of commentary YouTubers across the board.
He is tarnishing.
We have standards, dammit.
Well, I feel like there should be.
I feel like a lot of times commentary channels
just like, they're just so fucking stupid sometimes.
Of course.
I don't wanna be like the police of YouTube
because that's cringe as shit.
But like, I feel like it should be more like journalism
instead of like just talking shit about someone
and ruining like their reputation
without any actual evidence
or even like giving them a chance to defend themselves
or giving them a fair like trial, you know?
That's how I feel about commentary.
I think, ah.
I'd rather talk like, like if I'm gonna make a video.
I don't know if I entirely agree with you.
I don't know if I entirely disagree with you either.
I mean.
At least the way I wanna make my commentary videos
is I wanna find a topic that is either like unknown
and see how truly deplorable it is
and talk to as many people as the other side
and on the side that's like talking shit about them
and see what the truth is
because both sides gonna fucking like,
like, you know, be completely unfair to the other side,
you know?
And, and-
Yeah, sure.
And what people like Daph will do,
they'll like talk to one person on the other side
and completely cut out any context that they had
to make it a fair, you know, video or a fair anything.
And he doesn't even like cite his sources for why,
like, he won't even like put, he has a second channel
and he won't even put like a full interview on there,
which is something that like, like a technicals does.
Like, I feel like that is a very good,
like just like a safe thing to do.
And he doesn't even do the most bare bones commentary thing
is, do you watch commentary at all?
What?
Do you watch like commentary videos at all?
Uh, I mean, I give me, what's an example?
Like Turkey Tom, Leafy, those types of people.
I have probably seen a few,
but I don't like regularly watch them or anything.
So the most bare bones thing you can do
is just put a disclaimer at the beginning,
which is, hey, don't harass these people.
This is just either my opinion
or I'm just giving you like the facts,
but don't harass these people.
He's never done that in a single video,
not in a single tweet.
He hasn't said that like in his YouTube description.
So it's very just like unspoked, you know?
You think, okay.
You think that Daph Pina,
you think that his conduct is unbecoming.
Yes, exactly.
Of the honorable title of commentary YouTuber.
Yeah, it's a nightly manner of being a commentator.
I kind of get what you're saying.
I get what you're saying.
I guess because I grew up on commentary,
I just have like this nice image of it,
because I know it is pretty dog shit to be honest.
Like I know like it is probably the most cancer part
of the entire internet, but I just-
I don't know about that.
Oh yeah, true.
But like I just want it to be like,
I want it to be as fair as it can be to, you know.
That's, okay, yeah.
I mean, fairness is good.
Fairness is good.
And I understand what you're saying.
I mean, yeah, if you've got two sides of a story,
yeah, both sides of any story
always claim something different.
And so like the best way to do it is to get both
and then try and figure out like who is lying about what,
who is being honest about what,
what is the real story?
Because it's usually somewhere in the middle.
Yeah, yeah.
And like generally the more people you ask about something,
usually you can kind of suss out the truth
if you get enough different people to explain it to you
and you kind of like pick out the commonalities.
So I, I have, yeah, that's, that's good.
I get you, I get you.
You don't, and you don't think Daft does that.
The most he does is allow, so I grew up, or not grew up,
but I used to watch a lot of Daft Pina
while I was trying to figure out my style.
And I was like, yeah, this guy's,
this guy's pretty cool.
Cause I never seen like a lot of commentary YouTubers
like give interviews to, you know, people.
And he was like the first guy, I saw that I would do that.
But then, and then I started to research it a little bit more
and he didn't like include the full context.
So he would just like cut out context.
He would like change it to fit a narrative,
which is fine, I guess, but like if you're,
if you're going through all the trouble of create,
like going to have a interview with someone
and going to cut context,
at least use the entire interview on something.
Cause no one's going to like check the original interview.
Okay. Yeah.
I feel you.
Yeah, I feel you.
If I felt like someone was like deliberately leaving stuff out,
as they're trying to explain something to me,
I'd be like, well, well, fuck you.
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
But I mean, I was saying before a lot of people
reached out to me and shredded in general
to ask us about what happened there.
Multiple people wanted the story.
Antunes included because Antunes was a,
Antunes has a personal grudge with Pina.
I'm sure, I'm sure he does.
I'm sure he does.
But Pina has made a very large amount of enemies
and I didn't know that cause I knew nothing about Pina
prior to this.
To me, it was just some guy who stole my content.
Now I have a lot of people reaching out to me
because apparently he tends to step on a lot of people's
toes.
Sure.
Like a good example recently is his fight with Tina Fey
on Twitter, who was an artist that was pretending
to be female.
Oh yeah, okay.
Not Tina Fey of Saturday Night Live.
Yeah.
No, no, not that Tina Fey.
Okay.
That would be funny.
But so he was basically saying,
I know you're a dude.
I have your Facebook.
I sent you a friend request.
And then he said later, I had people email me
your information.
So he has people that email him the docs
of people he has beef with.
Well, what happened is he,
so he tweeted out that he's working on a video
on Tina Fey, right?
And what happened is he included an email
that was like, if you know any information
about this person, please let me know.
And so people were emailing him and some,
like a group of people, I guess,
were emailing Tina Fey's docs,
like their name, their face, all that stuff, right?
Yeah, but he didn't condone that.
I mean, he didn't condone that, he condoned it.
Instead of being like, what the fuck?
Why would you give me this?
This video isn't about their docs.
He was like, really, send me more.
I need to know who this person is.
Okay.
It was just a very uncomfortable situation.
And he made it worse by tweeting at Tina Fey,
like in an unhinged rant, or not even a rant,
just tweeting at them, like unhinged being like,
hey, I've gotten private information.
Tina was kind of like taunting him and being like,
you're cutting out context.
We should get a call, bro, and we can discuss this.
And Daft tweeted it, and was like,
yeah, I found your personal information.
I hacked your Google accounts.
Let's talk, bro.
Follow me on Twitter at my Discord.
That reminds me of someone.
Did somebody else do that?
Did somebody else, was that like,
maybe someone in the big, like,
monkey drama from a few years ago,
be like, I have your personal information
as like a bargaining chip?
Damn, I remember someone in some big drama
I was following doing some similar shit.
Der.
Probably Keemstar.
Well, it probably happens all the time.
Probably Keemstar, to be honest.
You know what?
Yeah, oh wait, I might be actually
drinking a Keemstar in the Wings of Redemption story.
Oh, it was Wings of Redemption.
Okay, so just Destiny.
Do you know who just Destiny is?
No.
Completely sidetracked,
but he's a commentary YouTuber who got called out
by like this like 13 year old.
He threatened to sue him,
and then Keemstar found his docs
and was about to like docs him,
even though it wasn't him.
I think I am thinking of Keemstar, actually.
Yeah, it wasn't him at all,
but he was like, I found this guy's docs.
Let's chat, bro.
Gotcha, okay.
Imagine.
Well, so all right,
I understand what you're saying about Daft Pina.
So what are you gonna do about it?
Well, Advil here also reached out.
He is making a video,
and a lot of the people involved
are going to push that video.
I hope so.
So you're making a Daft Pina exposed, basically.
Yeah, and I'm trying to keep it up
to the commentary standard, you know?
You have exacting ethical standards.
I have CSGO gameplay, vaporwave intros.
This is everything, the commentary video.
This is how to make a correct commentary video.
Okay.
I start off like, hey, what's up, guys?
Welcome back to another commentary roast.
Pretty much everything you need.
Yeah, well, one of the reasons why,
one of the reasons why I agreed to talk to Advil,
and I signed on for this as well.
That's cool.
Uh, no.
Okay.
Well, no, he does seem to have actual ethical standards.
But also, it's, you know, I looked it up,
and there's no video that really
puts all the pieces of the Daft Pina pie together.
You know, like his beef with Jaden animations
and Odd Ones Out, no one mentions that.
You know, there's no actual exposed video on the guide,
despite him doxing people
and just doing a lot of shady shit.
Like, do you know what he did to Jaden animations?
Uh, I don't.
He said, has a fan, you're at,
and I'm watching this video,
you're faking your mental illness.
Hmm.
What happened is she made this video
about her experience with Interrexia,
called Why She Doesn't Have a Face Reveal.
And it was like, it was just her telling her,
like experience through Interrexia,
but she was using her video and like, you know,
sounds and all that stuff, too,
to make the audience, like, understand her point.
And it was like an old video.
He's already, like, semi-apologized for this,
which I don't have, like, I'm glad that he apologized,
but he was just like, he was like,
why would you need to pad out the video this much?
Honestly, it seems like you are fishing for content,
and Daft Pina talks like, like he's a bit slow.
So he goes like.
Okay.
So he was like, you're padding out the video,
you're probably bipolar, schizophrenic,
like all that stuff, and he was just like, calling her,
all this like shitty stuff.
He called her, he said she did have,
like other mental illnesses?
Yeah, but not, but probably not Interrexia.
You're faking this one.
Yeah.
You probably have different ones.
Yeah, because you're fucking insane.
That's what he said.
Okay.
And then a couple months later,
he made a video about her music video with Boy in a Band,
about her bulimia, right?
And he basically did the same thing.
He said that because she didn't donate to the charity,
like a bulimia charity,
that she's just been profiting off like bulimia
without like giving back to the community or whatever.
First of all, fucked.
Okay.
Second off.
Okay, I get it.
Yeah, and then he apologized for the first video,
but still kept the second one.
And he's still profiting off the second one,
even though he did the exact same thing.
Yeah, sounds, I mean, I don't want to,
I don't want to stick my neck out too far
for Jayden animations.
I don't really care if someone goes after Jayden anime,
but it sounds like he's,
I mean, it sounds like he was being a bit of a shitter
in this situation.
Yeah.
And so, yeah.
All right.
That sounds like a bit shit.
Yeah.
He probably should have apologized for some of that.
Okay.
So what were we talking about?
Oh, I was talking about how Pina has made a lot of enemies.
He's done a lot of shitty things.
There are a lot of people co-signing on this video
to be made in the first place
because it's a common consensus.
You're in the process of talking to people.
If you talk to Antunes again,
tell him that I, Ben Saint, say, fuck you.
Shut the fuck up, you fucking mutant.
Tell him he's a sub-human mutant for me.
I'll let him know.
Actually, put that in,
okay, when you make the video
and you have Antunes in it,
make sure to include an addendum of me, Ben Saint,
saying, hey, by the way,
the person you just listened to is a fucking idiot
and you shouldn't believe anything they say.
They're big liar, big racist,
big, big fucking jackass and fuck him.
And that gets the PCP seal of approval.
There you go, Advil.
This is important, all right?
There you go.
This is important context.
You would be leaving out context.
I'm sorry.
You wouldn't be getting all sides of the story
if you didn't include this, so you better fucking...
Yes, sir, Mr. Sains, yes, sir.
Yes, sir, yes, sir, yes, sir.
That's right, I say jump.
You say hi, okay, good.
Yes, sir.
The publisher you want me to try to Antunes,
please, please, I need your approval.
I will begrudgingly give it to you.
Okay, all right, I'm glad we've sorted that out.
So, all right, well shit,
I don't fucking know anything about Daft Pina
except for what you guys have told me.
Oh, okay, he's like a...
So maybe I'll check the video out
and then maybe I'll know a little something after that.
See?
It releases tomorrow.
Is that good?
That's why I'm comfortable with talking.
Hey.
Hello.
You're an hour late.
Yeah, the clocks went back
and I thought it was now.
That's my excuse.
Wait.
So it is daylight savings.
In the UK?
No, it is daylight savings.
That's really stupid
because daylight savings time in America starts next week.
Why wouldn't they just make it the same week?
I have no idea, but it's a consistent problem every year.
I always forget.
Yeah, that's a good excuse though.
Yeah.
That one kind of makes sense.
Okay.
Sorry, we were talking about...
Right, Gabe, you know Reborn Pyro from Shreddit.
This is Advil who was just telling us
about his Daft Pina exposed commentary video
that he is in the process of making.
Yeah, and it's a right way to make commentary.
The correct, holy, sanctuary way.
Right, the holy...
The sanctimonious.
We need ethics, we need ethics in commentary.
We need a court, and we need a court of commentary.
Sure.
Exactly, yeah.
Why not?
Oh, we need to make laws.
Why shouldn't there be a grand council?
Exactly, yeah.
We should...
So wild west out there.
I'm trying to...
I'm trying like, how can I make this
like a funny like Holocaust analogy?
No, how can I imply,
how can I imply some kind of horrible war crime
is being committed or some sort of human rights violation?
I mean, it is what's happening.
Antunes is getting decimated by Daft Pina.
That's what I want to happen.
So it's not a war crime if I like it.
I have no idea who them are.
I think I've conduct Pina before.
What do they do?
They make commentary videos on the art community.
Oh, yeah.
Call it a lot.
And Antunes posts racist comics on Twitter.
Also known as He's Baste.
I'm sorry, okay.
I'm sorry.
And then he posts racist cartoons on Twitter
and makes weird...
Okay, his cartoons are like the funniest thing ever,
but not because they're like funny,
but because it's like amazing that these like exist.
He makes...
Okay, he makes these animations
where he like traces cartoon characters
and he traces them into...
Deathbed.
Of them like standing around another cartoon character's
deathbed and all like mourning
as like they die in a hospital bed.
Yeah, I have to be honest.
That's what he did.
That's his whole thing.
No, I'm glad.
I don't fucking get it.
But he's made like dozens of them.
No matter what I think about Antunes.
If he asked me what I think about them,
which he definitely won't,
because why would he care about my opinion?
But if he did, I would tell him,
I don't understand why that got you
to a million subscribers.
Is that bad to say?
I'm not trying to show him the guy or anything, but like...
That's literally what I'm saying.
So no, I don't think it's bad.
Yeah, he's the muppet guy.
I think I've seen something with him
being a idiot before on Twitter.
He's awful.
He's an awful, awful person.
But...
Yeah, he like was...
He had like a million sub YouTube channel, I think.
Or like maybe 900K or something.
Just because he made these weird like traced,
like fucking Homer Simpson's deathbed video.
And you know, there's no like commentary.
He is not involved in the channel.
Nobody knows like what he's like,
just that he has this channel,
that he makes these deathbed videos.
And then he started getting involved in Twitter drama.
Yeah, it's kind of like the Yo Mama channel.
Like no one knows anything about the Yo Mama channel.
Oh, right.
Right, yeah.
And then he did kind of try to use his YouTube channel
as like a platform to be like,
these people are being rude to me on Twitter
and I'm being deplatformed on Twitter.
And like nobody cared,
because like nobody's there,
nobody's at the YouTube channel to like hear him say stuff.
They're there because they want to see Marge Simpson
like mourning the death of Fred Flintstone or whatever.
Yeah, it is the weirdest pair.
I think it's like purely same channel,
like same like network stuff.
Cause it'll be like Mordecai from regular show,
mourning the death of like Finn.
It should have been Twilight.
Oh my God, he missed an opportunity.
That's a missed opportunity.
Okay, I'm going to scrap the interview with him
and ask him why he didn't make it Twilight.
All right, got it.
Look at this, it's WikiTube here
and he's got like the contents and it's like content.
There's three things.
And then controversies is one, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight things, subheadings.
Lamau, this guy, oh God.
Seven point to a minor, huh?
Antunes made a commentary video, god damn.
Yeah, he's made some fucking shit.
Well, it was like a review on like rubber hose style
and has over 12 million views.
What the hell?
I don't know, he made a review on rubber hose style?
Yeah, like the cartoon,
like the animation style of rubber hose,
like we're like old Mickey Mouse was rubber hose.
He reviewed cuphead style animation.
Yeah, he like talked about it,
like gave the history about it.
Okay.
12 million is not bad though.
I know, it's a big number.
If this daffy had got to 12 million,
I would probably just sit there.
We'd all love a video to get to 12 million.
I wish, should I just start making death bed videos?
Is that the meta?
I don't think so, I don't think so
because the market is, I feel like it's a saturated market.
Okay, what if I do reincarnated bed?
What?
Reincarnated bed.
Oh, he did one with, ah, boom.
He did one with Freddy Fazbear.
Okay, I don't care about this.
I don't care about this.
I got completely distracted.
Instead of, oh, like they come out of like a death bed
but they wake up.
Birth, I believe birthing bed would be the opposite.
No.
Or a homestuck God tier bed, you know.
It's still like, well, I mean, it's like, you know,
it's like all the cartoon characters gathered
in the manger, like the three wise men,
like for the birth of, you know,
I don't know, Tom from Tom and Jerry or whatever.
I don't know, I don't know what the equivalent would be.
That'd actually be really funny.
I wouldn't mind watching it.
I mean, it's the same, it's the same like weird,
like fixation thing that like made like, you know,
pregnant Elsa, you know, Spider-Man, like popular.
So it's like, it's like some weird like quirk
of human psychology that maybe like children
are clicking on these videos for some reason.
It definitely is, and I can't even be mad at them
because I would do the same thing if I was their age.
The content's not offensive, it's just bizarre.
Yeah, I, it's not like, yeah, indoctrinating.
It's just like a bit weird,
but I can't blame anyone for watching them
because if I was a kid, I would watch them too.
Like 100%.
I don't think, I don't think I would have ever seen
the appeal, but whatever.
I was an idiot when I was a kid, so I probably would.
That was fair, that's reasonable.
Um, Gib, what's, what's up?
What's up?
Well, obviously Halloween has passed
since, while you're listening.
No, it's today.
No, I know it's today, but like two for the viewers.
Halloween's over.
Oh yeah, I didn't even mention that it,
we're recording this on Halloween.
This is Halloween days.
Oh, this is a spooky episode.
No, it's not, it's a week later.
And there's, all the skeletons are dead,
but today I carved a jack-o'-lantern
and that's, that's it.
I hadn't really, I walked the dog,
I carved a jack-o'-lantern,
and then I forgot that the podcast was happening.
Dirty, dirty, dirty.
Dirty.
That was the real scary.
That's cool, I did not carve a pumpkin
and I don't intend to.
I love carving pumpkins.
You know, it's fun.
It's like sculpting.
I do not particularly like Halloween.
I just, I tolerate it.
Do you like Halloween, Gib?
I can appreciate the aesthetic,
but I don't particularly like scary things,
like actually scary movies or games.
They make me pee my pants in my runway.
But like things that are like, ooh, spooky ghosts,
but it's not scary at all.
It's cute, in fact.
That's okay.
It's not that interesting,
but I don't mind it.
What about you, Reborn?
I like, you know, I like the witch outfits,
you know, they're nice.
I love trick-or-treating as kids,
because you know, I'm a fat ass,
so I love that candy.
Fair.
And yeah, I also like it as an excuse to drink.
Dab, dab.
Yeah, as an excuse to hang out with friends or whatever,
like it's as good as any other.
So that's fine.
I appreciate that.
The real scary part of this episode, though,
is when viewers find out
that the first 40 minutes is YouTube drama talk.
Oh, no!
I mean, what else are we gonna do?
Right, you know, fuck it.
We could talk about Twitch drama.
Twitch drama?
Yeah, it's not YouTube drama.
There we go.
Oh, okay.
No, it sucks.
I hate drama, and the drama boys.
Who eat it up.
Yeah, I hate, yeah, I would never.
By the way, subscribe to patreon.com,
slash stuff for Acrassanators
to hear our line-by-line reaction
to Trixie dunking on the Piro Acrassanators podcast
on Who Are These Podcast, link in the description.
I mean, I wasn't particularly excited
to like live react drama gossip about Trixie,
but she attacked me viciously with a knife.
That's true.
I'm called for.
Yeah, I mean, that's definitely true.
Not actually with a knife.
I will admit.
Just in case anyone's not aware,
but you gotta listen to the bonus episode to find out.
I mean, while it is, she definitely started it,
so that's true.
However, I will personally admit
to relishing the opportunity,
not merely as an attempt to defend myself,
but as a...
Means to dunk on someone.
As an offense, yeah, as the means to launch
an offensive salvo of my own.
Yeah.
See, this is the same one in commentary videos.
See, I get it.
I make fun, but I can't really judge anyone.
I get the appeal.
It's just sort of, I see drama happening every so often,
and it's like somebody I've never really heard of.
Oh, this guy's a pedophile.
Oh, this guy was racist.
Oh, that person did this and that,
oh, there's a thing, there's a whole big thing going on,
and there's these people who are keeping track of it
and posting updates and being like,
oh my God, you've seen this thing?
And I'm just like, I don't like that.
I'm so done with any drama.
It just doesn't interest me as like a topic.
I may have mentioned this before.
I'm too far gone.
Every single person online sucks.
Learning that they suck more isn't that interesting.
I may have mentioned this before.
Someone linked me a video that I tried to watch
because it sounded like some drama
that I might be interested in.
It was two people like,
okay, I didn't watch the video,
so I can't confirm any of this,
but supposedly it was a video about how Vita,
remember Vita from Pony Days?
Yeah, vaguely, yes.
About how Vita was a pedophile and was a predator
and was being, and they were like, we're here to cancel him.
And I started watching the video,
and it's these two total charisma vacuum bronies.
Just start back and forth.
They start trading off, they're talking about it.
It's like a 40 minute video,
and I'm like 10 minutes in, maybe not even that much.
And they've spent the entire time, thus far,
not even getting to the point of like,
Vita abused a child or has an underage girlfriend
or whatever the fuck the accusation was supposed to be.
They've spent the entire time being like,
yeah, Vita would like harass the mods
in this Discord server.
Yeah, like Vita gained access to one of our other servers
and like, you know, deleted the whole server
just out of spite.
And it's all a bunch of stupid Discord drama
that is supposed to like,
it's just them airing their grievances
in a way that is maybe supposed to prime me
to like think like, oh yeah, this guy is an asshole.
I'm ready to hear you tell me why he's a pedophile.
But like, God, fucking lead with it, right?
Like, I don't give a shit that you made him
the mod of your server and then he like,
he like did some shit with the permissions you gave him.
I don't fucking care.
Like, tell me what the actual problem is.
I'm wasting my fucking time, right?
Sometimes.
That's probably the, usually the problem
is that it's small potatoes and it's petty.
Usually.
When it's petty, when it's petty,
just like strictly between two individuals,
personal shit, small potatoes, shit,
that's like, that's awful.
Yeah, that's so bad.
I could never hear about it
and it wouldn't affect anything.
Yeah.
And that's, if there's like, oh, you could see
the story being told turned into like a real documentary
that would.
You gotta convince me right off the bat
that this person is out, like, is victimizing people.
If you're leading with like,
he was a mod in my Discord server
and he did not behave appropriately
in terms of the role.
He made, he deleted roles that I liked
and he banned people that I didn't want banned
and it's like, shut the fuck, I don't, nobody cares.
I like commentary, but only the,
not the reaction commentators,
which are like the gameplay commentators
or tea channels.
I just like find some random ass tweet
and just run with it.
I prefer, I think the best commentary
are people that actually take time
and they don't have to care about the topic,
but like put actual effort.
Everything else, it kind of sucks.
Not how I think about it.
I have watched a couple of the right opinion videos before.
He's pretty good.
I thought they were pretty okay.
A lot of people call me boring, but I can say that.
I often find.
I don't have much to compare him to.
Commentary channels.
It's like the, it just feels like,
what if you made a YouTube comment, but it was a video?
And I'm like, ah, you know,
I don't really want to listen to a YouTube comment.
Like it, the commentary as a,
like a community or like a genre of video,
it feels like there's not a lot of meat.
There's not a lot of things you can really do with that.
It's entirely dependent on how interesting
the thing you're reacting to is.
And in that same vein, I often feel like
they're, they're like equivalent to
YouTube channels or like, like Facebook groups that like
put a, but like, here's the viral clip of the week.
Here's the viral video that's really funny.
Here you go.
And they're like barely doing anything.
They're just pointing your attention towards a thing
that is entertaining on its own.
And you could just go and see that thing.
A lot of, like a lot of like podcasts or even like, you know,
it's less like, not calling you guys up by the way,
but it's just like, like, it's just like, like, you know,
or not even podcasts, just like every YouTube video.
It's just thing of thing, like story time.
Hey, here's my story of the week.
It could be the most boring shit ever,
but here's my story of the week, you know?
No matter what medium you're in,
I feel like you can, you can make it as entertaining
as you put into it or like as engaging as you put into it.
I'm not sure.
I think a lot of YouTube is that in various ways.
I mean, a lot of videos about things
that aren't made by like smart people are just,
here's a Wikipedia article turned into a video for you.
Hey, that's me.
It's like, that's a lot of those things.
I'm like, hey, I guess it's interesting,
but like nothing new is being created.
It's all just redirecting your attention
towards things that have already been done,
already been seen, already been made.
Yeah.
I mean, the podcast thing is like, it's true.
We just do talk about whatever.
But I just think that like for every medium,
it's just what you put into it.
Cause you could just write like a,
you could just like,
if you want to do like a story time video,
you could just like make a blog,
but the medium of video makes it so much like more engaging
and you know, just so much more like entertaining
rather than having someone just read,
you know, your blog or your book or whatever.
And I feel like a lot of times people just miss out on that
by creating very non-interesting like,
you know, like, like video, you know?
And I do agree, you know?
Uh, uh, what, huh?
Like a story time.
I mean, a story is like, like art.
Like, uh, like a video game or a movie or whatever.
That's a story.
Joel Haver makes short films.
Yeah.
I love those videos.
They're just like a little story told.
Well, usually very funny.
And that's the sort of content I like.
But when it's, when it's somebody just doing a vlog
for like watch time or engagement,
there's not a lot to it.
I will say that, um, like if you put a lot of effort
into telling a small little story,
often stories are not like made for people like me
because I'm old now.
It's for young youngsters,
like YouTube animators, story time people.
Yeah.
They make very engaging animated little stories about,
oh, this is a thing that's relatable to you.
And they're all like, oh, he is.
Oh.
I've been to school once.
Literally me.
And it's like, okay, I don't care for it myself,
but like, that's all right.
Don't mind those.
Why?
They're making something.
They're telling all,
they're gathering people around the campfire.
I guess, I guess that's what commentary.
I hate this conversation we're having.
God, I'm so fucking bored.
Shut up.
Oh my God.
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
Let's discuss the important stuff.
The moral background of commentary.
No.
Let's go back.
I'll kill you.
I'll fucking kill you.
Let's talk about, you know, Trixie.
She moves.
Riley, he produces.
What?
You know.
What does Riley produce?
Nothing.
He just produces.
I mean, true.
Yeah, he just, he produces whatever that means.
Whatever that needs to mean at the time.
No, I don't want to talk about that.
I don't care.
Let's, the fucking,
well, hey, do you guys see the news?
Oh God.
What?
No, what?
I was going to ask you how your game's going.
Fuck you.
It's like compared to like.
My game, Phantom's Revenge, I'm back,
I finished the Lord of Ghost comic.
Yes.
I'm back on the grind for the Phantom's Revenge game
development numbers is good.
What did I do?
I fixed a bunch of visual, but yes, two days ago,
I fixed a bunch of visual bugs.
Yesterday, I was like completing a bunch of commands
and making a bunch.
I have successfully implemented the dab command.
Oh my God.
Phantom Warren can now dab in the game.
Sick.
So I, yeah, yeah.
What else?
I fixed a glitch with the screen,
the screen shake when you take damage.
Yeah, I'm on it.
I'm focused.
It's going good actually.
And I showed, I said I wasn't going to do this.
I actually like kind of betrayed myself a little bit.
I showed myself playing a bit of the game on the stream
on the Shackles for Heckles we did yesterday.
I showed more than I had meant to show actually publicly,
but fuck it, it's fine.
So if you want to go listen to that stream we did yesterday,
you might, and you're interested,
you might find some secret knowledge
about my video game in there.
No, I have two questions for you.
Number one, are you going to sign an exclusivity deal
with Epic Game Store and release all the way on there?
Absolutely.
Well, yeah, NFTs will be incorporated into the game.
You will have to buy real life NFTs
in order to progress.
Jesus Christ.
Only people with an NFT can get in and play the game.
Otherwise she dies only.
What's your game about?
I wasn't here for that arc, what's your game about?
What's it about?
It is the, well, it's the conclusion
of my comic Slime and Punishment
and it is called Phantom's Revenge.
And it features Phantom Horn, the unicorn, fighting enemies.
And I think that's all I'm going to say here about it.
That is.
If you watch the sample I showed in the stream,
actually gives away a bit more of the context
that I had not publicly talked about it before.
So the second question I was going to ask you is,
I didn't actually know you were making a game.
What genre is it?
I don't talk about it that much.
What is the, what is it?
Oh, I asked what genre it was.
Is it action, platformer?
It's a, I would say it's a turn-based like JRPG.
Oh, sick.
But it's with sort of a,
most strictly speaking, yeah,
it's a turn-based menu-based JRPG,
but it sort of has the vibe
of like a side-scrolling beat-em-up where you go,
where basically you just, you go like from left to right,
from room to room and you, you know, you clear enemies out.
Yeah, there's no like overworld, there's not RPG maker.
It's a unique little thing.
It's a linear, it's a linear,
it's a beat-em-up that you do with menu commands, basically.
Yeah, it's a strategy.
I put the demo out on my Patreon a few months ago,
and it was really hard.
It was really hard.
Very, very few people were able to beat it.
So the final release will not be,
I'm good, I'm making some changes
to make it a little bit more forgiving.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, you got,
no, you don't understand.
You should make like an insane mode.
You gotta make it grind people's testicles
or their titties, you know?
Honestly, I could make an insane,
if I made the insane mode.
That'd be sick.
Yeah, you get a funny achievement for it.
Yeah, if I made an insane mode that took out the ability
to like rest between rooms or whatever that would be,
because the demo, if you beat one room,
you had to immediately go to the next.
In the final game, you're gonna be able
to like prepare between rooms a little bit.
Yeah, you should just insane mode,
just what is called boss rush.
Boss rush, there's not many bosses in it.
So what is the process been like of making a game?
Because I've never really-
I don't know, you fucking open Game Maker
and you go tick, tick, tick, tick, tick,
and you put things in parentheses
and you put in semicolons, and it just fucking works.
All right, speaking of video games,
I found something absolutely magical today.
Well, found is the wrong word, but it was linked to me
and I'm already in love looking at this.
Sonic Robo Blast 2 Persona Edition.
What?
Where?
What does that mean?
What?
It is a fan-made Persona game with Sonic characters
and Sonic levels.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
I just, oh, I should put it in links, I'm my bad.
Now I get it, now I understand.
Yeah, it-
Why does this actually kinda look good?
That's what I'm saying, it looks actually very good.
It does, this actually looks really cool.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
Holy shit.
It apparently supports four teams of four players
so you could play with 15 other friends.
I mean, who has 15 friends, but, you know.
I don't know.
I was knowing 15 Sonic characters.
There are?
I really like this a lot, actually.
Yeah, okay.
You guys like Sonic?
Yeah.
No.
No?
Why'd they like it?
I've never played a Sonic game.
Damn.
I see how it is.
Yeah, I see what you like.
It's one of those series that has just been around
but I've never really played.
I think I had Shadow the Hedgehog
was the only Sonic game I had as a kid.
What games did you guys grow up on?
I played a bunch, I played a,
I mean, my favorite games as a kid were like,
were SNES RPGs, like Mario RPG and Secret of Mana and.
Yo, Mario RPG, that's a good game.
I respect that.
That's, yeah, that's probably my childhood fave
was Mario RPG.
What about you, Gib?
I was in PS1 for a bit and then PS2 mostly
is a wretched and clank, Jack and Dexter.
Hell yeah.
Tomb Raider 1, Rayman.
Oh, did you play Crash?
I did, yes.
I didn't have Crash for some reason.
I never beat, I never beat Crash.
I never beat Crash.
Dude, Crash is so good.
I had a weird situation.
So I had a Nintendo 64 growing up
and then I got a PS2 a little later on.
But well, the weird part is I never got a GameCube
or a Wii for a very, very long time.
So I played like Ocarina of Time and I grew up on that.
But then I also grew up on Ratchet and Clank
because those are my favorite action RPGs.
The guns are just amazing.
It's so fun.
I wouldn't call Ratchet and Clank an action RPG.
You can level up the guns in two and three, so I guess.
Yeah, I would, I think that's a straight.
I mean, you have some RPG element.
It's an action, it's a 3D action.
Adventure game with RPG element.
It's a third person shooter platform.
Yeah, or if you played Deadlock, it's a arena shooter
slash RPG.
Oh, Ratchet fucking bread, Dread.
Ratchet Gladiator was called in the UK.
I love that shit.
Hell yeah, same.
I remember getting that for Christmas
and I played it like after I'd opened the presents.
I had it and I just played the whole entire game.
And then it was dark.
I remember, so I didn't have an internet
at my house at the time and there was always
a big sticker on the box that says play online
with PlayStation.
And there was one time me and my family
were staying at a hotel somewhere
and I actually hooked it up to the PS2
and got to play online for the first time
and it was really fun.
That is like a-
You can never figure out, what do you need to do
to get a PlayStation 2 to be online?
I thought you needed a funny adapter thing.
Yeah, you did need, I think, I remember
we had to buy some kind of adapter
to play Ratchet and Clank Arena online.
God, that shit was so fun.
It was.
That was awesome.
Wait, so were you guys Nintendo kids at all?
I had no, I switched from the Super Nintendo
to the PlayStation because I wanted to play Final Fantasy 7.
So I started with Nintendo and then switched to Sony
when PlayStation came out.
I mean, I had the consoles was always Sony.
And then I had a Game Boy Advance SP
and then a DS Lite.
No, I didn't have a DS Lite.
I had, I started, I was borrowing my brother's DS lights
and then I got like a DSi XL and then a 3DS.
So I was like portable Nintendo,
like Phoenix Wright and shit.
Oh yeah, I still had, I still had GBA
and I think I got the S.
Was it the SD after the GBA?
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
No, wait.
Yeah, so I continued to be a Nintendo portable kid.
The same.
Advance, I think?
Yeah.
I only got the-
No, after Advance.
I definitely had the Advance and was it the SP after the SP?
Yeah, yeah, it was the SP.
The one, the silver one with the flip up screen.
Yes, yes, yes.
I remember fucking, I only cared about the Game Boy and DS.
Like I had to have them exclusively for Pokemon
and no other reason.
Were you guys play Pokemon?
I know a bunch of people that didn't and it's like-
That's funny.
It's so weird.
We have been criticized for talking too much
about Pokemon on this channel.
I mean, it's been a while.
Let's talk about Pokemon.
Yeah, I played red and then I played,
no, I played blue and then I played silver
and then I skipped gen three and then I played pearl
and then I played, was it, was it,
was black and white after pearl and diamonds?
Yeah.
Well, there was black one, but yeah.
I played black.
No, I bounced off black and then I didn't play
another one for a while.
Yeah, I played a bunch, played a bunch of Pokemon.
I have played blue and then I had Sapphire
and that's like my big nostalgia one.
And then I didn't care much for other stuff
because I think it was like, I was used to it being
like pixelated little drawings
and then they started experimenting
with having three dimensional buildings and stuff.
And I'm like, that's fucked.
That's incorrect.
You thought that was fucked?
They're ruining my game.
Wait until, just you wait, you didn't know,
young Gabe didn't know just how fucked
things were gonna get.
I had a little gamer moment where I was like,
no, things on the GBA, they look great.
Fire Emblem, right?
Fire Emblem seven and eight, perfect looking games,
incredible, great little sprite animations
on all the little people.
Then GameCube, Fire Emblem comes out, looks like shit
because it's like low poly 3D renders,
no good animation at all.
And I was seeing that as well with other games.
It was like, 3D versions of once two dimensional properties.
These fucking 3D Pokemon houses, this Pokemon center,
looks like crap.
I hate it.
And then I didn't play Pokemon at all until Pokemon Moon.
I thought the limited 3D stuff looked pretty good
It does look good.
I was just like an ancient for a reason.
And then like, was it in, was it,
yeah, like fourth and fifth gen had some 3D house and stuff.
Some pseudo 3D stuff and then actual 3D.
And they looked really good.
Yeah, they looked good.
And then they fucked it all up.
And then they fucked it all up, believe me.
I did enjoy playing Pokemon Moon.
If a little 3D looks good,
everything would look good in 3D.
Now, Sun and Moon suck, Sun and Moon are shit, honestly.
Yeah, Sun and X, Y, Sun and Moon.
Sun and Moon have gotten worse over time.
All right, yeah.
Well, I like the music from them.
I still listen to those.
Yeah, every Pokemon game has good music.
Yeah, I wouldn't play it again, God, no.
But like it had the team skull, that was epic.
Here's the hot take of this episode.
And the characters were cool.
The 3D stuff and starting with gen six,
I don't think it was bad.
I liked the new designs.
I liked the quirky way the world looked.
I just hated the fact that the DS
couldn't handle double battles in 3D.
So it lagged, like even the 3DS.
Like if you play Sun and Moon,
especially the re-release of them, Ultra Sun, Ultra Moon,
and you get into a double battle,
oh my God, the frame rate drops
to 10 frames a second sometimes.
And the battles just go by so slow because they're lagging.
I had the new 3DS too, which was the upgraded one.
The one that's supposed to be more powerful
and it was just lagging so bad.
Like 3D was okay, but not for a console
that couldn't handle it.
I remember when he fucked me up sometimes.
I think the move to 3D was just bad in every way.
It looks worse and it plays worse.
You know, like I did it for black and white.
Like they should have done like what Sonic,
like Sonic Persona did and have 2D sprites walking around
in a big 3D world.
That would have been badass.
Honestly, maybe it would have worked, I don't know.
It would have been a bold decision though,
considering how like every other game company was doing.
But it would definitely make them stand out.
And Pokemon was already so big at the time,
and then it didn't matter.
It's like no matter what happened,
people would have bought it, you know?
Yeah, fuck the crew.
It's still true today, haha.
Yeah, it's true, it's true.
It really fucked me up that sometimes like a game
built for a console cannot run well on that console.
Yeah.
Like there was a moment in Professor Layton
versus Phoenix Wright on DS, which is a 3DS,
which is a game I really like,
but there's like this one core section.
I can't remember your review of it.
Where there's like a bunch of characters on screen,
cause it's like they interview like a group
of some or of knights or something.
And you know, they're all wacky and cool models,
but because of there being so many fucking vertices
and points on screen at once,
the fucking DS 3DS can't handle it and it lags
and it just ruins like the game.
That's just the way the game is.
You can't play, you can emulate it.
Nice.
But like it was built for that and it just doesn't run.
How do they cool?
How do they sleep at night knowing that they made a video game
that wasn't quite up to standard?
That's a great question.
Nobody knows.
That's why everybody gets mad at Pokemon
because oh, you guys rake in millions of dollars,
but you can't optimize your games properly.
What the fuck?
Yeah.
No, I can think that I can.
Sad, but true.
I feel like there's like an interesting
like secretive documentary on like why Pokemon is just bad?
Cause it's like it doesn't make any sense
why they just don't do it right.
You know, you go, you get a guy on the inside.
They just don't give a fuck.
They sneak around the office.
They get private conversations of like the developers
at Game Freak being like, ha, ha, ha,
I don't care about what I'm doing.
Ha, ha, ha.
And then it was like, oh my God, what a scoop.
Yeah.
True though, true though.
Um, okay.
All right, I don't care.
I don't care about Pokemon.
I don't care about anything.
This doesn't, this don't matter.
You care about Yu-Gi-Oh. None of this matters.
I don't.
I don't like Yu-Gi-Oh.
Did you guys see, all right.
This week on YouTube.
What?
What, they're still making Yu-Gi-Oh?
Yeah, I did.
Stop.
Like cards or the show?
Both, all the above.
Cards, video games, everything.
I'm just kidding, I know,
I know that they're still doing that.
I wish they wouldn't.
Actually, no, I don't.
I stopped giving a shit after.
I don't actually mind it, it's fine, it's fine.
I wanted to say, this week on YouTube,
with two monumental videos dropped on YouTube this week.
One of which I expected and was anticipated.
The other, which was a total surprise.
Do you guys know what I'm talking about?
Probably not.
No clue.
Okay.
Well, the one I was expecting
was the new Tim Rogers action button review
of Cyberpunk 2077.
After like, what's it been like 10 months
since the Tokimeki Memorial review,
the new action button dropped.
And it is a sprawling epic
that was so big that it had to be split into like,
it had to be split into like seven videos.
Holy shit.
For some reason, it's, I don't know, it's good.
How long are all the videos?
Honestly, I don't even have that much to say about it.
It's an action button, it's good, huh?
How long are all the videos?
They vary, some of them are,
he started out making them maybe like two hours or so,
but they like, they got longer longer.
I think the Tokimeki Memorial one is like five hours long.
And this one is probably like nine or 10 hours
all total or something.
I don't know, action button is weird
because it's really not even about the game.
It's basically just, I mean, he does talk about the game,
but he also just like rambles about himself
and random shit a lot.
And probably some people would find that annoying,
which is fine.
That's valid.
Yeah.
Let's talk about something, you know,
not too spicy here, politics.
No, I wanted, fuck, no, my other video,
I said there were two videos.
Oh, shit, I'm sorry.
Another big video that I need to recommend,
that I need to recommend.
I want everyone to go and watch,
yeah, the new, the new Yan Misali video.
Did you see this?
What was that?
Yan Misali is a guy, he does, he's a conlanger.
He like made video reviews,
where he reviewed constructed languages,
stuff like Esperanto, and he would review them
and be like, how good is it as a language?
How shit is it as a language?
What's wrong with it?
How could it be better?
And then he was moderately successful doing that,
and then he recently branched
into doing more like YouTube-y stuff.
He did a big iceberg video about the Rhythm Heaven series.
He did a video exploring how many,
how many Mario games are like,
are considered part of the mainline Mario series,
and which ones are they?
That one's pretty interesting.
And his new one, which is Who Made Caramel Dancin,
is a masterpiece.
Oh, I saw that.
That was a great one.
It's so good.
Wait, who's this guy?
His name is Yan Misali, that's J-A-N,
and then space M-I-S-A-L-I.
And there's so much to the story of Caramel Dancin
that I just didn't know.
Who would have thought?
But it's true.
Yeah, it's weird.
I found the Caramella Girls just randomly,
and I was like, oh, I guess they made it.
I guess this is what they're unable to do with YouTube channel,
and I would have been fooled.
You would think so.
Yeah, it's a whole, yeah, a bit of a spoiler,
but it's a whole, yeah, the band,
that pretends to be responsible for Caramel Dancin
is just like a later invention
by the record label that owned the song,
and just is out here sitting on a throne of lies.
Amazing, it's amazing.
Yeah, great, that was a great video,
and I just wanted to fucking, oh, oh, oh, but yeah,
but in that video, he explained,
oh, this ties into the Trixie thing,
the Who Are These podcast,
because in The Who Are These podcast,
they make fun of me.
They rightfully make fun of me
for not knowing the lyrics to,
or the name, in fact, of a, fuck, what song was it?
Blitzkrieg, boop, Blitzkrieg bop.
I didn't know the lyrics to Blitzkrieg bop,
and I interpreted them as let's get fucked,
which is a phenomenon that I learned from that video,
from that Yan Misli video, it's called Mondegreen,
or in Japanese, Sora Mimi,
the practice of interpreting another song
in a different language in your own language,
just based on mishearing the words.
So yeah, I Mondegreened, Blitzkrieg, boop,
so it wasn't, it's not an L, it's not an L.
I was doing a Mondegreen, actually, it was W.
Yeah, yeah, so.
Wait, do you know what the actual lyric is?
Or probably not.
Yeah, it's Blitzkrieg, swedish.
Oh, okay, now I know.
Oh, you mean Blitzkrieg, boop, I don't know.
Some sort of words.
Cause, I-
Blitzkrieg, boop.
Wait, Blitzkrieg, boop, let's get fucked, okay.
Sorry, sorry, it just sounds like that to me.
And that's valid, and no one can take that away from me.
I just, yeah, when he said the Mondegreen thing,
I was like, oh, just like me and Blitzkrieg, boop.
Relatable, this is literally me right now.
Huh?
There's like a Reddit thread dedicated to
let's get fucked, bitch, Blitzkrieg, boop.
Excuse me?
Yeah.
So I'm not the only one.
No.
No, you're good.
Excuse me, did you just bring up Reddit?
Read.
Oh, fuck.
I mean, I'm in 4chan, I'm in 4chan,
I'm in 4chan.
Disavow, disavow, double disavow.
No, link me, link me the thread about,
link me the thread.
It's not a thread about it, it's about what song
you've been miss hearing, but there's like
three people talking about Blitzkrieg, boop.
That's, that's great.
Speaking of, how long am I gonna con, blitz?
Speaking of threads, yeah, I always,
seven years ago, Jetsetter underscore says,
I always thought that Blitzkrieg, boop was let's get fucked.
Some friends pointed out my idiocy just a few weeks ago.
Same, except for me, it was my mortal enemy
that pointed it out, cool.
This reminds me.
Oh, I love that, I love that.
Given Ben.
Okay, amazing.
Mon de Green, think about it.
How big of a fan are you two of Kingdom Hearts?
I played one and two, and chain of memories.
So I used to be kind of a fan.
I played one and two sort of recently
for YouTube videos that I made on the first one.
I never made the second one,
but I enjoyed them a fair amount, they're pretty good.
Okay, this is-
I think I played the third game as well
because that was hype, I just felt like it.
Okay, okay, so you two will very much appreciate this.
I'll post in the links.
I was linked this thread as it was happening
and this is the funniest thing I've ever seen
come from 4chan.
Yeah, click it and read it real quick.
In the reply, where is it?
I posted in the links.
Oh, indeed, I request a large cheese pizza,
plain of, cheese pie of pizza, plain of course.
Us nothing's required, nothing on our meals.
A side beverage of a Dr. Pepper.
Wait, we gotta post the image.
The image needs to go along with this.
Here we go.
So here's the image, and yeah.
Indeed, I request a large cheese pie of pizza,
plain of course, us nothing's require,
nothing on our meals.
A side beverage of a Dr. Pepper.
The ideal drink between drinks.
Oh, and how foolish of me.
Do not forget the garlic knots.
I will be waiting to pay in cash.
Please alert your courier to knock three times
at the door of Castle Oblivion,
so we are aware of his presence.
And it just keeps-
I shifted into Xemnas mode.
It just keeps going.
Oh, and then they just RP in character
for the whole thread.
The Sora ones are the funny ones.
Don't you remember Xemnas?
The savory, tasty, greasy cheese.
The sour feeling of tomato toppings.
If that's my favorite one,
there's a picture of salad in it and it's like too late.
I'm already going half and half.
Okay, all right, this is pretty good.
It goes on for so long too.
It just keeps-
Oh my God.
Yeah, it just keeps going.
I see Woody from Toy Story.
There he is.
Wait, wait, wait, I got this one.
I want to read this one.
I'm posting the image here.
Pizzas quivering with cheese.
Pizzas burning with pepperoni.
Pizzas scarred by anchovies.
That fool Ansem said the pizza's true nature
was beyond his understanding,
but it's not beyond mine.
Pizzas are the source of all power.
He's ascended.
All right, all right, all right.
Good thread, good thread.
Behold, these dried toppings used to be full of flavor,
united with the taste of their customers.
And this barren kitchen key cards of crepitant debt
of what were locked in combat
has a great three-for-one special rage.
Countless customers emptied their wallets
in search of one ultimate taste.
And soon it will belong to me, the X-Car.
Do you-
The idea of a key card instead of a key blade.
Dude, how many, dude, can you churn,
can you churn key blade cards?
What's the cashback rate on that key blade, bro?
Like what's the sign-up bonus like on that key chain?
Big card blade.
Dude, I'm churning chains, bro.
I'm chaining memories, bro.
And ironically, like a giant credit card
would make more sense as a blade than a key.
That would be sick, though.
It's time for me, it's time for me
to start workshopping my new manga series,
which is a shonen action about people battling
with giant credit cards and comparing,
like, who can get the best bargains?
Yo!
Who can do the best combos to get the most cashback
on their purchase, on their Christmas gift shopping?
Oh my god.
Yeah, money equates to power in that shonen universe.
Yo, when is this gonna come out?
Just like, just like, just like the conclusion,
just like the conclusion to Road to Radcon.
Literally, that's the final beat of Road to Radcon.
Not spoiler, I won't go in any more detail.
Literally, just like the dramatic conclusion
of Road to Radcon.
Check my pinned tweet on Twitter, it's also ugly.
Buy a copy, please.
I have 55 copies left in a box.
Please buy them from me, please.
We're gonna buy them, I'll get rid of them.
We're gonna buy them.
If you check my Twitter, like I said,
my pinned tweet on Twitter, it's also ugly,
has buying instructions.
It basically just tells you how much money it is
and where to pay pallet to me.
And then you can just DM me on Twitter
and I will say, okay, I will send it to you.
I'm doing this very DIY, like out the fucking back
of my car kind of thing.
I'll buy one and everyone who's listening
should buy one too.
No matter how many are left, everyone should buy one.
Everyone should just cop a quick one,
even if you already have one, you know?
Please, I have to move product.
I paid for these books out of my own pocket.
Help me.
You know what I say, having two of everything
doesn't hurt, you know?
Buy two, I would highly recommend buying two copies.
So you can do a wheel.
Maybe buy three.
You can put one, you can buy two
and then you could put one, like leave it mint.
So for future generations, you could sell it at a markup.
It's like a physical NFT.
I was horrified.
I came in, it was raining so hard yesterday.
It was pouring.
I was walking home with my umbrella.
My legs got soaked, but I was walking home
and I walked in my house and I closed my umbrella,
but I shook my umbrella out and it threw water droplets
all over my room and I realized to my horror
that several droplets of water had fallen into the open box
where the copies of Road to Radcon lie fallow,
waiting, just waiting to be given a good home.
And I was like, no, water damage.
And I pulled out the two top copies
that were sitting on top and I brushed them off
and I tried, I dried them and I was like, no, no.
They're gonna pockmark the cover.
They're gonna get little divots on them.
And it looked like it was true.
It looked like they had swelled up a little bit.
I was like, no, now I can't sell these.
Now I'll have to give these away as business gifts
to idiots that I find.
But then I left them, I have to give these to homeless people
on the street to wipe their asses with this.
But I just put them down and I let them dry off
and I checked them about an hour later
and they had dried off and they were no longer,
they had unswelled, they were no longer
noticeably damaged at all.
So I was like, few, saved.
Well, thank God, I don't want to get to homeless people now.
Oh, God, that was almost bad.
So back in the box.
And they're yearning for it.
They think, well, they better pay up then.
They don't, you don't understand.
These books ain't cheap, kid.
You don't understand how much homeless people
love the PCP podcast.
It's like a cultural icon.
They're our target demographic.
Yeah, target demographic.
We're aspirational to them.
They love it, but they can't access it
because their phone ran out of battery.
Every time that they listen to it,
they're just imagining what it would be like.
It's homeless people with dead batteries
who haven't checked the podcast in a year
coming back in the comments.
It's that one or two guys in the comments
every time being like,
just checking back to see if Nate's on the podcast again.
Like it's because they've been living
on the street this whole time
and they haven't found a starbucks to plug their phone into.
They have to go to a public library
to check in on you guys over a few months, you know?
That's right, that's right.
You should do a book signing at homeless shelters.
Would it be controversial to bring up Nate's new show?
Gamer's Zone?
No, we mentioned it.
You mean the Gamer's Zone?
Yeah.
It's not that new.
Okay, Worst PCP.
I have actually listened to like a full one.
I glanced at it, I skipped around.
I was like, okay, yeah, they're talking about
like hot button issues of, or maybe they aren't.
Well, okay, goodbye.
It wasn't that.
It was kind of like a PCP.
I assume they talk about video games.
I assume it's, I mean, it's like the PCP
and that it's a people talking
and one of the members is the same.
Yeah, exactly.
Is it real?
Yeah, I mean, I guess, what else?
I mean, we invented that concept.
Absolutely, we invented podcasts as a concept.
Well, I mean, wasn't the concept behind the PCP,
Nate's gonna get his friends together to run a show
and now Nate's getting his friends together
to run a new show?
No.
What are you talking about?
The concept behind the PCP was Nate's gonna get his friends.
Like what, where do you get that idea?
I have seen that idea.
That's a little genuinely offensive in the same way
that like, oh, PCP podcast is Digi Bro's anime podcast,
but actually worse.
Listen, I've heard that take so many times
in just the general PCP community.
I mean, I didn't do research, I didn't fight it.
I've just seen a lot of people say it.
I have never heard that and I, and they,
and I whoever thinks that better be glad
I never heard them say that shit before.
Let it deranged, literally deranged.
What were we talking about?
He's gonna track down the homeless people.
Oh yeah.
That's claimed though.
Oh yeah, I have more pizza things to read.
This is in the Mickey Mouse voice.
Say, fellas, did somebody mention the door to Domino's?
That's actually a pretty good Mickey voice.
Say, fellas, did someone mention the two for one special?
It sounds like a South Park version of Mickey.
Actually, it's a pretty solid Mickey impression.
It's better than I could do.
Geez, it's been Mickey Mouse.
Oh, wow.
We gotta kill the darkness or whatever, Sora.
I have another thing that happened this week.
You guys know the Drawcast podcast?
Yeah.
Yeah, not ours, the new one.
The one with the C-Tool in them, right?
Oblivionful. Yeah.
What did you say, Pyro?
I said the one with C-Tool, Oblivion,
and I think Teleparte is on a few.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
Well, I'm on a one that is coming up soon.
It's the draw, it's Telephone.
The idea being like there's a prompt
and then someone draws it
and then they show their drawing
to the next person for like a minute
and that person has to try to like remember it
and then like recreate it
and then they show it to the next person for a minute
and they have to remember it and try to re...
Yeah, yeah, like the game, Telephone.
Yeah, Drawcast Telephone.
So I had mine, I had my turn this week
and the next person after me in line was Teleparte.
So I had to get in a call with him
and show him the, you know, my thing for him to copy.
And it was very annoying
because my Discord stream like fucked up.
Like I put two minutes on the, okay, well, first.
First, he asked me like, hey, when can we do it?
And I was like, we can do it this afternoon,
I'll be around.
And then a like emergency situation
with my landlord came up
and I suddenly had to like run to the bank to pay rent
and then run to the post office to send rent.
So that was, by the way, by the way, side note,
my landlord is attempting to ask me to pay a late fee
on rent, which is illegal in Massachusetts.
It is illegal to ask your tenant to pay a late fee
on rent that is less than 30 days late.
And I was not 30 days late.
So she is simply breaking the law.
And if she asks me again, we may have to go to court over it.
And I will win because the law is unambiguous.
But so that's fun.
So my shitty landlord is fucking,
is fucking trying to do crimes against me.
So I'm out, so I had to run to the bank and all that.
And then I see on my phone that like Teleparte an hour ago
was like, hey, you're ready to do it?
Hey, let me know when you're ready.
Get back to me, whatever you see this.
And I'm like, shit, fuck, I said I would be around.
So I tell him like, oops, sorry, landlord emergency.
And then I come back and I'm like, okay,
it's like two hours later, but I'm like, okay, I'm ready.
And then I get on the thing and I open up my stream
and I show it to him and my stream is like fucking up.
I'm like sharing the window that my drawing is in.
And it's all like, it's like glitching and jerking
and like flashing around.
And I'm like, I don't know why it's doing that.
So I have to like stop that, stop sharing that
and then just start sharing my whole screen,
which partly shows the image.
And it's doing that thing where like,
you move your cursor around
and like it remembers where your cursor was been
and like the cursor stays on the screen,
like flashing and like a trail.
Yeah, it's doing that.
And I don't know why, I'm just telling it share my screen.
So, and this is like, I have two minutes,
he has two minutes to look at the thing
and it's all like glitching out and flashing around
and like the cursor is fucking up
and like marring the image.
I'm sure it was very distracting.
So that was kind of a shit show, but whatever.
I mean, two whole minutes,
how long does it take to fucking look at a thing
and know what it looks like?
So I'm sure it was fine.
Are shows like that difficult?
Two whole minutes to try to remember.
I would assume that'd be really difficult, right?
You were allowed to like take notes.
You're not allowed to like sketch it,
but you were allowed to like take notes
in that two minutes about what it looks like.
For me, it was pretty, you weren't on that.
Oh wait, nice.
I was, I was earlier in the train.
No, you were, you were, I saw your drawing.
Well, the person that called me on the discord
and said, hey, it's your turn to look at mine,
that person told me explicitly, you are allowed to take notes.
Okay, I guess at some point somebody decided,
Oh, can I take notes?
And someone was like, yeah, I guess so.
Even the rules, even the rules of telephone
are like changed like in between.
They're getting telephoned.
Yeah, they are getting telephoned.
That's kind of funny.
Lamal.
So it's not, okay.
Okay, that makes a lot more sense that you can take notes
because I'm not an artist at all.
But if I had to do that,
I would probably be stressing out about the little like.
I kind of think.
I think it wasn't that bad.
I think two minutes was too long.
I think two minutes is too long.
I had one minute and I think it was, it was like, yeah.
Why did they change the rules?
It did telephone.
Don't worry about it.
I had like one minute and I was looking at it.
I'm like, okay, humanoid with this, that,
what color is the hair?
What color is the thing?
What color is that?
Oh wait, no, I didn't have color
because the person who went before me
did theirs in black and white.
Yeah.
So I had to come up with colors.
They told me what the colors were,
but they didn't tell me where they were.
So my-
I feel like that's cheating.
I feel like that's cheating that they told you that.
I mean, I move the colors into various places.
Tell a perte, look, I mean, I'm not trying to judge,
but like that's definitely cheating
for you to ask for like additional information
than what's in the drawing.
I mean, that's what oblivion is for.
It's obviously, like it's definitely not
in the spirit of the game to be like,
hey, tell me more about the images.
I didn't ask for information.
They just said, oh, like, oh, whoops,
I drew in black and white.
What should I do?
An oblivion fool said, oh, you can just tell them
the general colors.
Stupid.
Well, I looked, okay, the person that went before me,
I looked at all the images in the chain,
and the person that went before me
took some weird liberties with it
in a way that I found kind of annoying.
Like, it seemed like they like sort of deliberately
tried to differentiate themselves
by just like adding a bunch of shit.
Wait, Ben, did you look at all
of the different ones previously?
Well, no, after I finished mine,
I went back and I looked at them.
Oh, after, yeah, I guess that's fair.
That's fine.
Yeah, the person before me, I don't know,
they like, you know, they drew the figure,
they tried to recreate the figure,
but like, they put it like floating in a void.
They put it like underwater, which was like,
Like what was the thing you were supposed to draw?
It was a girl.
It was a girl, well, it doesn't matter.
It's a particular character.
But the point is, so this person who went before me
decided, you know, they looked at a picture
of this person, you know, just kind of standing there,
and decided that for their iteration of telephone,
they were going to draw them like floating underwater,
which is like, I don't know,
that doesn't seem right to me.
That seems like they are deliberately adding things
and changing it.
That isn't the spirit of the game
that you were supposed to attempt to recreate
the image that you were shown.
And the changes are merely from like,
your lack of remembering your,
Yeah, you can't replicate it perfectly, so.
Yes, yes, so I thought that was annoying.
But yeah.
I'm gonna be a wild card.
Teleperte, yeah, it's a little bit like,
ooh, I'm gonna be a little different though,
like, ooh, mine's a little,
I'm gonna fuck this up on purpose a little bit,
like, mm, just so that I stand out.
The, yeah, Teleperte was, he was like kind of mumbling.
He said like, he was asking me like,
oh, so what is this?
Is this like a such and such?
Is this a so and so?
And I said like, mm, I don't think I should opine
on what it is.
I don't think I should say anything
about what I was trying to draw.
I just think I should just let the image speak for itself.
He also, he said he liked it.
He said he was very complimentary of me,
so that was pretty cool.
Yeah.
That's it, that's my story.
Wait, so.
It was a great fun.
What's this?
Sorry, I'm so out of the loop with all this stuff,
but what's, what is this?
Like, what is this channel on?
I'm gonna kick, I'm gonna kick your ass.
I'm gonna fucking kick your ass, dude.
What channel is it?
Like what, the channel is just called DrawCast.
Yeah.
DrawCast is.
They stole the name from us.
They stole the name, because we were.
And the format.
We didn't protect our copyright.
We didn't strike them down.
You should, 100%.
No.
They're squatting on our I.C. wall.
Give them a copyright strike.
I should give them a fucking.
DMCA here.
He didn't get my stern talking to, I think we should.
Yeah.
I'm a very faintly bullet.
Is that what you said?
Bullet.
Yeah, I should give them a bullet.
Oh my God.
That's what, that's a normal thing
that people say, right?
Oh yeah, I know, yeah.
Yeah.
Good.
Oh, yeah, speaking of the DrawCast,
the Halloween one that I was on
has just released as of recording.
And that is where I invented
the scraggity-agity, the scarecrow.
It was like a, like, oh, draw a scarecrow character.
Wait, no, that was completely different.
That's completely different.
I'm thinking of a different DrawCast
on a different thing that is not related.
Well, I was on that DrawCast that is on the DrawCast.
The Halloween DrawCast right now
is not where I invented scraggity-agity.
That was the big booby-mummy-milker's
Halloween DrawCast that was out.
You've lost, you've lost your mind.
You've lost touch with reality.
It's confusing, because there's two different
DrawCasts Halloween-themed,
where I, one in which I invented a cool OC
and the other one in which I drew punk
and some other things.
Hmm, I can see how that would be confusing.
Are you talking about big, bitty scream?
Huh?
Like, in the thumbnail for the DrawCast,
it's just like scream, but with big bitties.
Oh, yeah, scream, but boob-boob-boobs, yeah.
Oh, right, yeah, that's a Oblivion Falls drawing.
I think.
Yes, that's the one I'm talking about.
Go watch it, link in description.
Ugh!
Wait, I have one other thing on my list
of things to talk about this week.
Crypto gas.
This week I discovered that crypto is, in fact, a scam.
It's bullshit, it will never take off.
Discover?
No one will ever use it.
Well, I already kinda knew,
but I was reaffirmed to me, like, this is dog shit
and it's simply nonsense and it doesn't make any fucking sense.
I was, I had, okay, last year,
I had been watching a financial advice channel
called Clear Value Tax, just for financial advice.
And the guy at one point, he mentioned an app called KuCoin
and he said he uses KuCoin and he said it,
do you know what this is?
I don't know what KuCoin is, yeah.
What, KuCoin is?
Really?
C-O-U coin?
No, K-U, K-U coin.
Oh, okay, okay.
So it's an app that you can buy crypto on it
and then you can invest in crypto,
but you can also do things like take your crypto
and you can put your crypto into trading bots
that will make trades for you
and it's a low-risk way of quote-unquote investing.
It's sort of like a different investing method.
It's like investment firms but bots.
Yeah, something like that.
So I tried it just to see what,
I put a couple hundred dollars in it
just to see what would happen.
I put it into a few different currency
and I tried running some bots.
It did actually make some returns
but it was so effort intensive.
I had to be doing work on it every day
to be making these returns and I was like,
this is kinda, I'm not sticking with it, I don't think.
So I left it alone for a while
and then recently I'm not using that shit anymore.
I just wanna pull the money out.
So it was a nightmare to pull it out
because you can't just directly withdraw your money
from KuCoin.
You have to send it to a wallet.
I still have, you have to send it to a wallet
and then depending on the wallet,
you can maybe withdraw through that.
So what I should have done was just,
so I had to create a wallet
and then what I should have done
was send it to my Coinbase wallet
and then I could have maybe withdrawn it through Coinbase.
But instead Coinbase told me,
don't send it to Coinbase, use our app
which is called Coinbase Wallet.
Not the same as just a wallet on Coinbase.
Coinbase Wallet is a separate wallet.
So I sent it to Coinbase Wallet
and I also cannot withdraw it from Coinbase Wallet
and I'm like, okay, great.
I had to pay a fee for all three kinds of,
I had USD, UST and Bitcoin
and I had to pay $30 for each transfer
from each of those currencies to the wallet.
I'm like, okay, great.
And so now I have it in the wallet
and now I'm like, I wanna withdraw and I can't.
And I'm like, it's like, okay, no, no, no, to withdraw,
you have to send it from Coinbase Wallet
to the wallet on Coinbase.
And I'm like, all right, fine.
And so I tried to do that
and the Bitcoin transfer is easy,
but the USD and the UST both tell me
that it will be $100 to transfer like $70 worth of it
from Coinbase Wallet to Coinbase, the same website.
And I'm like, are you joking me?
And it turns out, and I complained about this on Twitter
and a couple people told me like, no, no, that's normal.
No, no, that's normal, that's gas.
That's what we call the gas fee.
It like pays for like the Ethereum blockchain mining
or something.
I'm like, oh, great.
Yeah, this is gonna take,
this is gonna take off for sure.
Yeah, everybody's gonna be doing this.
Everybody's gonna be paying for everything.
Paying like a hundred fucking dollars
to send less than a hundred dollars between wallets.
Like, oh, I'm glad we fucking have a decentralized currency
that everybody's gonna be using soon.
Get on this shit while it's hot.
So, I don't know, fucking...
Apparently if I wait, like the price fluctuates
and I might be able to find a day
where it maybe only costs me like $30 to send my $70
to my wallet that I can actually,
so like, I made modest returns on the money
that I put into KuCoin.
It has, all of that has been destroyed.
All of that has been taken and much more
simply by the act of me trying to get my money back out.
So, total dog shit, a complete scam,
a big pyramid scheme, and a few people get rich
and it is designed so that everybody else loses money
and pays into the system
and just doesn't get anything out of it.
It's for idiots, it's for idiots.
There's very few cryptocurrencies
that are actually worth investing in
and the ones that are are now like...
The only ones that, including the gas fee
that you can get actual profit on
are so expensive that it's not even worth your time.
It's...
I mean, I would have...
I mean, if I'd bought a bunch of Bitcoin a year ago,
it sure would be more valuable now.
The number sure did go up.
Like, investing in small cryptocurrency now,
especially when a lot of them don't have an audience.
Yeah, fucking...
Crypto idiots are always saying like,
oh, I invested in some new shit coins,
some new fucking coin.
Oh, did you see this one new coin?
Oh, it went from like a penny to like $100 overnight.
Oh, I could have made a million dollars.
Yeah, I...
Like, and all this stupid crap
is always happening all the time.
Some stupid new thing is always every week.
Some new shill is like, I have a new coin,
invested in my new coin.
They're all the same, they're all a scam.
They're all just, they're all a pyramid scheme
where the guy who makes it is gonna take the money and run.
And that's it.
That's all there is to it.
NFTs are so much worse though, like honestly.
NFTs are, I mean, they're all...
I guess they probably are worse.
They probably are worse.
Just like the amount of like,
hypebeasts and shills that there are.
Like, every single influencer has like an NFT
that they like support holds hardly
and it's like their profile picture on Twitter
and all that stuff and it's like, shut the fuck up.
Yeah.
All a scam, obviously.
All like a pump and dump,
like get people hype for this thing,
convince them it's gonna be worth a bunch of money,
get them to buy in and then cut and disappear.
That's why I'm so surprised whenever people believe
what influencers say on like, crypto.
It seems like such like a not,
you know, something you should never do.
I was reading Dan Olson's thread.
Dan Olson has a big thread on Twitter
where he was like, he was accepting invites
and do all kinds of like crypto discord servers
and just documenting them.
He has made a big spreadsheet documenting
like how they all were behaving and like,
it's all a bunch of like,
his story is that like, every one of these communities
is a bunch of people who sort of like,
pretend that they're there for a community.
But they're all actually just obviously there
because they think they can flip and make a profit
and they're all like delusional about it.
Like even after like the people that make it like,
cut and run and disappear from the server
and are obviously never coming back,
everybody kind of is just like, nah, we just gotta hold.
You know, this is just a temporary setback.
You know, this is all gonna be worth a lot of money one day,
but that's always the same.
Everyone's just massive characters in this entire thing.
Like in this entire like cryptocurrency.
Yeah, I actually, I feel a little cheated.
There was a YouTuber that launched Cluecoin,
COU coin, right?
CLU?
And I bought it, I bought it like the third hour was out.
So like I was one of the first investors.
I put $500 into it.
That $500 is now worth 14.
You know, yeah, like I know, obviously, obviously,
some people, there are some stories of people
who through some chance or maybe either through
the fact that like it was their plan all along
or through maybe through some random chance
made a bunch of money investing in crypto.
There are some sort of, but like, you know,
like the vast majority of people, you know,
for a few people to be getting rich off of this shit,
everybody else has to be losing money.
So most people are gonna end up exactly like that.
Ooh, I hates it, I hates it.
I mean, at least the good thing about NFTs is that when-
Is that it supports art?
No, it's that when somebody fucks up
and loses all their money and they go bankrupt,
they have a really funny image.
That it's like, it's funny to,
it's something to point and laugh at.
Crypto bros, like a text tweet of them being like,
oh no, I lost all my money is less funny
than a funny, like weird, gross looking ape saying
I lost all my money.
Did that have you like the only like copy
of Charlie bit my finger?
Instead of the fucking crypto shit,
NFT shit is a fucking nightmare, we can see live in hell.
Genuinely, like I thought,
man, I thought 2020 was bad.
I thought fucking coronavirus was bad
and was never going away,
but now NFTs are here and everybody's doing them.
And it seems like they're becoming,
like fucking Ubisoft is putting NFTs in their games,
they're gonna, they said they're gonna do.
This Adobe Photoshop is allowing you to make NFTs
from Photoshop.
Really?
Have you seen that?
The building functionality into Photoshop
so that you can like save as NFT.
Just fucking kill me already.
Just fucking end it.
I mean, that is kind of big brain on Adobe's part though.
Like it makes sense.
Well, I guess it makes sense.
Getting money from it,
I guess people will have to get Photoshop for it.
Yeah, I just like easier access,
but still that's like, it's just so brain dead.
But it's so weird,
because it was like from every conceivable angle,
it's stupid and yet everybody's getting on it.
I don't really understand.
I guess people just aren't aware,
but they aren't critical for some reason.
They're just going around just assuming it's perfect.
No, it's not that.
It's literally just dwarfish gold madness.
It's literally just people here
that somebody made a lot of money
and they're like, I also wanna make a lot of money.
Oh, you did a thing called NFT?
Well, whatever.
I don't care what it is, I'll do it.
Like that's what it is.
Nobody actually believes that like NFTs are like good.
They just think they can make a lot of money.
It's the hot new thing.
And they're just uncritically going along with it.
Especially for a lot of celebrities as well.
Especially for like how badly it fucks up the environment.
Put that cringe.
Yeah.
I'm just surprised that people are still like,
like it doesn't make as much money as people would think
and it fucks up the environment.
So I don't see like the...
Well, see, okay.
NFTs are weird because they don't have any actual use.
They are literally the only reason anybody gives a shit.
Any of the NFT bros, they always say the same thing
because it's a way to make money.
That's it.
That's all they see.
Yeah, that's all they see.
They see a dollar sign.
There is no functional use.
There is no reason to give a shit about NFTs
other than, ooh, what if I make money?
Yeah.
It's the equivalent of like participating in a fad.
Like, oh, planking.
I'll do a plank.
No, it's not like that.
If it makes me money.
Yeah, it's like if planking was like...
Well, the thing with planking is like, oh, it's funny
and it's fun being part of whatever's going on.
Replace that with, it's nice to get some cash
and then that's why everyone's saying it.
The reason why crypto bros are so cringy
is because they are operating under,
like they literally don't care about what they're saying.
They're saying whatever they think they need to say
in order to like, to hype their brand up
and like, you know, maintain the brand
and like help their fucking items like cost rise
so they can flip it at a profit.
They're not saying anything
because they actually believe it or like think it's cool.
They're saying what they think they need to do
just like serve their financial needs.
I got this like Black Mirror episode.
It's a crypto bro dad gets his son an NFT for Christmas.
That's not a Black Mirror.
It's just like, it's just...
That would be such a good episode actually.
You know, I forget what the legal term is called
but they have this issue in baseball for baseball cards
and there's still a lot of places with this issue
where somebody would open a store, right?
They'd have a pretty rare baseball card.
It's not worth anything.
They put a sign out or they have somebody come in,
you know, they give this person money to come in
and buy the card at $100,000.
So that way they could say this card sold for $100,000.
It really did.
This person just bought it.
You know, right now I'll sell it to you half off $50,000.
And you know, some poor person will walk in,
not poor as in money wise, but just poor as in this is sad.
They'll walk in and they'll see that and say,
oh, I could flip it at 100K and then they buy it.
And then this person will now defend the shop.
They'll say, no, no, no, this shop is legit.
I bought this for 50K.
I got it half off.
I can still sell it for 100K.
I swear the shop, you know, they defend the practice
because, you know, sunk cost fallacy, I honestly.
It's the, it reminds me of like, you know,
that in that HBomber guy had that video
about the anti-vax stuff and it's those people who,
it's like the most vociferous defenders
of like the anti-vax guy, that one guy
who like wrote the book and like is sort of
the starter of the whole thing.
It's like, those are like the people
that like were victimized the most by him.
Who like, like the people who have like lost the most
to the whole thing are like the ones that are most invested
in like convincing themselves that like it was not a scam
and it was not all for nothing.
Yeah, and I mean, I'm not saying all NFT trading websites
are like this.
I have a feeling most are, but I've definitely heard stories
of, you know, somebody seeing a piece,
cause you know, it's all anonymous with, you know,
Ethereum, you know, you see it go to wallets,
but you don't know who's who.
So you'll see something listed starting at like 10 Ethereum,
which is a lot of money.
And then, you know, somebody buys it,
but it could just be the same person, you know,
making a new wallet to make it and just transferring
their Ethereum from wallet to wallet, basically,
and then selling it for eight and then it sells.
Like there is a lot of that.
People get scammed every day with NFTs.
And I think that's the biggest issue of it.
It's just, you know, it's easy to scam people.
It's too easy.
Have you guys seen that?
Oh, look at it.
What's up?
Mm-hmm.
I understand I'm looking at Bitcoin.
Bitcoin is down slightly, but it's still just kind of
hanging out.
Ben, you can't keep paying attention to it now.
And yet, and yet I just did and there's nothing
you can do about it.
Well, isn't that, surely exposing yourself to it
continually will allow you to slip in and be like,
but maybe I could make some big cash.
Don't worry, I can fix them.
Like go back in.
I can change them.
I don't think so.
I really don't think I'm gonna buy at this point.
I really think I've basically missed out
on like the big gains.
If there are any more gains to be made,
I think I've missed out on the majority of them already.
I'm not really thinking of buying at the moment.
Right, clip that.
Don't worry.
Then repost it whenever it happens.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Clip that and then use it against me later.
Well, did I interrupt someone?
Speaking of, when you said anti-vax,
the first thing I remembered was the John-tron shit.
Was that this week that John-tron went on that fucking rant?
John-tron is such a fucking dude.
I like his content, but when he gets into like political shit,
that's where I like turn my brain off.
I don't.
His old videos were funny.
He doesn't even make funny shit anymore.
No, you know what?
You know what's an app comparison?
John-tron and his wife are like Trixie and Riley.
They're both,
because they were both giving out different information.
How so?
Okay, so John-tron's wife was being a reply guy
and replying to a bunch of people.
And she was saying stuff like,
oh, he's not really anti-vax.
He's just against the animal abuse saying one thing.
And then John-tron's going like,
yeah, we got to question the science here,
like with the vaccine.
Just like how Trixie was saying,
oh, I said that just to her kid,
but then Raleigh was saying, no, no, no.
And then, oh, no, no, she was just clarifying.
Yeah, I see what she's saying, I see what she's saying.
Fucking weasels, fucking weasels,
Weasley little liars, dude.
Still lying, bro.
I don't understand how John-tron could be
very clearly saying something
and his wife could be reply guying to everybody
in the comments.
No, no, no, he's not anti-vax.
You see, he just hates the animal abuse, that's it.
That's a coat.
I've linked myself to this idiot.
I don't know, I have no idea what she's like,
but you defend someone like that.
So obviously being like a stupid,
like anti-science, like numpty, that's a cope.
It's a cope when you're trying to defend that.
Yeah, of course.
I wonder if, fucking, I wonder if,
speaking, just a funny note,
I saw a funny tweet from Nino earlier today
that Trixie retweeted and I thought it was
particularly good, it was,
Nino says, I've always hated numbers
and people who think purely with them,
those who are ruled by arithmetic
are the actual root of suffering in this world.
So Nino says, numbers, I don't believe in them
and Trixie's like, hell yeah, dude, this rules.
That's the sort of tweet you make
when you're stuck on a mass problem
in like middle school or something.
It's like, I don't, I mean, I really think,
it's just like, yeah, I don't believe data.
I believe anecdotes.
I believe anecdotal evidence.
Oh yeah, that's probably what it's about.
Yeah, I think that's the only takeaway I can take.
I say all these things and people come at me
with numbers proving me wrong and I'm like, man.
And I'm like, bro, but like I experienced-
But I inferred it, okay?
I inferred it, I'm smart.
I know a guy who said something happened one time, idiot.
Yeah, literally that's what it is.
Did you, did you two talk about-
That's the mindset, that's the mindset.
Facts don't matter.
Did you two talk about the grade A under A?
It literally feels over reels, literally feels over reels.
Should I comment on that?
Should I reply to Nino and be like, yeah, feels over reels?
No, he wouldn't even get it.
He wouldn't even understand if I try to criticize it.
Did you two talk about the grade A under A corona video?
No, it got deleted by YouTube.
I think I heard about that, but I don't care about grade A.
So I don't know why, what do you do?
So he made a video using data from when the coronavirus
first started becoming a thing in China.
So about two-year-old data and he was basically saying-
Was this a recent video?
Yes, this was like within the past week and a half, I believe.
It got taken down like within 24 hours
and he got a channel strike.
But he was basically-
Oh, because it was so incorrect.
Well, he was saying-
Was he saying the virus?
His argument was, listen, here's data from when
the virus first escaped in China.
As you could see, it only kills very old people
and very unhealthy people.
Therefore, 99% of the population are safe
and you don't have to give a shit.
That's so intelligent.
Oh, wait, no, I think I did see a bit of this.
It was like, oh, so 99%,
well, that means only like 100,000 people died.
So the virus isn't even that bad
and it was like brushing over the fact
that 100,000 people died.
That's still a lot of people.
That's not a good thing.
We should try to avoid even that.
Yeah, but it's 99%, yeah, but it's 99%.
99% of people survived.
If you go through a crowd of 100 people
and you only shoot one of them,
then you're 99% safe,
which means you're safe.
That's very safe.
99% is like a big percent.
Yeah, I mean, it's no surprise to anyone
that grade A is a complete idiot
when it comes to anything.
Yeah, I was honestly surprised
YouTube even let that video release
because it was set to premiere
for like two days before it came out.
But they took it down pretty fast afterwards.
Look at it.
Did they take it down?
Well,
I just don't personally trust any influencer
with anything that can be taken out of sensitive matter.
I would say that's probably an excellent position.
If I watch a YouTuber
and he is like content
because of him screaming and yelling,
I don't want to hear his political opinions
on why the left is bad
and COVID is actually made by the bourgeoisie, you know?
Yeah, bourgeoisie is possible for a lot of things,
but probably not COVID.
I think the word influencer is too nice.
It should be like manipulator.
That's what...
Hey, I'm a manipulator online.
I mean, it's fine.
Yeah, it's kind of true.
It's not...
It ain't wrong.
Do you guys want...
We've been going for a while.
Do you guys want to move into voicemails?
Oh, um...
Do you guys want to start listening to voicemail?
Unless there's anything else you want to get out there
before we start?
I have one thing to do.
You know, last time I was on your show,
I feel really bad because I softball-gibbed
with a very, very clean ABDL post.
So, this time I've decided not to softball you.
Oh.
So, I have two ABDL posts.
One for Gibb, one for Ben.
All right.
If I must.
If I must, let's have them.
All right, I will post Gibb's first.
It's in links.
Okay.
And for those of you who don't know...
This is a Reddit post.
These are Reddit posts of the variety
that one might find on Shreddit.
We have a segment at the end of the episode,
every episode, ABDL posts of the week,
because it's not hard to go on the ABDL subreddit
and find a post to just make fun of.
That's funny.
Oh, God, I'm reading this one.
I'm gonna read it without reading it first.
Okay.
First time messing.
Didn't know what to expect.
Not safe for work.
I'm home alone right now
and figured that'd be the best time for some little antics.
I have my p-patchy.
What is that?
Passy.
Passifier.
Oh, my.
Okay.
Why'd you need to...
He said we're on a nickname basis.
I have my passy, my bottle, and I'm padded.
I felt the pressure in my bowels.
And while I hadn't anticipated messing,
it seemed like a good opportunity.
So now, here I am,
in a soggy, stinky, good night,
trying hard not to let my diaper leak
and laying on my side because I haven't tried sitting in it.
Any ideas of what I should do now?
Nine comments.
He doesn't say do now.
What I should now.
Any ideas of what I should now.
Not that that matters much.
Um, soggy, stinky, good night
is a fucking winner of a phrase.
So, soggy, stinky, good night.
So, what advice should you give them?
What should they do now?
What should they now?
Nine comments.
Well, I'll tell you what they shouldn't do.
Ninety percent upvoted.
Ninety percent upvoted is the funniest part.
What they probably shouldn't do is remove the diaper,
clean the feces off of their body,
and get a job.
Become a productive member of society.
Just working McDonald's.
Yeah, really, if you think about it, this...
You shouldn't let a child sit in their diaper
in their soggy stinky.
It sounds so...
It's child abuse.
It sounds so painful.
It sounds uncomfortable.
I feel sorry for him, but he loves it, I guess.
Oh, God.
Okay, well, here's mine, I guess.
That reaction.
All right.
Okay.
Do you make your guy's penis get smaller in the scene?
That's S-M-O-L, smaller in the scene, NSFW.
So this cold weather and my peepee being effected in that way
has me wondering, do you ever do things to make your 18-plus
baby's penis to shrink?
Like maybe having them do work in the cold or other methods,
so when it's change time, you're able to comment about his penis.
Sorry if this is too much.
There's so much to unpack here.
Oh, so this is from a partner of a baby ABDL person.
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay, you know...
They make them go work in the cold, so they're pee-
They make them do something cold to make their penis shrink.
So wait, but...
So that when they change their diaper, they have a little,
a small penis, more reminiscent of a baby's penis.
So their partner messes in a diaper and they change that
and they want to focus on calling out a small penis.
I mean...
I mean, if that's...
If that's what they're into.
Let's make an NFT of these posts.
And it'll be the worst thing of all time.
Jesus.
I've... I've just... I've just... I've just... I've just... I've just...
I feel like I have nothing to say about that one.
It just speaks for itself.
All right.
That one, for some reason, only 65% upvoted.
Yeah, people didn't seem big fans of that one.
I don't know.
I'm not sure what it is.
They like their baby penis big, I guess.
Honestly.
Honestly?
Same, though.
All right.
Real quick.
Where the fuck did you find these?
Oh, reddit.com.
These are on the...
R slash ABDL.
It's the adult baby diaper lover subreddit.
I literally was on there for less than five seconds when I pulled these two posts.
Like, I did not have to look.
Yeah.
This is about what I would expect.
I mean, what do you expect when you go on R slash ABDL?
Like, honestly, you're the problem here, all right?
These people are just trying to live.
They're in their natural habitat and you're going in and you're trying to fuck with them.
Hold on.
I have one more to show you.
Now, we did read this in an episode.
Oh, God.
But this is the pin post on there.
Give me one.
All right.
Pinned, huh?
Like, safety pinned?
Like, my dipey.
No, like, this is the head mod making an announcement to the subreddit.
Yes, I know, I know.
There you go.
Reminder, don't be creeps on other subs.
I'm appalled I have to post this once more.
We've had reports that some of our members have been trying to engage in a creepy way with people from incontinence subs.
Don't do that.
It's creepy and you give all of us ABDL peeps a bad rep.
We're working hard to make ABDL more accepted, but this kind of behavior will make many people think we're creeps.
Several people got banned from our sub because of this behavior.
It's perfectly fine to participate in those subs normally.
The F, you're actually incontinent.
We know there's overlap and we want both communities to get along.
Thank you and stay padded, Bottle Emoji, whether you need it or not.
So what happened?
Dude, ending my ABDL YouTube channel with, hey guys, thanks for watching and remember, stay padded, whether you need it or not.
Signing out.
I'll get you the next time.
Hey, everyone, it's Crinklebottom, seven flowers, seven ears.
I'm going to end my daffodil video by saying that.
Stay padded, bro.
Make sure not to shit yourself too hard.
Stay padded.
So wait, what's an incontinence subreddit?
Incontinence is where...
What do you think it is?
No, I know what it is, but why would you have a subreddit for it?
Because you like it or because you just know?
No, I think it's probably dealing with the medical issue.
The deep lore of this post is that people from the ABDL subreddit were going onto the incontinence subreddit and seeing pictures of women and commenting,
hey girl, do you shit with that ass?
See, that doesn't sound like a very little thing to do.
That sounds like something any creepy guy would do.
Or anyone who's a fan of Tommy Carson.
I assume they were doing weird little role play stuff.
No.
Or asking people about their diapers.
It was these people hitting on others for medical disorder that they fetishized.
Yes, okay.
It's nice to be valued.
I guess I never really thought of going to a subreddit for a medical issue.
Yeah, that's a new one.
I've never heard of this.
Sure.
I guess it makes sense.
It's like support groups.
Makes sense.
Yeah.
Yeah, basically.
Or asking advice on how to...
Yeah, I know certain subreddits for...
If your kid gets diagnosed with something, how do you deal with that as a support type aspect?
Yeah.
Yes.
That makes sense.
But commenting that...
And then ABDL...
Hey, yo, you shit with that ass?
Oh my fucking god.
This actually reminds me.
There is actually some overlap because there are some members of the ABDL subreddit that
quote have achieved the next level of human evolution.
End quote.
And these people that say that basically just train their body to be incontinence.
They took away their ability to control their own bladder and they'll go on the ABDL subreddit
and brag about it.
Like, ah, yes, I am now better than everyone.
I have achieved the next stage of human evolution.
I have removed my ability to control when I shit.
Except they're being...
They're not being ironic.
They're being serious.
So that's why there is some overlap.
They happily train their body to just lose this ability and it's so weird.
I want...
I want to move on voicemails.
Yeah.
I don't want...
No more.
I've had enough.
All right.
This is the first voicemail.
Here we go.
This one is called...
Fuck Trixie.
All right.
On the count of three, let's listen.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
What was that?
This is not...
I think...
I believe he said, I hope Trixie chokes on a fucking dick and dies.
I believe that is what was said there.
I heard dick and pole.
I couldn't hear it because it was coming out of my sp...
I thought bowls.
Okay.
Well, whatever.
I mean, whatever.
Yeah.
Okay.
The next voicemail is called Beyond the Pale.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
I just want to say that after the Golden Witches coked out like shitfests on Twitter today,
I'm upping my pledges to the various Patreons.
She can go burn hell.
She's a vile, wretched, like third rank intellect narcissist that's eating this fucking loser.
Fuck off and die.
I would agree with all that.
I love you, Ben, Gib, Tom, fuck.
Yes, definitely true.
Third rate intellect is the one that doesn't...
People talk a lot about what a shitty person she is.
Nobody talks about that.
She's kind of just fucking stupid.
She's kind of just like low intelligence, like idiot, and always has been.
We need more people talking about that one.
Next voicemail is called Why Would Trixie Say That?
Three, two, one, go.
I'm sure lots has already been said about Trixie and her weird little podcast segment,
where she just makes a pool of herself.
But one thing which I especially did not like was the criticizing of Gib for making funny
little words and phrases, like you give him an inch, and they'll take your splinch.
You're just messing with words, saying funny things that just sound funny, even if they
don't make sense, saying that, oh, Gib's not funny.
Why?
Why would you say that?
Gib is funny.
That's funny.
It's funny when she said splinch.
I mean, that's the humor that Gib's videos have always had.
That's the humor she's always had.
And it's always been funny.
Trixie used to think that was funny.
Because it's funny.
It was such a nothing little comment to then pick it up, like, oh, clip that out of the
episode.
Oh, I got to bring this to show my dick show friends.
What a loser this person is.
They're so not funny because they said this word.
They made up a silly word randomly.
I make silly words without really thinking.
And instead of making fun of someone and laughing at their misfortune or whatever, passes for
jokes on shows like that.
Yeah.
It's just, it's just, I don't know.
That was such a nothing thing as well.
It really, it really was like, why, why even bother talking about this?
Next one is called Go Gib exclamation point three, two, one, go.
Hey, after that whole crap with Trixie and what are these podcasts?
I had one thing on my mind.
And I hope I speak for others as well.
If I just say, hey, Gib, we love you.
You're a great and your best girl.
Peace.
Thanks.
Thank you.
I'm changing my voice to be more feminine.
Thanks for the voicemail.
Next one is called I'm so sweepy three, two, one, go.
Wow.
I'm pooped.
Gosh.
Has anyone else noticed that when you're tired, it's easier to go to sleep compared to
when you're not tired?
It's just found that interesting.
Anyone else that noticed this?
Please give me one.
Okay.
This is a reference to I think Trixie's last sub stack article, which is two pages of
her opining about how concentrating is hard sometimes and how it's easier to go to sleep
when you're tired.
Wait, is that what she said?
Yes.
How on earth could I guess weed?
I mean, it's sort of supposed to be like a metaphor for like, it's like, do things.
It's like, hey, do things because if you do things, you'll be tired and you'll have an
easier time sleeping.
Oh my God.
And you won't be forcing yourself to sleep when you're not tired.
That is the weirdest thing I've ever heard.
It doesn't make any sense.
That's so strange.
I don't get it.
It's stupid.
Is she getting it?
Okay.
I don't know.
Is she trying to say it?
This was the one that she wrote that she had to furiously tell.
It was after she posted the What Are These? podcast thing.
She spent the rest of the night writing that article.
She passed out writing that article about how it's easier to go to sleep when you're tired
and then woke up the next day and finished it.
And it has nothing to do with any of the stuff on Twitter.
It's completely unrelated.
It's just a totally pointless, like, concentrating is hard and sometimes I don't like when people
talk to me.
And also, sleeping is hard unless you're tired.
Okay.
Thanks for reading.
Bye.
Is she trying to imply that, oh, I know that you sleep better if you're constantly busy.
I'm such a hard worker, Teehee.
I think it's supposed to be something like that.
Yeah.
It's about working hard to get shit done.
Get shit done is the point.
The next one is called Staggering If True, and it's not a voicemail.
It's a Reddit link.
Oh, no.
So I guess I will...
How could you, Ben?
I guess I will...
Oh, here it is.
Link doesn't work.
Staggering If True, and here's the image.
It's this one.
I've seen that.
I haven't played Celeste.
I haven't beaten it, but I've played a bunch of it.
That's pretty good.
It's a good video game.
It's a fun platformer.
It's about how trans people can double jump, but nobody appreciates.
Yes.
Nobody gets to that.
Okay.
Good joke.
Next voicemail is called Trixie Disavows Hatred.
Here we go.
There it is.
Three, two, one, go.
If you're hateful, you're wrong.
You are wrong.
True.
This is a smart person must have written that.
That bar.
Next voicemail is called...
Next voicemail is called Riley the Golden Pimp.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys, it's Riley the Golden Pimp.
Cowboys.
Halloween.
What?
Insightful.
I get the ball coin.
I make things happen.
I produce.
I'm a producer.
I'm a visionary.
Best thing.
You know how it is.
I do.
Do you like receding hairlines?
Do you say receding hairlines?
Cool.
I like the nondescript diddly-diddly noises for what producing sounds like.
Just slurping.
I'm producing.
Okay.
Next one is called Cats.
Three, two, one, go.
It's a dead cat.
Oh no, it's a dead, dead cat.
What we gonna do about the dead cat?
I'm so very sad because we've got a dead cat.
One minute this cat was alive and now this cat is a dead cat.
Oh no, I'm so sad about this dead cat.
Oh yes I am.
It was such a good nice little cat when it was alive.
Now it's just a dead cat.
Okay, thanks for the song.
Next one is called Kodoma.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm still listening to the dead cat.
No, three, two, one, go.
Okay, I'm sorry if this has literally nothing to do with the current episode,
but I have a slight feeling that it probably is.
I'm guessing we're probably talking about a lot of how Trixie and...
A bit, yeah, a bit.
Just absolute idiots.
But I need to like put a bit of highlight on Riley
and how much of a fucking in-step moron Riley actually is.
This motherfucker, and ironically thinks that just because Trixie is trans,
she's exempt of being called out on transphobia.
I've been arguing with this motherfucker for 20 minutes on Twitter.
He explicitly thinks that.
And he's not understanding any point anybody's trying to make.
I think Shreddit tried arguing with him.
Nothing.
He's just some fucking weird stoner.
He's a weird guy.
I don't like him.
He might be the stupidest.
He might actually be the stupidest.
He is very stupid.
I don't know what.
I'm sorry.
Okay, bye.
Base Shreddit call-out.
It's pretty dumb.
Yeah, he, um...
I described him recently on Twitter to someone who asked like who is Riley.
I said he's just some stoner vagrant who's good at kissing ass.
That's what he does is he finds like people who's like money he wants
and he just kisses their ass until like they like say that they're his friend.
And then he can say, oh, I'm Dick Masterson's producer.
Oh, I'm Yeeg Studio's producer.
I have all these credits.
I'm a successful musician or whatever because I have,
I'm on a music YouTube channel with 300,000 subscribers or whatever.
Right?
Fake it till you make it.
I'm looking to the, to the, to the ultimate experience.
I do have to say this and you'll probably appreciate this, Ben.
Um, so my co-host Kai the Kitty Lewis, he is actually a fan of the Dick Show.
He keeps up with it.
Uh, and we were talking about the argument with Riley and he says,
no, no, see the funniest part about all this is that anyone that is deep into
the Dick Show lore knows that they just keep Riley around to laugh at them.
Like Dick...
Is that true?
I don't understand Riley's relationship to the Dick Show at all.
So apparently Dick hires people just for the meme.
He doesn't expect them to actually do anything.
That's why Riley doesn't actually do anything.
Like he just keeps them around for a circus.
Does he pay them?
Uh, I don't know.
Why would you just pay people for nothing?
Okay, I don't see what's so entertaining about Riley that I would want to keep him
around for, for amusement, but like, I guess it makes, I mean, I know,
but I know, like obviously he's not like, obviously he's not useful for anything.
So I mean, this kind of makes sense.
Like there's no other reason I could think of that you would want him around.
Uh, so I, I, fair enough, fair enough.
I could imagine Dick finding some amusement in the idea of, of Riley thinking that he's
the producer of the Dick Show and actually not really doing anything.
I guess.
Yeah.
That's kind of funny.
It would be, I would, I might find it funny if, if, if it weren't so, if I weren't like
personally annoyed by him on like a, on like, on like an in-person basis.
I mean by in-person, I mean on Twitter.
Um, next voicemail is, uh, is called, it's called, uh, three, two, one, go.
What's up, fuckers?
It's me, Riley.
Oh my God, he's here.
Hey, Ben and Gib, you are, respectively, a not cool dude and not cool lady.
What the fuckers?
How could you, how could you fucking say so?
I can't believe you'd be so transphobic.
I can't believe you would say something like that on national television.
Ah, but you gotta respect, ah, but you gotta hand it to him though.
But you gotta hand it to him.
What do I gotta hand to him?
Uh, whatever you got.
Whatever you got, empty your pockets right now.
Give him, hand it over, fork it over.
Oh, damn.
Oh, the one ring, oh, the one ring was in my pocket.
Ah, darn.
Ah, Gollum guessed it right.
My, my estrogen podrance.
Uh, next, next one is called Goll, question mark.
Uh, three, two, one, go.
Cat and phantom horn.
Strange things been happening down here in Equestria.
A mysterious pony named Nylon Tusk has come to Ponyville.
Nylon Tusk.
And he started selling something called Ponycone.
And now everyone's gone apples buying and selling them to each other.
I'm worried, Phant, what if Ponycone ain't worth a bit in a few years?
Where Pinkie Pie's already lost 30 nasinotic?
That was her and Aaron and Phant.
I'm not buying into Tusk, Esteem.
He's trying to run off with every pony's bitch.
So you know what I did instead?
I took my money down to the main Manhattan Stock Exchange.
I got invested in the pony tick industry.
You know what I bought shares of?
Apple.
It would be unironically based if like a kid show like My Little Pony had an episode about like kids don't buy crypto.
It's a scam.
Thanks, Applejack.
Oh, Nylon Tusk, Elon Musk.
I get it.
Very pretty good.
Pretty good.
You know what?
Just an unironically good and cool voicemail that I liked.
Hell yeah.
Also wait, that was wrong.
I hated it when Applejack buying stocks and Apple, but other than that it was good.
I didn't see it coming.
Maybe I'm just stupid.
By the way, sorry, that was the wrong voicemail.
That one was actually called Applejack.
This is the one that is actually called Goal, question mark.
Can we put Applejack in the voice grail?
Yeah.
I think Applejack the character from My Little Pony.
I think she deserves it.
I think Applejack deserves to go in the voice grail.
I think she's earned her place.
That's the first placement in there for a while.
Okay, this one is called Goal, question mark three, two, one, go.
And during your Patreon podcast, question everything, stretching your fast forward.
Six inches now.
What's your question mark?
Zena, fucking hierarchy.
No, I'm happy with six inches.
I've achieved everything I set out to do.
I've broken through, I've broken down the impossible already.
It's time for me to retire at the top.
Next voicemail is not a voicemail.
It is an Imgirlink.
Here's the image.
What is this?
Some people have read a few Marxist books and think themselves quite learned,
but what they have read has not penetrated, has not stuck root in their minds.
So they do not know how to use it, and their class feelings remain as of old.
Others are very conceited and having learned some book phrases,
think themselves terrific and are very cocky.
But whenever a storm blows up, they take a stand very different from that of the workers
and the majority of the peasants.
They waver while the latter stand firm.
They equivocate while the latter are forthright.
Mao Zedong, the little red book, quotations from Chairman Mao Zetong.
I mean, sounds true?
I guess what this is saying is posers bad.
Yeah.
Posers is bad.
This is like fake allies and whatever.
Fair weather allies.
Is he talking about the Democrats?
Maybe not.
Maybe that's not even...
I mean, Mao seems to have had some pretty based quotes in his life.
I've seen a bunch of Mao quotes around and he definitely said some things I agree with.
So that's cool.
Yeah.
Shame what he did.
I don't even know that much about what he did.
I assume he killed people and did tyranny.
It was sort of like a bad handling of China.
I'm pretty sure he's the one that said that he was going to reward farmers for each pigeon killed
because he was tired of all the pigeons and then because...
Well, that doesn't sound so bad.
And then because the birds went extinct, the insects no longer had a predator
and they had a massive famine that killed millions.
That's very funny.
They tried to do...
That's what they did with emus in Australia.
Australia and China are the only two countries that have declared war on birds and lost.
And they both lost.
Well, I guess for China they won, but it was like a Pyrrhic victory that damaged them just as much.
And then like, yeah, I think Australia just lost the war against the emus.
Birds, man.
Wait, how do you even fight the emus?
Prime Minister.
You can't.
They're too powerful.
There's a great Sam O'Nella video about it.
They literally took jeeps and mounted gatling guns on the backs of jeeps
and tried to just ride into the fucking outback and just gun down flocks of emus.
And it didn't work.
Are they bulletproof?
You can kill them with bullets, but they take a while to die and they don't go down immediately.
And when they're densely packed together, you can only shoot a few at a time.
They have strengthened numbers.
You can't just immediately mow down the entire herd.
What the fuck are people riding the war on birds?
You just gotta get a bazooka.
Just ride emus.
Oh my god.
Call America and get a drone.
That reminds me.
I saw in the news two days ago, I think it was Pablo Escobar's cocaine hippos
are now being legally recognized as people with human rights.
Cocaine hippos?
Is it white?
Yeah.
Oh, I saw that and it made so little sense that I didn't even think about it.
You're cocaine hippos.
What's a cocaine hippo?
Is it a hippo that is infused with cocaine in a DNA?
It's a hippo that will eat the plant that cocaine comes from,
but also protect them from people trying to steal the plants
or people trying to mess with his farms.
Because I don't know if you know about hippos,
but hippos are very vicious animals.
They can and will kill people very easily.
I've heard that they can kill these people.
Yeah.
Yeah, hippos are scary, dude.
I hate them.
They terrify me.
They've been rhinos.
I mean, I would probably, if one was coming at me, I'd be scared as shit.
Yeah, of course.
Next voicemail is called, it's just called DeVoo.
Three, two, one, go.
I love DeVoo!
Well, good for you.
Yeah, yeah.
Well done.
Next voicemail is an Imgirlink.
Here's the image.
Nate the type of fella to say nice kitty after falling into the tiger enclosure
at the zoo.
At the zoo.
True?
I can see it.
I mean, that doesn't seem like...
Nate has a little Harambe moment.
Harambe moment.
And he's like, oh, nice kitty.
I'm gonna be a friend to you, so you don't kill me.
I hate animals.
I fucking hate strong animals.
Get that shit away from me.
What do you define as a strong animal?
Like a zoo animal?
Anything that could kill me.
Anything that could kill me is unacceptable.
So like a dog?
If...
No, I'll kill the dog first.
Okay, okay.
No, I'll kill the dog.
If you're gonna make an exposed video on them, do not cut this clip.
It is out of context.
I will.
I will kill a dog.
I will kill your dog.
If I fucking see your dog on this read, it's over.
It's over.
You're a pain to judge.
Oh, no.
Not Scruffy.
Insanely dogfoaming.
If it's a big dog?
Yeah.
If it's a big dog.
Next voicemail is called,
Get fucked bitch.
Three, two, one, go.
Vod, Vod.
I have some cruel stuff to say about Trixie that I have no reason to hold back anymore.
I believe she's copying her new videos about an animal.
She's copying the style of this more successful, younger, hotter, trans girl, anime video aces
called Hazel because she was a young e-girl.
As she mentions in one of her texts on her sub-stack, she mentions how she loves how the
e-girls on TikTok have their little decorated rooms, while you're too old, let go, nobody
you live in a Prius, get fucked, you old bitch.
Yeah, I googled Hazel and I can't find anyone named that, I don't know how to spell it.
Yeah, I don't know how to spell it.
I know she likes the fucking e-girl makeup shit and wants to be an e-girl or whatever.
I think she's given up on physical aspects of transitioning.
She seems to be putting less and less effort into it and in recent sub-stack articles she
kind of implied like, yeah, people see me as a man, people see me and my fiance as gay
men but like, fuck it, I don't care, she probably does care but she is coping or something,
she seems to, she's saying, fuck it, it seems like, I don't know, that's just me trying
to, that's just me trying to connect dots, that's not any kind of like, I know that for
sure or anything.
Next voicemail is Red Five Rainbow, is that it, did I put the right one?
Yes, I did, okay, Red Five Rainbow, three, two, one, go.
I was just listening to Ben's Patreon podcast and I just absolutely love listening to Ben
talking about churning, it obviously works so well with this brain, with all the numbers
and this and this will happen, if I don't do that, then I'll miss out on this and yada,
yada, yada, but Ben, Ben, Bitcoin is not the same, Bitcoin is a gamble, it is not a guarantee,
you don't know how Bitcoin works, please stop talking about Bitcoin, you're not losing
money when you don't put the money in and then it goes up because you didn't know it
was going to go up, it's a gamble.
Oh my God, no, I know it's a gamble, but you're wrong, if a different currency goes up, you
have less value compared to like the sum total of all wealth in the world, I'm sorry, it's
just true, it's just true, it is an opportunity cost that you have lost, you have lost value
by not investing if another asset goes up and yours does not, it's just true.
How often do you talk about crypto, man?
Not that often, I mean, I've talked a little bit about it.
For a while there, it was all the time.
For a while there, I was talking about it a lot, I talked more, I went on a whole, yeah,
on the last Patreon.com slash Ben St Q&A, I went into excruciating detail about my credit card
churning strategies and stuff, I'm glad Red Fever appreciated that.
I know I don't understand the technical aspect of Bitcoin, please understand it,
when I say that I lost money, I'm talking about a missed opportunity cost.
Is it important, am I saying like, oh, I should always invest because what if I lose money?
No, because it's equally true that if you are invested and it goes down, then you've also
lost money, I understand like there's risk involved no matter what, but it's just true to
say that if something you are not invested in goes up, you have lost by not being invested in it.
This might be the most brain dead way of thinking about crypto, but I think of crypto and NFTs as
you know like CSGO gambling, where you like you get like nice and stuff like that and you gamble.
Yeah, I don't know about CSGO gambling.
Oh, so like you can buy like these skins and they go up or down in profits,
and they're like completely online to have no real world value, you know?
That's how I think about it at least.
I mean, I don't know if that's brilliant.
Well, in game, you can have a skin, I guess.
Yeah, true, and in NFTs, you get a monkey, so.
There's more than, yeah, but there's.
Well, you can just right click save the monkey.
True.
Yeah, you're right, you can't like right click save have the skin.
Oh, that'd be so sick if they did that.
Next voicemail is called, uh, subject bonus pod,
Solaru0311 they them pronouns at gmail.com.
Okay, three, two, oh, this must, this must be about the, uh, the recent bonus where we react to the,
the, who are these pods with Trixie.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey all, just wanted to send a message in for once.
The bonus pond on Thursday, which everyone here should be listening to by
signing up at patreon.com slash the procrastinators was cathartic and much needed.
I try to stay out of the drama, but enough was enough.
I'm really thankful for the bonus episode because not only was a way to dump on some really shitty
people, but it was also a way to share with the cast and friends on what makes the PCP community
worth returning to every week.
I don't really have much of a sign out, but I just want to tell everyone to take care of each other
and thank you so much.
Thank you, Solaru0311.
We appreciate you.
Yeah, uh, some, yeah, some people said that they found the bonus episode very cathartic
and it was, it was good.
It was a good, uh, it was a good, uh, I, it was, it was fun.
I, I, I think I said on it that like, I didn't listen to the, the, the, who are these pods
because I knew it was just going to make me mad if I listened to it by myself.
But listening to it with you and Simsie and like talking about it as we went, it, it was,
I mean, some parts of it made me a little mad, but most of it was like, uh, it was right,
righteous fury that I was then able to like immediately dissipate in a, in a, in a, in a,
in a more helpful way, uh, as we went through it, uh, and it felt good, uh, and I liked it.
Uh, good, good, good times, good times.
Next voicemail is called, um, the, the, it's called fun fact three, two, one, go.
Uh, Gib, you mentioned, you watched the little prince and the eight headed dragon,
also known as one packu o oji no orochi taiji.
And you thought that the main character looked like a wind waker.
That's because the art director of wind waker, yoichi kotabe,
actually did character animation on the movie.
They're connected.
No shit, no shit.
Actually one to one same, same guy.
I, I was assuming that there was like, oh, some, some, you know, person worked on wind
waker, saw that movie and was inspired by, but they worked on it.
Well, okay.
It sounds, he said, he says he did character animation.
So it sounds like it's not like it's the same guy came up with both designs.
It sounds like this guy, yeah, he worked under the movie, like a cleanup or whatever.
Well, no, probably not cleanup.
Animation.
Well, I don't actually, I don't know.
Maybe I assume, um, I assume he was drawing.
So it, yeah, like he, yeah.
So he, um, I have, I have an interesting factoid for you guys.
So this just reminded me of what's up.
Um, so I was on a show about, uh, reading axed shown and jump manga and talking about them.
And I read one called Boki-san.
Have you heard of it?
Probably not.
It ran for 18 chapters before getting axed.
Uh, but I looked up the artist and found out that, uh, he is, uh, completely stopped
working with shown and jump.
And he is now a VTuber and draws Hentai.
That's kind of funny, I guess.
Yeah.
I mean, I've, I've manga artist.
You know what, then a manga artist starts VTubing.
You know, I mean, I guess it doesn't sound that crazy, but it's funny.
Well, a lot of like, um, like manga artists or like, uh, anime artists start off from
Hentai, or I know that's like a common thing, right?
Yeah, that's why it's funny that he went from actually working for shown and jump.
And his first anime and manga he made was actually really successful too.
I guess he wanted to go indie, I guess so.
But it's still like, whoa, what?
It's funny.
I think it's kind of cool.
It's kind of cool.
I was like, fuck, fuck, I don't want to work for, I don't want to work for this company anymore.
I just want to do my own thing.
I really think I respect it.
Yeah.
Um, next voicemail is called, uh, Rainforest Be Damned.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey Gib.
I was curious why you were talking about how you're concerned about the
environmental damage that NFTs cause when you have bought and sold bitcoin
and Ben still does it and you guys talk about it all the time.
Because that's the same thing.
Thoughts?
Yeah.
Um, well, I have since sold all of my crypto and I haven't bought anymore.
I also have done that.
I haven't bought any in a while.
It's, uh, the, the, the hypocrisy is not lost on me.
Yeah.
I, I, I know that it's, it's just one of those, um, well, yeah, I don't know.
I, I've, I've, I'm not doing it anymore.
Okay.
So I guess my conscience is clean.
Now, I'm, now I, I'm on record as not really knowing that much about it.
I thought that the majority of the environmental damage came from the mining of bitcoin.
I know that it does take energy to do transactions as well.
It mostly.
I thought it was the, I thought it was the mining that like the, the creation of them.
That was the big problem.
Not as much the, the transfer.
As far as I'm aware, it comes mostly from, uh, creating.
So like, uh, Indy, like, like, uh, like mining, uh, you have to get so many more hard drives out.
So, so the, you know, making that also fucks up the environment.
And then, um, also like the mining itself takes up so much power that they have to
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah.
Get more resources.
And then, uh, and then like, um, what is it, then the transfer.
Yeah.
It's like, I'd actually argue it's, uh, significantly less bad.
Uh, for the sole reason that mining bitcoin is, you're basically solving very complex
math problems through brute force.
And what do you mean it's less bad?
What's less bad than one?
Well, it's less bad because of the fact that because it's.
No, what are you, what are you talking about?
What is less bad than one?
I'm making my point.
No, you have to tell me what you're talking about.
I'm talking about bitcoin is less bad than other crypto.
Okay.
Environment wise.
And that is because when you're mining bitcoin, it is because it's brute forcing,
solving a math equation.
There's always a chance you can get lucky and you could solve it, you know, in a millisecond.
And then that's it.
You mind the bitcoin.
Now that is extremely, extremely, extremely rare.
But because that chance exists, I don't care.
I don't care about this.
I don't care about what you're talking about right now.
The thing was like the comparison with NFTs to crypto currencies.
No, that's not what the, that's not what the question was about.
The question was, the question was, you criticize society and yet you live in it.
No, the question was, you say crypto has an environmental impact and yet you did some of it.
And yeah, I did.
And yeah, the transfer probably did have an energy cost that was not good for the environment.
That's probably true.
My understanding is that it is the creation of them that is the worst part,
more than the transfer.
But the transfer is probably also bad.
And I don't know, fucking.
Well, yeah, okay.
The thing I was going to say.
I wish crypto didn't exist.
I wish we lived in a world where there was no crypto.
But since we do, I don't know, you know, I don't know.
If I thought tomorrow that crypto is going to take off, it's going to be the only currency.
And if you don't have any of it, you're going to die in a Mad Max, no water hellscape.
Yeah, I'm sorry to say I would buy all the crypto.
Because I would just, you know, I want to fucking self preserve myself and survive.
I would do it, even though it would hurt the environment out of self preservation.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I mean, sure.
The thing with the NFTs, the reason I harped on about that, but I didn't harp on so much about
crypto was I think at the time, NFTs were becoming like a thing and people were talking about them.
I got the sense that the transactions between like NFT ownership created
like such a disproportionate amount of energy that it was like not quite comparable to like
transferring Bitcoin around for some reason.
Maybe that's wrong.
I didn't, I looked into it enough to realize that they were stupid.
I can't really remember exactly all the details.
I really don't know.
But that's why I was like really bad on, really hard on NFTs.
And I still had Bitcoin at the time.
But yeah, they might, they might be at this point, I'm not interested in either.
They might be different in the way they work in that way.
I don't know.
Next one, we only have two more, by the way, we're almost done.
The next one is called NNN, three, two, one, go.
It's November.
And you know what that means.
It's no Nate November.
That's right.
Myself and tons of other PCP fans are taking up the challenge
and abstaining from nating for the entire month.
I'll be checking back in every week to update on my progress.
And Ben, there's one thing you can do to help us all out.
And that's to not have Nate on the podcast for the whole month.
And remember the saying of the no Nate movement, no Nate, yes, watch.
I don't think they explained what that what it actually means to no Nate November.
Well, I think because I remember on the stream on the stream,
it was like a little joke, like, ha, ha, no Nate.
Maybe this is different.
Like Nate's not going to make content.
Yeah, the joke on the stream was that would be no Nate November would be
if Nate didn't make any uploads.
But this seems to be don't watch any Nate content.
So I solemnly pledge, I solemnly pledge,
never put Nate on the podcast for no Nate November.
It would be it would be breaking no Nate November.
If we let Nate be on the podcast.
Either way, I'm going to be doing not November.
Yeah, just just just not November.
No, just not that's also same thing.
Same thing.
Uh, last voicemail is called.
This is the jumble of random letters.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Welcome to the pro procrastinators voicemail,
where I say positive things about the procrastinators because gosh,
round you've earned it.
Yay, Ben excited to see your game come out and excited to see what comes up after.
Thanks, kid.
We'll have all the work you've done in the past and excited to see you keep creating today.
Calm, you're minding me about myself the way you source music,
but I'm so happy to see that you have a project going on right now that's sustainable
and I hope all the shit in the world goes good for you.
Gamers having?
You make puns.
I fucking love puns.
So good.
I am so excited.
I'm so excited to continue to work on Phantom's Revenge.
And I feel like I'm so close to being finished that I hate that I'm angry that it's Halloween today
because that means I have to go out and do stuff.
I would rather just stay home and fucking code.
You know, one thing about Halloween, this Halloween that I hadn't really considered until
my dad said it earlier today was that is that COVID, right?
People go into people's doors.
Yeah.
Who knows what those kids have?
Oh, I mean.
They could deliver COVID right to us.
Oh, that's kind of true.
I mean, yeah, I guess it's true that it could be a vector for infection.
Yeah.
Because it's like a weird thing like kids aren't getting vaccinated or they can't get the vaccine
or something.
I mean, you can still spread COVID even if you have the vaccine.
Even if you're vaccinated, you could potentially give it to some neighbor.
I just think I'm pretty sure a lot of people are just going to leave bowls out,
you know, on the door, like on the like porch or whatever.
Yeah, we might.
I'm not sure yet.
That's what I'm doing, just, you know, just to make it easier.
And also, if I was a parent, I would be like, yeah, you're not going up to the fucking doors.
You're not talking to any of those people because of COVID.
Maybe.
Yeah, I think it's fair.
Or a lot of cousins are going to have masks in them.
Yeah.
I would go out and get shitfaced tonight.
However, I got shitfaced last night on Lumia's birthday stream.
So that's very responsible of you keeping it to once, however long.
Once in a blue.
Not not not on consecutive nights.
That's that's disaster.
I trust me getting wasted multiple nights in a row is not a is not a good way to live.
It's a good way to like delete the next day.
It's a good way to stop living.
It is.
It really is.
Yeah.
Um, well, that was the last voicemail.
Oh, we're over three hours.
Eleazar hates it when we go over three hours.
Love you, Eleazar.
Fuck you, Eleazar.
Any any anything else to say before we wrap up?
Uh, go check out Clarissa Gunsmoke on my website, my comic.
If you haven't already, give and take that site.
And, uh, look out for a secret reveal at some point in the next few months.
That's what I'll say for now.
Oh, I think I know.
I think I know what it is.
But I also won't say.
Be sure or will I know?
Unless no, no, I must.
Be sure to check out Shreddit.
You know, we're a fun little quirky show.
Be sure to check out Advil's video on Daft Pina.
It will be out by the time you hear this.
Hopefully in the description, wink, wink, nudge, nudge.
Okay.
If it's out by then, hopefully it'll be out by then.
We'll put a link in the description to Shreddit and Advil's Daft Pina video.
Hell yeah.
Thank you guys.
Uh, no problem.
And, uh, buy road to Radcon.
Check my pin tweet.
It's also ugly for how to order it.
Please buy my copies.
I don't need 55 copies, but you need one copy, listener.
$5 off if you're a PCP patron, of which many of you are now, thanks to all the drama.
And, um, anything else?
Oh, um, yeah, listen to the bonus episode.
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Bonus episode, where we fire back.
Where we retaliate against this foreign aggression
of the, of Trixion, who are these podcasts?
And we, we keep it, we keep a W tally.
And, uh, we'll, I won't spoil the final result, the final score.
I think that's it.
I think we're done.
All right.
Hit in the star button.
God bless.
Wait, no, gotta say goodbye.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Okay.
Thank you for watching.
I'll see you in the next video.
Bye.