Hello everyone and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
the best guy ever and today we are joined by the likes of Digibro- oh wait no I'm not
him Bob. I was about to turn the podcast off but now it's okay. We can keep with him. Saved
in the nick of time. We've got Ben Saint, there he is. Yeah, hey what was that really funny
joke I made before the show started and I said hey I'm gonna say that on the show. Don't
tell anyone that I said it before. Anyone remember? No. It was a punchline of a joke
I think so. It was something about on my podcast what are you doing in my podcast. Oh yeah
with the steamed hams. Oh oh oh yes yes okay introduce someone else. Gibbontake is here.
Hello. Gibbontake in this part of this part at this time of day in this part of the country
located entirely within our podcast. You did it. Yes. What's the joke? You know steamed
hams. Steamed hams reference. It's just a reference the lowest form of comedy. No no
it subverts the original. Ben you have to say may I see him. You have to say may I see
him. Oh may I see him. No. Then I disconnect from the call and I leave. Someone else had
to say may I see him. You may have noticed mage is there. Hey I am here I am excited
I want to talk about anime, yes and other things. Oh that's a big oof from the audience.
You can leave, you can all leave. And of course Tom Oliver is here. MLP died yesterday and
I'm not emotionally bothered by it. Was it the finale? It was the finale, it was yesterday.
But it continues in the comics as I understand. The journey never ends. Yeah whatever. Did the
thing I watched be like a leaked finale then? Yeah that was leaked a while ago. I watched
the finale a while ago and I thought it was stupid but whatever. Stupid. You know I don't know
anything about these new characters but I do want to watch the final episode because I have a
feeling I will enjoy it. I'll get some chills. I got a thought on the finale of MLP and it's
I think I may have said this somewhere else but the finale of MLP it sort of goes against the
whole message of the show at the final moment when you think it wouldn't because you know they've
been like redeeming villains and that's been cool. In the last season three of the previously
defeated villains Chrysalis, King Sombra and Cozy Glow from season seven. Who the fuck is Cozy
Glow? She's a little Philly Pegasus. She's a Philly Pegasus pony who tries to take over the
school and thus the world. With her toxic femininity. Wait what? The school? Is this from
Equestria Girls? No they're the school. They make a school of friendship in season seven and she's
the villain of that. Anyway they come back right? Season eight they come back. They're gathered
together and they have to work together. There's a number of episodes where they work together,
learn to you know care about each other a little bit just so that they can get further in their
goal to destroy the main six and kill Twilight. And you think what's happening is that they're
gonna go they become super powerful. The season ender Tupada is like ridiculously over the top
way like super big you know Dragon Ball Z but like even more. Okay. Was it like like the
Tyric fight? Yeah Tyric but like a million times. Too damn. Imagine it's an army of Tyric showdown.
Like if you if you're into that it is very cool but yeah it was alright but like it's it's all
this stuff it's leading up you know these villains are learning the power of friendship to combat
the Princess of Friendship. Yeah it's a real force. You would think that by the end having learned
friendship they'd realize they'd have some sort of redemption moment where it's like oh right
right being a friendship is good and friendships and maybe I could be friends with more than
just the obvious place to go. Yeah instead they just kill them and they turn them into stone.
Princess Twilight and all her friends all of the friends she's made on her part of the season
come together and they do a gigantic beam blast like like exactly how they go to Discord except
Discord participates in this one and they Celestia Luna all the Alicorns all the ponies all the
characters every single person in the world like Lenby our energy this is the Goku moment this is
the you know the spirit bomb she just turns them to stone that's it no redemption kill them is the
end and that's the end of the show. If there's any kind of people that can't be redeemed there's of
course you know literally Hitler, Sombra and those goddamn turfs Chrysalis and Cosy Glow like a child
yeah this is why it's so strange. Straight off murder she's just she'll be back in the future when
they've got a way to fucking you know fix your mind yeah sure it feels like it feels like it's
leaving it open for them to be back but it's just sort of like I mean Sombra comes back at the
beginning but he immediately enough in the two putter in the beginning he decides to not work
with the others he goes out on his own and he gets not like blown apart like last time but like
literally disintegrated you see a skull in the like a few frames whoa wait wait wait you're
saying in the final episode in the in the in the in the opening episode of season 8 Sombra
comes back with all the four villains but he says no I don't care season 9 whatever he comes back
and he's like I don't need friendship to defeat the main six and he goes to do that and that's like
the the villain of of the opening and he gets completely killed disintegrated you see a skull
it's really kind of oh you see a skull jeez it's great as his skin gets ripped up in the blinding
flash of light and it's like wow they did that um so it's like it's it's set the president at the
end of brunswick yeah indeed indeed so like it says the president for the villains not being redeemed
but it seems like chrysalis terek and cozy glow they have like funny moments you see more of their
character they're not totally evil they have a song in this season together that they sing and
there's like why do they get blown to well turn to stone so maybe the real maybe the real world
conquest with the friends we made along the way oh wait no they're all turned to stone
you're saying that it's at the beginning of season nine somber doesn't join them and these
over the course of season nine these terek cozy glow and chrysalis they do their little friendship
thing and at the end of season nine they in fact are turned to stone not redeemed and that's the
last place we leave that's it okay gotcha gotcha that's not the finality of season nine though season
nine is just like this like flash forward right yeah at the end of the episode that well here's one
more episode after the two part which is right twilight's old and she's an alicorn and then we
see the rest of the main six come in who are they're all wrinkly and old and they're visibly
they're not they're not like they're not like granny smith they're not granny smith they're
sort of like they're getting up there though they're like they're like uh they're like milfs
they're like milfs in this stage uh applejack wearing granny smith's like fucking scarf
thingy because granny smith is dead fucking dead shit yeah yeah i caught that so yeah and dragon
spike spike looks like the the buff spike that he imagined himself being way back in a dog and
pony show circle of life so it's like spike's gonna live for a thousand years twilight's gonna
live for thousands of years everyone's gonna fucking and everyone else is gonna die and but
you know that's i i i mean i like i like that they went with that instead of like trying to not do
that because i i like when they do endings like this famously the final episode of star trek the
next generation is a two-parter i forget what it's called till we meet again i can't remember um but
it is it is the same kind of flash forward it's actually like it's like a time travel-esque kind
of episode oh my god it's like the best episode two part it ties into the very first episode it
ties into the whole series and the finale oh my god it's so fucking sick friends or my thing of a
different episode i you know i gotta fucking i gotta get the name right but the point is it's it's
it's a great way to end your series right he's like tabs in front they say that i know i don't
think so i think i'm thinking of a different episode isn't that isn't that a reference to doesn't
spock do you like this don't they do the same thing they do that in in the original and it's a
reference they do they do yeah that's okay that's when that's after spock dies kirk does two absent
friends yes yes that that's what that is this is um by the way the episode's all good things it's
all good things dot dot dot and it's uh it's okay i just want to say yeah for the record all good
things dot dot dot come to those who wait uh something like that but listen to this though
they i just this episode is so brilliant okay for example i'm gonna spoil it a little bit
in the episode and things could change it like with the it's a time travel kind of episode a
little bit they have to mix up some timelines and match them up whatever it doesn't matter
fix the time space continue them it was a big deal um in that episode we see that in the future
like picard's back on his vineyard in france um he if you don't know everybody uh star trek
has picard who is has a british accent but canonically he is from france because canonically
france was conquered by england so despite the fact that he is in fact yeah it was about time i'd say
so he is french but you know british too or whatever okay point is we see the flash forward
spock has left starfleet has become like a professor has like sorry i said spock i meant data data best
character of all time data is the greatest character ever conceived by man uh he got some
emotions he got his chip going he's he's grown in so many different ways he's left starfleet to pursue
his new passions because despite what you may think he wasn't programmed to be a starfleet
officer he's an autonomous free being who chose to join starfleet of his own free will because
that's what he is um and in that we see him like as this he's a professor at oxford i believe
and he's doing great he's older but that gets hard retcon in star trek nemesis where data just
fucking dies in the fucking piece of shit movies and it's just blown to fucking smithereens in the
last didn't you like rant this exact rant like like i know i know that's all i have to say about
it it's just the most retarded i'm just saying like the show is perfect very recently the show
ended perfectly so i don't want to what my point is i don't want these cowardly mlp fucks to go back
and start changing continuity oh like different things happen after the end before the flash forward
i mean they're going to i'm sure it was perfect comics they're already doing it it's gonna well
maybe those are before the end of the last episode i don't know whatever it's okay anyway it's
i like star trek that's what i have to say and i like anime and i want to talk about anime okay
go for anime do you want to talk about a lot a lot of several enemies have you have you have you
been guys like looking at the most recent uh new anime seasons a season i don't know i'm sure i'm the
only one who's even potentially doing that but i actually did look a little bit but not much
okay oh which ones have you seen no like none i think i watched like the new
season of uh of demon slayer is like the only one though i am looking for new ones i'm checking
them out okay it's just because i'm so excited about this like season because we i i don't know why
it just feels like it has better better like a lot better shows than last season did or at least i
the ones that i prefer and uh one one one of them is uh we called
and that's the one that has me in it just to remind you right oh i love that screenshot yeah
yeah i just i love this anime like um the first episode i laughed so hard just i was unable to
like communicate to bite her with words so i just started making noises through laughter
he said like what are you saying and i said i can't i can't even words
because it was so fun and then then second episode i just i just laughed till i cried and i don't
remember the last time an anime made me cry laugh i can just imagine you sitting there just sitting
in your own filth just going literally me literally me pointing at the screen maids no that that
no no that character is just a background character she barely spoke i don't know well
that's good it means you can imagine we can project that it really is i don't know like the
fact that i'm in it isn't consequential it's just like the rest of the anime is really good what
what sort of uh comedy is it is it like your typical anime uh bullshit comedy or is it actually
funny of course it is okay yeah it's a little hard to say um it's it's a little bit like
i can't i can't even say how do you describe anime comedy it defies words that's why they
invented a visual auditory medium to express these feelings with known as anime i mean you
could talk about like a specific joke i don't know because it won't be funny when i say it just
just one you gotta give the people a taste so they'll go watch the show they're like more like this
please no no you can't explain jokes no you can't explain you can analyze and explain jokes
you have to be as serious as possible no the only joke on my mind is like the most recent one and
it's like super funny and i don't want to spoil it because it's hilarious and that's the one that made
me cry it makes you cry okay with laughter i assume with joy okay all right i think it'll make me
cry okay but the premise is the premise is it's a very sad premise and it reminds me of another
anime that i never watched it's like okay so there's this boy and he's such a pushover and his parents
just sort of like use him make him work while they they're absolutely dead beats until they
eventually sell his soul to a demon just for some money okay so the poor poor boy sounds like typical
capitalism at right boys that's what yeah so the poor boy is busy like on a fishing boat in the middle
of like a storm or something like that and he's being like crushed by giant fish because of the
storm and like he suddenly whisked away into the demon world and the demon is like hi your parents
sold your soul to me so be my grandson and he wants to say no for once in his life he wants to say no
but then the demon cries and he begs and is like please i don't i don't have children i always wanted
to have grandchildren please my be my grandson and so he agrees reluctantly and he said oh good
i knew you were a good kid if if if if you had declined i would have had to eat you so yeah so
he's now a yeah now he's now a grand kid of to this demon he has to go to demon school where
everyone chants about how much they like eating humans and suck them dry and and heal them and
stuff and and yeah he's a human and he has to endure he has to be uh he has to go to the school
and be there and pretend he's a demon and the funny thing is it's like he accidentally becomes an
absolute badass that runs the school in a way without meaning to it's just it's just great it's
like it's sort of like absurd comedy in a way but like it makes sense in a way like it escalates into
things but it doesn't it doesn't go past a certain point where it becomes too ridiculous to be
unbelievable for the setting all right is it is it just sort of like uh the demons are uh they they
because they're like a different race the the the logic they have can be anything so it's just whatever
is really funny uh i mean they have their own logic uh that they follow they follow their own uh
the the the universal logic so it's not like low random i don't it's not it's not nature joe i would
say i i'd never like nature joe i know people like nature joe but it's not i'm surprised yeah i'm a
fan i if there's something i could compare it to for some reason like kaguya love is war it comes
to mind if anyone saw yeah okay yeah i i really love the comedy there and just like how it's a
that's kind of serious comedy for the for the baku man readers out there it's just like it's
it's such a simple premise and the comedy is just like how absurdly convoluted things yet
between them even though it's such just a simple matter in a way and it's something i don't know
why but it just like reminiscent to me of that and and i just did you ever did you ever play
diskaya i think it's it's either three or four which is about like a um ma i think it's a diskaya
i that's exactly right i think it's diskaya four where you play is no it's number three
fuck okay where you play as mau who is an honor student at like demon academy uh which means
that he has been truant every single day because in demon world you're a delinquent if you show up
to class so the number one what a twist what a twist so like the uh it's you you're mau you're
like an ace student so you never go to class or do your homework and uh like you're you're like
little friend you're like childhood friend girl is is a delinquent so she goes to school every day
and aces every test and is really committed to the bit and it's it's pathetic it's embarrassing
but you guys ever read helk i don't think so helk is a manga it starts off really strong it's about
like the demon world is holding a tournament to determine who will be the new demon king
and the demons hate humans but this dark horse candidate appears in the demon tournament competing
to be king and he is a human but all the demons love him and it's like what what's the deal and
like between rounds like and this human just like crushes all these demons at like every contest like
he's like damn he's really showing out he's really impressed and like between rounds like this
the demon reporter goes up he's like uh mr helk was it uh why are you why are you here in the demon
world competing like what's what's your story and he's just like looks at the crowd he's like
humans suck and everyone in the crowd's like yeah we love helk why does he hate humans uh he's got a
whole fucking backstory he's from like a kingdom that turned evil basically and he's like okay he's
like an exile for it it kind of gets worse as it goes on because he and like he and like the demon
like uh this like demon um accountant who works for the kingdom get like they get like teleported
somewhere and they have to like make their way back to the demon world to is this the guy turns
into like an episodic little like buddy comedy like uh you know travel uh fantasy kind of i don't
so it is this him is this human man the guy uh sorry let me let me look at what you're
with what you're doing yeah it's in the discord looks like an abby both gross discussing in the
normal pcp one yeah that looks like an absolute unit okay yeah that's helk that's helk uh it's pretty
it's pretty funny although i i quit reading it after a while because i was like yeah i think i
i get it you get the chan test what's another anime okay that you're loving oris key uh it has a
big all ass name uh but it translates to are you the one who loves me and initially initially it is
not gonna lie it had me in the first half i thought it was gonna be like a harem or love triangle or
something uh you know just your basic bitch anime uh but uh but oh it's so good it has it's it's
quite interesting i i also don't want to spoil the premise but like okay so it starts like this this
guy right he uh he's just a normal everyday school school guy he has a best friend named son
kunwal that's his nickname anywho so he has a childhood best friend and she's really cute and
happy and ganky and and there's even a panty shot it's just got annoyed by and then like this is
school school school school president that's also really pretty and and and she's cute and stuff and
he's like he he and it it and it looks like it looks like both of the girls have a crush on him
and um the he sort of sets up a date with each of them one day with one the other day with the other
and but it turns out that both of them have a crush on his best friend and they want his help with it
and it's and it's just like and there's a girl that likes him but he hates her
and it's just and it gets complicated sounds like a wacky situation but like the comedy there
comedy there is insane because like initially i i i didn't know what i was expecting but god
i was so surprised it was just he gets traumatized by a bench and out of context that sounds really
silly but it makes sense but even with with context it's also really silly and it's hilarious
it's even more hilarious with context because you know why that bench traumatizes him and i
wonder if they're gonna keep the bench coming back every episode will the bench be a recurring
character yeah exactly it's in the opening it's in the opening the bench is in the open yeah i
like that all right it's great i love it it's it's it's definitely a comedy i would recommend
because not only is it like top-notch comedy it's also like it has like it ends in such a
suspenseful cliffhanger on the first episode and and then like the second episode also ends in a
cliffhanger and just like oh shit what's gonna happen next and it's just like i'm so intrigued
because there's like one of the characters is weaving a web of lies and deceit and it's just it's
i want to see how it plays out because everyone is playing into it like puppets on strings and it's
just oh boy it's so good i didn't expect it to be so good also the art is really nice as well
the way they draw the lips for the girls is is quite interesting it's a bit different it's a bit
more detailed what's it called uh oresuki it is in short but also i can't spell this
fuck bullshit okay are you the one who loves me that that one i want to see these so-called lips
as do i you really should have procured an image for us mage it was very unfortunate i'll google it
and find you well mage hey here go ahead and do that or or a suki or a suki
any fucking day now oh i see i see what you mean oh they got little they got little baby lips
for the love of god link it ben plush plush little okay well this is not a high particularly
high res it's fine
i love talking about visuals on an audio podcast
we can just describe we can just just like describe the pixel by pixel by pixel like
say that it's just like out loud oh that's good that's good there's enough there's a bonus episode
idea just we just talk about images the whole time and we don't link any of the images at the end
oh that's a good idea no it's a good idea here's a better bonus episode idea um we show images on
an audio show but we don't say anything oh good call good call it's even less work i mean more
avant-garde oh hey why don't we why don't we put in like two thousands like music just to go
like uh like a link in park am v this like with like the transition of like the spinning images to
transition between the still and we just get like like for whatever topic we talk about we just have
an image on screen but like no audio and then it changes to a different image and people have to
guess what we were talking about this episode of the procrastiners podcast is brought to you by
windows xp movie maker the premiere movie editing application for all your youtube needs okay all
right guys i have a life update uh speaking of misha uh mage here was mentioning spinning a
web of lies this was not an intentional lie i'm i'm so glad that munchie isn't here munchie would uh
would destroy me he's around he could have been i don't know maybe he's probably got a lecture or
something it's probably gonna learning to do god it's sunday it's the lord's day not in my america
well so so here's the here's the cinch everybody so we had to take sesho to get his uh it was like
time to renew his heart worm medicine or whatever it is so we have to renew his heart gotta get a new
yes now when we got sesho sesho is a corgi and beagle mix he's a mutt freak and so he's hard
to know what he's supposed to be like oh i saw a dog whoa no way um the other the other the other
day there was a hole into your conversation that's no go on go on there was a dog here uh uh some
some people were over one of them brought one of not their dog but like a friend of a friend's dog
and this dog oh what's his name
his name was buttons and he was a pug doxon do i say doxon right or is it dash dash
it's like german pronunciation so we're never gonna get okay well i say doxon i don't know if
it's correct someone correct me in the comments okay well it was a a pug doxon mix named buttons
and he i don't not look much of an animal lover but boy this was a cute dog this was a well-behaved
dog he's quiet he just like flopped over on his belly whenever you went and go pet him
he couldn't go he could only go upstairs but not down them uh it was pretty cool pretty cool
dog sorry just over the course of his life he just keeps getting higher and higher
that's really an aspirational way of living i only go up i never yeah i respect that he's
literally incapable okay oh it's like that time in one piece where uh zoro was fighting me hawk
and me hawk was like why do you not step back zoro and zoro said i feel like if i step backward
i'll lose everything so me hawk he didn't step back yeah that's that's that's buttons that's one
piece um that's my that's my uh catchphrase okay so here's the deal i took my dog to the vet sesho
lord sechomaru please address him by his full name and they said so he got his shots he was fine
he was a good brave little soldier but then at the end they were like okay so when you first
got sesho all right he weighed about 17 pounds he may have been a little bit underweight he may
have been a little bit underweight at that time well they they looked into it and they were like
um sesho's probably a little bit heavier than uh he should be and i've been we've been lowering his
who could have seen this coming it this is no one could have possibly not no it's not true
and damn that's one rubenesque dog in short in short sesho went from 17 pounds to 27 pounds
i was gonna i was gonna say do we want to guess do we want to like okay well i guess i was gonna
guess like 30 but no okay he was he's 20 in this very picture here snoozing his life away
it's in the gross links chat or whatever he's 27 pounds apparently that fat second shit you
gotta hit the gym sesho you gotta hit that's a potato and uh in short he needs to lose probably
about like five pounds i mean imagine you weigh let's say like 180 pounds that's you know approximately
average for a male and then you go to 280 pounds like that's approximately the the the change of
look what you've done yeah so i sesho i apologize uh i didn't realize if only someone someone
close to you could have given you warnings weeks or months ago i just didn't trust you guys i just
don't trust your judgment on any of this i have a dog and he's extremely healthy if only if only
someone could have told him so on his special day you might say with the greatest gift of
honesty yeah there you go there you go it's like that calvin and hobbes strip where he's just
sitting at the booth and he's selling for five cents and it's like a lemonade stand but instead of
that it's a frank appraisal of your looks ooh that's a good one oh what a fucking best
mediocre at best that's uh that's a what do you do when you take him for walks do you like throw a
ball does he run around no we pretty well the the longest walks we do we just take like a longer
walk that's maybe like a 15 to 20 minute just you know walk we just walk no really he's got he's
got to get sprinting he's got to get chasing something he does race around inside some but
i mean obviously that's going to be a limited he'll he'll just he'll do the neumes where he just
runs up and down the hallway for no reason uh don't know why he's doing it but getting one of those
exercise machines like where were you we can get like a uh get like a tennis ball that squeaks or
something that he'll like yeah we got we got things of this nature all right well we well
we're gonna work on me and him we're gonna we're gonna punch the heavy bag oh that poor chunk
it's all right sessho look at you sort it out um so there's there's the sessho up got i really i
really i really want to meet that dog i want to meet that boy i i miss like why what what does
munchie have to do with this munchie has been fat shaming my dog since day one frankly it's
fucked up and i don't respect his opinion uh on that or anything else so you know i just i'm glad
he's not here to gloat and to pretend he knew things he could have known for real revel in that
poor dog suffering exactly exactly he's i can i'll do that for him i can do that for the both of us
i just want him to be healthy so we're gonna we're gonna fix it we're gonna sort this shit out
so there you go there's there's sessho update uh oh actually sorry one other thing about sessho
was just um we went to a pumpkin patch yesterday and we were walking around saw those images oh
this is a good michelle's post and some of those this is a good segue for my next topic okay well
good this will be brief uh you know uh here there are michelle posted some on her twitter uh let me
let me see if i can get them while i'm saying this it was just the funny thing about it was
me and michelle uh we took sessho to walk around we we thought it was the same one we'd been to
four turns out it was different didn't really matter it was a good time and um uh dogs actually
were not allowed in but like no one said anything so we just got in anyway so i mean that was convenient
and good uh so we were in we were walking around doing stuff and um we noticed that like okay so
i'm it's it's it's one of these things where i'm noticing that i'm at the point in life where people
approximately my age maybe a little bit older are there like with their children
and it's me and michelle there with our dog and like this you say that like it's you say that
like it's weird that's not weird it's not super weird but like i am noticing this difference uh
you know between me and these other people no i feel you i have a cat i have a senior
old cat he's my baby who needs well maybe it's time to go full hashtag breeder mage no i think
it's time to make the transition i'm only gonna have more cats well that's that's just fine that's
just fine um oh here you go here's hello plumpkin oh that's adorable he's loving the pumpkins that's
pretty cute um and oh yo there's more well we'll get more easier one worship my dog feed sesho on
like on uncertain times during the day or do you just feed sesho in the morning in the evening
and we were just giving him a little bit too much food you're reducing his rations we are
that's correct that's correct and look at that that last pic he's just all head
yeah he's all smiles oh look at him oh he's he's very him michelle will freak out when she hears
this section so let's talk about pumpkins yeah go for it go for it oh who's that other dog oh
fuck sesho who's this other dog that's a that's a plastic dog that is a fake dog oh look at how
oh you're right it's a beagle we think it's sesho's father encased in carbonite do you
say sesho's part beagle yeah he's like half god look at that more unrealistic expectations for dog
beauty disgusting i know this is like in this in this image i can really see how much of a chunk
sesho is but he says that's fucked up of you to say i mean it in an endearing way i mean like he
did does need to lose weight but like oh he's so cute oh Jesus the fact let me find a picture of my
dog okay oh we can talk about how much fitter your dog is in fact i got a video i got a video of
him running at max speed oh max speed what's your what's your dog's name hippo sonny sonny sonny
oh sesho why can't you be more like sonny i hear i hear sonny's sonny's gonna be a doster sonny's
got a job at the bank sonny's doing just great in life all right i'm supposed to go my sense of
throwing the ball thing and off he goes i'm watching it i'm here in this room
that's a speedy boy all right do you have like a do you have like a like ball throwing lever
device yeah for like maximum distance for greater ball leverage he's very fast so you need that to
throw it far enough he's so cute look at me so happy ego oh what's the proximity of this dog park or
just normal park to your house i'm just curious it's like a i don't know like five sort of minute
walk from my house not that far that's like five five to ten don't duck yourself yeah he went into
the river because he likes to like like cool off every so often just toss that ball into the river
and get him get him going downstream he used to he used to like not bring the ball back but it was
like it's funny because like you know we had him since he was a tiny puppy and we've been training
him to like like obey orders bring the ball back or we won't be able to throw it for you you idiot
and he eventually learned how he learns to bring it back he's um oh he's a little bit more than one
year old oh okay so he's a new dog how nice yeah he's even younger than sesha right yeah yeah yeah
sesha's like two and already and already ahead in life no no no sesha's bulking for his for his
summer cuts in the uh in the gains department so yeah don't you worry about that it's like that uh
you ever see that post on um i don't know like a bodybuilding forum or something where someone's
like hey guys i've been bulking for a while now like you know i've like i made some real good
gains i'm you know i've gained like i like i gained almost a hundred pounds like i'm really
happy with my progress at what point in the bulking process do i start lifting though
oh that's good shit
um never you just skip that part no no no that's secondary um it's all about diet um
the so it's being a pump let's talk about how much i hate halloween okay let's talk about
how halloween is the worst holiday what no there's plenty worse but i was loving the vibe i mean
the vibe yesterday at the pumpkin patch was great we had we had hot a apple cider
when we walked around in the cool air it felt great so you're gonna be i'm a hard sell on
this i don't mind the fall aesthetic i like think i like cider the colors are fine uh you know i
don't mind that it's getting cold um i don't still nice i don't um i was gonna say something oh like
i'm not a snob about like pumpkin spice lattes or whatever like that's fine pumpkin spice tastes
good um i just don't like halloween i don't i don't like it there are there are less consequential
holidays like there's um i don't know uh uh uh veterans day i don't celebrate veterans day like
who cares like whatever okay um hates the troops understood i just i just i just i don't want to
do any of the things that are associated with halloween you don't have to i don't you gotta you
have to fuck sluts on halloween it's the thing it's the american tradition and you're not going to
do it i don't you'll just go unfucked ban and is that pumpkin spice is good i'm i'll i'll i'll
i'll stand up i'll put my neck out for pumpkin spice but um i don't want to put on a costume i
don't want to see other people in their costumes i don't want to trick or treat or to receive trick
or treaters i don't want i don't like uh uh uh plastic skeletons the home invasion aspect of
halloween has always been a bit like move out of usa all your problems will be solved uh i mean
i don't like carving jack-o-lanterns uh i don't like i love carving jack-o-lanterns that's the
best bit i want to carve one one it's it's because it's like it's like a sculpture thing but like
it's not weird to do it like like you can't cut i mean i you can technically like buy like a pineapple
or like a watermelon and carve it at any time um but you never think unless it's halloween
yeah like i didn't think it was out and like lighting it like making like a reference to
like homestuck or bail jpeg or whatever uh really fun one year i did one year i did carve a uh
candy corn vampire uh problem sleuth jack-o-lantern which was good it was good um the i did like in
in um what's in gravity and gravity falls they do summer wean and they just do it with with uh
yeah uh uh watermelons maybe yeah that's pretty cute um no i'm the i am the grinch of halloween
and i know that the grinch had a halloween movie but that doesn't count what yeah yeah yeah there's
this i i don't know the night before the grinch i didn't know grinch is in a halloween movie where
he i don't know tries to hashtag cancel halloween or whatever didn't you learn a lesson the first
time i don't know if dr seuss was involved with that one at all or if the studio is just like
we gotta make a sequel guys so wait a minute what what like does he like forcibly make people not
scared as that like he calms everyone down that's what he does i haven't seen it so i couldn't tell
you what the plot is but i have some guesses from the love from the love that he learned from
christmas he decides to spread it to halloween and ruins the spirit of the whole thing by making
people feel okay apparently it's called halloween is grinch that's what i just said and it's written
by dr seuss it was written by dr seuss how bizarre and about that and the grinch has like
orange eyes he's got scary orange eyes in this one maybe the grinch's grievance is that like this
is like his people's holiday and this is cultural appropriation as a ghoul or goblin himself uh
which i presume that he is he's an abominable gremlin is he just like a fucked up whoville
citizen who you know moved away and i think you know i think that the the implication is that he's
like he doesn't shave and he's green because he's ugly and stinky i agree i agree i think he's one
of the whoville people just fucked up or something isn't that what happened in the jim carrey movie he
was like adopted or something he was like one of them but uh well jim carried the actor uh yeah when
he played the grinch you know what i'm saying i'm reading the plots in opposite it was just overgrown
with hair good it's just like no okay so the grinch does not steal halloween and in fact
in spite of the name of the movie there is no halloween in this world there is only
grinch night which just is their version of okay and it's basically just grinch fucking abducts a
child and puts him in his drug wagon and gets the kid high and the kid just has a bad trip
but he doesn't like he i guess he he doesn't like actually die of terror and so the grinch has failed
in his quest and is defeated and that's it so all the spook of halloween is condensed into one
small child and the idea is just to spook this one guy as hard as possible to whatever effect his
desire dude that's like that time in one piece when luffy got pulled put all the shadows in him to
like as much halloween as possible to defeat like that to defeat us that place was definitely
halloween coded so there's no doubt about that um thriller bark that is of course so i guess i'm
not the grinch halloween because it seems like the grinch is actually like the grinch is out and
about like yeah grinch night is his night you're you're that child on on grinch night yeah i'm
that child who refuses to get spooked who doesn't whose toes don't come off because i guess that
that's the challenge is like i'm gonna scare your toes off but his toes don't come off so he's like
darn time let me get my axe i'll get you i have been making a slight effort to uh uh do spooky
things i've watched several horror movies including uh the exorcist three after red letter media did
their review and it was revealed to me it's not a completely terrible movie saw that review good
review good movie liked it um and i watched last night i watched mid samar i was finally able to
acquire mid samar and uh that that did indeed spook me to my core mostly because like because
like the bad guys just won and that made me sad and like feel bad about humanity and i lost faith
for a while but then i got it back uh so that was all right speaking of spooky i finished watching
like season nine of of the walking way i was gonna talk about oh you're still talking about i was
i was going to talk about what i think about halloween but if walking dead is okay we'll get
there yeah yeah so i and it just it it wrecked me i knew i knew it was coming i knew like why
does nine seasons of that so far nine seasons that just terrified me i'm so still going yeah it's
still going there's wait i said the wire right talking about the wire zombie scare me the walking
dead okay yeah i've been saying that has to end for as long as it's been going on as far as i
funny thing is okay they just started season 10 there's a spin-off called if you're the walking
dead it's on season five and i think there's gonna be another spin-off uh starting at some point
and that's not counting all the little smaller spin-offs that's already been i remember watching
season one and thinking like hey this is a pretty cool show it's it's gotten it's gotten really good
like at first it was okay then it got really bad and then it started getting better now it's quite
good again is it good again i'm i'll believe you i'm i'm willing to believe that but i think my
window of care has definitely passed i mean it's fine yeah it's fine i don't expect anyone else to
care but it's just like with season nine it's just like the way the end it is just i hate how they
i hate how they make me care about characters and then you just kill them off like that like the way
they did i just spend nine seasons since you get the pattern by now i think they call that the cock
carousel huh what nothing is uh is fan favorite norman readus still a character is alive
do you mean like he regrams or what no i don't know what his character's name is
from um he's the guy with the crossbow yeah yeah deal yeah yeah he's still alive he's one of my
favorite characters and there's no norman readus from um that that kojima um yeah he's the main
character and death stranding who's the other no no i wasn't norman rockwell who's the other
guy who worked on death stranding i mean of many people guillermo del toro guillermo yeah guillermo
del toro aka norman rockwell why the fuck did i almost say norman rockwell okay whatever moving on
okay but what do you think of halloween i just want to quickly say it's like the daryl uh and and carol
are my two favorite characters and they're all in carol yeah uh they are they're also best friends
and then i think carol's still alive yeah she's such a good character though i love her she and and
and the character and i'm so mad huh wasn't she like dying or something did she have like some
sort of like sickness and now she's not dying anymore no no i don't remember about any sort of
sickness no maybe i'm making this up maybe you're misremembering the character it's been a while
sounds like it uh i mean she died she dies in the comics but uh maybe i'm gonna do that i did
read those for a little bit yeah but she she's such a good character he's one of my favorites and
they hurt her and i'm mad like i the character the character they oft didn't care too much about him
i mean it's sad but like but they hurt her and that's what makes me angry because like she's finally
she was finally happy she was finally happy and they hurt her so i'm mad how can you be happy
again the world of zombies it's impossible she she managed to find happiness she was so
wrecked she went through so much the things were so bad for her and she was finally i mean that's
the that's the thing as soon as the characters arc is complete and they achieve happiness they can
either kill them off or fuck with it because they just or ignore them i know there's the three options
it was just i i know i that's why i knew it was coming but i'm still mad i'm mad it's it's the
it's one of those things like whoever finishes the arc at the same time the show ends is the only
person who gets to live in something like this like if they finish their arc earlier they're
dead wait so they either have to die or they have to leave the show in some other way indeed it's the
only way to stay alive like uh rick protecting his son or did he die i don't you know i don't know
okay okay rick is assumed to be dead but there's gonna be a movie with him so yeah well yeah there
you go but like he's been missing like canonically from the story for like several years now
oh i like how movie is still a term we use like it's such an old fashioned old-timey
sort of it is how it's not i try i try to say i at various points i've tried to switch to saying
film but it's never stuck i mean film i think i used to say film yeah but film makes more sense
film is like a more what's the difference honestly tell me explain the differences i mean they mean
the same thing they mean the same thing but like movie is derivative of of like talky
because like a movie is like it it's moving pictures wow and a talky is like oh they added
sound now you can hear it that's that they called them talkies for a while but that was stupid so
they changed back to movies and film is like the the thing they used to film it on that's what it's
called um so like both are like i guess movie is more descriptive of what you're what it is
because it's not shot on film anymore unless it unless it's quentin taratino
but yeah i don't know i think about that a lot of how the words are weird like computer it's just
like it's computing it's a computer it's doing quite a bit of computing still it's just like it's
such a simple term you know it's just like we didn't like we didn't really come up with a word for it
we just kind of like described what it did and said it's and then like other other languages and
like other languages like okay correct me if i'm wrong but i think in japanese the word is just
like komputa or something that's correct that's and like it's like they could have they could have
just uh used like you know made up their own word that also describes its function like nah
this word standardized we'll just take this one is there is there like a japanese word for cake
because all i've ever heard is this cakey yeah cakey i mean there are there are many japanese
desserts but they use the word cake all the time i mean i mean i mean cake cake cake as we normally
think of it as like a western dish so yeah that's makes sense it's the same way that a cookie no
actually that's not the same or whatever uh but like words right where was i going with this what
was the thing well like how about like a waffle like a waffle is a very specific dish and you know
you can't call that anything but what would be awful because a cultural shit we could make up a
new word for it the dutch word i think right yeah oh yeah computer like i think did computing exist
before computer did they have to come up with a term for what this is yeah yeah i mean i mean you
can do i mean it's math called computation in your head or on paper i mean that's what they
they designed a computer initially to take the heavy lifting out of doing traditional mathematical
computation hence the name computer i would assume okay i i always assumed it was like named after the
device and like maybe the first ones were called like uh electric uh abacuses or whatever yeah that
would be a calculator doing calculations right uh i guess i guess calculation was already a word
yeah calculation yeah and computation as well see i can't i can't divorce computation from the
computer as a word uh fucking fucking zoomer back in my day we back in my day we used uh we just
counted on our hands and back in our day and then they invented the abacus and everyone got lazy
and it all went did you have everyone lost their minds then did you have the weird you go to math
class and they'd hand out the uh the blue calculators with like the white buttons and you'd have to do
calculations on there but then they take them away for the tests the scientific calculators like the
yeah the sign like the ti 83 uh that too but that's not what i was talking about like elton
they gave out like they'd give pass around the class these dinky little like
bright blue calculators with white buttons and they'd be like now do your times tables
bitch but you can't use it on the tests so we're teaching you how to do something that we're not
going to let you do when it counts mickey mouse teach you math yeah yeah that's how everybody
talked back then i know it's been said before but remember in school when they would say you can't
use a calculator on the test you think you're gonna have you think you're gonna have a computer in
your pocket to do all your calculations for you in the real world oh it's night it's 1992 and the
future is bleak children we're at the end of history die that's what we should have said
probably we knew before i talked about the walking dead you wanted to talk about halloween
oh yeah yeah it's not here but hippo is halloween hot take it's not really a hot take it's just
i appreciate like the aesthetic of all of the halloween e things like pumpkins ghost skeletons
the the quote-unquote spooky stuff that um but like i hate scary things anything that's actually
scary i'm like yeah i'll pass i won't thanks i'd never look at scary movies i only i only
like same like funny things that have scary things in them like nightmare before christmas is
obviously like a fun movie that has scary things in it um and uh that's why i like pumpkins and
vampires and ghouls doing things that are goofy rather than scary things i am so torn because i
like scary things but also i hate scary things so i just i can't i cannot exist i don't i don't
like scary things i'm over i'm over spooky things even things that aren't scary but are
just quote-unquote spooky no i'm over it it's done when i played silent hill 2 it opened my eyes and
i began to appreciate scary things and now i watch them they do disturb me deeply mid-summer
kind of fucked me up yesterday i was very spooked and scared but more than not like that there was
like no jump scares in the movie there's a couple but mostly it was just like in the x you know
actually was funny i mentioned the exorcist before i was watching i mean this was in uh like red
litter media's review but they talked about how the writer of the books was working with the director
the director just wanted to make a cool movie and like didn't give a fuck about like the message
behind it or anything uh or you know something along those lines and but the author was very
concerned about the message and they were doing an interview and the guy like the the director was
like i wanted to have like a big finish wanted to like blah blah do this because spoilers at the
end of the exorcist they the guy performs the exorcism the devil comes out of the little girl
possesses him and in that moment he hurls himself out the window and like kills himself
thus killing the demon which is currently in him um and like the the the the writer the author the
screen guy was very concerned that people would perceive this as like the devil successfully
killing someone as opposed to the priest doing a heroic sacrifice to like delete the devil from
this girl's brain or whatever and he's just like in the interview he's just like man i just don't
want the people to think that the devil won and you could see how deeply this was important to him
that people get the message of like hope and and goodness and inspiration as opposed to bad things
win but in fucking Midsommar there's just a bunch of human sacrifices and frankly it all goes like
clockwork and it's great and everyone yay we did it uh we killed the guys and good for us
they were kind of jerks and that's it we win happy endings aren't that scary they can be terrifying
i mean it depends it depends uh you know what i mean can a happy ending be scary okay i watch
the bad guys happy it depends on what you mean by happy ending like if if you it does depend it
like like in a in a horror movie a happy ending usually means uh surviving getting out safely
right yes but even then they'll give you a jump scare at the end i mean a great example of like
things with happy endings that can still be terrifying is like anything like cosmic horror
right because you've you've been revealed that there's so much more going on than humans even
have context or the capacity to understand and so it just recontextualizes all of like life
and even if you get away from it it's like well what i thought was meaningful now is meaningless
in the face of this greater truth i'm like that can be a happy ending but it's because like the
character survived they got away they didn't die but like the world's fucking totally different
now dude i'm not even sure i call that a happy ending necessarily but yeah what if like i mean
i guess it's down to the guy there's there's the guy in the monster and he guys like oh
shit there's the monster he's fucking killing my friends but then he kills the monster but
he he he was sleeping he didn't actually kill the monster he was just being eaten alive while
asleep oh no darn i hate when that happens cut to black or like at the end uh what was it
fucking baguille or whatever just shows up for one frame right before we cut to black with a big
right right the lazy you know showing off one frame it's like a youtube thing i like
spooky things but i hate things that make me feel sad and and like i have a very weird
capacity for what things make me sad like i cannot take it when like old people are being abused
or die or or just something like that something something about that it just makes me die boomers
die super upset it's just like i watched i was watching duro and i liked duro but there was one
one part one one part about like this guy he kind of banded his old mom uh and and like uh she she
clung to him but he thought it was like the monster so he swiped with his sword backwards and
cut off her hand and and he didn't even realize up until he came back uh to his village and that he
realized oh shit you know his mom clung to him for help and he was so scared that he loved her behind
not only did he leave her behind but he cut off his hand her hand when she tried to cling to him
and it's it's still hurting me it's still hurting me on the inside there's a there's a movie there's
a movie called um uh drag me to hell which is uh i watched it years ago and uh i mean it's it's
like over the top in a way that is like comical a lot of the time but it's still like you guys seen
it you guys seen drag me to hell i'm aware of it i have seen it that's it it is um it's kind of kooky
but it's also like genuinely scary in a lot of places and it has like a big fucking like you
think there's gonna be a happy ending but then it's like no everything's the worst like right at
the end and it's like it's so miserable it left me like it let me like emotionally bereft i was like
i can't i can't i can't live in a world they should have done they should have done a social media
campaign share your stories it wasn't fair no it wasn't fair what happened to her she didn't deserve it
yeah don't you i i hate that i hate that that's not cool yeah i mean i'm typically not a huge
fan of horror movies because they tend to go for like like low hanging fruit scares it's yeah i mean
they're a great one there are exceptions of course yeah but like there are some there on the one hand
there's like the low hanging fruit stuff like the stuff that like rate pg-13 and full of jump scares
just to like get money from children around halloween you know and then they also and like
good horror movies a lot of the times they rely on like the visual aspect like really like intense
gore and stuff and i'm not usually hugely into that either there's a movie called uh creep and it
is a horror movie it's not supernatural at all the premise is basically just i won't go too much
into the specifics but it's basically just our protagonist is just like hired to do a job by this
guy and he goes to meet this guy and he's for a while he's trapped he's kind of is isolated with
the guy and it's just about like this guy seems kind of off like oh he's he's really off like
why is he acting this way like what like and like it it uh it's just it's just the horror of like
i've i've met this person who is so off-putting and i am genuinely scared of like what they're
going to do but i don't know because i'm definitely more of a fan of like the esoteric or like
psychological horror of where it's just like instead of like presenting like a very tangible
physical thing it kind of lets your mind fill in the blanks with its own worst-case scenario
because you never know because like this guy is like he's like a liar but like you kind of have
to like like sometimes it seems like you know like in the same way that he's like he's like
tricking and manipulating this character into like thinking like no no no that was just a joke
that was just a joke it's like you the audience are like like how much like like what is the real
what's this guy actually like like is like how much is this uh like he's be he's gas lighting
you he gas lights you the audience and it's like really yuck movies are scary understood but it's
all pussy shit it's all pussy shit compared to legitimately scary video games like silent
hill too that game was so fucking hard to get through it was brutal to try like just watching
a movie it's gonna keep playing just close your eyes you'll be fine but with a game you have to
do it right you have to go into the room you have to oh my god you have to like reach in with your
character into the fucking hole grab the key and you can feel the fucking vibration is something's
touching you it's you playing the fucking game it's a new level if you want two spooks man go play
silent hill two and three it's a shame that they'll never be another good silent hill game well yeah
did you hear about the new silent hill game that just came out like a few days ago oh what is it
i don't care about that shit that's is it a phone game no it's not bad it's a little sucks we all
we all know that konami sucks well i i want to talk about video games as like okay the the more
scary medium because i lied before i do like scary things um specifically in a video game
but not just because you are like your actions and inaction like are constantly causing all like
you know you're constantly uh responsible for whether or not you're being killed right now
in certain video games but it's also the fact that if you if you're in certain video games if
there's like not really a character you can skip all of the boring parts of the movie where
they have to set up characters that you have to care about so that when they die it's scary
like i don't when it's you who is the character you know who you are you don't want to die
so you can skip all that and you can just get straight to the scary parts which is why
i love five nights at freddy's let's plays by markiplier because i can i don't have to play
the game but i can sit there with him and and look around the screen like is there a bear kona
is there a bear coming for you are you gonna be able to survive the night oh my god
wait is this a hard game just about being stalked by a bear
oh you don't know what five nights at freddy's is oh five sorry i checked out okay okay like
you're a hunter just in the woods and the monster the idea you just pitch sounds immensely interesting
though and i kind of wanted to exist now yeah like it's just as scary as anything else you could
think of it might be stalking you you'll be just you'll be just as dead whether the thing that gets
you is a bear or the babadook or whatever or freddy fazbear of fry i don't i don't like playing
hard games but uh no go ahead people the the the purest distillation of like fear in a video game
is just like a game where it's dark and you have to press a button to move forward and at any moment
something could happen and even if you don't do anything something could happen and that's it
it's just a game you press forward or you don't press forward and you're like oh god click
click like i would i would play that game i would shit myself and i would have a great time
and there wouldn't even need to be anything there i i would need to believe those the last
actual horror game that i played was fatal frame two and i loved it i to this day i still like
remember things about it that i absolutely adored um like in somewhere near the beginning of the game
you explore the house and you find like diary pages of like a woman searching for her husband
or something like that and she's lost in the village and stuff and and the very final final
piece you find it's it's like several pages like the first page is like i don't know i can't go on
it's like i i hope i i hope i i'll find you or something like that and it's like it's a blank
page and then you turn the page blank page you turn the page blank page for a few pages last page
so it's like found you or something like that and you put it down and suddenly you get attacked
like by the but the ghost of the woman that was like here and it's just like oh it was so spooky
to experience it but like it shivers down my spine like and it was such a fun experience and then like
later this house um was where there were like two twin girls and and at the one of the girls had to
be sacrificed and uh the girl was so sad about losing her sister that the dad made a doll that
looked just like her and the doll a doll became possessed over time or something like that and
and it's just like i love i love reading the stories of how the people happen like how the
shit creepy stuff it's just i'm sorry i'm just like i'm getting overwhelmed with my
nerves about the game there's one great moment so many good things such a good game there's one
moment i always remember well the first time you see pyramid head in sound hill two is terrifying
he can't even get you but you see him through a grade but in sound hill three there's a moment
that's probably the scariest thing i've ever experienced in a game which is just you walk into
this room and there's a big mirror and you walk in and nothing happens and you walk you like try to
interact like you know you're trying to look for ammo or enemies there's nothing it's totally quiet
and then you go to leave and you click the door and it says the door is locked and it's the only
way out and then suddenly these like worm noises start to fall creep into your ear and you go back
to the mirror and you can see that like your whole body is being covered in like these fucking
disgusting ass like bloody tendrils or something and the whole mirror is getting fucked up and the
whole room is getting fucked up and of course you try the door again but it's still locked and you
can't get out and you try it again you still can't get out and then you have to try it like a bunch
of times and you can't escape but the whole time you're taking damage so you're freaking the
fuck out you don't know what to do oh my god it was very very spooky is the point okay this
reminds me i heard about this a while ago but and i kind of meant to ask you about it um do you
did you hear that like um uh you know you're a twin perfect you know twin perry you show you
show me of course uh do you know that like um there was kind of like a backlash against them at
some point because like was it not todd howard you know in their in their silent hill videos they
they harp a lot on this one guy and like he got a tom tom tom hulet yes tom hulet yes and they
harp a lot on this one guy's involvement and i think at some point people like he got a lot of
hate for it and it seems like maybe he wasn't as responsible as like yeah i saw that video you're
talking about yeah like like yeah there's a video where they yeah they they criticize uh twin perfect
a lot for how how hard they go on tom hulet and and maybe they were i mean they didn't like directly
incite anyone to harass the guy but like i don't like i think it's there was people definitely
harassed him and were like fuck you tom hulet after they put a lot of the blame on this
i don't know i don't know fungo apologized fungo apologized for but the other guy the whatever
his name is didn't rosseter i don't know i was yeah rosseter i was just interested because like
you showed me twin perfect and i love that uh silent hill series and then like i was kind of
but i didn't hear like anyone talking about it in like the broader discourse or whatever and then
to suddenly see it come up as the center of i don't know i mean controversy would probably be
overstating a bit but like people you know just yeah it pops up on social media like people are like
uh you know this this wasn't cool this was this was dumb and then i don't know i was interested
to see a particular into the public consciousness i didn't expect that yeah i remember that that
was interesting uh and those were the guys who got me into silent hill of course it was yeah you
you know they worked with fungo at first um they they haven't been terribly active recently
fungos but uh yeah indeed fungos streamer twin perfect themselves don't really upload much
fungo did a lot of blood borne content but i think stopped after a while i don't know
yeah he made a ton of very popular like blood borne lore videos explain okay which i thought
were very good they they were i watched a lot of those i know he vaped so that's pretty cool
i like i clicked his channel like one time just to see like what it was about and i watched a
little bit of video and he like he vaped on i was like yeah brother in arms i actually i did do a
little research just out of curiosity i there was i don't even remember what the video was but i
remember someone made like a video about this drama such as it is and i went and i looked i actually
joined the twin perfect discord which i think i'm still in just to because i was curious what the
people on their side of the table were saying i mean it should be noted twin perfect absolutely
went hard against tom hewlett yeah and ascribed much like uh a lot of i wouldn't say malice but a
lot of mistakes they put at his feet yeah they according to them he was like very uh he was
like very well they describe him as kind of having a fairly high like executive like like
directorial role in it and being the decision maker behind a lot of the things that they didn't
like about the direction the series took indeed that they say that like you know he doesn't understand
the lore he doesn't understand the appeal of the series he fundamentally misunderstands the the stuff
and so on this particular drama was interesting because there there is there was a very explicit
point if you watch the whole series which i have many times they there is an episode where they say
like who is to blame who is to blame and they quite this is years before the drama came out
and they're like if you watch this is like part 15 or something but you know such as it is
and they were like who's to blame tom hewlett bears responsibility but the main man who is
responsible for the downfall of silent hill is akiri yamaoka akiri yamaoka is the guy who's
done the music i believe for all the silent hill games and he at some point was put in charge of
the series and he he like they say this is the man who really did it to silent hill we love what he
did in the past because these guys these guys the hard like one two three four are great beyond that
shit you know they get them i mean they get criticism for going too hard on tom hewlett like
even as the series was coming out because there is like at the beginning of one video they they
respond to a question it's like it's not all tom's hewlett's fault and they say like we didn't say it
was all tom's hewlett's fault and then they give a bunch of like it's like you know a lot of this
they talk about other people's involvement and decision they do talk a lot about tom hewlett
though the abs okay but which i'm not saying they shouldn't do necessarily uh yeah i mean i i a
little bit feel like people are being a little bit i don't know like should they i agree they
probably exaggerated some things but like clearly these are like passionate nerdy fans or like obsessed
with the shit and you know they're looking to place blame on someone tom hewlett's obviously at
least partially responsible was it totally fair to put it on him probably not i i don't know it's
like fans get a little bit carried away sometimes with their excessive if they were to do it again
they'd probably be a little bit less it's all on this guy but there is some responsibility yeah i
don't know i don't necessarily it's like what's the i don't think twin perfect like did anything
wrong exactly i mean they might have been i mean they may have been somewhat mistaken in like
i mean like they might have thought that he did more than he did like they could be factually
you know i don't feel like they were in the wrong to criticize a guy for the things he did
in a video game it you know it did always strike me that even as i watched that series i thought to
myself like you know kodami is a very big presumably complex company yeah a lot of these guys say
that it's hard to maneuver in a big company they have to get approval from executives and like
how much can one man be responsible they say that in the at some they talk about how like you know
this is a like this is a corporate machine that is that is like you know that has set this up
you know so i mean i would just agree i would agree to his employers i think tom i think perfect
did in fact put yeah i i agree i think twin perfect did put too much responsibility on tom i agree
with that but i don't think they like we're deliberately trying to get the guy harassed
or nor do i like if we if we held like i don't think they expected the series to be that popular
it's like at what point you know it's it kind of come to that thing that that topic i talked about
months ago which was like what is it the journalistic concept of like not doing harm or whatever it is
like there is accountability for anyone who makes a youtube video to like be accurate and precise
that you're not like doing any negativity and i have no doubt tom got a good amount of yeah i mean
there's definitely a probably a large contingent of the silent hill fan base that now associates
tom hewlett as the guy who ruined silent hill sure the question to the interesting question
is a legitimate one is to ask like how much blame let's say tom at an absolutely terrible time as
a result of this these were a bunch of dudes making videos about silent hill how much responsibility
do they bear for simply yeah going perhaps a bit too hard on a man they feel is responsible for
a downturn of a video games i don't feel like more than zero less than i don't feel like you
can point to any like particular thing they said and say like this is unacceptable for you just for
you to say this no sir have you no sense of decency sir and you know i'll just say i always
found this a little bit funny they they did a thing i was always a little bit suspicious of this
where they say like here okay god it was after i think this criticisms like this began to come out
and they were having their fights with the sound hill wiki they're like okay guys new gimmick for
this episode we want you to smash the dislike button because um uh because we want to show them
that we hate it was like the remakes and i mean i agree there's tons of problems with the remakes
total very shitty product they go into incredible detail into all the problems and i salute them
for it but like the way they're saying like smash the dislike button it's like oh now like no one
can hold you accountable if there's any negativity to this video because if it's all positive you
can say wow even though we said it smashed the dislike button everybody loves us and if it's
tons of dislikes well you're just making that a positive now which i thought was a little bit
silly but i mean i get the point it's just uh an intro i was wondered if there's a little bit of
of gamesmanship going on there you know trying to cover themselves a little bit how you play the
game i suppose i suppose what yeah i mean you know they're they're these guys were going on a big
culture war of like we want to defend classic silent hill and that that raises innumerable
issues about you know it's it's the cult it's all about the cult it's not a it's oh yeah i don't
think we'll remember that it's a silent according to the lore of silent hill one this is all caused
by the cult and alessa was a sacrifice alessa was not a deliberate sacrifice the fire was started
accidentally i mean these i mean you know me i made my fucking like tifa video about retardedly
overly analyzing details that's all they do this is all they do it's a good series these are the
it's a really good it is a good series the twin perfect silent hills is really fucking oh the real
world dark world and foggy town they all the production values on these songs they roll out
like incredible the only one with another worldly name i think about that song all the time hard to
believe it's a great song it's a great song about such minute plot details one yeah just like who
would do such a thing it's great it's great yeah and i mean just if you watch the series like the
amount of editing and the hard work that is just so apparent in every part of the video i always
thought their delivery is pretty bad they really come off like they're stiff and like the way they
read their lines it's like it really feels like they're reading cue cards you really feel that
they're reading cue cards and like their jet they gesticulate a little too much i don't know uh we've
had this disagreement before i've always liked rosseter he's like he moves his head and shoulders
in a very like explaining way and like a by the way twin perfect not uploaded a video
since may 4th 2018 so it's been all like over a year and a half now and i miss you guys rosseter
please come back oh my god in my head i was thinking of dude perfect you dude perfect oh my god the
trick shot people uh yeah they do trick shots never they like they do trick shots wait what where
you throw you know like you throw a ball into onto the wall and it lands in a cup and then
they go like oh my god my guess i don't know this my guess is that they're the most profitable
youtube channel in the world that is my guess dude perfect because dude perfect yes i mean they get
insane numbers and what they do is not i mean i respect the work they put in they make props and
they do crazy tricks but we all know they just practice the trip over and over until it works
you like um like the jackie chan thing you seen that uh you seen that yes yeah that every frame
every frame painting with jackie chan now he would just do like hundreds of takes until he got the
shot or the hit or the perfect or broke his leg and i respect it oh yeah or or dies in trying
um well okay that's enough about dude perfect uh that's enough about twin perfect all right here
i got i got something to say about uh a content creator um you know andrew hussey that guy who
made homestuck and so mother things i've heard of him i've heard the name but i've never met the man
but beyond that uh he has opened an instagram account semi recently um and he is a hashtag
eboy now um for his for his 40th birthday i think it was he started being an eboy
tell me more he started to being he started being an eboy on instagram and i followed him
and the the the the posts initially were just like him wearing like extremely young people
hip trendy clothing okay um with sunglasses doing silly poses in front of horses in you know in a
place yeah uh then it was like a bunch of images from him like in a different swag outfit fresh as
fuck you know all that sort of you know and he's just sort of hashtag eboy hashtag hussey like like
is like in places being fresh and it's it's funny it's just it's unironically the best thing he's
made since uh like i don't know cascade yeah so um but then uh like more recently than he started
making these these posts he's been like doing Toblerone hot drops uh they're not hot drops but
like Toblerone secret location find the Toblerone quests he would he would take picture of Toblerone
he would sign them and he would hide them in a place he would take a few pictures of himself
and then like a zoom in on a google map and people would go out and find the Toblerone
and uh this most recent one he was in taiwan i think according to comments so he's in taiwan
put in Toblerone and it was just so funny he he took a picture of the Toblerone
and then he took a picture of a shop and then he took a picture of the bathroom stall of the shop
and then of a painting on the wall so presumably he just shoved a bunch of Toblerone with his name
on it in this in in this bathroom stall uh painting for people to go and find and um the
the last time the first time somebody found the Toblerone the Toblerone uh you know secret quest
thing uh they he said he'll make something canon they want to be canon oh and they said june egg
Bert just generally i guess in homestuck was yeah and and then they said uh make june egg
Bert canon and he said yeah sure june egg Bert is like uh john eggbert but trans cool so like
that's all right so so people went nuts like oh my god june is john just trans now is that what
happened or no i mean it's just it's just a bit of fun like it's not like he hasn't written anything
it's just sort of like yeah sure that's canon and everyone's like yeah and i i just really like this
like so much of like what has followed from homestuck at the decline of homestuck in x6 and
then everything that's followed has been like kind of depressing but i like the fact that
hussey himself is still funny that is cool that is that he's that he's doing this e-boy stuff i'm
gonna i'm gonna link his instagram i just want to see what kind of fresh outfits he's wearing
yeah me too i want to be like i want to be like that i want to be a fresh e-boy
this is disgusting by the way and i don't approve of this this is an old man he used to get into
his coffin and stay there no his name is e-boy hussey instagram.com
e-boy hussey uh fashion girl he looks pretty good for his body he's got the sports yeah he looks
pretty good for his body yeah i i think it was 40 i i mean i heard that's a word i don't actually
know that sounds about right because he's like yeah he's elderly he's about that he's he's uh he's
basically late 30s oh him his his fucking emo striped uh some of these are almost unironically
good or like you would see yeah like people people were like laughing at first but then a few people
like damn oh no my my erotic senses all the one with like with the wings behind yeah exactly that's
the one i was thinking of in in boston there is a an alley near harvard's you're in harvard square
and in this alley on the wall are these pair of like big white wings and uh everybody every
fucking thought or whatever every every femoids gotta have their uh you know their picture of them
in front of those wings and these wings okay not only is that like a really uninspired uh picture
to take like every obviously everybody does that like there but they also suck for like one they're
at the wrong height like they look like they're coming out of your like hips so they're okay they're
too low they're not positioned correctly more importantly they're just bad like they're just
badly painted like the wings are not the same size like one is just longer than the other and
like they're completely lopsided it's like bad execution of a bad idea and uh i hate everything
perspective they look good no no no they're just no no okay no they're they're just they're just
like a fucking hack put them there and nobody had any better ideas so they've just been there
presumably since the dawn of time ain't that just the way it goes but it's a it's an institution
now on boston area social media you gotta see those fucking wings everywhere it's like
the london bridge exactly just gotta blow it up you take a you go to france you take a picture
in front of the eiffel tower you go to boston you get your stupid fucking alley wall wings
how embarrassing for us as a species yeah but of course i see hussy here in front of his cool
like big like tropical parrot wings and he's he's making it work he's dressed for the occasion yeah
i love the little chain he has on he should have a turtleneck really but uh i appreciate the
little chain damn he's actually a little fresh right hello fresh i say when i see hussy go to
go to instagram.com slash eboy hussy and follow all right what do you say voicemails yes yes i was
about to say ye okay all right i think it's about that time ladies and gentlemen uh oh you know
interesting update uh which is just for the we've been i think we said last episode for the longest
time we don't understand why um uh why speakpipe which is where you should leave the voicemails
has just been allowing us to get more and more things despite the service apparently shutting
down and also we have a free account which is supposed to have a cap and we have way too many
voicemails we just got a notice on our speakpipe account that's like hey you have 500 out of your
available 100 megabytes of space filled uh please please empty them or something so i don't know
should we try to empty them or should we just roll the dice and like see if they do anything
we should empty the old ones the only ones that matter are the ones that actually got played on
the show i mean yeah i mean those are all preserved on on the show if nowhere else uh whatever man
it's fine oh preserved we're usually talking over them well okay i have i have a small insignificant
out announcement before we move on okay i yesterday i bought a switch switch yeah
congratulations yeah i'm so excited i'm gonna i i bought it together with fire emblem of three
houses i'm gonna date everyone yes i will be i'll date everyone it's like it's a dating game right
yeah it's a yeah pretty much yeah there's a war in there somewhere i don't know it's it's it's a
dating uh anime game yes mage keep me posted i am playing as long since died yeah long before
mage keep me posted i hear that the blue boy i think is dimitri i hear he's the best and i hear
he's sick as shit so let me know let me know your impression i will i the biggest the biggest
dilemma i will have is like who to romance first i because of course i like at least eight of them
already well i mean this that's the game right the you gotta have to get to know them you have to
you have to pick your favorite you know you gotta you gotta get educated i also have a small
announcement about the Kickstarter which is uh as you know obliterated all barriers again uh right
now it's sitting at ten thousand nine hundred dollars trying to get up to it's almost at one one
one one one one one one one to send that i gotta i'm going to college what does that what does that
actually entail i mean we'll just have to find out oh wait oh no we just passed eleven thousand
just right now right as i was looking at the page it up what is it me um we gotta get to one one
one one i mean i don't know i don't know i mean you know who knows what the future has in store
for this little guy but uh boy if he doesn't if he doesn't get that education if he's not qualified
for a white college job then i i don't know gulp um i mean at least with with the radcon three
Kickstarter we did promise one video if we hit the meme goal of nine thousand dollars nine thousand
one dollars sorry which we did uh but with this i mean oh the possibilities are endless i suppose
i mean i guess all i'll say is that uh one way or another we will we will see what becomes of it
okay all right this poor little sly boy doesn't have a name but that's an education please um
and so he he had a fortune but it was lost in the rain as i understand i mean he had enough to afford
college though i don't know if he actually had enough sorry it had enough okay sly moids very
particular about their pronouns it only please oh then i'm glad that you're shameless enough to
rip off that one joke from undertale with the temi go college i'm glad you're welcome i do feel
the same thing you know you know i didn't think about that but i see it what about what about tiny
baby ben saint does that he him pronouns are used for tiny baby ben saint or uh well i'm i don't know
how's what kind of parent is gun girl gibb any any comment i mean she she raised a gender very
she's she's very she's very conservative she doesn't believe in she believes in traditional
values yeah yeah traditional values it's a gun in every hand in a book in every hand she's teaching
him how to shoot clearly believes in the second amendment she's teaching him how to recite the
flag thing whatever the fuck that is home of the prosperous don't you dare kneel at the football
game don't do it um um i had another oh god i was oh oh the one last thing about that um there
were some people a couple people contact me during the course of it and said you know i'd love to do
it but i can't you know i don't have a credit card or whatever reason i can't do kickstarter so
for for two weeks i will have paypal donations open and you will be able to if you didn't if you
weren't able to do it through the kickstarter you will be able to paypal me the money um just like
check the kickstarter see what the tiers are send me whatever you want you know send me like say what
the tier you want include your your mailing address and you know which tier you're please if you're
out of the united states include shipping mexico and canada two dollars anywhere else five dollars
don't make me hassle you and be like you forgot the shipping guys so yeah for for those people who
weren't able to do kickstarter i'm gonna uh do it's you can get it through paypal for a limited time
that's good that's good yeah that'll be on my on my twitter we'll probably have that pinned um
yep okay that's uh whoo eleven thousand boys eleven thousand and four dollars only ninety three ninety
seven dollars away from a from a prosperous white-collar future time time to roll my other uh most
famous catchphrase that's doable um i'd buy that for eleven thousand one hundred and eleven dollars
uh oh by the way so we're going to the voicemails um speak pipe link down below lose voicemails
okay quick note on the voicemails there were some quality voicemails but alas the audio quality was
too shit notably there was a person who's done this twice i'm sorry do you know who just kicked it over
into eleven thousand do you know who it was who don't know and who i will give you do you want to
guess you'll net was it bungee i don't know it was riddle my ass batman hey what do you know
okay okay welcome to hell truly truly epic okay uh so okay so listen so there's been a girl who's
called in i think twice now telling us about the saga of a girl learning to pee standing up
and this is a this is a tale i want to hear more about but your audio quality is just too
shit oh i see so you gotta you gotta do something about it i just i can i can barely hear you i don't
know but that goes for everybody i'm interested oh okay there was another note so some of these
were too long so this is my little summary section okay never paint heard last episode where i was like
inktober sounds like the never paint lifestyle and go never paint and so never paint left a voicemail
it was fairly long of just being like oh no i actually haven't been doing inktober and i feel
guilty now that's okay fucking tober i went and i checked i believe never paint has in the
style so the voicemail was like i won't sleep i will finish inktober now because i've been told to
you don't need to do that i absolve you of any need to do this because they were very clear she or he
was like i am busy with other things that's why i'm not doing inktober you don't need to do inktober
i don't want to put any pressure on you dog you're working hard already it's clear i'm not so but
but alas alas they had already caught up and clearly had been burning the midnight oil to do this so
i just want to absolve you with whatever little authority i have here since i was the one who
said go go inktober never paint man so okay there you go month tober i'm i'm like two days behind
but i'm gonna do two little drawings today also did by the way check out red noir i just posted a
new page oh yeah that's good stuff i love red noir dude i love red noir it's really great was that
was that smear glass chapter no it's um what's the name of the shraft shraft that's the one that's the
one shraft and gurren by uh yeah yeah please please continue red noir uh give i i forget what's the
name of your of your slime lady who can't speak correctly uh katie katie yes i like katie want
more more draw pornography everyone please you've been destroyed uh okay last last thing i want to
say of these voicemails that were too long or boring to play which is so a mysterious man who
actually we have a voicemail of his but i like i don't know his name i don't know what he really is
there's a guy who's been leaving many voicemails and they're not bad and apparently so on my stream
yesterday he just said like he was like hey nate if someone gets five voicemails on a piece of
episode do they become god and i'm like impossible but if they did yes and apparently this guy has
in fact done that as of last episode so go listen to the last episode apparently five of those were
from one dude i'm a little incredulous though if that's actually true and this person provided no
proof so i'm just saying call it with a better voicemail and prove it does he assume that it was
like of all time like over time no i mean they said like last bcp episode that we played apparently
five of their voicemails was the was the claim here so i mean i find that's it's hard to believe
so okay there's just an opposite prove it is my point i don't believe you um okay with that
enough of the announcements let's get on to the actual voicemails here we go so first one is from
our old friend scumbag chris uh let's see what they have to say for themselves go it's been four
weeks since i left home to become part of a group of you social insects unfortunately the kamikaze
ants wouldn't let me join them since i was too much of a weeb even for them so i've had to scrap
my plan to suicide bomb the pcphq fortunately my many years spent studying the blade made me an
excellent candidate for the leaf cutters and i really did want to see what all the hype for ant
fungus mutualism was about at first they were hesitant to accept a guy who's 185 centimeters
tall and a bipedal mammal but i think they're starting to warm up to me all it really took
was for me to make my intentions clear that i was mainly just there for that sick ass ant pussy
and i landed a job as an apprentice drone so being a leaf cutter ants pretty neat all day it's just
walk to the forest cut some plants bring the pieces back to the nest and feed them to the fungus
i'm surprised by how much the repetitive menial physical labor distracts me from the systemic
inequality of this militant classist regime but more than that it's the fact that i get to smash
that sick ass ant queen pussy for real the queen cast exists to take cock especially in a colony
with no gamer gates and she doesn't even give a shit how laughably minuscule my micro penis is
compared to the other drones ants don't give a fuck okay there you go i good story they sure get
a sure as a i feel i can't wait to see here where this goes i get it too yeah scum bag chris
hey hey tell us more hey mage i see a i see a little i saw something pop up on my little
vapor suit kickstarter backer report there yeah i saw you it can't be true it could yeah some somebody
is somebody somebody pledged to my kickstarter mage who could that be thank you thank you she's
just trying to help an honest sly moid get an education i wanted to pledge earlier but i was
saying well for that switch so i wasn't sure if i had some to spare but i did the money's not for
you ben it's for the sly moid it is i've told uh christine that all proceeds are going to uh the
new lost angel city aka new milwaukee emergency rain relief fund so uh that 300 dollars education that
300 dollars is just off the table you know they needed they needed more than me you know that that
that favorable exchange rate we got to make it work while we still can slime will become the next
president yeah mage have you ever played a game called forager by any chance oh hold on i'm gonna
go but it sounds familiar it's it's it's one of these monotonous grindy games where you start off
with like no tools on an island no i haven't i looked at looked into it and like it seems like
something i would like but at the same time there's things i would not like about it so no i didn't
try it the so i first read about this game from um uh what's his name what's discount
matthew matthew matthew matthew's his name oh andrew dobbson joseph anderson joseph anderson
Yeah, I still never watched Noah, but yeah, Joseph Anderson, he made his travel logs.
I have I never watched him one day. I should check him out. But Joseph Anderson made a video
about forager. I found it interesting. So I went and I got it. And it that game is like
it's probably the most addictive game I've ever played. It's similar to cookie clicker,
but as a better gameplay loop such that like, there's a point where you hit like the curve
where you it takes a while to like increase and expand and do other stuff after you've
like bought all the land. And I've hit that. And then I just wiped my game and replayed
it up to that point, like three times, because it's just addictive. And oh, my, my famous
me a math of a two video, I have no time and I must game is about the addiction to this
to this very game. But okay, nonetheless, so it's fun, but it's a total waste of time.
It's just a satisfying gameplay loop is the only is the only good thing about it. It
is satisfying. Okay, next voicemail. I'm scared actually to play. I mean, it's not worth
your money. I don't play it. It's literally when I when I make fun of people who play
games and games as a complete time sink, this is the epitome of the time sink with like
in the same way as cookie clicker or monster clicker, any of those derivative games. Okay,
whatever. Anyway, next voicemail, this is from it was an inside job. Okay, go. Hi PCP.
I've got a question. As a content creator, what do you think is the right strategy to
incorporate? Patreon, should you have it from the beginning and as your audience grows,
you grow to, or should you wait till your audience grows and then introduce it once
you've kind of developed a following? Thanks. I think what do you think that the best way
to do it wait until and this is cynical and I didn't do this, but I wish I had I wish
I had had wait, you know, grow an audience. First, don't have it from the beginning.
Wait until something bad happens to you and then announce that you started a Patreon because
something bad happened to you. But Ben, what if nothing bad happens then you're fucked.
Pray for tragedy and strike. You can have it and if you just don't talk about it that much and
then bring it up when a bad thing happens to you, then that could also work. Yeah, that's true.
I think in terms of like, like actual strategy, if you're going into like making a career in the
internet stuff, probably on YouTube, I'm assuming, then you want to like gain a following first and
then announce it when it's you're pretty big. You want to be like at the peak when it's like
you're you've made your best video yet and loads of people love you and then say, hey guys,
if you want to support me because like if you leave the ability for people to support you off
the table, they the yearning grows strong and people who would support you are more likely to
support more. It seems to be from what I've seen from from the the small amount of cases where
this has happened, where a channel has gotten incredibly like good vibes from the from, you
know, their fan base, they got loads of subscribers, they got, you know, pretty solid niche. And then
they announced their Patreon as just sort of like a thing. They don't even need to do much
marketing about it. They just need to mention it. And then those people will jump on it.
It seems seems to work in that in that order. It's kind of a complicated question. I think it
I think there is another thing. If somebody if somebody is very small, they don't have a lot
of subscribers and have a lot of stuff, and they have a Patreon link and they say at the end of
every video, I habitually will go and click on that link to see how pathetic they are. And if
they're extremely pathetic, I'm going to be like, right. And I don't really need to do that. It's
not like I was planning to pledge to them if they had a lot of money already. It's just sort of a
thing I do. And it's a it's another way people can speak. It's all about marketing. It's all
optics, right? Like that's the entire game. And if you you don't, you if you're small, you don't
want to advertise that you're small. And the worst thing you can do is just be starting out and
having a Patreon with zero dollars, because it just reinforces the fact that you don't have any
cloud. And that's a bad look. So you just don't want you don't because also, if you have like
that one person who's interested, and they click on your Patreon, and there's nothing,
that's the absence of social proof and will disincentivize them from wanting to actually
support you. So sad, but true. What you want to do is you want to wait until you have people
starving to actually support you anyway. Like you should wait till at least you have 1000
followers subscribers, like a big enough volume that like when you say I have
a Patreon, you'll get like five to 10 people do it immediately. And then the barrier is broken
and it's all up from there. I don't disagree with that. I just like
if we're talking about like small ish amounts of money, I mean by that, by that I just mean
like anything like under, I don't know, like 500 bucks or like under like 1000 dollars. Like I
guess I'm just wondering like who, what's the intention of this? Because like if your intention
is to like make this a job, I would say that like it doesn't matter, because no matter when you make
it, you're not going to make enough to live on until you're like significantly popular.
Like more popular than like me at this very time. You need to be like a big boy marketing. Like if
you're if you're trying to do it as a job and you're not making any money, like you're probably
working a day job anyway. You don't you don't have to make enough to be like a middle class
income for Patreon to be worth having. No, but I mean that's why that's why like the question
it kind of depends, because if you're if you're trying to like live off of it exclusively,
then I would say the answer is it doesn't really matter, because you have to get
we're talking about ways to maximize how much money you'll get.
It's the idea is the idea is that when you're growing during that period, if you have a Patreon
at maximum, you'll have like a few patrons. And later you will have more patrons because
your audience will be bigger. But right, it's sort of like an explosion that happens. If you
start if you open the Patreon, it's like when you're big, you get more than if you had been
gradually accumulating them because of the marketing thing. Yeah, I mean, I suppose.
But then I firmly believe that's true. It's not always like a terrible thing. Like the the
podcast, we're not huge. Right. And we have our Patreon. I mean, people do know us from other
things that definitely plays a part. But we can get like a couple thousand to like 10,000 views
on a video. Yeah, pretty, you know, in that range, it falls to you know, depending on how
hype the chapter is, it goes up and down. Indeed, indeed. But like, that's a significant audience
that is consistent. You know, it's not like we're getting like 10 to 100 views per video.
We're actually we have like a fan base in that way. So like having the Patreon at that point is
you don't need to be having hundreds of thousands before you start. You just need to have
some sort of audience that is, you know, not like incidental. I think it's not a number.
I honestly do. Yeah. I mean, because like the problem is like it's all this is all about
social proof. And it's all about like, before you can have it be like, this is worth paying for,
you have to approve it's worth watching. You know, that's the first goal. So like getting a
consistent view count and getting getting people to come back. That's the step one. Then you can
focus on monetizing it. Because you already have people you've already you've proven that it works,
right? Because like monetizing something that isn't proven in this kind of like method where
you're writing on cloud and you're writing on basically like forming a cult, that's what Patreon
is, you make a cult essentially, like there has to be like actual interest there. So if you well,
what if you're making content that's really good? I know some people like this, you're making great
content that you believe in, you just feel undiscovered, but like you're getting very low
views like sub like 50 views, right? You know, that's, we're not talking about quality, we're
talking about social proof. There's, but it's all it all matters. But there are tons of great people
out there who make incredibly good content that nobody cares about. This is about being cared
about. This is not about making something good. They're two separate things. I mean, but we're
just, we're talking about like maximizing and I agree, it could match, but like, we're at such
low percentage at like the very start of the career that I really wonder how like, is that $5
that you might win or lose at the very beginning of your career really makes such a big difference
when we all know what actually makes a difference at the end? Why are you, why are you arguing our
point as though you're disagreeing? Because I think I do? I don't know. The point is to wait
until you get at least a thousand subscribers or something to that effect before you open a Patreon.
Don't start it from the beginning. Well, wait until you have an audience,
wait until the moment when you can ride a wave of goodwill, whether you release like a really big
project that gets a really good reception that you think will, or like I said, if like, oh, YouTube,
I got YouTube struck, I got demonetized, my videos get demonetized, my last video got taken down
because trolls, trolls reported and it got demonetized or something. I've been victimized,
now's the time, whatever, we don't know. I know that's cynical, but I've seen it work.
You know, something that will give you a wave of like community goodwill
that you can coincide with and I've released a Patreon and that's how you do it. That's how you
maximize your return. I just don't see that much difference between saying I just created my Patreon
in this moment and here is my existing Patreon. Well, no, that's true. I guess. But I guess it's
okay, you can make it whenever you want. Don't push it until you have an audience.
I suppose. If you're putting your Patreon in front of people's eyes and you have like
one patron and it's your mom, then it's like, yeah. It's the same thing like when you go to Amazon
and you see a product that has like no reviews, like you're just put off by even like purchasing
it because like there's no social proof. The social proof there matters because there's a
quantifiable metric that you expect in that format. So if you go to Patreon and you see zero
patrons and this is a small creator, you're just, there's no social proof. So your monkey brain
naturally assumes that this is bad or not worth my money. And even if you were going in there with
the intention of giving a dollar, seeing the zero, seeing nothing makes you feel less inclined to do
so because we're herd creatures and the fact that no one else has done it makes you feel less
likely to do it. It's all about marketing and branding and optics. Do not start until you have
an audience. Period. Yeah. You know, I agree. I realize the only way that I feel differently is
because because we're talking about such beginning of career situations here, I feel like I just
wouldn't want to encourage people to put off a job to later that they could do today. I have seen
people like too hesitant to start. Like Nightmare Masterclass didn't start a Patreon for a long
time, even though he had like, you know, like his Petscop investigation series was getting a lot of,
but it wasn't until like that, it wasn't until that series, like even though it was popular and
getting viewed and people loved it, he didn't start a Patreon until like well after it was over.
And I think he was just like, oh, I'm not big enough yet. I'm not big enough yet. It's like,
no, he was definitely big enough at that point. He could have been doing it. My fucking boy,
limit breakers, like my current like favorite YouTuber, just like these crazy insane Dark Souls
edits and they're like the best videos on the platform. He like just made a Patreon at like,
he had like 274,000 subscribers. That's way too late. Don't wait that long. I guess he just decided
now is the time to get money, I guess. This will be good to have. Yeah, and it's kind of a shame
because it's like Dark Souls 3. I mean, I don't know whether he does Sakura videos. He's done
some here and there. Like all of the videos that he's like, the game's really old now. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, hopefully Elden Ring. I mean, this guy, he's insane. He will succeed at whatever he tries to
do. He's just that good. I love him so much, but it's Elden Ring, right? Yeah. That's right. That's
right. Did you hear that George RR Martin is writing for it? Yeah. He's doing all the work.
Okay. I don't know if I got, okay, whatever. My friend told me that and it blew my fucking mind.
It is interesting. It's gonna be pretty legit, hopefully. Yeah, that's really cool. We'll have
to see. We'll have to see. Okay. I hope there's dialogue that I like. There's always been dialogue
I like. Okay. Next voicemail. Get ready for this because this is the Tom Oliver secret agenda.
Looking forward to hearing that. All right. Here we go. Man, I kind of just wanted to
fuck Western society and the ass bitch. That's it. That's it. Wait, and the what bitch? I think he said
I wanted to fuck Western society in the ass bitch. I believe was the full phrase there. Tom, what do
you have to say? Okay. Sounds like something I can kill a first Friday night doing. Let's make it
happen. Western society, call in with your response, please. Yeah, let us know. Oh, speaking of
responses. Okay, good news, guys. As we requested, as a response to the grammar, was it the grammar
Nazi, the grammar fascist, grammar Antifa is calling in with response. So let's see what grammar
Antifa has to say in rebuttal. Okay, go. Hello, it's me, grammar Antifa. I buy books about slaves so
I can burn them and set history free. I'm calling in to address the political enemy, the grammar
fascist, who appeared in last week's episode. What grammar fascism fails to understand about
communication is that it is a dance. An improvisational duet, the code's meaning through
language. Unlike real dance, however, if there is not an understanding, both parties are at fault.
You take an idea, you encode that idea, the second party receives the coded language and then
decrypts it back into an idea. If the second party's idea is too different from the intent,
both the encryptor and the decryptor failed in communication. The encryptor did not make their
message simple and clear enough and the decryptor failed to extrapolate true meaning due to
ignorance. Those who are good at communication are good at both standardized rule sets need not
apply. Fact of the matter is that if true meaning is found to communication was a success. The sheer
fact they were able to tell they had fucked up means that there was no miscommunication about
what they were saying. English is controlled by the people and how they use it naturally evolves
over time. Rule set doesn't fucking matter. Address miscommunications directly. Instead of
being caught up in pedantic semantics, I imagine plague you on a daily basis. I can only assume
you're getting pissy with your far more chad-minded friends talking casually in a discord or some
shit. They're writing messages exclusively for the friend group and no one on the outside.
Shut the fuck up, piss boy. The dictionary is a guideline. Your high school English teacher
is a hack and the soy-guzzling skinhead language prescriptivist just got yeeted on by the
Zoomer cacophony that is language descriptivism. Vote single person pronoun they as word of the
year, hashtag dabble my haters, and dating white is not all right. Grammar Antifa signing out.
Thank you, Grammar Antifa. Well, I love this person, and I would say that they're completely
right. You mispronounced cacophony, so every point you made is in there. I'm sorry. I can't
understand what you mean because you mispronounced cacophony. You failed to your half of the dance,
Grammar Antifa. How did they pronounce cacophony? They said cacophony. They said caca- fucking
digi-style cacophony. Was that supposed to be a digi-reference, or was that legit fuck up? No,
no, no. That's a super bunny hop reference. Oh, yeah, that's right. Actually, do you think that was
actually a reference, like, deliberate? No, no. I kind of think so, but I don't know. I mean,
like, super bunny hop may said cacophony in one of his videos, like, straight face, he didn't
realize, and then he got so much shit for it that every time there's a word that he could
potentially mispronounce, he does, he has a robot say it, and that's like a running thing in his
videos now. That's a good bit though. I like, I like, no, this, do you guys agree with this? I
agree with this. It is a failure of communication. I mean, I think I would say that the burden is
probably more on the person speaking to make their message understood. I don't know if I'd say the
blame is 50-50. I think that like, the message here is correct, but I think all the rules and
structures are serving to make the speaker and the recipient's job easier by having a standardized
set of rules that you stick to, so you don't have to spend as much time encrypting or decrypting
the message. That's the whole point of grammar rules in the first place. You're right. I think it's
an interesting point that the fact that you can comment on the, on the quote-unquote mistake
means that there was no failure, that you do know what they meant. I think that's an interesting
idea to point out. It's probably true to some extent. Like the fact that you can be like,
you know, obviously you meant T-H-E-Y, apostrophe-R-E means you do know what they meant.
So fuck, yeah, that's a good point. But here's the bad news though. In anticipation of Antifa
calling in, we have another voicemail from this person is known as grammar, a white
identitarian with nationalist traits. Let's, let's see what this individual has to say.
All right, go. All right, Nate said someone should send in a bash the grammar bash. However,
I am here in having anticipated that to respond to the bash the grammar bash with my rehash the
grammar bash. Listen, it's just really annoying when people put like use the wrong form of your
or there. It's just annoying. We don't need to justify it. It just puts like two seconds in
effort and just rub your fucking brains together and figure it out. Just, just don't be a fucking
war on phones. As always, a stellar point from the far right. That's pretty convincing. Yeah.
He used, he used simple vernacular and I understood his message. So, you know, he's got a point.
I think he succeeded at communicating better than grammar and use too many big words.
It scares me and intimidates me. I like that. I do like big words. I feel smart when I understand
them like cacophony. The debate rages on. I may I'm a grammar centrist. Damn, that's a big brain
position. I'm a grandma. All right, next one. We've got another update from a not even cluster
punk can save me now. Let's let's check in with him. Go. Shit. Shit. I've been on the run for the
last seven days straight. There's not much time. I didn't have time to leave you guys a warning
last week. The PC police were hacking me when I leaked your search histories. So now they have
all your locations. There's no time before they make a move. They're going to be. Wait, no. No, no,
no, I'm not going back. You'll never take me alive. No, no, no.
Is this thing on? Well, it is. Welcome, PCP members. This is the PC police.
I am one of the four elite generals in charge of taking down your operation.
Our first target will be the man we've deduced to most likely be the leader best guy ever.
No, it's digi. It's digi.
This is Dachshund.
Early intervention can make a lifetime of difference. Learn the signs at autismspeaks.org.
Next time, we'll be talking about Ghost in the Shell standalone complex, the best anime ever.
How embarrassing. How did we get here? What a journey.
It just kept going. Maybe that was the true attack by the PC police.
Yeah, me too. I think that was the true attack by the PC police to shame me for my
continued delays on certain projects. That was their assault. I don't want them after me. I'm
glad they think you're the leader. That had about as much effect as a Kersjehame Ha on my
soul over here. I'll try to recover. There's only one Polish guy. Once they got you either done,
they don't need to go after anyone else. Any other guys? Don't worry about it. Yes.
Although Poland and Lithuania. It's all his fault.
All right. Next one, we've got PC Pi is calling in.
What does PCP stand for? Well, I'll tell you. It stands for professional
subit peruiners because you ruined my fucking bit. All right, let's try this again.
Everybody come to a consensus and pick a whole number between one and 244. Thanks.
Is there any way we can fuck him over again? Like a whole number?
Is a fraction a whole number? Is a fraction a whole number?
How about 144? Is he still like 144? Sure. Yeah, that was the runner up last time.
That was the runner up. Mage said 66, but that's two Star Wars referencing for me.
Okay. Gib, Tom, what do you like? 144. I'm trying to think of
relevant numbers that are cool in between 0 and 244. I don't think there is one. I think all
the numbers between 0 and 244 are lame. In between 244. What about 151 in homage for the original?
Wait, wait, wait. 119, 119. 119. That's fine. That's 9-11 in UK dates.
Are we in agreement? 119, 119. Good. Sure. That's fine. All right, done. There it is.
There's your answer. 119, PC Pie, or whatever you were called last time. There's your answer.
Okay, good. Moving on, we got... We don't know. I don't know. He's going to add 10 to it,
and then he's going to divide it by three, and then he's going to say fuck you.
Is this your number? And we'll say how do you get... Wow, you got the same number back after
an operation designed to do that. Fascinating. Well, tell us, I can't wait to be dazzled.
But in the meantime, calling in is The Spirit of Halloween, which is perfect timing,
because we could use some of that. All right, let's hear you have to say. Go.
Go back to Grinch Night.
October's the season where all breathings emerge just to bring joy and horror to people's hearts.
I'm the spirit of Halloween. I encourage you to go out and complete this Halloween bucket list.
Kara Pumpkin, Data Witch, Give Pumpkin Spice Latte, Performance Seance,
Watch Soulweeder, Do Graffiti, Read Edgar Allan Poe, Kill a Man, Attend Costume Party,
Wear a Blackface, Go Trick or Treating, and Eat Lots of Candy. I've been the spirit of Halloween.
There you go, everybody. Really? Really, that made the cut?
It's your full bucket list. It wasn't great, but it was seasonal.
I told you to be picky this week.
It was seasonal. I loved the season. It was August in Halloween.
The only season here is the spice latte.
We do not endorse any of the views of the spirit of Halloween.
No, definitely not.
So just clarifying. Just clarifying that.
Quite the opposite.
This shows beyond a shadow of a doubt that Halloween season.
Yeah, thanks for proving my point, Mr. Spirit, sir.
This one, okay, this one's short. I can't remember what this is. It's a PC promise.
Oh, wait, I think I remember. Okay, it's a PC promise play.
Listen here, you fox. Vote Andrew Yang.
I will pledge 100 a month to your fucking Patreon.
Thank you.
Wait.
Well, okay, so right there. Ben, you are already possibly going to vote for Yang.
No.
If you just do that, I think he'll just give us $100 on the Patreon.
I'll vote for Andrew Yang.
You can give $100 to my Patreon, because I'll actually do it.
Here's all vote for Yang.
Is this illegal, by the way? Is it illegal to sell your vote?
I'm pretty sure it's illegal to sell your vote, but I'll do it.
But let's do it anyway.
I would do it if I thought I would actually get $100 or even my proportional fraction of $100.
This is just a coincidental exclusive exchange.
It has nothing to do with paying for the vote.
Right, totally unrelated.
Here's the thing. Here's the thing about buying votes.
When you're in the booth, nobody can know what you're doing.
So you could take the money and just not vote the way they want you to.
Yeah.
I guess they'll break your legs if they lose or something.
Maybe.
If they lose.
Yeah, well, this guy listens to the PCP.
I don't think there's going to be a problem.
Damn.
He sounds like he's 90 pounds soaking wet, if you know what I'm saying.
If I thought that I stood to gain, I don't know,
whatever fraction of that $100 would end up going to be.
10 bucks, maybe.
I don't know.
Yeah, 10 or 20 or whatever.
If I thought I would do it, I would sell my vote.
Right, because my vote is individually weak.
It's not yet.
But I don't think I'll get it.
I'm calling this bluff.
No.
You won't do it.
Don't say that.
It's a scam.
It's a sham.
And I'm a Bernie guy.
It's a scam.
It's a sham.
Vote Bernie.
Vote Bernie, where yang?
That's my slogan.
Are you at all...
Bernie just had like a heart attack or something.
Is he doing okay?
He had an operation.
He had a heart operation.
He's doing okay.
His poll number is not so much.
Well, I guess I'm not surprised.
Warren's the leader.
She's the front runner.
I hear us with one.
Shut up, Mage.
Shut the fuck up.
No, you should have.
I mean, Mage has nothing,
has no horse in this race, literally.
She's not even American.
So, you know, what can you say?
Well, neither am I.
I don't know.
I mean, I heard...
It's not that I'm just falling asleep.
Not because of you guys.
I told, like, at the beginning,
I'm just, like, extremely tired right now.
That is a personal problem, Mage.
We feel the same time every week,
so we bear no responsibility.
I know.
Okay, we'll go.
I set my sleep schedule just for you guys.
I appreciate that.
I heard that Bernie's heart trouble
was not, like, an immediate life-threatening thing
or anything.
It's not like his heart's gonna stop anytime sooner.
I mean, he is old.
Well, in the great scheme of things.
I'm sure I know he could die.
Like, this is...
Obviously, this is always a possibility.
Anyone can die.
Yeah.
But...
Yeah, Ben.
Makes me mad.
Why is he, like, I have fucking bad experience on that.
He's still on the campaign trail.
Pretty sure he's still doing all this shit,
so that's great.
Okay, great.
Great.
Thanks for ruining our country, uh, everyone.
All right.
Blame Bernie for not having...
Oh, remember the senator from Metal Gear Rising?
How he had that fucking Super Armistall...
Yeah, the original...
The original Magamon.
...Nanomachines?
Now, that's what Bernie should do.
He should just pull a senator Armstrong,
and start the war economy up,
because God knows we could use it.
All right, let's move on.
He doesn't even like that guy.
Oh, that's why he's going to lose,
because he's not even utilizing the war economy
to its full extent.
Put some brains in vets.
I always felt a senator Armstrong was like Milhouse.
You know, Milhouse...
In that one episode where they go to the future,
Milhouse was canonically jacked as shit,
and was super ripped, and...
Except his damn ankles,
because that's the hardest place to add mass, damn it.
And how dare you judge him for it?
That happened in that episode.
All right, next, next voicemail.
Is that the one where Lisa becomes president?
No, I don't think so.
She's going to get married in this one,
and then did it at the end?
Is that the one with Hugh?
Like a monkey's paw.
Yeah, like her British fianc or something from school.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Do you know that according to Christine Weston Chandler,
Lisa Simpson will be president in 2020?
I heard about that.
I do.
And so maybe Bernie is going to die,
but Lisa's going to show up with an equally progressive agenda.
Okay, just point of order, though.
Lisa is eight years old canonically,
which is under the age of, you know...
Not in...
Look, ask Chris.
Like, I don't think so.
All right, all right.
Fair enough.
Okay.
We got another one.
Okay, a little baby one from Timmy Sorris.
Let's see what this is about.
She's been there for like 20 years now.
Well, yeah.
Maybe he's incorporating the like.
Yeah, but in, you know, 1998...
97 or whatever it is.
When the episode aired,
she would have been, you know, 30, whatever, in 2020.
Now that...
But now that it is 2020,
she's still eight, but...
Perhaps, perhaps like...
But not in that one episode.
Maybe when the dimensional merge happens,
all timelines will like merge into a single streamline,
like single time progression.
So like, Lisa will age up to a proper age in our dimension.
Do you know, do you remember like how...
I think there was a YouTuber who did a Simpsons lore thing.
Was it the real Jim?
He like...
I can't remember.
I love the real Jim.
There was a video.
There's a video where he explains like,
or he shows that like a Homer and Marge's relationship,
you know, back when they were kids.
It used to be in the 80s or the 70s.
Then it was the 80s.
It was the 90s.
Yeah.
Soon they'll be having like a millennial childhood upbringing.
Oh, right.
He had...
It's true.
Yeah, that's the real Jim's.
He did...
He does Simpsons histories where he talks,
looks at like the timelines, past, present, and future.
He just released...
Well, a couple weeks ago, he released...
He had a series of like,
who really shot Mr. Burns?
And he just released like the final piece of it.
And he lays out five different theories for like,
like the canonical explanation is that Maggie shot Mr. Burns?
Right.
But he makes...
He actually makes like four different compelling...
No, five different compelling cases for why actually that's a fake out.
No, actually Bart shot Mr. Burns.
No, actually Lisa shot Mr. Burns.
No, actually Homer shot Mr. Burns.
What's this guy's name again, Ben?
The real Jim's.
The real...
I'm watching that shit because I fucking love that episode.
The only good Simpsons YouTuber.
Period.
They all...
He's the only one.
That's great.
I just noticed that it says it's Simpsons mysteries,
who really shot Mr. Burns finale.
Was this like a series of videos?
Well, yeah, he did five episodes,
like one episode is Bart, one episode is Grandpa,
and so on and so forth.
It's...
Each one is a different theory.
Well, I gotta fucking check this shit out.
Those are really good.
Post a link of that.
Here, I've got the video.
This is the finale.
So don't watch this one first, I guess.
Maybe I'll find the updated one.
Okay, boom.
In the audio links, there you go.
And I'm gonna go watch more.
I'm gonna watch these after we run here.
Do you like the Simpsons?
And I love the Simpsons.
I would encourage anyone to check out the real...
I think he's got like 40k followers,
or like 30k subscribers.
He's got 50k, it looks like.
Oh, okay, he's growing, that's good.
There you go.
I mean, it's such a niche market,
I can't see him getting that much bigger than that,
unfortunately.
People love their big video,
analyzing one possibly beloved piece of media
in thorough detail,
and possibly teaching us about life
and lessons beyond the mere panels of the artistry.
I don't know, whatever.
Okay, anyway, voicemail, Timisaurus, go right now.
Son of George Soros?
I feel like I'm the only fucking one
who fucked PCP through the YouTube search bar
by typing in meme podcast.
That's it.
That's the whole message.
We were talking about how people found us last time.
Is, man, could that be true?
Is that possible?
Let me try it right now, meme.
Oh, that's a great idea.
My podcast.
I want to try it too.
Let me see how far down I have to scroll to find...
I mean, I see...
Oh, wait, I'm logged in as the PCP.
It's lots of...
It's lots of H3H3.
What, who are you logging in?
Okay, to be fair...
I logged in as myself.
To be fair, it might not have been directly
from the search result.
You could have clicked on something
and, like, in the related, eventually,
it found the PCP, but it started...
Yeah, I didn't know if I exactly had one.
We must have an episode that has meme in the title,
so I'm assuming that you found...
Memes that need to die.
It's right here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The Professor's Podcast, episode 16.
Wait, you got it on a search?
Yeah, it's way down, but there it is.
Memes that need to die.
That could be it.
That could be the avenue right there.
Oh, fuck, what's the thumbnail on that again?
It's a bunch of our icons and the old logo,
and it just says in green text,
PCP, episode 16, Memes that need to die.
Oh, yeah, it just says, like, the green text thing.
I can't find it, but I'm sure you're not lying.
Check the playlist.
It's episode 16.
No, no, no, I mean on the search.
Oh, yeah, yeah, okay, okay.
Well, there you go.
There's one avenue.
Okay, we got two more voicemails.
Let's burn through them.
Okay, here we go.
This is Poo's Adventures in Communist Hell, episode one.
Episode one.
Let's see what Poo has in store for us.
Take it away.
Hello, it's now time for another one
of Poo's Adventures in Communist Hell.
Please enjoy.
Yay.
I am so excited.
There it is.
Feels good.
My dad's home.
Yeah.
Peglet, I've got a rumble in my tumble.
Do you want to join me for a sport of honey?
Dear Poo, we don't have any honey.
You ate it all.
Hi, Peglet, I knew.
But what if we went looking for some honey?
Poo, I'm a little tender as a bitch.
I'm too scared to go on a adventure
to find some honey.
Peglet, I'm going to find some honey.
And I bet to see you right behind me.
What else?
Dear, dear, I just hope we don't run into that
Christopher Robin boy again.
Thank you.
And please look forward to the next episode.
Goodbye.
Yeah.
I loved it.
Guys, I cracked the code.
Memes podcast.
Memes plural.
Third one down is our podcast.
Oh, OK.
OK.
When you do memes podcast.
E.
I did.
I did a venture.
Yeah, OK.
It's for me, it's like the eighth one down or ninth.
But yeah, I did find it on the unjust meme.
It was down.
I had scrolled past it.
It's down maybe like 20 or so.
I did a good job.
Good work team.
More importantly, Poo, tell me more.
That wasn't communist enough.
I think he's warming up to it.
Now, is it communist because of the honey shortage?
Perhaps that's where the honey shortage is exactly.
They have to go foraging because the supply lines have failed.
I don't know.
The honey lines have dried up.
There's no more.
I don't know.
I remind me.
I saw Christopher Robin.
Just reminds me of my own depiction.
And the boy, the human.
My own depiction of something that you might call communist hell
in the pages of my nightstar, phantom horn,
strawberry milk, New Los Angeles City, and less war comic.
Indeed, indeed.
And their musical number.
Neath the city.
Oh, yeah.
Slime left us wanting.
So now we're haunting the bourgeoisie.
I was delighted to see that wisely strawberry milk and phantom horn
knew better than to accept the temptress that is the human nature
defying evil system that is communism.
No, no, they are firmly entrenched in neoliberalist capitalism.
They are in that mind cage for life.
Well, there's always hope for tomorrow.
So things you learn in a question.
Well, OK.
Pooh, keep us updated.
Looking forward to episode two, Piglet Godspeed.
OK.
We've got one last one.
This is brief.
This is from a little guy named One Second Voicemail.
Let's see.
You were yesterday.
Merciful.
All right.
See you in the next one, PCP.
Yeah.
And with that, that's it.
Thank you, everyone.
That's been another episode of The Proof.
Crastinators podcast.
In my head, I was imagining like the firstest dab caught on film.
Yes.
All right.
You're done.
Patreon.com.
You think that was in response to what we were talking about
before about the One Second YouTube video?
I think it was.
I think it was inspired by that.
That's my guess.
And it should be done.
Someone should still get out there and do it.
Maybe next time he'll give us another One Second Voicemail
episode two.
All right.
Thanks, guys.
See you next time.
We can only hope.
All right.
Patreon.com.
Slash the procrastinators.
$1.
Patreon.
Bonus lounge.
Good times.
$5.
Bonus episodes.
There's 30 of them.
Another one coming soon.
Do you want to talk about it?
It'll be up by the time this goes up, right?
Well, the last one's already up.
The next one, no.
It's only the 13th.
We don't put it out till the first.
So we might film it before then.
But no, we're not even...
We're actually filming it after this episode goes up.
So no, we'll keep them waiting.
We'll keep them waiting.
We have something more in the oven right now, cooking.
And it'll be a good time.
It will be a good time.
Something to look forward to, actually.
I think people will be excited about it.
And yeah, that's it.
So also follow us at tpcrastinators on Twitter.
And that's all there is to it.
Okay.
See you next week, everybody.
Thanks for being here.
Another episode in the can.
See you then.
Bye.
Bye, Dustin.
Good night, everybody.