I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Hello, I am the Nostalgia Critic and this is my host, the best guy ever.
What's up? It's me, the best guy ever.
Turning red should have been about 9-11.
Is that a thing?
You must not have been looking at Twitter this week. That was a big funny thing this week.
Was it Mr. Enter's review of Turning Red said it was bad that it didn't properly reflect the fact that it takes place in 2002,
and that to reflect that, paranoia over 9-11 should have been a big theme of the movie.
What the fuck?
I don't know. I don't know.
I've seen bits and bobs about Mr. Enter being a horrible, terrible idiot.
But I already knew that, so I guess it's not that interesting.
It's funny, people lost their minds at him for this unbelievable take,
and on Twitter he responded by being like,
Jenny Nicholson put it best, his response was basically,
I've had way even worse opinions than this, and I can't believe this is what you're all mad at me about.
He's like, I'm literally an anti-vaxxer, and you guys are mad about this at me?
Fuck you!
And it's just great.
I don't know what drives a person to do that and be like that.
Oh yes, and Mr. Enter, one of Nate's aliases.
Yes, I remember.
Oh shit, did I say that out loud?
Well, you got, you killed him.
He's Mr, Mr, more like the best guy Enter.
What?
The best guy Enter the building, ladies and gentlemen.
Uh, I, what was it?
So this week, I did something, I just, I just, just as I finished before we started recording,
I finished, putting the finishing touches on what I was working on all this week,
I took a break away from doing the formatting on the Slime and Punishment book,
because I was drawing a guest page for Tales Gets Trolled.
Oh yes.
If you can believe, I spent a whole week, I spent a whole week doing that.
How big is the page?
It's not one book page.
It's like, can be huge because it's intimate.
No, it's like long, it's like long.
Here, I'll show, I'll show you my, my page.
Or, uh, yeah, mine was 18 panels.
Oh my God.
Yeah, so it's, it's not like one book page.
That's, that's more like, like three or four or five pages?
More four pages.
Probably, probably something like that.
Um, I think, I think this will have been published on the website by the time this episode comes out,
so it's probably fine to show it, but I'll link in the description to the page if it is,
uh, released on the website.
Um, so yeah, I spent like a whole week drawing this because I wanted to make it really good.
Meanwhile, back to Coyote.
Yeah.
In a great yard.
So, um, I had to, I had to catch up.
I am caught up on the story of Tales Gets Trolled, by the way.
It has, there's a lot, there's a lot that has happened since, um, like when I did the
lecture on it, uh, although they're still locked in battle.
Like Coyote and Demaro are still locked in the battle.
It's like the same day.
Uh, but I mean, there's like chapters and chapters and chapters have gone by.
I will eventually get around to, to reading it all.
Yeah.
I, at some point, I just sort of stopped because it was, it was getting, I mean, obviously
it's like, it's stupid, but like I feel like some of the gut buster, like I can't believe
this is a comic moments were very early on.
I don't know if like it continues to be as hilarious as it goes.
It continues to be, it continues to be very like shonen battle anime.
It also continues to be, you know, it has, it has, there's cutaways to like a bunch of
like trolls talking about like the ramifications of the battle and like they're kind of pursuing
their own side missions and whatever.
And those are like, you know, weird and bizarre and all the trolls look ridiculous and stuff.
Uh, the battle between, the cosmic battle between God and Satan continues to be a central
focus of the, of the plot.
Uh, I requested, because on the, on the semi official, um, audio books that one guy is
making on YouTube, I was, I was given the voice of Satan.
I voiced Satan in the scene where they, they drink the blood and get the neutral powers.
So I asked, um, I asked Emmergram if he had a page with Satan in it that I could draw.
And he was like, as a matter of fact, I'm like editing one right now.
Uh, so he gave me this page.
What happens in this page?
Okay.
So previously, after four reasons that are too complicated to get into, Coyote does some
stuff, but he like exhausts himself and he's, and he's going to faint.
So instead of fainting out in the real world, he off screen sort of puts himself into his
book world and then he falls to the ground in the book world.
But Demaro, he also put Demaro and the ghost of Gary into his book world.
So now Coyote is unconscious on the ground in the book world and Demaro is there and
Demaro tries to get to him, but also passes out unconscious while attempting to go and
kill Coyote.
Uh, and the ghost of Gary is here and he doesn't like either of them.
Uh, so that's, and then there's a cutaway to Satan.
Uh, and then some, some things happen.
Things.
And that's, and that's my page.
Yeah.
I spent all week drawing it.
Uh, and I'm pretty proud of it.
It's very good.
Yeah.
I'm, I'm very happy.
I'm very happy with how it came out.
Some, some guest artists, some guest artists try to duplicate, uh, you know, the, the laser
bot style of drawing.
And sometimes it works.
And sometimes it, I think it just doesn't, like they can't quite do it.
And it ends up kind of just looking bad anyway.
I decided not to even bother with doing that because I thought, I don't think I could do
it.
It would actually be harder to like try and make it look like exactly the way laser bot
draws.
So I just drew it like the way I would draw.
I was like, fuck it.
Yeah.
Um, although I maintained the, um, the, like the shape, the shape of the text boxes and
the formatting of the text boxes and like the fonts used for the text.
I used all that the same way, but, um, the drawings are just the way that I would do
it.
And, uh, um, I'm very, I'm very, I'm very pleased.
I can't wait.
I can't wait for it to go on the website and, uh, I'll be famous finally.
Yeah.
Uh, so that's pretty exciting.
Nice.
That was most of my week.
Yeah.
Although I'm, I'm now behind on the book formatting.
Uh, I've still got a lot, still got a lot to do, uh, with like making the, making the
phantoms revenge scenes into pages for the book is what I got to get back to and do for
the rest of this week.
I guess hopefully I can finish that soon.
What's she been up to?
Um, what I, well, I don't, what I might mostly been up to is playing Elden Ring on stream
still.
Oh yeah.
Uh, Elden Ring twitch.tv slash Gibbon take if you want to watch.
Oh.
I've been doing a whole lot of stuff, um, and refusing to go to the first major dungeon
and I've explored many, many, many optional areas and it's, it's very fun.
Hmm.
Uh, how far through the game do you think you are?
It's hard to say at all because you haven't gone to the first dungeon.
Well, you can skip round the first major dungeon with the first main story bus and once you
do that, there's a whole like northern area that you can explore and like there's I, I
don't think I can count the number of like little dungeons and little bosses in little
areas tucked away all over the map and it's just sort of like, oh, I go from here to there
and I'm like, oh, there's something distracts me and I get distracted.
I go and fight a bunch of enemies and they're in like standing around some ruins and there's
like a little, uh, you know, hidden staircase down into a place with a treasure chest.
Sometimes it's a staircase down to a dungeon and sometimes those dungeons have bosses most
of the time they do and so I've just sort of been exploring the map, like getting like
the graces, which is like the bonfires and I can teleport to a grace.
So like, I've got like all of these points all over the whole map that I can teleport
to and then explore from there, like, oh, I haven't gone to this little corner, I haven't
gone to this coastline here, I haven't like checked out this weird thing that looks like
a, looks like a hill with a, with a thing on it.
And so I just have been doing that over and over and over and over and over and it's very
good.
Hmm.
Fascinating.
Give the game a ranking, rank it out of 10 right now.
Um, gosh, I don't do 10 rankings.
Too late!
Uh.
Now I gotta choose.
It's a four.
It's just not that good.
Oh, okay.
Sorry.
I hate this game.
I don't care if you're enjoying it.
Um, yeah, I don't know.
I feel like the combat is like probably the most freeing, feeling combat in any of the
Souls games, the amount of like the freedom you have to play in a certain way.
And then the horse combat is like the funnest thing ever.
It's like, really?
Like you can, sometimes there are enemies on horseback and you can ride by them and
like a normal attack with R1 or L1 will like swing your weapon like quickly, like a little
quick slice.
So you run past them, you slice them and you get them.
Um, but you can do like a power attack L2 or R2 and the LOR is like which direction
of the horse you're attacking from the horse.
And then if you do it like a power attack, you can hold it and they sort of hold their
weapon down low.
And then at the end of a certain time, they'd like swing up and it's a big attack.
But you can do that to like, you can hold like a halberd or something and do a power
attack and run past a bunch of enemies and it'll just hit all of them.
You go...
So that's, that's a very fun and the horse double jumps and it's, it's very manoeuvrable
It's great.
Good horse.
Well, I, on the other hand, despise video games and I would never, and I would never
play one.
I have not been playing much Hades.
I have not made a lot of progress, although I'm getting pretty close to finishing the
fated list of minor prophecies.
I've only got like six of them left and I finished, I finished like the most annoying
one, which is to, I think to get every, every combo boon, like every boon that is like,
okay, you need one from Dionysus and one from Aphrodite and if you have them, then
you can get this other one that's sort of like, sort of a buff to both of their things.
I managed to get every combo boon, which is very, very hard to do.
I have some other random ones left.
Oh, you know what I want to mention?
MarinPan has, was asking, and I think we should do it.
He wanted us to shout out, he wanted us to mention again and remind everybody that the
PCP Minecraft server, if you are a PCP patron, you have access to the Minecraft server and
if you have any trouble getting in there, you should find MarinPan on Discord.
He will help you out.
And I think he wanted to say, he wanted me to shout out the Pokemon League in the Minecraft
server.
There's a whole, there's like a league, you know, they do once in a while, they do, yeah,
yeah, they do tournaments of like, yeah, stuff you caught.
Wait, tournament?
Well, they've done them before.
I thought they were talking about like, the gym battles, like you have like Major's Gym
and your Gym in Copkill Town.
There is, yeah, there is that, there is the whole like, have we like really mentioned
before that there's sort of like a whole like, set of challenges in there?
There's sort of like, there's almost like a whole like, single player campaign.
Yeah, yeah, there's a Pokemon video game built around the buildings that we make or
MarinPan makes in the world.
Mostly MarinPan makes them.
If you, if you catch the streams, you would know.
If you don't, then you wouldn't know.
So probably most people don't know, but yeah, there is, there are whole, there are big like,
Major's Gyms in there to battle through with your team.
There's Major's Gym was the first one.
There's like, there's like, St. Ben's Cathedral in Copkill Town.
There was, there's like that Graveyard one, that like the Tomb of the PCP.
Oh yeah.
There was some, there was one, there was other ones, I think, but there's like a whole, there's
like side quests and stuff.
MarinPan has like, crafted a whole like, a whole like, a video game, a sort of a whole
video game in there.
Yeah.
Sort of a whole, sort of a whole little Pokemon region.
I mean, you know, yeah, I mean, you know, that's not, I mean, I mean, more is being
made all the time.
As much as you could do that, I think the, yeah, but there's areas, there's like themed
areas and stuff.
It's great.
It's wild.
And probably most people don't know about that because most people don't watch the
streams, but it's true.
Yeah.
There's a lot.
MarinPan has done a huge amount of content, like genuine content.
Is it there?
Yeah.
The entirety or like soon to like, very nearly the entirety to scale, basically, of, of Nalacacum,
New Los Angeles city, aka New Milwaukee, is in the server.
It's just a place you can go and it's like the shape of, you know, the actual map.
The map is down.
Not every region is full of like buildings.
There's so many regions that are full.
There are.
It's, it's, some areas are so rich that actually lags a bit.
The downtown area and Copkilt, yeah, a lot of like the, the more central regions are
like fully built and fleshed out.
And yeah, Rowdy Rough House can be a little tough on your, on your PC performance.
And like, you know, oh, and the, oh, the Rowdy Quest, the, the, the, the, the, what was it
called?
The Rowdy Marble Quest.
Yeah.
Rough House stuck.
The Rough House stuck based on that, that RFCK comic by Forks.
There's a whole quest where you have to find all of the realist rowdies and battle them
for their magic marbles and get into the, the, the Rough House.
That's a whole, that took me like, took me like weeks.
We don't talk about it on the show that much.
We usually leave it for the streams, but Marin wanted me to mention it and it does in fact
bear mention it.
We should mention it more.
Mm-hmm.
So if you're a PCP patron of five dollars or more, you get access to the server at no
extra cost.
It used to be a separate patron.
If you weren't aware, it's just in the, the procrastinator's patron now.
No, we, we combined it.
So I should say this, this week, this week, uh, I, I am going to, uh, I'm gonna get those
bonus episodes that Marin, not Marin, Eleazar made weeks and weeks ago that I never posted
and I'm gonna, I'm gonna post them this week.
Um, I will also attempt, I don't, I can't promise it because there may be technical
issues that I don't know about.
I can't promise this, but I will, I will, I will make my best effort to actually get
the old episodes up on like Spotify and Apple podcasts and, and whatever.
Uh, I will use Tom's instructions to figure out, uh, all that.
Uh, also the final thing I want to say about the Patreon, you know what I'm gonna say.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
This is a terrible situation.
Terrible.
It sucks so much.
But everybody who's been a patron, everyone who's been a patron got it for free for the
last month because we all simply forgot to, uh, post and monetize our usual.
It's not that I forgot, it's just like it's a, it's a part of the presses that I'm never
involved in.
I just assumed that you were doing it or whatever.
Yeah.
You, you never were involved in it.
It was technically Tom's job, although Tom's, Tom simply stopped doing it without saying
anything a while ago and I did do it a couple times, like thinking like, oh, Tom just forgot
this week.
I, I guess I'll do it.
I guess I'll, I'll back him up.
And then I forgot that, um, and then I forgot that it had to, it had to continue to be done.
Uh, so, and then it didn't, we didn't get money for the entire month of March and a little
bit of February.
We charge per episode and we have to post it as a charge thing in order for it to count.
So nothing was charged for March.
So that's, so that's quite a bit of money, uh, that we've lost.
Terrible.
We missed out on our whole months.
Hey, our loss is the patron's gain, so, uh, you know, you're welcome, everybody.
Uh, yeah.
That means you have to double your pledge now.
I, I, I would say, I wouldn't say that you have to, but I would say that if you don't,
you're a bad person.
So there you go.
Uh, but I will put, I will put those, those unreleased, uh, bonus, um, what do we call
the ones that are just like, uh, off, off air banter behind the scenes?
Behind this, I guess the behind the scenes, I didn't know there was a main for them.
I don't, I think I call them behind the scenes.
I'm pretty sure Eleazar made two of them and they've just been sitting there and just
haven't posted them.
I will actually go and post them, uh, this week.
This week I'm going to do it for real.
Like before, like before this episode is out, so they will be out when this episode goes
live.
Um, so everybody's got homework.
You got, you got to go this week.
You got to go check out my tails gets trolled page.
You got to check out the bonus episodes.
You got to pledge to patreon.com slash the procrastinators and get on that Minecraft
server and build a house and get on the Minecraft server, assemble, get in Pixelmon, assemble
a team, challenge, challenge me in cop kill town.
I will destroy you.
Um, I, uh, the cop kill town, which was really hard.
There were a couple of like gimmick fights in there that had like a like a single like
hunt, like level hundred and fifty legendary or something, like a great or edgy gigas or
whatever.
That's like, I just don't have the stats for it.
Um, yeah.
The Pokemon's actually quite like a serious Pokemon stuff.
It's not casual and therefore I have not tried it.
I enjoy catching the Pokemon and looking at them and finding like a really big or a really
small version of a thing.
I, I have a team in there that has gotten me through most things.
Sometimes I have to fuck around with it to deal with something or other, but most of
the time my team can, can meet, uh, Marin's challenges, uh, it's a lot of fun and it's,
and I mean, we've been doing it for like, for like years now, I guess, like every, you
know, we don't stream that often, but I mean, it's been an ongoing thing where often when
we stream, Marin has made some new, some new bullshit for us to cope with.
Some new bullshit for us to gore cat and scope out.
Some new nonsense, some new nonsense to vex us.
Yeah.
Um, shout outs to Marin for everything he's done.
That's really incredible work.
Uh, just a huge amount of time and expertise has gone into it.
I don't know how he does it.
I really don't.
Um, hey, let me check it out.
Yeah.
So just, so just check it out.
Check.
So just go to www.nfl.com and just check it out.
Uh, I've got a thing to say.
Yeah, please.
Um, all right.
So Lord of Ghosts, there's like 13, 15 or so more packages I can send.
Uh, it's beneficial that I send because they're all going to America or Australia and I can
send those, uh, through Transglobal Express all in one big collection and, uh, that's
better for me if I can do it all at once.
There's a few people who still have not, even though I've emailed them directly, still
not responded about their address.
So I'm just going to read out their names.
I'm going to dox them, uh, hopefully they, they either they like think they've done it
and don't realize, um, or they, I don't know if they'll listen to the podcast, maybe they're
just not paying attention to anything.
They might not be.
This is my last, this is my last attempt after this episode goes live for a few days.
I will then send the last big batch of Lord of Ghosts.
And if you're not in that, if you haven't given me your address, I just, I can't do anything
about it.
Um, so.
Your package goes in the bonfire goes in, I'm going to burn it live on stream, uh, including
the plush, which will be terrible, terrible and sad.
You don't want that happen.
Um, okay.
So here, here's the list of, of, of names, uh, Mimi Menzies, O-R-N-O-R-I-N, Panda Pop
Loin, Xtreme, Dag Zagals, James Gottwig, Adam O'Donnell, D dot S, Chromel, R-H-O-M-E-L-L,
James Dollar and Milo Rocks.
Uh, I could put an image actually as well as well.
Um, get your things in because I, I want to give you your, your free shit that you paid
for.
I want you to have the thing you, you, you gave me money for.
I want you to have it.
Yeah.
There were, there were, there were not too many, but there were a few people who, who
just simply never got me there, like info from the Vapors Kickstarter, uh, for, for whatever
reason.
Uh, um, yeah, that happens.
Um, but yeah, I hope everyone gets their fucking shit together.
But yeah, that'll be the ending of the Lord of Ghost thing, uh, hopefully, and then I
can, the, the, the next thing I'm going to be working on is Pumpkin Alley.
And I want to like, I want to do like a, a lot of pre-production before I can, I can
like figure out the, the possible cost of making the game.
And then I'll make a Kickstarter once I know that.
So the pre-production is going to be like, I guess, like thinking about all the levels,
what they will require in terms of number of assets, number of enemies, uh, you know,
game mechanics, and then like making a lot of, like an, an exhaustive list of everything
I would need.
And then, I don't know, ballparking figures of like time it would take to make all of
those assets, uh, for various people and, uh, hourly rates.
So I can figure out like, what's, what's good money for this, this amount of work?
Mostly it's going to be me and Charlie, um, working on it.
So I'll, I just have to ask him, but yeah, Pumpkin Alley pre-production.
And then at some point, Clarissa Gunsmoke, I want to finish, uh, the, the Clarissa Gunsmoke
and the Bandit King.
I want to finish that and make it a real finished thing and maybe even look into like
going to a publisher and saying, Hey, I got a Western cowgirl comic.
What do you think?
You think you can put this on store shelves?
Man, if you figure out how to get a publisher to distribute your book, fucking tell me how
you did it.
I, yeah, I mean, I have, I don't know.
I don't have like, like connections, but I do have some good recommendations of
publishers I could look into.
So I'm just going to, I'm just going to finish the, the, the Bandit King and then
send it out to people and say, what do you think?
And then they say it sucks.
But you got, you got, uh, I like your moxie, but yeah, but yeah, but you got
gumption kid will give you a chance.
And then the Clarissa Gunsmoke and the Bandit King will be like the pilot and then
I'll make a better version.
Hmm.
Yeah.
I don't know really what to do with that other than like, it was, it was a cool
idea and I liked the, the character and I want to continue it.
So I will.
Wait, what do you mean you make a better version?
Um, well, you know how like, uh, there's a, the, the pilot version of a thing is
like different and then, uh, if you get a publisher or, or like, uh, people, they'll
say, uh, well, we suggest you do this and that.
And are you talking about like serializing it?
And potentially, I mean, it's a Western.
You could do loads of things with it.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Cause initially for, for a while I was like thinking, Oh, I'm, I'm never going to
get published.
I'm just like an internet content creator.
I'm just going to draw some things and post them online and get some likes and
hopefully some patrons in this.
That's going to be me.
That's all I can do.
Um, but I got some feedback about it.
Some of my dad's friends were like saying my dad showed it to them and they were
like, Oh, this is really cool.
You should, you should look into getting it published.
I'm like, really?
This is interesting to me actually.
You serious?
You, you're giving me like good vibes on this that I made.
That's nice.
No, no, there's a thought.
Are you telling me that are you telling me that are you telling me that
organized business structures exist for the purpose of creation and distribution
of an artist's output?
Is that what you're saying?
It's, it's more that they thought you fucking with me.
I just felt validated.
You know, like I felt validated that a human being that wasn't online said that
what I drew on was cool and should be made real.
And I'm like, wow, I never really thought about it for some reason.
Sure.
And they're probably right.
I just, that's a thing.
I don't know.
I just, I guess I never really, that's a thing that I thought about.
And I sort of immediately dismissed as like, well, that'll never work.
Like that, that's impossible.
But, but like, well, I don't know why I, that I may, that may be a limiting
belief that I have that now that you say it out loud, that makes me think like,
that is a good idea.
Could I do that?
How would I do that?
I mean, the way you've done probably so far is
like it's, it's a new way to do comics is to crowdfund the printing of them
and then send them out and it's doable on a small scale.
But if you could get a publisher, so much of that hassle of logistics
and buying and selling and marketing is like taken care of and you can just work.
This is like, this is like, yeah, exactly.
Like when I, when I went around to comic shops to, to ask them like,
hey, would you like to put my book on your shelf?
Some of them were like, yeah, sure, I'll take three copies.
What do you want?
Like, what do you want?
Like $2 for each?
I'm like, yeah.
It's like, well, what's literally not worth the fucking bus fare to like get out
here and ask you in person if you want.
Yeah, they would give me like, they would give me like $3 for each copy
and with the intent to like sell it for five.
I'm like, well, it's simply not worth, it's simply not worth my time.
The only way it would be worth it is if I had a distributor, like if Diamond
distributor were putting my shit in a catalog and like hundreds of stores
were looking at that and being like, yeah, I'll take a copy.
I'll take two copies, whatever.
I'll take 50.
Sure.
Well, sure.
They just, well, they just don't want to, they don't want to stock that many,
especially of an unknown thing.
Yeah, they want to put, they want like one copy, put it on the shelf.
And if it, if someone buys it, like, well, I guess I'll get another one.
Maybe someone will buy that, you know.
So you got to work at scale and I just lack that ability.
So I just gave up.
I was like, well, I guess I'm only selling my shit online.
You know what I got to diversify that portfolio.
Yeah.
What I thought, what I've been thinking occasionally is that I should get an agent.
You know, that's a thing that artists do sometimes.
They get, they get an agent.
What does that mean?
Well, what I understand is that an agent is someone who basically knows people in the industry.
You don't, you don't pay them to be your agent.
What they do is they take a, a good day.
Like there are some fake agents that will scam you and ask for money up front, but those are fake.
A real agent will just basically knows people and knows the industry.
And when a job comes up and someone's looking for someone, they might be like, Oh, I know a guy.
And then they'll call you and be like, Hey, here's a job I thought you might be good at.
Would you want this job?
And then you go, yes.
And then they take like a, I don't know, 15% cut or whatever of the pay for that job.
So that's what an agent does.
Just they know talent and they know people that are looking for talent and they connect them.
And I'm like, Hey, I'm talent.
I flatter myself to think.
Uh, so it was like, I, I guess sounds like something I should have, uh, but apparently, you know, there's a lot to, that goes into like picking the right agent or whatever.
Like I haven't even really looked at all.
It's just something that sometimes I think I should probably get an agent.
Cause I mean, how would you go for that?
Like agents.com.
Great, great question.
Great question.
I have no idea.
I feel like you'd need to go in person to like a comic thing and then like hold a glass of champagne at an after party and say, Yeah, I'm a comic person.
Oh, you should talk to X, Y, Z.
And I'm like, Oh, okay.
Now I have to do this, like all of that socializing.
Then you, you might look around and find the perfect person.
And that's it.
Yeah, I have no idea.
I think that's probably not how it's typically done.
I can't imagine.
I can't imagine most people, uh, could really get much out of something like that.
No, there probably are just like, there probably are just like listings and maybe you can like check out an individual agent or like, or not.
Or you wouldn't, you wouldn't have an agent, like an individual agent.
You would probably apply to an agency and maybe they would assign you an agent that works for their agency.
Right.
Maybe you might have one dude and like, you're his responsibility or you go on his list or whatever.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't really know how it works, but it seems like something I should have or should, I should look into getting.
I would like, I would like to, I would like to do work.
I would like to do productive work in my, in my field.
Sounds good.
It'd be cool just to like, I don't know, transcend from my shitty website that I made that sucks.
Sure.
And put it into places where I can get a little bit of money all the time.
Well, I don't actually know how that works, but like, the, like, I'm not generating any revenue from my comics at the moment.
Yeah, I get Patreon money and people like what I make.
And so they patron me, but like that's, there's no like direct link and I don't know if more comics is more better.
I like drawing them, so I'm going to keep doing that.
But God, I got to get money, got to get cash, you know.
I believe me, believe me, I know, I know about the need for cash.
Uh, I was telling, so I went, so I did Easter, right?
This, the Sunday was Easter.
So yesterday I went to a little, a little family get together with my parents and some of my, some of my mom's sisters and their husbands and talk to some of those guys that I haven't seen in a long time.
And I was telling one, one of them was asking what I've been up to and I started, I didn't go into huge detail about it, but I talked about Slime and Punishment and like how I'd been, I'd drawn this comic and I was hoping to kick, hoping to crowdfund and print it and make, distribute it soon.
And I mentioned that I had made a, I had mentioned that I had made a game that I had sort of like dipped my toe into game development and made a little game to go along with the comic.
And this aunt told me something that, that astounded me.
By the way, this is, this is not career talk, by the way, this is just an anecdote.
So I'm sorry if I changed the subject out from under you, if you wanted to talk about more.
Um, no, I can, I can talk afterwards.
Okay.
Sorry.
Um, but, but the, they told me she was like, Oh, that reminds me.
And she said, so I had this aunt, I had this aunt that died, like right around the time that I was born, this aunt died, she was like 30 and she died of leukemia.
And apparently, like before she died, she had made a little game, and this would have been in like the late eighties, she had programmed a little like game for her, for her boyfriend and this boyfriend was still like a friend of the family.
He still occasionally shows up to family functions.
She had made a little like choose your own adventure or a little like click through pages as like a Valentine's Day present for this boyfriend.
Yeah.
That's cute.
I was like, that's the cutest thing I ever heard.
And also you telling me a woman made a video game in the eight, in the eighties.
I couldn't make a video game in the eighties.
I mean, you weren't a born.
I know, I guess I feel I feel like you would have to be, I feel like you would have to be a somewhat serious like computer person.
Oh, you mean like in the eighties, most people didn't know what computers were.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, like today I was like, I feel like an idiot because I boot up Game Maker and like, yeah, there's tools there that I can like use to sort of design a game, but it's all shit that someone made for me, like I'm not, I'm not doing anything novel.
I'm just using shit that someone like laid out for for an idiot like me to use.
I feel like to do that in the eighties, you would have to like, I don't know, you would have to like put your own circuit board.
You have to build your own circuit board with resistors on a little cork board and like put the transistors together.
I don't know about quite that, but yeah, it's definitely more difficult.
I remember seeing like sketches of like Super Mario Brothers where they drew like a grid with pencil on paper and like, okay, we're going to have a, it looks like this.
And it's got the, they have to type in code what the squares look like and what color they are.
Yeah.
And it's like, wow, you can't just draw with a mouse.
What's a mouse?
They said.
Nothing.
It ain't nothing.
No such thing.
So anyway, I just thought that was a very cute little story, cute little, cute little thing surprised me a lot.
But it was true.
Anyway, were we talking about publishing?
Publishing.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, I guess the only other thing was that like my thought process of like how I'm going to to juggle pumpkin alley and Clarissa.
Cause I want to get both of them done.
So I'm going to have to like seriously manage my time in the coming months, very, very sensibly and very deliberately in order to get the stuff done.
I don't want to get burnt out on anything.
I don't want to work myself to the bone so that I can't do either thing.
And I don't want to leave one thing for like seven months in the future.
I want to be getting them done at the same time.
Yeah.
And I'm not sure how that's going to work quite yet.
I guess I just like designate a certain day for like this or that.
So you're saying, so you're talking about on the one hand, doing like the pre-production stuff for, for pumpkin alley, like in preparation for like kickstarting the full game and also completing the Clarissa comic, right?
Yeah.
Or no, wait.
Clarissa Gunsmoke.
You, did you, did you finish that?
I posted what I had done for the Tezuka award thing, which was not the finished thing at the very end of that.
She's in prison.
I had written more and I had sketched like, like 35 pages after that, but I hadn't like lined them or anything.
I guess I blocked them out.
I didn't really sketch them, but there's like a bunch of pages left to go that I haven't drawn.
And I, I would love it to be finished because I think it's very cool how it ends, like epic.
You might say like, like a showdown.
And then I would, oh, oh, I see how it is.
And, you know, it's just like, oh, what a great thing that nobody fucking knows at all.
I feel like people have sort of forgotten that I drew Clarissa Gunsmoke.
And they don't, it's just sort of like, oh, yeah, yeah, that thing.
No, it's my best thing.
It's my best work, but you haven't seen it yet.
So, but that would take like not so much thinking time, at least for the pages that I've already sketched.
I've got to, I've just got to block it out because like there's, there's, there's two types of work.
One's a lot, it depends on who you are, but one is more difficult than the other for me.
There's the creative work where you come up with everything.
And then there's the, the, the labor where you, yeah, like you zone out and you just physically move your hand around and do it.
Yeah.
And so I need some blocks of like creative work to, to like think how is this page going to be laid out for the rest of the pages?
And then the labor is just sitting down for like six hours and just drawing.
Yeah.
And so I want to make it so that I'm not, and then Pumpkin Alley is like a lot of creative work for the pre-production.
That's entirely creative work.
I'm coming up with everything.
So I, I don't want to be flip-flopping between creative and labor work too much because then it's like you get,
you get like momentum doing one type of work.
I think creative work is just harder in general.
It takes more brain cells, neurons to fire.
Yeah, I agree.
It's more like, yeah, like the grunt work, the like just the busy work, you can kind of just like chug away at it.
And it's like, yeah, whatever.
So I think what I want is I want to be in a position where I've done the creative work for Clarissa Gunsmoke.
So that I can, I can, I don't know, I can do like the labor work for Clarissa Gunsmoke on one day and then the next day,
creative work for Pumpkin Alley or just creative work the whole time.
I don't really know how to properly do it.
I've got to look at a calendar and be like, put everything on the calendar and then say,
I'm going to do that on this day, hopefully.
It's difficult scheduling things.
How does one organize one's life?
There's like 700,000 apps for organization.
And I know why, because it's hard.
I those are both two like really long term projects.
And I understand why you would want to be like, well, I kind of want to be making progress on both at once.
I'm trying to, I don't have any, I don't have anything that's like that long term, like that I'm going to be working on for like a whole year,
like like Pumpkin Alley or whatever.
But or not not pump.
Yeah, yeah, Pumpkin Alley.
I'm really trying to just be like, I have a bunch of ideas for things that I should be doing.
I have a bunch of like plans that I've been coming up with that maybe I'll do in the next year.
But I'm really trying to just like cut down and focus on one thing at a time.
Like I was just doing the book.
I was like, not worried about anything else, just finishing the book.
But then the Tales of Gets Trolled page was like, I kind of, I have to do that now.
Like that can't wait.
So it's like, OK, I'm not working on the book at all this week.
I'm only doing the Tales of Gets Trolled page.
Now that's done.
So this week it's going to be just, just the book.
Well, except for, you know, I have to put those fucking podcast episodes up.
I can't wait. So I will have to do that.
But other than that, it'll be only the book and then it'll be just, just the book until that's done.
And then, like I said, I have some, I have some, I came up with some, not a scheme.
I came up with some, an idea and, and how do I want to say it?
I had an idea, I had an idea that I need to somewhat change the approach that I'm using
to my, my online presence, because I feel like I've been mostly just spinning my wheels
for the last, maybe a couple of years even.
And I think I need a new strategy.
And I think I've come up with some ideas for how to do that.
But I don't want to say what they are, but I'm not work, but I'm not.
I don't get it, though.
Yeah. Well, I'm being cagey.
So you mean like your approach to being an online person?
Yes. You're talking about your own like brand of Ben Saint?
Yes.
Okay. I don't know what you're, yeah, I guess I kind of guess.
No, I don't want, I don't want you to know.
I mean, I'll tell you, actually, I will tell you after the show.
I don't want to say it on the show.
Sure, sure.
Because I want, I have some things that I want to do and I think I really should do,
but I don't want to talk about them before they're ready because like, what's the point?
It's, it's, I just like, I was like, this, I don't know.
I have a bit, a little bit of a revelation that sort of hit me like, it's obvious.
Like it's actually kind of obvious.
It's actually kind of obvious what I should have done.
And it's like, well, now that I've thought of it, maybe it wouldn't even be that hard, but.
I've decided to change my name to the Ben guy ever.
Whatever, but anyway, the point is I had that idea, but I'm like, now's not the time.
Now's not the time to worry about it.
Got to finish the book before I think about doing that.
Because I don't want to put the book off anymore.
The book should be done.
And then while the Kickstarter's running, you know, maybe I'll have time to, okay,
maybe I can start like preparing for anything I want to do in relation to any of that stuff.
So yeah, I'm trying to really, I'm trying to really focus on some,
some particulars, but I don't expect anything, I don't expect the book to take more than
maybe like a month.
I would like to have the book ready to go and maybe, maybe I could, maybe I could do
the Kickstarter a month from now, I would, that would be amazing.
I don't know if it's realistic, but I feel like I should try.
Maybe that should be my sort of optimum goal.
Yeah, it's working through creative projects.
I sometimes get lost in like working on the one thing.
And then when somebody says, why do you see yourself in five years?
Like that sort of a question.
I'm like, I don't fucking know, doing more of it, doing a different one.
Yeah.
It's like, I don't know where I want to end up at all.
It would be nice to be like, oh, I've got a stable income now because of I released a
game and people like it, or like, oh, I got a comic published.
I mean, that would be a great, like end goal, but like a goal, like a big goal to have to
have a goal post to move, and like, but like, I don't know where I want to end up other
than that, sort of, I'm just sort of like, I'm picking one thing that I have in my head
and I'm like, all right, time to make this thing that was in my head for a while, a real
thing.
And there it is.
Then I just pick another one.
I've got, I still in my, in the back of my head, I want to, I want to do more red noir
and I want to tie it into slime and punishment in some funny way.
Oh, that would be sick.
It'd be sick, but it would be like a very big distraction from like bigger things that
are probably more of an importance for me today.
You, I hate to say it, but that's probably true as much as I, no, no, no, actually, actually,
after the show, let's talk about this.
Let me, let me explain to you why actually making, making slime and punishment adjacent
content is probably the most important thing you could be doing for your personal future.
I'd love to know how.
I have some, I have some thoughts about it.
Yeah, I'll share them with you.
I mean, in a way, like the Lord of Ghosts act three, which will also be a thing I'm
going to work on, will, because of all of the things it's like linked to, it will have
to, all right, I don't want to spoil it, but I was thinking the beginning of like the Lord
of Ghosts act three would take place in Nalakakam from the perspective of perhaps red man.
And then, and then the, that everyone will arrive and it'll be like, what the fuck?
And that'll, that'll, that'll be like the act three thing makes, makes perfect sense
to me.
So if red noir is going on, that could also lead into the events of Lord of Ghosts act
three, and it would just be a whole big fucking thing and it's like cool and based and epic
and like, what, wow, they're going to fight, Flowey's going to slice somebody, there's
the army of the dead, what are they going to do?
I have a question, I was, I was watching Oblivionfall, this was, this was after you went to bed
and Oblivion, it did not stream the other day, Oblivionfall played Phantom of Revenge
and, oh yes, after you went to bed, he was continuing to look for that, that elusive
eighth lizard, which he never found tragically, but he, they were looking at, there's that
part near the end of the game, the end of the demo area, where there's a rock on the
side of the hill and it has, it has the flower head triskelion.
Yes.
I was going, and it made me think like, why does, is there a reason, like there's got
to be, like, why does he have that, why does he wear the triskelion?
There is a reason, but I'm not entirely sure what the reason is yet.
I know Flower Head's backstory, I know where he comes from and I know, like, the lore of
that location and the reason he's doing what he's doing.
The symbol is like, what symbol could, like, represent this thing and, like, looking at
things Celtic?
I was like, yeah, that's a cool, that's a cool thing.
Yeah.
The places from, also uses symbols like that, as is the extent of it, it's just, like, finding
a cool thing from the real world that links either thematically or, like, aesthetically
into, like, the fictional world that I'm building.
That makes sense.
I looked it up and I was looking through what it means and it, it had, like, it was like,
it can mean, like, a billion different things and I was like, okay, that doesn't tell me
a whole lot.
Yeah.
It's his, like, backstory iconography or it's related to, like, where he comes from.
That makes sense to me, yeah.
Really it's just that he had, in Canon's story that nobody has read, he just had, like, the
Scorpio sign for no reason.
Scorpio is, is this six and nine?
No, that's cancer.
Scorpio's the VSCO one, the M with the, like, little, little, little, little, little, little,
little.
Tell.
Why did he have that?
Was it a risqu reference?
It was a risqu reference.
Yeah, of course.
It's nothing more than that.
Fair, fair, fair.
Yeah, I always forget Flowerhead was in Canon's story, Lamal.
Um, what are we talking about?
I dunno, just creative projects.
That's all I really had to say is that I want to be working on Clarissa and Pumpkin Alley,
and somehow doing both of those at the same time in a way that doesn't ruin me because
I would hate to postpone either of them, and I can postpone things like Red Noir and
Lord of Ghosts because they're like, what if I could get a published comic, and what
if I could make a real video game, like those are really cool things that I want to focus
on.
After I'm done fucking around with Elden Ring for another like 10 weeks.
Right, of course, of course, priorities.
I have some things that I have been meaning to do that I've wanted to do and I still want
to do for like probably the two most pressing of which would be finishing Beast Capades
and doing another Nuzlocke.
These are things that I've been saying I would do for a long time.
I definitely want to do those things, but you know, I have the thing I'm doing right
now, which is the book, and then I've had this thought about, I've had this thought
about, you know, my how to better, you know, that stuff about my brand and stuff about
like the direction I should be.
I've had some ideas for like how I should be spending my time as a content creator,
and I'm like, I think I should look into that.
I think I should try that for a bit, and I don't think it's going to be like, oh, well
now I can't do any of those other things that I want to do, but I do think I'll have to
be like, alright, I'll need to make one thing like a priority, and then the other things
will have to sort of be fit in around that.
I'm being so cagey.
I'm being so cagey just because like if my ideas don't pan out, then I don't ever have
to acknowledge them ever again, and no one will make fun of me because I said I was going
to do a thing, and then I didn't do a thing.
You're going to make a, you're going to make, you're going to like redraw Sonichu, and you're
going to call it Benichu.
You're going to call it, you're going to horse eat you because it's like horses.
I'm going to do another one of those damn, hey, I redrew Sonichu, but good, I'm going
to start all the way at the beginning, and I'm going to do all like 14 chapters of it,
and I'm sure this time, I'm sure I'll be the one that doesn't get sick of that totally
pointless process, and just the whole thing that makes my whole life.
No, never, never, ever again.
Yeah, I was telling my, that aunt I was telling about slime and punishment.
I was explaining to her like, yeah, I'm a little, I'm a little, I'm a little unsure
about whether I expect to make any money off it because, you know, it's the whole thing
is sort of like a big in-joke that like is really hard to understand and like nobody
knows what it is and doesn't make any sense, and it's nonsense and it sucks, but I don't
know.
I just got it, but I can't, I can't not sell it.
I can't just be like, eh, well nobody will buy it, eh, won't make any money, eh, fuck
it, I can't, I can't just give up on it.
I have to see it through all the way to the end, just to see what kind of numbers it does,
just to, just so I can tell myself, well, I did my best.
I mean, it's anything you do will probably do more than nothing.
I think, I think, yeah, I think it will sell enough to be made.
I, my, my hope, because I put more time into it than I put into like either of the Vapors
chapters, my, my hope is that it gives me a bigger return on investment for time spent.
My hope is that it makes, you know, proportionally more money than those did, basically.
If it doesn't do that, if it just does similar numbers, I will be like, I will consider
that somewhat of a failure.
But I mean, that still won't, that still won't be nothing.
Like that'll still be worth doing.
Yeah, that's, that's where it's at.
I just want to, I just want to get it done.
I really want to, I got some paper samples.
I got to choose cover weights.
The, I got to choose page, page thicknesses and stuff, pick a printer.
The reality of the situation is that I might have to change printers later on.
Like I might decide on a printer now and then based on the number.
Like if I, if I pick a printer now, I would probably pick the one that is the most cost
effective to print, like the minimum number.
Like if I set my goal, like while I want to sell 100 of them, I'll pick the printer
that's like the cheapest to print 100.
But then, you know, if it were to sell 500 copies, which would be incredible.
But whatever, just for example, if it does that, then I'll be like, well, okay,
actually at that number, there's a different printer that's a more cost
effective price point.
So I should actually switch printed.
So I actually probably shouldn't commit to, I'm definitely going with this printer.
But I want to get at least one test copy made.
And it's like, okay, I can't guarantee this will be the exact, like exact print
quality, the exact, like glossiness, the exact dimensions, but it'll be, it'll
basically be this.
And they're like, okay, this, this is the product being sold.
And that's hard because I got to, got to finish the page layout, got to, got
to pick a printer, got to pick one printer to just to make the test copy with.
And then got to go through whatever process it requires to have that made
and shipped to me.
And then once I have the book in front of me, be like, okay, now.
Also, I think I've been thinking, and I think that the way to do it, I think the
way to market the book is to make a YouTube video.
And I think that the YouTube video, it should be, it should be a Kickstarter
announcement, but maybe even more than a Kickstarter announcement.
It should be a little bit of a explanation of like what it is and like how it happened.
So I think I kind of want to make a little video that's more of like.
A trailer for a book.
It's not, not just a trailer.
I think that the video will sort of be a little story essay video that's like.
Oops, I accidentally made the last chapter of Sonichu.
Here's, here's how it happens.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, tying it into to that.
And then in that video, I will mention that, like, and it's, and I'm, you know,
I'm selling the book.
If you want to buy the book, I made a Kickstarter.
It's going on right now, but it'll mostly be an explanation of like how it
happened and what it is.
And maybe make, maybe try to make a little funny story out of it.
I think that's, I think that's the move marketing wise.
So that's work.
That's work that I don't want to do, but I guess I got to do it.
Haven't made a video in a while.
Imagine making a video.
Yeah.
Imagine scripting out a video and then editing it together.
Like that's something I haven't done in so long.
And I'm actually like dreading it and terrified of it.
Yeah, I haven't scripted a video in a long time.
I've recorded myself like the most like closest I got to making a video recently
was I recorded myself playing wordles where I couldn't figure out what it was.
And I was going to call it, I can't fucking think of the wordle.
Oh, that's good.
Hey, that's good.
And it, and it's mostly when I do a wordle and I was like, oh, I don't know how to do.
Oh, what the fuck is this?
And it's just like me fumbling around for like maybe five minutes, maybe 20 minutes.
And then I'm like, wait, yeah, I did it.
It's like, wait a minute, that's, that sucks.
I don't want to, I don't want to go to the effort of putting that in a video editor
and then like messing around with it and then rendering it and then uploading it.
I mean, it's a funny, it's a funny joke as a reference to I can't fucking
think of the word.
Yeah.
So I feel like it, I feel like the same thing could have been done.
Like the same content could be made in like tweets.
But the problem with wordle is that you can't post something the day that it's
the wordle you have to wait until afterwards.
And so like, and it's just sort of nobody posts their wordles like old ones.
So I feel like nobody would care in any event what happened.
So I might, I might, I might leave it.
I think it would make an okay little joke video.
I think it'd be fine.
Yeah.
I mean, I've recorded like five or six of them and I'm like, maybe I could put it
all in one big video where I can't fucking think of the word all.
Yeah.
I think that's from, from months ago.
That's good.
I think that's totally fair.
Yeah.
No, no sort of thing you could like, like do to keep up with the times.
It's just sort of some content that might be interesting later.
Sure.
And what more can you, what more can you ask for?
Um,
there's a, there's a thing, there's a, there's a funny thing that happened.
I don't know.
I guess I should bring it up.
Oh, I don't, I just don't want to dwell on it too long, but did you see, uh, I
got in like, I got in some stupid Twitter arguments this week.
Oh, which ones?
About the VTuber.
Oh, yeah.
You responded to a VTuber doing some sort of parasocial relationship post.
Yeah, something like that.
And you said, this is disgusting.
And then you refused to elaborate and then muted her.
Yes, that's correct.
Well, I thought it was amusing.
Her fans did not think it was, her fans were angry and were like sending me like
threats and like sending me like gore and stuff.
Yeah, threats are not good.
But I just thought it was like, like, of course, somebody would not know what the
fuck you mean if you don't say anything.
You just say, fuck this.
Okay.
Disgusting.
And it's like, what the hell is that guy's problem?
Like, it's just sort of like a weirdo thing to happen.
Sure.
But like getting threats for it is like, uh, why do you care?
Why do they care?
Those, her fans are the VTuber fans in general fucking suck and I hate them.
I have no respect for them at all, like the hell with all of them.
Like they're, they're devils, they're monsters.
Um, but more, more than that, um, I just, she, you know, I tell, I said, like,
hey, fuck this post.
I, that's not what I said.
I said this post is horrible.
Hate this post.
Horrible.
I'm hated.
Yeah.
That's it.
Um, and she said, like, why?
And like, I don't know, when I see that, she's like, why do you not like the post?
And I think, and I'm like, I don't know.
I just, I don't, I don't owe you an answer.
I, I already don't like you.
I don't like what you do on here.
And you ask me to do the work of explaining to you why I, I, I feel this way about you.
You don't, you don't deserve that.
I'm kind of offended that you think I would waste my time explaining anything to you.
No, I won't do it.
I refuse.
Um, so that's why I said, no, like I don't, I don't want to explain.
I don't owe you an explanation.
I won't do it.
Um, but yeah.
So she, she was, and then she, she screenshotted these posts and made a little post and was
like, what is he's bullying me?
This, this was like a, this, this girl was like a character.
It was like she calls all her reply guys big brother.
Like she does, like she pretends to be like a baby.
She's pretends to be like your little baby sister.
And like all her reply guys, no big brother, some, some idiot.
Some freak in the, in the replies is like, oh, I can't believe this guy was rude to you.
Should I go, should I go do a mass harassment campaign?
Should I go and get all my friends to down, to downvote his video, his shitty video game
that looks like shit on itch.io.
Should I go to his website and fucking, should I have his YouTube channel, uh, uh,
the reported for harassment?
And she's like, no, no big brother.
No, we can't, we can't seek to his level.
We can't be like him.
I'll be okay.
I promise, I promise big brother, I'll survive.
I have nothing but disdain for all these people.
But so that, that's what she did.
And so then I was like, well, OK, she made it public.
So I made a little post that was like, I just called it gross.
By the way, I haven't even said what the post was.
I haven't even explained what the post was for the audience.
The post in question, it was a meme.
And it said that it was just a picture of her character.
And it said, um, normalize having a comfort VTuber instead of a comfort person.
And I thought, what is a comfort person?
Anyway, well, that's the thing.
I turned out to be a little bit wrong, because what I thought that a comfort
person is like someone that you like take comfort in, like, like, like a friend.
Right.
So I was like, so I was like relationships with VTubers over having friends.
That's what you thought they were saying.
Something like that.
And I was like, that's like, fuck, like, fuck this.
This is weird.
Like, shut up.
Uh, yeah.
It's like, it's like, oh, put your, put your emotional, put your emotional
burdens on VTubers, rely on, on VTubers.
OK, there's actually a lot.
There's a lot here to talk about.
Because, yes, if, if that is what it was saying, it would be an
unacceptably, like, cloying, like, call to parasociality, like, and that would
be disgusting, and I would hate it.
So that's what I was initially responding to.
It turns out it's a little bit different, because I guess what a comfort
person is, is not like a friend.
It's like a, like a celebrity or someone that you, like, see and feel good.
A non-VTuber, parasocial relationship.
It's like, it's like a comfort character, but it's a, yes.
Yes, it's a not yes.
So it's, so it's a little different.
It's not saying replace your real life attachments with VTuber attached.
It's not quite that bad.
But still, but still, it's a post celebrating, you know, I feel like I
was misunderstood a little bit, because my problem, like, yes, it is parasocial
and that's, and that's lame and whatever, but that's not really why I
didn't like it, because it, because lots of things are parasocial.
And I don't think, I don't think that a parasocial relationship is in
and of itself bad or harmful.
Like it's okay to like a YouTuber.
It's okay to like a VTuber or to watch them and have an opinion about them.
And that's a parasocial relationship.
And that's not wrong or bad in and of itself.
So it's not, it's not just, a lot of people seem to think that I was just
saying, oh, this is encouraging parasocial relationships and that's bad.
And it's more than that.
What, what bugs me about it, because I see VTuber posts on the Endless War
RFCK account on Twitter, I followed a couple of slime themed VTubers just
because I thought it was funny.
And now all I see when I log into that account is recommended tweets from
VTubers and they're all, not all, but lots and lots of them have this attitude.
It reminds me a lot of the attitude of, it's like the attitude of the
Baroni analysis community that was all like really into the specific thing
they were doing and they were all just really like focused on this.
Isn't it cool that we all review my little pony?
Isn't it cool that we like, look at this, this community that we've built.
Oh, we all support each other.
We're all going to upvote each other's videos.
We're all going to like each other's videos.
We're all going to make it.
We're all going to make it guys.
It really reminds me in a lot, in a lot of ways of like the NFT space where
everybody's got a fucking ape, everyone's talking about how great their
apes are, everyone's hyping up their apes because they've, because they've
invested, you know, financially or emotionally into this thing.
And they're all there to hype each other up and get engagement from one another
because they all, they need to feel like this thing they're doing is important.
And they're all there to hype it to themselves and to one another.
And they're all there just like, whew, whipping themselves into like a VTubing
is the wave of the future.
V, it's VTubing is the fucking, this is the most important thing in the fucking
world.
I'm exaggerating a little bit, but that's the attitude that I, that I see a lot.
And it really annoys me.
Isn't that like content creators largely?
Yeah.
And whatever like theme or like genre they're in.
I'm not saying it's exclusive to the, it's, it's a thing.
It's a thing, comics too.
Like when I would go on like the Topastic forums and see like, you know,
these small comic creators with no, no audience at all, just like all posting to
each other about their, their stuff, asking each other questions about like,
how do you like to write, you know, your protagonist?
Like, what's your favorite ship dynamic or whatever?
They're all talking about, it's fine.
Like it's fine, I guess.
This, the, I don't know, this, the attitude of like this, like, they're all being, you
got to be really positive.
We're all, we're all posting about whatever, whatever the interest is, whatever
the field is, like we're all here, we're all posting about it.
We're all being really positive about it.
Because we all, we're all hyping each other up.
Like we're all, none of us are getting anything out of it, right?
Like the people that do these kinds of posts, they're not successful.
They're, they're, they're, they're low on the totem pole.
And they're there because they, they need to convince themselves.
They need to have the sense of community that, oh, sure, I'm not getting anything
out of this, even though it's an interest of mine.
But, you know, everybody else is also not getting anything, we're all kind of here.
It's a community, we're doing, it's for the community.
Uh, I'm not successful as a VTuber.
I'm not, like, I don't have a big audience.
I'm not making any money at it.
It is just like a big sink for me, but we have a community and all
my other VTuber friends are the same.
We're all just fucking, fucking around and floundering and not getting anything out of it.
But we're having fun in its community.
You're saying that they're coping?
I'm saying it's, it's coping.
And it, and it's like, that's, that's what's unappealing to you is that they're,
they're not actually successful, but they're positive about what's going on.
It's part of it.
That's part of it.
But it, it, I feel like it exists.
I feel like the attitude, the attitude, I feel like it's an attitude that
benefits those at the top.
It's an attitude that is like this thing we're doing, this, this field that we're
all engaged in is important and let's, let's hype it up.
But the, but like, but they don't benefit from that hype.
They, they keep themselves engaged in it, but like the, the, only the people that
are already, the people that are already popular are going to stay popular.
Everybody's, all right.
VTubers want to be popular.
They want to have an audience.
That's what they want.
That's why they're doing it.
It's, it's, there'd be no reason to do it unless they wanted attention.
They want engagement.
They want an audience and, and they're all, but they're, they're, I feel like
they're, when they post like this, their audience is each other.
They're, they're appealing to each other and convincing one another about like,
yes, our feelings are valid.
We are all going to make it in this VTuber space and we're going to do that.
And we're going to do that.
It's like shout out, like, where are all my fellow, like male VTubers, all my
fellow male VTubers, we're all going to follow each other.
Everybody, like, like post below so I can find you and I can follow you.
That's what you do.
When you're a VTuber, you post a thing that's like, Hey, where are all my X
adjective VTubers, uh, uh, post below so I can follow you.
And the, and I think the unspoken implication there is that you hope
that they will also follow you back.
And it's, it's just this big incestuous slurry to take a phrase from Homestuck.
They're all just, they're all just people with no audience, just watching
each other, trying to get each other to watch each other.
I don't know, man.
That this is, this is, I, I, I can understand that that is a thing.
Yeah.
I could, I could see, I can, I can see that.
I don't know why it makes you so mad though.
I just would be like, eh, they're not going anywhere like that.
They got to like think differently.
And then I just move on.
I don't really think about them.
Yeah, like, you see, it benefits those at the top.
I don't really get how exactly if they're all just incestuous in their little group.
Are they, are they building like a bedrock of like, of VTuber in the public
consciousness that is benefiting the VTubers that already, already exist?
Or are they having no effect at all?
Cause I feel like it's, it's the, it may be the other way around that the big VTubers
are, are giving them hope that they can do something.
It just isn't doing anything for them.
I don't know.
Maybe it's both.
Maybe it's neither.
I mean, it's just, maybe it's just a feeling I have.
Maybe it's not even real.
Maybe it's just a phantasm.
Maybe you want to be a VTuber.
Maybe that's what this is all about.
I don't know.
Okay.
Ever since you saw the red man VTubing model, you were like, damn, I want that.
I want that for me.
Okay.
Well, even, even if they're a little bit incoherent, I've explained how I feel about
posts of this kind.
That's, that's why they annoyed me for all those reasons.
Parasocials thing.
It's, it's cloying.
It's like, it's sort of, I don't know.
It's sort of something about it to put one final, it's like, it's like, it's a little dishonest.
It feels, it, these posts feel to me like they're presented
neutrally.
But when you make them, when you post about something like that, like, replace, replace
replace, replace something else in your life with VTubers.
It's like, you're, you're, you're asking me for something.
You're posting this as though it's about VTubers in general, as though it's about some
general thing, but it's about you.
What you actually want is for me to do it with you, but you won't say that.
I don't know.
So I don't like it.
I didn't like it.
I called it bad, whatever.
Her fans went in apeshit in my comments, sent me gore, whatever.
A couple of people that followed me said that I was being a big meanie.
Ben, you're being too mean.
Ben, you've crossed the line.
Ben, you're a big jerk.
And I think those people are confused because I've been way meaner
and I've been way more problematic and said more offensive things on Twitter.
To Trixie and, and like, to trick, if you're just worried about the meanest,
then, yeah, I've been way meaner to Trixie.
If you're worried about me being like, you know, unfair or or cruel or whatever,
there was that time that I got mad at that black person for saying not to
draw us off a certain way.
I think I was a little unreasonable in that situation.
So so I've so I don't know why this would be this particular one.
It's just sort of baffling.
It's not exactly a bad thing.
It's just sort of like, man, you're you really hate VTubers, Ben.
I don't. I don't hate VTubers.
I truly swear to God, I don't hate what you hate that thing that you saw.
I swear to God, it's not it's not that I have a problem with VTubers
in specific for any reason.
It's just this is the thing that some of them do and it's an attitude that I hate.
And they're not the only ones to do it.
But the was it going to say, yeah, I genuinely think that some of the
reaction that some people had that were not even fans of this person,
they just saw this reaction and were like, Ben,
this is not OK.
I genuinely think some of them, their lizard brain neurons were activated
by the fact that this person posts in character like roleplays as a baby.
Like they reacted as though they thought I was like attacking an actual baby.
Like maybe intellectually, they know that this is not a baby,
but they sort of treated it as though I was like beating up
like an actual like small girl child instead of like an adult
who's like roleplaying this, this, this creepy like I'm being bullied,
big help me.
So, yeah, as always, I have no respect for those that disagree with me.
My enemies are all ontologically evil.
Sounds reasonable.
But the odd thing is, right?
So this was this was a bit of a Twitter kerfuffle.
There was a bit of an argument about it, a bit of a debate happened.
Whatever, who cares?
But then, and I don't want to dwell on this too much,
but a couple of people who I would have considered to be my actual friends
in real life, a couple of them decided that they hate me now
and they're not my friends anymore and they like and they've disowned me over it.
If you can if you can believe that.
So, yeah, these these people who had been my my friends for years
suddenly decided that I'm bad and they hate me
and they and they they joined they joined like a new server
devoted deliberately specifically to to attack me.
And they started spreading
they started spreading completely spurious
lies and accusations and just totally fabricated
criminally pseudo criminal allegations
against myself and other friends of mine, based in no facts whatsoever.
So this is just what so I so I found this.
So I found this to be a very surprising reaction
to me being sort of rude to a stranger on Twitter, like somewhat rude,
maybe a bit uncalled for idly mean.
Yeah, I feel like it must have been like that.
There was something brewing.
I agree. That's what I was going to say.
I think this this is this must have been some some
something was percolating under the surface for a while there.
And this is just the the the moment that that brought it out.
I don't think I would.
I don't think I would actually lose a friendship over something so stupid.
But so that was like a big thing for me this week is like a lot.
Actually, it really bugged me because for a couple of days there
in the wake of this stupid in the stupid VTuber Twitter drama
and this weird fallout with these people, I was like kind of
sort of fixated on this drama and on like these like, you know,
these lies that were being told about me and people around me.
And I was kind of had to like think about that.
And it almost made me late for my stupid.
Tales gets trolled, a guest page, but it worked.
It worked out OK.
Phew. Yeah, kind of my fault,
because I didn't start working on it early enough.
But yeah, I don't know.
It's a bunch of bullshit, a bunch of that bullshit happened to me this week.
It was a bit of a bummer.
But, you know what, these people will get through it.
I mean, the PCP has survived.
PCP more dangerous bombardments than such such as that.
Oh, speaking of speaking of.
Do you see what released on the PCP channel yesterday?
Oh, yeah, we should definitely talk about this.
Yeah, although I did not watch it because I'm I'm scared of cringing too hard.
I also had to kind of I didn't want I didn't watch.
I saw it. I skipped through parts of it.
I didn't want to watch my own part.
I don't want to see it.
So embarrassing.
I feel very validated that some people said my and Munchie's verse was like the best.
I remember.
I worked hard making that sound pretty good or like like right rhythmically.
I was thinking rhythmically.
I remember liking I can't like like I can't actually rap.
But like, I think I think I wrote something pretty good.
I did not.
I think I wrote like the first line of mine.
And then and then I couldn't think of anything.
So Trixie wrote my verse and that's why it's bad.
My verse is bad, but it's because Trixie wrote it for me.
But I mean, the asterisk on that is like,
I'm sure it would have been even worse if I had written it.
So, yeah, I mean, I remember distinctly, we were like,
all right, we got to we got to do the we got to film the rap
because it's going to be good weather today.
And then we're going to have to do the OVA tomorrow.
And then the good weather is over.
Yeah. And we were all rushing.
And I think we were just sitting around waiting for you to write your verse.
Yeah, I had a pen and pencil and paper.
I was like, just sat around like all morning just staring at a blank page.
Just being like, I can't I can't think of anything.
And Trixie eventually was just like, OK, here, you want me to write it for you?
I was like, yeah, fine, just just write something.
And then it was kind of dumb.
But I was like, it's better than nothing.
It's better than what I was going to get.
So, OK, I'll do it.
Yeah.
Rack on four, baby.
The ride never ends.
It'll never end.
It'll never end. Two years.
There's still 2020 in March.
Still the 2020 will never go away.
The last.
Yeah. So this video was one of there's one more video that needs to come out
and it's the OVA, which we have.
So we put we spent real money.
We spent real money on like producing the OVA.
Yeah. So I'll be funny when it comes out.
At this point, it's just hilarious to me.
Like if these people still are actually coming out.
Yeah, I mean, it's better like at any point.
You know, better late than never.
I mean, I saw a comment on the thing saying, why now?
And I'm like, OK, yeah, why?
Why are you suggesting that we should simply never do it?
Yeah, we got to do it.
Yeah, we have to do it.
They have to be made if only so that we could say we could put the whole thing to rest.
You know what that is?
That's the kind of cowardly attitude.
That's a cowardly, trixy attitude.
That's a kind of like, yeah, I promised I'd do a thing.
Yeah, I took money for a thing, but it's been a while and I haven't done it.
So nobody cares and whatever.
I don't have to actually do it.
It's fine. I'll just pocket it.
Whatever. Fuck you. Fuck you, fan.
Die. You love it.
You love Radcon four.
Everybody loves Radcon four.
We're going to make it trend in twenty twenty three.
Yeah, absolutely.
When in twenty twenty three, when the OVA comes out.
I'm I'm hoping that it won't take too long.
Also, the dojin, I know.
I have not. I have still not heard any word from
Kaiju, Kaiju about him having a time available to do that.
So I don't know.
I'm still hopeful that that can happen.
I just I don't know.
Kaiju is a hard worker.
Kaiju is the problem is not and not a flake.
So it will eventually happen.
It just might not take a while, I think.
Kaiju is not flaked.
Kaiju told me I'd love to do it, but I am very busy.
I will do it if I can find the time.
And I said, OK, and, you know, he's he's got other things to do.
And he just has not been able to do it.
And I mean, that's what I said when I when I agreed to hit with that.
I made I agreed with that possibility.
I would I mean, I would be open.
He said, like, you know, it might be easier if you find someone else.
I would I would do that.
I would be OK with letting someone else do.
I would just need to see their style
and like know that they are going to do something good.
And I don't know anyone else who I who I don't know anyone else off the top
of my head or who has the right style and the right, you know.
If someone if I if someone were to, say,
at me on Twitter or DM me or something on Discord with an artist recommendation,
it's like maybe this guy kind of has the sort of, you know,
black and white kind of classic anime mango look that you're looking for.
I would be willing to consider alternatives.
In fact, I think Kaiju would would understand.
He's told me this, in fact,
if anyone knows anyone who they think would be a good fit for the.
I mean, please tell me, I just don't know anyone.
I've looked around on Twitter, but I didn't find anyone who exactly
matched what I was looking for.
I mean, there's so many artists.
I'm sure there's somebody out there.
I just I just don't know him.
Help me. OK. Help, help, help.
I actually kind of think somebody needs to help me.
Because I have money.
I have money to pay the artist who eventually does that.
I just need to find someone who will do it.
I'm I'm I'm mad.
I'm still mad about that other guy, that other guy, that other guy
just disappeared and he is still not he is still not returned.
He is still not posted anything anywhere, except on
not my anime list, but that but that anime website.
What are you saying?
I was thinking, have you maybe asked
Maryweather if they know anyone?
Oh, my God.
You know, Maryweather does, you know, lots of anime style people, you know.
You know, it didn't it didn't even occur to me.
It didn't even occur to me, but.
He might know, actually, he might know someone.
Yeah, although demo, I wonder how much.
I mean, his artists are some of his his artists are like big.
Some of his like 100 100 K follower artists on Twitter
that like draw his stuff sometimes.
So some of them might be expensive, but they might be.
I mean, they might be expensive.
They might know other people.
I think it's just sort of hmm.
It's it's a good avenue to look at.
It's actually a great idea.
You know, he he messaged me.
He messaged me just just like last week.
Just to see how I was doing, actually, like just to check in on me.
That's nice.
It is nice.
I it's it's it's funny, I don't know.
I it's it's it's it's nice.
It's nice because like I have like nothing.
I have like nothing to offer that guy.
There's no there's nothing he could possibly want from me.
I can't be suspicious of like any ulterior motive.
I guess he just I guess he's just.
Wants to be I guess he's just my friends, which is a nice thing.
But what what a guy.
Yeah, maybe you should ask him about that.
He would he would he would be a guy.
He would be a guy to know about that.
OK, yeah, there's an idea.
Still still if anyone has any recommendations,
I mean, feel feel free to message me about him because I would.
Like to see options.
I don't know.
OK, OK, OK, Nate is to do the OVA.
Yeah, and then that'll be the entire thing completely done
after the after the dojin, yeah, the OVA and the dojin.
And then we get our and then we get our radical money.
Truly the longest wait.
Yeah, it'll it'll partially make up for
for missing for missing out on that on that March Patreon money.
Yeah, Nate's I've been talking to him about it.
There's still Radcon for money just in a pile,
just waiting to be waiting for everything to be completed so we can all just get it.
I mean, you need to fund Radcon five.
If we were if we were Trixie, if Trixie had the money, Trixie would have just said,
it's been like it's been a while since the Radcon.
Never mind. We just won't do it.
I'll just take it. I'll just take it.
I'll just take the money and spend it.
And then I'll say and then when someone says, hey, Trixie,
what about all that content that was promised to be delivered over the money?
She'd say, oh, well, you know, I actually couldn't do that
because I just spend it on like my food and house.
I just spend it on my personal expenses, you know, sorry.
But, you know, that's that's just content creation.
You know, that's just what it's like.
That's what it's like to be popular on YouTube.
You just take money from people and just spend it on whatever.
And then you say, ah, well, I spent it all so I can't do it.
You see. Oh, I hate it.
And I hate you. I know all too well.
Not, not you, Gib.
I hate you, random commenter that implicitly agreed with that attitude.
Why? Why now? Why now?
Sh, shut the fuck up, you coward.
You're a fucking coward. You know that?
You're a, you're a quitter.
I'll never quit.
That's true.
OK, what do you think?
Um, yeah, I got nothing else to talk about.
Yeah, you want to go voicemails?
Yes, that's all right.
What's voicemail? Let's voicemail.
Yeah, we got. OK, it looks like the.
Oh, my God, it's a number of pages.
There's two and a half pages.
Looks like the first one here is this is this vocaru.
All right. All right.
Three, two, one, go.
Just like in Marvel Cinematic Universe, there exists a lot of parallel worlds
similar to ours in some ways, but radically different in others.
Today, we will look at one such world.
Welcome to the Twilight Zone.
I am supposed to be taking a break.
Instead, I'm working.
I'm doing something.
I'm sending taxes.
Sending taxes.
I am a cool guy.
I am a godlike.
I've got a deadline already done it.
Hello, this is the workaholic podcast,
and I am your host, the most masculine and manly man of all men, Gorilla Gifts.
And today we are joined by the creator of the hit indie game of 2016.
Hyper Light Drifter, the most feminine woman of all women who never drinks
sparkling water, Jane Devil.
Unfortunately, Tommy Oliver, the healthiest person who has ever lived,
has died when selecting best voicemails, so he won't be joining us today.
I am kidding.
Tom will never die.
Not in this world, not in any of it.
I like that that's a universal constant.
Let's start as usual from crowning the voicemail that our commenters decided
was the best in the previous episode.
Welcome, the Twilight Sparkle.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you, Jane.
I must ask, did you receive my email?
Yes, we have reviewed your CV and we accept you.
Welcome to the workaholic podcast.
But this is only one of the possibilities.
I will see you next time in the Twilight Zone.
Wouldn't that be fun?
Twilight Sparkle joined the workaholics podcast.
That would that would ruin everything as far as I'm concerned.
I would quit watching.
I would cancel my subscription on Hulu.
OK, yeah.
I like how everything was the opposite, except Tom still never dies.
Oh, Oblivionfall is.
Hmm.
Oblivionfall is posting some posting some cringe.
This must be.
Oh, this was his.
Oh, I think it was his friend Twi-Pi from the stream said that they were drawing Virginia.
And I guess this must be those Virginia.
Oh, they're very.
Why does she have a cock?
Why does she have a glowing green cock?
Yeah.
I mean, why not?
You could.
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
You could reform it using slime.
Damn.
Sure.
Yeah.
Well.
No, Virginia, stop fucking that sexy lady.
I want to fuck that sexy.
Get off her.
Let me let me at it, please.
Oh, she's got the she's got the horrifying, the horrifying utter, utter boobs.
Crotch tits.
Yeah, the crotch tits that I just my favorite.
What reaction, Emote?
OK, here we go.
An exclamation point and a little phantom horn looking on in approval.
I think that's, I think that's what we're going to be, we're going to be dealing with.
Nice, nice glowing nipples, Virginia.
You, you nailed it.
You hit it out of the park.
All right, we can't show that.
No, we can't show that on the podcast, so we're not going to dwell on it anymore.
OK, here's a next voicemail is an image.
Oh, it's the workaholic podcast.
The workaholics podcast, Jane Devil and Gorilla Give.
These are cool.
Yeah.
Deep symbolism of the egg.
Yep.
What's that?
She says that.
Oh, deep.
Yeah, that's what.
Yeah.
All right.
Good, good thing.
Next.
Next voicemail is called.
Trixie admits she's stupid in recent stream.
Bird agrees.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
You were up to and saw you were streaming.
Didn't know you rebranded.
Welcome back.
And yeah, the rebranding effort.
It complicated matters.
Not a lot of people really understand what happened or.
So I made this mistake when I rebranded of taking down all of my older videos and then telling people to re upload them and make archives.
Yeah, that was a bad idea.
Yep.
It's almost it's almost like everything that I said that made her so mad that she rage quit the podcast and swore me off forever.
It's almost like everything that I said that made her do that was exactly right.
Almost.
You might.
I mean, that's one way to interpret the situation.
Next.
Next voicemail is called.
Trixie still desperately tries to justify keeping a studio.
Three, two, one, go.
Are you going to stick to your studio brand?
IMO as a current fan.
I consider it to not be a very memorable, identifiable moniker for your work, both individually and as a collective.
I feel like a specific name is a lot better than blank studio, which feels more general, but it's supposed to feel general.
It's supposed to feel like a studio name.
I'm not supposed to feel like the name from my content.
I'm Trixie the Golden Witch.
The ex-studio is the ex-studio.
You know, I understand where you're coming from.
I don't think YouTube names matter very much at all.
If you look at popular YouTube channels, a lot of them have nonsense names, stuff that just doesn't mean anything.
Like people aren't looking at the name of the channel except to figure out what it like.
The only reason my name is confusing specifically is that I had a different name, you know.
And so it's like, what the hell is this?
People show up like literally what the fuck is the ex-studio?
I don't know who this is or what this is.
But like, you know, if the channel had always been called ex-studio, nobody would be questioning it.
I don't think it would have had a harder time getting popular.
Yeah, that's their point.
You changed the name.
It does hurt my YouTube SEO for me to have changed the channel name, but that would have happened no matter what I changed it to.
I think that in terms of, it's not really meant to be as memorable as it is meant to be timeless.
Like I said, I wanted a symbol that will always make sense and that will always be like applicable, you know.
So it's just, it's meant to be very broad so it can last forever.
It's meant to be something that you can just always recognize and everything can be tied to it.
And it doesn't have to be, you know, changed to fit a different project or whatever.
Like, everything that's released under the umbrella of the ex-studio is a ex-studio work, you know.
But that can encompass whatever the people who happen to be involved happen to do.
Who's involved?
Most people pronounce it like what does that mean?
What does that mean?
Okay, well yeah, yig is not, yig is not just for me.
Yig is for everyone who's releasing under the yig name, is yig.
I mean, you tried that.
You had a bunch of like, stoner idiots making shitty raps.
You turned it into a rap channel for a while.
It was a complete failure.
You shunted all those projects off to new channels and then didn't advertise them and just left them there to die because nobody watched them.
And now, it's like, it's like, it's like, I, okay, I'm gonna radically rebrand, right?
I'm no longer, like, Digibro is dead.
I am no longer just an anime analysis channel.
I'm more than that now.
I do, now I do raps.
Now I do shitty vlogs with my friends where I harass strangers at stores.
Now, now, this is the channel and everyone that doesn't like it was never a fan in the first place.
And you're never, and you're not even allowed to talk about my old persona.
You're a fake fan if you do.
And then a year later, like, oops, everything about that was a failure.
Okay, well, I'm gonna, okay, here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna go back to doing the exact style of content I did before.
I'm gonna do the exact stuff I did before I rebranded that people used to like.
Because you're gonna try and do that again.
But I'm still Yig Studio.
I'm still not that old channel.
You're still not allowed, Digibro was still just a character I was playing.
Not even a real person.
It was all just an act and you fell for it.
I am going to continue to do exactly what they did.
But it was still just an act.
I don't know, whatever, it's dumb.
There's no, there's no studio.
It's just me posting anime reviews again, but I swear, guys,
Yig Studio is still a thing.
One day we'll make low rent, which one day we'll make that original anime drawn by Mint Salad, LeMau.
Okay, whatever.
Next voicemail, I guess.
It's called B321GO.
Okay.
Next one is a YouTube video.
Bitcoin $100.
Experts are now saying Bitcoin be worth $100.
Okay, 3, 2, 1, go.
Experts are now saying Bitcoin could be worth $100.
And what this means is basically that if you have $100, you could purchase one Bitcoin.
Or if you had $1.
That would be the equivalent of something that you would need $100 of to purchase one Bitcoin.
He's trying so hard.
If a Bitcoin is worth $100, that means it's worth $100 more than $1.
And if you have $100 Bitcoin, then you have that's worth...
Got it.
The most brain-working crypto bro.
Damn, imagine Bitcoin $100.
Okay, the space between the bit and the coin.
Okay, I get it.
Very funny, very droll.
Imagine if Bitcoin $100.
I for one can't even.
Alright, next one is called Soul Link Nuzlocs.
3, 2, 1, go.
That sounds cringe.
That's why you don't fucking play it that way.
The point is to play it with a jolly good friend at the same time.
So you can turn the single player game with Pokemon into a cooperative experience.
So that you care about what happens in each other's runs.
And you can go further than just having that one fainting rule.
You can require both players to have each Soul Link Pokemon in both of their parties at the same time.
Which creates a unique team building experience for gems, dungeons, and especially the Elite Four.
Okay, okay, yeah.
If you were playing it, if you were sitting in the same room and playing the same battles as someone,
then yeah, I guess I can see how that would...
It seems really inconvenient, but I can see how it would be fun.
And I can see how it would be a more unique experience than a regular Nuzloc.
I guess I would get it, if that's how you did it.
Okay, next one is called...
It's a YouTube link.
It's 11 minutes.
Oh, it's a Yeeg Studio video.
Who cares?
We're not watching an 11 minute video as a voicemail.
What's...
Am I supposed to have an opinion about...
Spy X Family is for everyone.
Maybe it is.
I don't fucking care.
Why would you send this?
Okay, whatever.
At least it wasn't long.
Next one is called Casual Gamer.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey Ben, I don't know.
I started your game and I couldn't make it through the first hallway.
I don't know.
I guess I'm pretty casual gamer, but it just made me feel like I didn't want to play anymore.
And that's it. Bye.
What do you mean you couldn't make it through the first hallway?
The game is all one hallway.
Maybe I assumed it was bigger than that.
You're gonna have to be more specific.
Just use all of the buttons until you win.
Yeah, if you're losing, try shit in the menu.
Explore the options in the menu until you find some stuff.
And then just see what it does.
You gotta just trial and error, fuck around, and find out what stuff does,
and then you can figure out how to win.
That's how you do it.
I don't know.
I don't want to get more specific than that.
An idiot like Oblivionfall figured it out.
Even someone as lowly as Give and Take figured it out.
Surely you.
I consider myself a casual gamer.
Right, so there you go.
Oblivion said he doesn't even play video games, or not much.
So he said on the stream.
So even my mom was kind of figuring it out on the second try.
She just was bad at selecting the Sonichu.
And you know, I gave the game to my dog, and my dog won.
Right.
Even quicker than I did.
He just rolled around on the keyboard, and he won.
So you gotta have better excuses than that.
I gave it to a zygote, and the zygote completed it.
Like a fucking speedrun time.
I sacrificed the game on an altar to God, and God sent it back, and he had won.
He had beat it quite easily.
It only took him like two hours, so he was actually pretty good at it.
He understood the mechanics intuitively.
Next one is called, At It's All So Ugly.
Hey, that's my Twitter handle.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben Saint, after relentlessly abusing a drug-addled neurodivergent trans woman,
and now setting your sights on a small, seven-year-old Japanese girl,
is there anyone you want to rest?
Well, Ben.
I swear to God, people were acting as though she was actually like a little baby.
Even though, guys, she was like posting about the thing.
She was posting about my bowying, ooh-ooh.
She was doing it in character.
She was staying in character, and she was posting about it.
She doesn't give a fuck.
It was fine.
Nobody cares.
If you care, you're fucking stupid, okay?
You're fucking stupid if you think this was a big deal at all.
You know, Econ.
Econ wrote pages and pages.
He wrote like 30 fucking replies to me about it.
He was like, he would not shut the fuck up about this dumb nonsense.
That guy's fucking stupid.
That guy fucking sucks.
I don't know what the fuck is wrong with him.
This was intolerable to him.
That guy's full of fucking nonsense, and I can't fucking stand it.
That guy did me a solid.
That guy did me a solid when I had that breakup,
and he let me crash on his couch for a few weeks,
and I appreciate that so much that I've put up with him on Twitter for this long,
but I can't fucking stand it anymore.
He's too fucking much.
I can't deal with it.
How long do I have to abide by someone's nonsense?
Just because the game did me a solid.
Alright, how much?
How much is too much?
70 times 7.
Turn the other cheek.
Not anymore.
You should do him a liquid.
Okay.
Next one is called Lord of Ghosts vs. King Herod.
Oh, it's a vocaru.
It's a vocaru.
Okay, here it is.
Three.
You got it?
Yeah.
Alright, three, two, one, go.
God, it's three fucking minutes long.
I'm gonna kill myself.
Lord of Ghosts, I am overjoyed to meet you face to face.
You've been making quite a name all around the place.
You've been spooky, not raising from the dead.
What?
That's stupid.
Now I understand your mayor.
Taste.
At least that's what they say.
So if your mayor ghost, yes, the sweet lord of ghosts,
Prove to me that you love slime, let's go do some crime.
That's all you need to, and I won't kill you.
Come on, lord of the ghosts.
I only ask what I'd ask any slimy bro.
Look, there's a juvie.
Let's hit the death blow.
Oh, I love killing, as I'm quite a fan.
If you're gonna be mayor, well, you gotta lead by example, man.
So if your mayor ghost, yes, the sweet lord of ghosts,
Let's go and gorge on slime.
It'll simply be divine.
If you do that for me, I will let you go free.
Come on, lord of the ghosts.
What's this?
You say you have a comic all about your life?
But will it make me a pog?
You're saying it will?
It will.
Well, I guess I gotta read it and support the artist on Patreon.com.
Slash give or take.
Yeah.
Enough haunting, it is time for you to kill.
Slice and maim him, and slurp his slime with skill.
Oh, I'm slime cooming.
Yes, I can't wait.
I'm dying to be shown that you can truly titillate.
So if your mayor ghost, yes, the sweet lord of ghosts,
Prove to me that there is no cracks.
Cleave this juvie's head with an axe.
Is something wrong?
Lord of ghosts, what do you take so long?
Come on, lord of the ghosts.
Hey, aren't you scared of me, dude?
Mr. Spooky Attitude.
You're a joke.
You're not my mayor.
You're nothing but a spooky surveyor.
I'll kill you for good.
I always knew that I should.
Goodbye, you lord of the.
Goodbye, lord of the.
Goodbye, lord of the ghosts.
What's that above us?
That's a mega slime?
I've never seen that before.
What's going on?
Wow.
That's exactly how it happened.
Huh?
Yeah, that was great.
That's my favorite song from Jesus Christ, Superstar.
I don't, I can't, I don't think I have anything to add.
No, it was wonderful.
Wonderful, wonderful.
Thank you, Dusty Dumps, for another masterpiece.
Yeah.
Next one is a YouTube, it's a YouTube link.
18 minutes long.
Pro-skated to award-winning actor, the Jason Lee story, looking back.
Who?
I don't know.
Oh, this is the guy.
He's a skateboarder.
I know this actor.
I know he's been in stuff.
Wait a minute.
There's other skaters than Tony Hawk?
It's true.
No more skating, Tony Hawk, because you're just skating by after all that high impact sport,
destroyed your tendons and ligaments.
Destroyed your taint.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
The next one is an Imgirlink, dudes be like.
Oh.
Don't reply to me weirdo.
My brother in Christ, you made the reply with a soul utility of provoking a response by being more incendiary than it,
by being more incendiary than it is anything else.
I don't know, fucking cry about it.
Fucking, fucking cry about it, that I was rude to someone.
Like, shut up and die.
Shut the fuck up and die.
Why are you so upset?
Why are you so upset that I was rude to someone?
Who fucking cares?
You're literally more upset than she was.
She didn't even break a character, you psycho.
You don't know how upset they were, they just made a meme.
She didn't break character.
Who didn't break character?
The VTuber.
Oh, yeah.
I'm talking about the person who made the meme.
Oh.
They seem upset.
Well, I know this is a contemporary meme.
This seems like a genuinely meant criticism.
And anyone that genuinely gives me authentic criticism
is automatically mad and wrong.
Okay, whatever.
Haha, very funny, very good meme.
Ah, yeah, love it.
Okay, next page of these fucking voicemails.
Oh, it's another YouTube.
Oh, it's from smiling friends.
It's from smiling friends?
It's a Gilbert Gottfried scene.
It's 30 seconds long.
Well, whatever.
I'm not going to watch it.
Yeah, smiling friends good.
Gilbert Gottfried's dead.
That's too bad.
What are you going to do?
Next one is called Blue Wave.
Am I right?
Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys, what do you think is going to happen
during the midterms?
I think they're about to get silly.
Silly?
Yeah.
I think they're going to be pretty mid.
I've been seeing a lot of speculation
that the midterms are not going to go well
for the Democrats, and that's a shame.
I mean, Biden only barely beat Trump,
which is embarrassing.
And I don't think people have improved
their opinion of him too much.
Yeah, I don't see it going too well,
which sucks, but that's what you get
with Biden, I guess.
They have not really done that much.
They have not really done a lot of the stuff
they said they were going to do,
like student loan forgiveness didn't happen.
So, yeah, I think it might not go so well.
Also, they're like, I don't know,
like all the stupid, like anti-CRT
and like don't say gay stuff seems like
weirdly popular with fucking
the brainwirmed American populace, I guess.
I don't know.
I don't know if that's true or not.
That's just my impression.
Yeah, it's my impression as well.
I hope it's not true, but maybe it is.
I think it's just that the Democrats
are not providing anything of interest
to anyone to oppose it.
The only thing we're hearing about is like,
look at how evil the Republicans are being
and the Democrats say nothing.
It's like, okay.
Well, I guess that's the only political information
going on right now is the bad stuff.
I mean, that's my impression.
Oh, well.
Next voicemail is this YouTube link to,
this is, I've seen, I haven't watched these.
This guy, the gamer from Mars,
decided in the year 2022 to make a whole
like the story of Chris Chan series.
Boogie was in it and I fucking hate Boogie.
I know that this, I know that this,
this series does not respect Chris's agenda.
So it's bad.
How many times can one person be documented
by so many different people?
I mean, that's true, but that's been true.
People have been calling Chris like the most
documented person in the history,
like for a while.
I don't know why this guy decided
that now was the time for another one,
but I saw it going around.
I guess it got a lot of views.
So I guess he was right.
I don't know, whatever.
Fuck this guy and fuck Boogie.
True.
I don't know, man.
It's just, it's really easy.
It's really easy to just not misgender,
but you chose to do it.
So, I mean, that's on you forever, I guess.
Next one is called A321GO.
It is finally time to review another Paper Mario game.
I reviewed Color Splash when it came out
and that was pretty early in my channel's life.
Covering the game was what really launched my career.
So it's kind of surreal to be here again.
Enough time has passed that Nintendo has made
another Paper Mario game and here I am reviewing it.
I barely hear that, but what was that?
It was Arlo reviewing a new Paper Mario game
and saying that, wow, dunking on Color Splash
is what made me popular in the first place.
Can't believe they made a new Paper Mario
and I'm reviewing it.
So interesting.
Next one is called Slavoj iek on VTubers.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben Sheint is correct about VTubers.
Thanks, Slavoj.
Community is insular and cringe.
Thanks.
Good job.
Someone who was convinced that I am simply
a hater and an anti-VTuber bigot
and just had declared war on all VTubers.
Someone apparently sent Tom a question to do
on his Patreon podcast or whatever and asked him,
I don't know, I didn't hear the response
and I didn't hear the question.
I only heard it secondhand, but my impression is
that they asked him, like, Tom,
what do you think about Ben,
like cruelly harassing VTubers for no crime
other than being VTubers?
What do you think about Ben using his platform
to harass and destroy people who have done nothing
other than be VTubers publicly?
How do you feel about him going after them
for their identity like that?
And I assume Tom's response was like,
it's bad.
But apparently...
Anyway, the point is somewhere in that question
they said cringe and my problem with the post
was not that it was cringe.
I guess it sort of is, but that's not really...
It's not merely that like, oh, the post is cringe
and so I hate it.
It's not so banal as that.
It's mischaracterizing what I hate about it.
But whatever.
Okay, next one is a stupid YouTube link
that I'm sure I guarantee we won't watch.
It's Yig Studio again.
Why would you... Why?
Yeah, I get it. Yeah, she's putting out...
She's shot gunning out a bunch of stupid little videos.
Who cares?
I think the person putting all these YouTube links
might be the same person.
We don't watch them, so don't do that.
I would suspect probably so, but I would never...
I don't... I don't even...
I mean, obviously we're not going to watch it.
Maybe you think that this is like
suggesting something for us to talk about,
but no, of course not.
You should put that in a voicemail
if you want us to talk about something specific
and then have a YouTube link as like context
that we can watch later if you really want to,
but like just putting a link isn't going to do anything.
Okay, but even if the question is
what do you think about this video?
The answer is nothing.
Sure.
Next one is a very innocent question.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben Saint, I have a question.
Does your sister look more like you as a girl
or more like Nate as a girl?
I need to know for my masturbation fantasy,
kay, thanks, bye.
Oh, okay. Oh, that's why you...
I think my sister...
I think that my sister and Nate
look a little bit more like our mom
and I look a little bit more like our dad,
so I think Nate Grace looks more like Nate.
That's my opinion.
Like that one picture of Nate with the long hair.
Sorta, yeah.
Okay, next one is called What's in Your Fridge?
Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys and gal, what do you keep in the fridge?
Like all the time.
Me, broccoli, goes with everything.
Ben, you can't say seltzer.
I don't keep my seltzer in the fridge.
I keep it on a shelf because I don't really care
if it's cold and I don't have enough space
in my fridge to hold all the seltzer.
I have like 30 bottles of seltzer on my...
maybe not 30, maybe 20.
I put milk in the fridge
because I either have cereal with milk
or I put milk in my tea and I always need milk.
I keep low calorie ice cream in the freezer,
but that's not what you asked.
In the fridge I keep some vegetables,
some tomatoes and some greens,
like some spring mix greens.
I keep cold cuts, ham, turkey, eggs, cheese in the drawer.
And I keep low carb, bandurita tortillas.
I have several big stack of bags of bandurita tortillas.
And that's like it, that's like most of what I eat.
Oh, sauces, you know.
Caesar dressing, ranch dressing.
Butter, cheese.
I mean, stuff needs to be cold, I guess.
That is basically all I keep in my fridge
because that's pretty much most of what I eat,
what I just listed off there.
Make a lot of wraps, cook a lot of eggs,
make egg wraps sometimes if I'm feeling crazy.
We have eggs outside the fridge.
We have eggs on looker.
We have one of those weird egg spirals.
I guess you don't have to refrigerate eggs.
Yeah, I don't know what they're called.
Egg, we'll type in that egg spiral.
Egg holder spiral.
Oh, yeah.
Huh.
You know, I guess, I think eggs do keep longer
if you keep them in the fridge,
but like I know you don't have to keep them in there.
I eat eggs basically every day, so.
I see.
You know, heck, maybe I should,
I do need to conserve fridge space.
Maybe I should just start keeping my eggs out
because I share my fridge with like four other guys,
so I'm always like,
you pushed my shit out of the way.
All right, next one is called
vinegar man, vinegar man, vinegar man
from the at rapist.com.
Next one, okay, three, two, one, go.
The Simpsons women stared in amazement
at the saint.
Send the end word three times
without flinching.
Holy shit.
I love Benzane.
Oh, they made you say it.
Vinegar.
Oh, God.
Dude, you're gonna get canceled.
That's good.
I feel, wow, this guy really got me.
This guy really, really,
he really planned this one out
and the plan worked perfectly.
I tip my hat to you, sir.
I've been bested.
Okay.
Next one is called Killer Prince 930.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, listen to my speech impression.
Oh, Hannah, my father-in-law.
I can also make
an Obama.
No, let me be queer, Michelle.
Your stitch was a lot better
than your Obama.
Which one was which?
Which one was stitch?
You mean? No, you don't.
No, that's not what you meant.
I mean, there's only two things
I could have said that.
Post image.
This one, this is a link,
but it doesn't work.
Wait, it's got to work.
It doesn't work? Sorry.
No.
This post image link doesn't work.
Next one.
You should test it.
I don't know whether, like,
SpeakPipe shortens titles,
but double check, please,
that your links work before you post it.
Wait, what if I just did the part
in front of that last slash?
Does this one work?
No, it doesn't work either.
Sorry, it doesn't work.
Okay, next one is called Hi Ben.
What's your opinion on Super Smash Bros.
3, 2, 1, go.
Okay, I think it's just empty.
I'm not...
I like it, it's fun, I guess.
It's fun to play.
Sometimes I'm not very good at it.
The only people who...
Well, I used to play it sometimes
with my roommates, which could be fun.
Nowadays, the only people I would ever
play Smash Bros. with are the people
at Munchie's house,
and those guys are way better than me
to the point that I just can't play with them.
Yeah, yeah.
They're just playing a different game
than I am, so I don't really play it anymore.
It's fine, I was never like a huge
fighting game guy anyway.
I was pretty similar.
It was fun when I was young,
because I could, like,
spam, like, Samus's, like,
be over and over again,
and get them every time.
And then, they got the, you know,
whoever I was playing with, they just grew up,
they learned how to play, and I didn't.
Now I can't play the game anymore,
so I just have not bought the new one.
Remember, remember, if you will,
the slime fest where me and Munchie played,
we battled in Smash Bros. Brawl,
and it was the least fun thing
that has ever happened to me
in my entire life.
Because I just, I just don't know the game
at the same level.
I just don't know what I'm doing.
That's not the game's fault.
Okay, next one is an Imgur link.
Remember this?
Hey, look at this.
Yeah, yeah.
Remember this?
Well, egg on my face.
Benz, dudes be like,
don't reply to me weirdo.
My brother in Christ,
you made the reply with the soul utility
of being incendiary.
I've since changed my mind,
realized I hate this discourse.
So now I'm the one whose message
unprompted an unwanted response.
How rich, Benz St. undefeated once again.
I am genuinely...
That's character development.
I'm genuinely, honestly,
I wasn't, after thinking about it for a second,
I wasn't that mad about the first one,
although I still disagreed with it.
I'm genuinely impressed
by the level of like,
I thought about what I said
and I've come to a new opinion about it.
I feel like this is an...
What's the word?
An uncommon level of like,
self-reflection has been displayed here.
Um, I...
Yeah.
It kind of is, it kind of is true.
You also said something
to frustrate me.
Anyway, all water into the bridge.
Man.
Good meme, actually.
Fuck that dumb bitch and her stupid baby
talk.
Let's kill her.
Next one is
the quantifiable PCP member formula.
Three, two, one, go.
Alright, listen up, right?
Yeah.
So, you know,
Ben and Gibbon take,
they have all these sorts of guests
and they're on all the time,
but they're not members of the PCP,
so you claim.
Now, how do you quantify a member of the PCP?
Let me tell you, okay?
You might remember him.
There's a man named Jeff Thu.
And he was at one point
considered a host of the procrastinator's podcast
and he was only on three episodes, okay?
So, I think, quantifiably,
that means that any guest
that's been on the PCP more than three times,
an official member of the PCP now,
you kick them off.
Like, you kicked Jeff off.
We did not kick Jeff off.
Fuckin' cheesy manfredo, PCP.
Gamer's Tavern, PCP.
It's fuckin' all PCP all the time,
Ben's saying.
It's all PCP.
You can't escape it, Ben.
I'm really fuckin' high right now.
I can't believe it.
Okay.
Oh, boy.
Ben's saying,
I hate your guts,
but you have a good podcast.
Thanks, man.
Fuckin' keep doin' what you're doin'.
Woo!
If you're there, hi.
I like you.
I have no problems with you.
Yeah, thanks.
Bye.
Thanks, dude.
We didn't technically kick Jeff.
We basically just...
We and Jeff mutually agreed,
you're not really a part of his podcast.
Yeah, I think he just sort of left at some point.
There was a very brief period where
Blind Skywatcher was in the chat.
What?
Do you remember that?
No.
Trixie brought them in.
I don't know whether they were to be
a member of the Progress News,
but it was just a friend.
And they were cool,
but they didn't interact either,
so they left.
Yeah.
A member is just whoever we say is a member.
That's it.
We're just...
We're just not...
That's it.
That's the answer.
The member...
To be a member
means you have to have gone to Brony Khan.
Yeah.
And no one has done that, except us.
That's the disqualifier.
Next one is called
This voicemail has lore,
three, two, one, go.
Oh, God!
The name-fuckers are here.
I left a voicemail
saying they were cringe a year ago,
and now they've come for me.
Oh, God!
That's insane.
What have I done?
What have I robbed?
That's insane.
They teamed up with Sotchu.
They have dragons.
They're fucking here, bro.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Well, what did you fucking expect?
You called the name-fuckers cringe,
and they didn't get to fuck Nate,
so, like, where do you think they're going to go?
Final Fantasy VII.
They have dragons.
And Sotchu.
Man, that is lore.
That's accurate.
Okay, next one is called
Nate Theory, three, two, one, go.
All right, I've got a theory
about what happened to Nate, okay?
Now, listen up.
Listen up, you fucking sheephole
that believes the real story.
The real story.
Thank you, Mr. Truth.
Here's what happened, okay?
Nate, the best guy ever, fucking died.
He's dead.
He slipped and fell and hit his head
during a shower speed run.
And that's why he hasn't
just been on the PCP now.
He's thinking, like, he's streamed, right?
But how?
It's Ben's saying.
He has a weekend at Bernie's saying,
Nate's corpse to spread a narrative
that he is not dead,
but he can't be,
they can't be in the same place
at the same time,
because Ben is Nate,
so that's why he's not on the PCP anymore.
Case closed.
Well, I guess he cracked it.
Yeah, I like the shower speed run,
because that's around the time
Nate stopped coming on,
is when that was...
He slipped and fell and died
during a shower speed run.
We can't let this get out.
We can't let this get out anyway.
We've got to retain the sanctity
of the shower speed run.
We've got to keep people doing that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We can't let them know that it's dangerous.
If we let them know that one of our own guys
slipped and fell and died
during a shower speed run,
then we'll be liable
when other people inevitably do that,
and we don't want that kind of responsibility, so...
You know, the rest is history.
Next one is called,
Is Gib Dead?
Three, two...
Well, Gib?
I don't know.
Let's see their case.
Let's find out.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Gib...
Did...
Last year you talked a lot about
your mystery illness.
Did you ever get that, like,
sorted out or figure out
what it actually was?
Are you doing better?
Are you dead?
You don't have to answer
if you don't want to.
I was just worried.
Seagulls in the background.
Seagulls on a pirate ship right now.
I am not dead.
What it was was...
Well, it was...
It's still a mystery,
exactly what it was
caused by,
but I was, like,
extremely low on vitamin D,
and I had to take supplements.
I guess because I was inside a lot.
I feel like I'm inside a lot anyway.
My vitamin D was low.
I have a hunch that it had to do with, like,
like, weird doses of, like,
the HRT I was taking.
I'm taking it still,
but, like, it's fine now,
so I'm not entirely sure what it was.
At the time I was living somewhere different,
so it could have been something in that place.
I don't know,
but I'm alright.
I'm fine.
Well, I'm glad that's over.
Yeah.
Yeah, weird.
It could also be, like, a number of things,
like, little things colliding.
Like, maybe I was eating badly,
as well as all those other things.
I don't know.
So you're saying you faked it?
I'm saying I faked it for attention.
I got loads of money.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Alright, alright, alright.
As long as you made a turn to profit.
As long as you faked it.
As long as you faked it and made money.
Okay, next one is called Fuck Trixie.
3, 2, 1, go.
Shut up, man.
No!
They got you.
Next one is called Ben's Weekly Reminder Play Delta Rune Chapter 2.
Okay, some day.
Next one is called Oblivion Fuck.
3, 2, 1, go.
In Episode 295, Oblivion 4 said he'd upload all of his compilations of voicemails
to the ThemSnakes channel by the end of February.
And then the comments he said might take until March.
And now it's halfway through fucking April and they're still not there.
Where are they?
I saw him.
I think they are up now, right?
I think I saw a video.
Oh, did you?
I saw him replying to a YouTube comment this week saying that he would do it soon.
So maybe he did.
I don't know.
I could swear I saw it posted somewhere kind of recently, like within a day or so.
I don't know which chat it was in though, so I can't find it.
I don't know.
I don't remember which channel he said he was going to upload it on to.
It's either up already or he says he's going to put it up like soon.
It was on the ThemSnakes?
Well, maybe it was unlisted on ThemSnakes because it's not public.
Man, I don't know.
He said he was going to post it.
Like yesterday or the day before, I saw him reply to a comment saying like,
yeah, I'm going to do it like tomorrow.
So probably soon.
He's been saying that he wants to get that up and people have been asking him for it.
Next one is called Ukraine Loves Nazis 321 Go.
Yeah, I think after that episode finished, I went to look into that particular thing
and I came to the same conclusions.
It was a Russian propaganda thing to make it look like.
And so it was like, that's why the U.K., the U.S. and Ukraine voted against.
And everywhere, the country abstained because they just didn't want to get involved, I guess.
It was not what it seemed as on the tin.
As these things often, they get blown out of the work.
I guess it worked then because now they can show that graph being like C,
only the United States and Ukraine voted against it.
Yeah, that's sort of the point.
Well, I don't know if that's the point of doing it in the first place,
but certainly a result of it is that people who do not look into it too hard
get the impression that that's what it's saying and then they just use it as a point.
They could just post it.
I see.
Okay, next one is called Slime Times Exposed 321 Go.
RFCK is socket.
RFCK is stinks.
It's endless words.
It's a shitty game, shitty community.
They'll take you and they'll cheer you out and spit you back out.
They'll all betray you.
The game itself isn't even fun.
Killers just fucking cheat.
That's the whole thing.
They just openly love exploiting and abusing.
They're just making the game not fun for anybody.
And then the Raddies are fucking cowards.
They just enable it.
Which bar is this guy at drinking?
He's at the king's wife's son.
Going out there loud and proud.
Like they're king ones, whatever.
Fucking starting an open and honest conversation.
Don't do it.
Don't listen to that.
Literally, your profile comes in every week.
Fucking tells you to play RFCK.
He's just tempting you.
He's literally a demon.
He's a fucking snake.
We just talk like if you don't believe me.
He's literally a demon.
That's true.
Don't do it.
I've seen him.
Thank you.
Thank you?
Yeah, he's like...
He's crying into his...
Oh, I forget if there's a name for like a slime beer.
There might be one.
But he's crying into his...
His slime and tonic over about how...
The Raddies just enable the killers.
They just exploit and everything.
Culture death.
I lost all my slime and it sucks.
That's thematic though.
I appreciate it.
That's in line with the vibe.
You've got to have some losers, you know?
You've got to have some losers.
Mary slime and alia to all.
Even the haters and losers.
If you, if you, listener want to be just like this guy,
a loser, go play RFCK.
Next one is called...
Am I like Ben Hughes autistic for making voicemails?
Three, two, one, go.
Damn.
This Ben Hus person.
You know, Simpsons of Blue Ninjas person.
You said how they waste a bunch of time on this because of their condition.
Ben Hus.
I am spending a lot of time on voicemails too.
I am so on the spectrum, oh god.
But it is pretty fun to see just what you are capable of,
even if it's not perfect and doesn't even always work out.
There is joy in creating something from scratch, crafting a story.
This guy's standards for a story just slightly lower than mine.
That's all there is to it, really.
I did actually download Sony Vegas and Vocaload.
Just you wait.
I will learn to write proper music just to mess with you, Ben.
I won't mess with Gib.
Only compliment.
Then it's funny to mess with.
Gib is fun when Gib's shy.
Instead of Elden Ring Gib, God, it's Elden Ring Gib cute.
Thank you.
Thank you, Twilight.
Is there more?
Is that a pig?
Maybe.
Okay.
Yeah, the more time you spend on something, the more autistic you are.
Yeah.
It's a metric for how much you care.
You go to your doctor.
They say, how many autisms am I exuding?
Like in radiation, they get a little machine out.
And they say, how much time this week did you spend on an activity that brings you joy?
And you say, some doctor.
And they'll say, well, then you're somewhat autistic now.
Get out of here.
That'll be $100, please.
So true.
Next one.
Well, there's a Twitter link, and there's also a voicemail to go with it.
So I guess the Twitter link is to, from this at drinking moth, is this animation.
Which is a reply...
It's a reply to teleperte.
There's a teleperte animation here.
Okay, let's listen to it.
Three, two, one, go.
So anyway, did you ever notice how the coolest animation has crazy camera movement?
Talput always has something going from front to back.
Perspective movement is my sexuality.
No, no, no.
Let me try this again.
Perspective movement is my sexuality.
Is my sexuality.
Like this clip is so simple, but those two hushes had so much.
This is why we don't like top-down perspective games, probably.
I mean, they're saying that they really like how the animation includes the box moving in perspective.
Which is true.
Is this person drinking moth, or are they...
I don't know.
I don't think they are.
But they might be.
But they didn't say that they are.
I feel like I've seen that at somewhere before.
Yeah, me too.
Are they following me?
Yeah, no, they're probably drinking moth.
Yeah, probably.
There's a nice little animation.
I mean, I like perspective.
It's good.
You should follow Ululilia, who really likes parallax scrolling.
Sorry, it's our reply on Twitter that I'm going to ignore.
It's not pertinent to what's going on right now.
Next one is called, Are voicemails dead? 3, 2, 1, go.
Okay, the answer is yes.
That was the last one.
Next one is...
Okay, it's another drinking moth link, which is not embedding.
Whatever, I'll just open it up on Twitter.
I got reincarnated as a Lithuanian girl, but I need to take revenge on Benzane
for stealing the Kawasaki scroll.
This image will be seen by the right person at the right time,
though I believe it will be next week, not this one.
Is that Mage?
That's the idea, I think.
Yeah.
Funny that you wouldn't make her purple then.
Okay, well...
What's the voicemail?
Oh yeah, let's listen to the voicemail.
3, 2, 1, go.
Did you translate the name Saint?
It's said like Benzakoni or something.
I think they translated the word Saint, which is dumb.
Benno santo san.
It's Benno santo san, yeah.
Well, I'm laughing.
I'm not sure if this is Mage or just some girl.
Other than being Lithuanian, there doesn't seem much Magey about her.
I think it's not literally Mage,
but the thing they're going for is the reference to Magey's violent childhood.
Yeah, yeah.
Her battle warrior youth in Lithuania.
Yes, I think so, which is fair.
What is this thing she's holding? Is it like a staff?
I thought it was a scroll, not a scroll, a katana that's wrapped up.
Wait, it says, hold on, there's something written on it.
Enhance? Oh, it says at drinking moth.
It looks to me like a gnarled wizard staff that's been wrapped up in leather
and slung across the shoulder like one might sling a guitar.
So, I don't know, that's my best guess.
Good stuff, good stuff, drinking moth.
Next one is, to give spoilers for Sonic 2.
They show Shadow after the crit.
Three, two, one, go.
Gib and listen to me.
What?
Watch the Sonic 2, the hedgehog movie, whenever, however you can.
Watch a camera or something.
Spoilers, it sort of follows the story of Sonic 3 and Knuckles.
And then, after that, it's going to follow the Sonic Adventure 2 timeline.
And if you know anything about Sonic Adventure 2, Ruge the Bat shows up.
And they're going to have big, old, bouncing titties.
Yeah!
4K on the big screen.
Wait, you're saying that, does that happen in Sonic 2?
Or is it going to happen in Sonic 3?
Well, if the character of Ruge the Bat is in the next one, because I know that Shadow is a hedgehog.
Isn't it Rogue the Bat?
No, Ruge.
Is it Ruge?
Oh, fuck.
Ruge is in like femme fatale sort of.
Yeah, yeah, makeup, yeah.
But like, the, I know that Shadow was like hinted at at the credits of the Sonic 2 movie.
So Shadow will be in the next one, and then with Shadow comes Ruge probably.
And then that robot guy, the Eggman robot that goes good.
Oh, E1M1. Yeah, I know the one you're talking about.
Yeah.
The Rogue.
I would be very interested to see...
There's no way they'll put him in.
He's too specific.
He's specifically in Sonic Adventure 2.
They'll never put him in anything again.
They put him in...
He was in Sonic Heroes as well.
Oh, was he?
In the dark trio.
Each team has a trio of things, and it's like Shadow, Ruge, and the robot.
It was a different robot though, right?
I thought it was the same one.
I think it was also in Sonic the Six.
I remembered that it was just a similar robot.
But maybe.
Okay.
I feel like he's a recurring enough character to be in there.
And the idea of it like a robot from Eggman going Rogue and being a good guy...
I don't know.
I think that was...
Yeah, it's a whole...
Interesting story thing to add in.
It is.
That's true.
It would make sense.
I feel like he's an even more minor character than someone like...
Is it Vex the Alligator?
Is that his name?
I don't know their names, but yeah.
I feel like he's even less important than that alligator.
And that alligator is not good.
He might make a cameo.
I don't know.
In any case, if Shadow's in there, they'll probably have Ruge.
And I would be interested to see how big the boobies become for a family movie.
Because her design is so like...
Boob-centric.
That's nice.
Sexually bad.
A little bit.
I mean, if you look at the original models from the games, they're not like...
They'll probably cover up for a film, I feel like.
But not that much, but will they?
That's the most important thing.
She was an original...
Oh, wow.
Yeah, they're actually really big in Sonic Adventure 2.
They're actually really prominent, I forgot.
Wow, okay.
Yeah, maybe.
Ruge the Bat.
Which one's Sonic Adventure 2?
Yeah, I feel like they'll tone him down a little bit from this.
Next one is...
An image.
No, it's a YouTube link.
Yeah, you're right, sorry.
It's a YouTube link.
I bet this one's gonna suck.
That's just some gay.
It's another review.
It's a review... whatever.
Okay, I'm not watching it.
Bye.
Next one is an Imgur.
There we go.
Oh, so Beno Saintos.
I'm directing Ben Sento.
Ben Sento.
Because of Ben Affleck's Wikipedia, there are evidence of Ben Shapiro.
Oh, that's very interesting.
Yeah, okay, I guess Ben.
I guess you just say Ben.
Ben?
Is N the only consonant?
Ben.
Is that the only consonant sound in Japanese that doesn't have a vowel?
Maybe there's not.
Because I thought most of Japanese consonants were like...
Well, they have N.
You can't really...
But is that the only one?
I don't know, I don't speak any language at all.
Okay, we'll fair enough.
We've all learned some.
I like that it's...
I'm looking at the symbol for no is just that curved line.
And the symbol for N is a very similar curved line, but with like another dash on top of it.
I find that fascinating.
Next one...
I lost my place, sorry.
Okay, next one is called Crisis Averted.
Three, two, one, go.
Thank God.
Last week I thought I started HRT on Ben's birthday and like...
That would have been too cringe.
Could you imagine I would have had to de-transition out of embarrassment?
The only thing more cringe than starting HRT is starting it on Ben's birthday.
Thanks for clarifying, and happy belated birthday, Ben Saint.
Thank you.
Next one is called Re Phantomhorn, one of two, three, two, one, go.
Ben Saint, your game Phantom's Revenge?
That was a lot of fun.
I just have one request.
May I, pretty pleased with the cherry on top, have permission to draw fan art of your OC Phantomhorn?
No.
Thanks for asking, no.
Ask for permission if you don't want to do it.
Always ask for permission if you hate yourself.
Sorry, the answer was yes by default, but when you ask, it flips that switch.
I'm sorry, these are the rules that I made up.
Next one is Re Phantomhorn, two of two.
We'll listen to it first, three, two, one, go.
Surprise, bitch.
Happy belated birthday, Ben Saint.
Curious Phantomhorn getting squished by a train.
No, no.
Okay, let's see.
Oh, no.
Wait, is this post-squish?
He's got stars swinging around his head.
That hurt a little bit.
Yeah, I guess it must be.
Damn, he looks pretty good for having just been run over by a train.
Yeah, he's probably made of that gumu gumu gumu, you know?
Yeah, because Luffy ate the Nika Nika fruit.
So actually, the real gumu gumu fruit, Phantomhorn, just found it in the trash one day,
and just ate it by accident, as he often does.
I like his hoodie.
I actually gave him a little pink hoodie with a black one.
That looks cool, I like it.
Oh, this is pre-slime, he has the old horn.
I mean, if he had the slime, he would definitely survive being run over by a train.
Yeah.
Obviously, but this is pre-so, it's a little scary.
Okay, next one is...
Oh, next one is...
Thank you, by the way, I like it, I love it.
Next one is Ben's weekly reminder to upload these episodes to Spotify.
I will, I will.
Well, I'll do my best.
I don't know if it will work, because I've never done it before.
Okay, next one is a YouTube link.
It's a link to the garlic house music video.
Okay, cool.
You want us to talk about it? We already talked about it.
We already talked about it.
It's cringe.
It's cringe, but I'm glad it exists.
Yeah, yeah, it's fine.
Watch the garlic house music video, it's funny.
It's painful, but it's funny.
Check it out if you want to have a fucking rollicking good time.
Okay, next one is an Imgirlink.
It's a...
CHCW.
Oh, it's CHCW.
Who's that?
This is the guy who always comments, no Nate, no watch.
See you next week.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, his name is SHCWVideos, and yet his channel has no videos.
I wonder what the SHCW stands for.
I also wonder that.
Maybe you can let us know in the comments, along with your typical response.
If you feel so inclined, I'd be curious to know.
Thank you.
Okay, we're almost done.
Wow, we're almost through these.
Yeah, a lot of them are just YouTube links that we're not...
That's another Yig one.
Why? Yeah, I'm not gonna have anything to say about any particular video.
I am not subscribed to the cultural conversation nor the channel.
Yeah, there's just nothing to say about this.
Next one is called Introducing Poogee.
Poogee? Poogee?
Three, two, one, go.
So since you don't hate pigs, I thought formal greetings are in order.
This is Poogee.
Poogee, say hello.
Oh, pig it.
Holy shit.
He whistles.
Did Upload and Fall just follow me on Twitter?
Oh god, I am dying again.
Aren't I?
Oh well, better get over with it.
Hello?
Well shit, now what do we do?
It's the pig.
The pig was at the door.
There's a pig at the door.
Damn, that's a horror story for me personally.
I like Poogee.
She said Poogee.
She said Poogee, so I'm gonna assume it's meant to be Poogee.
Unless you typo it in the voicemail.
We have to protect Poogee from the pig.
From the big, from his big evil cousin.
Poogee's good.
Poogee can grow up to be, he can make something of himself, not like that psychopath.
Next one is a YouTube link, WaitHe'sReal at gmail.com.
Oh, it's a link, it's a video about Brad Garlinghouse.
It's Brad Garlinghouse.
Yes, Brad Garlinghouse is a real human person with real human feelings
and a real human cryptocurrency that you can buy right now.
It's Ripple, baby!
That's it, that's the last voicemail, we did it.
It wasn't even that bad.
What do you think?
I said that's the last voicemail, we actually did it.
It wasn't as bad as I thought.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a good day.
It's a good day, I'm feeling good.
I got up early to finish my, to finish that Tails Gets Trolled page
and now we've done the podcast in it under three hours.
Yes!
There's a few people who are crying right now.
A few people say no!
I saw someone...
I have two more hours to work my shift digging ditches at the graveyard.
I'm sorry about those people.
Yeah, somebody on the last episode, it was four hours long
and they're like, ah, could you please make a five hour episode?
Yeah, come on!
Come on, only four!
Just, why?
Just keep it going, man!
Yeah.
No, I will, alright.
I will put those bonus episodes up.
I will attempt to get that shit on Spotify
and Apple Podcasts and whatever else.
Hopefully before this episode goes live
and take out my Tails Gets Trolled page.
Link in the description, check out my Tails Gets Trolled page.
I've worked really hard on it.
Yes.
And we have to keep posting to the Patreon.
We have to remember that.
Yeah, I don't think I'm going to forget again.
I'm really mad, I'm really fucking mad about that.
But it's too late to do anything.
Yeah.
We were considering like posting all of the episodes individually
and people would get charged for them this month.
But I feel like that would have scared people
and made them like unpledge
because there's like a bunch of stuff happening at once.
All that would do is a few people would just get charged like eight times for one month
and it would be shitty for them.
And most people would probably, it would just exceed their monthly limits that they place
and it wouldn't even like get,
it wouldn't make, it would make a little bit of the money back,
but not most of it.
So like, I don't, yeah, I don't even think it's worth.
We just got, we just got a call.
We just got a call March of March of a lost month.
It's a bummer.
It's a bummer, but hopefully the patrons,
hopefully you patrons will consider it a gift.
A lucky strike.
Yes.
As they say.
And pay us by pledging to the patron at $5 to get access to the Minecraft server
and have fun in that video game that you love so much.
I wouldn't say no.
I wouldn't say no to that.
Yeah.
Become a patron, get the bonus episodes,
get all the past bonus episodes including the Radcon 2 documentary.
Join the Minecraft server.
Marron Pan will help you get it set up and he will,
surely he will be overjoyed.
If you're, here's the thing.
When you're a PCP patron, you're not just getting the bonus episodes,
you're not just getting the Minecraft server.
You're getting a man-servant who will be overjoyed.
You can, you have a 24 hour helpline that you can DM on Discord and say,
Marron Pan, I can't find the next NPC.
Where's the next step in the quest?
And he'll be like, I'm in.
I'm joining the game.
I'm going to walk you there right now.
I'm confident that nothing would please him more
than to receive queries about his Minecraft server
and be empowered to enable you to appreciate all that's on offer there.
So that's a deal of the lifetime as far as I'm concerned.
Anything else?
Check out my streams if you're interested in watching me.
If you need time to fill and the PCP isn't long enough,
I guess watch my Elden Ring streams on Gibb and Take on Twitch.
Yeah, also, if you want to see Oblivion Fall play both of our games,
Phantom's Revenge and Pumpkin Alley.
You can check out the VOD for that stream he did last week.
It was very fun.
Oh yeah, and check out Pumpkin Alley because there's the pumpkin patch.
It's slightly different and there's more lizards.
I still have not.
I might go and hunt that eighth lizard because he never found that eighth lizard,
but I might.
If I have some free time this week in between doing all that other shit,
maybe I'll hunt a lizard.
Okay, check it out.
That's going to be it.
That's the episode, baby.
That's it.
See you next week.
I love you so much.
And you could do anything you put your mind to.
Even subscribe to our YouTube channel.
Okay, goodbye.
See ya later.
See ya.