Hello everyone, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm the best
guy ever, aka Ross, and today we're joined by Munchy.
Hey guys, it's me, Joey. I want to let you know that I am really funny. Just trust me
on this one. I say things that don't make sense and I am stupid. Please laugh.
Tom is here.
Hi, my name is...
A.K. Rachel.
He is totally Rachel.
I don't know what we're talking about. Fuck this shit.
Jennifer Aniston had the best career of any of them, so things are looking up for you,
Tom, in the long run.
Alright, I got decent tits, too.
Accurate.
You don't know she's a guy.
Speaking of decent tits, here's Hippo, A.K. Monica.
No, no, wrong.
Just Monica.
No?
No.
No, no, you're Phoebe. You're definitely Phoebe.
I was trying to think of what they are called. That's the only one I know, Phoebe, because
she says something and people laugh afterwards, so I assume that is...
She's funny.
Yeah, she's like, what's a fridge? What's a fridge, guys?
And people are like, she doesn't know what a fridge is.
I just keep my food in organic ice chambers.
Dude, that's not totally me.
Dude, that's Moana.
Yeah, that's true.
And then the actual Monica.
Monica.
Mage.
The only Monica I remember is from Doki Doki Literature Club.
They're the same character, a little known fact.
We literally have a PCP theme contest when our theme is, I'll be there for you.
Oh my God, I almost forgot to say, hey, hope you enjoyed that intro song that was the
new PCP theme, everybody.
There was no intro song because that was a cold open when we were talking about this.
Fade into the thing.
And now we'll go to the theme right now. Boom.
Connie, I know. What is this? You're supposed to be working right now.
I'm sorry, darling. I'm listening to the PCP right now.
It's so interesting.
And now we're back.
We'll play two times. Don't worry.
That would be good, actually.
Yeah, maybe we should experiment with cold openings more.
I don't know. Okay, well, whatever. Hello, everyone. Hope you're doing well.
Hope your week's been good. Glad to see you. Glad to know you.
Congratulations to Sasuke Pro, by the way, for winning the contest again.
Thank you for doing this to me. You've made my life infinitely worse.
You have recommended me a laptop that has Windows 10 on it.
And I asked you. I asked you specifically, like, two times, is Windows 10 evil
slash a scam? And you said two times, no, you should get it.
You should get Windows 10. And I have it. And I can conclude that it is indeed a scam
and I am brainwashed thanks to you.
Oh, well, sure. I would love more explanation on that so I can thoroughly destroy that argument.
Yeah, Munch, I think when I got Windows 10 on my new computer, I've been using 7 for a long time,
I figured out ways to turn off most of the more insidious features of Windows 10,
which was good.
Okay, I open up Windows 10. And the first thing during it's like setup phase
is just asking me outright. Keep in mind this is asking me so I can turn it off,
like, thanks for letting me turn it off.
But just the fact that it is opening upon, like, do you want us to track everything that you do
and give you ads on your computer? Like, not anyone's been on your computer?
Just strike one.
Then second, I try to go install Google Chrome and then it won't...
Big mistake.
It, like, it asked me, I think, like, three times first when I Google search Google Chrome.
Like, when I am in the search bar, I am Google searching Google Chrome.
It's like, hey, can you do that? Microsoft Edge is better.
I go down to Google Chrome and I start to open.
Hey, did you know that Microsoft Edge is better?
I go to set it as default. Hey, by the way, just want to let you know you should not be using this software you downloaded.
You should be using our software because this is how we send the subliminal messages to your spinal cord to make you buy more products.
I go to, I have to download, like, Classic Shell because the, like, normal, like, what was it called?
The little icon down the bottom left.
I open that. There's, like, ads for fucking, like, Disney and Minecraft built in.
Wait, I can undo that?
That's like, that's been, like, the worst thing. I fucking hate it.
Dude, you have to install Classic Shell.
It just puts the Windows 7 menu back on there. It's great.
Damn, I want that real bad.
What is this problem? I haven't seen any ads. What are you talking about?
Well, do you have Windows 10?
Yes.
If you click the little start menu on the bottom left, like, I get, like, right now, I get, like, Royal Revolve 2.
I am pretty sure you can disable those.
Yeah.
You can disable those as you dig in the menus.
Okay, I should probably do that then.
I just, like, the design of Classic Shell better.
I'm sure most of the, I mean, I've turned off most of those things.
But the fact that they were there in the first place makes me not be able to trust it whatsoever.
Yeah, I would never be able to trust Windows 10 because it has Disney ads for it.
Have you trusted an operating system in the first place?
I mean, they're all fair enough.
I feel like when I turn on my computer that has Windows 7, I'm not instantly going to be reported to the NSA.
Not for, like, when I Google search something, I know Google's gonna give me to the NSA.
But I feel like when I turn, like, press the on button on my computer, I'm not being catalogued in a do not fly list.
That's how I feel when I turn on Windows 10.
I'm terrified of the dystopian nightmare that is clearly being foreshadowed here by, like, the fact that these, like, specific ads are here.
Like, I know that Windows is a Microsoft product, but, like, I gotta think here, it says, like, buy Minecraft for Xbox.
Like, that's in my start window right here on Windows 10.
Like, what if they just turn, what if they just get rid of the switch to turn off these ads, which will happen one day?
You know, and then we're fucked.
Oh, yeah. I mean, well, Microsoft's always gonna be looking out for their own shit.
The reason, like, Windows 10 is such a clusterfuck is because the new CEO of Microsoft is, like, trying to pivot their entire business away from selling Windows licenses and making them everything I paid service.
Windows doesn't cost, like, forever, Windows didn't cost, like, money, like, Windows 10.
Like, for, like, two years, they're like, just take it, just take it, because they're trying to build a database like Google's.
So they're just, like, doing the same thing Google does on the web, just on your computer.
Yeah, so, like, that's just the modern way.
If you want to, like, get rid of that, we all just have to go become fucking woke as shit and just use a little bit of Linux.
This is why, this is why Adblock is actually, like, a really good societal thing.
It's not just that it's, like, you know, a nice convenience, like, I don't want to see ads and you can block them.
The fact that so many people use it all the time puts them in the mindset that seeing ads is bad, because if ads were all over the place, all the time, your whole life,
you would have, like, generations of people that were, like, conditioned to expect ads everywhere and, like, the inability to turn them off.
This blows my mind to shits. I always forget about it until I accidentally go on a, uh, go on without an ad blocker.
Do you know the YouTube.com homepage has a giant banner ad above all your recommended videos?
Yeah, I, yeah, would I ever go on my mom's, like, like, laptop for whatever reason.
I did that the other day to fucking, be, be, be, be, be, my phone was dead and I had to check my email for something.
I went on there and I checked YouTube for a second and there's a huge giant ad for, like, some car thing, just, like, covering the entire screen.
Yeah, just, like, can you, I can't imagine using the internet like that.
Like, you, you poor peasants out there who don't know what we're talking about.
I feel so bad for you and you're unenlightened lives.
Like, how, how are you not just, like, in a Mercedes Benz right now?
You've been brainwashed by these giant ads.
I'm gonna try to put an ad blocker right now and I'm gonna look at, I'm gonna look at square in the fucking eye right now.
Staring at the beast.
I heard rumors a while ago that, like, ad blog was taking bribes for certain ad companies to own certain ads.
Ad block plus is. That's why I don't use ad block plus anymore.
I have, like, three or four different ad blocks.
You block origin represent.
We all just need to get a VPN. That's, that's how you really.
What is that? I don't know what that is.
It basically, it masks your IP address and stuff so, like, the companies don't know where you are or what you're looking for.
It, like, blocks your internet, like, shit.
But what, can I still set up my Minecraft server with my IP?
I'm sure you can. Yeah.
Well, thank you.
I've been needing to get one of those for a long time.
We need, we need to get the PCP sponsored by private internet access because they give out sponsorships to everybody.
We need to get the PCP on fucking...
I've seen plenty of ads for, like, on Tim Pool and stuff.
Who's, who's a bigger, who's a bigger defender of free speech than the podcast that drops racial epithets,
like, every episode. That's true.
We need it more than anybody. They'll partner with us for sure.
We're on this page.
Bener.
There you go.
There's your pledge for the day.
Is that against people who wear beanies?
Yeah.
That's always been the fucking weakest one I've ever heard of.
Yeah, that's incredibly tepid.
So, so fucking weak.
What is the origin of that even?
As, as the person who Bener refers to is not, like, that's, that's no, that is not, that's not compared.
Oh, I see.
I've heard that, like, also, like, like, I know Jap.
Like, the weird, the weird thing about Jap is it is simply an abbreviation of an actual word,
but it's more about the way you say it that makes it a film or not.
That's not, that's not with Jap. That's with every slur.
I guess you're right, I guess you're right.
That's all context. Everyone's just a fucking coward.
That's, that's why I unabbreviate Jap to Japan.
So I say to people that Japan over there.
And then for some reason it's, it's silly enough that people don't even mind.
Oh, Mage posted one in the chat I really like.
Probably because she doesn't want to say it, which is understandable.
But Zipperhead, I've always liked the word Zipperhead.
Oh, like the guy from Rainbow, the TV show.
It's, I see it in like, in like, Vietnam films.
They call them Zipper, I don't know, I'm gonna Google it.
I have never heard this before in my life.
I think it's from because, like, um, something about crushing heads I don't remember.
Oh, okay, well that's pretty rough.
Alright, look, here, I'm gonna go into Urban Dictionary.
Let me read it real quick.
This guy right here.
Whoa!
That guy's a Zipperhead, yeah.
Or, hey, remember that guy from One Piece who had a zipper mouth?
Remember that guy?
Yeah.
From Chinese Lobby.
I have an OC that has a zipper mouth.
Damn, look at Ross.
I just like to point out Mage posted that in the chat, then immediately deleted it.
Got to cover her tracks.
She's not using the VPN yet.
That's true.
Yeah.
We're running Windows 10 Honor right now.
Alright, listen to this.
Oh, shit.
Okay, this is pretty fucked up.
Alright, Zipperhead.
A derogatory term in reference to people of Asian descent.
It is said to have been coined during the Korean War by frontline troops who had run
over enemy troops in Jeeps.
The soldiers claimed that the tire tracks from the Jeeps left a pattern resembling that
of a closed zipper along the corpse.
Holy fuck.
Okay, that's pretty fucking brutal.
I have no idea.
That's what I'm talking about.
What race is this for?
I mean, it's just generally Asian, apparently, but I mean, it was done during the Korean
War, apparently, so maybe it's specifically Korean?
I don't know.
Nonetheless, it sounds cool, but so therefore I like it.
But it's not something you want to be, I don't think.
I don't want to be one personally, but I want to know a Zipperhead, you know?
I want to be around him.
I'm trying to have a great conversation.
With his crushed in skull.
Yes.
He's a great listener, let me tell you.
Munchie is posting Joe...
This is Ross.
God damn it.
Yeah, this is fucking Ross.
God damn it, hippo.
You really are the moniker.
You've shown your truth and you are the moniker.
No, no, listen to me.
Are you saying that it is a bad thing to have not watched enough friends to know who the
fuck's name is?
No, okay.
I would never claim that you must watch friends under any circumstance.
Yeah, yeah.
But all I'm saying is that...
All the way to the bank.
That's his name.
David Schwimmer, not swimmer, but swimmer.
Schwimmer is a God actor.
It's something akin to a God orgasm, watching Ross on television.
Just watching fuck of his life episode after episode.
He's like a modern day jug head.
He's like a modern day Ku Klux Klan, like, birth of a patient.
He's a modern day court jester.
He's a modern day zipper head.
He's out here every day getting fucking run over emotionally by women.
I can't say no more.
David Schwimmer's going to become an instell in real life.
Oh no.
He probably led the instell movement.
Can you imagine, like, I can't imagine that someone like Elliot Roger wouldn't watch an
episode of Friends.
See just what happens to Ross every episode and be like, you know what?
Women are evil and they do need to be subjugated.
Well, hold on.
Like, it's understandable.
Hold on.
Okay.
After I post this image of him in a potato suit, there's something even more pressing
here.
Yeah.
All right, all right, all right.
What you just said, you say that he's an instell, you know, he's behind Elliot Roger.
Yeah.
He's behind, you know, the hand just saying the hook shooting.
I see this.
Right.
There he is.
He's a confirmed affiliate.
One of the rare instances of a young monkey hang out with Elliot Roger.
There it is.
My God.
The connection's confirmed.
All right.
This fucking topic sucks.
Get off of this.
Okay.
All right.
But let's go on to the one.
Can you explain to me why Monica?
Because you're a bossy and you always tell me what to do and you're all nagging.
You're all nagging.
No other things.
Yeah, I don't know.
Because I don't know.
Yeah.
What do you say?
All I remember from Monica is that...
Nothing.
There's nothing.
She was like a bossy bitch kind of.
And she, you know, kind of bossed around Chandler.
We were talking about the government.
Yes.
You could have been like, ah, well, anyone who knows TIN is the government.
Haha.
I wanted to see where the Ross train left us.
Yeah, there was a lot of gold to mine from that topic.
Okay.
All right.
That's a cool topic.
Yeah.
Because I was out walking, as I often do, playing a Pokemon Go.
And this is not about Pokemon Go.
But the point of mentioning it is that I was at a gym and I was fighting a raid.
So I was standing in a place and I didn't really want to leave.
And this guy comes up and he just sort of stands near me and he just starts ranting
into the air.
Like he's not looking at me.
He just starts ranting into the air like crazy things.
Like the world's fucked up, man.
The government's fucked up.
Ah, this is so bad.
You can't even get a good fish anymore.
You've had your first crazy person playing Pokemon Go.
Congratulations.
Yeah.
It was great.
And he started ranting and stuff and he, you know, I was standing there not running away.
So he assumed I was okay with it.
And he didn't seem that like, he wasn't like a homeless person.
He didn't stink.
He had a backpack on.
I assumed he was just sort of, you know, having a bit of a moment.
Sure.
So he was ranting about like the government and then he started ranting about fish and
how like you could get good fish if you just, you know, you put the salt on it and you get
it from the plate.
I wasn't really paying attention.
But he was going on about like living off the land and how it's so much better to live
off the land and to rely on like government stuff and the bureaucracy and stuff.
And the more he was talking, like he was getting closer and closer to me, like looking at me
every so often and saying, do you understand?
Right?
You understand?
And he was getting closer and closer.
But I started to understand where he was coming from.
He was just like, he said he was, you know, originally from Portugal and he came over
because of like some sort of problems.
I'm assuming like monetary and his brother lived in England and he came over and he was
like, he was ranting about like having to be on customer service calls for three hours
and you're like, you don't want to do that with your life, man.
You don't want to do that.
And I was like, yeah, you don't want to do that.
Fuck customer service.
Fuck being on the phone.
Fuck doing all of this bureaucracy, getting letters in the mail and the bills.
By the end, we were like best friends.
We were like talking about how everything sucks about the government.
And it was just putting me into perspective because I don't know people like that who
like live in, you know, a more, not squalor, but like, you know, he was from Portugal
and he had a very simple life where he caught fish or something.
Sure.
And he had a small community of people that he all, you know, he talked to everybody
where he lives and now he's in England and there's, he doesn't know anybody.
He doesn't like anybody.
He doesn't like the whole system and all the bills you have to pay.
It's very impersonal.
Sure.
I could feel.
And it was just like, yeah, I feel that.
I feel that a lot.
And it was interesting to see that perspective.
And I was thinking about like, what happens?
What happens if you just go away and don't come back?
What happens if you just...
If you just like to live off the land?
Because there's another thing that is related to this is my brother, my littlest brother,
has been like, he recently volunteered for a thing to just do some work for a guy and
the, you know, you would get paid in food and shelter.
And he went for a week to just help this guy build a house on some land that he bought
and he just, he doesn't have the money to hire builders.
So, you know, there's like a site you can go to.
Okay.
You can volunteer to just go and live in a place for a bit and help a guy and get food.
And it's like, you know, initially when I heard that, I was like, ah, that's crazy talk.
You know, what are you going to do when you come back, huh?
Yeah.
You're not going to have any work done.
But the more I think about it and like this crazy guy, I'm like, that's all you really
need.
You only really need like food, like reliable source of food, water and shelter.
And doing all this volunteer stuff and like living off the land and living just within
your means is like really cool.
Because what he was looking at a thing on the site where he got the first volunteer thing
and there's this guy who wants like a photographer, this Italian like guy who owns an island.
And he's like, I want a guy to like photograph this place and do some like, you know, do some
live music for this thing to like, to, you know, for advertising for, you know, a resort
or whatever.
And if you were to do that, all you need to do is you pay for your own travel, but you
basically get a free holiday in this really lovely place and all it costs is a bit of
like menial labor.
And it's like, yeah.
He owns an island, that's cheaper than, at least pay for the ticket, gosh darn.
I mean, I guess he's not paying despite owning an island.
That is kind of strange.
Well, I don't know whether he owns an island.
I can't remember.
Okay, fair enough.
The idea is nice.
Like even if you have to pay for travel, there's lots of places within like, you know, in
England, like kind of local where you can pay a small fee to get a coach drive out into
the middle of nowhere.
And then you can, you can, you know, you see a lovely holiday destination.
But can't you do that without having to do manual labor?
Well, you'd need a place to stay, you'd need a place to live, you'd need a place to buy
things.
But like if you're volunteering and a guy just has food and shelter for you, like, yeah.
Isn't this the relationship they used to have between Lord and Surf?
Are we bringing it back?
I don't know.
I was just, I was just thinking about all that stuff a lot recently because of those,
those instances.
I like the idea of making life as simple as possible.
I think, I think there's too much unnecessary complexity in modern living.
I mean, not to say that I'm against modernity.
I think there's a lot of good things that modern innovation has brought us like the
internet that allows us to do this show and give us money and live.
Yep.
But just in general, I feel like there's so much, there's so much bureaucratic minutiae,
so much bullshit that's been attached to this steady stream of progress that I desperately
wish to escape because it doesn't interest me and it doesn't affect me in anything but
a negative way and I don't like it.
Such as?
Yeah.
But what about the whole internet thing that is like how you wish to live your life?
Right.
You know, that's pretty good.
I just said, that's why I just said the internet is a good thing.
But you can't just separate that one thing from the rest of like bureaucracy in general.
It's all part of the same machine.
No, I think the thing I was going on really is not that bureaucracy is bad because I don't
want to have to deal with everything in my life like other people to do like secretary
things like Nate does with the paying us and it's like, but I feel like certain authorities
are stupid and like especially councils and the government of an entire country.
It just is all stupid.
It doesn't work.
They sound like extremely broad generalizations that are not.
I got a story about it.
I'm not like, I don't have like a political like stance that I've even thought about.
It's just like a feeling I have because when I was at uni, first year, I was in like a
house rather than a student accommodation owned by the university and when you do that,
landlord has to register that there's a person living at the premises and then the council
is notified and then if you don't say that you're a student, they will expect you to
pay council tax and all that sort of stuff.
What the university does, you write a form and then you give it to the university and
the university will give it to the council to make sure that you are confirmed a student
and have to pay it.
For whatever reason, that didn't work on one of the years and since I was like living
alone away from parents for the first time and it was all sort of like a big thing and
I didn't really want to go to them for help, but I was also really, really scared because
I got like a court issue notice in the mail and I was looking at it and like, you have
to appear at court at this date because you have not paid your council tax and regardless
of the verdict, you have to pay the court for its time and I was seeing all these numbers
and things and I was freaking out and I was scared out of my mind, but I ignored it because
I didn't know what to do and I didn't.
That's the right attitude.
I ignored it because I didn't know what to do, but I went to the university and said,
how do I fix this?
And I said, just send another form.
I sent another form and then I got another court issue notice saying you still haven't
appeared at court.
You have to appear.
There's another court date and now you owe us like a hundred something pounds.
And I was like, okay, this is not going away in the way that it should.
I don't know what to do, so I did ignore it and it just went away because the more I thought
about it, it's like the only way that well, it's that they have no power to really enforce
menial matters like this.
Like one guy is not paying his taxes.
They're not really going to have the manpower to send somebody around to make sure that
he pays it by roughing him up or something.
I don't know about that shit.
I had a similar experience to HIPAA actually.
Well, nobody came and nobody like it's still be like a warrant for you.
I mean, I don't know.
Knock on the door in the middle of next week's PCP.
Yeah.
Here's what I would do.
I would call these people and be like, hey, just want to let you know.
I did.
I wanted to resolve this.
I tried to call them and they said, well, you should have had a thing from the university
and sent it.
I said I did send it.
I never got like a confirmation that it was resolved, but the letter stopped coming.
So I assumed it was resolved.
I'm not saying like I ignored it completely.
It's just that the whole like you have to pay the money.
You have to do this stuff.
It's a lot of the time, you know, at least in the UK, it's fear mongering, especially
for like students who don't know what they're doing.
Like they don't have the resources to actually make you follow all these stupid laws.
Like TV license, right?
There's a TV license thing that says to watch TV, you need a license.
And that's what they say.
But the only thing enforcing it is not the government.
It's the BBC.
They would, you know, pay for people to come around and say, knock on people's doors and
say, you need to buy a TV license.
Otherwise you're breaking the law, which there isn't of a law.
There isn't a law of it.
But people get scared into thinking they should.
And so they do.
And that's how they make the money.
Yeah, like, and it was really annoying because the person who opened the door while I was
at uni was somebody who got scared into the thing.
I mean, I didn't know at the time, but like my brother has since told me like people do
that and he just refused to say anything at the door and he closed the door on them and
there's nothing they can really do about it.
Well, okay, I hear you on this game.
I understand what you're saying.
Here's where we disagree in our approach to this stuff.
Like when you like go about like life this way about like trying to like just kind of
duck things that people expect of you, you know, warranted or not, there will like as
long as that's an outstanding thing, there will be like a cloud of fear like over the
whole thing of like, oh, someone might expect something from me.
Like, I hate having that over me.
I would rather just do whatever it takes to resolve it.
Can I just say something about the TV license because fucking if you own a TV, you have to
you have to pay the TV license or at least, you know, they're going to make you because
like my dad, he doesn't speak English.
He doesn't see he doesn't watch English TV.
He just owns the TV and he owns the satellite to watch with Indian TV and he still has to pay
the fucking BBC for the channels that he's not going to ever watch ever.
He doesn't even have the cable or whatever for the.
Well, I mean, what are we doing right now?
We're just complaining about the system that is like, I'm sorry.
The system isn't perfect.
But what are you going to do?
Just like sit around playing about it and change it.
Here's the thing.
All right.
You don't have to pay a TV license and there's no problem.
The only reason there's a thing is that the BBC doesn't run ads on their shows and they
expect people to watch the BBC.
And if you're watching the BBC, you are morally obligated to, you know, pay for the privilege of having it without ads.
But see, even if I lived in the UK, I don't use a TV.
I just use the internet.
So that wouldn't even be a factor.
Exactly.
Which is the case for me.
So like when the TV license comes around, I don't need to pay it.
I'm not going to watch BBC.
Right.
And I'm just going to pay the internet companies to get stuff on the internet.
And they don't give you the thing until you're paying.
So it's like, that's very clearly a transaction.
The BBC is free.
It's just that they, you know...
They've got the Gestapo, the cut marches around.
They've got like the idea that you have to pay for a TV license in the public consciousness.
And now it's a thing.
That just seems like a terrible system on the BBC side.
It's fucked up.
Yeah.
Why didn't he complain about it if he doesn't like it?
Well, I was specifically responding to Maeja's point with that.
Of like, I mean, I don't know, if you don't use the...
Whatever.
I can't even remember what it was.
I'm pointing out that it's nonsense.
I don't mind paying for things that I use or do or whatever.
But like, we're not using the thing and we have to pay for it.
That's nonsense.
I guess the general idea of like government is charging you with taxes on all these things
that you're not necessarily using.
And I understand that it, you know, it's one of those, as the Hello Internet podcast would put it,
one of the necessary lies for society.
If there weren't taxes where you had to pay for, you know, government created infrastructure,
then they would crumble and people would not really do anything about it.
But you can start like a new society in which that isn't the case.
But like, you can't really change how it is.
How did you...
Yeah, I mean, I think taxes are pretty...
What do they call it?
They call it like the object poverty of the common space.
There's like a phrase for that.
Like, when there's a public utility, nobody gives a shit about it.
And it like goes to hell, whatever it is.
It's like, it's one of those things.
I don't have like a way to say this, this like smart and like a soapbox sort of moment.
But I just think the government and like the things they try to get out of you,
you live your life thinking that that is an authority and that's an absolute authority.
But it is in the end just a bunch of people trying to get by doing their job
of enforcing stuff that they didn't invent.
And it's all sort of like nobody really knows anything that's happening.
That's why politicians are so, you know, so disconnected because they don't...
They just fuck the government guys, burn it all down.
That's my political agenda now.
I'm no lover of big government.
I don't know.
Yeah, I mean, your point seemed reasonable there.
I disagree about all these things being dumb.
I guess it's just like I said before, I just...
I'll adapt to whatever systems around me and then, you know, you can try to change it too, of course.
I guess I'm just saying I used to think that like the idea of like people living off, you know,
from their own merit, living off the land and doing things by in like as small as group as possible
was like backwards thinking and stupid and you shouldn't even think about that.
And now I understand it a lot more just through having lived through some bullshit from the government
and seeing how it just doesn't really work for everybody in the same way.
I hear you on that.
I just wonder if there is in fact any going back for society.
You can be Amish, Amish or something.
Yeah, but that's like...
To me like that, I don't want to give up like technological advancement the way the Amish rejected.
My thing is that like I like how far we've gone and there are problems with where we are right now.
I don't want to solve them by going back.
I want to solve them by going further forward.
Yes, indeed. Exactly.
That's what we talked about.
Remember when I talked about that ASMR video that that guy made about like how society is cancer or whatever?
Pretty much the same thing.
It was just like he was just like, oh, I want to go back to when we lived in tribes.
I'm going to go live in the woods and it'll be great.
This isn't my fair and balanced voice.
I'm giving this person equal weight as my own opinion.
Exactly.
It's not that like literally anti-government is going back to the past to play the shitty games and suck ass.
It's that I used to think it was, but now I understand that it's more nuanced and more sensible than that.
Like there are people who can live by their own means outside of the systems of government.
They just ignore them and they don't really do anything bad and they're just happier.
I mean, that's totally within your prerogative and I feel it should be.
I think there's a lot of like things in place to like prevent people from circumventing the system.
And I don't think there should be.
I think it should be if you want to fucking just skedaddle and go live off the grid and just be a fucking weirdo.
And like you're chill, but just like cutting wood and hunting for food and like living in a cave.
You're on the government's land still.
That was a cool thing.
My brother was like researching this because he's kind of, he's on this sort of like anti-government, like living...
Terrorist campaign.
...wherever you like sort of like...
He's being a radicalized sloth right now.
He's going, you know, he's thinking about like he's doing the volunteer thing.
He's thinking of just volunteering on a farm for a month or something.
It sounds weird, but it is kind of cool because there's nothing really bad about it for him.
He explained to me that there's this weird law where if you live in a place on a piece of land for long enough
without getting like, you know, shooed away, you technically own it after a certain amount of time.
I think you need to like build a house or like have some sort of structure and then live there for like five to ten years
and then you own that land and from then on like you can just do whatever you like.
Ancient, oldie times law that never got updated that fell through the cracks.
Yeah, and usually it's like people like if a farmer owns the land, they'll find you and then shoot you.
Get out of my land, like you're not allowed.
But you know, that's how...
That's just a funny little quirk that you can exploit if you put in the time and effort.
To claim some land first on.
I mean, he's talked about it.
I don't know how...
It's so sick.
But it is a sick idea.
I want this to be a real thing.
I'm rooting for him 100%.
I totally get...
Well, that's what I was going to say.
I totally get people's desire for a simpler form of life.
But here's my real question.
How does this lifestyle get us closer to Starfleet?
No one fucking cares.
No, everyone should care if you don't reevaluate your priorities.
This is your priorities in life.
The last thing you're thinking about is Starfleet.
Okay, forget Starfleet.
Okay, here's the thing. Here's my actual objection.
This is fucking selfish.
This is selfish. You just want to be happy.
I just want to go live in the woods and be a happy little sprite.
That sounds shitty and lame and boring.
I hear you, Nate.
I hear you because I don't disagree.
If everybody did that, society would collapse and we'd get nothing done.
Indeed.
For the very few...
You need to be exceptionally passionate for this particular thing
in order to go through with it.
There's only so many people.
You need to be extremely driven.
I feel like people who want to do that so much that they actually try
would not be able to function in the society
to add towards Starfleet in the way that you would want them to.
They would just be depressed and probably kill themselves.
If that person wasn't able to...
If they're that passionate about it, I want to go off the grid
and just live off the land.
That's what really intrigues me.
They're so against the paradigm that we're currently kind of...
to direct people going towards it.
You could even argue that they are just like a drain on society
by not being depressed, taking medication and killing themselves.
And be fucking not helpful.
That's what your brother is.
I'm just saying in general.
Everyone can contribute to my glorious future.
But I have no interest in telling people...
I have no desire to tell people what they can and can't do.
But what I want to do is...
No, no, no.
I don't want to enforce any kind of laws enforcement.
What I want to do is socially shame them into contributing
in a vociferous way as is appropriate.
I feel like there's enough social shame to make people feel like
they have to fit in and do everything else.
Everything that everyone else is doing.
Shame is just the societal shit test.
There's enough pressure as it is already on people to fit in
and do something with their lives.
I don't care about fitting in.
Be productive.
Exactly. I'm talking about being productive.
There's enough social pressure on people to be productive
and people who are not being productive with their lives
just feel this pressure and shame for not being productive
and some of them get depressed and even kill themselves
because they feel like they're being a waste and that's terrible.
I fully encourage those people to do whatever they need to do
to feel better and have a decent life.
But if they come asking me for a dollar, the answer's no.
They have to fucking run their own shit.
I mean, on the one hand, begging, I don't really care for.
At some point, you can't do anything but beg
and that's really unfortunate.
I pass two or three beggars whenever I go to the marketplace
and looking at you.
I'm not saying that I have no sympathy or that I would never help
like people who are truly impoverished
and can't get out of whatever death spiral they're in.
I mean kind of in a larger societal way.
There's definitely a type of person who has this crazy ideal
but doesn't have the passion to do it themselves
or the drive to actually get it done.
They will just leech off of others until...
That's what I don't like.
Nate, there's no way I can phrase this question in a non-confrontational way
but I do not mean a confrontational way.
Okay, what are you doing to make Starfleet real?
Okay, I think about that question a lot.
I've thought about my deep shame
at the fact that I am not a scientist
trying to pursue scientific truth
that will enable us to create things that will allow us to be.
Here's what I'm doing. This is what I tell myself at night
and I think it's a reasonable answer.
What I'm doing is I'm trying to encourage people
through my YouTube stuff.
My day job is basically just so that I'll survive.
It's a job that's fine.
It's part of the military industrial complex a little bit.
So that's kind of not great, but whatever.
I'm doing it just to survive.
But my YouTube stuff, I am talking about things
and specifically I pull out ideas from shows
and I repackage them in ways that I find are valuable.
They're like little morals.
I think that if people listen to my point to them,
they will better contribute to a positive future.
For example, here's one.
He said that not every game needs a fucking easy mode.
I didn't think about why I'm right about game difficulty.
The real point of that is we do not need society
to just bend over backwards to allow every single person
to be able to participate in every single activity.
I'm sorry that the guy without arms can't play Dark Souls,
but maybe he'll figure out how to play with his face
and be all the better for it.
We need to neuter a video game so that someone could
completely change it so that every single person
is able to get through the whole thing
and experience every single kind of content.
The point of that statement is I'm encouraging people
to rise up and achieve things on their own
as opposed to expect everyone else to lower things down
to the standards that these people are demanding.
And I think through those kinds of messaging,
which I would argue is the fundamental core
of my content online,
is better themselves, which I feel is the way
that humanity as a whole makes progress
towards things like Starfleet.
That's what I tell myself at night,
and I think it's kind of okay.
It comforts me somewhat.
It's very easy to laugh at something like that
and say, oh, you're just making content,
you fucking fool, but I do see that you are
making videos because you have something about,
you have a very clear world view,
and you bring it, you don't say,
you don't make videos just to make videos
about X anime or X video game like some people do.
You always take points from media
because people like reviews of things,
and it's a good way to get the message across.
So I see that.
And I'm not saying that's 100% of everything I do,
but that's an element there
that I think is a pretty strong one.
So yeah, that's me.
It's part of why I've had trouble with Hippocrite
is that I don't have a world view message
that I want to push,
and so a lot of it, initially, it was like,
I like these video games.
I'm gonna explain why I like them,
and it worked for a bit,
but now I don't really care about explaining
why these old video games are good,
and I don't really know why.
I mean, when I think about the success
of AVGN or whatever,
I think, because nobody really cared about
the video games until he played it,
it's specifically the character of him
and what he brought to it, you know?
That was the X-Factor.
People like AVGN, they always have the drive.
Well, he specifically has a drive over.
He loves making movies,
and he's made movies all his life.
So AVGN is a character he plays,
and it's a movie.
It's a short film that he's making every time.
It's not a review.
It's always about how this comedy character
can make people laugh.
And with Hippocrite,
I don't have a core thing,
and that's why I haven't been...
John Tron, too, doesn't have a core thing.
He used to have a few games
that like Banjo-Kazooie and Star Fox and stuff.
He ran out of that narrative.
He ran out of games from his childhood
that he really wanted to talk about
and explain why this was a bad thing
or why this game sequel sucks
and Rare was great and now they suck,
and it's so bad.
I love this game, guys.
John has pitted out because he's stopped...
He's ran out of things from that part of his life,
and now he has to think of just things to make jokes about,
and it clearly shows that it's not as interesting to him
as it is as his older content,
and that's why he's slowed down so much.
That's why I've slowed down so much.
That's why a lot of people slow down, I think,
is because they don't have a core reason
for making the videos that they have made for a bit.
You know, this reminds me of just the...
There's a phenomenon people are talking about
more of, like, YouTuber burnout,
and I think it really is something like this.
It's like so many people, like, telling stories
about their life or talking about, like,
things that have interested them,
either, like, I don't know, like, there's people like...
You know that Michelle Fawn was, like,
the makeup queen of YouTube,
but she, like, got bored with it,
like, stopped her channel and now, like, is an animator
and just, like, wants to be...
Like, she's got, like, millions of fucking subscribers
on her main channel.
She had, like, 10 million or something,
but she completely abandoned it
because she, like, ran out of juice.
I mean, this was years and years ago at this point
and just, like, wants to be, like, a YouTube animator
or something now, which is pretty fucking dope.
That's the problem with YouTube, right?
Yeah.
I don't even say it's a problem.
It's just like...
It's a problem that everybody who's creating
on the platform has to kind of try and reconcile
is that YouTube is a show that never ends.
Yeah, well, what do you think about this?
Let me throw this at you.
I've been thinking...
I've been cooking up kind of my thoughts on this subject
and here's what I've come up with.
Like, being a YouTuber is basically offering up, like,
yourself as a service.
I've said that many times.
But, like, what do you really have to offer?
Like, your life experiences, your opinions on things.
And here's my question.
Like, if you've just lived a life as a YouTuber
and you have no particular expertise,
you're just relaying, like, your...
however you lived your life.
Let's say you're, like, a Logan Paul type guy.
Like, you're an entertainer.
You're, like, a hype machine kind of guy.
But there's not much substance beneath it.
I'm not even trying to insult the guy.
It's just like he's not, like, a physicist
who has extensive knowledge about something
and can, like, make interesting physics-related content
or something.
And I'm wondering if, like, where does that road end?
How much can you really mine from that kind of world experience
as opposed to, I mean, just as one example,
like, Jordan Peterson will, like, be able to talk forever
on his YouTube channel, which is quite successful,
because he has spent, like, 30 or 40 years
as a clinical psychologist and has, like,
an endless reservoir of experience to draw from.
And I feel like, like, him?
He's not gonna get, like, burnt out as a YouTuber
just from having to make content day after day.
There's two different audiences for that, though.
Like, because if you gotta remember that, like,
at the end of the day, like, all of humanity's on, like,
a life cycle, right?
Like, you're always gonna have new little kids
who don't want any, like, depth to their content
and just laugh at the meme jokes.
And there'll always be a Logan Paul to serve those young kids.
And then as they get older, they want something with more substance
as they start to develop their own worldviews.
And that's where you get people like Jordan Peterson
who are talking about more bigger, headier ideas
that you need to sit down and kind of decompress
and, like, unpack in your own brain.
I guess I just think that, I wonder if it's just, like,
that kind of content, like, Logan Paul makes or whatever,
is just inevitably not going to be kind of sustainable long-term.
But then again, I mean, maybe he'll just pivot into, like, being an actor.
But, you know, just because one person at the very tip-top,
like, makes it, doesn't mean that, like, the whole trend is sustainable.
I don't know. I don't know. Just, uh...
My biggest thing with YouTube is that I think it's interesting
how, like, it's shaped the way content is kind of served to people
and what people expect, right?
Oh, yeah.
Like, you can't...
Like, it's interesting because now that I'm...
because I don't really do YouTube anymore
and that was, like, the reason why I stopped putting so much effort in it
is, like, I don't want to make a show that never ends.
Like, I want to make a product that deliver it
and then move on to the next product.
Sure.
It's understandable.
It's, like, that doesn't fit in the paradigm.
Like, if I started a YouTube channel right now
and said, oh, I'm going to, like, document my game development stuff,
like, eventually the game will be finished
and then the show will be over.
You end up in, like, a Yandere Dev situation
where I think that guy's milking it.
There's a whole clock...
Yeah, there's a whole thing about that guy.
There's a whole other topic.
But it's just, it's like, you...
if you get into YouTube and you start picking up the traffic,
like, you can't ever stop, you know,
because there's no, like, end state on YouTube.
It's either you're continuing to make things at least weekly
or you're dead.
Well, you say you can't stop.
Do you mean that you can't stop
without, like, tanking your progress
in this particular career field?
Right.
Yeah, okay, okay.
I hear you.
And you can't just...
It has to keep going.
It has to keep perpetuating
because that's how the whole YouTube system is set up.
Yeah.
You know?
Like, you can't...
It's because if you are a filmmaker or something
and you are promoting things on YouTube
and, like, oh, I'm making this movie,
it's a fucking crazy movie
and everyone's really invested in that movie
and then you make the movie,
like, you've done your job, right?
Like, your goal was accomplished
of making the movie,
but all those hundreds of thousands of people
who are following you,
they're like, okay, when's the next movie?
And it's like, I will.
And this is, like, New Game Plus, bitch, go.
And it's just like, no, I don't really want to.
So it's like, you have this whole...
And, like, all the things you've built up now are gone
unless you find a way to keep perpetuating somehow.
I mean, there's ways.
It's really just a...
I can't think of the word.
A thing of variety
and, like, having a lot of different...
You know, I can't think of the words.
I can't think of any of these words I'm trying to say.
I missed that segment, dude.
I need more episodes if I can't think of a word.
Neil Cicerega has, you know,
he has fingers in a little different pies.
I think that's an expression.
He has his YouTube thing.
He has his guaranteed video series
on Patreon thing.
But they're, you know, they're very wildly
in, like, podcasts and skits
and he's had so many different, like, just things
that he, you know, he's got those funny albums,
mash-up albums with the smash-mouth things.
And he's just, like, really good
at a lot of different things
and people love him for lots of different things
they didn't even realize that he was the one who made them.
And I think as long as you have, like, things,
like, creative things
and you don't care where they go, necessarily,
like, if you have, like, a creative idea
but it won't work for the YouTube series
you're currently making,
then just make it anyway
because it's something you want to do.
And then if it's good, people will like it
and then you'll, you know,
people will associate your name with a thing
that is, you know, not necessarily one thing,
but like a person who can make lots of cool things.
I think there's...
Yeah, go on, Tim.
I was just gonna say, I think it's the interesting strategy
that seems to be, like, the most effective
for fitting in this paradigm
is something that none of us really do.
I guess maybe Digi kind of does it,
is that you make a brand based around you as a person
and everything else is just kind of a subsidiary of that.
Yeah, yeah.
Because then, like, as long as you're not dead,
like, your story's still going on.
And so if you can sell people on who you are
and they are interested in who you are,
no matter what you decide to do
or what projects you decide to work on,
the true line is that it's you that's doing it.
I mean, I would agree with that, except for the fact that
the majority of the people who watched Digi
watched Digi because he does good analysis of anime specifically.
And if he completely stops doing that,
and he became like, if he became like,
well, yeah, I guess,
but like if he became like a full-time rapper,
he wouldn't be as successful.
But it would still be, you know, alright,
because he's proven himself a couple of times.
I don't think he's doing it perfectly.
I don't think anybody that we know is doing it perfectly.
But there are clearly channels that exist,
like vloggers and stuff on YouTube who have tons of success,
that just do whatever.
And you care because the point is that it's them doing whatever.
It's not that they've developed a channel around a certain topic.
The topic is, this is my life.
Yeah, but that inherently, like we were saying earlier,
will lead to burnout.
Like Game Grumps, Game Grumps have been doing,
you know, Aaron especially has been doing it the entire time,
has like, they've run out of stories to tell about their life.
The only thing they can talk about is the things that are currently happening
outside of Game Grumps.
And it's usually just banned promotion stuff or, you know,
they met a guy or, you know, there's less about their life.
They met a handsome lady and they've got lots of stories to tell.
Well, that's the thing, that's what I'm saying.
Like you have to make your brand basically about what you're doing in the moment.
Because then that's always...
I feel like that, I mean...
You know what stories will never run out depending on the person?
What?
Dreams.
Oh God, oh...
Sorry, I had to say that too.
Did I tell you guys about a Game Grumps episode that I watched recently?
And I watched, I mean, watched the first half and I was like,
oh my God, and then I was like, but I don't care, and then I stopped.
You don't think so?
What was it?
There is a series on Game Grumps about Aaron Hanson Wikipediaing himself.
Oh, I watched some of those.
And in part two, he just blatantly and openly and like,
honestly talks about the genre, just like,
just like, nonchalantly and not weirdly.
Like it's not like a big deal, he just talks about it as if it were just,
you know, common, common knowledge.
What did he, what did he say?
He didn't say anything particularly insightful.
It's not like he, he doesn't explain it in any way.
Did Danny fuck...
Fuck Susie, yes.
Susie, I mean, John, whatever, yeah, okay.
Did Danny fuck John?
He did.
And that's how it went right away.
I mean, he didn't talk about it, like he, he talked about it in reference to
Did You Know Game, you know, whatever, I don't care.
But the fact that he did that at all was extremely surprising to me.
And I want to know, anyone who watches Game Grumps Drift,
that's any, any percent of the population.
And by that, I mean, any of you four and point seven million people who might be watching,
what is happening?
Is this, has there been like a, like some video, some monumental video
that just has explained everything?
Is that what's happening right now?
You know, have we stumbled upon that?
I'm pretty sure that did not happen.
And now that I think about it, there was like three parts to that Wikipedia thing.
I'm pretty sure I watched all of parts one and two.
And he's just kind of, like, I don't know.
It's kind of strange that he, well, what isn't strange is the way he talked about in that video.
He was just very nonchalant, like you said.
He was like, yeah, I mean, I worked with these guys.
These guys, oh yeah, we've, John, we broke up with them with the fucking Game Grumps stuff.
And, you know, we'd already been hanging out with Dan a lot.
And I'd been saying, like, if John ever left, you know, Danny would like take his place.
So this was kind of in the works already.
And I was just like, oh, well, why wasn't any of this clarified in the past?
Maybe it was just something as simple as he didn't feel like talking about it
and didn't think it would like be a big deal.
I could imagine he could tell it was, I could imagine he knew it would be a big deal.
He just didn't want to talk about it.
I always wonder about this.
When there's a, when a drama shit storm happens, like the world can go a flutter.
Like tons of people will be talking about it.
But the people or person at the center of it, like they have only one person's perspective
as to what the whole drama situation like would be.
Whatever it may be, maybe it's Aaron, maybe it's John, whoever.
Like, maybe things don't look that bad from their perspective.
And like, even if the whole world is up in arms, like, gasping or whatever,
if this person only hears from like a handful of people specifically
and like doesn't go to seek out drama about it,
probably just doesn't seem like a big deal.
And maybe that's what happened with Aaron and like the whole John drama.
I mean, it doesn't even seem like, like it would be difficult to imagine that John,
like John already had a lot of reasons to want to go to New York.
And then he eventually had a girlfriend there.
So like the idea that John would eventually leave to work more on John Tron
is like maybe they were already talking about that.
I mean, these are the things that Aaron said at the time too.
Like just John went to go work.
So I mean, he may have just been 100% clear from the start.
I never really thought that there was like a big like argument
or like a big like scandalous event.
I really just thought it was sad and I wanted to know why they didn't,
they weren't friends anymore, seemingly.
But then Stargate happened and it was all okay, hopefully, kind of.
I thought it was interesting that he, that that happened.
And that's what I wanted to say about that.
But I don't care about that.
And what I do care about is going back to what Hippo said, except not at all,
because I don't care about what he said.
I care about what I thought he was going to say,
which is the following about the government.
The government is worse than ghost.
I've been thinking about this a lot lately.
Specifically last night, I was walking past a abandoned government,
like military, government military base in a town I was visiting last night.
I was visiting my covens in an impoverished California, like desert-y type area.
Super scary.
Late at night, walking past like government, like a medical center,
like an abandoned government military center.
Terrifying.
And the government is worse than ghost, because ghosts are real, of course.
But the government, like you need to be able to prove ghosts are doing something, obviously,
but you can do that very easily, very easily.
But the government, you can tell me the government is doing literally anything
and I will believe you.
The government, like from a young age, watching Game Theory not a joke,
Game Theory revealed me what MK Ultra was.
And ever since I knew what MK Ultra was, thanks to game, this is not a joke.
Watch the fucking The Polybius, the Polybius episode.
I watched Game Theory as a lot as a kid.
Ever since that moment, I've never trusted the government, ever.
And I can never trust the government.
I don't know how anyone can, like, vote or participate in the government in any way,
knowing that nothing is real.
Like, I cannot believe anything that the government, any, like a politician,
like a government worker, like a post office worker, nothing.
I can believe nothing anyone is saying.
You might be getting MK Ultra'd right now without even knowing about it.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly.
I could be in a, like, drug and do a stupor right now.
That's not a joke.
This is not, like, me trying to be funny.
Yeah, it's possible.
Like, oh, like, what if it's happening?
It is happening.
All conspiracy theories have basically all happened.
They've all, like, like, you know, they've put HIV into a black community to watch how it progresses.
MK Ultra, oh, it's just real.
It's not like, you know, what if, it is real.
So how do I know I don't have HIV right now?
Well, you could go to the doctor.
No!
The government!
The doctors are bought off by the government, too!
You think the MDs don't know about what's going on?
They are the ones who have manufactured it.
Well, you'll find out if you have HIV sooner or later.
What?
It's going to happen to all of us.
HIV minefields are going to be your future.
You guys aren't taking this seriously.
The government, like, can do anything, and they can give me HIV.
Okay, all right.
Listen, when conspiracy theorists always go crazy
and assume the government is way better at stuff than it actually is,
that's what I think.
Why do you think-
Okay, listen, listen.
My opinion is this.
Give it one ruse by the government that could not obliterate-
Okay.
Munchie.
Munchie could not kill me.
They could.
Cover it up excellently.
Have no one remember who I was.
Give me one reason why they can't.
Munchie, munchie, munchie.
Okay, like, let's say they could.
Let's say they could do all the things you're scared of them doing it.
Just because you're aware of it and are scared of it
is not going to stop them.
So what's the point of being scared of it?
I mean, it's still appropriate to be scared, I suppose.
Just not to obsess about it and let it fuck you up.
I don't like obsess about it.
I think that the government-
I just don't trust the government now.
The reason I don't think the government would do anything like that
is not to say they wouldn't have a reason to kill Munchie.
Which they have many, of course.
The reason it would be difficult for them
is because everything's run by money
and doing good things really well
requires a lot of money
and they would need a lot of money to try and-
If they have an enemy number one
they're not going to make a real return on investment
going out all out with 100 billion spies
with gas weapons and stuff.
It's going to cost a lot to get rid of just one secret guy.
I mean, what was that Snowden guy?
He's alive, right? He's in Russia.
They haven't even managed to assassinate him.
That is true.
I'm not saying that I am going to be assassinated
or that there's any reason to kill me, murder me.
But there is plenty of reason to brainwash me
because I am part of the populace.
Well, yeah.
I think that's all of society's job.
Brainwashing is harder than you think.
I think it's socially influencing.
Everyone does it on a daily basis to everyone else.
Yeah, I basically agree with that.
But here's why.
Do I believe that there can be grassroots movements?
Let's just say, for example,
a government agency says we want this candidate to win
so we are going to put lots of money into campaigns
and support super PACs and whatnot
so that they will win.
Yeah, definitely possible.
Hillary had so much support
just from every famous person in the world to try to win.
It didn't work out, which is actually quite...
That really is a conspiracy buster in my mind.
It's like, thank God,
even though the entire government apparatus can conspire
to put one person in office,
they can still overwrite that authority
and get someone like Trump.
At the very least, I find that a somewhat comforting thought.
It's also kind of scary, but whatever.
I just don't think that, you know,
even the most well-equipped,
well-funded group of people,
they can't really do that much
because they're still just humans
and humans are fucking idiots.
That's fair.
You really have to take these things
covering up a scandal
and they've done that in the past.
There's probably hundreds of scandals we have no idea about
and then one will leak out in a year
and it will be like, oh my God, I didn't know they did that.
But it won't be anything as like,
unbelievably alien technology,
like brainwashing...
I'm thinking of brainwashing in the cartoon way
where your eyes swirl and then you are a zombie.
But like normal amounts of brainwashing,
the schools, they tell you to do certain things
and because they need people to be disciplined
and so they can be put into jobs
that are meaningless pieces of crap
and they fucking want to go live in the woods
and it just makes sense to go live in the woods.
It makes sense.
I think most of the things are privately owned by people
so they catch you.
All you need to do is live there secretly for 5, 10 years
and you own that tree.
I feel like this is completely separate from what I'm trying to say.
I'm trying to say that the government is extremely powerful
and I am an ant.
I kind of disagree with that
because I think that the government is far less powerful
than most people think that it is.
I truly believe that.
It comes down to one thing.
I don't mean in a little government way.
The military can shoot me really hard.
I find myself comforted by many thoughts
on why that will probably never ever happen.
A lot of them are just political ramifications
of an actually tyrannical government.
Here's the thing.
Is it possible the CIA could say,
Munchy, Nate Best Boy, Hippocrite, whoever,
X person is a threat.
Let's PCP gang get him out of here.
I don't know.
George Bush wanted to leak some state secrets
because he felt really bad about some stuff he'd done
with the Iraq war or something.
Is it possible that the government would say,
for national security, we're going to kill him.
It's the only way to keep the secrets safe
and we're going to do it.
Then we find out in a week that,
how weird George Bush, W,
died from a heroin overdose.
Man, isn't that weird?
They found some injections that can't be explained in his wrist.
Pretty strange. Don't know what that's about.
Could they do that? Absolutely.
I'm sure that they have in the past.
But when it comes to you and I,
we are not important enough
to do these sorts of things too.
I guess I'm kind of comforted by that,
as well as two words that I'm a big believer in.
I know that it can potentially make me blind
to some things, but these two words,
I am a strong believer in.
It's Occam's razor.
It's just that the simplest explanation
is usually the correct one.
In that way, a conspiracy buff
like Alex Jones might be right about something
every once in a grand while,
but then we'll say absolutely crazy shit
that is definitely not true.
That which is asserted without evidence
can be dismissed without evidence,
to quote Christopher Hitchens.
Then he'll be right about one of these random things
once in a while, whereas me,
I'm an incredible skeptic.
I don't believe anything without evidence
on a grand scale.
I need hardcore proof that anything is true.
Even the fact that I am a human being
living in this world, I have absolutely no proof
that that is 100% true.
I could absolutely be a brain in a vat,
a program running on a computer in another universe,
and this is all a simulation.
100% true, so I would never assert
that everything around me is real.
Thinking of that sort of mentality.
I sort of agree with you, there's absolutely no proof,
but I think whoever is running the simulation,
if this is a simulation,
they probably wouldn't want to put in other people
questioning whether or not this is a simulation
because then you'll start questioning
if this is a simulation.
What if it was a little Jesus alien
and he's like, I'm going to create a universe
for my science for a project,
and I'm going to test to see
how many people figure it out,
and then he gets his little checkbook out
and he's looking at Earth and he's like,
okay, most people don't believe it.
I've seen specifically about a simulation though.
I'm using Occam's razor here as well,
in the sense that I can't prove
that I live in the real world,
but I'm happy to just assume
for the most part that this is probably real,
this is probably reality,
even though there's a couple of thought experiments
that show that it's actually more likely
we live in a simulation than not,
but I won't get into all that.
Yeah, whatever.
I'm happy being a synthetic little man.
That's the main thing.
It doesn't impact me in any way,
and I heard one time I listened to a flat Earth
call into Stephen Mollinieu's show,
and this was a very interesting show.
So Mollinieu just puts up with this guy,
talking about all his beliefs,
and then Stefan is just like,
okay, I have a question for you.
How much benefit has come to your life
through believing that the world is actually flat
and that everyone is lying to you?
And the guy was like, well,
and he was like, and how many hours per week
do you spend on this shit?
And the guy's like, well, you know,
I spend like 30 hours a week maybe,
and he's like, okay, maybe your time would be better served
devoting that time to improving your life,
learning new skills,
working more to earn more money to put away for savings.
And it basically turned out that this guy
was just a sad, sad man
who had very little in his life
and clung to this conspiracy theory
as maybe some grand secret that like,
ah, me and my elite few are privy to.
So this is something I can use to give myself
a substantive ego in this life,
that I have this knowledge.
But really, he's basically tricking and fooling himself.
And I find that highly edifying
when it comes to the mindset of the overly credulous.
It's people who want to know things a lot of the time.
Can't that like same argument be used against somebody
who's trying to push forward towards starfleet?
Is that they just are a scared little boy
and they watch this TV show as a kid?
Well, but I would be happy to go into detail
as to why, and I have on many occasions,
as to specifically why I find that to be,
in fact, kind of the only noble goal of humanity
as opposed to believing things that, you know, aren't true
or asserting that, like, just like any kind of outage.
Oh, no, I'm a staunch believer
in believing things that aren't true.
Well, this is a little bit of a deviation
from Munchie's point, regardless.
I'm so fucking distraught right now
that you people don't agree with me
that the United States government has funny gas
and it has a Batman utility belt of people.
I'm so fucking mad right now.
You know, the government is fucking really fucked up, dude,
and I totally agree with you.
I was, like, on the government conspiracy train
for a long time, and I honestly still am.
Yeah, me too.
I'm a huge fucking government conspiracist,
because why wouldn't I?
Because it's not because MKUltra is real.
It's not like it's, oh, I believe it is.
There's tons of fucking evidence on the book
that these people do some fucked up shit,
and it's totally messed up.
What are we going to do as a result of MKUltra being real?
Like, what should we advocate for the government
to be more transparent, to, like, shut down
these kind of programs?
I can never trust that.
Even if they say that they shut them down,
I will not trust them.
This is not like I want change to happen.
I'm doing this expressing the human emotion
of fear that I will die
at the hands of Barack Obama.
You know what's all this issue, though?
Let's all advocate for tiny, small government,
so that the way to get rid of MKUltra
and all these other things
is to slowly, democratically defund the government.
So it just doesn't have the power to do this shit.
That's what I said.
I'm just trying to say
that I agree with Munchie
that the government is evil
and could do so many terrible things.
Good difference, though.
I mean, they're basically the same.
Everyone has new-world orders.
Everybody has an idea of, like, controlling people
and, you know, blah, blah.
It's just I don't give a shit.
What could they possibly do to me
and Ant scurrying around
like, I'm doing nothing to them.
They could just nuke me right now.
They could nuke me and Ant.
Here's the thing that gives me...
It would just be a waste of money.
That's why I was saying, like, money runs the world.
The most...
The cheapest thing is probably what they're gonna do.
Well, right.
Even if, like, in the future,
like I was saying, like, humans are stupid.
Even if they invent, like, smart robot
AI people
to, like, do things
that humans can't do.
That's not going to, like,
immediately run the world
because it's gonna be expensive to make stuff like that.
And, I mean,
far in the future, it's gonna be less expensive.
But, like,
I feel like
the amount of money
things cost
gives humanity time to adapt
to whatever changes come about.
I just don't feel...
I feel that everything
that you're saying, Munchie, is real.
I just don't feel the paranoia about it.
Because, like...
What paranoia do you think I'm on edge
and all hippo? What do you mean?
All right. Not paranoia.
What's the fucking word? Like, I'm fear.
Like, I don't feel any fear.
Fear has three instead of an E.
That's how I am right now.
The thing that gives me some comfort is the fact that
at the end of the day, we're all
the government's pay-piggies, okay?
And it's much more...
beneficial for us to be alive
and continue to give them money
so they can experiment on black people
in, like, a backwards country
than it is to kill us,
even if we're making some noise.
So... Yeah, that's the whole, like,
the stupid, like, why every, like,
villain of everything is always
a complete idiot, because they just want to kill everybody
so they can rule the world.
And then they're just gonna be the king
of an empty rock. Like, what is the point?
Yeah, that's dumb. That's dumb.
I mean, the best villains are the ones...
I mean, you've probably seen the villain,
like, tier chart, with the top
as being, like, one whose motivations
are, like, as good or better
than the actual protagonist.
Like, Vite from Watchmen and whatnot.
Anti-spirals, et cetera, et cetera.
Me.
Thanos from...
Thanos is up there, you know, in the movies.
Why didn't Thanos just step
his fingers in half the effective birth
rate of all of the universe
instead of killing people?
Why didn't Thanos just snap his fingers
and have everyone have enough food
to survive forever?
There's some argument about it, but only
has so much power or something, and he can't do that.
It's bullshit. It's lame.
Why didn't he snap his fingers
and then all the anime girls,
panties flipped up, dude?
He could have made anime real, and instead
he killed half the population.
He could have made anime real.
Snap his fingers and allow me to learn how to snap.
I'm trying.
Do you not know how?
Fuck you, hippo.
You're a government. You're a government fucking the shill.
You're a government.
I can't do that.
I can do the eight click.
I can use all eight of my fingers.
What's that?
I can do that a little bit too. What's that?
Munchy can't snap.
Snap. That one's going in my cringe complex.
I do, man.
I'm not going to snap for that.
Yeah, thank you. Appreciate that.
Nate, have you ever found yourself
unfortunate as a reaction
because I did the other day
and it was really bizarre?
I actually did the other day.
It was me from a live stream
holding...
I think I saved the image or something, I think.
I'll see if I can dig it up later.
It's me holding my hands over my head with my mouth agape.
It was not the soy boy pose, but it was similar.
It was me reacting in horror, probably
to one of my Pokmon dying
that somebody posted.
It was just in the context of
green texting, some bad thing happens
my face when.
It was just like my face.
What was yours?
I've actually done some digging into this.
This was actually a little bit old ago,
a couple of months ago.
I found on V, I don't care at all,
completely randomly.
I do not go on Twitch a lot.
I used to go on it a lot, but I only check
and never go on it.
But just randomly, this day I come
and it's a really bizarre photo of me.
It's a screenshot from
I think it's
one of the Brobnicon videos.
It's when I'm looking intensely
into the camera during the course cast.
The panel or something?
And I'm looking as hard as I possibly can.
And I
reversed image search using like
Desu, storage or whatever.
That image has been
used like somewhere a lot.
Like 11 times over the course of it existing.
Do you have it saved?
No, I don't.
Unfortunately, I don't know.
I'm sure you could like
search 4chan4munchy
because I know that at least once
it has been replied to with
my name.
So I'm sure you could find it that way.
If I can find out,
I'll give it to Hippo to put in the show notes
or whoever is editing it.
I'll do the same with mine. I'm pretty sure I have it.
But anyway, it's really weird.
Whoever is doing that,
why? I don't mind.
If I were to be
a reaction image,
I could live with myself.
That'd be a pretty good life.
But I don't know. I don't know what's happening
right now. And I like it.
I like it, to be honest with you.
It's funny
and fun is what I have to say about that.
It makes me laugh.
Being talked about on 4chan
is sort of a mythical experience.
Yeah.
It's something about it.
It's really just a forum
and whatever.
But
the harsh community there
is really interesting
to see what they say
because they can be as
brutally honest as possible
and you don't know who it is.
I know about it.
How brutally unfiltered it is
and completely unapologetic.
Whenever I want the raw shit,
I just go to 4chan.
I don't go to fucking Kotaku.
I don't go to Polygon.
I never get the sensation of
just a mass of people I don't know who they are.
I always feel like
it's not like I can tell who's making each post.
But I feel like it just is
a person who I'm talking to.
I don't know what they look like.
There's like some illusion
is created through 4chan
of that effect.
I kind of take their opinions far more
valuably than I would
any individual person who is saying it.
I guess it's because there's no ego
to protect at that point.
It's straight up.
That's true. I think that's a big plus.
It's a big plus.
I mean there's kind of an ego because
people can reply and say that's dumb
and see all the replies.
It's a big currency.
Everybody wants those sweet use.
Yeah.
I was in
Hawaii recently, as you all know.
And I was snorkeling
for the first time in my life.
And a side note.
I believe any animal can kill me.
Fish, pigeon, dog, rat,
rabbit, anything.
There's a lot of those fish and those snorkeling things.
It could very easily kill me.
I'm talking about a little baby bunny.
Shark attacks are not uncommon.
If a rabbit
truly wanted to,
I could think of like seven
different ways it could kill me.
I see Monty Python.
I've never seen that.
But if it really wanted to,
if it's got big buck teeth,
it could kill me.
That is true.
If you stood there, if you laid down
and you didn't try to run away.
And you gave it like 20 minutes to gnaw through your jugular.
You know what rabbits,
this is completely different from what I was about to say.
But rabbits are the government.
I know they probably will kill you.
But they can, therefore, I will never trust them.
I cannot look
at a bunny
and like not fear abject
horror. Because I know
what it could do to me. It doesn't matter if it will,
but it could.
Is it because like you can't?
Is it because
bunnies look cute?
But you can't see their teeth normally.
Yes. And I know that they have them.
They're hiding it from me. It's a concealed carry.
It's like a fucking mass shooter walking
into a target with a gun in his belt.
That's exactly what it's like.
All bunnies are wearing burkas.
It's just terrifying. What's under there?
We don't know.
Okay, another aside besides the bunny one.
I am so surprised
that mass shootings don't happen all the time.
Because like, okay, this will sound
vaguely like gun control, but I don't mean it in a way.
But like,
if you are just like a normal person
and you know, you pass all background shelks
and you're not like insane. You're just a normal person.
You can reasonably acquire a gun in America.
So like, couldn't you just
be normal and then just decide
to shoot a lot of people and then like,
can't you like, you can just get a gun
and then like, walk into
a Chipotle and kill everyone
in the Chipotle. There's nothing to stop you.
I don't think there should be something to stop. I'm just saying, you know,
like, you could do that. So why doesn't that happen?
I wouldn't mind if your gun shot's outside my day all the time.
Part of being normal
is not wanting to shoot someone.
Yeah.
Mass shootings do happen in America.
Literally, I think it's more than once per day.
Like, throughout the country.
Which is, that's pretty high.
I don't think that's true.
I think shootings probably happen, but not mass shootings.
Well, when I say mass shooting,
it's like, that doesn't involve
like 20 people dying. It's like one
or more people dying from like a public shooting
event or something.
It's not a mass shooting.
Let me quickly interject.
From what I've heard,
I could be wrong, but from what I've heard,
those statistics,
whichever say like about the mass shootings,
they're overblown because
they include people that like accidental
discharges and stuff like that.
Okay, that's possible. It's definitely possible.
And this is like a guns thing.
Go to the most gun-respective
country on earth. Go to wherever.
Go to the country where they don't even have
like any weapons. They have no knives or anything.
If you get a fork
or like chopsticks or anything,
it's so easy to kill people.
Why is there not just death in the street
all the time? Here, let me explain
to the thing that you have just
explained to us.
It's because the bunny's there. The bunny is there.
And everybody knows the bunny has sharp teeth.
Yeah. So like they, and if
you kill a person, the bunny will bite you.
It will do. So like people don't
kill because they'll be attacked
by the government. And the government is so much stronger
than just, you know,
you with your gun.
You'd have to be completely delusional to actually
go on a mass shooting, which is why people
who go on mass shootings are like
mentally fucked up in some way.
Yeah. Like even, I'm sure plenty of people,
we've all had fantasies about like,
I just want to kill XYZ
person because they're annoying me right now.
But some people, I don't know, I guess
the difference is that some people are unhinged enough
to then act on those pretty normal impulses.
I mean, way, way back, way
back, like in medieval,
like probably pre-medieval England
or whatever. People, the way
it would work, because there's no police, there's
none of that. If somebody
like has a fight, an argument with somebody
and they kill them, then
that's just okay. Like, oh shit, that guy
killed that other guy. And if
yeah, you know, the guy's brother or something
comes up to him and says, you killed
my brother, I'll kill you. And then he kills him.
And then that's justice. That is
that was what it was like. Yeah.
Killing is not, it's not necessarily
a thing that is like humans
are afraid of. But
you know, like, like in a society
where killing would be more normal,
we would do have, you know, have more
shootings. But the reason we don't is because
the government will kill us.
That's true. I was having this feeling in a
Chipotle, where I just was walking
to get, oh, here's my Chipotle order.
It's a burrito, brown rice, fajitas, double
steak, queso, hot sauce,
and cheese. And then I get a small water
and it's always free. They just ask for
a small cup of water, but I fill up the brim of water
because I don't put ice cubes in, because I'm on a bitch
scum. Anyway, oh, here's Chipotle.
There was a full line. There was like 10
people. There were like five people in the back
of like five employees. And there was like
a couple of people scattered around. He was kind of a big
Chipotle. So there was like, like
30 people. I think if I have a gun right
now, I can kill at least
10 people. At least 10 people
would be dead if I
had a gun right now. So I was
just thinking, like, it's so easy.
Like, there must, like,
it's like, it can't be that crazy to do.
You're right. It is easy. It's just that
most people legitimately don't want
to shoot up an area. I can't
believe that, Nate. I can't believe people
don't feel the way I do. All I'm getting from
this conversation is that Munchie really wants to kill
some people. No, no, no, no.
It's easy.
I've had thoughts like this at a
similar age where it's like, man,
if I had a gun, I mean, I could,
you know? But it's what
that is. It's not that anybody is insane
or like a gun nut or like,
you know, it's just like your
brain is like
considering possibilities that you don't
consider normally. And it's for the first
time, like, you're doing this, I guess, for like
more often than you have done
in the past. It's just sort of like
blowing your mind because it's just
a new thought. Like, I've had
thoughts like, man, that guy really pissed
me off. Wonder what would happen if I
stabbed him up and shanked him in
a cool anime way. That's
what you get for messing with me. That's
what you get for bullying little old me.
And I imagine it and it's like, oh,
oh, god.
Am I an evil man? No, I'm not.
It's just the way your brain
sorts this sort of
stuff out is you just imagine it
and then it's gone.
Yeah, they're all intrusive thoughts of it.
Yeah.
If I
kill everyone in Chipotle,
will I go to jail? Yes.
Not if they can't catch you. Not if you kill
every policeman who comes to get you.
Just keep the kill train running.
Okay, wait, okay. Go infinite with it.
Guys, guys, the perfect
crime. I've
come up with it. If you shoot
the police, they can't arrest
you.
Wait, I've cracked
the code. That sounds like
cop killer talk, frankly.
Oh, okay, no, you guys
need to understand. It's not that
me, the Renault Africa in a cop killer is
mutually excusable. It's that Ben is the
cop killer and he is 51%
in favor of killing cops.
And 49%
rowdy. And I am 51% rowdy
and 49% in favor
of killing cops. And yet there can be no
peace. There can never be peace.
Yeah, yeah, under no
circumstances.
I was actually getting to
an actual real point about
when I started this.
I remember.
It is illegal to touch
a turtle in Hawaii.
Oh, that was a big thing. Yep, I remember
that. Because they want to
protect them.
I assumed this was just something that they
tell you to be like, don't touch a turtle.
But I was researching.
The news article is about some guy
on the news
some guy was like, man
harassing a turtle.
And it was like some guy touching a turtle shell.
And so
I was snorkeling for the first time.
I see a huge fucking tortoise
and I swim.
It was huge. It was like the size of
me. It was the size of me.
That's fucking dope. I saw some on the beach, but never underwater.
It was great. It was fantastic.
And I swim over to him and I touch him.
Oh my god.
You're just committed to a crime in Hawaii.
Don't touch the turtle. It's illegal.
Stop touching the turtle.
Michelle made it
in no uncertain terms. Michelle made it
explicitly clear what will happen
to me if I touch a fucking turtle.
You will be ran out of town
and murdered by the locals if you touch
a fucking turtle. And Tom
before you say anything, I just thought
well then let him die.
If I can't touch this
turtle, why should it exist?
That's what I feel about women.
Why should we protect turtles?
If they do not pleasure me, if they do not pleasure humans
then why do we let them exist?
They are in our
world. We may have been not
equal terms when we were animals, but we have risen
above them and we could easily
kill every... we're well
in our way. They're endangered.
We could easily wipe out every turtle we want
to. So if it is not bow to
my whim and let me touch him
then what is the point of them
existing? Munchie, now you're the bunny
of the animal kingdom.
Well, all I'm saying
is I want to touch a turtle because I like
Mr. Turtle. It's this
Mambi Pambi-Pita
Nambla Alliance that protects
these turtles because they like... ooh, we like them.
We want them to continue to exist.
They're cool and all. And I mean
I guess that's true. No, turtles are cool.
That's why I want to touch it.
I want to touch it because I like it.
I like it. Yeah.
You can see a turtle image
and video online
right now on your local Google.
You don't need to go to Hawaii
but the point of seeing a turtle
in real life is the 3D
interaction in real life. You
get to see him react to you doing a funny dance.
That's true. You get to see him
like if you give
a leaf to him and he chomps on it.
That's the leaf I gave him that you're eating.
Even something like that is like
that's why you go to see animals of the zoo
is to see what they do.
Is it legal in Hawaii to give
a turtle a leaf to eat?
Frankly, you're like not allowed
to go within like some
number of feet of a turtle.
It's just stay the fuck away
from turtles in Hawaii.
There has to be a reason.
The reason is because they're an endangered species
and they really want to protect the ecosystem.
Hawaii is 100%
hardcore about keep Hawaii
as sick as Hawaii is now.
Department of Agriculture shit
around like every corner.
You have to sign those forms when you go to Hawaii
that says I am not bringing in any outside
plants that could possibly fuck up the
ecosystem of Hawaii.
There are a few issues with mongooses
I understand.
Dude, did you see a wild mongoose out there?
I saw a bunch of them. They were fucking
awesome.
There's a contradiction here.
You can't touch the turtles
because they're trying to artificially keep
the turtle population going.
But you can't bring seeds because they're trying to
make sure nature takes its course.
Let the turtles spend for themselves.
Let nature happen.
They want nature to interact with the turtles.
They don't want the human population
to interact with the turtles.
We're not part of nature.
We're literally better than nature
is what we are now.
This reminds me.
It's just a human hand.
They're not going to touch me.
It's a fish.
This is the natural
course of evolution.
Some rat or some potato
is going to evolve to be
a shout.
This is how sharks get opposable thumbs.
It's going to evolve to have the human
facade so that cows like sea turtles
are lulled into a false sense of security.
Oh, it's just my farmer.
No, it's a gross potato.
I'll kill you.
It's kind of like mimics from RPGs
that member of Treasure Chest
only talking like full human.
Speaking of sharks with arms,
I'm imagining that.
It's really funny that he would swim real fast
and then just punch you instead of punching you.
This turtle reminds me.
They're not that aggressive.
I mean, some sharks are not all of them.
Snapping turtles are assholes
and they're monsters that should be wiped out
the face of the earth.
Turtle Gate.
That is the title of this
PCP episode, Turtle Gate.
This Turtle Gate turtle
reminds me of a fountain.
Of a fountain near my home, San Diego,
Balboa Park, Google it.
I'm going to show you an image.
There's watermarks. This is a fountain.
It's good.
When I was a little baby lad,
you could walk in that fountain.
I remember we went on a field trip
to Balboa Park
to play in the fountain and it was great.
It was a great time.
You go to Balboa Park now.
Do not go in the fountain!
Danger! You can drown
in this one feet of water.
It's extremely important
that you do not enter this water.
Then why is it here?
Why do fountains exist
if I cannot play in the fountain?
It is despicable.
Even if, let's just say,
a baby drowned in that fountain.
I don't know that it did,
but even if it did,
why should that ruin
everyone's good time forever?
Here's the point.
Hold on.
A quick point about the fountain thing.
I'm not sure how fountains work,
but I'm pretty sure they recycle the same water.
It goes into some pipes
and goes out in the fountain again.
If someone, let's say,
goes into the fountain and pees
or whatever,
they have HIV or something,
everyone in the fountain
gets infected.
This is kind of a question.
Infected people with HIV
isn't even a felony anymore, so it's fine.
Are you not allowed to go in the fountain,
or are you discouraged heavily?
No, you're not allowed.
That's what I thought.
That's some bullshit.
I think if a baby drowned in there,
that wouldn't be the baby disobeying
the rules.
If there's a rule that you can't swim
in the thing,
a baby is going to not notice
and fall and die,
regardless of the rule,
it's up to the parent to make sure
the baby doesn't fall.
It made you respond to your point.
I'm not saying there should be rules
to play in the fountain.
If you want to have a no-peeing rule,
I understand.
But the fact that no one
is even allowed to interact with this fountain
in any way,
that far-fetched
HIV-P scenario,
when I pee, I spread my HIV.
I piss on every animal that I can see.
I infect as many as I can. It's like a video game to me.
But still, that will probably
never happen. But even if it does,
in that one scenario,
that shouldn't affect
the 99 other percent of the population.
I was just playing devils out of a good munchie.
Sure, I understand.
Here's a great example of some, though.
In Hawaii,
the beaches are public. As I said,
there are no lifeguards, and you can go to
any place where the water touches the land.
You're allowed to just go there, because it's all public.
So, like, among the
places we went to, me and Michelle went to, like, this big, huge,
rocky fucking place
with incredibly huge waves, and we just went in the water,
and you can just die
there, and people do
all the time. But we just didn't
give a fuck, and nobody tried to stop us,
and it was great. And I want to do that
all the time. Let me die.
Let the evolutionary process take its course
and wipe me out.
Right? I would agree.
It's these meddling moms.
It's fucking meddling parents,
fucking helicopter parents, that only have one fucking
kid, and they, uh, I care about my kids
so much. Your child should die.
Uh, if you're, if,
okay, just across the board, your child should be dead.
Uh, but specifically,
we need to, danger is, like, good
for people. You should have to face danger
and be responsible for yourself.
It's fucking nanny state cowards
expecting, like, uh, why isn't there systems
in place to protect me from every danger in the fucking
world? Maybe because we can't afford to protect
you from every fucking problem that exists
on the planet. It's not even like they're doing it out of, like, a genuine
care. It's because they don't, they don't reflect badly
on them, like, oh, I'll be a bad parent if my
kid gets fucked up. I'm sure there's some of that.
I'm sure there's some of that. You've got responsibility. Disgusting.
Disgusting.
People are weaned. In regards to
into the, the, the dangerous
rocky area. Yeah.
I think most people with, uh,
sensible senses will see
that it could be dangerous, but sometimes
something looks fine and, like,
there's a weird, uh, current
and that you could get dragged out or, like, dragged against
some rocks and die in a way
that, like, I don't think
there should ever be a rule to say you can't swim
there, um, but there should be
signs up if something is, like, kind of dangerous.
There are signs. I can do it.
There are signs up on every beach in Hawaii.
Every beach I went to there was, like,
you will die in this water if you go to it.
Alright. Then, then that's good.
I think, I think we can all agree that that makes a lot of sense.
People, yeah, yeah. But, but I would say
that, like, it's not anyone's
legislation. That's my motto.
And it's no one's responsibility
to make sure you're safe. It's your responsibility.
Like, so you've got to just,
I don't know, like, sure,
we want to rely on each other and, like, share
knowledge about, like, this beach is safe, this beach
is dangerous, you know, people have died there, so, you know,
take that into account and then go be free
and then go live your life and do whatever you want.
That's, that's what I dream of.
Yeah.
I'm saying is that I am not
allowed to touch this fucking turtle. I don't know why,
why even they fucking exist.
We can easily nuke who I can finish the job
we fucking started.
It could be under fucking water.
If you don't let me touch this turtle,
then why do you
look, we can play a settler game here.
We can play a settler game. Let's just,
let's just provoke North Korea
a little bit more, a little bit more,
and get them to do our dirty work for us.
I'm ringing up old Kim Jong right now.
Today I learned
baby turtles are penises
and they have foreskin.
Oh yeah, we can just fake and make the
volcanoes erupt. Easy.
Easy.
That being said, I love turtles, they're my best friend
and I am king of the turtles and
they have elected me as their president slash god
and I rule over them.
I think I, you know, due to my new
found superiority when it comes
to communicating with turtles, I speak
for them and myself when I say that they
love to be touched and they want nothing
more than to be my personal pet.
You should get a turtle or a tortoise.
I will.
I mean turtles are really the, the, the, the
optimal state of everything we've talked about. Think about it.
They have a shell so they can hide from the
prying eyes of the government and they can
go off grid and live wherever they want
to live.
I think turtles are the best friends on their back.
Oh my god. Guys. Okay. Idea.
Like hashtag idea. This is even better
than my shooting cops idea.
Okay.
Okay. If you hold on to a turtle
and you let him carry you away, then you'll
be in the ocean and no one will be able to
find you. So you can live off the grid
with turtles. Damn.
That's smart. That's smart.
Well, uh, is it, is it fair to say munchy
and everyone that the summary of this
is that, is that, is that good me?
Yeah, I think it is. Is that good me?
He had juggalo mask on.
Oh my god. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Hashtag idea again. I'm just fucking
I'm wrapping fire in this shit out right now.
I'm having fucking brain blasts of a brain which
I am baby Einstein right now.
All right.
Instead of juggalo face paint
it should be called juggalo face like
blackface because it's just as offensive.
If you want a real juggalo point on juggalo
face, then I don't want to fucking see you
near me. Yeah, that's good.
Stay a half mile away at least.
I find like, like, the equivalent
would be like somebody who just has a
skin condition that makes them look like a juggalo
because like, like blackface is
then putting on makeup to make them look
like something else. Yeah, yeah. And a juggalo
puts on makeup to be themselves
but if you don't put on makeup
and you just have a skin condition that makes you look like a juggalo
that's offensive.
I agree. You need to be purged.
Do we all agree that human happiness
comes over all animals?
Do we not agree with that? Yes.
Well, actually, I would say it's a little more
if we ever found an animal that had a human level
sentience, we would need to incorporate that.
Yes. I mean, I mean, sentient life
equals
greater than like a fucking cow
or something. 100%.
So I should be able to
do whatever I want to any animal
at any time. I don't want
to kill animals. So I'm a nice guy.
I'm not going to hurt it.
I just want to be able to touch it.
All I'm saying is that I am a good person
and I alone should
have domain over the tourists.
Honestly.
I suppose the counter argument there would be
is that like animals are part of like the
ecosystem and that if you brazenly
destroy them, like you're
inadvertently fucking up your own happiness.
Yeah, it's not about the animals.
It's about like other people who live there
want to enjoy turtle culture
and they don't want you fucking it up with
your radical, you know, right wing
ideas about reforming the government,
the turtle government that is, and, you know,
overthrowing shit.
The turtles need to secede, I think.
They need to get their own independence.
They need to see, see the
oceans right now.
Just a quick question. It makes me happy.
Oh, yeah. Okay. I'm just making sure
you could hear me. Okay, because I said something
and no one heard it and now the only...
Oh, no, we just thought it was shit.
No, we didn't hear it.
No, but no,
only the editor will know what I said.
So, have fun. Okay.
Alright.
Guys, we've been talking forever about this bullshit.
Maybe it's time to move on to calls and stuff.
I think it's time. Please, guys.
Um, I just want...
Hashtag Turlegate
at Hawaii right now on Twitter
with my hashtag idea.
Let's know about hashtag Turlegate.
Exactly. You want to be able to touch turtles?
Yes, yes. I, alone,
I don't want to reform the law.
I want you to make a new law
forbidding anyone else but me
from touching turtles.
Those Hurraions are wily. We need to
resurrect the zombie King Kamehameha
and have a commandment be ordered
so that you're allowed to touch the turtles.
Kamehameha was such a fucking cuck.
He was so... No, he wasn't. He was a fucking warlord.
He fucking killed everyone. It was pretty cool.
Yeah, he was like, oh, the British hot,
like, hey, dude, please, annex us.
Please, please. I'll put my...
I'll put your flag on my flag. Please, please.
I thought he was super opposed to that.
Am I wrong? Is that totally wrong?
Look at the Hawaiian flag.
Well, I mean, it's that now, but I didn't think it used to be.
Uh, maybe it was changed.
I know that when it became
a republic, not a kingdom.
The colors, the stripes were flipped upside down
but the union jacks still there.
The union jacks still there.
By the way, the Hawaiian flag sucks.
And every time I saw the Hawaiian flag, I barfed a little bit
Hang on, Hawaiian flag...
Let me see.
It has a union jack on it.
Dude, it looks dope.
Are you retarded, question mark?
Look at this flag. I think it looks dope.
It's good.
Is that the Hawaiian flag?
Yeah.
It's so weird.
I was thinking of that too.
England and Russia had a baby and it was Hawaii.
That makes sense. That makes sense to me.
It's super fucking weird and busy.
Yeah.
This is not designed very well.
Okay.
Real quick, the bars
have always annoyed me.
Look at the red bars going diagonally.
They do not meet
in the center.
They are off-center from each other.
What is the deal?
What's up with that?
The Irish flag is weird.
They want to preserve how the Irish flag sucks.
Not like the Republic of Ireland,
like Northern Ireland or something.
Right.
God, it pisses me off. I hate it.
It's terrible.
The Northern Ireland flag
is just like a normal fucking cross.
It's not a weird one.
It just is normal.
I forget why they do that.
That's an aesthetic as fuck flag.
I know what you're saying.
I agree with you.
I don't know why the stripes on the union jack are not like that.
Is it Scotland?
What they're doing,
if you see underneath
the horizontal vertical cross
in the middle,
the diagonals
are making a very, very, very tiny swastika.
You can't really see it.
That's what it's doing.
Here's another visual meme.
This is a Hawaiian flag I can get behind.
Resurrect the empire now.
I love the cropping on that.
I love the same quality.
Oh my god, guys.
There are questions in a second.
I have to tell you about the dinosaurs.
The dinosaurs in Hawaii are rampant
and they are on the loose.
Every single time that I entered
a fucking car
I would hear
these two guys
of very different my qualities.
I mentioned a blue snowball.
Over the radio?
Yeah, a commercial on the radio.
Living breathing dinosaurs!
Can't see the belly cover
the sun right there.
Breathing dinosaurs!
He had a baby T-Rex!
He had a wife!
Two people screaming
for like,
three minutes
of non-fat back and forth.
Come see dinosaurs!
Who in the mouth?
Military discount!
Living breathing dinosaurs!
That's like back and forth.
It's like JurassicTour.com
Yeah, because they filmed Jurassic Park there.
Yeah, something like that.
And it was just fucking
every single time I got in the car.
I heard that commercial
eight times. I haven't memorized
back to fucking back.
You could be listening to some shitty
R&B or whatever other shit stuff
that Hawaiians are listening to nowadays.
And then it's like, I love your baby
and fades out. Living breathing
dinosaurs here in Hawaii!
Why?
Why did the guy
have such a shit microphone?
I don't know!
It was so bad!
It was just this guy
screaming at Tom's lungs and then like his buddy
his like hype man, his wingman
coming up, talking in inaudible
tones. Trying to like
desperately trying to come see the fucking
stupid dinosaurs. They have
manufactured. That sounds like
Hawaiian T-Bap right there.
Oh it does! Ben with this terrible mic quality
even though we use the same microphone
for every episode to you at.
I'm trying to find it right now.
I forget what it is.
It's Jurassic something.
It's not Jurassic Park obviously.
It's Jurassic
Landmobile.
I hope someone else can find it. Anyway,
the point of that is that I Google search them
because they had a website.
And then they have, they're preaching about
all these fucking sick ass dinosaurs
that are so realistic.
It's like a cartoon depiction of a dinosaur.
It's got like big like bulging eyes
and it's like fucking little puppet like muppet
shit. And they're talking about living, breathing
dinosaurs that can come and see.
It just is a guy who is like
holding a puppet of a T-Rex looking at
children right now.
Alright, so there's a bit of an exaggeration
there. You know, a bit of an upsell.
Living, breathing dinosaurs
here in Maui!
Can't see this!
That is it. It was great.
It was my favorite thing about it.
Okay, that sounds incredible.
Moving on everybody.
Yeah, so here's the deal everybody.
In case you haven't heard,
you haven't heard, what is it?
It's www.speakpipe.com
slash PCP voicemail.
We've got the box open
and in the two days it's been since
the last episode we've got a whole
bunch of voicemails.
I listened to a few of them before the show
I listened to a couple as well.
Now we might need to work out some kinks here
because we have to do some roundabout shit
to get to play so we can all hear it.
But you don't give a fuck about that.
That doesn't matter.
By the way, if yours isn't played, that means
you are gay.
I did not click on these to quality control
like which are good and which are bad.
I will be doing that in the future. I just was
busy with this.
I figured...
Indeed. Let's play the very first voicemail
that we got
from a little boy
with a big dream named Connor.
Let's see what he's got for us
on this edition of PCB voicemail.
Here we go.
Look
I am a three step plan
for how you guys can make this show so much better.
What you need to do is you need to
get five different recordings
of everyone except
G.E. saying
Yeah.
Yeah? Okay.
And then just
you guys don't have to appear in the episode
and then we can just have this guy yelling
at the top of his lungs.
Sample that for about two minutes
and then repeat it all and stop.
And then you've got another episode.
You guys win. You can just take all the picture
of money without having to do anything.
That's my two step plan for how to make
you guys rich quick.
Sam.
Okay. First of all, that's how we do the
PCB AI that we talked about.
We just get recordings of all of us
nodding in agreement, like the sound effect
of us moving our heads up and down.
And then we just
we get the words Starfleet how
and then we just have like
we're played over and over again Starfleet how
Starfleet how Starfleet Starfleet
and then we just have that play and then us like
nodding in agreement.
I just like the idea of like Nate doing a thing
with his voice like saying Starfleet how
we'll just talk over it.
Starfleet how.
It like ignores us.
I'm not even opposed to doing this as a bonus episode.
That would be a great
that would be a great idea.
So thanks Connor. Congratulations.
You're the first ever guy.
Hey, come
come back out to Armour Treatment Con 4.
It's not happening, but just do it
and then hope it happens.
Was Connor there? Do you know that guy?
Connor came to Armour Treatment Con 3.
He cosplayed as the arm.
Oh, he was the arm.
He was cosplaying as the arm and he had the
Terezi glasses and horns.
He was cool. And now he's a notorious
Freemason
in the RFCK
discord. So I know Connor. Good for him.
Notorious.
Alright, let's go on to our next one here. This is from Tep.
This was the next message. Let's see what we got here.
Let's see what we got here.
Oh.
That was it.
Very nice.
Thank you. Appreciate that Tep for that
lovely belch.
Okay, let's see what we got.
Who was that? That was from Tep.
Hey Tep, I got something for her.
No.
Okay, there you go.
I'll be prepared next time.
I'll be carbonated and I'll fuck you up.
Appreciate that.
I'll throw my headphones out of my ears.
Let's see what else we got. Here's one from Liam.
Okay, this one's 19 seconds.
Let's see what we got here.
G'day to the PCP.
This is Liam from the upside down and down under
that apparently is fake.
My question to you is,
we know that mage is the violet violence.
So what action color
combination is each other member
of the PCP?
Oh, that's cool.
This is a boring question.
The turquoise terrorists.
Oh, that's a good one.
I'm the pink passion.
The pink passion.
Okay, I'll just be
the
the lime green
lime man.
Lime green limestone.
Tom is the bitch bitch.
He's the blue bitch.
Tom's the red scare.
He's the red scare is where he is.
No, he's the red retard.
I don't know why you're taking it
in such a negative place.
Muchy, do we need to like
pass to the guy? Is there a problem here?
Yeah.
Check out this black guy I just found.
I'll be the green machine.
That works. All right, let's see what we got here.
Oh, that's a good black guy you got right there.
I like that. That's Ben St.
He's the black guy.
The black guy.
Ben St.
My favorite alliteration.
I call him the black panther.
Yeah, that's a good one too.
The black banther, so it rhymes.
Let's see.
Only people who are here get him.
Also Ben, because I felt like it.
Nobody else gets them because they're lame.
What was Ben's?
Ben's?
He's the black guy.
I'll just have everybody know right now,
Digi is leaving the house immediately.
He could be on the show right now, but he's not.
He's being a faggot and not participating.
Well, there you go.
No nickname for you. Doc is pay forever.
Yep, we'll do. Doc's is pay.
Like find out where his payment is.
Let's get another one here.
This is from Marky Mark
and the Funky Bunch.
Let's see what we got.
Hey, I just want to say
you should all kill yourselves for doing the PCP theme song thing.
It sucks.
And that's it.
He's saying what we're all thinking.
Now, I assume he's in the
the loud camp of naysayers
who are being like, oh, the second one should have won.
Why didn't that one win?
Arkans was better than Sasuke's.
Sasuke will pull a fucking
Susano Genjutsu on your fucking ass
and turn your asshole inside out
in an illusion.
I haven't listened to the thing yet and Arkans got second.
I really wanted
because I voted for Arkans and
I wanted what I thought is if he's in the theme
we should do a channel trailer
to that.
It was great.
We're going to use these for things
and I think that one will definitely be around.
We're setting such a bad precedent right now
playing all of these.
It's going to be all fucking shit
and burping and some guy's going to piss
and be like, hey, Munchie, try me out.
The great news about the way that we're doing it now
is we can just cut ones we don't
like or censor things if we need to
or do whatever the fuck we want
because we don't owe these fucking people anything.
So it's great.
Now, there was like one or two good ones.
Okay, here's a good one, Munchie.
You'll be into this. This is from
Take Down Big Weed
is this one.
Let's see what we've got here.
And away we go.
Hey, big fan of the show here.
I was just wondering,
what's your favorite anime?
Oh!
Okay.
Voice actor hired immediately.
Whoever you are.
If I ever make
like a children's television show, you will play
the main character.
I loved it. I loved every second
of that clip.
Thank you. Thank you
for participating in history.
You guys said the anime shit
questions would never pay off
with a punchline. Well,
eat your words, friends.
If you think this is the end of it,
you have no idea what the fuck you've just bred.
Now that they know that they can get
on the show and make us laugh by saying
what's your favorite anime, every
fucking week we're gonna have some dumb
ass be like, um, what's
your favorite?
It's already a week.
We can cut them.
Or we can just, we can screen them ahead of time
and not play ones that are shit. We can do whatever we want, man.
Or we can screen at them as they happen.
Okay, that one was good. But I've got big
expectations for our boy. Her anime is
Karikano. That's a good one.
But here's XXX Epic Gamers
69 420 XXX
with an epic question
I've no doubt. What do we got?
What do we got here?
Hey guys, Epic Gamer here.
Today, I'm gonna teach you how to become an epic gamer.
Step one, you need to
learn the two tenets of gaming.
Number one, abusing women.
Two.
Now I have to step two.
Now you'll want to get your battle
station swept up.
So now that you've swept up in the winds
of capitalism and that you've
just solved the same.
As the Lord would want of you to.
Now on to part three. Getting your games.
Go to newtaku.com
for 10% off.
We'll see you later gamers. I'm off to
jump off the battle bus.
Okay, okay.
Don't take this the wrong way.
Any of you guys. This is not an insult
in any way. But,
the thing that makes these,
if any of us were to say this,
it probably would not be as funny as you saying it.
You got your, like the fans,
your mic quality and lack of
like confidence
on stage.
Make these extremely funny.
When you're saying like, you gotta
beat women and
I love it. It's really funny
and thank you.
I'm not trying to shame you.
I'm not trying to make you upset.
I would
specifically endorse people who have never
used a microphone before to do this.
I like it. It's so easy.
It's a great like rick and moody
improvisational sort of feeling.
It's just so you know guys. It's so easy
to do with SpeakPipe. There's a link
in the description. SpeakPipe.com
slash PCP voicemail. Do it now.
Go just record and be
a funny boy and get
your voice heard because it's funny
shit and I like it.
People who screen this don't like it.
Well, yeah, fair enough.
I mean, you know, that's why we'll screen them or whatever.
Alright, let's do like one or two more. Here's a
philosopher king almond milk
has left one.
This is like a minute. Alright, let's see what we got here.
You know what
fucking pisses me off
through common rules
when Nate and Jesse
objectively fucking
destroys did you stupid opinion
about renounciations when he says
it feels like a little child he's screaming
and then he screams
and the objectivity isn't real.
I like this guy. He's got a sound thing.
He's got objectivism.
He's got a fucking
topic.
He's got an objectivist
with relatively unpinning.
Or because a relativist cuck
has an objective statement as a cunt
in a debate
because all they say is
it's all subjective. Fuck off
and get raped you stupid motherfucker.
How the fuck can you
get raped in our objective
statement
by disregarding objectivism.
It just doesn't fucking work.
You think one of the rules
of objectivism
but you...
Alright.
Okay. Whoa, this guy
just slain.
There's so much about pronouncing words
he just can't help it.
Don't get me wrong, this man is objectively correct
about being mad at didgy for fucking
the pronunciation of words.
But more than that, what he's really doing
is recoiling to didgy's cuck
mentality of relativism
and while it's true
there's many things that we cannot prove are real.
Just be like, oh my god.
Okay, didgy's point has always been
terrible about pronouncing. Like, I want to
pronounce words this way, therefore
I can do whatever I want because language is just a social construct.
Like, okay.
But...
We live in a society.
In a society.
Not if you live in a tree.
If you go to a tree,
stay there for a very long time.
You won't have to speak words at all.
They won't get it.
Oh.
The sole point of a language is
so people can communicate.
So there are standards that we use.
I know that.
Guys, you're not gonna fucking believe this.
Okay, what's up?
You're not gonna believe this.
Who called the Pokemon?
Oh no, I'm not gonna tell you what the Pokemon is.
I'm gonna see if you can see it.
Kinkillian.
Can you pronounce a Pokemon's name?
Kingler? What Pokemon do you think he's referring to?
Was it Kingler?
No. Kecleon?
Yes, Kecleon. It was Kecleon.
What? Why?
That doesn't make any sense.
The word is not written that way.
This is what didgy is arguing for right now.
Isn't it because it's like
chameleon?
That's exact justification.
Wait.
How terrible.
I can see that actually.
Kinkillian and Kecleon.
You know what?
I have not looked into it. Okay, tell you what.
Let's just do one more.
There's this one about a guy traveling Japan
that I already listened to.
I'm gonna try to find it.
Play this one in the meantime.
Let me see where the fuck did it go.
Okay, this one is from
Sorry, I already played that. OneSpar.
This is one from OneSpar.
Who's an old fogey.
An old codger around these parts.
I can actually beat this.
Okay, let's find out.
Hello, Procrastinators. This is OneSpar
of OneSpar Weekly.
My favorite program.
I think that you guys could be giving
more of a spotlight on the podcast
to
fan highlights
and fan animation videos
of the Procrastinators podcast.
Fan animations?
I've seen definitely a few
really great ones and
I think they deserve an honorable mention at least.
Of course,
none was standing. I've made my own highlights
and I plan to make more in the future
and it would be great to hear your guys'
opinions on some of the ones that exist
and where they're good and where they're
not so good.
Anyway, that's my call.
That's why I did it
and now I'm done.
It's over.
Goodbye.
He was really polite.
I like him.
OneSpar's a good lad.
I think he had made some of the PCB
highlights that I put onto
the PCB Highlights Channel
which I made a while back.
I think a lot of people know that it exists by the way.
I made a PCB Highlights Channel
back and I was going to do more with it.
It simply became apparent that
it took effort to do this
and arrange this and I was already spending too much
time working on PCB stuff
as is. The channel exists.
There's a couple highlights on there. I always meant
to put more. People have produced more and
there's a thing in the Patreon and Discord.
I think it's called the PCB Highlights
Chat where I ask people to give us
good things to do.
Give us cool segments to clip and turn
into a highlight because I do think that's actually
a very good idea to grow the show
and get more people to watch and stuff.
It simply is a matter of
it takes effort to do that
and I'm already
fucking pressed for time.
I want to find a solution. We talked about
possibly paying people for doing it
but I don't know.
I'm not really sure what the best way
to handle it is. To highlight them
on the show, to show
fan art we decided not to do that
because it's a visual thing.
That seems reasonable. But how exactly
would we show highlights on the show?
I don't think that makes much sense.
I think he is just
talking about shouting out the fact that
the highlights exist.
I think what would be the best plan would be
to work with people who want to do them
whatever. Maybe do the re-uploads
of people's highlight stuff
onto the PCB Highlights. Of course give them
as much credit as they
want. All that shit. And then
shout that out more in
main episodes here. I think that would probably
be the best thing to do. I think that's a good call.
Yeah. It's just a question of
I did that stuff. I started it
I didn't do much and I always
wanted to do more. And ideally if I had infinite
time I would. I just don't...
Oh he did so many highlights.
Yeah he did.
He's fucking done a bunch of them. So
here's a quick shout out to celebrate the more
Oncebar. Go check out his channel
on YouTube. Oncebar weekly. He's done a bunch of cool shit.
There you go.
We should listen to One More by
Jamie. I don't know if you have that
download. But I listened to
Jamie's beforehand. I liked it. And I think
it's important that we have it in the show.
Jamie. Yeah. I have it right here. Okay.
Let's give it a listen. Hang on.
Hang on. Over here.
Okay. This is like a real one.
A real one. All those ones were bullshit
up to this point. Let's hear the real one.
Real ones recognize real ones. Here we go.
Hey guys. How's it going? Big fan here.
We've got a request for help, which is
that I'm going to Japan in like two weeks
and we'll be spending a week or so in Tokyo
and don't want to just get stuck
visiting gay ass tourist tracks
the whole time. So if any of you
have been, and I know Nate definitely has,
where are the cool places?
And how do I get
to them? And as a side question
what cool food should I
eat that I can't get in the west?
Excellent question. Also Munchie is right and the
old theme should stay as the outro.
Thanks.
I don't even really oppose
that as being used for the outro.
But we'll, I don't know, I guess you'll find
out when you get to the end of this episode
how that's been resolved. Won't you, fair listener?
Okay. So you're going to Japan.
Here's tip number one.
This is for everyone, regardless
of where they're going, you, anyone.
Whenever you want to eat
food, ask
your hotel manager, or better yet
your cab guys. It's a good idea. Someone
who lives there, ask them where
to eat. Say,
Sumimosenkabisan
Doko tabimasuka
give them one of those
and they'll say, you know,
Hey, since then, give me a asshole
bug. I can't believe I ever
said what Nate said, despite the horrible
accident.
Oh, you understood it? Yeah, yeah. I mean, that was
actually a relatively correct way to
say something. It's just like, it's
a very, very kind of way of saying it.
Well, yeah. So
Munchie's a way better like travel guy. He
knows about doing cool things. Okay, okay.
TripAdvisor is
ironically a lifesaver. You got to know how
to use TripAdvisor. What is TripAdvisor?
Is it a website? No, it's
it. Well, yes, it is an app as well, though.
Oh, it's an app. Okay, okay.
You can sort things, like TripAdvisor
people are mostly based,
like they mostly, when you
go to Google or something, you're going to have
you know, like crack heads
and fucking, you know, Johnny Depp
and shit like that. You don't know what, who's
going to tell you what. So when you go on TripAdvisor
they are mostly people who care about
traveling and, you know, want to actually give
accurate information in my experience
going to Rome and Hawaii and stuff like
that. So using TripAdvisor
you are going to want to use that as sort
of like a baseline. If you just
have no one that you can turn to a local
to ask for directions or anything like that,
you're going to use TripAdvisor as a sort of
backup so you can have, you understand what's
going on in your life and you have some big idea
of what to do. But honestly, you should ask the
people in Japan, because I've not been to Japan
I'm sure Nate can tell you a little bit of cool stuff
but really you should be asking the people
who are actually living there
and have similar interest to you. I mean
it depends on what kind of trip you want to
have. I can't
really know if it's like an Eiffel Tower
or anything like that.
Fucking Tokyo Tower. Go to Tokyo Tower.
It's like, it's kind of, it's modeled after the Eiffel Tower
I don't know if you want to go, I don't know if you want
to go see monuments like that or if you just want
to have a good time in a foreign country
and learn what it's like.
Restaurants, the most important thing
in your fucking trip is eating good food.
That is the most important thing
in going to any country is eating
the food and the real food that they eat
as well. You don't want to eat fucking hamburgers
while you're in Japan. You want to be eating
ramen or fucking, you know, whatever
the hell they eat in that fucking fermented
shark, Johnny Depp, shit like that.
So you want to go there and you want to have
some fried debt and that's what you want to do.
Have ramen because they're like ramen.
So find out what good restaurants
there and Nate you probably know more specifically
about Japan. I mean, yeah, yeah,
I can give you some of the
some of the good shit.
I mean, you got to go to, you're going to enjoy
I think just hitting up
there's like what's called like the 404
Square or something. You're going to want to go
to downtown Tokyo and just walk around
because there's dope shit. It's really cool. It just
looks really nice. Go into some shops.
Go to Uniqlo. They got they got good
shit around there. You're going to want to go to
Akihabara. Give yourself
like a day or two or three
of your trip I would do to
simply go to Akihabara and walk around
because it is gigantic and here's something important
you got to know about Japan.
A lot of the cool shit
has like small signs out
front and like there's
like small passageways like get back into
buildings that like host like
20 different businesses in it. And then
only once you get inside do you see how
there's so much dope shit hiding
like behind the
storefront or whatever that has like other
advertisements or whatever. So I would say
do some research and find out cool
things you might want to go to. You should check out
Super Bunny Hop just made a video on like the
like the game
what was it? It's like
video game bars basically in Japan
and how they're having tough times. That's just
a quick video to watch that's educational
about the nature of this stuff. I check that out
because that's helpful and interesting.
One thing you definitely
should do is learn a little
bit of the history before you go there. On the plane
right it doesn't take a lot of time. You don't have
to go get a fucking history book or something
you can just do simple some fucking like
extra credits or some baby shit like that
just learn a little bit of the history of Japan
where you're going, where you're staying
because learning about the country
in which you are happening is probably the most
important thing you can do. I mean that's the reason
you're going. No, no, no. Throw that in the trash
that doesn't matter. You've seen anime
you know everything you need to know about Japan.
I forgot, I forgot. Yeah, that's right.
But just, I don't know
what it's really like in Asian countries
I've never been there but if they have
equivalent to like European style monuments
and stuff, read all the monuments.
Shinto shrines. Check out some Shinto shrines.
Yeah, check out Shinto shrines.
Catch a farfetched
and trade it to me. Don't forget to do that.
Okay, okay, okay. Real fucking talk
Jamie. Real fucking talk.
I have got a Mr. Mime and a Corsola
with your name on it
if you give me a farfetched.
You can have a fucking Corsola from Hawaii
from me.
Your god king if you give me a farfetched.
Hang on, hang on. Are you saying our Corsola
is exclusive to Hawaii or something?
No, they're exclusive to the equator.
Oh.
Oh fuck. I didn't know about that. God damn it
I would have caught one if I'd known.
Hey, hey, I can give you one for a price.
Oh, no.
I've never heard of a blow job, Nate.
Because you might need it.
He's pretty familiar with that.
Here I go again.
You wind up in jail.
Anyway, Jamie,
I wish you all the best. Learn about Japan.
Understand it. Ask the locals.
And don't be afraid
to go on a tour, but do know
that you should be picking tours pretty smartly.
It's kind of hard to know what tours to go on
when you're already out traveling.
But don't go on tours that are too restrictive.
Don't go to
a general Tokyo tour
because you might not see.
Just go to pretty specific things.
Focus tours. Focus tours are good.
And just learn
as much as you can while you're there.
Learn about the culture, learn about the people,
learn about the history, and that's what you should do.
Here's just some tangible things to keep in mind.
Just rapid fire. Here's what you do.
Go to Don Quixote in Akihabara.
You're famous. You're going to want to tell your friends
you've been to Don Quixote in Akihabara.
It's cool. Go to
a made cafe.
I regret not going. Go to a made cafe
and enjoy the experience
and you will be a true anime boy.
Just do it. Don't push the out like I did.
I like to go to a cat cafe.
Go to a cat cafe.
They got those. Those are cool.
You're going to want to... Okay. I don't know how old you are.
I don't know what your deal is.
I don't know if you're going with family or friends
but that changes the whole experience.
It absolutely does.
I had some of my best times in Japan
at like 5 a.m.
at Roppongi, which is the red light district
like the club areas.
Go there. Get wasted
and
go to Gas Panic.
If that club still exists. That was a dope place.
Tell them Nate Bestman sent you
and they'll let you into the VIP lounge.
That's a lie. That will not work.
Oh, best guy ever.
Oh!
America Jean.
I just checked it right now
but I will tell you
about a company.
This is free advertising.
Please unironically sponsor us
the company Secret Food Tours.
Oh, that sounds good.
The best fucking time I had in Rome.
The highlight of this trip
not a joke
was this tour by fucking
Secret Food Tours.
They do not have one for Tokyo.
They have stuff like Hong Kong
but America on there.
Not just you, but anyone who's traveling soon.
Search for Secret Food Tours
and see if they have one in the place that you're going to.
Because it was fantastic.
You go around
to local ass
real restaurants that locals go to every day.
It was fucking delicious.
You could have little samplers across the entirety
of Rome in my instance.
You just walked around Rome.
Your tour guide
tells you about daily life in Rome.
What it's like to live there.
The history of what everything is like.
I learned about how in Rome
there's these weird
fountains that are everywhere
that are constantly dispensing water.
They're just wasting tons of water.
They talked about how the government
is too fucking lazy to clog
the water pipes.
They called them big noses.
I learned a little quirky little shit about there
in Rome in the city.
I learned a lot of history. It was great.
Secret food tours, good shit.
When it comes to food, let me just say three things.
One, go to Yoshinoya.
Yoshinoya is the McDonald's of Japan.
So it's worth going to.
And it is simply an unagi
which is an eel on rice, like bowl.
Their motto is like
fast, quick, and cheap.
You slap down one fucking hundred yen coin.
You got yourself a delicious bowl
of rice and eel with sauce and shit.
You'll see all the cool businessmen,
all the Japanese business boys
having that shit for lunch. It takes them like five minutes.
They got their little tea dispensers.
Go to Yoshinoya. It's dope.
Go to a McDonald's.
Experience Japanese McDonald's.
Highly recommended. It is
a thousand times better. The people are pretty.
The people are professional. They are clean.
It's a world different.
They've got unique, special, just Japan
items on the menu. Go there. You won't regret it.
It's like a fancy restaurant in Japan.
And final point is that I just agree
with Monchi completely.
One of the most striking memories I have of Japan
was just when I stumbled.
I was just like, I'm hungry.
Turn to the left. See a random curry
shop where you just walk into.
Got like the best curry of my life
in this random, absolute, no idea
how I could ever find it ever again
curry place. Let yourself be free
and experience things like that.
For a close food boy.
I don't know about.
What can I say? I'm still, I'm not perfect.
I'm not a perfect person yet. When I replace my brain
with cybernetics. Food is culture.
Food is culture.
I like your food. What were you saying though?
I don't know about you, but like
if somebody said
all that to me
when I was asking, what do I do in Japan?
I would get overwhelmed with the amount of stuff
and I would end up not doing anything.
Well, that's his problem.
I think it's that hard.
I don't know the words, but what did we
actually just say? Go on TripAdvisor
and ask your family what to do.
Look, Akihabara, Gas Panic, Don Quixote
various game shops, Made Cafe
Shinto Shrine.
If you do those, you'll have a great time in Japan.
Do those locals do and learn the culture?
That's all I'm saying.
No, I'm just saying like
I don't know who else feels this way,
but I feel sometimes a lot of pressure
to experience things while I'm at a place
and it ends up stressing me out.
You don't have to experience anything.
You could just go to Japan
and go to McDonald's every day.
I mean, you say it's different, but you know,
it is McDonald's.
You don't have something familiar
and you could do that in Japan and it would still be different
because you're in a foreign country.
You don't have to do the major sites or anything.
This is your vacation, assumably.
You're an adult and you're going for fun.
Let's be with your family and you are fucked.
I'm sorry, but you will have a terrible time.
It's inevitable that the food is quite different though,
but I wouldn't worry too much about it
because you'll encounter tons of crazy things.
I'm saying is that you don't have to try too hard
to have a different experience in Japan.
You don't have to feel pressured to see everything.
Just do what you want to do
and I assume what you want to do is have fun
and then we're telling you how to have fun.
Yeah.
Well guys, that's enough of those for one day.
Let's grab a couple of questions real quick.
I see one question.
Here's Jamie. Here, can you do one thing for me?
Go to Japan and don't come back. How about that?
How is he going to bring you that farfetched
if he doesn't come back?
Please come back.
Please.
All right. Who wants to go check out
the old lounge there with the questions, everybody?
Go pick something out while I grab
a little pity question here from the Twitter.
I have a question. I have a question.
It's from Oncebar, actually.
Let me just say don't forget, everybody, follow us
at tpcrasnators for these announcements on Sunday
when we record and send a question with hashtag
askpcp. All right, Mage, what do you get?
Oncebar's political parquet
at Hippo and Mage.
What are politics like in England and Lithuania
right now? Do you guys even into that stuff?
To answer my part of the question.
I'm really not into it.
The last I know of Lithuanian politics
is that we have a female
president and she's been
a president for like 10 years, I think,
now, 9 to 10 years.
I think she's the first president to get
re-elected as old in Lithuania.
So yeah, not only the first female,
but the first to get re-elected.
So go
her, I guess.
Yeah, good for her.
We, in England, we have a female
prime minister and she is
Oh my god, the women's are taking over.
She is like
the worst thing of all time
and I hope that she falls down the stairs
and somebody films it
and turns it into a very funny game.
Damn.
I generally don't care about politics
but what little I know is that
we suck at the moment.
We're in a fucking mess.
Brexit was a mistake and everybody's an idiot
and I don't trust anyone.
Well, fair enough. Except maybe Jeremy Corbyn
but I don't know enough about him
necessarily.
Oh man, look at some of these questions.
Some of them are too real.
What do you think about socialism, guys?
What do you think about redistribution?
Oh god, no, stop.
It's not a politics show.
It's not a politics show, guys.
What do we got here?
Okay, here's a little question.
This is just a general one, whatever.
At Alien Observer asks,
we don't need to go into this too much, but
if PCB HQ becomes a thing,
what do you see actually changing
in each of your content?
What new things can you not make now
that you would be able to make then?
I'll tell you one thing.
Every show that I have, I would get immensely better.
Ethan's editing right now.
What's he working on right now?
Stealing your dad.
Stealing your dad episodes.
And they are infinitely better
than just the pure audio show.
They are fucking incredible.
We're in our own house.
We're not in public.
We're allowed to say the swear words
really loudly.
It's great. It's fantastic.
They were great. Hippo was there.
Hippo, I can imagine, was scared
during the recording of his episode.
No, no, no, I like it.
It was fucking funny.
I enjoyed the leftover pizza.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Okay, spoiler alert.
We had a pizza place for the second episode.
And we left the pizza
open in the basement overnight.
Like the rags of pizza.
These like shreds.
There's like a couple pieces across.
I go there and spoiler alert.
I like crushed the pizza with my hands.
Completely obliterated.
It's over. This pizza is non-edible.
Overnight, it stays.
It rots there. This is in a fucking basement.
I'm sure there's bugs and shit.
Ben comes at night.
Ben comes at night the next day.
And I was like, ooh, pizza.
Don't mind if I do.
It was me, Ben and Nate.
And none of us knew.
Because none of us were there.
So we all had a bit.
It was in fucking pieces.
These were not pieces of pizza.
These were like...
I can't wait for you all to watch this episode
and see what you consumed.
I had a bit of the crust.
It was nice.
Maybe it's not too late.
Ethan, if you could edit in
the fact that we ate this pizza
after whatever is done to it.
People consumed this pizza later.
That footage is in the
behind-the-scenes red color stuff.
Oh, it is?
Of us finding the pizza.
Oh man, that'd be pretty good.
Okay, well whatever.
Enough spoilers for stealing your dad.
Anyway, I don't know.
There's all kinds of stuff we can do
when PCBHQ becomes a thing.
I mean, you wouldn't be part of
the change of the content
since you're not there, that's true.
Nor would anyone else who isn't physically present.
But if, for example,
the PCP became a show
that had a video component
and then we could have people call in
a major set, like it's certainly possible to do still.
So, you know, could be
a visual aspect to it. I would be able to do skits.
I want to do skits so bad.
They're my one passion in life. I want to do them so bad.
I want someone to write a script
and I'll be able to be their autonym on
and read a script for them.
Yeah, I want to set up a big,
actual, proper green screen
and do full-body green screen stuff.
I stand with a green screen suit on
in front of my green screen.
I get so many shenanigans.
I mean, I'm already doing some stuff with Digi
since I'm here.
IM Games has a marriage since then.
Which is fucking dope.
And once he's done with this gay month of making videos every day
I guess I'm fucking try hard bitch.
He's almost done. He's almost done.
Yeah, he's almost done.
Then we're going to do IM Games pretty hard.
It's going to be sick.
And yeah, that's going to be dope.
I went to the...
Everyone, I encourage you to do this.
Go to the IM Games YouTube channel.
YouTube channel with zero content
and like several hundred,
maybe thousand now subscribers.
And I went to the...
I would go to the discussion tab and post your feelings,
your strong feelings on IM Games.
I put the words
put me in the screen cap
on the top of the discussion board.
And I encourage everyone else to tell them
how it's your favorite YouTube channel with zero content.
Yes.
The shirts are selling like fucking hotcakes.
They are.
You got to get on that shit.
We have a new design.
I don't know if you saw the new IM Games t-shirt.
In addition to the IM Games
and the IM Games After Dark,
which is just white text on a black shirt
and a black text on a white shirt.
We also have the JoJo meme shirt,
which is
quality shit.
It was a very painstaking design process.
Lots of back and forth in the
design process.
But at the end of the day
the pink comic sans
with a
bright green glow that just says
JoJo meme in all lower case
just seemed like the perfect
representation of our vision for the broad.
Listen. Don't take our word for it.
Listen to Steve.
Steve.
IM Games After This.
After the release of IM Games,
Steve.
IM Games.
I got to be honest.
The whole
selling the shirt before making
the thing
disgusts me and I hate it.
For
various reasons.
It just makes me upset.
Well,
I'm sorry, the pre-order.
As someone
who supports Jeremy Corbin, I'm not surprised
you don't like capitalism. Anyways, moving on.
Tom, are you making those shirts
or are you getting them printed somewhere?
Well, we have them on red bubble and spread shirt,
but the first run I made in house.
Okay. Cool.
Everyone who got one from that first run
were handmade and shipped out.
They were made with love.
Over a thousand
shirts sold, right?
Over 10,000 shirts sold, right?
Yeah.
It's just that
it's, you know,
money spent, actually I can't talk.
I can't talk. I bought the fucking drill
book of just his tweets.
But it is a book. It's like, I mean, that is the content.
You know, you're not like...
Well, yeah, I mean, it's just like
buying a shirt because it's funny to buy
a shirt so quickly after the creation
of a thing that you're not really a fan of,
but you think it's, it looks cool and that's why
you buy it. Like, I get it.
Is that why you buy clothing?
I don't buy things with things
on them. I don't like shirts that have
text on them and the fact that like
90% of commerce is T-shirts
with words on them
just makes me sad in general
and the fact that this is like a big thing
that people are really... Yeah, that's true.
I just...
makes me want a crumpled paper cup.
Oh, fair enough.
But I mean, see, you're like...
I'm not that mad, but I'm mad enough to crumple a paper cup,
but not enough to like smash
like a steel girdle. I am games
that's made given I am rage, so...
That's true. What about... I am...
Alright, well, enough of that.
From Oblivion Fault.
What song would you listen to
during the apocalypse?
I hate my life and I want to die
I don't got no iPhone
My heart is breaking
thinking suicide
I ain't got no iPhone
I was listening to that.
That's a pretty good one.
Ever listen to that
Tricia Paytas song
I Hate My Life?
That's a good one.
Imagine some fat
muckbang eating
vlog YouTuber
with a severe depression
who's constantly being
discarded by the men in her life.
Just saying a song about how she hates her life
and then immediately the next day
releases a song about how Jesus made it all okay.
That's the arc I want to go on.
My song of choice would be
I'd be in the middle of
the war-torn desolate wasteland
air everywhere
air thick with smoke
a giant meteor slowly descending
towards the fucking
doomed face of the planet.
I looked down at my iPod in my hand
and I clicked a button
and the lyrics would rush over me
and speak to my soul.
I just want to play video games
as the flames engulf me.
Black Hole for Life
whatever they're called.
In the Boston Institute
of Contemporary Art there is a VR exhibit
like a piece of art
that is you put on the VR
and you live through the apocalypse
and you get to see yourself go to hell and stuff like that.
Is that true? Yeah.
You get to see everyone die around you.
That's incredible. Yeah, it's great.
Like, really. This is actually real.
Yeah, this is actually real.
It might be gone now because it might have been part of an exhibit that is gone now, but
but I was there
and I got to see
the giant tidal wave crash over myself.
The best part about it
is that because it was made for this museum
you start out in the museum
where you are presently standing
in real life and you get to see the wave
actually crash into you.
That's dope. Yeah, it's great.
And then you get to see yourself go to hell and get eaten and shit.
What's hell like?
It's just kind of like the PS2 opening.
Yeah, right.
That's what I think about it. By the way,
if this video is not a joke,
if this video gets 300 likes,
I will cover at the top of my lungs of
I ain't got no iPhone. I will do a full cover.
There you go, people. Smash that motherfucking
like button right now.
Don't forget to subscribe and ring that mother
flippin' bell so you get every notification
from the procrastinators.
Are we done?
Let's play Tobuscus. Can we do like a crossover
with Tobuscus? That's a really good idea.
I think we've got a lot in common with that guy.
Both rape apologists.
Hey, he was
not convicted of anything.
He is innocent until
proven guilty.
That's what I have to say. There you go.
There you go. A woman defends him,
therefore he didn't do it. That's it, everybody.
That's fair. That makes sense to me.
All right, I think we're done.
Thanks for listening, everybody, to this episode
of the Procrastinators podcast.
That's patreon.com
slash theprocrastinators.
$1 pledge. You're in the Discord chat
hanging out with us, asking questions, etc.
$5 page bonus episodes.
By the time you hear this,
there will be a new episode
up and running, and I won't spoil it,
but let's just say
come hungry.
Come hungry and come often.
That's my motto in life.
I hate my life
and I want to...
Thank you for listening to another episode, everybody.
We'll see you next time.
Thanks for being here.
Bye!
All right, I'm done.
Don't want to do it.