Uh, do you think you would ever consider coming back to Game Grumps in the future?
Unfortunately, I don't think...
No, I won't be returning to the Game Grumps.
Sorry.
That's a fine word.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast,
a podcast about a bunch of people on the internet who do shit there talking about garbage.
I'm the best guy ever and today we're joined by Tom Oliver.
You'll all pay for this!
I've got 4,700 followers on Twitter and each and every one of them has a sniper rifle
trained on your location.
This isn't about ethics and podcast journalism, this is about harassment of me.
I've got some drama for you, a drama's into your fucking house and breaks all your legs,
every single one of them.
These are all death threats.
I'm sending this all to the cyber police.
The next draw cast is going to be more like a PCP drama cast.
Leave Brittany alone.
Hello, thank you everyone for joining us on this very special episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast,
all about drama.
All about drama.
It's many forms.
The thing we like the most in the entire world, as is evident.
That's correct.
And before we get into it, let's read that old Urban Dictionary definition here.
Drama, definition number two, making a big deal out of something unnecessarily.
That bitch, I'm going to kick her ass.
Dag, Jenny, all she did was look at you.
Why you got to be so drama?
Wow.
There you go.
Thanks Urban Dictionary.
You're beautiful.
You're fantastic.
You said it all.
It's even more and more evident that the Urban Dictionary is actually just the ebonics
dictionary for when you want to go into the...
That is what it means by...
Learn about the Urban Demographic and you're going to go in, quote, the hood.
We're going to start some drama already right off the bat because we only introduced me
and Nate and no one else got introduced.
We just went right into the fucking podcast.
You're trying to throw me under the bus, Nate.
You're trying to throw your own brother under the bus.
I get it.
It's a pup to play.
It's the upper class and the lower class divided by being introduced and that.
I finally joined the bourgeois where I belong.
God, it feels great.
I'm from fucking proletariat revolt, in my opinion.
Just shit talking podcast hosts for half an hour.
Oh, God, what have I done?
It's time to seize the means of production.
We're locking you all out of the Patreon.
We're taking...
Come on, no!
Here's a cheapo triple introduction.
We've got Digi Bro, Munchy Warsh Tiny Hats, and Ben St. Say Words.
It's me, Munchy Warsh Tiny Hats.
I've never been in drama before.
I've never been in pajamas before.
It's me, Digi Bro.
I've been in all the drama before.
He's very popular.
He's very well versed.
I'm Ben St. and everyone likes me.
All right, team.
So drama, it's not even real.
It's not even something that happens in the real world.
It's some fantasy that happens online that isn't true and is fake.
So what do you have to say to that shit right there?
Internet drama sucks, but real life drama is great because...
Yeah, like the fucking Civil War?
Yeah, exactly.
That's exactly what I unironically mean.
Whenever there's internet drama, it's like,
Oh, PewDiePie said nigger, like,
Oh God, fucking cry me a river.
But whatever, one of my friends does something.
Munchy says that to me every second of what you did.
Get over it at this point.
And I beg for more.
When I sleep, I'm like...
But whenever there's something that happens in real life,
I'm like, yes, I can finally talk shit about this person.
No one will get mad at me when I do.
I feel like that's a big excuse.
That is such a great point, Munchy.
That is what...
In some ways, I love drama for exactly that reason, which is that
there are some people that basically...
I hate that they're in my life,
but there's no excuse to get rid of them yet.
You're constantly harboring this like,
Oh, fucking that guy.
Like, you always come kind of like...
You always pull your friends aside.
Like, have you noticed that that dude's fucking like a piece of shit?
And they're like, I don't know what kind of notice.
And you're like, I feel like I've really...
Like, didn't you notice he did that?
And they're like, well, I guess.
And you're like, fuck, man.
And you're just waiting for the day that they fucking step over the line.
And then it's just like, all right, I knew it.
You know, it's like, I knew it.
I knew this was a problem.
Now let's get it all out.
Let's get it all out there.
This is hyper-realistic.
This is too realistic.
This has too many graphics.
I love Monkey Jones.
God damn it!
I'm just popping that bubble right now.
There it is, there it is.
That's not even close to what I was thinking.
That's not who I was thinking about at all.
You guys don't even know how much fucking drama I have.
I got drama with everybody.
Offline, online, I always got drama.
We get drag into your drama all the goddamn time.
Yes.
Sometimes, sometimes.
Well, more lately than in The Bed is True.
Shitstormed by association.
It's fantastic.
But okay, we can talk about some of these stuff,
but really we're here to talk about the meta-concept of drama.
And it's the place in the world.
That's the important part.
Yeah, indeed.
Indeed.
And yeah, it's like, drama, when it doesn't affect me
or the people I know specifically, I don't really
concern myself with.
And whenever I see really epic and funny tweets
with Hollywood actors saying cool things in TV shows
with impact text over them, reacting to some pedophile
coming out as a pedophile, pretty good, doesn't really
matter to me.
I don't really care about that.
But when it's the real people in your real life,
and you get to finally just air out all of your greed,
you get to have the air of grievances,
then I truly enjoy it greatly.
Oh, boy.
Let me tell you a story.
I'm with you.
Let me tell you about the story about a guy.
I've codenamed him D on the internet, usually,
when I bring him up.
But I also say his real name Derek all the time,
so I don't know why I bought it.
All right, this dude was a member of my group of friends
for a very long time, like six years.
And he was a guy who he knew from Japanese class,
and he was just kind of all the intellectuals gathered.
Yeah, exactly.
Most of my friends, I met the Japanese class.
But he would come over to my house,
and he was always kind of a shitty house guest.
He complained about my music.
He'd be very demanding.
He would want you to almost acquiesce
to what he wanted while he was in my house.
But he also regarded my house as a paradise on earth,
because he hated being at home,
and we were so loose in free form that he loved hanging it out.
But he wasn't the best guy to have around, you know?
So he super wants to be everybody's friend,
but everyone's kind of tepid about having him around.
But he's into some good stuff.
He likes some good animes, some good music here and there.
He likes drinking.
So I hung out with him, you know, a pretty decent amount.
But as time went on, he would just do so much annoying shit.
And gradually, it got to a point
where everyone else in my group of friends
would just hang out and shit talk Derek.
Like, that was our main pastime.
Because it had gotten so bad,
but he'd never done any one thing that was like,
let's never talk to him again.
Like, it's hard to cut somebody out of your life entirely, you know?
It's hard to just be like, you know,
you don't have enough redeeming quality.
And like, especially when they want to be your friend,
when like they want to be, like he totally wanted to be around.
And, but like people would constantly have fucking,
even my parents would shit talk him.
Because he pissed them off so many times.
He would say like weird shit on Facebook, piss off my mom.
And we got to a point where my mom was like,
if he does one more thing, I'm kicking him out, right?
And we were all like waiting.
Like everyone's like, oh man, I hope he fucks up one more time.
So my mom could kick him out.
But he wasn't doing anything.
And then finally, on Christmas day.
Oh my god, yeah.
He says something off color.
He fucking had the audacity to be Jewish on Christmas.
That was the last fucking straw.
He, my brother Victor had been talking
to a younger cousin of ours for a while.
He was kind of like mentoring her.
And Derek says, Derek says to Victor
that Victor's other good friend had said something
about Victor like wanting to fuck this cousin, essentially.
How old was this cousin?
How old was this girl?
Young.
She was like 14.
Okay, okay.
So Victor was like probably 18 or 19 at the time.
Sounds ripe.
Sounds nice and ripe.
Okay, go on.
Don't, don't.
So Derek says that another friend has said this about Victor.
Victor, whether Victor doesn't care whether that's true or not,
the fact that Derek has brought that up at all,
like called that into question at all,
has infuriated him massively.
So he goes, tears into him.
He's like, fuck you.
I don't want to see you again for like,
he was like, I don't want to see your face
for the next six months.
You know, and like basically kicked him out.
And everybody was just like, ah,
and it literally ended drama in my circle of friends.
Like it was all gone.
Like all of the drama, everything anybody was complaining about,
all of it was sourced by this one dude.
And as soon as he was gone, it was like,
oh, like we can live again.
And this is why drama can be beautiful,
because it can have results.
You don't want to be the person that the drama centers around.
You know, like, that's not a good look.
Like some, some people, some people seem to like,
kind of like drama and get off on it
and find like pleasure in starting shit.
But like to me, that's like-
Didn't we all just admit to that tacitly?
Well, sure.
And more or less.
It's not that I enjoy starting shit.
It's that I enjoy ending shit.
I'm talking about, I'm talking about Derek.
Well, actually, no, I'm not even talking about anyone.
I'm just talking about, you know,
there are some people who stir up drama
because it's, it scratches some itch that they need.
It like gives meaning to their life in some way.
It gives them, it gives them something to do when they're bored.
I'm a big one.
Oh, go ahead.
But, but, but, you know, it's, it's draining.
It's draining on the people around you.
And if you are a person like that,
like other people are gonna, if they know what's good for them,
they're gonna, they're gonna cut you out
because you're a source of problems.
And like to me, I think that even if
even if shit's going on, it's better.
If you can help it, don't fucking turn it into drama
and make it everyone else's problem.
That is a bad look.
And I do not appreciate it.
Yeah.
The thing that interests me about drama
is drama is like a tool that like, I don't know,
like like the worthless people of society can, excuse me,
fuck, can wield against like people who actually matter.
So like the way that people can like start gossip about like,
like, like, it's kind of like Jesse's situation recently,
you know, like people just talking shit about Jesse forever.
And it just, it's just an example of this idea
about how people can, can talk about stuff like that
and, and just make it into a big deal
whether or not it was in the first place.
And I, it's, it's this kind of lever of power
that people have.
Better example, the PewDiePie Nazi thing,
where it was just, it's just a bunch of old media fuckboys
trying to fuck over the famous guy.
Exactly.
They're like, oh, that guy's got 14 billion subs.
Let's take him fucking down a peg.
More than the population of the earth.
Yeah.
It's interesting you bring that up.
There's like this really interesting video series
that this guy did about that whole controversy
and saying how like all, like the two,
I think it was like NBC and the Wall Street Journal
or something were the two things that initially reported on this.
And they're both owned by Rupert Murdoch.
So they were, he was saying like, doing this deep dive,
like actually had nothing to do with PewDiePie.
It was all an elaborate plan by old media
to make YouTube look like shit.
So all the advertisers would pull out
to make them relevant again.
Hey.
It was like, it was like an hour long expose.
It was super fucking interesting.
And it worked.
Yeah, it worked fantastically.
So like, oh, Ben, I have a question for you.
And this isn't an accusation.
It's just that with something legitimately,
I'm legitimately interested in what you just said.
How, how do you, and I'm not like,
how would you explain away the fact
that you take that stance on drama
and then the whole Rowdy fuckers cop killers?
Like, okay, we need to bring in fans
aboard to consult on this issue.
Yeah, yeah, let me, let me just go summon him.
I'm just going to summon him.
Strawberry!
I'm sweeping.
Oh, I'm, oh, I'm, but I'm here now.
Let me, let me, let me just pick up,
let me just pick up my like my magic,
my magic fairy wand and do a little like,
like magical girl transformation into fans porn.
Like I always do.
It's the little toilet paper roll.
After you've taken a shit,
your toilet paper roll like Dover is the magic.
It's like a scepter.
It's like a scepter with like a glowing like jewel on the,
anyway.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm fine.
There's like a box next to my desk.
They just have to like,
like poke the inside pink lizard with a cane
and like fucking like,
drum his head and like beat the shit out of them
to wake him up.
It's like, it's like those old,
it's like those old Power Rangers transform.
Like in the first season of Transformers,
when they like wake up the dinosaurs
and they lumber out of their ancient slumber.
I'd assume, I'd assume the transformation
for bed would work.
He'd run into a public restroom,
go into a stall,
get a roll of toilet paper,
stick it on his head,
and that would start the transformation.
Hold on.
Yeah.
And then it just,
what?
For canonical clarity's sake,
are you implying that Phantom Horn only exists
when you are performing Phantom Horn,
like when you have become him?
Canonically, no,
canonically he lives in Ponyville.
Okay.
This, this, this, this, this flight of fancy is merely that.
All my other flights of fancy are canon.
See, your pony's thought a retarded
metapony thing like mine was.
It's a solid stuff.
That is what makes Peg and Fett
to the greatest OCS of all time.
Are only meta in that they canonically
live in Ponyville,
but also post to YouTube.
And review my little pony's reviews.
Yeah, yeah, they watch the show in world.
And like, yeah.
Strawberry milk lives in my house
and he doesn't pay rent,
even though he's Dragon Royalty
and he's just crashed out of my house
and they can rap day in, day out.
He won't fucking pay rent,
no matter how much they want to.
Yeah, sorry.
This is a terrible fucking off time.
Okay, well, all right,
the thing about that,
the thing about the Rowdy,
Munchy, I don't know if you agree with this,
but I'm just gonna speak for myself for a minute.
Of course.
I don't feel like the Rowdy Fuckers Cop Killers
was stirring up real drama.
I don't.
Because let's just be fucking frank.
Nobody really gives a shit what FNGR
or Miss Anthropony or anyone else on that thing.
Yeah, give us a primer.
Give us a primer.
I don't think everybody who listens to this
is gonna know what the fuck
the Rowdy Fuckers Cop Killers is.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, god.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
What?
Like, basically,
Rowdy Fuckers Cop Killers is like a,
I guess, a let's play show
that me and Ben have,
but it's so much more than that
in every single possible way.
It's evolved.
And when we start playing Frog Fractions,
the infamous Homestuck spinoff game,
we eventually just get so bored
and we are using like a screen sharing software.
So I just start tabbing over outside of the Flash game
and just start googling old pony reviewers
and we kind of spiral into just shit talking
everyone we know from that community
for like three hours.
I just started shit talking everyone
that I remembered from the old days
and like looking at OCs
and being like, oh, god, I hate this
and like talking about what was wrong
with the whole thing.
And it incurred,
it incurred some backlash from a couple of dudes.
I believe, I believe,
did you refer to as the most like,
something along the lines of like,
the most like haphazardly,
feminist thing he's ever seen?
I have a lot of venom.
I have a lot of venom on the subject.
It was a lot of piss and vinegar.
It was the most,
I don't remember the word I used,
but it's, it's a word that means
like you just didn't think about it.
Like that this was going to come out
and be public
and people were going to watch it.
Like.
No, but I know, I know, I know, I liked it.
We knew.
And that's, that's incredible to me.
The way I felt,
it was like, I'd been,
I'd been sitting on these feelings for so like,
I didn't want to come out with this
when like leaving the pony thing was fresh.
I didn't want to be the kind of guy
who like came out and shit on all like the people
I'd previously been associating with.
But now that this is like years in the past,
who gives a shit?
And I'm like, let me just talk.
I'd like to, I'd like to point out
that I am literally wearing my brony shirt
right now.
Very fucking moment.
All right.
But anyway, after that initial shit talking,
which we basically went on like the wiki
for all these people
and just went on each of their pages
and shit talk them for maybe like 30 minutes each
or you know, less beyond how relevant they are.
And we kind of dug into a couple of people
for like hours.
Dr. Will.
Which was great.
Yeah.
Which was very fun.
It was all, it was all good and fun.
And like, you know, it was pretty great.
Anyway, we get attacked by fucking, you know, assassins,
a top grade brony assassins named Miss Anthropony
for no good reason.
Coming at us with fucking, you know,
venom and fucking poison,
trying to, you know, ruin our day
and ran on our parade.
Before you go further,
we should probably point out
that for no good reason is a name,
even though Miss Anthropony basically did just
try and come at you for no good reason.
Yeah.
Right.
For no good reason is a person, sort of.
Yeah.
Nominally.
Strangely.
He's a changed,
maybe he was a human creature.
And then after that, we recorded,
we basically, what we did is,
we made a response video
to Miss Anthropony and FNGR's video.
And after that, which was also like five hours long,
then we made like a seven hour long video
where we invite FNGR on to watch,
for us to watch our response to his video,
of his video responding to us.
So basically it's a clusterfuck
and all you need to know is that
Bronies hate us now,
even though we're the saviors they deserve
and we're telling them everything we need to.
So, well the reason why I can feel this way
about drama and not see any conflict
with what we did on Rowdyfuckers' cop killers
is that this is not a real fight, you know?
Like this is not, like nobody,
at least nobody who's relevant to us
is, like nobody who's on board with the PCP
in any way is going to side with them.
Like this is, this is, this is mean,
like their opinions do not mean anything.
And it's just funny.
Miss Anthropony, in the comments of this video,
I think would argue otherwise.
Well, they know he will do.
I don't even have any particular ill will
towards Miss Anthropony,
even though I think that his arguments were pretty dumb.
But like, it's not a real fight,
like it's just funny and it's just like
a chance to like have like a good time
just shitting on some people, you know,
that I feel like deserve.
Even if Miss Anthropony, whatever,
like that seems to resolve.
And FNGR certainly seemed to have an attitude
of not sincere like investment in this like fight.
He seemed to, you know, so I don't know.
Well, I don't know what's that scoundrel.
I knew I was making people mad,
but I didn't, I feel, I felt like we were pretty safe
that this was not going to result
in any like meaningful schism
among like the people that are important to us.
I, and that's, that brings me to one of the things,
the things about drama.
Every time I get into drama, people are like,
why would you do that
when you're going to make some people so mad?
And it's because there's always going to be
just as many people who are like really glad somebody said it.
You know, like, if there's a problem,
then probably a lot of people have that problem, you know.
And when I call like,
when I did the shit talking anime YouTubers video,
which is like a very infamous drama sparking video I made,
30 minutes of me shit talking a bunch of anime YouTubers,
like it got, first of all,
it brought up conversation with all those guys.
I ended up talking to all those YouTubers, you know,
like coming to greater understandings.
Lots of people were like, yeah, I echo these sentiments
and you know, every, literally everyone I mentioned in the video
gained shitloads of subscribers and patrons.
Like it was because it just drew attention to people
and drew attention to things, you know, like anybody I praised,
people were like, oh, I got to see why he praised that guy.
Anybody insulted, they're like,
let me see if I agree with these insults, you know.
So like in the end,
and this is why drama is such a hot commodity on YouTube now,
which I, to clarify,
none of my drama videos have been for popularity's sake.
If I wanted that, I would go way harder on it.
But like, there's a good reason it works for that.
And it's because people want to be,
it's, it warps you into the conversation.
Like more and more people keep involving themselves in the drama
to bring attention to themselves.
And in ergo, the drama grows and becomes a bigger and bigger deal.
And therefore, more and more people want to pile on it.
And so it's just, it's just really beneficial for everybody involved.
But you know, it's, it's vapid content.
Yeah. Exactly. Exactly.
The thing here with Rafferty's Cop Killers
is that first of all, the original video is not a directed attack
at any one person,
but is instead us degrading a certain mindset and community as a whole.
Of course, we pick out certain people,
but those are only symptoms of the larger problem
that we have both faced individually within our lives.
So it's not directed, and it's not exactly the most, you know,
you know, like trained, you know,
calculated video as he stayed many times.
It's just, you know, us riffing.
And I think that kind of plays into the atmosphere.
Well, you know, you gotta play these things case by case.
It's not like, you know, not everything can be judged by the exact same merits.
And I think Rafferty's Cop Killers can easily,
well, you know, it could obviously be taken as wrong as it was by the people who we shit on.
A lot of people I don't think would even consider it a drama video per se.
It is just us talking as we always do.
I mean, you know, PZP shits on a lot of people all the time, 100% in fact.
So I don't think it's that far out, you know, out of left.
I just, like, the thing is, like, anyone who's on the side of the Brown Alice's community,
I think they're dumb.
And I don't want, I don't care if they're mad at me.
There shouldn't even, there shouldn't need to be a divide.
Like, Brody Analysis Community versus, like, Ben and Munchy.
Because, like, you specifically attack individuals,
which is, like, kind of the whole point of it.
Like, the individual people are shit.
To have that kind of group mentality, like, oh, we need to, like, look out for our own?
Yeah.
No, you don't.
Lightning Bliss is an idiot.
And she makes terrible shit.
The weird group mentality is what we, like, is what, like,
I go, like, almost, or one of the hardest things that I hit on.
Yeah, yeah.
That's not, as being not a fan of.
And, yeah, the final, but the final chapter closed, we laid all our enemies to waste
in the final episode of the Frog Fraction Saga.
Rowdy fuckers, cop killers, nine, Frog Fractions, episode two,
Frog Fractions two, part three, Frog Finale.
RFCK9FFE2FF2P3FF.
Wait, is that out?
Is that the latest one?
That's the latest one.
I just wanted to make the title as long and as obnoxious an abbreviation.
We completely melted and dissolved their avatars.
And now we have, we have fucking add them to our stew,
and we have consumed their entire being.
We have consumed our entire consciousness.
And now we have gained complete and total control over both their Kundalini
and their Merkaba.
And now we can drive them as we see fit.
We took, we took their polygons and added them to our character models.
And now we're like, now we're HD.
Well, okay.
I want to talk about, like, why I think we can get away with,
with some of this stuff that we do, because like,
I think the PCP being such a strong foundation for all of us,
kind of allows us to like burn other bridges.
Like, there's a lot of people, I know content creators who will never say a mean thing
about another content creator, because they're just terrified of burning any bridge.
They're like, I want to be able to work with all these guys in the future.
And, and like, you know, I'll, there'll be people who I know everyone has a problem with
and I bring them up around people and they go, oh, yeah, you know,
he's a little, uh, you know, he's, he's him.
And I'm like, yeah, like, yeah, you're not going to say anything about it.
You know, like, no, I want to be able to work with them in the future.
I think with us, like, we, we know we've got these guys out though.
It's not a cop out.
It totally is to say that you want to work.
If you don't like them, of course, you don't want to work them.
You don't want to start any shit.
You don't want to be the guy that has the first stone.
Yeah.
And for me, it's like, I already know I've got the PCP, you know,
at the very least, I've got this group of friends
and, and business associates that I don't have any problems with
who I can work with, you know.
And, and so everybody else is like, uh, like, look,
I don't need to have a thousand friends.
I don't need to have a thousand connections.
You know, I'm really, if insulting this guy means like
his entire fan base hates me from now on, cool.
I'll be over here with this other fan base who also hates that guy.
You know, I think, I think an important distinction here to be made
is that like in the, like in the, uh, you know, fucking definition,
drama is about like nothing.
Like, like the kind of drama that everyone, you know, hates
and, you know, dislikes makes fun of,
is kind of drama that is about nothing.
When you have like legitimate problems with people,
obviously it can still be considered drama,
but it's more pointed and, you know, constructive and important
and actually, you know, worth having around as a species,
as opposed to just someone disliking someone for,
you know, miscellaneous reasons
and just bringing up like, like just kind of waiting for them to do,
you know, like the PewDiePie thing.
He didn't do anything wrong.
You people just wanted to, you know, take him down a peg
or I guess in the conspiracy theory just destroy what you do.
You could argue that what PewDiePie said is not cool for whatever reason,
but like, I know that's not why they went so hard about it.
Exactly, exactly.
So I'm trying to say.
What about, what about, would you call,
would you call what like the things happening right now
with guys like like Harvey Weinstein or Kevin Spacey that's like,
you know, like molestation allegations and whatnot, sexual harassment.
Is that drama or is that like something else?
That's like a legal issue.
You know, I think it's, it's like a lawsuit, which is not.
Yeah, but I think it's both because I think that what those guys have done,
yeah, that's obviously a legal issue and like it deserves to be brought,
like brought to light probably, but the motivations for bringing it to light
are by the way, by the way.
Here's the problem with that whole thing.
There's, there's two sides to it.
There's the legal issues, which is like, hey, you diddle the dude,
that's bad, probably shouldn't do that.
That's, that's not good.
We can all agree on that.
There's, there's also the people like who hop on the bandwagon like,
yeah, it happened to me too, by somebody, somewhere, sometime,
please pay attention to me.
I want to keep this fire burning.
And it's like, you're not sure if you cared about the actual legal issues,
you would, you would actually constructively solve the problem,
but you don't, you just want to keep the fire burning.
Cause again, like they're very, they started as an observer.
They feel empathetic towards the cause, but they don't,
again, they don't want to cast that stone.
So they're going to, they're going to take that half step of like,
I'm going to make this a bigger problem,
but I'm not going to actually incriminate myself in any way
or actively get involved.
That's like, that's like people, people taking like,
like monkey talked about, like taking the Elliot Rogers thing
and like, like taking, taking something else that happened
and using it as like a platform for their, for their agenda.
Right. Yeah. Good point.
That's what a lot of people are doing with this whole sexual
drama thing right now.
And that's when you, when you do that.
Yeah. When you do it that way, that's drama.
By the way, I'd like to come out real quick
and castigate the guy who came forward with the allegations
against Kevin Spacey.
Why the fuck didn't you wait till season six
of house of cards was done?
You piece of shit.
You're literally fucking me right now.
You're fucking me right now.
This is rape.
This is fucking rape. Congratulations.
You are the monster that you claim to fight against.
When I heard those, the allegations I heard
were that he like flirted with him.
Like, did he even actually do anything to him?
I have no idea.
I have no idea what the situation is.
If you can even look at somebody the wrong way,
it's rape now.
Okay. Okay.
Let me spell it out.
There's, let's keep this light, guys.
The first allegation against Kevin Spacey was just that
like he basically tried to have sex with a 14-year-old,
not like super aggressively, but somewhat,
which is like fucked up and you know, pretty weird.
Sure.
But Kevin was such a fucking beta.
He couldn't even get with a 14-year-old.
He easily overpowered, but he fucking said it.
And this was over 30 years ago.
So like that one's a little bit shaky.
Who knows?
Okay, but like the new ones are like people working on the set with him
on House of Cards, like since the beginning of the show,
are saying like, oh, he's like groped guys
and made inappropriate comments,
which all sound very nebulous.
And I don't like, what's your actual core testimony for this?
I mean, as Stereo's Kokano said,
that he's been hearing rumors about this for like 15 years or something.
So I'm willing to believe.
Okay.
As someone tweeted,
someone tweeted that like family guy made a joke
about Kevin Spacey having like sex slaves in his basement,
which like I feel like maybe might have like colored the waters for something.
Like maybe some people heard that and internalized it.
Or maybe that was based on true.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know.
Okay.
On one of the episodes that we had Stereo's on,
on the insufferable social media argument,
he was talking about,
or maybe this was on the dick show.
I don't remember.
All my fucking Asterios is bleeding into each other.
But he was talking about how in the industry.
The Asterios diaspora.
When something like this happens, there's,
no, it was on the dick show.
He was talking about the heart, the Weinstein thing,
and how like everyone had known this.
Like this was just something that everybody knew in Hollywood.
And he was like, every time one of these things comes out,
that is always the case.
Like everybody knows there just nobody's going to say anything
until that person's like number is up.
You know, it's just waiting for the pin to drop.
When someone decides that you're next,
that's when they come for you.
You know, and there's no real,
I mean, to me, it's like, it's never surprising
because it's like you've got to be,
you kind of have to be mentally damaged
in some way to work in entertainment.
You know, like why the fuck else would you be here?
None of us is sane, I don't think.
Probably any of us qualifies as sane.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
I do my best.
I'm cultured.
I'm a philosopher.
Well, okay, let me.
So, okay, this is all interesting stuff,
but let me just, so all of you guys,
to some degree or another,
have involved yourself with some drama-ish situation.
Including Tom.
Hashtag leaving the fandom.
Hashtag burning breakfast, you know.
See, it's interesting to say that
because I was going to bring up-
This is a really pony-charged episode today,
I didn't expect that.
We all had a lot of pony trauma.
Well, it's true, it's true.
It's because that was my one exception,
but for the most part, I think I probably,
in general, I'm the least drama person here,
question mark, maybe.
I have something to say relevant to that.
Oh, well, I didn't mean to interrupt,
but if I have the floor, I just want to say that-
Well, it's too late now, isn't it, Ben?
The reason why I felt comfortable making that
Dungeons & Dragons Attack video, responding to it,
and the reason why I jumped on that so quickly,
is because I knew that I could make a counter-argument
to yours, and make it into a thing,
and joke that, like, ah, fuck Tom,
and I knew that it wouldn't escalate into a real-
Yeah, that was hilarious, I loved that.
I figured that you would appreciate it,
and I thought it was fun, and I was, you know,
glad I saw an opportunity to be like,
yeah, let's make a little thing out of this.
Everybody got the joke.
That's like anti-drama, almost.
I mean, it's faux drama, I guess,
and yeah, I think everybody appreciated it,
but the reason-
I, yeah.
Sorry, yeah, finish your point if you're-
I was just gonna say it was great,
and we should, I hope more of that.
We should do more of that here on the PCP.
I already do more of that.
Well, that's something I was gonna bring up, is that-
But only when there's an issue that I actually-
Oh, wait, we should make a Patreon goal
for the procrastinators.
We will start PCP inter-PCP drama with each other.
We will create an issue for you to love
and latch onto a side, what were you saying, Tom?
We'll just manufacture it.
Well, I was gonna say, I was saying,
I tend to try and avoid drama for the most part,
and when people latch onto stuff,
I tend to not jump into it,
because even now, I still, I don't know,
I just kind of, even if there's something I want to say,
I don't, and I think that's a problem.
I think that makes my internet personality too boring.
I think I need to start shitting on people.
I think that would do good things for my career.
I feel like-
I have the same fear that I'm not contentious enough.
I just feel like I'm not that interesting.
I feel like because I don't jump into conflicts head-on,
that it's actually actively damaging my prospects going forward.
Better, better to, what's the saying?
Better to be hated than not to be discussed at all,
or something like that, you know?
All right, it feels relevant online.
I used to say and think a lot,
that like what I would really enjoy
is if the PCP did get into some drama,
not like inter-PCP drama,
but like if maybe some other podcast,
or other show, or other group of creators.
We need to pick a fight with somebody.
Yeah, with maybe like a similar clout to our own,
like if maybe there's like some genuine,
and some genuine-
Wait, what did you say?
Art retrieval.
Yeah, I'll pop up the entire thing
so they have no real threat against us,
but we can still attack them mercilessly.
I don't know.
It's controlled drama.
I wouldn't mind if we had like some genuine,
non-manufactured beef with some other group of people
that maybe have like similar,
or like slightly greater clout to us.
The pony book cast.
And it would be like a fair fight,
and like we would trade blows,
and people would take sides,
and like people like that kind of thing,
and it could be fun.
Like that's the kind of thing,
like remember back in the pony days,
sorry to bring it back to pony,
but remember back in the pony days
when we all saw it as like we're all in Bakuman,
and we're all the fucking,
we're all like competing with each other, right?
It's like a hot-blooded rivalry.
I don't know, I missed that a little bit.
That sense of needing to best of it.
It drives creation and enthusiasm.
That's true, but the smart business decision for us to be
would be to manufacture drama with a much larger podcast,
like the fucking sleepy cast.
That's true.
We could somehow make drama happen with them,
like that would be the best way
to like suddenly boost our relevancy
if we could do that or something.
Dick Vaster said that he used to constantly like shit-talk
Mark Maron on Biggest Problem and the Dick Show,
like trying to make that happen.
For no reason, just bringing up Mark Maron and being like,
yeah fuck that guy, like just hoping that it wouldn't...
Who is that guy again?
Mark Maron's like the biggest podcaster in the world.
He's the one who interviewed Obama that time.
Well then why haven't I heard of him?
If he's so great.
He had a fucking show on Netflix, Maron.
I never heard of Netflix.
When is the PCP Netflix show going to come out?
Thanks for spoiling Biggest Problem.
And when is there going to be male on male rope
on that one, huh, Kevin?
It's not much of a spoiler,
because they never managed to get Mark Maron to fight.
God damn it.
You spoiled that part for me too.
Here guys, okay.
The reason I brought up this drama, Tom's drama,
I'm just interested to hear everyone's individual story,
but the reason I bring it up is because
I want to point out how I am literally perfect.
I am an evolved being.
I am superior to all of you,
because I have never, ever been involved in drama.
You're starting some drama right now.
Well Nate, I think the thing about with you not having drama,
you very much have tried to be like a,
in spite of the fact that you're in the PCP,
your YouTube presence has always been very independent.
And like you do not associate as part of a community.
You do not really like,
when other people ask you about YouTubers,
it's always either like I watch them or I don't.
It's never like here's what I think they do
to my content or like what they do to the atmosphere of YouTube.
Like you don't really care about that kind of shit.
You're just like, I'm over here in my own world doing my videos,
you know, which is a healthy way to even how
most YouTubers probably are.
Nate, Nate can get away with that
because he has such a natural charisma by default,
where I don't.
So I need something to make me interesting
because right now I'm just a boring piece of shit.
I need to start shit with somebody.
I also think, Nate, that you would have more drama
if it weren't for the fact that you tend to play things off
in a very playful, like you shit talk people,
it just never starts anything.
Like you will blatantly like just shit on somebody,
but because you do it with such a like,
like a smiley, laughy gravitas to it,
like nobody really cares.
Like nobody takes it personally.
They're just like, oh yeah, well whatever.
You know, like when I do it, it's like,
I get drunk and like tear someone's whole life apart.
And like, yeah, yeah.
It's a different atmosphere behind those sorts of things, you know.
You can tell there's anger when I start drama.
Yeah, yeah, it's true.
I have, I don't, I try not to shit talk people.
And I think it's because that if I did,
it would come off as very like serious and grave.
And like, I don't know.
I can't, I can't.
I don't shit talk anyone, says Ben St.
with 15 hours of rowdy fuckers cop killers.
Well, they don't care.
Well, Tom, Tom, what the fuck is with you
and all the boring thing?
I'm like, oh, Ben is so mean.
Ben, Ben did all of this.
No, I was there too.
I'm a mean, I'm a bully too.
Hashtag, what about Munchy?
I'm only responding because Ben was talking.
Munchy, you are just as much of a dick.
Thank you, Munchy.
Finally.
Munchy in many ways has the same thing as Nate,
where Munchy's a big memer.
So like, people aren't,
like both of you guys are constantly spouting memes.
So like, when you guys shit on somebody,
it's like seen as more of a meme, you know.
If Ben, who's, Ben is more of like a,
I don't know, Ben is a very like funny, lighthearted guy,
but he's got a little bit more of like a heady persona,
where like, if he insults somebody, it's like,
well fuck, if Ben thinks it, it must be serious, you know.
Oh, I think Ben just has like that,
he kind of comes off as a judgmental person
in general sometimes.
Oh, Ben is a very judgmental person.
Jesus.
So when he does it, you know, it's like,
I know who this Ben St. character is.
This isn't for chuckles, this is for real.
You know what it is, I can be really judgmental sometimes,
and I don't really like that about myself.
So I think that I like avoid, not with the pony stuff,
but with most things, I try to avoid,
I try to avoid coming out and like making statements
like against people because I know that like,
I don't want to let that out into the public sphere
because I don't like it, you know.
I also like to,
I know that no one's going to appreciate it.
Wait, hold on, Ben, correct me if I'm wrong here,
but I feel like you and I and Nate are different in this way.
I think Nate, when he doesn't like somebody,
doesn't think about him.
Like, when somebody brings up a name that like,
Nate's like, oh, that guy sucks, you know,
like it's because Nate like watched one of his videos,
thought he sucked in that moment and then forgot,
and then he hasn't stewed on it.
With you and me, Ben, we stew on the people we don't like.
Yeah, I definitely do that to an extremely large extent.
We sit around, I know we have sat around and like,
like we all sit around and just shit on people all day.
Like if there's someone we're both stewing on,
you know, it becomes a little bit of a circus.
You know, I try, I try to like keep that down
and not stew, but like when it comes up,
I can't help myself.
Sam, you know, I'm naturally inclined to stew
and to be like, yeah, fucking,
here's what I think about this shit and it makes me mad.
This does kind of, I mean, it sort of is explained by
our sort of different approaches to life, I guess,
because I really am, and here comes your dose
of hashtag weird utilitarianism.
All right, well, I expected that to be your whole place
in this one.
That's where I've been trying to steer
this lumbering massive ship this whole time,
and we're moving in that direction now.
It's like, I'm always, like,
I'm totally pragmatic about this.
Like what good is done by me dwelling on people I don't care?
Like just yesterday, I was telling you guys
about a YouTuber, I have decided now
I do not care about anymore,
and I'm not going to think about them anymore,
and it's been great, and I have not.
They broke the bridge and I'm done with them.
Yeah, like I'm not gonna say, I don't hate the person at all,
but I appreciate that.
I appreciate that.
A while, I don't know.
And like, I've tried to do that.
Here, I'll type it.
I'll type it.
I've tried to do that with like, I don't know,
with like, I don't know, people with political opinions
or social opinions, like the whole Sargon
and everyone like him that makes me so fucking mad
to think about, like I just decided,
like okay, all I want to do is destroy these people
and make them not exist, but I can't.
So the best thing to do, all I can do,
all I can do is not watch their content
and not think about them.
That's the only thing at my disposal.
So yes, when possible, that is my weapon of choice.
I wish I had the mindset that you have, Nate,
because for me, people can become like a meme in my mind.
Oh, I'm fully on your side.
Munchy me and you, I know you're like this,
because we need to do this thing where the more we bitch
about somebody or the more we think about them,
the funnier it gets.
Oh my god, exactly, exactly.
It's kind of like with Sword Art Online,
how like that show, just watching it's a bad show,
but the more me and Victor made fun of it
and talked about it, the funnier it got to me.
And so like, it got to a point where now I've got like,
fucking posters and toys of Sword Art Online
because I just want to make fun of it.
And like, it brings me joy to see it.
And like, I get that way.
And I don't want to start any drama by saying this,
but it's exactly what Mother's Basement is for me in my life.
It's someone who I've made fun of and talked shit about so much
and it keeps getting funnier.
And especially because like, people, for some reason,
this is not provocated by me, I don't know how this happened,
other than that, we're sort of around the same sub count,
the same like kind of around popularity as YouTubers.
But when people decide they don't like him, they tell me.
Like people, I like very frequently get messages
about people being like, oh, I'm real sick of Mother's Basement.
I'm glad you're still doing this kind of videos you're doing.
Like, it happens all the time.
Do you want to accept this like frightening?
And I want to be like, like, you know,
I got to talk to these people and be like, yeah, I see that.
Like, I see why, you know?
And so like, somehow when I created my discord,
like the first thing that happened was like,
it became a huge meme to shit on Jeff.
And I was like, wait, hold on.
This is starting to get out of hand.
Like, let's snip this.
And then Troll started coming in who like recognized this
and tried to start a war between our discords,
which thankfully didn't work because they were fucking retarded.
But like, you know, and I still,
I'll still work with Jeff on some things.
You know, I don't hate the guy,
but like it became so funny to make fun of him
that now he has a big meme.
When you start drama with someone and like,
and you focus on them so much, like, like,
initially there's no, there's no like funny parts there,
at least most of the time.
It's just like, man, I fucking hate this guy.
But the more you dwell on him and like,
talk to other people with it, especially,
you sort of get this like,
character in your brain of like,
like you pick out all the words parts of it
and then you just create this horrible monstrosity
of all the worst possible aspects of that person.
And just watch them dance around in your brain.
I won't say who, I won't say who in this call,
I did that with, with Jeff,
that turned him into a meme in my mind.
But what if he was partially responsible for that?
That, that, that isn't,
Jeff is an example of where I have taken
the opposite of approach,
because thinking about Jeff feels,
feels bad to me.
Thinking about, thinking about someone like Jeff,
thinking about someone like Jeff,
turning out, turning out content
that is like designed for SEO optimization and stuff,
like turning it out mechanically and like,
get like, wheeling and dealing and like,
getting industry connections due to this fucking,
this whatever it is and people,
but more so than that,
more so than him doing it,
the thought of people buying into it,
this goes the same for like someone like Dr. Wolfe
on like a larger scale,
the idea of someone doing that and people buying into it
upsets me and makes me mad.
And so like, while it is kind of funny sometimes,
ultimately the laughter dies and I just sit there stupid.
In my impotent, impotent rage and the best thing to do
is just stop thinking about it.
As funny as the meme, as funny as it is
to make fun of Jeff,
I do eventually enter that state where I'm like,
well, I can, I can laugh at this all I want,
but that motherfucker's laugh into the bank.
You know, that guy's making way more money
than me at the end of the day.
And no matter how many of his fans leave him
to come bitch to me about him,
he'll always have more fans coming in.
It's just about what kind of,
what do you want your life to be like?
You know, whatever.
Jeff can do whatever he wants.
I guess I should focus more on the drama itself.
Yeah, I don't know.
Tom, you were saying something.
I just take everything to like the worst degree possible
with this because I have the same issue where I don't,
the only people that bother me are people
who are shittier than me and make more money
or have more respect because fuck that.
Or people that are a different race.
That's how I feel.
That's a big issue for me too.
That's how I feel about every single one of you.
There's like the Nate method where there's like one stage
or just like fuck it.
I don't care anymore.
And by the way, I want to point out that that stage,
this is not like a lighthearted thing.
This is a cold calculated.
This is the optimal way to destroy these people.
I would expect nothing less than you, Nate.
Of course it was.
Yes, good.
I come off lighthearted, but I want to destroy people.
I have that seething desire.
Okay, go on.
Then there's the Ben.
Just kidding, I'm fun.
Hey guys, send me messages.
There's the Ben and Digi approach
where you try not to care, but you can't.
And then it gets funny and then it becomes bad.
For me, it's like I try not to care.
Then I get mad.
And then I'm just like, well, the problem is me.
I should be doing better.
And then I just get mad at myself.
And that's what I do.
Oh, right, all right.
That's tough.
I have the skills.
There's no reason why this shouldn't be working.
And then I just hate myself.
And that's the worst.
I have an element to that with the Jeff thing,
where sometimes I'm like,
but why am I not doing what he's doing?
Like, that man is going to surpass me.
And for most people, they won't be able to tell the difference.
Like, I can sit here and say like, oh, I make real content.
He doesn't, not so much so that it's a huge difference.
That only matters to you, right?
Yeah, me and my fans, yeah.
But like, to the average Joe.
To the public at large, the numbers.
It's like that fucking goodwill hunting thing
about how Will is like the super genius,
but he's so good at math and shit.
The only people who even recognize he's that good
are like fellow genius math people who just aren't white.
And I'm not trying to suck your dick here.
You're fucking pathetic.
You're a piece of shit.
I hate you.
But I am the one I'm talking about in this situation.
He smiles.
Terry, did you laugh a lot?
That's the genius, the, what's it called?
Like the genius paradox or some shit like that?
Basically, you can understand people who are like either
like 30 points below or 30 points above you in IQ.
And anything beyond that, like if it's less than,
or if it's more than 30 points less,
then they just seem like a fucking retard.
And if it's more than 30 points more,
they seem like a fucking god
and you can't understand what's coming out of their mouth.
Like that episode of a regular show.
Right from his cop killers.
It's just too big.
We're 7,000 IQ points above the pronounces community
and they call me a neighboring retard.
They say that like the best play,
if you want to be like a businessman,
the best place to be is in like the 100 to 110 range of IQ.
Because you can, you can, you can sell stuff to idiots.
You can sell stuff to normies.
You can sell stuff to people who are kind of smart.
And you don't got to worry about the extremes.
I think everybody in the PCP sits around
anywhere from like 125 to 145, you know?
Like we're all in this upper level.
And like, so when we get down,
when we get down to the people who are like IQ 80,
like Ms. Anthropony.
Damn.
It's like you just, you can't, you can't.
Start drama again right here.
Do you, do you think Ms. Anthropony has an IQ above 100?
Ms. Anthropony, I have no problem with you.
You tried your best out there buddy.
I don't know enough about IQ to make statements like that.
Oh, it doesn't make you a better or worse person to be stupid.
It just makes it so people like me
can't positively fathom how you think.
I'm glad, I'm glad according to Digi,
we all have excuses now for why we love Morgan Morty so much.
I won't make any sweeping statements about the man,
but his arguments in the videos directed at me
did not give the impression of overwhelming intelligence.
I've seen Digi's content since back in the pony days,
when he made videos, by the way,
shitting on all of us, and yet is somehow like the biggest fan.
I'd like to point out for the record that,
as far as I know, mine is the only one that's still up,
even though it was-
Oh, is that true?
Oh, really?
Wait, you won.
His attack video by Ms. Anthropony?
Yeah, he deleted all the other ones,
but he made mine and then put the apology
at the end of mine and kept it up.
What?
Yeah.
Great, great.
Which I always found was kind of funny.
That is very amusing.
So that's the most I'm going to get into that drama is that.
That was kind of weird.
No offense to you Ms. Anthropony, you might be fine,
but I'm just saying, you might not be the most intelligent person.
And that's fine.
The statement that did you, bro, do not reflect the-
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think there's some intent,
offense going to come through there.
Is Ms. Anthropony a patron?
Should I be?
Hey, we're just breaking ball.
Oh, he should be getting it out of this.
I don't know.
We're just breaking ball.
No, no, no editing, no filter, nothing.
Yeah, this is all good.
This is all going on.
In fact, it's going to be echoed so they hear it twice.
Now I feel bad because Ms. Anthropony
like comments on this channel and like really likes the show.
Yeah, he does.
Look, we're just joking around here.
Right guys, right?
He's the one who shits on you all the time.
Like, he did, he did.
He did, but it didn't make me feel bad
because it just bounced off
because it didn't mean anything to me.
Because it seemed to make Jackie pretty mad.
She was pretty fucking pissed.
She did, she got pretty mad.
I'm not going to specify, I'm going to keep it vague here,
but why was that Benz just a week ago?
It was the most euphoric time
because every time we got on the car
we just hot boxed insults about like the various people
within our lives.
And it was just like a drama hot box
where we were just high on vapes and anger.
And we just fucking, we just rode to Valhalla.
It sounds like a normal day in the St. household.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, pretty much.
It was very cathartic though.
Did they get you to vape?
Did they convince you to vape?
No, no.
Please say no.
Please don't let that disgusting substance
touch your lips, Mudgey.
Thank you, thank you.
My horse, my horse, my voice got so hoarse
and like my voice wouldn't work
because I just inhaled so much secondhand vape
that my voice just got so fucking high
I couldn't speak anymore.
It was really, it was, it was really awful.
Like, like, like after like an entire day
I just was like, hey, I can't, Ben,
I need some pizza, please.
I just couldn't fucking, I just couldn't speak anymore.
I actually believe that's possible in a car
with Ben and Jackie because they vape way harder
than normal people vape.
Yeah.
Like when Jackie, when Jackie pulls a vape,
there's a fucking clown after they have fucking vape.
Yeah, there's a haze, there's a haze in the house.
I was surrounded by vape, I was surrounded by fog
the entire time I was at Ben's house.
The fucking neighborhood children
gather outside the St. House windows
to inhale that sweet cloud coming out of the practical wall.
Jackie hits the vape like, like asthmatics hit a,
like a truck hitting a brick fucking wall.
What does the vape, what does the fucking thing
call that goddamn asthmatics he uses?
I don't even know who that is, Doug.
An inhaler.
Jackie hits that vape, like my dad hit my mom when I came out.
Hey.
My deepest, my deepest apologies for your
oncoming emphysema.
Indeed.
I'll never forgive you.
Okay guys, let's, let's center ourselves here.
Yeah, center our chakras.
Let's, let's talk about how drama has objectively
zero worth and is a waste of all your time
to even engage it in, even a little bit.
I completely disagree, but I'm, this is what I can't hear
to argue with.
That's what I want to talk about.
Because the, the, the, the rowdy fucker stuff was fun
and you know, people liked it.
It was a great time.
It was completely fun to record and it was fun for all
of our audience.
It was fun for the whole family and everyone
enjoyed it.
I see, I see, I see the rowdy fucker stuff
as kind of like a version of like the digi
and that anime snob thing.
Cause it's like, like it's fun to shit on someone like that.
And like all at the end of the day, who gives a shit
what they have to say.
There's nothing at stake.
Both snob and F and GR, they deserve it because
they're dishing it out constantly.
And it's all anybody wants to see is for someone to come along.
Just want to go on, just want to go on the record and say
that F and GR is far inferior to Miss Anthropony.
F and GR is by far the greater building.
Oh, oh, oh yeah.
Miss Anthropony, I honestly don't have that much
hard feelings towards, you know, I don't like what
he said about me and, and my, and my brother, but you
know what, uh, F and GR is far worse.
And honestly, he should be eliminated from the game.
He should be himself.
Oh my God, he needs to be removed from the board.
My 20 player kill streak should end with all of him
being each 20 players that I kill.
And that's how I feel about the subject.
Okay, okay.
F and GR and that anime snob are both dudes who thrive on drama,
who think for some reason that everybody wants it.
Like, like that everybody wants them to do that.
And, and no, like, no, no one really does.
That's the excuse they make.
Yeah.
And I think that in both cases, there's a huge amount
of people just waiting in the wings, hoping someone
destroys these guys.
Yeah, they're not very smart.
And most people won't bother.
Like with, with that anime snob, like what, what
everybody always told me is like, just don't, don't
bother with them because like, what's the point?
You know, you're not going to change it.
I think I told you that too, but in hindsight, I, I
under, because on the one hand I hated that anime
snob and I didn't want him to gain the exposure
that would inevitably come from me talking about him.
But, but now with the benefit of hindsight, I can see
like why you would just for your own enjoyment and for
your own like catharsis.
Well, the thing about snob and FNGR is that they
will never stop.
They're both, both of those guys are in their late 30s.
Both of those are guys in their late 30s who've
been on the internet for decades who have been
doing the same thing forever and will continue to.
FNGR is still making weekly videos about the My Little
Pony fandom in 2017.
No, November 2017.
Like nothing's going to stop those two guys from
continuing to do that.
So like you're not going to, people are like, oh, if
you give him attention, it's just going to empower him.
Nothing's going to stop him.
Like he's always going to be doing this.
So you might as well just fucking shit on him for
the hell of it.
You, you will not be able, I'm totally with you.
You will not be able to stop people who wish to engage
in drama.
But here's what my, my argument would be that, but
your time can be better used than wasting it on
involving yourself with these people.
That's, that's true.
But like, you know, what are you going to be 100%
optimized all the time?
Are you going to be, are you going to be, are you
going to use your time constructively 100%
of the time, realistically?
Using my patented formula of weird utilitarianism
available at all CVSs for 1999, you can strive,
you can strive to achieve getting as close to that
goal as possible, which I think is what we should
all try to do.
That's my, you know, that's what I would want.
Here's my, I, I, like.
And certainly drama on this level is not something
that I would want to like overindulge in, or even make
like a regular, even make a regular part of my diet.
Can the value of drama be from that, it, it gives
your, it galvanizes your audience against something
and that kind of gives them something to be invested
in and enhance your personal narrative?
I, I even think, I would even admit that there is,
okay, but I would even admit that there is
entertainment value to drama.
I would say that it's limited and to keep everything,
keep things in perspective.
That's, that's all.
I mean, you don't want it to be your character.
I want to, I want to bring up this, this amazing
Dick Masterson quote that, that a really like for me
clinched like why drama is, is fine.
And he was talking about how, because a huge part
of the Dick show is him making fun of Maddox.
It's a huge part of it's the drama he has with Maddox
because of the fact that Maddox did all this shitty stuff
to him and continues to do shitty stuff to him.
And so Dick airs it all out immediately, partly
to protect himself because it makes it easier
for him to have all the cards if, you know,
if the public is swayed to his side.
But he also was talking about like the criticism
he always gets like this show just relies on drama.
And he said, I'm sorry that I provide serialized content
with deep archetypal characters who, you know,
who to tell you something about the world around you.
And like, yeah, it's, it's just a show.
Like what he's turned it into, he's taken real life
and turned it into a TV show.
And what we get out of a TV show is that it helps us
to better understand the world, you know, like looking
at Maddox and the particular ways that he fails
is actually kind of helpful to like dealing
with other people like Maddox.
You know, like it makes me look at him and go like,
oh, fuck, you know, now I get why that guy acts that way.
Because he's just like fucking Maddox.
The important distinction here, I think, is that Dick,
Dick is his own person with his own character.
He's not just defined by being the anti-Maddox guy.
And like that, that makes it, that makes it like mean
something that he has these opinions.
Right.
If you're, if you're like FNGR, oh, you're fucking,
your whole thing is you're in there coming down on people
left and right, nobody knows why, because what do you
fucking stand for other than to shit on people?
Like, you can't understand enough of what comes out
of his mouth to figure out what his stance is.
No, I mean, there's nothing, there's nothing
that could save that particular content.
That particular soul for being reaped
by fucking Satan himself.
His Kundalini is so wicked and fucking, you know,
twisted up that you can't even straighten out
even if you want to.
The day of reckoning is coming.
His Merkaba is artificial as fuck.
And he's going, he's not going to go well for him.
He was one of the original Martians that came to Earth
and then, you know, integrated into the population,
and he's just so greedy and power-driven that he needs to stop.
FNGR is fully, fully left brain, fully mental.
Indeed.
At least a proto-masculine ideology will not
survive the test to come.
They will not endure.
Is this spirit science shit you guys are about right now?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Of course, of course.
Okay, I got to ask, do you think that that's,
is spirit science where the mind expansion meme came from?
Because that imagery is in there all the fucking time.
I was just like, I don't know, I don't know.
Me and May got really baked and watched spirit science
yesterday and that shit feels, dude, it feels so weird
because it feels like, like a parody of an educational video
that will be in a movie.
It does, it does.
I'm still not sold that it's not a fucking joke.
I'm sure it's real.
But like the comments, we weren't sure.
We read this guy.
This guy named like, it was, it was like Bobo the Bacon Lord
or something like that.
And he had this comment that I read and it was, it was,
it was amazing and I just was stewing over like whether it
was a troll comment or not.
Like I couldn't tell.
It was fascinating.
I highly recommend going to watch spirit science
and reading the comments because it's just,
it's just getting lost.
It's, it's again, it's like the genius thing where,
where it's so out there.
You can't believe it's real.
But it, but it must be real.
I learned, I did some research and I found something
interesting.
I'm going to share with you.
It shed some light on spirit science because in that
fucking history of humanity or whatever video,
he talks about thought.
He talks about like the, the Egyptian god thought,
like reveals these things and that's how we know.
And I was like, how are you talking to him?
Like where is this source?
And I looked it up and it turns out that in that video,
he references a book and the book is by some guy.
And in this book, this guy who wrote it,
claims that he has like met this like ancient,
like time traveling wizard who is like the Egyptian god.
So basically all of this is based on one guy's book
where he says that like a fucking time traveler visited
him and told me this stuff.
Dude, I didn't know that.
I didn't know that.
Yeah, that's what the whole thought thing is about.
Anytime you can't, anytime you're sitting there
watching spirit science debating yourself,
whether it's real or not, just remember that every
religion is real and they are all
fucking weird as that.
We just grew up hearing it, so it doesn't seem as weird.
But if you told, if you described like the,
the stories of the Old Testament to somebody
who did not grow up with them, they're just gonna
look you like, what in the fuck are you talking about?
Like that is fucking insanity.
I don't know if this constitutes as like drama,
but me and Munchie, we're, we're watching the videos
at one point, we were considering doing something
similar to a ratty fucker's cop killer's
like four spirit science.
And I think it could be like the greatest idea of all time.
I would like to do that in the somewhat near future,
before the world ends, of course, and before we
re-reach the end of the perception of the Equinox
and we turn back into our spa and sleep phase.
We have to use our third eye while it's still open,
if you know what I mean.
The world needs to see this shit.
It's unbelievable.
Okay, okay, well.
We haven't been watched the human history movie
in its entirety, by the way, and it was a
transcendent experience.
It shed a lot of light on a lot of things for me.
Yeah, it really does a lot of clarify.
Let's get back to our topic with the drama.
We've been sitting into the spirit science episode.
I'm just saying, I'm just saying, there were a lot.
Oh my god, we should have a praise consciousness episode.
That's a great idea.
I'm right there, Dan, right now.
I'm just saying it really shed light on a lot
of the mysteries that I had not understood,
like the, like the energy networks permeating the earth.
I'd always wondered.
And that's why all those military bases are on this grid,
on these tiny islands.
On the nodes, they're on the spirit nodes, dude.
It all makes sense.
Let's get into maybe the negative effects of drama.
Yeah, I want to start that off with saying that I, too,
have had a Derek in my life.
And eventually, he became like a joke to me.
I would eventually just go to my friend's house,
and whenever we would talk, we would just be like,
hey, I wonder what this guy's doing.
I bet he's fucking that kid, if you know what I mean.
And so it would just turn into such like valuable entertainment.
That would be better than watching a movie.
It would just be us like thinking about what he's done
and what kind of a person he is.
And, you know, picking apart like the characterization of him
and like, you know, writing fan fictions about himself
in our brain.
And that became our entertainment.
And basically it was an entire, it was a great time.
And the negative effects of drama is that it is inherently
unsustainable.
Like these people, the guy, it is an instigator.
And he, you know, obviously when you're an instigator,
you want to start drama.
So when you start drama, and that's your entire deal,
then eventually it's going to get to the point
where the drama you make is going to be about you
and you are going to be the drama that is removed.
You are going to be like, like-
I think that's kind of what has happened to Snob.
Like no one pays attention to him anymore
because all anybody knows about him is that he wants to start drama.
Yeah, that's what I was saying before.
Like drama can be fun and all, but if you become,
if you become a drama person,
then you become the one causing the drama.
He did get literally booted from the platform.
So that didn't help his visibility exactly.
It's like, when you are trying to start shit with someone,
that's exactly what we're doing.
You're starting shit with someone.
And after a while, they're just going to be like,
okay, well, this isn't fucking worth it.
And then they're going to cut you out.
It isn't inherently like, once you go down that road,
unless you fucking do it in absolute sincerity and beauty,
you know, as depicted, the right-of-hook is cop killers,
then you can easily tumble and fucking fall
and eventually become the very, like when you want it,
like say if you like don't like someone,
when someone does and you start, you know,
taking the piss out of them and do that constantly,
then eventually you're going to be the one
that people hate and want to take the piss out of
and eliminate from society.
If you indulge too much in drama and you love drama
and like drama is a source of enjoyment for you
and becomes like too much of that,
then what eventually happens is you might run out
of other drama and you will be like fucking hooked on it
and you will feel the need to start it where none exists.
You'll have to create, you'll have to create new drama
so that there will be drama for like your life
because you need it.
If you develop that appetite, you will need to feed.
Drama is best served as a side dish and not a main course.
I gotta say though, like it's,
the best is when drama just falls in your lap.
That's when it's truly beautiful.
Yeah, that's why I think it's an opportunity.
Exactly, it's just giving me permission.
It's like life handing me a sledgehammer
and then putting a watermelon in front of me
and being like go ahead, dude.
That's what it was with Forever World a few months ago
where this, I just made a video about anime streaming
and some idiot YouTuber just like decides to start drama
for no reason.
He's just like saying all this shit about me
and like contacting my sponsors,
like contacting Crunchyroll and being like how dare you break.
Yeah, the reason I came at Forever World so hard
is that he got on Twitter
and was like at messaging Crunchyroll
and Miles from Crunchyroll, like sending them my video
and being like how dare you have this person at your convention
when he's like anti, when he's anti legal streaming
or whatever, which I'm not,
and he completely misinterpreted the video.
So for me, I was just like,
oh, this is such a beautiful opportunity.
You know, like this is such a-
Forever World is a dummy who just misunderstood your point.
I thought you're just like, no, never pay anything,
even though you literally pay for whatever.
It's not what you want.
It's okay.
It was just that feeling of seeing this guy
who I've never really watched his content
because I mean, it's terrible, you know,
and it's like I have every reason to fight this dude
because there's nothing I can gain from being friend.
Like nobody likes him that I know.
You know, there's no bridge that I'm worried about burning.
So this guy just drops-
This guy's number one fan right here,
see my little on a seven on the plate real quick.
You can engage with drama and it can be fine
as long as your hands are clean.
Like, but if you're the one stirring the pot,
it's dangerous and people will come at you for it.
The best part is that he has more subscribers than me.
So it wasn't like I was punching down.
It's like a guy-
You could unshackle the beast.
Oh, he handed me himself on a platter.
And as soon as he did, I fucking railed him.
And he actually like has continued to talk shit about me
in like live streams and stuff,
but he seems to be keeping it on the down low.
Like, so like, for now, I'm just like, oh, whatever,
you know, everybody know, like after I made my video,
everybody told me like, yeah, everybody knows he's retarded.
Like it's not a big deal.
And I was like, okay, well, I'm not going to keep picking on him
if nobody takes him seriously.
But like, you know, but at the same time,
it's like, just give me the push, dude.
Just come back.
You know, just come make another video about me.
I'm ready, you know.
Here's the thing that's frustrating me.
And it's, this is semi drama related,
but it's the idea of sort of the prodigal son.
You know, the story of the prodigal son,
who, you know, from the Bible and shit.
So there was a father with two sons.
He had one son that was a good old boy
and just did his homework and did his chores
and drank his milk and grew up being strong.
The other son left home and was a big fuck up.
And like the son who stayed around, like,
like he just continued to do his job diligently.
And the father, you know, I thought it was okay.
But then the fuck up son comes home and like begs for help.
Or he's just like, dad, oh, I fucked up, please help me.
And like the Bible says, like canonically,
the father loves the fuck up son way more
than like the son who stayed around and was the good old boy.
And this is evident in like every level of human interaction
that like people love like redemption stories
or like people getting saved from shit.
So like, I feel like like drama is one of the ways
that bad behavior is rewarded.
And not just because like you start,
like even if you like bad intentions
are what get rewarded when people do this stuff.
Like if you, like if someone starts drama
and then gets called out because like,
or someone doesn't commit a crime
and then they are redeemed some way,
that person will be more loved
than the person who did nothing wrong the entire time.
And like drama is very much related to this.
And this is a little different,
but like it's the idea of how many times have we seen
people whose YouTube channels got deleted
and then like a gigantic campaign starts
every single time.
I have ever seen someone's channel deleted
for like not for like legitimate reasons.
It comes back and surges in popularity every single,
I want YouTube to delete my channel.
YouTube, please delete best guy ever
so I can do a fucking campaign
and double my size instantly.
It will happen.
I'll tell you that never, it never helped me.
I've had my channel deleted twice.
It never caused a surge,
but I also never made a big fucking deal about it.
Well, there's your issue right there.
You got to make, you got to cry and scream.
Right, just indignation.
Exactly.
Okay, but that is true.
Maybe, maybe it doesn't double everybody's size
all the time, but it never hurts
as long as you actually get the channel back.
I mean, yeah, that's, that's, that's been fun.
It did probably increase my Patreon though,
because like people just get worried about you, I guess.
That's the most important, yeah, yeah.
Start going money at you, which is interesting, you know?
So that's the concept I'm talking about here.
It's like this, when you're filled
with the righteous indignation here.
Yeah, and I'm not, like, obviously.
That is why the Dick Show is so successful.
Like, the Dick Show, the Dick Show is already
a successful podcast.
It probably had like seven grand before
Maddox made his big Dick Lies video
and a couple weeks, like a month later,
it had like 20 grand.
You know, like people were,
it was the anger people had towards Maddox
that spurned them to raise their donations to Dick.
And the fact that Dick capitalized on it so well
by making it such a good story, you know?
Whereas Maddox was being silent, like a fucking idiot.
And Maddox is effective at like,
Maddox is effective at like, since he is famous,
he's good at like giving other people stuff.
By attacking them, he gives them, you know,
like Dick achieves success in this way
through Maddox fucking with them.
And like, but he can't do it for himself
is the point I'm trying to get to.
He like, it's, I don't know, what the fuck is he doing?
It's because he's a fucking idiot, that's why.
Anyway.
Well, the man did literally invent the internet,
so credit for that.
I wanted to talk about the negative effects of drama.
The main ones that I've felt, mostly that
whether or not the person you have drama with
takes it seriously, some of their fans will take it very seriously.
And they will come, like, there was a few,
like the people who were the most mad at me
when I made my shit talking anime YouTubers video
were not anybody who I talked shit about in the video.
It was other auxiliary people who thought,
like who were just upset that I had done that.
The worst, I'm just gonna call them out.
Let's start drama right now.
Oh, there we go.
It would not be a drama cast without it.
All right.
The worst of them all is Nolan B from the pizza party podcast.
Oh my god.
Because that guy had invited me onto the podcast,
he was a big fan of me, he invited me onto the pizza party.
I just have to mention that pan pizza is a meme,
like that I hate him so much that he is a meme
in my own circle of friends, so I'm very excited to hear.
Apparently my friend Blind Skywatcher,
like obsessively watches his videos as a meme,
like because he's like deeply fascinated.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But yeah, so the pizza party podcast
was a very popular podcast, apparently.
I was invited on by Nolan B,
nobody else in the podcast really knew who I was.
It was kind of a mediocre show.
I didn't really enjoy doing it.
They edit the shit out of that podcast,
like they cut out all the silences and they speed it up,
so it sounds way better than it actually is to record.
But after that, he kept trying to stay in contact with me,
but I never really responded because I didn't really know the guy
and a lot of the stuff he would ask me is stuff you could
just find out by watching my videos.
So I kind of kept him at arm's length.
After I made the shit talking anime YouTuber's video,
that dude writes this huge screen about what a piece of shit I am
for doing that and just all this stuff
about how I'm like a monster on his Tumblr
and released it publicly and was just shitting on me
on Twitter and stuff, all this out of nowhere
because he was mad on other people's behalf.
Nobody who was insulted in the video was even angry about it.
But this dude goes fucking ham and I was just like,
this is like, this is the, on the one hand,
this is a negative effect of starting drama,
is that you got to deal with people like this.
On the other hand, you also get the fun of,
you know, like showing all your friends this guy
and going like, look at this fucking idiot, you know,
which is very gratifying in itself.
I think we've all done that at least.
Like whether we start open drama, when people come at you,
it's so satisfying to show your friends and point and laugh at them.
Oh, definitely. That guy, by the way, on that guy,
I forget how I found his Twitter,
but apparently he's like still going hard on like the PCP itself
is horrible and we're all bunch of crazy losers.
Yeah, yeah. Oh, wow. I didn't know that.
Can we start some, can we start?
Let's start some fucking drama.
Do we have a P?
Hey, Peter Party podcast is a bigger podcast than us.
In PCP versus PPP.
PCP versus PPP, dude.
We've got it.
It's that C versus P. It's that C in that P.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, god.
C, P.
Fuck.
Can we, can we?
Oh, no.
We need to do a few, we need to do a few months of research
to categorize the actual accusations made.
Yeah.
Before, before I jump into that, I will say we do have,
Prepare a legal case.
We do have shared audience with them.
I know that.
I know that there are people who like both our podcasts and theirs,
which means it's even a better reason to start drama.
Oh, my god.
I have an idea.
Do you think they'll go?
Do you think they would bite if we deliberately started drama?
You've already got one guy who hates drama.
Maybe I'll listen.
Maybe I'll go listen to some just as he,
because I may not listen to them.
I have to have legitimate grievances,
but the fact that they should talk you is,
that's like the first bullet in my clip already.
That's a good springboard.
I don't remember if he took down that Tumblr post,
but like, if I could find it, if you guys read that thing,
you'd be like, oh, god.
I remember reading this at the time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I want to know where he,
I'm curious about what he said about the PCP in specific.
Yeah, because that doesn't have some skin in the game now.
It's just some offhand comments like the PCP.
He has the same air that Vita did in that first Miss Anthropony Vita.
Like, oh, Munchie, I don't watch that channel.
I have standards.
Well, I mean, hey, that's cool and all, guys,
but the PCP doesn't feel the need to heavily edit
and speed up its audio in order to be into it.
Yeah, just saying.
Yeah!
I'm about over here.
Just fucking saying.
By the way, I do have an old grievance
with Rebel Taxi in that he's one of the legions of people
who made disgusting and unworthy Gern Lagen reviews
that I had to correct on my channel.
So you're welcome for that Rebel Taxi.
Your scene has been washed away.
Let's do it.
The funniest thing about this,
if we did start a drama with them deliberately,
is that our entire audience would know we were doing it
just to fuck with them and troll and start drama.
That's true.
Like, everyone in our audience knows what we're doing,
but it would be so funny.
I'm so happy that this character arc that has been like,
this storyline that has started within my group of friends
is becoming a real thing,
not a joke that is actually transpiring in real life now.
Oh, how fortuitous.
I know, it's terrible.
Well, is there anything else to say on the subject?
Or should we move on to questions?
I think we'll run the...
I mean, I don't know.
Drama is good unless it isn't, most of the time it isn't,
but sometimes, mwah.
Oh, I wasn't...
It's a great spice on top of your normal content.
Yeah, there was one more negative consequence of drama
I wanted to bring up,
which is just that because I personally have started
so much drama, it seems like a lot of smaller creators
are afraid of me.
A lot of people seem tepid about approaching me.
I don't know if that's more because I'm popular
or if it's because of the drama.
I think I may have seen that a little bit.
But it seems like both.
Maybe.
I've definitely had people seem like they're afraid to approach me
and when they want to ask me for something,
for a project, it's always like they'll do it
through somebody else I know or try to work their way in.
And I'm like, dude, I've talked to my fans in the comment sections.
I'm not hard to reach.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, so people should have a normal amount of trepidation
about trying to show something to someone
who you might be wasting their time.
Not even that.
Like, for instance, I mean, there's the big anti-tuber chat room
that I was initially not added to.
Jeff claims that's because he forgot to send me the message.
Oh, fucking yeah.
But I had heard that there was some trepidation
about whether I should be invited
because I might hate everyone in there
and start a bunch of shit, which is like,
it's just a mischaracterization of like,
yes, I get into drama, but it's usually because we've reached.
We've reached for a specific reason that hasn't been laid
over the course of millennia.
We've reached the end of a rope, and it has to,
something has to give.
And I'm not willing to stay quiet forever the way
a lot of people are, you know?
But I'm not like, it's not like if you start talking to me,
I'm going to flip shit on you and make a video about you
immediately, you know?
Just because you like said hi.
I think that was, yeah.
I get a lot too, weirdly enough.
A lot of fans that always be like, you know, Munchie,
like, I'm really sorry, please don't kill me.
I don't want to die.
Please, and of course I kill them instantly.
Of course I don't allow them the time to prove themselves.
Whereas if they had faced me unblinking
with the sheer terror they could on their face,
then I might have spared them.
I could sense that Kundalini was severed,
and I needed to fucking chop it into a million pieces.
Exactly.
Currently in one piece, Big Mom has this power where,
actually, you know what, I won't spoil it,
never mind, forget it.
Excellent.
It was relevant, but I'm not going to spoil it.
Life is just a big game of Beyblade,
and everyone's Merkabah is their Beyblade,
and you just have to crash your Merkabahs into each other,
and whichever one breaks is the loser and die.
That's just a game, and you're a new.
I don't feel the need, I guess, to go into it in detail,
but I personally choose, in general, to live my life
like just talking about ideas.
I know I say this a million times,
just whatever, like Elna Roosevelt,
like big people talk about ideas,
whatever, small people talk about people.
Whatever the fucking quote is, you know the one thing.
And I try to do everything by that,
and I just think it makes the most sense.
And Best Guy Ever talks about Star Trek.
Hey, Star Trek's not bad, you could do worse.
You could do worse.
Especially Star Trek Discovery on Sundays at 7 p.m. on NBC.
To me.
No, I'm just kidding, I don't know.
Drama is just like, treat it as if you're watching
like a funny YouTube video,
and expend that exact amount of time on it,
a.k.a. like, you know, not that long per day, if at all.
And just use it as a funny entertainment.
Every once in a blue moon.
Yep.
Yeah, that's how I feel about it.
That's good, good, good.
And when your friends wrong you in any way,
please go to your other friends
and shit talk about them constantly.
Preferably while hot boxing, vape in a car.
That, there you go.
That's my strategy.
That's the news from the street, from Munchiewares.
Tiny hats, I feel like I'm gonna regret
that I potentially just started more drama with Nolan B.
Like, I already regret having said anything.
What have I done?
Oh God, what have I done?
His podcast is gay and so is he.
Okay, he's done.
We need to start a PCP drama
when you told us to take it out,
but we didn't cut it out.
Now you're mad at all of us,
and we begin, the destruction begins.
Who's the Maddox of the PCP?
Davoo.
Yeah.
Oh, he will be very insulted to hear that.
But anyway, thanks.
All right, let's do some questions
while we're doing this motherfucker.
Let's do it, everybody.
Okay, how about, this isn't a question,
at Janiz Makudobaru, when is they progress?
Maybe there's a bingo board.
I'm finding that him and all of his fans
seem to shit talk us pretty regularly, so.
Well, all right.
Okay, we'll look into this.
We'll look into it like we'll update you.
We'll really know next episode what's about to inspire.
I'm for real gonna fucking look into this,
and if there's fucking shit being slung,
I'm gonna have something to say about it.
Whether or not he's slinging shit,
there definitely seems to be a sentiment
among people who follow him that is very anti-PCP.
Okay, okay.
Oh my god.
What was Janiz Makudobaru?
This is gonna be our first Moby Dick.
This is gonna be the whale that we have
to fucking spear through the heart.
This is gonna be our fucking,
we're gonna have our wiggling day
where we have to fucking face the seven trials
and come out as baby trolls.
We've been assembling this motley crew
for just such a promised day.
For the record, the opinions of some PCP members
do not reflect the opinions of others.
Anybody who does not want to be involved in this drama
is not involved in this drama.
Do not throw everybody under the bus of the PCP
just because me and Ben and Munchy happen to be.
This has nothing to do with anybody
who's not on this episode.
None of them give a fuck about Nolan B
or the Pizza Party podcast, I'm sure.
Unless they at least not yet.
Yeah, at least not yet.
They will, they will.
The only reason I'm so enthusiastic
is because whenever I see a pan pizza video thumbnail,
I just laugh so hard that I cry.
I gotta check this out.
Okay, whatever.
All right, listen.
Listen, this is bullshit.
I'm just seriously interested.
Okay, good.
Update us.
Here's the thing.
At Janny's Muckin' Tomorrow asks,
or doesn't ask, but says,
when does a procrastinator's bingo board getting made
get on it, fans?
And I actually think that'd be a great idea
when listening to the PCP.
I'm surprised we haven't done that yet.
That should be a real thing.
I think maybe because we have a rotating cast,
maybe every individual member
would need their own bingo board.
Oh, that's a bad idea.
Because if it was something like
Nate's Weird Utilitarian,
well, I mean, that doesn't count
because you're on every episode.
But if it's something like...
I don't have to be though.
But if it's something like, you know,
Tom Bowman leaves your writing in the first place.
Every time Ben vapes or fucks up Eddie.
Yeah, yeah.
I made a drinking game with that already.
Yeah, we already did the drinking game
with all these things you guys are freaking up.
That's true.
That seems more our speed than a bingo board
to be honest.
Oh, okay.
Well, whatever.
Bingo board.
Well, some fan wants to make a bingo board.
Please do.
Yeah, please.
This is interesting.
If you want to do all the heavy lifting for us
because we're just too busy
with all this amazing content.
We'll retweet it so everyone could use it.
For sure.
From the procrastinator's Patreon lounge,
don't enter our Patreon for just one measly
miniscule of a dollar.
And you'll get in and we'll fuck you.
Yeah.
Remewersalists.
And if you're in the Discord,
you're much more likely to have your questions
right on the show.
Exactly.
A question from-
No, I want to say by Garbage Burner,
who's the worst pair of you on the podcast?
Like who of us?
You know, there's these social social media
podcasts, The Right Focus Cop Killers and all of that.
Who would be the worst two people to have
on a podcast at any given time?
I think me and Davoo,
even though I really like Davoo,
I remember you and Davoo did not gel at all
on the first Rowdy fuckers.
Yeah.
Davoo did not know what to make of you.
We gel kind of real in real life,
like a little bit.
I mean, it was more like we have a lot to say
about Mario and Luigi, but other than that.
Yeah.
And when I'm trying to fucking sleep
at like 3 a.m. in the goddamn morning,
you worthless creatures.
I think, I'm going to say me and Jesse,
because we do not see eye to eye on anything.
And even like as far back as the show has gone,
there have been things that Jesse has said
that I have tried to argue.
Like I remember we're talking about like
attitudes towards fans and stuff
and like attitudes towards criticism.
And I have, it has made me so mad before.
And I have, and it just does not,
it's not, but not in a good way.
You know, a lot of us approach things differently.
The problem with this question is that
it depends on what the podcast is about.
Like, I think, that is true.
Just in general.
I think if Ben and Jesse were doing a podcast
about like a specific game they both liked,
they would have an incredibly in-depth conversation
and both notice a bunch of shit
that the rest of us wouldn't.
Because you're both like very attentive viewers.
I think if Davoo and Munchy had a conversation
about like weird art.
Like weird, like deep web art.
It would be a fascinating podcast.
So like any combination of us,
it's just a matter of finding the thing
that the two of us can discuss, you know?
I agree, I agree.
I asked Davoo to which he replied,
ha ha, if you wanted to do an arm retrieval
about the Kirby anime.
And I think that would be hilarious.
That sounds like a good plan.
Yeah.
Hey, listen to this question.
Me and Davoo were gonna do,
like when we were in Atlanta,
we were walking around and Davoo was saying
that we should do like a two-person show
about like weird art.
And I was into it at the time,
but it never got brought up again.
What a shame.
There's still time.
Hey, let's do this question here.
At Mozu Disposition asks,
is Reverse Bukake pro-feminist?
Now first of all, first of all,
can someone explain to me what the fuck Reverse is?
Yeah, yeah, that's what it asks.
Secreting?
No, no, no, this is a girl stuffing
the cum on her body back into your dick.
I assume it's a girl squirting on a guy.
Okay, I checked it out
and I went to my friend Urban Dictionary
and he told me that Reverse Bukake
is the actor of one man being ejaculated
on by a group of girls.
So there you go.
Is that pro-feminist?
I'm gonna say it's like it.
No, no.
No?
Why?
It's still a cuss.
Because it's still meant for a guy to jack off to.
This is a really hard question.
Let's move on to another one.
This is bullshit.
You're scared of...
You fear women's power.
That's why you want to get away from this question.
Of course I do.
Of course.
Student of Ethereum
who always asks like a thousand questions
on every episode,
but they're usually all right ones in there.
Favorite internet content creator
who isn't making content anymore?
Mr. Beton.
I was just gonna say Mr. Beton.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I would say Christian Weston Chandler,
but he's back.
But his new stuff is sucks and is boring.
So as far as I'm concerned, Christian is dead.
What's he making now?
What's he doing?
He's still making comics, but they're stupid.
Like they're just like him,
him like sending a positive message about trans rights.
Snore.
Agreed.
Fucking Jan Rankowski or Parker91.
I'm fine with Parker91 over.
I'm fine with that.
Chapter might have been closed.
But his new channel, Wisdom Gun,
is fucking gone dude.
Like some sort of like drama that I don't fully understand.
I need to research this.
I'm so fucking upset.
Jan, please come back.
I love you with all my heart.
I love DIY high guy where you play the role of a CIA agent
trying to test out various different drugs.
I want that series back in my life.
DIY high guy.
Yeah.
That sounds good.
Oh, did Shalegett like delete it?
Or was it to take it down for some reason?
No, no, no.
It's just like he's just not.
Okay.
He's just not there anymore for like some unfortunate reason.
Maybe he tried every drug
and there was nothing left to do.
Let's hope so.
I want to ask a two part question.
Mostly because the question itself is fascinating.
More so than whatever answer we could give.
It's from SquidMiku who asks,
Have you ever had a food phase?
For example, I ate nothing but SpaghettiOs for one year.
Also, what's something weird you like to eat?
For example, for me, it's yogurt sandwiches.
Oh my fucking god.
SquidMiku, you have a problem.
And it doesn't just stop at this question.
I got really into tea for a while there.
I was drinking a lot of weird teas.
I'm currently in my tea phase.
I'm surrounded right now by pure leaf unsweetened black tea bottles
just surrounding my complete naked facade right now.
Whatever you guys say tea
and then tell me that it's like store bought bottled tea,
I just throw up a little by now.
No, I'm talking about stuff that I got from like an herb shop
that I like to eat.
Good.
That's the good shit.
Yeah, I got some like fancy white tea
and was like way into like learning the exact temperature
it'll to brew it at and stuff.
Oh my god.
It was fun.
But I don't do it anymore because it's a hassle.
I didn't know that was an aspect that could.
And the reward is not worth it.
I didn't know that Beyblade customization
was the thing that you could do with tea
though I realized it's now obvious in retrospect.
I'm going to do that now.
It's going to be a new thing that I do.
Okay, I actually did.
For sophomore year of college,
I survived mostly on gigantic boxes of goldfish.
Gigantic boxes.
I mean bring them up to my roof.
I would not leave.
That's as bad as eating nothing but spaghetti for a year.
Yeah, it was terrible.
It was terrible.
I think that may be even worse.
And by the way, by the way much,
and literally I lived above the mess hall.
All I had to do was walk downstairs to free food all day
and eat it.
But I chose to stay in my room, play video games,
and eat fucking goldfish exclusively.
There was light.
I'm a monster.
It was a year after that I started working out and eating more.
So that was probably why.
When I first got in sixth grade,
which by the way my sixth grade year,
I started off the year like the last day of summer,
I watched the human history movies for the first time.
I believe that was the year at least.
Anyway, great year to start off.
For like the entire first half of the year,
like six months,
I ate nothing but bags of croutons.
Whoa, weird.
Like would you get them?
Where'd you get them?
I just went to Bons.
I went to Bons and I just had packets of croutons.
How did you live off of this?
Just croutons and goldfish in both of your cases.
Yeah, just carbs.
Simple carbs.
Yeah, that's it.
It's all you need, dude.
Don't you need like protein or something?
No.
Digi, look at me.
Look at me, Digi.
You think I need anything that's not carbs?
No, no, never.
Mochi's body consumes its own waste products
and recycles it.
I start to like,
I start to feel sick if I eat the same dish like twice in a day.
Like I feel gross and I need to go eat another thing.
You just got to delicate stuff there, Digi.
You got to hard the fuck up with the bombs dropped by Digi.
When World War III stops,
I'm only going to have packets of croutons
that's all I'm going to be able to assist off of.
Yeah, I'm only going to have fucking goldfish just to survive.
This is crazy.
Digi's just been spoiled by all that sweet Patreon money.
He can afford to buy something new all the time.
I can afford to buy a place in a day.
I'm a relatively picky eater, but like I won't, I don't know.
Like it has to be like a different,
like the other day I had a garbage plate
for that video I did about garbage plates
and like I ate until I was full
and then later I tried to eat more
and like even though it was delicious,
my stomach was like,
you need another kind of nutrient than this.
Like you can't keep eating this
because this will kill you.
Right.
You know, so go eat a different thing.
He has an acute case of rich person syndrome.
I guess so.
Well, maybe your body is like more attuned
to what it actually needs or something.
I don't know, people, it's bad that my body
like doesn't immediately punish me
for just eating goldfish for a fucking year.
I do have a habit where like if I like take some shitty food,
like I'll eat a ton of shitty food
and I'll eat it and I'll be full and disgusting
and I'll be like, oh God, that was so bad.
Like I'm so full of crap.
And then I'll be like, oh, I'm so full, I'm gonna die.
But then I'll be like, wait,
and I'll go and I'll eat an apple afterwards
and like think that it'll make me less full than no.
It just makes you more full.
It doesn't actually work to make you feel better.
I would say I've never been through a food phase
like what you guys are describing,
but like I've been through lots of like just,
what's the word for like all the foods you eat?
Like your diet, I guess?
Yeah, your diet, sure, sure.
I've been through like diet phases,
not like doing a diet, but like where every,
like I'm eating the same seven or eight things
and then it cycles into a different seven
or eight things at some point.
You know, so like it might,
and I'll have phases where like I got really
into spicy food for a while,
I was trying to eat like spicy shit all the time,
just like boost up my ability to eat spicy foods,
or I got like way into onions for a while,
but it was never to an extent
like just eating onions all the time.
It was just like, oh, maybe I'll get onions on my burger
every time I get a burger.
I did, when I was in California
and I was super poor and living for free
and some guys in my friend's side room,
I did have a phase of like,
I used to just eat tons of egg sandwiches
because eggs are really cheap and bread is really cheap.
I had a just, I would just fry eggs and put them on bread.
See, like I had a phase,
I had a phase of being way into egg salad sandwiches,
but I wouldn't say it was something I was eating all the time, you know.
I love egg salad, by the way.
Like I did have a phase where I would make myself
an egg salad sandwich probably every other day,
you know, for lunch, but it's not like all of us eating, you know.
Side note here, how awful is it
that we've let anime gone the better of us?
I mean, it didn't do a spicy bro pack to anime expo,
named Digi.
How fucking abysmal is that?
It was, we tried, but we had like some game with it.
What do you mean we tried, dude?
I was there too.
I said Nate.
Oh, you did?
Oh, okay, okay.
It's a shame, that needs to be,
Rycon 3 coming up real soon.
Part two of that question though,
did any of you have a weird thing you like to eat?
Like, I don't think any,
there's lots of stuff I would describe as like,
maybe not something everyone eats,
but nothing that's not considered a dish, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I kind of eat, I mean, so like after,
okay, I mean.
There's even cans of beans, Nate,
even your cans of beans.
My famous patented dark red kidney bean cans,
which I love, and I'm ready to eat.
It's weird to eat as much of it as you eat,
but it's not weird to eat kidney beans.
Well, I wasn't even gonna bring that up.
By themselves, I would say that it is.
I mean, I eat them uncooked raw out of the can,
and I do wash them off, I wash up the goose.
Our example was yogurt sandwiches.
I don't have anything like that.
What I was gonna say was like,
I feel like this sort of counts,
so like after I work out,
I would normally consume like protein,
chocolate protein powers, just the kind I like,
and then I have, I got the stuff creatine,
which is, I don't know, it's famous and fitness stuff.
It helps you grow muscle,
but that's fruit punch flavor,
and I used to drink them one after each other,
and like that was like, oh, my stomach's full of water.
What am I gonna do?
Brilliant plan.
I literally combined them,
and I drink chocolate fruit powder,
fruit punch mixture, and it's really gross,
but I drink it anyway, because it's efficient.
I did for a while do a thing that I think was actually good,
and I don't understand why people thought this was weird,
because I think it just makes sense,
and it is tasty,
but I would make my morning coffee,
and then I would put a scoop of chocolate protein powder in it,
and blend it into like a protein mocha thing.
Dude, I tried to make a Ben Saint,
and it got all, I think my protein was too sticky.
That's not a Ben Saint, that's a Ben,
well, I won't say my real last name,
even though I don't care, and lots of people,
yeah, yeah, that's the Ben, my real name,
which I don't know why I'm being weird about it,
but now I've done it, and I'm gonna stick to the decision.
I like not saying my name on light, it's just fun.
It's fun for me.
The Ben Saint is, the Ben Saint is whole milk, ice, and cherry.
Ben Saint's not your real name?
Juice from a cherry, from a Maraschino cherry jar,
plus some cherries.
Wait a minute, that's your last name?
That's my last name.
Whoa, are we like related weird?
Impossible.
Wait, are you two keg and phantom horn from T-Pap?
I never knew.
Wait, you're saying that your real name,
your real name isn't Guy Saint?
What the?
My real name isn't Standard, after all, I betrayed you all.
Okay.
That's bizarre.
I, anyone else have an answer to this?
Yeah.
I wanna accuse Tom of having one.
Me?
Ooh, drama.
Drama, alright.
This isn't even something that's like weird to eat,
it's just weird to think about the existence of,
because Tom, I don't know if you still are,
but you were a vegetarian.
Are you still a vegetarian?
I still am, yes.
And you are big into Taco Bell,
because they will replace the meat with beans
on all of their stuff.
Yeah, okay.
Which to me has always been like,
why the fuck do you have to go to Taco Bell as a vet?
Just don't go to Taco Bell.
It makes sense to me.
Because Taco Bell's fucking great, I love fast food,
and Taco Bell's amazing.
Really eating, buddy.
You're just collab with Report of the Week, Tom,
in a big way.
All of us should all die.
I love Report of the Week.
Oh my god.
I've never heard of this.
Next piece of pee will be Report of the Week episode.
Yeah.
Him just like sitting there in his car,
in his like, in his three-piece suit,
with his fucking like,
fastidiously fastened tie and his little pocket kerchief,
just looking like a fucking,
looking like a some 20-year-old like,
Wall Street wannabe.
No, you look like a fucking 12-year-old, dude.
Yeah, yeah.
He's just terrified of his mind.
Same thing, same thing when you're ancient as the winds,
like me.
And just sitting there like,
like bringing out, bringing out a little,
a little packet of like,
fucking a Burger King, like Cheetos,
like Cheetos curly fries,
and just being like, and talking at length,
talking at length about like,
the merits of these Cheetos curly fries.
I've actually already done this back in,
back in my youth.
I had, I had a YouTube channel with my friend,
we reviewed fast food,
and we would record,
we would record in the store,
we brought the camera in.
What if, what if this friend was right?
What if this friend was right?
Is it possible?
The best thing about Tom's show
is that they did it in the restaurant,
like they would sneak a camera in,
which was so much cooler than any of the other ones
that do it in like their car,
like game drops.
The couple times that we, we did it at home,
we would always drink Mountain Dew out of wine glasses.
Sick.
And I tried to copy your show, Tom.
I tried to do the, the go into a place.
I had like several ideas for fast food review shows,
but one of them, me and my brother Shade,
were just like recording a random podcast one time.
This never saw the light of day,
because it was terrible.
But I had, I was holding the laptop
with my fucking preamp plugged into it,
sitting on top of the laptop,
and I was holding the microphone,
like XLR cord and everything,
and just like walking to Taco Bell.
Like we walked to Taco Bell over recording the podcast
while walking on the side of the road.
Then we walked in and I had Shade hold the laptop
and everything while I ordered,
and like everyone's giving us looks like,
what in the flying fuck do you think you're doing, you know?
So we sit down to start eating,
just having the microphone going,
and the manager comes out and he's like,
yeah, you can't record in here.
Can you like, and he made me,
he made me delete the recording in front of him.
But of course, what?
But of course, he doesn't know
that all you have to do is hit the X
on audio track and audacity,
and I went, it's done.
And then of course as soon as it left,
I controlled Zed and it was back.
So, but it was a totally worthless recording anyways.
So, I'm glad.
We only got kicked out once, and I was at a KFC.
But on the rest of the time, we just,
we had free reign, we could do whatever we wanted.
Nobody really cared.
That's amazing.
Unfortunately, you've never had
another fast food review podcast
in your entire life, did you?
And you've been yearning for that in your entire life.
The only intent, no, I've had a bunch,
but there's one that's currently running.
I say that, but there hasn't been an episode in months.
I have fucking cried.
Even though there's generations of past.
Two of them have been recorded.
The people cry out.
It's true, it's true, it's unfortunate.
Once a month, May looks at me and goes like,
what the fuck is up with the fucking stealing your dad's?
I'm like, I don't know, man, I don't know.
Munchie's a busy boy, a busy boy.
It'll happen, it'll happen.
All right, one more question that I want to...
Wait, let me read this meme one.
This isn't a real question.
It's just like, at Mark McAuley on Twitter asks,
found out I'm at the same uni Gibbon attended.
How cucked am I doing an animation degree?
And then in parenthesis, he says,
I recognized his animation in a show reel.
First of all, cool, that's dope, dude.
And I would like to say that second of all,
Gib currently this month is working real hard
on various gigs he's gotten through his efforts
in animation shit, one of which is a commercial project.
He's animating a whole fucking thing for a dude.
So I'd say you're not completely fucked.
I think he's writing for it.
Well, there's that thing he's working with a company on,
and then there's one guy he's just animating for.
Yeah, yeah, so you're not totally fucked.
A documentary or something like that.
Oh, indeed.
And I want to say that he goes into this on his Patreon's only podcast.
Are you a patron of Gib?
I am, actually.
Shit, I want to hear that shit.
Incidentally, I'm sure he would just link it to you if you asked.
I will ask you.
I've always been waiting for one of my friends
to be interested enough in my Patreon exclusive content
to ask me for it, but nobody is.
It has never happened.
There's too fucking much to do, bro, dude, I'm sorry.
We're past the saturation point, it's true.
But the Patreon podcast might be more up you guys' alley
than a lot of the main...
Here's the thing, Digi.
We have exclusive access to your best friend's content,
which nobody else has, because you don't have to pay shit for it.
Oh, that's cute.
Also, Digi, the snippets you've released of your podcast
have been pretty interesting, so I actually would like to listen to those.
There was at least one or two that I specifically wanted to send you, Nate.
Oh, yeah?
There's even one where I talk about you,
and probably for some reason...
I wouldn't hear that.
...a utilitarian reason or something.
Now I'm interested.
For drama reasons.
Anyway...
That's where he announces that he's leaving the PCP joint
and then the pizza party pod.
It was a ruse all along to pay it out the unbelievers.
Okay, all right.
I really do regret having brought that to fruition,
because I know it's gonna be a thing now.
We'll see how it goes.
All right.
This is what I always wanted, dude.
This is what I always wanted for us.
It's so worth it, though, because if there's one podcast,
I'd love for us to have a thing that's gonna be available.
We need a battle.
These fucking Rowdy fuckers' cop killers
are a negative influence on the PCP,
and we need to obliterate it.
No, we need this.
What is Sparkoil's undigisoul?
What is Superman without Lex Luthor?
You're so right.
He needs an enemy.
We need our nemesis within, of course.
Of course, yes.
All right, all right.
Okay, Digi, listen.
Visuals asks,
if there was one piece of content you wish you never made,
what would it be?
It's easy.
Analyze this, Anarchy.
I want to kill myself every time I think about it.
Also, to remind everyone,
I read the script and turned that down.
I am literally 1,000 times smarter than Ben Superior
in every way.
I know things.
Really?
There you go.
Fucked up, and it makes me mad.
I don't know.
Everything I've done is fucking flawless.
I'll think.
Go on, Digi.
I think I, on some level,
I don't know if I would have regretted this at the time,
but by this point,
I can't remember anything good
having come from my most boring taste in anime video.
Like, I feel like the point was mostly missed,
and that even the people who did get the point,
it didn't do anything to have gotten the point.
All it did was ruin 3x3 threads on 4chan forever,
which is actually great.
I'm actually very happy with that result.
But it also meant that I am forever inundated
with people's 3x3s,
and I don't care and have never cared.
That's probably the video that had the worst consequences,
and the worst cost benefit.
Like, it had more cost than benefit to have made.
I don't know why it became such a big deal in the first place,
because it was,
I shouldn't have given it a thumbnail,
like, I give my video thumbnails
when I think they can become big,
and in that case, I was like,
oh, this is a chance to be a big video,
but I should have realized that I didn't want it to be a big video,
and I fucked up by letting it become one.
So.
I have one.
Even though I'm happy with it now,
and I don't think it's bad,
in hindsight, I do wish that I didn't do Nuzlocke Conquest,
because it ended up being way more work
than it was actually worth.
But, you know, like, yeah.
I kind of wish I had stopped after the first one.
Nuzlocke Conquest should have just been made six months later
after the champion was done,
and then it would have made tabs.
Yeah, it really should have,
and it was foolish of me to want to jump right into it,
just to coincide with the release of Sun and Moon.
Because, like, it's a long-form series
that came out over months.
It's not like it was one big explosive thing
that was like, oh, everyone who's hyped about Sun and Moon
is going to want to watch this, you know?
Right, right.
I mean, it was a bit ill-conceived.
In terms of marketing and, again, cost-to-benefit ratio stuff,
like, yeah, it did succeed.
Even though it's cool and people like it,
like, it really did not do much of anything for me.
I am, canonically, the biggest Nuzlocke Conquest fan,
and I absolutely loved it, but that's what that just means.
I mean, I like it.
But that doesn't help you.
That doesn't help you.
No, not at all.
I don't know.
I guess I'll just use my old answer of, like,
I worked way too long.
All my old videos, I worked way too long on.
The Lucifer and the Biscayne number one
is, like, over-edited to the point of being
almost, like, indecipherable to some extent.
And the Undertale one is kind of like the two,
but that has positives as well.
Nothing I've made is, like, terrible,
but I guess I would just say, like, the Lucifer,
because I worked too hard on it.
But I am happy with what it is now, so I don't know.
That's all I got.
Tom, you got any videos you regret making?
I probably should have done the leaving the fandom one better
because it cost me, literally, all my money.
But at the same time, it, like, set me on the path to making it.
But what's that black money that was illicit money anyway?
That's my whole point.
It set me on the path to doing things that actually matter.
So, like, I set out to make it because I wanted to do a hard,
like, get out so I couldn't go back,
because I knew I would just crawl back if I didn't.
You succeeded there.
I'm glad that happened, but at the same time,
I'm perpetually broke forever now,
and I'll probably never make money again, so.
Unless I start some drama.
So, that's kind of why I'm always on the show.
Start some drama.
I'm really poor.
I could probably make some money with some drama.
That's what we're all counting on.
Give me money, guys.
Don't make me start shit.
The only way that it's going to work is if we are very careful
to make ourselves not the bad guys in that drama,
which is going to be difficult, you know?
But we can manage.
We can do it, though.
I'm confident.
We have the skills.
The video I most regret in my entire life
is not on any YouTube channel that I currently have access to.
I've completely forgot the password for it.
But I believe sometime around second or third grade,
I made a YouTube video, right?
Accidentally flipped off my grandmother,
and I got really sad.
I didn't.
I apologize.
I obviously bad it.
You accidentally flipped her off.
Absolutely intentional.
I was trying to give her a thumbs up,
but my brain forgot how to make the thumbs-up motion.
I flipped her off instead.
Well, the old bitch probably deserved it.
Yeah, she did, if I'm honest with myself.
Okay, I guess that's all our questions.
That's it, everybody.
Thanks for sending those using hashtag askpcp,
and we're at TP Crasnators in Twitter.
Or also by hashtag putting money into our fucking pockets,
you absolute pig at the-
Indeed.
Most of the questions we read are from the Patreon,
so that we can encourage you to become a patron.
So-
Exactly.
Yeah, yeah, boy.
So do that shit up.
Become a patron at patreon.com slash the procrastinators,
and you get fucking that shit happens.
And of course, the $5 pledge.
You get access immediately to all the bonus episodes.
We are up to eight now, and the last one was alcohol.
I'm on it.
It was a-
I was on it.
Did you saw it?
Yeah, and I got drunk, and DeVoo got shit-faced,
and it was great.
It was pretty fucking fun.
Yeah.
If you want documentation.
We are also on iTunes and Google Play,
so if you want to listen to these on your phone
without having to keep a tab open or whatever,
you can do that.
Google Play Music and iTunes,
just search for the procrastinators,
the same way it's spelled on this video,
and they'll come right up.
Along with other podcasts we intend to murder,
probably by starting drama with it sometime.
Excellent.
I can't fucking wait for this.
And anything else?
Merch, red bubble shit in the links below, whatever.
Yeah, that's it, everybody.
Like, comment, and subscribe.
Oh man, someone finally tweeted a picture of himself
wearing the sick PCP shirts that I designed,
and I'm so proud of myself.
It looks so great.
Did you see that?
I did see that.
It looked incredible on a shirt.
It looked pretty good.
It looks pretty good.
Yeah, it's hard to believe.
I was like, I was so glad to see that.
Good work, Ed.
Incredible.
I think that's all we had to say on the subject
of our favorite subject in the entire world, ourselves.
Bye!
Yeah.
Bitch.
Ed, I don't want to do it.