Well, there is a lot that goes into making these game reviews and there's actually so much that I could sit here for like three hours and still, you know, there could be more things to talk about that I forgot to mention.
I kind of just take for granted that there is a lot that goes into making these videos.
See, for me, I don't really think about it that much because I've made over a hundred episodes and I've become very efficient at it.
So to me, it's like the same way I don't think about brushing my teeth. You know, I do it so many times.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. Thanks for tuning in.
And today, actually, we're starting a special new thing. But before we get to that, let's just see who's here with us.
It's of course me, the best guy ever. We have Digibro with us.
Hey, what's up, y'all?
The Hippo Crit.
Add me in in post.
Tom Oliver.
Yo.
And The Davoo Collective.
Zap, zappy.
Okay, so here's our thing guys. We're doing a new thing. So as I'm sure everyone in the world knows, the new Twitter for the PCP is officially made and it's out there in the world.
At TP Crastinators. So go find it there. There'll be a link in the description. All that good stuff.
And what we did was that we asked people for suggestions for topics for the show.
And so today is the first time that we are taking someone's suggestion and it is at SpaceyFilmer.
It is their suggestion. I think that's a guy who was going to say his, but I don't know for sure.
And their suggestion was the writing slash editing process. And I think this was a separate suggestion, nitpicking slash overanalyzing.
But since that applies to my writing and editing process, I'm going to pretend it was part of the same thing.
So who wants to start us off talking about their writing and editing process?
Nate, why don't you, since you have the most complicated and intimate and deeply disturbing process of us all.
I think yours is going to be the one that makes the rest of us look like we don't work.
I think that's probably true. It was funny. Just before we started, Tom said,
if editing a video takes more than one day, I want to kill myself.
And here I am, looking at my chart I've got here two weeks into this current project at 53% completion.
And yes, I've been calculating it and that's the exact percentage.
What's your average hours per day you've been working on it?
About five hours per day.
Every day?
Every day, that's right.
You see, these things are not practical, but I do them anyway.
And this whole project, I've been working on Ghost in the Shell,
but I decided to pick up this one just to get something out,
because it'd been a little while since I'd put out a big video.
Of course, I can't remember what the fuck the word is. It was a masterpiece,
but I thought I'd do something else a little more in tune with my regular content.
Of course, like everything, it's taken way too long.
But anyway, for this current video I'm working on, I just had an idea,
and it was kind of similar to my process for making the first Gern Lagen,
best guy ever, whatever video it was, where I just had an idea,
and I just did whatever it took to make it real, whether or not it was practical or not.
But since that was the first video for the channel, that didn't matter.
But I think probably the process of making shit is more interesting
for things like the part two of the Gern Lagen one.
So for that, I also just, I had an idea.
It always starts with just the seed of an idea for the video to make, of course.
And it was, the context of making that was just,
I've already got this initial kind of reaction to the show in this case,
and now I want to expand on the reasons why I like it so much.
So I always start with a thesis statement of that nature.
And then the way that I made that into a video was, first, watch the whole thing twice.
So I watched the whole show through, and as I went through, I just took notes
on every single episode and everything I thought that was noteworthy.
I then took all those notes, having completed that,
and organized them into a series of topics that were relevant for the thing I was trying to make.
So I did that, and then I organized them into an order that made sense
to get to the ultimate point I was trying to make,
which in this case was the stuff about how there's things to be learned from Gern Lagen,
and all these practical lessons that it's trying to teach us.
And so everything was building to that point.
And then I had to go through, and because the video was already,
because there were way too many topics, I had to cut a bunch of shit
that wasn't directly related to what I was talking about.
That video only focuses on narrative stuff.
It doesn't talk at all about art or any of that stuff.
So all that stuff I just threw aside because it wasn't pertinent.
And then I then converted those notes into a script.
And this was probably the hardest step, turning them into actual senses and doing that shit.
I mean, that took a while.
And up to that point, it was probably like two to three months of work.
And then at that point, it was just the three month more process of converting all those notes.
Or I did the voiceover, did the voice recording, that's fine.
And once I have the voice recording, I do that first.
I then go back over it.
I drop that shit in Vegas or Premiere or whatever.
And then I just start from the beginning and just start editing all the way through.
Yeah, what's up?
Sorry to cut off your momentum there.
No problem, no problem.
The what you're describing to me, this is in my mind the classical idea of how to go about.
And I don't just mean that in the writing sense.
The whole concept of the video is like back when I started as an animate writer,
exactly what you're doing is what I sort of dreamed of.
I saw it as you've got your favorite shows and nothing in the world matters
in the face of just talking about your favorite shows.
Everything else you talk about is because it's whatever, you're just interested for a week or so.
It's just a little flight of fancy.
Oh, here's an idea I had for a video.
But your favorite shows is these titans that you feel like you're never going to be able to sleep right until you've done it.
Until you've really sold everyone and why it's so special.
And for me, I had this thing I did starting in 2009 called The Epic Journey,
because I was a fucking teenager and the word epic was the word back then that you used.
The Epic Journey, the idea was I was going to analyze or just talk about all of my favorite anime
and first I would write about how I remembered them, then rewatch the show and then watch it again while writing about it.
And I did this with FLCL, where that's the only one I ever actually did to completion,
but I wrote about it beforehand, watched the commentaries, watched all the episodes,
wrote these in-depth analytical pieces about each episode.
So I covered all six episodes and then a final thoughts kind of piece.
So it was this big huge project, but then the prospect of doing that for every favorite show I have
is so much work just to do FLCL.
And for a long time I dreamed of doing things the way you're doing.
What finally got me past that was Evangelion, because I wanted to tackle Eva,
but I felt like I have to say everything there is to say about it.
There has to be no stone left unturned, because so many people have talked about it before,
it has to be the ultimate, it has to be the most thorough analysis of Eva possible.
And what I had planned to do was to do a podcast about every single episode,
half of them with guests, where I'd take people who I know have talked about the show,
like Demolition D, Go Jesus, Jesse, I had already told all of them about this.
This was going to happen, this huge project of podcasting every episode.
And then I was going to take all of the ideas presented by everybody in all the podcasts
and then write a book about Eva, like a full stop book and cover everything.
And that project is just so huge that there was no way it would happen.
It was like, you know, I'd think about it and I'm just like,
if I start on this, this is going to be my life for half a year, you know,
which is exactly what your process has been.
Well, I mean it was never my goal, I see what you're saying,
but it was never my goal to talk in depth about every aspect of the show.
And in my opinion, I only talked about a very narrow range of ideas.
I only talked about specifically like the scientific application
and like the philosophical meaning behind the show.
I mean, I would have loved to spend time talking about like the humor of the show,
which I think is nobody talks about like analyzing humor and stuff.
It's a huge problem in all of analysis.
No one's doing good analysis of comedy and humor.
It's tough, it's a shame.
But yeah, I mean, I'm glad that you didn't cover absolutely everything
because when I finished your video, I like mental note,
I still get to do cool character designs growing the gun,
which I'd planned for long before you ever made your video.
I had that plan, you know, that was always going to happen and it finally did.
But you know, that's, I just think that, sure, you didn't cover absolutely everything,
but it's just that mindset of like, I have to say all that I have to say
and make it this big, huge deal, you know.
And what finally got me past that was looking at Ava and just going,
all right, maybe one day I can write a book about Ava.
But for now, what if I just like, every time I have a thought about the show,
let's make a video about it, you know, doesn't have to be the whole thing.
Just every single time I have some thought that hasn't been expressed,
let's make a video about it.
And I sort of went with that approach and I've made like seven or eight Ava videos
that people seem to really like.
Well, okay, okay, but I mean, this does tie into my, you know, video making process.
I mean, at this point in my career, I guess you'd say,
I feel that I need to do things to distinguish myself from, you know, everyone out there.
And I think I'm definitely doing so.
And to be honest, I think I'm making some of the best content
when it actually comes out, which is rare.
And obviously that's a huge problem.
So, I mean, do you think that's a mistake?
I mean, obviously it's not the most efficient way of doing things,
but it is the way I provide that.
I think it's not a mistake because, I mean, you're getting more subscribers for less,
for less content because people really like the,
the quality level.
If they just wanted to, you know, I mean,
the way I think about my videos is I could technically do the stuff you do
and it would take probably a bit longer because I'm not used to doing that.
But I just, I don't care so much about it being as flashy as possible
because I just want things to be made.
And it's like, but as a result, I don't get quite as much clout
or whatever word I'm trying to think of.
Yeah.
Like I'm not seen as like the flashiest, coolest guy.
Yeah, I mean, I talked about this in my last decompression vlog
that like people look at Nate or Jesse and they look at those big videos
and those are videos that like they will always be coming back to
and talking about and thinking about.
Like, I think for most people who've seen the Gurren Lagann analysis,
that is now like intrinsically tied into Gurren Lagann for them.
Like, it's not like a YouTube video about the show.
It's like a part of the show.
It's part of how they recognize it now, you know?
Yeah.
And you're sorted online.
And AstraScore, I'm sure, are similar for people.
Oh, certainly, yeah.
Especially AstraScore because for most people, that's the only exposure they've had.
I mean, yeah, people didn't have much to say about it before that, I'm sure.
But yeah, I think it's great that you do those kinds of videos
and I'd love for you to always have them come out, you know, once in a while.
But I think that, well, here's what's going to save you,
is that you don't have that many favorites.
Like, there's not that many shows I think you could cover this right.
You know?
Like, I mean, there's Ghost in the Shell.
There's One Piece.
There's, you know, Star Trek, TNG.
And like, once you've covered all those, there's not going to be a need
for a 50-minute best guy ever analysis about something
because you've covered the giants that you care about.
You know, it's a shame about this whole thing.
I think I can get away with continuing this sort of thing
with, like, you know, we're going to Ghost in the Shell now.
But I've already, in my mind, come up with a solution to this,
which is just basically just splitting up the fucking video.
And then, like, by doing that, I can still talk in as much depth
and crazy editing as I want.
But a video will come out maybe every month, possibly every two months,
just because they're all part of a series as opposed to, you know, one...
It was a big mistake to do all of Gern-Lagan one thing.
It's great. I love that it's a package, but, you know...
That's what I've been doing with my Rayman review.
Right, and it's perfect.
Like, the first part...
Exactly the right way to go.
It was really good.
Thanks.
But, like, the part one is 10 minutes long.
But if I had included the rest of the part one that I've written,
it would be maybe 40 minutes long.
Part two is going to be 20 minutes.
I don't know how many parts it's going to have.
I really wrote too much.
But having that little, you know, 10 minutes is, you know,
is decent enough for a...
You know, it's important for guys like us, you know,
at our early stage of the YouTube game here,
to be producing, you know, just shit as fast as possible
and to get ourselves out there as best we can.
And by the way, before we move on from the How Great I Am thing,
now's an appropriate time for me to put out the story about how yesterday,
Sy, a man with 150,000 subscribers,
came to me asking me for creative expertise
on how to edit something better.
So I'm just saying, people out there are taking note of what I can do.
I mean, for the record, Nate, I have 250,000 subscribers.
I would definitely come to you for editing.
Yeah, but I don't...
You don't matter.
You're nobody.
If I wanted to know how to make a screen stretch and explode,
I would ask you about it for sure.
Right.
But we're friends.
You know, I've known you for a long time.
I've known that thought of the splitting videos in parts.
And I want to touch on that, how that happens for me.
And it sounds like it's going this way for you guys as well.
Because it used to be that you would write a video to be shorter
because YouTube audience retention was so low.
People's average three to five minutes watch time per video.
And it used to be that people tried to keep videos short
or tried to break them into parts so that more people would watch it.
That is not a concern anymore.
And YouTube length does not matter.
You've got Matthew Matosis putting out six fucking hour-long
commentaries that have well over 100,000 views.
The market's there.
But what it's become now is it's really about money.
And I say that with as little cynicism as possible,
but we need to be able to make enough money to make...
If I make a video that's like Mob Psycho 100,
the one I did on that, it's like seven minutes long.
And it's like concept of completion in like a day.
I watched the whole show.
I already knew Victor had already given me an idea of something to say about it.
Because Victor requested me to watch that show and do an analysis of it.
He kind of gave me the idea of what it was going to be like.
So I watched the show.
I already have in mind what I'm going to say about it.
I write the video.
I give it to Davoo.
He edits it that night.
It's out within like 24 hours of being conceptualized.
That's a beautiful thing.
And that video...
If I post it on YouTube and it gets...
And that video has a shit ton of views because it was a popular show.
But I can post that out and I can post it on Patreon.
And it's like considered one video.
Then you've got Akiyuki Shinbo in the 90s,
which is months of watching anime.
It's tons and tons of shows that me and Davoo watched.
And it's 40 minutes long in total between the two parts.
And Davoo spent days editing that.
And the product, if it was one video, if it had just been one video,
it would have had like 50,000 views, much less than Mob Psycho had.
And it would only be one post on Patreon.
So it makes just as much money as Mob Psycho did.
And if not less, because it depends on when it comes out in the month.
So for me, that video was written as one video.
I just arbitrarily split it at a point where it could be split into two.
And each one is substantial.
There's no problem with splitting a video.
I mean, who suffers when you split a video into two parts?
Nobody. It just comes out a little later.
I think it's interesting that that's kind of the way we're having to do things
because YouTube rewards frequency.
It rewards multiple uploads.
It rewards people remaining on your channel for multiple videos.
That's a huge part of how you get paid is when people go through your catalogue
or they go from your videos to another one.
And longer videos are actually better for the YouTube algorithm.
But multiple long videos in a string is even better still.
And each one will probably have better retention on its own
than the whole one would have had by itself.
It's crazy how fast you can get to 100k if you make videos for your niche every day.
Yeah. Oh my God.
You need to be frequent.
And even for the big channels, this is a huge concern.
You saw how H3H3 had split between Ethan and Ela and H3H3
and they were posting way more on Ethan and Ela
and they were like, this is killing our main channel
because we're only uploading once every two weeks
as opposed to once every two days, our fucking rates are just dropping.
So we're fusing our channel so this won't happen.
I mean, that's a channel with 2 million fucking subscribers
making crazy money and even they're worried about the frequency of their uploads and shit.
If you want that growth, if you want that steady growth
and if you want to keep making money, you got to have frequency and some regularity
and each individual splitting a 40 minute video in two.
I mean, I could have split it into fucking four,
but I like it to be in these big chunks.
I wanted you to get enough of the narrative to get invested.
Because with RoboPixels, I've been releasing one video every week, every two weeks
for like the last year and just the last two weeks
I started doing vlogs and now there's two videos a week.
My subscriber growth month over month tripled
and if you count, doubled and fucking earnings doubled.
You know, that's why I was so happy with...
I saw Gabe's video, I can't remember the fucking word, you know, whatever
and I was just like, this is hilarious, I'd love to make something like this
and just that night, like it came out in the morning, I watched it while I was at work
that night I rushed home and in the span of like five hours
I was able to get a video done and I was just so thrilled about that fact
I was able to get something done that I had to put it on the main channel
instead of BestieBoy, which it obviously belongs on
but I was just so thrilled to actually have something to post
with that level of speed that I couldn't help myself.
It's a great video.
Yeah, but we should be talking about the process of making videos rather.
Oh, there was only one thing, we can move on from me.
There was only one other thing that I thought was interesting
that people might enjoy hearing about, about my editing style
and it's that, so I talked a bunch before about how I get up to the point of
I've now got my voice recording of the script
and then I just start to edit through it
but did you know, viewer, that the first thing I do
after I have the voice recording script, before I do any visual editing
is I go and I pick music for every section of the video
and not only do I just put an appropriate sounding song behind it
I attempt, it's amazing how well this usually works out
I attempt to like sync important things with like relevant beats
and drops in the audio
and sometimes it works out astoundingly well
like, remember in the end of the Gernlagen part 2 video
I'm playing that song from Bravely Default, it's like the ending theme song
and there's all this epic shit going on when I say personal fucking responsibility
like, the song just happened to drop exactly at the right time
for me to like put that explosion and be like pfft
it was synchronicity of a fascinating degree
it was serendipity, that's right
and then, so yeah, I do that and then I edit the visuals
and I put a bunch of memes, all that shit
so there you go, that's an interesting insight into how I do things
so we can move on from me now if we want to talk about somebody else's
well, I guess I'll go
because I'm speaking about the music
I usually leave the music until after I have all the visuals in place
because I know it
well, I mean sometimes I think, oh, I've got to have a specific thing here
but usually I just like having something vaguely relevant
and, you know, a beat to keep it going smoothly
but yeah, music is, I don't really think about it too much
even though I like music a lot
I actually have several, I think about it way too much
and I have a folder of songs that I think will evoke certain emotions
on my computer that I just have in place for when I'm going to use them
I've already got like three picked out for Ghost of the Shell at various points
yeah, I tried to make a database of that
like collect songs I could possibly use as background
and add tags to like label their aesthetic elements
and I gave up
I don't have an organized system or anything, anyway, sorry again
well, I guess I'll talk about my writing style
because it's quite regimented now
what I have, I have a Google Doc called Video Ideas
and every time I have an idea for a game that I want to talk about at some point
or something, I go in there and I just write it down
in a big long list
and whenever I start to write it
I make another Google Doc and then link to that Google Doc in the Video Ideas document
so I have a big old thing where I can scroll through
and see which, I highlight which ones I finished
which ones I've recorded the audio for
and which ones I just need to edit
and I've got a whole big thing of that
hey, can I ask you a question about your process?
I'm just curious, if you're like me in this one aspect of
when I'm writing a script
and I thought that you're more like this than anybody else I think
when I'm writing a script, I find it extremely hard to write anything
that I think will actually be funny, like any real jokes
but when I'm editing and I have like my fairly serious voice
it's really easy for me to just put something retarded
and it's hilarious, like juxtaposed against the fairly serious things I'm saying
do you do that too? Is that where you get most of your humor?
I think, well I do write a lot of jokes into my scripts
like if I just look at a script now
I would put in Asterix how I would edit something to be funny
like pause for effect, zoom in on this guy's face after I say
oh dear, I actually write that into the script as I'm going
like that'll sound good
sometimes the live action stuff that I record
doesn't actually work in the way that I intended it to
or the way I wanted it to
but when I am editing I can sometimes make it better
like some of the live action sections in that Rayman video
I didn't like them, but I added some weird effects and then they were funny
but you know, more funny than not
there's a lot of changing things as it goes along to make it flow better I experience
so the way I do the reviews, I mean it used to be different
for Dark Cloud I didn't play the game at all
I just knew it so well that I wrote the entire thing
and then played the game to get some footage
but nowadays obviously it's a better idea to play the game
and take notes
if you've ever watched AVGN
he has a video where he goes through his editing process
called I think he does like a pixel just a random game
and he goes through the entire process of playing the game
writing the review, editing it and all that
and it's really interesting and really informative
so you should look at that AVGN
making of an AVGN episode
and I based a lot of how I write scripts and take notes off of that
especially for GRPJ
I think, no not GRPJ
I can't remember what I do
Or the miniscule review?
No miniscule reviews are just sort of like I just write about it
and I don't really
the thing about miniscule reviews is that there's no live action
there's no big skits
it's just sort of me being a goof and playing a game
Those are probably the most like traditionally
probably would be successful YouTube videos
If I could make loads of those all the time then I would
I'm always trying to make a big hypocrite video
How hypocritical of you
Not really
You really are the best guy ever
Oh no
But yeah, I write down things
Oh, specifically regarding game footage
because making a video game review is harder than anime
in the fact that you have to get footage for everything you're talking about
Oh yeah, yeah, totally
So I would only try to write notes on stuff that I'm actually doing
So I would play the game something like Rayman
I would record like level one
the whole level through and then stop recording
so that I have a file of that level and just name it that level
and then continue playing
and every time there's like something particularly like
if I need to look at a walkthrough
for a certain part that's hard
I write down in my notes this part's really hard
this is the link to the walkthrough that I'm looking at
in case I need to take a screenshot and put that in
Interesting, early on into me making video game related videos
especially back then when I didn't have a very powerful computer
where editing with files that were very long at all
just completely choked up the editing software
It's really annoying to scrub through a whole like two hour thing
I always try to split it
I was not very good at scrubbing either at the time
so I was just splitting the recording up every like two to five minutes
like every time it felt like I was doing a different thing
I would break it up and make a new recording
and then when I was done
after writing the video
think about the different dynamics of the game
that I'm going to talk about
and then look at each of the individual clips
and put them into folders corresponding to the different things
like hey this clip shows off the level design pretty well
this clip shows off the main villain pretty well
put them in their respective folders
and that's how I did that
but I haven't really made any video game videos in a long time
I don't even know how I would do it now
see that's quite a clever thing to do
because what I do with just having a level
usually what I'm writing the script
I'm like I go through level by level things that happen
so I'm sort of walking through the game as I analyze it and stuff
but sometimes I can't find a particular moment in a thing
but I know it's in A level
so I just go to that level and I still have to scrub sometimes
quite a bit
if I had the patience to put things into specific folders
so I could just instantly grab them from there
that would be pretty good
to comment on this
because obviously I'm not as known for doing game videos as you
but I have done a number of them
and it's funny because my process is like
almost entirely built out of desperation
to do as little work on it as possible
because I hate editing
smart way to go
and I hate capturing footage
because when I play through a game
it's usually like I don't usually play a game intending to analyze it
like most of the games that I have written about
I had the idea after the game
and then it's like there's no fucking way I'm going to play through the whole thing again
to capture the footage
but I need enough
I need enough to work with
so I'll use like
I'll use as much let's play footage as I can find
if I'm talking about specific moments
if it's like
this boss is super hard or whatever
I'll just grab a let's play
and it's kind of funny to me
that gaming YouTubers
seem to be so
proud in particular about capturing their own footage
and about having it be 60 frames, 1080p
which is a lot that I don't do
I don't care about that
I mean when it comes to the footage
me recording it
it's mostly just because I have done the whole
let's look at let's plays and get the footage
it's easier thing
but it's so frustrating when
they don't have the specific moment
that I'm looking for
or like the videos
all the let's plays are like really bad quality
or like one of them is a low quality
but it has the bit you need
and all the high quality footage
doesn't have what you need
I've gone through that
but like for me
I mean I don't fucking care
like if it's low quality for like 10 seconds
I don't care
you know because the audience
isn't going to
they're not going to say anything
you know I've never had a complaint about it
and I get why like for guys like
hyper bit hero and gaming Brit and stuff
you know they want the 60 frames
because they really care about that stuff
those guys they're fucking 60 frames per second
they're so into the idea of
like all games have to be 60 frames
and I have to prove it through my
I hear that if you kill yourself in the name of video games
you go to heaven in art
and live in a giant bed with 60 virgin frames
it's like they think that by
is a virgin frame a frame with no picture in it
they think that by like putting the 60 frame
1080p video on YouTube
that that's going to help like sell people
on that but the reality is
that fucking 99%
of everybody is watching it windowed
in 720 you know
we're not fucking upscaling it
60 frames makes my fucking computer chug
even on you know because YouTube's horribly optimized
for it so like
I'm not going to fucking watch a video in 60 frames
I'm not even going to play the game in 60 frames
but like when it comes to me
collecting footage for a video like when I did
the Bloodborne vs Dark Souls
player character one it was like
most of the Dark Souls footage was from
me and Victor's Let's Play of Dark Souls
which was shitty looking in itself
because I had bad encoding for a lot of it
and then I like you know grabbed like
cutscene footage from different
Let's Plays and stuff or just cutscene uploads
on YouTube and then like for Bloodborne
I captured a bunch of me like
testing out all the weapons
so because I like really needed footage of like
somebody just using weapons and stuff
but like it was just you know
maybe 10 minutes. Luckily the PS4 makes that
pretty easy with this whole recording thing
well that thing sucks
because you can only record 15 minutes at a time
you get to start a video and it's fucking retarded
but I have an Elgato so it doesn't matter
so yeah I recorded like probably
like 20 minutes worth of
my own footage for that and then you know
pulled again cutscene footage and stuff from
online so like for me it's just like
how can I possibly edit this
with as little of me recording
and like as specific of me recording as possible
so I don't have to scrub through anything
and you know I'm willing to show
really non-specific shit
you know just like I'm because a lot of my videos
are like me rambling about broad concepts anyway
so it doesn't need to be like a specific boss
or something but like yeah
there's like a sense of when I edit
there's a sense of desperation to be like
I just want this fucking thing to be
out I want I don't want to have to go through
you know a huge
part of why I have DeVoo edit my videos
and we'll get to this when we talk about
his editing process as well
is that DeVoo will
I'll have him watch an entire
show for a video you know
it'll be like um here's
Mob Psycho we just watched the whole show together
he goes and edits it and he puts
all 13 episodes of the show
into a thing and then he
edits it what I do
is any episode
that I mentioned something that
like from that episode I take
that like let's say I mentioned that there's
a certain bad guy who does this
so I'll download the episode where that guy's
from and I'll put that in there
everything else is episode one
like or episode two sure
it's just anything you don't need that
bit yeah that's totally anything that's not
specific is just gonna be from episode one
so that I don't have to edit every
you know I don't have to go through every episode looking for
stuff but that I mean
clearly what DeVoo's doing makes a better
product you know like that's why I hire him
to do it because he pulls scenes
that I would have forgotten about or just
not bothered with whereas for me
like often times by the time I'm done editing
an anime video I have used
all of the good parts from episode one
like I have gutted that thing to death
you know and
and probably there's like
some 30 second chunk of the episode
that just isn't edited at all
somewhere in there you know like for me
it's like how can I maximize
impact with minimal effort
but you know it's funny you
if you can see like the way my files
look I have you know in Vegas
how you can put those like orange lines
with like a message indicator of like
or a tag or whatever I discovered
my talent is fucking full of like
specific things that need to go here
here here here here for a full fucking
that's I discovered that kind
of Vegas note taking because
of Neil X when he was doing the
elements of Brony series
I had to render those for him
because like his computer his laptop
was weak and he needed it for work
and he was like rendering those on a fucking
laptop yeah and he was like
you know rendering this will
literally seize up my laptop all day
I won't like I won't even be able to use it
so he would send me all the files
on copy which is like a
Dropbox alternative
that is dead now dude that was
my fucking the first
Gern Langen video the music one
I made that whole thing on a laptop too
and that fucking thing like Vegas
it was too long I used like clips from
like fucking a hundred episodes like
two movies they were all in the timeline
all to be loaded every time I opened it
it was like a ten minute process just waiting for that thing to load
and after a while the fucking thing would not
play in the fucking preview window
so my tests for editing were
to render the section
see if it looked okay if not okay adjust it
render it again see if it looks better
that's why that video took six months
to fucking make
anyway I know what that's like
well sorry a point I was making about
Neil is that he would send me
like all of his project files which is these
huge folders cause those
videos were the longest shit and they had tons and tons of sources
and he would have just like
shit loads of like notation
markers with like you know full sentences
in them like huge descriptors
like everything cause
Neil is a fucking lawyer you know he's
like a study guy
he knows how to take notes and shit
and like you open up his book
and it looks like fucking Twilight Sparkles
annotations on a
fucking book you know it's crazy
how much stuff was in there I was like I didn't know Vegas could
do this stuff and to me
it's also pointless cause I'm like
I don't need this organization I can just
memorize what everything is you know
but I guess for some people it's
more necessary
yeah you're a genius did you
we're all just a bunch of fucking fuck boy
idiots that's alright I agree
I agree I just have good memory
but um whatever
what was I saying oh yeah um
in relation to like
forgive the fucking ten minute tangent
yeah I fucking
oh yeah Nate the
thing you were saying about every
video about something you love having to
or whoever said it being
something you love you can't you have this feeling of
you have to talk about
everything properly and stuff
that's how I think that
the way I write and the way that the fact
that I record the gameplay
is because I need to make sure
that I'm right about whatever I'm about to say
so if I do
my Ratchet and Clank video
like I played the whole game again
and I record it and you know while I'm playing it
I might as well record it so I have the footage of what I want to talk about
and I play
the whole thing again just to make sure that yes
that is true what I'm saying
dude there is nothing more devastating
for every miniscule review any miniscule
review is like a game that I'm not that interested in
and I can make a short video and I can leave
out a lot of analysis and it's mostly
just me just
talking about something very vaguely
but the hypocrite reviews
they're usually long because
I want to make sure that everything I say
is real
there is nothing more devastating than putting
something in a video that turns out to be
wrong in any way and
this is also what I'm
bad about this because I judge people
extremely harshly if they get
anything wrong in their videos too
when I said that Nio was 14
or when I said Yoko was 14
people were like no she's not what are you talking
about dude and this consumed
me for like a month and I had to do
an in-depth research campaign because I realized
I actually had not investigated this
thoroughly enough to make that claim but in
time I was proven out to be correct
I believe I found the proof for you
it was on some website or something
some developers
you were looking for it and I got interested
and what I found was the official
the official Gurren Lagann website
in Japanese
when you translated it
it said Yoko is Simon's age
it specifically says
something like that
I remember we had a big argument
because there's two uploads for that Gurren
Lagann video the first one that's in my
playlist of deleted videos or whatever
because it got fucked up by copyright
there's a comment thread in there
that's like the full discussion about
that
oh god yeah
in regards to being wrong about stuff
and like playing through the whole game
to make sure you're not wrong about stuff
it's funny because
unlike Nate I play very fast
and loose with facts
and when people point out something wrong
like if it's something I agree
is wrong I just kind of like
upvote their comment and comment on it
and I'm like oh yeah good point
and if it's something that like
because I'm very obstinate about the idea
that like it doesn't matter to have everything
right as long as you get the point
you know as long as the overall video
is not wrong then that's what matters
this is something I've disagreed with you
for a long time about Digi don't you feel
a sense of journalistic integrity
to need to represent those correctly
there is a phrase there is a phrase in the
journalistic world called you don't get
the facts you get the truth
now I don't know how many journalists follow
along with that but if I may speak on behalf
of Digi's research process
that seems to be something that he does
can you break that down for me
when you tell stories of things that happen
you usually tell a fairly condensed
version where things are a little bit
flanderized well the reason they say that is because
you can't really know
all the facts about everything
like there's always going to be some detail
that maybe like if you're trying to talk about
say you know what the messages is
of Gurren Lagann for instance
like unless the creator
outright says like that's what I intended
then it's not so much that
you're saying like a fact about it
as you're you know talking about
what it makes you think and what
what you think it's about
it's not so much whether or not you're able to present
this overwhelming symphony
of evidence that makes you look infallible
it's more important that no one
in the comments is able to
create this symphony rebuttal that makes you
well that's fine and all
the thing is like
if you're basing your opinion
on something that you say
and it's actually incorrect
then people will call you on that
but like if your point is
this show is good because of the action
but you said the name of a character wrong
this show is good because of climate change
but if you say the name of a character wrong
that's not devaluing your point
your point is still correct
the point of that video was
obviously my interpretation of things
but if I had said Nia was 14
and Nia was just wrong
then that's a whole different thing
but the thing is that the reason
you were talking about her
whether or not she's literally 14
didn't matter
the point is that she's Simon's age
that she's around that age
that she's you know
relatively 14
is like what matters
not that she's literally 14
the argument that follows is based on that fact being true
I say she's closer to Simone's age
because it's a thematically relevant
because it's about her not being like Kamena
she's closer to Simone
she's like more mature
and you know that would still be true
if she was like 16 or even 18
I guess
but the things are predicated on getting your facts right
and if you get your facts wrong
and then you have faulty interpretations
then you're just misleading people
and I'm not saying that you're evil
I'm just saying it's your responsibility
I have definitely had
like frequently
I have just like outright
incorrect facts in my video
and people will point it out
but like usually
I mean it never creates an uproar
it's never destroyed a video
at worst one guy gets mad
and leaves a comment about it
and I laugh at him for being a comment
this is actually a large motivating factor
for why I'm interested in making videos
in a series as opposed to one standalone obelisk
because if I get something wrong
like the first one like YMS did
in his review of
Synecdoche New York I think
then like in the next video you can say oh by the way
maybe guys I saw you commenting about this
I got this a little wrong or
I just want to clarify this point
something like that is a very useful tool
I did that in the SAO2 video
I made this pretty glaring mistake
in the original and I corrected it in the sequel
but I also made the defense in that video
that like you know yeah I got this wrong
and I shouldn't have got it wrong
but the point I was making
stands like
it didn't matter that I was wrong about that
in the grand scheme of what I was trying
to say about Kirito
I just think it is such a valuable thing
to like to be able to say that to
to be able to show like I have
seen your arguments on this particular point
and created you know a rebuttal to it
or an opinion and doing like a multi-part series
like that is the perfect way to handle it
I really wish it was easier to like
on YouTube to keep
at it or something
like you can always do
a follow-up video but it's always
going to have way less attention
given to it and like
I mean it's nice to be able
I used to kind of like obsessively
want this but now I've just kind of given up
because I've gotten to that audience size where I just
it's unmanageable
where like if I make a video
that blows up and I make a small mistake
in it and then I were to make a follow-up
video where I correct that small mistake
it's cool that I've
recognized it and that it's out there
and I have my conscience is clean
but the number of people who are actually
going to go find that video
is so much less than the number of people who are just
going to keep commenting on the original about how I fucked up
you know it's like a newspaper retraction
like buried in like the depth of
whatever that says by the way that guy wasn't
the murderer it was the other guy sorry about that
please don't kill that guy to this day
new comments on my first
SAO video come out
that criticized that mistake
you know like yeah of course nobody reads
the comments so there's probably like several hundred
comments about that specific mistake
on that video even though I corrected it
two years ago you know
there's just no there's no victory
with that and so I've kind of given up
like I like to be able to address mistakes
but it's like you know
if you care that much read the fucking comments
cause yeah
yeah there's something to that argument I think
in that specific situation
there's probably just butthurt people who love SAO
so even if you did have a follow up
they wouldn't give you shit anyway so
yeah being butthurt doesn't make your argument invalid
but whatever this alright we've addressed this
I'm sorry Gib we interrupted you
in a big way
oh yeah I guess we're still talking about my stuff
yeah
I guess we could talk about
I have a question that could springboard you into something you can talk about
that we can't interrupt you on because I don't know the reason
I think you've probably addressed this somewhere before
but where did the
idea for the green screen just sitting around
on shit come from
cause that is the fucking coolest
idea
oh hang on you cut out for the idea
oh I think you said the green screen like effects
for a GRPJ and shit
where did you get the idea and just like I'm just gonna throw this on the ground
in a pile
it's fucking great
well I just thought
I mean I wanted to have
the whole thing with the GRPJ
it was supposed to be the least amount of editing
even though it's still quite intensive because I got to cut out all the stuff that I
like you know
the pauses and stuff
but I wanted it to be
as least editing
possible so I thought I'll just film myself
doing the whole thing
there but I thought that would be too boring
so I thought I'll put a thing in the corner
with the game footage
but I also thought I don't want to have to
edit the game footage to be that relevant
and
I didn't really care so I thought
well I'll put a green screen up
but I couldn't find a way to put the green screen up well
so I just threw it in the background
and from then on it became a meme
I'm just now I'm gonna
put things
creative ways you've been using green screen since then
and like other videos
is great
I would say it started before that
because on the give and take channel
then like there's been a long history
of these weird green screen
meme videos but originally
on an actual green screen he would just
remove all the green from
the actual footage
it'd be like him in the grass
outside and then remove all the green from the grass
and put another clip down there
even your rayman video
when you're like oh I'm gonna be rayman
so I just wear green sleeves
and key out my arm
it was fucking great
that was great and not even just
green screens but like your jump cut jack
video is fucking great
just you know it's actually
green screens I actually had a moment
where I watched jump cut jack back the other day
and like realized that
you created a sentence
through all those jump cuts
which means that like every position you got into
you had to say a tiny fragment of a word
right well what I did
I said the whole sentence and then
moved a bit said the whole sentence and then I spliced it
all together oh perfect still genius
I hadn't even thought about like
hey guys jump cut jack
back here with another fucking
video
it's genius
but yeah speaking of
live action we could talk about
the process for that because that is quite a lot
of extra bullshit though
I feel like I'm obliged to do
but I also enjoy doing it because
I can pull funny faces and that's funny
but it's
it's a lot of hassle having a camera and
lighting and getting a
no one understands how much fucking harder
it is to do live action that it is
to do footage and it seems
I mean like okay if it's a vlog that's
easiest thing in the world right turn on some
shitty lights and
point a fucking phone at yourself and record
but like if you're trying to make something look
good then it's not
just a matter of like
lighting yourself you have to
you have to basically become a director
because the lighting also
has to reflect the tone of what you're doing this is the huge
this is the big fucking problem I have with
John Tron like with his modern videos
is that he has like the
high budget set the high budget lighting the high
budget cameras it's all like pristine
and clean and beautiful but the
way that it's lit
is not fun he's making fun
videos with this like dour
cold lighting set
that does not look like a place somebody lives
and it's fucking weird
and like that's and that really detracts
from the comedy because it just feels like what the fuck
why are you on a set why aren't you in your house
playing video games that's what the narrative
is suggesting of the video
you know it's a weird
like it's not quite
awkward enough to be awkward funny
and it's not quite funny enough it's not quite
light-hearted enough to be a video game
romp
it's weird total garbage
and then you watch like hypocrites videos
and it's usually just like natural lighting it seems
like you just open like a curtain yeah
it looks like you're in your room
you know
because I can't really film anywhere else
but yeah the natural lighting
I always try to do that because I don't have
a big old bunch of lights
with stands and stuff so
I usually try to film during the day
when I have the window open and stuff
getting the light in
but for this Rayman video I had
a genius idea that nobody would have picked up on
obviously because I didn't show it
but you see my TV
the big TV on the thing
you might see in certain shots
in certain videos or whatever
and all I did was I got
a 1920 by 1080
picture of
just white
just ffffff white
put it on a USB plug that into the TV
and then just had that be on the TV
just a big white TV
thing and that lit me from the front
as I recorded
hey good thinking I've done stuff like that with
like when I'm recording a vlog I might turn up
the brightness on my monitor all the way
and just have that be like lighting for me
because
my house, my room especially
like even though my room has three windows
getting ffffking like natural lighting
is really hard because just the way the windows
are angled and my room is huge
and I usually film at night
and like lighting this fffking
room is impossible it just
swallows light like we would
do all this stuff and if you watch my older videos
where I had like you know vlogs or had myself
on camera in certain videos if you want to see the worst
look at the lucky star video
that's what happened when I tried to
light myself because
when Victor's around you know he does this
professionally and he'll take three lights
and he'll fffking set him up and he can make something
presentable but like when it's
me by myself trying to light myself
I can't see where the lights are pointing
on me I can't see where I'm
casting shadows I can't see
where you know if the camera is pointing at me
correctly I can't fffking adjust focus
on a DSLR on myself
because I have to lean forward
to adjust the focus and then lean back
I'm doing all that right now
it's fffking it's a huge pain in the ass
and
it sucks ass because it's
always gonna look shit
you can never make it look great
it's just gonna look like acceptable enough
that you can publish it but you can't make it look
great that way
and if you see that fffking lucky star
video it's like every single shot
the lighting is different and terrible
it's all every single one is
in a different bad way
sometimes I'm too blown out sometimes
the shadows are too harsh sometimes the casting shadows
on my face the framing isn't quite right
I just had the camera just out of reach
and that was with shade helping me like I had
someone helping but shade
doesn't know what the fffking is doing you know
so like if you don't have a crew
to help you film live action
segments then just don't
and that's why I don't you know
it's like something really brief or simple
or easy and thankfully my new
phone like can capture
just enough light that like I did a little
live action segment in my you know
high school anime video where it's
that was just filmed on my phone with just
the lighting of my room and it looks fine
because that phone could capture enough
but even in that shot the framing is slightly
off because I had to use the
outward facing camera which I can't look
at I can't see what it's filming
so I just kind of pointed it as best I could
to look at me but you know my chin's
a little too low my head's not quite
at the top of the frame and I'm a fffking
stickler for that stuff so
you know that fffking
a fffking CWC
lecture bended with
you know Victor camera-ing
and doing all the light it looks great
it looks wonderful you know
that was a shot I mean you can see in the three
if you watch the 360 version of that
you can see there's a whole fffking light
set up like there's like three or four lights
professional lights and Victor is
sitting up on a stool with this huge
tripod and this giant fffking camera
rig you know like it's it was
shot professionally
you gotta have a lot of patience to be a
cameraman just fffking sit there and watch
that's why I can't even do it like
nobody wants to watch you talk about
anime for ten minutes in your room
you know speaking of
cameras
I film all my stuff
on a camcorder and it's mostly
because I can turn the screen around and flip
so I can adjust myself see how I look
and I know I know Nate
you have a problem with this because you use a DSLR
dude let me just tell you I might the fffking
I can't remember the word again
I used my shitty DSLR doesn't
have a flip around you should have seen the fffking
process I went through like an hour of that
time was just focusing getting back
filming a little bit running back
watching it see if it was focused adjusting
doing it repeat that process for fffking hour
but I got it eventually what camera
I'll tell you afterward I don't know
a piece of shit that I don't like
it's like a rebel T2I right
I have a T2I right now
and I have found a way to solve this
problem very simply it will cost you
six dollars and you can fix this problem
let a stand up mirror
shop after this
it's fffking great
wait was it a stand up mirror
is that the six dollars solution
I mean that's one you could do too but I have another
I'll talk about when I talk about my video stuff
okay cool yeah great great
but yeah the you can
tell my camcorder quality camera
is not that great and I
could be using my dad's DSLR
because he doesn't use it that much
but you know I always choose
practicality for shooting over
the quality because when I record
my camera my camcorder is really terrible
for low light so when I usually
try to record it's during the day
and I only have a few hours especially in winter
when the days are shorter and I wake
up late and I'm like okay I got to do all this
I got to set up my mic just out of shot
so that it can pick up my audio
because my camera audio is terrible
I have to have that there and I have to
do the performances I have to do them over
and over again to get them right and I'm not
ever entirely sure how good they
are until I'm done oh and
my computer fffking my computer fan
is really loud you might be able to hear it
in my audio right now but
every time I record something
either just voice over
all my live action I have to turn my computer off
get my laptop out and put it on the other
side of the room and then plug in the things
from there so that there's no noise
and it's just like
20-30 minutes of setting up just to do
like 5 or 6 small takes and then move
the camera do a few more
it's a bitch I think your live
action segments come out great
because and that's what
I want to emphasize to the audience here is like
yeah Gibbons using a shittier camera
but you're using like Z optimal
circumstances for it and that takes
patience and time
it's like you can only film
during these hours of the day
during this certain time and like and also you
can't you know you couldn't film
like multiple takes of the same like let's say
you filmed uh like you saying
half a sentence and then hour later said
the other half the sun's in a different place
it looks totally different you know like you can't
fuck around too much with this stuff
and like yeah so the reason
Hippo is able to have stuff that still
looks good in spite of the equipment is
that patience that I don't have
because for me everything has to be like
instantaneous I need this video Don it has to be
on my desk by Tuesday I have to just
film it in the shit conditions I have
you know for all the videos
that I film in my
my cabin garage thing at the end
of the gun where you can see the drumset and all
that um that's
all like I have to stay down there for
2-3 hours because like
the Harry Potter one I do a lot of skits the
Jack and Daxter what all all those
things I do a lot of skits as well as
doing a lot of like talking to the camera
which I don't do anymore I tried not to do
any live action where I'm just speaking
because there's no point it has to be
either a skit or like a cutaway
gag to a visual of me doing a funny face
anything else is too
is too like there's
no reason for me to record that because it's just extra
work right and the hardest
thing is is not just
getting it all done but like trying to get it all
done at once because that's I can't
really do it the next day and if I do
it's sort of weird so I've got to do
everything in one go
and it's
hard to keep your voice going and to keep
energized and I'm like
by the end god like trying to match
a later voiceover with one you did
oh yeah it's impossible
that's that goes for voiceovers too I try
to do them all in one go and sometimes
my voice is not noticeably
like
haggard by the end of it and you might be able to
tell in some videos where I'm like
but I kept that in anyway because
I can't be bullet to do it again
because you're a goddamn professional
how many takes do you usually
like do you have to do multiple
takes on most lines or would you say it's like
only occasionally like
do you usually get through the whole thing in one sitting
well I usually
get through the whole thing in one sitting but I the
sittings are very long and how much longer
is the recording than what
the video is
let me think
I mean I do multiple takes
for every line at least one other take
just in case the first one wasn't bad
was bad sometimes I don't do
multiple takes and the take I thought was alright
doesn't actually sound good
and I'm like I hate me
but I mean I know Jesse
records like hours for each of his
yeah it's I mean for that
Rayman thing I'm trying to think
I mean the the session was like two and a half
hours but that was for part two as well
right so
it's it's a lot of extra time like
it's a ten minute video is probably like 45
minutes to an hour of
of doing the recording
Nate how about you
I definitely don't
do every line like I feel
like I have a pretty good sense for if I fucked up a line
and like if
I'm just going through I try to do the whole thing
in just one take and don't really worry if I got it right
if I did it wrong I'll just repeat the line
and then just place it in later and then like
I'm more inclined to try to get the thing
done reasonably good and then if there's
a problem after I put in Vegas and I'm editing
then I'll just do it over yeah usually what I
do is if I think the first
half of a paragraph I say is okay
and I find like I
like I mess up the second half I find
I think of the area where I could
splice in a second take of the second
half and then I just say that part
again instead of I do that too I
mean I definitely don't think
my method could work for Hippo because
your comedy is so much
about line delivery and it's like
there's so many moments in that Rayman
video where it's just the way you say a word
makes me fucking laugh what's the
eggplant but the other word for it
aubergine
what the fuck is an aubergine is that an eggplant
yes
well what the fuck why don't you say eggplant
because I'm not an American you
crazy boy
the machine sounds way funnier when you're
implying it also sounds French so
it's just like the British word or like
the European word for it or something
it's just the word that non-Americans say I think
man
like for me you're an inferior
race my recordings are usually
at most like two to five minutes
longer than the actual
video like it's just any
if I stumble over a line
I redo it but it's immediate it's just like
this time I was
wait this time I was
you know like
there are some lines that will stop me up
for a good 30 seconds or something
there's some little tongue twisters in my
scripts but it's all one go
and recently when I did
because there's five videos I have coming out
in November all of them being edited by DeVue
I've written them all before November started
wait five are coming out in November it's already
halfway through dog
alright there's already two out
oh I thought you meant they were all coming
no no no five total and
I had written them all before November and
like I had them all sitting there and I just
literally went into my closet
for two and a half hours and recorded all five
of them in one session so
if you listen to these five videos back to back
you'll notice my voice sounds the same in all of them
which is not normal usually I sound kind of
different in each video this one is just like
I fucking just
belted them out one after another and by the end
I was dead
yeah I really wish I could do that
yeah
but I don't think it would work for you
because it's the comedy would not
come through you know unless you
I love doing the uh
I love doing the script recording I just
wish that I produced scripts faster that I
could record and then do shit with
yeah it's always got it's always feels so good
getting getting a script done
is hell and I feel
great when I put the video when I record it
put it into Vegas and I start
to edit I'm like yes this is what I
was born to do being the editing process
and then of course a month later when I'm only
halfway through editing the thing I wish I was dead but
you know yeah
the way I do the editing
usually like I said I don't do the music
first I do the music last
what I do is I get my audio put it in
obviously and I put that that blue
background on and I basically
I cut every section where there's a live
action bit and you know
space them out really far and then I
just go through it
and then
first I put like the game footage
and then I leave like editing bits with
images and stuff for later
so I've got all the game footage and then
that's like the skeleton of everything the
skeleton of the review that's the
timings that it's going to be
not always though
I can see why you like making videos if it
involves skeletons
yes
the backbone
rattle rattle
first and then live action
and once everything is in place where
it's like I can reasonably say
this video is going to be a certain number of minutes long
then I will start
properly going over it I don't usually
do that I've tried to start
doing that like I'm usually I would
just go and do the finished
thing
but now I'm trying to
do like a first draft of the thing so
I go through it and I finish it
and then I know it's not done so I go over
it again and all that
yeah that's reasonable
yeah you know this highlights I think
a difference in the way I've seen Hippo
and Nate's editing based
on screenshots of their Vegas
timelines is that you guys
I believe just put in the full
recording of your narration and then
edit the audio as you go
true is that true yeah no I
edit the thing in
audacity and then if I need to
add pauses or
cut things out then I will edit
it in Vegas. I just remember seeing a screenshot
of one of your timelines and
the audio track had tons of cuts
constantly was that just you adjusting
for timing are you sure that was me
I'm not sure I saw one of you
but maybe not maybe I just
I saw Nate I thought it was you for one time
I mean I know that
I do eventually cut
the audio a lot but like
I just just to move
it around a bit like if I feel like this
this joke needs like
half a second of
quiet after it I will cut it there
and maybe it looks like a lot
I don't know the way I remember
ever posting my Vegas timeline
the way I do audio is like
you know I recorded an audacity
then I remove all the gaps and all the
mistakes and then it's just like this tightly
grouped thing that I put it in Vegas
and I add gaps back into it
then I like once it's all perfectly
formulated then I you know render that
and then put the full file in
and the reason is that I
I have a tendency I want everything to be
like as as unbroken as possible
because it's so easy to fucking
misplace things and move them around
without realizing it and then
you know then you've already made
a hundred more edits and saved
and you don't know what happened to that
audio file that was accidentally grouped
with some clip you deleted
and did you know I gotta
say you don't you use
Vegas still right yeah
for the for things like that
you could open a new Vegas
file and then drag
the old Vegas file into the new one
and then it will just be a continuous
thing so you won't have to render it at all
what do you mean exactly
oh like if you do the audio
editing adding the pauses in one Vegas file
and you drag that file into another
a new Vegas file it will become
a street like a single chunk of audio
yes in a premiere that is known
as sub sequences and
nested projects that is what I do as well
yeah I know Davoo's way
into sub sequences I need to do that
shit with Vegas because like I you know
what I do instead and this is retarded I should just
be this is why I need to use premiere it just is not
working with my fucking drivers I need to
re-steal it from the internet instead
of that I will like I'll take all the
I'll take the keyframes on like
two different tracks and I will just have
them be the exact same keyframes
between all the tracks and then sometimes
there's gonna be like ten fucking things
moving and that need to like expand
or like glide along a path
it's retarded it's the worst idea
okay well like if there's two things on the
screen and they need to move in the same way
what you should do is have them be part of
the same sub sequence and then animate that
sub sequence in a particular way
but what I've been doing instead for the longest
time just because Vegas doesn't make it easy
to do it the other way is I just
will keyframe those two with
the exact same keyframes you know so
moving together that you could make a sub
sequence to do that
well you know a Gibbs dad discovered it one day
I've recently learned
the I don't
I don't know why they're called not called sub sequences
maybe something else but nesting if you right
click a bunch of video and premiere
and you right right click
and there's a menu and you click nest
it flattens it all down into another
sequence what you can
holy shit yeah you just highlight it
right click nest and it becomes
its own video file that include
if you double click on that it goes to
all the files that you just squashed
and then you can move that
it's probably the same
thing but oh my god
alright and then you can move that as its own
thing what hippo just described is exactly
like what subsequences already are
so yeah you have
I know I know I've used premiere and I use
subsequences I just didn't know that existed
in Vegas but this is
I'm talking about premiere
oh well fuck it never mind
yeah no everything
for me I don't do anything fancy
within the events that I do
edit but like the reason that subsequence
thing with the audio wouldn't help me is that I
send all my completed audio files to DeVoo
and he edits it around
so yeah and he
usually doesn't do anything to the audio
it's just like a purely the unbroken track
unless I have to request something like
with the Kuroko no Basket
video where we later added in like chapter
headers and just had to split
all those up but I'm so fucking particular
about audio and
I'm teaching myself
to care less about audio
but at the same time it keeps getting more
complicated because like you know I've got
all this fucking great audio equipment
and I surround myself with it and I
criticize people on their audio and I'm like
I really want it to be perfect because
I listen to everything through
speakers through like a pretty good
set of speakers and I can
tell massively the difference
between audio quality of different things
but people who are on shitty speakers
can't and like Ben
had no idea
that his audio was worse than everyone else's
on the PCP he legitimately
did not know really yeah he had no idea
oh god so
all this time I failed as a father you know
he sounded like a tin can because he just
listens to it there was laptop speakers you know
or like the headphones he uses which are like
fucking stock
like iPod headphones
so
he's listening to it in garbage quality audio
so everyone sounds just as shitty
and but that's how like most people
do like most people don't have a nice
set of studio monitors or a
fucking $150 pair of headphones
most people are either listening to it like
on their cell phone or their laptop
and so like that's why so many people
can get away with having such shitty audio
like you know Jimquisition doesn't feel the need
to update his fucking audio quality
or movie Bob or something because
it's never been a problem for enough people
and like I've kind of
learned to accept that but then
fucking god damn like
because it used to be that
I wouldn't do vlogs because I had to set up
my fucking microphone you know it's like such
a pain in the ass to have the microphone just off screen
and but like you don't want it to be
intrusive in the video but then it's also
just a pain to set it up and all that it's like I just want to be able
to touch and go so I had my
Galaxy Note 3 and
that thing I was using the
inward-facing camera which looks like dog shit
but the fucking microphone
was on the inside so it sounded
decent and it has pretty good
like it kind of auto compresses
the audio so it actually sounds
pretty good comparatively
so I used that for all these vlogs
and stuff and then I upgraded
to the
you know first I had the Note 7 had to replace
that now I got the S7 Edge this
thing has a much better front facing
camera but the fucking microphone
is on the outside
and it records in stereo
and you can never whether you're recording
inside or outside you can never
have the audio levels of the left and right channel
be equal so the left channel will be
super loud and the right channel
will be super quiet so what I've been
having to do is then
like I put the whole file into Vegas
and then I'll split it into left
and right and then
because you can't do that in Vegas so I have to
render it as a WAV put it in audacity
split the left and right track make the left track
mono put that like render that
put that into Vegas this doesn't
take long it's just a pain in the ass
are you sure there isn't a setting to record
the audio in just mono
there's nothing like that on the phone I mean that's not normal
like mono recording
is mostly for high-end devices
it's not normal for stuff to even
offer that so which is fucking
sucks and it's just bizarre
yeah well it's funny too because I always
thought on the old phone I thought it was
weird that the microphone was on the front
facing camera because it seemed obvious
that you're mostly going to be filming other stuff
not yourself because most people are vloggers
this is the selfie age my friend you're going to be
filming yourself 100% of the time so now it's
just weird they put it on the other side instead
but like it sucks for me because
that audio will sound like dog shit
when I mix it that way like it you know
it's even worse than it would have been so
now I'm like well I guess I gotta
fucking hook up the microphone every time I want to do a
vlog again which thankfully I have a much longer
XLR cable than I used to so that's not
as much of a pain but
yeah that's like
it's just such a nightmare to do anything
why is everything
so hard
yeah that's
what it comes down to
so where were we
I was gonna
talk about
because we know the process
we have like what we do
but there's always that moment where we're like
I don't know what the fuck I'm doing
I'm stuck I don't know what I don't
feel like I know what I'm doing right now
and I try to alleviate that by writing
in the script ahead of time how I should
edit some parts or how I should
record some live
action bits like
like extensive notes like so that there's
no way that I could interpret it in
properly like two weeks later
when I'm actually doing stuff
but
there's always that moment where you're like
I
like
there's usually a process that you have to
come up with to get out of that or to just
keep going and for me
I don't really have one yet
some people they can find out ways to
like
just do stuff
when they don't know what they're doing
the most dangerous thing you can do in a moment
is like start a new video that you're interested
in and then you got two and like oh no
I never start another
well actually I do sometimes
make like a video that
hair thing that Voldemorty video
I made that because I just had an idea
the best thing you've ever made it's a sensation
it's got 11,000 views somehow
holy shit
yes
I just thought oh wouldn't it be
cool if I could turn my head into my heads
there while I was editing Rayman
so I just put Rayman on hold
I filmed it in five minutes
I put it up and I'm like okay now
back to editing I'm like wait a minute
no I should do something else I should
look at all my
all the comments in every single thing I've ever
ever made
you go down that rabbit hole but
why would you ever do that
I'm glad I have too many videos for that to even
be slightly viable
oh yeah every time I go to my
notifications there's like oh
there's a brand new comment on give and take
I better look at it
we're not over that hill yet we will one day
but right now
two years gone on a notification bell
but yeah
I really wish
it was easy to just keep
editing because sometimes you get on a roll
and it's great but a lot of the time
I'm not on a roll I'm just sort of like
forcing myself to get to a certain
point before the end of the day like I've been
writing on a pad of paper in front of me
every time I get to
today I was like okay
get to the two minute mark
of the Rayman part two and I'm almost there
but things came up
but every day I would
like okay I did that cross it off
now get to the five minute mark and I would just
that's kind of
helpful but sometimes I just
don't do it
with that whole getting stuck at parts
that's the period where I'll
just get up and go do something
I don't have a smoke or
fucking just do anything
to help me
you know jog my brain
and think of something that'll go there
what I usually do at the moment is
I've been going on pokemon go walks
with my brother
and it's been nice because it's autumn and the leaves
are falling and it's really beautiful
did you pokemon go to the poles
but I can't because I'm English
I'm English I'd voted
for trumpy spirit
now
Hippo are you about wrapped up with yours
you've been going for like 50 minutes now
can I quickly just bring up
a quick just say a problem I have
to selfishly bring up a problem that's different
from that that I have is that I constantly
running up to it's the end of the night
I now need to stop my productive
work and go to sleep so I can get up for my
wage slave job what I'm trying to say
is people help me help me
go to patreon.com
save me from this fucking life
I just want to make my videos and I know
you want them too so help me
that's my biggest problem in the world right now
okay moving on
Tom let's hear your writing and editing
process
if you can do debu first I'm like
and speaking of wage slave jobs I had to start
around to my job so all my audio is just going to echo
like fuck on an old abandoned building
it's fair enough
if you're still even here
yeah debu let's have you go for it
okay well you know in order to make a good
video you got to be at your computer
in order to be at your computer you got to sit
down or stand up or have some sort of pose
right now it used to be
I had like an office chair
that was like really old
like it was an old office chair from like the early 90s
and it just got so much it turned
them into such a concave
that my back was just hell
sitting in it so I had this other more
low-end office chair that
was okay but as the years
went on it just made my back
ache so much and what
a fascinating thing it is that you would interpret
this question to be addressing your
seating situation in terms of
how you make videos I'm sorry but please
go on yeah so
you know eventually I basically just gave up
on chairs all together there's really no chair
that's not going to make my
back hurt eventually unless it's a
$600 one like what did you
has but I haven't even tried that one out extensively
you know so like
in my room where I am right now
where I edit more
all of my like Saturn videos
or anything that's like easy
you know I just don't
have a chair I just sit on the floor
my computer is mounted on
my computer like
my monitor is on
my computer tower with a couple
of books stacked up to get it just
at the right height relative to my head
where's your keyboard though
well the keyboards either on the floor
or on my lap and I have a little
box where I put the mouse on
okay right now I have
said box then with more
boxes and then my microphone
stand which my microphone
is on in front of my face right now
so I use
boxes I don't use chairs or tables
I have one token
table in this room
that I put some things on but everything
else is on the floor a token
table in a room like cheese okay
yeah alright he had to have a table
in the room we all know that's a fucking
unnecessary right
watching all of this anime the weaveness
has been slowly creeping up into my mind
and I've found myself just sitting on the floor
yeah yeah like a fucking animal
in the other room in the like
living room area where the
where the advanced computer is which is
good for editing and has high power
and such you know I
I messed around with different seating
positions but then eventually
I I scooted
up this one like piece
of a couch how deep
are we going down this rabbit hole
that belongs to
Digi's family like they
Digi's family has this awesome
couch that has like 17 million
parts to it all of them are
excruciatingly comfortable right
if you go to the
the PCP 360 podcast
we're sitting on all of that
like Jesse and Nate and hippo
I believe all
sorry bed is coming into my room
fascinating they all
slept on those couches
right for a week
and it only started to get uncomfortable for them
eventually
so and I myself will sleep on that
if I want to like if I
am in the heat of editing a thing
and don't want to feel like I can take a break
and go to my room I'll just sleep on that couch
because it's close to
to my computer to my advanced
computer and
there's one little wedge of that couch
that was like in a totally different
section of the room that was close
to where my computer ended up being
and so I slided that little wedge
over and I sat on
that and you would think
that a couch piece would be
not good for editing video
but the the fortitude
of this material was such
that I could just like sit like
on the edge of it like a stool
and it would always be pushing me forward
and just such a way
that it gives me like the perfect
back position
without having to like force it to do
I'm sorry to interrupt but I mean we've got to also cover
like the floor situation like the table
situation I mean can we spend all this
time on chairs there's a lot of furniture
we need to address before you're done
let's chair
well I understand that
I mean it is important to be comfortable
it helps the process
because for me I mean there's a reason
why I've bought all this expensive
fucking furniture like
I sit in a $500 chair
I have a nice like a mattress
because when you
when you have to edit for 8 hours
in a day and your fucking
back starts hurting it is
just makes the whole process worse so
yeah comfort is important
right now I mean
I'm getting sort of the sense that this whole
chair discussion is not
like what you guys were expecting and I did
have more to say about the wedge
but if you want me to move on
it's perfectly fine
it's not a big deal
I mean it doesn't matter that this wedge has
improved my life exponentially
let's move on to like the more relevant thing
of course
so okay
I don't know what you guys are thinking about
the creation of videos I could talk about
the chime in on the whole audio recording
thing I have always
hated doing the audio recording
I mean I love the idea of doing it
but it never comes out right
I always get very frustrated
any amount of frustration I have
will ruin my line delivery
if I get too anxious
and I get short of breath
and it ruins it which just
creates a downward snowball spiral
in which it gets worse and worse
in which I have to attain a zen like
mental state to recover from it
and if I do an attempt
of a recording too many times
it's going to be ruined forever
I'll never be able to deliver it naturally
so I have a limited number of attempts available to me
I do not know how people like Jesse
are able to do so many attempts
and eventually come out with something perfect every time
he always does
he's able to channel his rage into these things I think
I guess so yeah
he said that like usually it's just
he kind of goes
it's not that he goes until he gets the one he likes
it's that he just goes and goes and goes until he's sick of it
and then often he'll pick like one of the first two takes
yeah it only works
with those two because you know you're about to do a hundred more
so you're able to do it with such
naturalistic motions
and you know it's interesting for the last several
videos I made that are like full on
scripts
it's pretty much always three attempts
it's like the first attempt is just to
start programming the rhythm
and delivery into my mind
then I listen to it and hate it and throw it away
then do another one which is like
too unnatural because I'm a little bit tensed up
then
I snap myself
and I break
and then in that broken state
with the broken brilliance rather as you might call it
I am able to do a third attempt which is
more acceptable
is that done for every line or like for the whole
script? no no no I go through the whole thing
once, twice, then the third time
yeah important thing to talk about
that me and DeVu sort of discovered
once I started getting him to edit
is that
one of the things I've been having DeVu do is
like edit these scripts that I wrote ages
ago that like I just
never got around to making the full video
because either I thought it would be too much
effort or I just like
I didn't finish it because I knew it would
be too much effort so for instance
like the Yakiuki Shinbo in the 90s video
like most of part one was
written last November
or so and then like I kind
of finished it up recently and what I found
is that if I sit
on a script for too long
I have no idea how to read it anymore
because you're a different person
well it's like when I'm writing
a script I have a certain
rhythm that I'm reading it back
to myself in you know like I know
the rhythm of the post as it's going
and yeah it's based on
whatever my writing voice is at the time
whatever kind of thing
I do then and I
don't know what that is anymore
that's kind of what makes me think that
he's got a backlog of tons of scripts but I don't
think he's ever going to make any of them
just because he's no longer the man who wrote them
and doesn't care anymore
and I mean a lot of them are he rewrites
you know in like insight doing a different
video about the same subject I mean he's
mentioned that he's written like 15 different
Evangelion videos over time
he keeps trying to do it
but never you know feeling right
about it but yeah
I was going to say that
the way I write
it never really seems to
to go that way
if I write something months ago
or if I start writing it like
loads and loads of months and then I finally
get to the part where it's finished and I can record it
as long as I've written like
like a little notes on how
I should inflect like
if I'm going for a specific
type of voice that I had
in my head at the time like
it's like John Tron from this particular video
this particular scene like I would write that
as a note next to the
part where I say that so that I know oh yeah
and then I can just I can
you know it's always
it never feels weird to come back to a script
for a long time because of that
for me it'll be like this whole
like the whole cadence of the script doesn't
make sense to me anymore sometimes like
the worst example was this video that I was
working on early last year
that was supposed to be
a movement in the Legend of Zelda
franchise where I was going to do like a whole
project where I played through every Zelda game
and like analyzed the way that the character
moves the way you do all your attacks and stuff
and I wrote part one which is like
20 minutes long and it covers the first
four games and
like even at the time it was
kind of a stilted and awkward script
like it was a little too stiff but
you know I had recorded it
I had uh
delivered it or whatever but then I
redid it again like like a year later I went
through and I rewrote parts of it because I wasn't satisfied
with the overall writing but then when I tried to
voice this new version it just
felt like this fucking Frankenstein monster
of a script and like I came off as this weird
like I was doing almost the Digibrony
voice of like way too
high pitched and like like a salesman kind
of thing because I don't really know what I'm reading
I feel like I'm reading somebody else's lines
that were written for me as opposed to a script
I wrote for myself and so
and you can see this too in the Shinbo
video and like you probably hold on for
no we got to go on the record
that the Shinbo video was where you learned to
defeat this at least for
temporarily you know you have a number of videos
that you wrote then you read them
like a year later and you sent them to me
and often we just redid the audio
for them we did another take to try and get more natural
and the voice you were often doing was like
you know Guts from Berserk
is an interesting anime
protagonist and it was like kind of awkward
but the Shinbo one is where you
created a new persona
to match this confused state
where like it's this weird like dub character voice
like ah you can Shinbo in the 90s
he has got this
not intentionally I assure you
it was unintentional but it was like
it felt more right and natural
I'm sure you can defend it
as not being a terrible read
but like nonetheless it has this
it has this issue whether it's like a problem
or not that there's a definitive
moment and you probably
wouldn't be able to find it unless I told
you like exactly where it was
like I don't think it's so blatant
but like after I talked about Hurricane Palomar
the stuff after that is what I'd written
later like and
there's like if you listen to the
early part of the script it's like I start off
every second real or every sentence
really high like Akiyuki Shinbo
and then he went to this studio
and I know exactly what you're talking
about Digi for some reason I always
end up going into a sentence really loud
the first time and I don't know why
and then like if you listen to later
in the video it suddenly feels way
more smooth and natural like the last
five or six minutes are like totally different
and that's because those have been written more recently
so yeah I really try now
to like if I write a script
let's try to get it voiced before too long
I mean it really takes a long time
for it to be that awkward like these are both
scripts that were a full year you know between
writing and and and reading
so I'm like a totally different writer
at that point but um
well you know aside from the whole
voiceover aspect of it I often get
because I'm working on projects for so long
and I know that you've gotten over this
Digi by just working faster
to like you get to a point
where everything that you're saying
in the video feels like of course
like obviously all these things are true
like why am I even making this
like I have not gotten past that
that's actually it's a big part
of why I like
handing things over to DeVoo
because usually it's the moment
when I've listened to it
back like when I've edited the audio
and then I listen to the audio back
that's the moment when that happens
that's the moment where it's like I've internalized it so much
that I no longer understand
if this is actually interesting or not
and like you know I'll be pacing around
my room listening there's there's a lot of scripts of mine
where I listen to it back and I'm just like
I don't even remember if this is good
and then I'll send it to DeVoo and he'll be like
this is the best thing I've ever heard and I'm like great
edit it because like
this project is really complicated
that involves me personally going over the script
several times like I always
almost always read the
post before I hear the audio
so that I can like get more of a sense of the
feeling of the pacing of the script
then I listen to it in some videos
are more complicated like aesthetic is
narrative that's one where I listen to it
a bajillion times over the course of making it
and I never had this moment of
maybe this isn't very good because
it's not my ego on the line
I'm able to distance myself
from the potential doubts
that was definitely one of the videos where like
every step of the way I was questioning it
like even you know
like up until people were commenting
that they thought it was great
I was still like I have no idea if this is
even comprehensible like the whole opening
segment is so esoteric that I was just like
I don't know if anyone's going to get this
if anyone's going to know where I'm coming from
the video was way more successful than it had
any right to be granted I put
the thumbnail but I remember
thinking like on the day I released
Girl Logging Part 2 like everyone is going
to fucking hate this it's going to be so
shit and no one's going to give a shit
and yet that was that was not the case
alright anyway let's let's move on
well what else you got to do
let's see um I could talk about
the specific editing
of doing a specific thing
putting a specific item
in a video how about that
you want to hear that yes
let's see we'll use the example
of like having an image that pans
into the screen during a couple of seconds
so like you know imagine I go
this game is almost as good as
peanut butter jelly sandwiches
and I'll get a picture
of a peanut butter jelly sandwich preferably one
with a uh an alpha background
meaning there's no background you know
if I can't find one I'll just open up
Gimp and you know isolate the color
white get rid of the white no background
so I put the image
into Premiere and
I then drop it from the library
of Premiere onto the timeline
now at the bottom of the timeline
there's going to be footage of the video game
and I'm going to put
peanut butter jelly sandwich image above
that so that way you see
a peanut butter jelly sandwich image
in front of you and the video game footage is behind
you but I don't want the peanut butter jelly
sandwich to just appear out of nowhere
you know sometimes that's good
sometimes you want the image to just snap it
in the middle of the screen all at once
sometimes you want a little bit more
of a smooth delivery
let me guess did you click
opacity well I could do that
but and for this example
I go to the X value
which for people who don't know
the X value is your horizontal position
we're going deep
I'll drag it left
words so that the peanut butter jelly sandwich
careens off of the screen
so it's no longer visible
now I then decide
a big mistake
you're going to go off the right side
with emotion like this I can tell you
emotionally with the peanut butter sandwich
it's always going to be from the right side
I will not question any specific details
that you would want to iron out
so take Nate's word on it for stuff like this
you know so
I try to decide
how long exactly
at what point of my audio delivery
do I want the peanut butter jelly sandwich
to be involved right like do I want it
to start scrolling in
during the this game
is almost as good as
or do I want it to start scrolling in at
peanut butter jelly sandwich
right so
I'll arrange the image
to be at exactly the point I want
and then I do have an actual
point about that is the timing
about like you've got to
take into consideration how
long it will take people
to process the image that's on screen
because when you're editing something
and you cut it to like
okay that's enough footage
and then you cut to the next thing
sometimes it's not enough time and you have to
make sure you watch it over like
oh yeah I can comprehend this and then
people will know what it is
before I move on
I was watching one
of my earlier videos
the mini clip one and there are certain parts
where I just cut way too quick
obviously because I didn't rewatch it properly
now there were like what I'm just curious
about what you think you did that with
do you
do you remember offhand anything that you thought was too
fast
I mean there's a lot of
parts in the mini clip video there's
alright fair enough
but it was just certain points where I was like
there's even one part where I
cut off the beginning
of the next sentence by like
half a syllable and it sounds a bit
weird oh so you mean like audio wise
well that's interesting audio and visual
I only ask because the current thing I'm editing
right now like basically a hundred percent
of it is exactly dealing with this
issue of like I'm trying to convey
these these ideas
with these visuals like as
as as efficiently as possible
while being able to like get the entire
like section
of information and like this sounds confusing
but like when you see the video in like two weeks
it'll make perfect sense but it's really
it's a struggle to manage like how long
and at what point you remove
an image or put it there so that they can digest
it and understand like what it means
that's like when I when I edit
with like images on screen that's like
what I spend by far the most time on is
like going back and watching it over
and over again and trying to figure out the timing because
the the other problem is you already
know the information and this is
the thing that's the thing with text
that's the hardest because you can read the text
faster when you already know what it says
so like I always
I always kind of like read it
like relatively slow like I like
read every word to myself
and then I I go like half a second
more than that you know to account for
like people who are slower readers than me and I'm
not the fastest so you know
I feel pretty confident about my text
speeds but I leave it for like just long enough
that I'm confident you can read it but even
then you know a lot of people aren't fucking
really paying attention at the
you know when when the text looks like they're not ready
for text to start appearing and then have to have to
have to read and engage in the video
there was one moment in my Rayman
video where I did the Paninkoic
style thing with the music and
and I had the
graph with Rayman and I had text on there
but it didn't really tell you anything you didn't already know
but I can tell like it's a bit too quick
for people to not want to pause
part of the joke
yeah that's the thing and you know it's interesting
I've been watching a lot of like
Mr. Donut the Donut
and he does a lot of like Jojo
and V's and I've been taking note
of his technique where he'll
he animates a lot of Jojo manga panels
and I'll have a panel come in and he'll do things like
just like have like
there'll be a sentence in it but what he'll do is on the
same side like on the opposite side of the screen from the panel
he'll like just have the words
like the crucial words like
he attacked and they'll be like
big and like ballooned out of the thing
despite like the sentence on the
right side had a sentence that included those words
but he's like emphasizing them
by showing them separately and it's an interesting technique
and I've been taking inspiration from it
so okay you know the thing I was saying
before about timeline positioning
there was actually a useful point
I was trying to make there
but then as I started making it I realized that
it's only something that people who have
edited lots of videos before or at least a couple
will understand so I started
like going into like exhaustive details
so that you could follow along otherwise
but I'm gonna give up on that alright
so forget about it
if you don't know video editing at all
you're not gonna understand this
so you know when I started making videos
and like wanting to have a peanut butter jelly sandwich
on the screen I would be like this constant
back and forth of like trying to adjust things
and move things around here and there to get the timing right
to get the positioning right all that kind of stuff
and it just felt like I was going back and forth
so there's a very simple layered
method of positioning things
and getting down those keyframes
so first I decide how long
it's going to be in the timeline right
I decide when it's going to come into existence
and when it's going to lead from existence
and then
I decide when the keyframes
will begin and end like
you know this game is almost as good as
I know that it's going to begin
moving at the
and then it's going to end at the
peanut butter jelly
that's gonna be where
it is done careening into the screen
so I make two keyframes
at the puh and the eh
and then I decide how it's going to leave
like sandwiches
that's when it's going to begin leaving
new keyframe then
like a half second after the
ends that's when it will be done
leaving the screen so I now have the
four keyframe positions and then
that is when I decide
where the thing is actually going to be positioned
into like where it's actually going to be
coming from and where it's going to be going
oh so you sort out the timing
before you sort out the position
I guess I will probably decide the default positioning
that way I don't have to adjust
every keyframe afterward you know
and this is not a strict
method but that's like hypothetically
that's a way to do it I'm getting
the truth not the facts here by the way
like that's how I'm
the best that's what I'm doing here
so uh yeah
all that aside I wanted to
like I want to ask about this because
when I watch Davoo edit
even though I'm pretty sure he's ultimately
doing something similar to what I do
which is to pull a bunch of clips from a show
and put them in a timeline
the actual way of going about it
is like radically different
and it's fascinating
because when I walk by and I see
to be editing this is what it sounds like
this is the sounds coming out of his computer
it's a constant like
and then I said to him
and then I said
like he has the audio
coming out at all times
and he's like scrolling back
through the timeline and you can hear the audio
being like fast forward and re-winded
interesting I just pause
and then I skip back and locate all the syllables
peanut butter
sandwiches you know
and then you also
you do the same thing when you're looking for clips
like you scroll through the footage
well I would like it
if it didn't happen then
what Digi's referring to is
maybe a 20 minute episode of THING
and then I'll show
some scene from 3 minutes in
and I still have the other 17 minutes
of the episode still sitting there
on the timeline I gotta deal with
so then maybe Digi's next sentence
addresses something that happens 11 minutes in
so I gotta go find the 11 minute mark
so I'll scroll through
and you know something like that
I wish it didn't make audio then
I wish there were a feature
where the
you can stop after like the first couple of like minutes or so
um yeah
wait DeVoo
you use a premiere
why don't you just
double click the footage
and have it be in the preview window
I do a variety of all of them
so I never get tired of one or the other
you know one thing I would love is if you could like
punch in like a timeline code
and you would skip to that position
of the timeline of that specific item
which I know you can but not very efficient
I use the preview
box or whatever it's called
because it has the whole thing in there
from start to finish and you just say
11 minutes in you can easily see where that is
I believe that's what I do most of the time
but I believe it even then will do the max
headroom audio even if you do it that way
so what's funny to me about it
is that like the way I select clips
is I'll throw the whole episode into
Vegas like somewhere way down the timeline
and then like
if you grab the edge
of a clip and drag it
then that you know cuts into it
and if you're looking at the preview window
you can see everything you're
cutting into it's like if you if you grab the edge
and let's say you move it 30 seconds
to the side you can watch those
30 seconds in the preview when gosh
that would be very useful so
so yeah so that's what I do is I just
I just grab the edge of the clip and then I just
keep scrolling until I find what I want
and then I you know
that works in Premiere as well
yeah you don't need to hear the audio
yeah and then I just I just take that that whole
I take the whole like let's say
we're not here to like correct Davoo's technique
I'm not describing my technique
you're gonna have to show me what you mean
I may very well do that already
yeah like I
you know let's say the clip I want
is two minutes into the episode so I throw the whole
episode into Vegas I grab the edge
of the clip and I just scroll until
I see that moment I want
then I drag the entire episode you know
into the timeline that I'm using
you know hit play until it reaches the part
I don't want hit cut and then I just move
that I move the entire rest of the episode back
out to the far edge of the timeline
and then I just keep doing that like I keep just
scrolling through and finding the things I want
but I absolute I
I cannot fucking stand
to hear like any audio
at all from anything happening in my timeline
I don't want to hear my voice I don't want to
hear the clips I don't want to hear anything
like you know I play music over all the editing
so I just I don't want to hear it
it drives me crazy it drives me crazy
edit if you don't know what you're hearing
I mean I can like I just have it
like you know I don't have music in my
videos so it's just my voice
so you know I just you can hear your voice
over the music I have the music turn
pretty low you know
and then I just but everything
is based around like I always edit based around
the exact length of a sentence so it's just
the clip starts when the sentence
starts the clip ends when the sentence ends
and that's how I do it so
which is pretty simple
and it just
it's all about minimizing how much like
I have to hear it and stuff
because I don't want to hear it
it drives me crazy
I just want to explain the way that I select clips
because it's very specific and it uses shortcuts
that might be helpful for people
I have my videos in the side
and you know for levels and stuff
I click on one when I know
that I need a clip from that level
and a lot of the time
if I'm talking about something specific I would
have written down in my scripts
the timecode for when that happens
in the video
so I would go to that I would find the thing
and I would press the I key which is the in button
and then move a bit and press the O key
which is the out button so that
is the section that is being
brought in when I drag it into the timeline
then what I do is
I unlink it from the audio
delete the audio because I never really need it
etc
couple times
where I might
so the audio is gone
and then what I do is
I will have a
way that all of the video game footage
in that review
has been cropped and resized
to fit the frame because
not always correct
there's a way that is really handy
if you just
have like a certain
thing set
you right click on the video footage
click copy and then right click
on the new video footage
and click paste
stuff I can't remember
exactly what it is but paste
a tribute
and you can basically paste the keyframes
for the motion for the size
for the opacity whatever it is
and all the effects and you can just copy
that into that new thing and you can do that
by dragging a box as well
so
anytime I put a new clip in
I just copy all the information
from the old clips
and I put them into the new ones
alright that's cool let's not get so bogged down
of the weeds though
it amuses me how
technical everybody else gets because
I've said this before
the reason I use Vegas is that I just think
it's incredibly simple
and what I mean by simple
is not that like
it's not all that advanced stuff
but you can also just like
manually do everything very easily
and so like for me it's
you know I could optimize everything
and I could make it easier on myself
but like it's easier for me to just parse it
if I just do everything
in order start to finish
I don't know why
obviously it takes more time
but I mean I edit fastest shit anyway
so it doesn't matter that much
I'm not sitting on a project
for days or anything
or even months as Nate would be
but yeah David was that
about wrapped up with your writing and editing process
please say yes
depends on what you want to say
I don't really need to add anything additional
okay Tom are you there yet
I'm back I'm here
yeah you want to talk about your writing and editing process
um yeah I mean
I hate editing
a lot
preach your brother
knows that like I've questioned multiple times
if I should even be making videos
because I hate it so much
like it drives me to suicide
it's the worst it's awful
I hate it
that being said I do a lot of it
so I mean my writing
you have some of the most pro looking videos
of any of us
your branding and stuff has always been
totally on point
I remember just like in your end cards
from the old you know brony curious videos
those were right away very professional
I remember modeling myself after them at one point
yeah I mean
I'm pretty good at the graphic stuff
just because I've been doing that forever
and like I don't it's funny because I don't mind doing
like uh
vfx stuff like the end cards
and the animation stuff like that I find really interesting
it's just the grind of like here's my
fucking dumbass voice and my dumbass face
and I'm gonna shoot all this fucking video
and find all these stupid clips I don't even care
but I've made my point I wrote it
just read the text if you weren't also fucking lazy
you goddamn millennials
and that's like my mindset the entire time I'm editing
it's like if youtube is never invented
I'd be fine
fuck everything so that's my mentality
when I'm editing so it's just hellish and I don't like it
um I don't think
I can probably I don't really
I can't get too much in the technical stuff because I use hitfilm
which I don't think anybody else uses
um
it's free it's free there's also
a paid version I don't have the paid version
well I do now because they just emailed me
they're like here's our $300 paid version
do a video on it and I'm like okay
so now I have the new version but what I like
about hitfilm is that it's free number one
if for the free express version
which is still really good it's like way better than iMovie
way better than windows movie maker
and what's cool about it it's like it's a adobe premiere
and adobe after effects in one
because you can do all the video editing
but you can also have like all the vfx stuff
if you want to do like animation and visual
like stuff like that
it's a lot of source or sloths than that too
it's the same program
because you can do everything which is pretty dope
but um
my writing process is pretty much like
very similar to yours Nate where you just get the idea
you have like the thesis concept
and you kind of just go and write it out
like I don't do a super fuck ton of research
because a lot of the writing that I did back
when I was doing reviews
and stuff was very much like personal
like my personal thing like that was the thing that I
always thought was really funny it's like people give me shit
like
like this isn't true or whatever
this isn't like true or what we want to hear
this is just my personal views on it
you know it's very much like a vlog style
like I'm just talking about
this is my interpretation if you don't like it
like that's fine
so I don't do too much research
on videos unless
like the point
I'm trying to make mandates like knowing the facts
I mean that's pretty crazy because you
you talk a lot of techno jargon
about all the fucking reviews you do
and I guess you just know that shit
well I mean
I don't do a lot of research on those either
just because I'm doing research for fun essentially
like I've read Engadget every day
for the last I think 10 years now
that's just part of my day
is going and reading blogs about all this shit
like that's just I wake up
and like 10 minutes in like that's what I do
I'm just like oh I wonder what happened when I was asleep
that'll do it
so I know a lot of stuff about that
but those
it's two different processes
like we're doing like a review versus doing a product review
because there's like a lot more
camera work and stuff involved with the product
because it's a physical object that you have to get
footage of and that's obviously different
than you know
tracking down a cartoon and getting the
clips you need out of that
so it's required a lot more like knowledge and learning about
photography and cinematography
and things like that
the beginning videos I did were really bad
I didn't have any of that shit
so it was all like handheld done with like
a point and shoot camera which did not look very good
yeah of course
but now it's slowly starting to get better
than
the thing I was going to talk about with the camera
because if you're using the same camera I am the T2i
what I ended up doing because like
it doesn't have a flip screen which sucks
my old camera did have a flip screen
but it was a point and shoot camera and I had to sell it
because I needed money because I had to pay my bills
so I had to let that camera go which sucks
so now I'm using a T2i
which is still a good camera but it doesn't have
the flip screen it's like older
it doesn't have a lot of modern features
the no flip only now am I realizing
what a fucking waste of money it was
to get something without a flip screen
you can't do it unless you have a guy with you
but okay well this is
my like ghetto tech solution
which is not really ghetto tech at all but it's a good way
the nice thing about those big DSLRs
they have a ton of fucking ports
and one of the ports on the side is mini
hdmi so if you get
a mini hdmi adapter on ebay
for like a dollar take
your hdmi cable from your monitor
take it out of your computer put it in the adapter
plug the adapter into the camera then turn it on
and the screen is on your
computer monitor oh my god that's perfect
I never fucking knew
that is fucking
amazing it's great and then
what you need to do with the Canon firmware is there's
an aftermarket firmware you can download called magic lantern
and I put that on my T2i
you put it on the SD card
and then you go into the Canon settings
you hit update firmware and it will overwrite
the stock firmware with the magic lantern
firmware it adds a bunch
of new cinematography features you can monitor
your curves right on the screen you can monitor
your white balance it adds what's called
that's great because I swear to god the managing
of like the white balance of the shadow of this computer
is I mean this camera is fucking impossible
I can't navigate these
the best thing that's gonna save your fucking life they have an option for
focus peaking do you know what focus peaking is
yeah so you
put focus peaking on there and it'll
have like red dots around whatever's
in focus so when you go to stand
back away if your face has like red dots
on it you know you're in focus
I didn't even think this kind of shit was possible
you've blown my mind to shit Tom
like I'm about to go dig up
Victor's old fucking T4i
that he won't use anymore because he's got a real
camera now and I'm just gonna fucking steal it
dude I would like sell
my left nut for a T2i those things with magic lantern
are great so
my baby little T2i
is like very jealous but yeah
magic lantern like will save your fucking life
and that's kind of like the last like
seven videos I've shot were on the T2i
and I'm slowly kind of trying to figure out
how to make this dinosaur work for me
you're fucking video quality
like definitely jumped up in the last
view like in terms of framing
and being in focus and
the lighting not being shit
or the white balance not being shit like it's gotten
a lot better
on the one hand I'm doing a lot of the camera stuff
on the other hand I'm looking into like post-production
so like I'm not doing like color
balance and white balance and
crushing blacks and whites and getting like the contrast
looking good I'm trying to make it look very filmic
like everyone's like oh man 60fps I'm just like
I'm gonna do 24fps so it looks like a movie
because that's the look I like
so I'm like I'm going down when everyone else is going up
so it's a lot of just like
tweaking with things like that which
all of that I find fascinating
is the actual editing part that I want to like
make someone else do because it's
sucks and it makes
something I want to know about
is you still do this right
you use a teleprompter
for all your stuff
like a makeshift one
yeah so there is a video on YouTube
by Film Riot they're a great channel
for like DIY filmmaking and stuff and they had
I'm completely cut out
am I alive?
yeah so there's a channel
called Film Riot which is great for
DIY filmmaking and stuff and they have a tutorial
on how to build a teleprompter
so
just like to build
so what you do you take like a 2x4
or like a piece of plywood
and then you screw in like hinges on
a picture frame and then prop that up
at 90 degrees and
you put your camera in there
and you get like
a screen or something you drop onto the plywood
and reflect onto the picture frames glass
and then you can read it
so what I did is I took my old
iPad that someone from Twitter
I actually went on Twitter like a couple years ago
and was like I need an iPad
I will pay somebody and this guy was just like
I'll just give you this old iPad that I don't use anymore
it's sitting in a box it's like super old and it's like cracked
but it doesn't matter I'm like dude I don't care
I just need that so I got this old iPad
and I used that and there's an application for the iPad
called Prompt Smart
and it saved my life because I was using
other online
teleprompter software but it auto scrolls
so you have to like keep up with the
prompt so if you fuck up
like it's gone
and so you're just like well I got to figure that out
Prompt Smart is great
is because it uses the iPad's mic
to track your voice so it only
scrolls as you're talking so you can
stop talking for like 15 minutes
when someone comes downstairs and like
bitches you out or something and then you can just
go back and start right where you left off
and it'll just start scrolling again
so whenever I do like reviews
and stuff where I need to sound like an intelligent
human being like I'll usually script it out
and throw it on there and you just throw
the camera behind it and you throw a piece of glass
or a piece of cloth over it so it blocks out the light
from the backside so
the camera lens doesn't
see the reflection that's on the glass
it just looks like you're looking into the camera lens
because the screen is right in front of it so you're
reading but it looks like you're making eye contact
so that's super handy and the only reason
I like it like
I watch your videos and like I can
just barely see the subtle movement of
your eyes and only because I know
that it's teleprompter do I
like you know detect it I don't think most people
would ever realize
it's getting more noticeable now because
I just got the t2i and it doesn't have the right lens
to do video it has a 50 prime
lens which is great for photos if you're going out
on the street and doing photography because it has
already a good amount of zoom built in
but when I'm shooting now with this
t2i it's like 4 or 5 feet away
from me even though it looks like it's right in my face
because the prime lens has so much zoom
so I need to get like
a $70 pancake lens or something
that'll be work better for that but like I'm super
getting into photography and like cinematography
and color grading now because I have to like
force myself to learn it so I'm like oh this is cool
you can do this and you can change the colors
of like the shadows and the highlights independently
to get a more film look and I'm just like
you know what I do I get a footage
that's hopefully reasonably in focus
and then I just throw that shit into Vegas
and then I open color corrector and I just
fuck with the knobs until things look
reasonably okay and it works
amazing it's awesome
I mean it does but I can always tell that you've
color corrected your videos you know like it doesn't
look natural you can't tell shit
you don't know nobody fucking knows
I can always tell that you've color corrected your videos
that's kind of what's nice about Hillfilm
is that you're feeling lazy they have like under the
presets it's like auto color auto contrast
auto lighting it's like do-do-do and then it fixes
like 90% of the things
great for saving cell phone footage
like every time I shoot with my iPhone
cause I'll do that sometimes
it always comes out like Duke
and then I'll just like throw that on there and it'll
magically look like it was shot with like a $100
better camera just from doing the color correction
that's like
I'm fascinated Tom that like cause I feel like
the rest of us we encounter a problem
and then we're just like trying to solve it
through like
you know it coming up with something
and you actually just like find a technology
that can do that
you know you're like surely something out there
is built to fix this problem that I can somehow
get for free and you'll find that thing
and the rest of us are sitting here like
trying to fucking like reinvent the wheel
or something just to have a
image score across the screen
I don't know I just I just don't want to spend any money
I'll spend a little bit of money
just say that you're an internet reviewer
and please send me your product so I can do a
Tom is amazing at finding
like he said he uses fucking HitFilm
to edit like it's a free program that
you know that's as powerful as
like a real fucking
big boys program you know
that we're all stealing and barely
know how to use
it's it's pretty good
and they're probably they usually come out with a new version
every
Wizard of Vegas bitch
in the next few months which will probably be even better
but it's really good
works great
I like it
I don't know
when my editing process itself
though is usually just like lots of cursing
lots of swearing
lots of racial slurs that I regret later
because I really couldn't be saying those things
and just getting the supremely fucking
pissed off at shit not working
Tom I heard a tweet recently
that you discovered my
ancient method
for dealing with editing
which is the good old fashioned
alcohol method
yeah I mean at this point
I'm just like getting
lots of rum and I'll get
and I'll just have that by me while I'm
editing and every time something happens
I'll just take another drink
the reason I started doing it is because
I don't know if anybody else has this problem
but the reason I hate editing so much
is because editing hates me
I've been doing YouTube for almost five years now
and every single video has fucked up
somehow I've never had a video where it's just like
I started and ended and nothing
happened footage will always get corrupted
if the camera will always fuck up
the audio will always die on me
every week something happens
and I just want to blow my brain down
I mean it's like you've been forced to adapt
to learn all these advanced technological solutions
because it's trying to fuck with you
well just last week I recorded that video
on the Artistle D10
and I had to shoot it three times
because the first time the camera died
and I found out the camera died because my SD card was too
low tech to use with this new camera
my $30 SD card
the second time I did it
the framing wasn't right
and then the other time I did it
I've had everything right and I was like
oh man this video actually went
like this recording was great
no problems I didn't even stutter as much as I usually did
I put it into my computer
or sorry your memory card has been corrupted
so all the files were lost
so I had to record the video of me talking again
and all the B-roll I had shot
the three previous hours
it was like a two hour project
because everything fucking hates me
and it's just like oh my god
I really think god is up there
you should just be blogging
I'm going to make your life hell until you quit video
and just blog like a normal person
I've definitely experienced some of that shit
but it sounds brutal
I've experienced a lot of it
but it doesn't happen as much lately
and this is going to make everybody mad to say
but I just bought
better equipment
the way I fought my way around it is like
I don't want to have these problems
I'm just going to buy all the best shit
and the best shit doesn't fail as much
like when you've got a computer
that can just crunch through
you know I mean I can be
too past rendering something
and recording a podcast and listening to
well I wouldn't be listening to this
I remember watching your video
yesterday or today
about the whatever
the new guru thing or whatever
on the screen you were rendering a video
while you were recording this and I was like
what is this nigga doing right now
I was recording
the screen capturing
in 1080p with open broadcaster
and I was rendering a let's play
at the same time a two pass render
at 720p I think
so
I didn't have audacity open
at the time because I was recording through the program
I fucking closed Vegas before starting this call
because I was afraid it was going to fuck my shit up
consider this
after that after I had finished
that recording I edited
that video and I rendered it
at the same time as the other render was going
well that's just stupid I just rendered two videos at once
it worked perfectly fine
comment on the alcohol method by the way
I want to say the alcohol I do that too
sometimes like if I had enough alcohol
around me I would do it probably a lot
because if it's a video
where it's basic stuff that I
know how to do sufficiently really well
without having to double think it
there's that level of drunkenness
of mildly moderate drunkenness
where you can do things you're really used to
you don't want to get actual drunk
because then you just have a headache
but if you just buzz
that makes
that dulls the pain of like
repetitiveness
it's quite useful
not to cut you off too soon
but perhaps we should just move on to Digi
so we can wrap this thing up
Digi, holy damn
I always see
you might have noticed that every time we do one of these podcasts
where we round Robin I always make myself go last
so that because I know
I'm gonna piggyback on what everyone else says
throughout the podcast and that'll get out half
of what I wanted to say so that it's not
like an unbroken hour of me talking
but yeah
so okay
writing process
because for me writing and editing
process are like two totally different worlds now
because the videos I actually write are edited by somebody else
and the videos I edit are usually not written
so it's like
I've got two whole different schools going on
you know and
the writing process is totally different
depending on what kind of video it is
if it's one that's like
let's say
ten cool directing tricks in Evangelion
you know that involves like having to watch
Evangelion and like take notes
and find episodes where
those things happen and stuff like that
or
I just did one on the scene from Shirobako
I had to go rewatch that scene
make sure I had all my facts straight and even then
I'm helped by having
an unbelievably good memory
I can usually remember most of what happens
in shows that I've seen
usually I can remember down to what episode it was
sometimes even where in the episode it happened
so
I don't struggle too much with having to take notes on things
and I only really
have to go and recheck
and rewatch stuff if it's a show I hate
those are the ones where I probably
wasn't paying the most attention
like the asterisk war
I've seen all of it like three times
in total
because I had to watch the whole thing
take notes then watch it
and then pause
every minute
when I dissect the first episode
it's like I'll watch 30 seconds of it
and then hit pause and then write a page
about those 30 seconds I just watched
probably have to rewatch them a couple more times
while writing it
when I do
watch stuff for a video
it's never like I watched it
and took notes and then wrote
it's usually I just keep going back
to the show like I have it open in another tab
and I'm like you know
write a paragraph then watch
the clip back and make sure
the Shirobako one
you list yourself as having rewatched
the asterisk war on Mal for that reason
I've rewatched it three times according to Mal
okay well I'm going to go and mark myself as having
rewatched it six times
that's probably it
so yeah
I'll go through
for stuff like that but then a lot of it is just from
memory and it really depends on how much
I can get away with like cool character designs
Gurren Lagann I've seen Gurren Lagann three times
in the past the last time I watched it was
early
last year so almost two years ago
didn't matter I was able to write it without rewatching
the show I was afraid I would have to
rewatch the show but I was like I fucking know
the character designs in Gurren Lagann you know
it's not going to be a problem but I have
this excellent failsafe
which is the Deveu because
usually when I write a video
you know he's going to have to watch the whole
show in order to edit it because he has to know
everything that's going to go in he has to find all the clips
so
I'll send stuff to him and like if there's
something I say that outright is wrong
he'll usually tell me like hey I wasn't able
to find a scene like that you know
and I'll be like well I guess I have to
rewrite it or I'll tell him well this
scene's kind of like it so use that one
you know like this is close enough
this will make it look like I'm correct
so yeah
I kind of like I use the fact
that Deveu is going to watch the show like
with Gurren Lagann you know I had him
go back through and there is there was
one thing that like in that
video in particular
Deveu was editing it down to the
fucking wire on the deadline with it like it was
due by midnight
and it was uploaded
like at 11.30 you know because we had to
get it out by the end of the month and I
would have probably had him
cut out the part where I say that the beast men
all have sketchy outlines
yeah was not proven
visually like the stuff you
show didn't prove that at all and I would have
totally no believe me I looked
extremely thoroughly and I could not
really find it. Well that's the kind of thing where
if I had rewatched the show I would have just
cut that line out because it's obviously not true
I don't know I feel like the fact that
the art direction did something
to give you that impression
means that there's something going on with
the art there. Well there is such a thing as fucking up so
you know. I mean I think I just should have
the sentence is
factually inaccurate they do not have
sketchy outlines consistently across the
characters and like
you know Davoo showed footage which clearly
proved me wrong so I was like
okay this should have been cut but at that
stage it was too late. I picked the clips
that prove you the least wrong possible
yeah that's fair. Which is sad because I watched them
and I went oh well I guess I was wrong.
You know what I believe I was going to tell you about that
like when I was at that part but you were like a sleep
yeah well that's the problem. A sleep at the
wheel more like making these fucking videos. Editing down to the fucking
literal last minute because I noticed it and I
was just like we can't do anything about it it's too late
this video has to come out by the end of the month
you know. And thus that corporate
shill influence starts to take the
art here we go down the fucking
rabbit hole. More importantly has anyone
complained about that. Right now
fuck you guys.
You know I was like
when me and Ben were watching it back I was like
oh that's clearly like a point I didn't
make and Ben's like yeah you
you know that not proven. Yeah but
then you'd have to cut out the part where you say
that Lord Genome has the most
crazy out. Now and I mean
the other problem would be that by cutting
out time the video because the video is exactly
ten minutes and one second long
and it's over ten minutes that means you get
the double on the advertising at the end of
the video so you know like how
what am I going to cut out twenty seconds
worth of the video because I was kind of wrong
and then like lose half the ad revenue
I could have on it in retention you know. You fucking
shill bitch. You
don't fucking lie and say
things are intentionally wrong. I feel like
in this case it was a mistake. Maybe you could
just alter the line. Throw money at it.
No you can get the better equipment
but you deserve to be shit on it. Throw the
shackles at everybody and you win.
Well think of it. That's what I've learned today.
Think of it this way I mean if the
on-screen footage is actively proving
me wrong then everyone can observe
that I was wrong. You know I don't
have to make a correction. What is that excuse
like oh I don't need to be right because they'll just prove
me wrong later it's totally not on me guys it's everyone
else's fault. No no no I'm saying
everyone you could have. Everyone can look at the
screen and go well he clearly was wrong about
that. His editor found that out you
know. So
I don't know. I feel like most
people would probably be like
I guess those lines are sketchy. Maybe
they just didn't show the sketchy part. Yeah
I think most people would doubt
themselves. You know you could have the line
could have just been altered to the beast
men are drawn in a subtly
different manner. Yeah no
it could have been fixed but we didn't have
time because the fucking true
I mean Viral looks the same I mean you know
he's weird but yeah
whatever I don't care. Point being
it was it was a mistake and
but anyways
the writing process you know for something like
Shinbo in the 90s is like we
like me and DeVoo would watch through the OVA
I'd note down all the things that happened
in that OVA and then I'd
write three paragraphs about that OVA
you know and contain all the information so
some of it's written like that then some of it
is just like me just pulling from
my wealth of anime knowledge and
the way that my writing usually works
is that it starts
with the first sentence like I
I have an idea I'm thinking
alright
anime there's too much anime about
high school and my theory is that
it's because high school is secretly the most
interesting part of a Japanese person's life
how do I start this post
and I'll go outside and I'll be walking around
and I'll just think like it's
usually just a catchy sentence like something fun
like god whatever
I say at the start anime and high school
are practically inseparable
you know like that's how I'd present this idea
and then from there it just
it just goes like as soon as I figure out
that first sentence the rest of the thing is
pretty much locked in place and I just sit
down and fucking go
and it's rare I don't know how many of you guys
like know Digi's writing history
but for those who don't like he just
has always I guess he said he always just
writes in a stream of consciousness
most of the time and he just did it so much
for so long and I'm just so that he would
actually be really good and I mean yeah you can go
through my whole writing history on my
blog and see everything I've written and in the early days
it's a lot of it's barely
comprehensible and there's so many
extraneous details like
the way I used to write is just
I mean it's always been just whatever comes into
my head but as a result of that
like I used to just not cut anything
and it was just like I
hadn't I wouldn't think about it enough
for writing it you know like
I don't take notes but I think on the thing
like if I have an idea for a video I walk
around I consider it I think
what's the angle I'm going to approach it from
and then I write it all at once back then
it would just be like there's all these personal
anecdotes in there that don't belong or just like
notations on like how
hot this character is totally
out of nowhere and not in the funny
way I do it now where it's like you know and
by the way dairy's got the best body in the
series just saying you know like it's kind of a little
tricky thing but but also something I did
want to be in the video
like how can idiots
like you say that when Nia there
and I'm talking about little baby Nia little baby
Nia's got the best body in the series that's a
close second I mean I'm like not even
joking that like child Nia 14 year old
Nia is one of the most attractive characters
ever in an anime I agree
I don't think she's less attractive
than dairy I just think dairy has the
best bod like
damn maybe she's got that fucking ass well she's
one who was in the tight fitting outfits
you can't really compare
Nia's got kind of a banana body
you know she's she ain't got
no ass dairy's got that
she really she's
not much better dairy it's
whatever I'll study it later
please do
but anyways
yeah like my old
writing was just a total chaotic mess
and I've talked about this before how like what
I what I
had this revelation where I had this teacher in college
who told me like
I had to write something for him and he wanted it to be like 500
words and of course I way overshot
went for like 700 because back in high
school that impresses a teacher
if you go over the word count
yeah for sure and college this was not impressive
he was like this is too long I asked for 500
words and he's like you know cut
out all these extraneous details and stuff so I start
removing shit and I give it to him again it's like
550 words and he's like look you really
he was like I think you you have like a great
written voice but you need to learn how to simplify
he said he's specifically said simplify
simplify simplify and I was like
okay now I gotta get serious
so I start like running through this thing with a fine
tooth comb and like making every sentence
perfect and like it was so satisfying
to do that that I then
totally changed my anime
blogging style and like started
just like obsessing over
every script and like perfecting all the sentences
until that came naturally
and then I switched back to this more conversational
freeform style but now I
can just condense information well I
just know how to do that
so yeah it was just like this learning process
of if you yeah again if you go back
through read like my stuff from 2010
and read the stuff
in the summer of 2010 because you'll see this
moment where
I think the last post I'd written in my sprawling
style was
being an anime
lifer or like being a Yu-Gi-Oh
life or something like that where it was it was
me observing how different people have
called themselves like there's certain shows
that they're just obsessed with for their whole lives
and I never really had something like that and I was like
I guess Yu-Gi-Oh is a show
I've always been into but like I'm not like
way into it or anything that's the point of the post
it's like 1300 words
and half of it is totally extraneous
it could have been cut and so after
like I you know got this simplification
simplification lesson
I looked at that post and I was like god this is awful
like why did I write all this extra stuff in here
this is not what I should be doing and so the very
next like three posts are like spartan
it's like 500 word tight little
posts and then it like expands back out
from there so you know that's sort of the
development of my style and now it's
just the ideas in my head
write it all out and it's very
fast very instantaneous
unless it's a huge
project in which case there's a lot of getting
up going outside smoking thinking of
the next sentence like you know
my favorite example would be the
psychopaths video because there's
you know it's broken up into five parts
and I remember distinctly when I
was working through the part where I was comparing
Makishima to the villain from season
two Kamui and I'm just
comparing these villains and like every paragraph
I had to like
go out think about it for a while
and like think of the perfect sentence
and then start the next paragraph and I just kept doing
that I just kept getting up and going out and thinking of the
next perfect sentence and then writing the next paragraph
and it was so fun time
you know out of all the videos I've written
and made there's only one where I think
I had kind of a pretty interesting to describe
writing process which was roller coaster
tycoon 3 where I
basically this was my method
I start talking about something that annoys
me or yeah something about that annoys
me about roller coaster tycoon 3
and any time I use the word
just as in
this is just annoying as in just fuck my
shit up fam as in
this is just ugly or like that right there is
just annoying any time
I felt the need to use the word just
I then blew up the just
into a whole paragraph of explaining
of justification and that
was how the whole thing eventually became
really long that's like just did
evolved into that's really interesting
actually
I was actually on a huge anti-just
kick I was super opposed
to the word just at the time
for that copier aware that just
just the all caps word just
is a big meme
it's a big meme so
yeah so
most of my writing happens like that
in these violent spurts
and it's also about figuring out what kind
of video is this gonna be it's like
the most important thing because
most other youtubers have a
defined structure like Nate you have
best anime ever it's always
kind of following this formula
where there's gonna be some kind of intro joke
there's gonna be and
as well you know there's gonna be
introductory sort of comedic scenario
then you're gonna introduce the topic
of the the the media
you know go through this and that all of mine
are so different that each one is like
it's really mostly about what
is the what is this video
like what is even is it is
it a retrospective
is it me like talking about
just cinematic techniques is it gonna be more
emotional is this gonna be personal
you know and the
hardest video ever to write
in that regard was aesthetic
is narrative because I had like
10 different ways I could have approached it
that were all totally different like some of
them were let's take one
picture and analyze that
picture in depth and that'll prove that aesthetic
is narrative and some of it was like well what if we
made it really broad and talked about it in the
way that like art can mean all these different
things and I just kind of ended up
combining all of them in the video it's like
20 minutes and it's broken up into like
all these different 5 minute sections of
just like exploring these different concepts
and it took forever to write
well I don't know how Gib feels about it
but I think it's a little bit inaccurate
to say that things are always the same
in our vids and rears are always
a totally different format because I mean they
follow the formula of you know converting
this text piece into video
like aesthetically they're very similar
in the way that they're done well sure and
I mean sure the topics are different I just
mean the approach
like yeah the approach I take is always the same
it's write it out all at once
and you can clearly tell my written voice
and you can tell it's me you know but
it's just that the most
important part of the whole writing process
is figuring out what it is
you know it's not about
like if you know you're gonna do like an
intro then it's about how am I
gonna do the intro you know what is
the joke gonna be how am I gonna stage
this introduction to
the video for me the
entire thing is
what the fuck is this video you know
is it an analysis is it not
is it a review is it
does it contain information about
the thing because I don't like to summarize
you know so something like the mob psycho 100
video is like
just analysis like it's
just a very bare bones here's
what's interesting about mob psycho
no real plot description except for where
it like you know where I can work it into
talking about the show but it kind of just starts
off like you know this is
this is what mob's character is like
and here's what Reagan's character is like
and that's that's cool you know
and so
figuring out what the video is gonna be
is like how that came together as opposed
to you know
where's the plot description gonna go where
am I gonna talk about characters and stuff like that
which I feel is more what a normal
review is like you know what
I think most people go into it like
there's gonna be a
description of the thing in there somewhere
I spent a lot of time
wondering about how I'm gonna work in my
x out of 10 you know at the end of the video
that's really important you gotta get that right
without that execution the whole video is pointless
yeah um I'm sure there's
a lot of people who for that is
entirely accurate
I'm sure it is
yeah so so that's how the
writing comes together for the ones that do
edits and then I just fucking I do the
audio I ship it off to him and it's done
and those are very much like
they're just in my mind they're just
text posts that are set to video
they're not videos in the
like strictest sense of the word they're not
constructed like with the
idea that they will be a video first
and I mean I incorporate a lot of elements
that I couldn't do in text you know
where there'll be unscripted segments like in
that high too many
anime high schoolers or whatever
you know there's a segment where it's just me in front of my
collection and I just use that
as an example I mean you do you have
evolved your writing style a lot
knowing that it's going to be
in the audio video format right like I
write but what did you mean
is he's not like thinking about like
how the video will be formatted like
with things that can only be done with
video with like live action segments
it's it's you know back in the
text blogging days you would have to
if you wanted to describe like
the way a scene plays out you
would have to like literally
describe what happens in the scene because
you can't show it I mean we would usually use
images and stuff and you know ghost
lightning innovated and you slide shows and stuff
like that but like you had to go into a
lot more description whereas now I can say
a sentence like you know
when animator Yutaka Nakamura
does a scene like this
and I say this and like in the
text post that is totally
unhelpful but in video
it's on screen so that's what I mean by this
course so like I do make
illustrations like that but for the most part
it's written like a blog post
that is being adapted into video
and I love that because I always wanted
back in the anime blogger days like we were
always saying wouldn't it be so much more helpful
if we could show you what the fuck we're talking about
you know like wouldn't it be so much more
helpful if I could just like when I say
you know Shinbo has
a weird aesthetic if I could actually
show the aesthetic you would get
it way more easily and like
that was something you know that me and ghost
lighting we're always saying like oh if only we could do
video and then suddenly we could do video
yeah not that he could exceed enough time
so like that's sort of where I come from
as opposed to coming from it like
like I feel like you guys more
come from I want to make a funny
video and you know the review
is more of a like
like a vehicle to make an entertaining
video I think of myself as
a film director personally yeah
exactly and I don't at all
but then the funny thing is
that I actually do take that
approach to all the other shit
I edit because I actually
it's funny I hate
editing as much as Tom but I only hate editing
when it's the scripts
that I'm doing when it's a video about
like what I'm you know giving to DeVoo
I enjoy editing when it's all just
making shit up on the fly when it's
like just finding solutions
when like the video is being created in the
editing because then it's about
of course creatively that makes it more
making something up so like my
vlogs there's a reason that
you know you might get a few more
random musical interludes or just like
weird things that pop up in the middle
of a vlog or something because it's like
it's a lot more fun to
problem solve there and
and you know I don't do a lot
I'm a big fan of the idea that
like even the smallest edit can change
things massively and I really picked that up from Jesse
where Jesse will do a video that's
ostensibly just a vlog
but then like there's one moment
where just the camera zooms in on his
face right when he drops something
and it's fucking hilarious you know
and it just totally changes the nature of
it even though it's such a minor edit in the
middle of what could be a 15 minute vlog
you know I mean
Plebe and the Weave is kind of edited that way
like most of it's just us talking but then he zooms
in on our faces at funny moments and puts
text on screen here and there and it totally
changes it into a much funnier product
or just those weird explosions
of things happening at parts and so
that's sort of the approach I take to like after
dark and to any more experimental
stuff I have is just I
take a bunch of footage and
just if there's anything I can do to it
I do it if there's not anything I don't care
I don't go into it like I don't go
into filming thinking this will
be edited into a joke later
I just film what I have and then when I'm watching
it back if there's something that I'm like oh that
would be hilarious you know then I'll put
it in there and so that's why it's very
inconsistent if you watch all the after dark
vlogs most of them are me talking into a camera
and then some of them suddenly have like all
this weird stuff happening and it's like
where did this come from
or suddenly it's a a work out
vlog where you know I have Victor filming
me working out and I've got like
I've got the anime playing on a
monitor that's sitting next to me on
a stool and then I've got
like three cameras set up in like
weird locations like to capture different
angles on it and you know
microphones like barely hidden out of
camera so like sometimes
one random video will
be like a totally new setup
it's nothing I've ever done before it's just like
completely inventing the
style of a new video just
for this one video and that's when editing is fun
that's when it's like all just
cool stuff and like how am I gonna make this
vision I have come together that's like
nothing I've ever done before
but none of it's ever too complicated
I'm more about that's right you know
all the all the like regular videos
that I make for the didgy bro channel
almost all the time it is
in as little
time as possible as efficiently as possible
getting to a normal acceptable
quality because that is the most
efficient for like being successful
and actually getting statements out there
but in the event that there is a video
that is like this mess
of different information lying
on the floor that you need to staple together
improvisationally
as you go which I only have
one big video like that which is my
debate with a commenter the story of Dow
which is like this video with like seven
different parts which I was writing
and recording and editing like as I
went through it out of order like I
completely did it out of order and I just
did it all in one hectic 24
hour editing writing
recording session in which I didn't sleep
and I barely ate because it was so
exciting like I feel like Nate for as much
work as you put into your videos
I feel like the percentage of time that you
spend being like tedious
out and just being like it's probably
lower than most people because
you give me the sense that you put a lot
of fun creativity into every moment of
it that's true it's certainly true yeah
I mean that's anytime it's more
a sense of despair looking at the timeline
and seeing like how much I accomplish today
and being like just let it right that's why
I eventually didn't go with that style like the
first like main like originally that is how
I went into videos whether or not I was good at the time
I did that whole every detail
of something I've poured over
style and if I got paid a million
dollars every time for that I would have never
broken away from it but
I mean but then I would love
to see what Nate would do if
you just made more stuff
like I can't fucking think of the
word or like what what Gibbon takes
whole channel is where it's like
it's just you have an idea
and you just like violently go
about it messily and you just
make it a thing and like that's because
the Dow video I can see where there's
lots of like weird inventive tricks
in there like the way you do text where like
there's these like these reveals
of text on the screen
and it's like all these slow
wipes like I can tell you had to time all that
out and think of how the text was going
to appear and I thought it was really cool and
it was like something that you know that's a technique
you just kind of came up with for that
video haven't really had to use again
but that's where it's the most
fun and I've done stuff like
the anime is getting lazy
with its meta video is like one of the last
ones that I edited that I like
really put effort into and it's
dirty as hell it is way grungy
images are just like flying
in and out of the screen at random there's all these
like weird low res things because
I love like the most fun to
me is when I do like really multimedia
visuals when I grab like
you know footage
from real life and then footage from
anime and then images and then like
weird pictures and like it all kind of
coalesces in this like maelstrom and
it's ugly but it's a lot of fun
to do to have like weird
footage and my favorite
and this is this is the most
like ever that I had an idea that way
outstripped my ability to execute it
is where I'm trying to say
a tidal wave of light novels
crashes over and I just
I took footage of a
tidal wave like you know crashing over
Japan which is not as easy to find
as you would think like to have one that was
like actually at the shore like most
of it's in city so I wanted one that was
like the waves actually coming onto the beach
and
the problem with it is that the camera
moves in this shot so
like you know if it was just a stationary
shot of waves coming in it would be really easy to keyframe
and animate a bunch of light novels
you know surfing up over the shore
but unfortunately the cameras moving
so I have to constantly change the
perspective of all the light novels and
like each one has to be like
halfway poking out of the water
and they have to be moving on like
the same kind of speed it was
a nightmare like it was way beyond
what I could do way way way
beyond like trying to measure out every
keyframe to match the camera movement was
fucking impossible even if that was
like five seconds long doing every
frame for like I don't know exactly
it took too much it took like
I think it was ten
seconds of clip and it took like
two hours to do and it looks
like shit you know like two that's
two hours to get it to even the
level that I was willing to go
and you can clearly see everything looks
like a fucking mess and it's ugly as
hell but it was a lot of fun
like to have that idea and
to just go and do it you know
and I'm sure if Nate had done the same idea
he would have executed it all the way
and edited that for two fucking days
until it was perfect it is what I do
like there that it's definitely
that's when editing is the most fun
is when you have this vision of something
that you have to like completely invent
how it's going to be made and
you know even if it looks like
shit at least it was fun to do
like with the whole girl login
part one I just came up with that whole
motion thing and yeah
I think the only time I actually had fun
editing was
editing tale the smartest pony man
it was when
everyone was proven wrong and edited all
the comments oh right yeah
you were so right about that yeah it was awesome
that was the best video ever
that was the one time I edited with a smile on my face
because the fuck you I've been waiting years
for
I forget what was the event that transpired
just reminds me it was when
the little princess bitch was born
and she was born in Alicorn and they were both
we don't fucking know how that shit happened
and for like three years I've been
heckled for my position on that
completely contradicts other things we've
learned in the series but it's all
out the window so whatever
it was a good
a lot of the time when I'm
and then it was a bad day
fuck off everybody
I only really like editing
when
I can make myself laugh by a joke
like if I've got a joke going
and I play it back and it's like yeah
yeah then I have
the power to continue for the day
but a lot of the time it's just like
oh it didn't work I did all that
preparation the recording the live action
the putting all the things in there and it
just falls flat so sometimes I just have to
delete it it's really annoying
the joke you did recently give that I really liked
was in the Rayman video was when
you're talking about the game and then you
you stop and you turn and it goes
with the other camera angle you make your next point
then you just stare at the camera for a while
and you're like that was a joke
that's why I changed the angle
you just you hold on that and like
spell it all out and it takes like
20 seconds to do
I'm gonna be honest
didn't care for that joke
thought it went on way too long
that's what made it funny was that it was
awkwardly long
so I went through the like giggle initially
and then the like okay let's move on
and then the like secondary oh okay he's doing it too
and then it just kept going
I laughed harder the longer it went
alright sure enough
so you know what I was gonna say about the whole uh getting bored thing
um the great thing about
having uh like doing things the way
I do where I put my my music down
and then I edit uh
visuals after I've got that laid in
um like the like the video I'm currently doing
like I already know
where all like the emotional
uh fucking hits are gonna come
and I've got it all mapped out
so like at the end of the day I have a ritual I sort of do
at the beginning of editing at the end of editing
I just watch everything I've done from the very start
and like I can see it starting to develop
and it feels so good
funny thing about that because
Davoo was saying that like with
the current stream of videos he's been editing
for me he has not been watching them
back at all like at no point
in the editing because he knows that
I'm gonna watch it. It's half the time
half the time I just I'm already
tired of it before I even watch it back
but the other half like the shinbo ones those are more
complicated I do need to watch those back
well like yeah with the uh like
the girl in the gun and shiro bako
and anime and high school ones
like he finished and then he called me over
and like I sat down and watched it he just fucked off
to another room like and I just
watched the video like you know if I didn't have any
complaints then then what does it matter
to him you know like because he's editing it for me
I'm the client so like uh
you know and I usually have like one or two things I want
him to change he changes those things doesn't even
watch it back which fascinates me because
I watch back what I'm editing
constantly like
every time I do like
even if it's a long video I'll watch
back like the whole fucking
right now I'm in the middle of a
fairly inventive editing
not well I won't say it's inventive but it's different
for what I usually do
for like this kind of unscripted
um vlog thing
where I'm splicing in lots of stuff and like
just to check the flow I'll like
watch like 20 minutes
of an hour long video back just to see like
do I think this feels right
you know like do I like how these clips
are cutting in or like you know or
do I just like the rhythm of how I talk
even like my totally unedited vlogs
I usually watch a few times before I post
them um and so
like yeah I just I really want to know
I want to know exactly what I'm posting
I want to know it
down to the core so that
you know if I look back at it I'll
immediately recognize it and not have to like
especially for comments and discussion
because when there's a video I haven't
seen as much then like people will
bring it up and I'll be like what I don't
even fucking remember saying that you know
yeah yeah so
I want to have a good grasp of what I've been talking
about recently it makes sense though that
Davoo doesn't I mean since he knows
someone else is going to be reviewing he has the luxury
of you know just not worrying about as much
I remember
something I was going to say about the
being happy when you're editing
whenever I'm editing like a
stupid joke video for give and take like
um the one I did
about the you should
why you should vote thing I had the
idea of like the thumbnail is just boring
but the video itself is weird
and that that I made that
like real quick before the election
was over because the election was going on at the time
and I was like my
I was smiling the whole way through it was like
yeah yeah it was so cool
and that's that's why
I wish give and take was the most popular
channel ever because
I would get so much money
I have moments where I'm like
should I just start putting
better thumbnails on Digibra after dark
and just try like part of
me doesn't want the channel to grow because
I like that I can do whatever I want
there's no expectations and the comments
aren't total shit most of the time
but like you know
all I'd have to do is like give it nice
thumbnails and that channel would
would blow up and it already has 50,000 subscribers
but like it could be
it could be like Ethan and Hila where like
they their side channel became as big as
the main one eventually
there's always a temptation because I'm like
man wouldn't it be fun to switch to
just being this like fucking
unhinged oboe vlogger
you know
but um you know I kind of value
the the main channel
and I like having a place
where I can dump literally whatever
the fuck I want and nobody
will question it too hard
yeah that's pretty important
to have I mean because if you did that
I'm sure you would just make another channel
where you could post things that you really don't give a shit about
and it would just go on forever
I even had like I've had a few times
where like I actually
had to debate like is this
so shit that it shouldn't even go
on Digibra after dark
should just be on
Modal Soul you know
I love these tier lists of like
I mean it actually was like because originally
originally after dark was not
just anything it was like
just stuff that wasn't for the main channel
so like I did have my old channel
Modal Soul Productions where I'd post like weird music videos
and stuff but then eventually I was like
you know what like I want these
weird music videos to actually have some audience
so fuck it fuck everyone
who subscribes to Digibra after dark
if they can't take it you know like this this channel
is for the powerful it's not for
people who are going to meekly unsubscribe
because a weird rap video that says
nigger 200 times showed up you know
agreed
so uh are we done here
are we all wrapped up? yeah I think so
he's been going for quite a while
I guess I should have known
yeah I suppose
any time that we do one that's like each of us talk
about a thing on our own
it always ends up being too long
well we didn't know Davoo was going to be here until
like the last minute so like I had kind of thought
we're short we only have four people
and I demanded to go on because this is the first time
in like 20 episodes
I really cared to be on an episode
because god damn it my couch
is so cool I need people to know
well I'm glad
it got out there
alright well thanks for this everybody
and by the way once again
let me say that
this whole suggestion
this whole topic that we were in was a suggestion
by a guy sent to our twitter account
at tpcrastinators
so please go tweet
all your suggestions there give us everything
give us suggestions if you want to make art for us
give it to there there's finally a place
we need these suggestions we every week
we like we like scrap
you guys don't know
the shit I go through every week
trying to get these fucking people to care
about something for long enough to start
to make a fucking call about it
so please save me from myself
help yeah help help me out
send shit there and once again let me thank
at spaceyfilmer
for their suggestion for the writing
slash editing process
alright thanks for listening everybody and we'll see you next time
bye bye
not working
I'm doing nothing
my dick I'm jerking
myself I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a
deadline
don't want to do it
what the hell is wrong with me
I'm supposed to
be making money
be creating
funny things that
the people
gladly will pay
for artistic
genius
that's what they came for
instead I'm tweeting
hashtag repeating
that's why
there's no heat
and holes in the ceiling
yeah
it's quite the burden
it's a hard knock life
being
a genius