Hello ladies and gentlemen, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm the best guy ever, and thank you for joining in a very unfortunate episode because
Ben Saint is here.
Oh boy, best guy ever.
You gotta do something about that cough, you gotta take care of your lungs, I'm vaping,
I'm vaping into the microphone, I'm vaping into the microphone, that's what I'm saying.
Mage is here, Mage is here.
Hello, I'm in a good mood, I ate like three chocolate bars in a row.
You know that according to Harry Potter, that's pretty good for your mood.
Remember it kills the de-no, it staves off the dementors.
It doesn't stave them off.
It staves off the deleterious mental effects that proximity to the dementors have.
That's true, that's true. Hippocrit's here.
Hey it's me, it's me, I'm here.
And Tom Oliver.
Hey guys, sorry I haven't made a video in a while.
Just been too busy hanging out on The Pro Crastinators Podcast, the best podcast for artists everywhere.
Where are the reason people are dying? Nobody said it, so I will say it every time.
I'm really happy that you're taking charge on that.
Is this our new catchphrase guys?
It is.
What's the other one? Oh, just being cool.
And we're also just being cool.
We need a new theme song contest, but this time you have to, the lyrics have to be,
hey guys sorry I haven't made a video in a while.
That's good, that's good.
Speaking of things in that vein, I'm fucking sick.
I feel sick, I am sick.
Maybe I'm exaggerating a little bit, but I do feel shitty in general.
So sickness, I feel sick, times you were sick, discuss.
Tell us your symptoms.
I was quite recently sick, if you remember.
Me too, I got a cold, I got a fucking cold.
You might remember as of a couple weeks ago I was coughing like on every episode.
I was very sick for maybe a week there, it sucks, I could fuck with my sleep.
I have been blitzing myself, I got a huge fucking bag of clementines right here.
I have been chowing the fuck down.
I've got these vitamin C concentrated cocaine packs that I've been pouring into my water
and chugging by the gallon.
And I do feel I am successfully staving off the march into Poland of Hitler's troops,
of the sickness that is progressing through my body.
And I feel like Poland is actually going to win this one baby.
Our horse cavalry is going to turn those tanks around with sheer vitamin C force.
I don't know if vitamin C actually makes a difference, but I'm banking on it and it's all I got.
It's like ammunition, you're supplying your troops with more ammunition.
No, no, no, it's like the Poles had those winged hasars or whatever,
like the winged horse riders, we're just adding more wings,
more wings equal more power to fight back the tanks.
The winged knights like sweet robins in the veil.
Fuck off Preston Jacobs.
Your theories are shit, dude.
No man, their quake is fucking using the moon to bounce signals off of to spy on Daenerys.
That fucking boy, he finds one tiny justification, makes a 45 minute video about it.
He's just as bad as your soy boys or any of your fucking theory crap, your motherfuckers.
Okay, okay, yes, I blinked for a second.
What are we talking about?
Is this like the Game of Thrones version of A-Cross right now?
Is that what we're talking about?
I don't want to skip this because this is a huge ideological divide.
I was saying on the other episode that we shouldn't be afraid to delve into the real shit.
This is the real shit.
Preston Jacobs is an unsung genius because, see the thing is, his theories sound...
He thinks sweet robin is the most powerful character in Game of Thrones.
He's an idiot, he thinks way more shit about things than he should.
His theories are bunk.
You're fucking bunk, and here's why.
The reason...
Okay, yeah, if you listen to some of what Jacobs says, it sounds totally nuts,
but everything that he says is...
It's all justified by the fact that similar things happen in other George R. R. Martin stories.
Almost every one of his theories is based in George R. R. Martin wrote another story,
and basically this is what happened, so let's assume that something similar is going on in Ice and Fire.
Dude, I watched a fucking video of his about how Quentin might...
Okay, he didn't say he was definitely alive, but he said he was leaning hard on the fact that Quentin is alive.
If you remember people, Quentin was the martel who went to try to steal the dragons from Danny and got face melted.
I mean, he was on fire, he was burned.
He goes into this whole big fucking theory about how...
No, no, no, no, no, he was holding an oily whip at the time when it's described that something was burning.
It was the oil on the whip. He's only a little burnt, he's totally fine.
And he goes into all this fucking mind reading about the characters, like there's one character who never expresses emotion.
When he expressed emotion that Quentin was dead, that must indicate that he's lying to fool people.
Not that just narratively, maybe he cares more about his fucking lord than the random other fucks who die.
Quentin, you're overreaching, my dude. You're overreaching, and that's why I hate theory crafters.
Yeah, when you say it like that, it sounds crazy, but he gives a huge list of reasons why.
That example, you just said, yeah, it's like, oh, why wouldn't someone show emotion?
Well, I mean, he's an ironwood, which is the second house under the martels in the books.
Secondary houses are always the ones that are vying for power and try to take over their lords.
The ironwoods probably don't have any love for the martels.
You know, the whole mission was probably sent with them because they're not interested in martel rule.
There's all these reasons why the party doesn't actually care about Quentin.
And then there's all these other reasons why they act weird and the lies they tell after he dies don't make any sense.
I admit, I love Occam's Razor, and I use it liberally all the time, and I just feel that this boy's videos are ripe for it.
Super fucking ripe.
I don't care about...
Shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, all right.
Here's the real thing about that is that I have a cold.
You know, a few podcasts ago I was talking about having the eternal cold?
It has not stopped. I am still constantly kind of under the weather at all times, but I feel like Mr Burns.
Is that Sweeney Todd London atmosphere, bro?
It's killing your mind.
It's called getting older.
As an old man, I can confirm.
And Ben can confirm with me that it happens.
Eventually being kind of sick is just normal once you get older.
I don't think that's true at all.
I'm happy to say that no, no, I honestly don't feel any different.
I don't feel any different.
Well, then I guess I'm just broken and need a robot body immediately.
But it has benefits, because I have no idea what is causing it or whether it's even a thing,
but it's like I feel sick more so than I was when I was a little boy, or like a teenager.
So I assume I actually have a cold.
And like there's evidence to suggest that it is sort of like a Mr Burns.
Like I have too much stuff and therefore I can't get sick.
Because like I haven't had like a cold in, well, the whole time.
I've never had like a sniffle.
The whole time.
But whatever that means.
I've never had a cold in the whole time.
Like, you know, I go out in Boston.
Oh, it's so cold out here.
Oh, and I don't sneeze.
I don't sneeze.
I get a little runny nose, but like I never feel like, you know, like, you know,
snap fingers and now I'm bedridden.
Like I haven't felt like that in years.
The only times, I've gotten sick maybe twice in the last like several months.
And that was almost the only time I've been sick in like recent memory.
And both times were when I was out of the house like visiting Digi's.
And I think it was just like being out of the house in the cold for the journeys.
Got me sick both times.
I wear shorts out in the snow a lot.
And maybe that combined with public transportation and exposure to germs and all that.
This is almost definitely spurned on by the recent trip to Boston and whatnot.
I was exposed to the cold quite a bit.
Yeah.
But doing a lot of snow moving and pushing around and stuff.
I'm sure that's relevant to this.
I'm just, I'm so proud of myself for fighting it back.
I feel like I'm over the hump and it's only going to get better from here, baby.
It's great.
I think I just, I'm debating if I should exercise or not.
I don't know if it'll make me sicker or will help blast out the demons.
One of those two.
I love that feeling of blasting out the demons in a sense.
Me too.
When you, you know, you're really like dying and you're like, no, I'm just going to tense
all my muscles as hard as I can until it's gone.
I'm just going to go, I'm just going to smoke out of my ears.
Like the demon.
There it is.
Like, fuck you.
Kick it into the sewers.
I'm just going to immerse myself.
I'm just going to boil a cauldron and dunk myself in it.
Let's talk about, let's talk about times we were super sick though, because that's interesting.
Stop me if I've told this story before, but there was a time when I was really young
and I had a crazy high fever.
Have I told this before?
I remember that.
I remember the dead made me think you were going to die.
I know I've said this before, but I remember they measured my temperature and it was something
like, I think it was like 106.7 and there's something about how brain damage starts at
like 107 or something like that.
Well, now we know.
Right on the edge.
This is why I am the way I am, but I was so delusional and out of my fucking mind, I
had these crazy dreams about Lord Ooze from the Power Rangers movies that still haunt
me to this day.
Ivan Ooze.
That's right.
With his Ooze.
Yeah.
It just, I was completely out of my mind and I don't remember what was happening in
the real world.
I only remember what happened in the Ooze world, the better world, where I wanted to be.
Do you think Ivan Ooze is...
It was the first visit to Slime City.
Yeah.
I was the pioneer.
Is Ivan Ooze a rowdy or a killer?
He's definitely a rowdy.
Well, you know, look at him.
He strides the line, I guess.
He dresses like a killer.
You know, I guess you're right.
I was thinking that Ooze-ness made him rowdy, but now I think about it.
Everyone's a ooze.
Yeah.
That describes the territory.
I guess he is a killer now that I think about it.
Yes, we got him.
We got him, boys.
Ivan Ooze has been recruited.
A guy I know in real life messaged me on Discord the other day being like, I tried to play,
I was enjoying your game until someone...
Until he actually started playing.
Until someone killed me, and I was like, haha, was it a rowdy or a killer?
And also, I hope you enlisted killers.
And he was like, I did enlist killers, but also it was a killer that killed me.
And I said, yes, we bullied you into joining.
I'm giving the guy who did it a promotion.
Nice job, Coonrat.
Good kill.
Way to go, dude.
Wasn't Coonrat a rowdy?
He switched a little while ago.
Oh, okay, okay.
Fucking traitors.
I have no respect for traitors at all.
There's a lot of them these days.
I know.
There's so many.
I've never switched.
No one is clean except...
The cleanest of all...
The cleanest of all are the mud puddle knights in the mud puddle Discord.
The Discord war is still happening except nobody cares at all.
Yeah, nobody cares.
It's a cold war now.
It's a funny meme, I guess.
But hey, guys, tell me more about when you were sick.
I want to know when you were sick.
The worst times that I've been sick...
I have huge tonsils, naturally.
I have huge and asymmetrical tonsils.
And sometimes, the right kind of illness will swell your tonsils up.
And that is awful for me, especially.
Does it choke you or something?
I mean, I can still breathe, but it just feels so bad to swallow or even just to exist.
That is the thing that I fear most when I get sick.
Is that my tonsils will swell up.
It's just a horrible, horrible experience.
It hasn't happened in a little while, which I'm glad for.
There was this one time where I thought I was going to die because I had a cold.
And it was just like an extreme situation where I had a cold for a while.
Sneezing and spluttering and the throat cold where it's all stuffed up and clogged up.
You got to have a drink.
And we were out driving somewhere and we were stopping.
And we got out to look at some cows or whatever.
I don't really remember.
But I had a fit of sneezing and coughing and I couldn't breathe.
My throat closed up with the stuff and I was like, oh shit.
I'm not in the safety of my home.
I'm not very close to a nice drink of water.
We're out on the road, out in the field.
And I'm like, what happens?
What will happen if I can't draw a breath right now?
I'm going to die right here.
And that panic increased the floundering and the spluttering.
And eventually I managed to cough it up.
But that was the closest I ever felt like I was going to die because of a cold.
I hate how fucking vulnerable.
I've said this before, but I'm terrified of getting stuffed up and choking to death.
This is giving me deja vu because I think I've told that story and then you followed up with that exact thing.
I think you're right.
Nonetheless, it still haunts me.
We're so vulnerable to just lack of air.
It's fucked up.
One body is weak.
Robot body is now. Transhumidism now.
How does she tag H plus?
Something that can really easily freak myself out is thinking about how we're basically in an ocean of air.
We're basically in a soup.
It's like a gas soup, but we're in this chemical soup that keeps us alive.
And if we were taken out of it, we would choke and die like a fish out of water.
And it's weird to think that what astronauts have to do is they have to preserve that aura around them.
They have to bring soup with them.
They have to bring the soup.
They have to bring that atmosphere with them in their little soup.
They have to keep themselves in a little artificial bubble of it.
Did you hear about the Chinese astronaut people?
They were trying to grow stuff on the moon.
They had a little cubicle and they had this little plant that they had.
I don't think it was bot flies.
There were some sort of flies in there.
They had fly eggs and plants.
And what they wanted to happen was the plant would grow and then create carbon dioxide.
And then the flies would create oxygen.
And then the flies would emerge because of the oxygen and then an ecosystem would form.
But it all died because on the other side of the moon, the nighttime of the moon is like minus 730 degrees centigrade.
It's like super duper freezing.
And it's dead.
And they fucked up.
And I don't know why they couldn't see that coming.
There's no way to even deal with that.
More important question.
Who the fuck allowed the Chinese on the moon?
Trump needs to get on that shit.
That's not allowed.
Our flag is up there.
Correct me if I'm wrong.
People think that the moon landing is fake.
Some people think that.
I thought we hadn't been to the moon since.
Correct? Or am I crazy?
I can imagine things have been to the moon.
I thought only America and Russia had a space program.
I thought the conspiracy was that the initial moon landing is fake, but we have since been there for real.
I wasn't sure.
I don't know either.
I thought that it was possible we had never been to the moon if the moon landing was fake.
I hear of things.
There's a radiation belt in space that a human could never pass through.
They die if they actually try to go to the moon, so it's impossible.
This is false, by the way.
These are all false lies.
Yeah.
But they may be false, but I still believe them.
We got any moon truthers in here?
Raise your hand if you're a moon truther.
Raise his paw.
Praise Luna.
Praise the moon.
Oh, that's what I'm talking about.
Luna should have taken care of that flower on the moon, that bitch.
Yeah, that fucking slag.
The flower that died?
The plant.
Why didn't Luna take care of it?
What an uncaring bitch.
Tell me more about times you were sick.
Mage, I bet you were sick.
You're a real sick puppy there, Mage.
Tell me more about it.
I have been sick so many times in my life.
Was it ever really bad?
Quite a few times, my favorite.
Actually, quite recently, when I was sick recently, my favorite had gone up to almost 39 Celsius.
I'm not sure how much that's in Fahrenheit.
What's that in real numbers?
102-ish, maybe a bit more.
Okay, it's pretty high.
Yeah, it was, yeah.
But it only lasted for like a day, so thankfully I survived.
I think I told you guys about the time when I got super really ill, when the gallbladder thing happened.
Yes, and you went to some kind of camp?
It's a health camp, yeah.
They put you in a concentration camp?
Yeah, that sounds terrifying.
No, it was a health camp, but oh man, the health camp was like...
A health camp or a hell camp?
Both.
You told me about this, and I don't know if we do health camps over here.
I've never really heard of such a thing.
Unless you were a Japanese during World War II, we never did health camps.
It was amazingly terrifying, because it was held in a building that survived since World War II, and it was really really old.
And the bathroom was absolutely terrifying.
Don't get me started about the showers.
I was going to say, they knew you were a weeb, which is why they put you in this concentration camp.
Any traces of Japanese culture had to be, you know...
No, man, the Japanese were the master race of the East, of the Orientals.
Yeah, but we did, well, okay, only the U.S., I think, did concentration camps.
Oh, we're talking about Japanese internal camps.
I don't know anything about all that.
Yeah, it was just... it was like very unpleasant to look at it.
I did not look forward to going to that.
What was the benefit of even going to a health camp?
Is that where doctors are or something?
Yeah, there were quite a few.
Doctors had me monitored what I had to eat, because I couldn't eat a lot of things, because of the whole gallbladder thing.
I don't remember the details, and I couldn't really describe it, but there were like a few treatment stuff,
and there were massages, and now you think massages are nice.
Those massages gave me...
I hate massages, but that's just me.
Like bruises. It was terrible, and it was even worse, because right before the trip towards the health camp,
I had like a really nasty fall, and like...
I hit my ribs on a very hard surface,
and I burned... it wasn't exactly burned, but when I tripped, it was like on...
Oh, like friction burn?
Yeah, friction burn. Yeah, it was friction burn on my foot, and some skin just was missing, so...
Dude, that was the worst.
Yeah, it was just before they tripped as well, so it was just...
Forget my gallbladder! Fix this!
Was everything in Japanese internment camps that they call it massages,
but actually just the guy would go in, and then two guys would hold them by the arms,
and a third guy would just work them over with brass knuckles,
just like punch them in the torso a bunch of times.
Was that what was going on?
It sounds about right.
But yeah, so the time I was actually sick before the camp, it was terrible,
because when I read about how people have experience with the whole pains of the gallbladder,
some people don't even have pains, and some people have mild pains,
and some people have pains that lasted up to four hours.
Mine, at the worst, lasted 16 hours.
I couldn't sleep, I couldn't eat, I lost a lot of weight,
and I was just constantly suffering for a month.
Oh man, I want to use weight, maybe I should fuck my gallbladder up.
What a story, man!
At some points, I went to the ER at least two times, I think,
and there were points, I just had to...
I was just crying with frustration, because I couldn't do anything.
Was this in the UK?
The pains started in the UK, and I went to the camp as soon as I got to Lafiania,
because the camp was in Latvia, so...
Little shit, bruh.
I mean, I got a mean tweet once, so I think I know a little something about the pain.
That lasts all damn day. Emotional pain is the real exquisite.
Hey, you know, speaking of mean tweets, I did a little drawing last night.
I drew mega-clifable, aka cliffangel.
That was nice.
And it's only got 57 likes, and I don't think that's enough.
Oh, that's the suffering.
Is there a worse pain?
Listen, no, it's really clever, guys, because I based its shape on mega-gangar,
because, like, gangar is cliffable shadow.
Why don't people appreciate me?
I didn't know that. You should really spell that out, so it's obvious.
You gotta really drill it home for the stupid people out there.
Yeah, I said it in a reply to someone else's, but now the vast people who don't engage with the tweet will never know.
Ben, it's because it wasn't pornography. You gotta have to make it pornography.
I used the fairy-type background from Pokemon Go, you know?
I did everything for these people, and they stabbed me in the back.
I googled USSR bathrooms, and I found a picture, and this bathroom is a lot nicer than the one I was stuck with.
That sucks, bruh.
Where's the...
This looks like the bathroom that I think I've talked about.
When I was living in Poland, the company I was working for set me up with a real nice apartment,
and then when I got fired, basically, I had to downgrade to moving downstairs and sharing a set of rooms with some 90-year-old woman.
I had a real shit bathroom that I had to heat the water manually.
It kinda looked like this, but darker, much darker. Dark, dark, yet darker, you might say.
The last apartment I lived in was gross and disgusting, but with the bathroom specifically, it was a...
Okay, it was better than this. It was definitely better than this, but there were roaches.
Moving out here, roaches have just become a part of life.
This might freak people out a little bit, but maybe every two days, every three days, a tiny little baby roach.
I'll just be at my desk working. I will see one walk across my desk.
Which means 100% there's way more somewhere else, and I don't know where.
That's disturbing to me.
One of the guys I live with, he saw a mouse, like a mouse just ran across his desk.
Oh, Christ.
This was a while ago, and we have killed lots of mice.
Excellent.
It is a fucking slaughterhouse. You don't want to talk about a constant... It's like mouse Auschwitz in here.
No, please don't talk.
You're gonna make that mouse skull throne, right? I mean, that's in the cards.
We haven't really seen them much, but last night, I saw one running around in the living room, and I was very incensed.
We have a bunch of traps still out. They haven't caught me in a while because their population has declined.
We've been on a genocide run, and I knew they wouldn't be gone that easy.
Dude, Sans is gonna be so mad at you.
No, we've reduced the population enough that I no longer hear them scrabbling around in the ceiling above my room every single night, which was going on for a while.
Well, that's good.
And the thing about that, see, I think it was mice, but something about the acoustics amplified the sound.
It sounded like a full fucking raccoon was running around, like feet above my head, which was very, very upsetting.
God, talk about sickness. We live in a sick world where you have to still deal with the fact that things besides humans live in this fucking planet.
They're gross. I wasn't gone.
We get out of here.
It is pretty gross.
We should really segregate.
We need to.
My least favorite, surprisingly, is Big Old Spiders.
When I see a Big Old Spider, because they're so slow, they're so, like, keep to themselves.
At the moment, there's been a Big Old Spider just in the bathroom, and occasionally, you know, I just walk in there and, oh, he's in that corner now.
He's just hanging out in the top corner.
But, like, he doesn't do anything.
At the moment, he's, like, squished his arms in.
So he's just trying to get comfortable, trying to get warm in the crevice, like, in between the wall and the ceiling.
It just looks kind of funny.
So I'm like, you know what? You can stay. I don't really give a shit.
Actually, though, since I have a cat, I don't want him to get numb.
So what I do is, like, I have, like, this...
I have specifically set aside, like, a little plastic container that has, like, the Q-tips for ears stuff.
Like, so I have an empty one.
So whenever I see a spider, I place one on top of the spider, then I slip a piece of paper or something like that under it
so I can pick up the spider, and then I release it into the wild through the window or the door or whatever.
Yeah. You know, I don't like spiders.
Everyone tells me, like, oh, but Ben, oh, what do you mean? They eat the other insects.
I think I've said this before, like, yeah, they eat the other insects, but they themselves are the worst and most disgusting of them all.
No.
The things I hate most are the things that are small and fast.
A small and fast spider is gross because you blink and it could be anywhere, and then it could go up your butt in the middle of the night.
When a spider jumps, I am spooked.
That's pretty freaky, yeah.
You know, the average American eats hundreds of thousands of spiders every year and they're asleep.
That's an exaggeration.
They just, they just cry.
As soon as you fall asleep, just they march in a line, just a huge army of them just cry.
Like, one giant spider shows up, like, pulls open your mouth and just shoves handfuls of spiders.
And just gives birth into your mouth, and like, they entire, they're entire, they're entire.
What?
No!
Dude, it's like Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets following the spiders into your mouth.
What do you think you're fighting?
I'm full of spiders! They're fighting their way out!
Oh, it's fucked up, bro.
Hey, but you know what? You know what, though?
Spiders? Fucking keto.
They're jokes on them, dude!
Yeah, that's good, that's good.
You know, I have a, my friend Chelsea sent me a, a while ago sent me a bag of a fucking, oh, cricket flower.
Which is made of crickets.
Right.
This is like a thing now, I don't know if it's a fad thing, or if it's something that is, I don't know if it's new,
or if it's something that's like, comeback, or just going to Vogue for whatever.
But, but eating with spiders, like, or eating with bugs, like bug ingredients.
I saw the worst thing yesterday of, of my life.
I suppose I want to try, I really want to try cooking with it, but I don't know what the fuck to make out.
Like, I don't know what cricket flower tastes like.
I'm sure you can find a recipe for it.
Just sub it in for regular flowers, but dude, okay.
I don't know, maybe.
Oh, was that, was at the gym on Friday, about to do a Q&A, and I totally...
Yeah, don't!
Wait, what?
Wait, did you know about this?
No, what the fuck is that?
Did we talk about this on the PCP?
I don't think we have.
Please explain.
You want to explain, Tom?
Yeah, okay.
So there's this weird meme that Kaze started of, of, there was this one time, I do, sometimes on Friday,
I'll just say, hey, I'm bored, ask me questions on Instagram.
Viewer engagement, great stuff, 10 out of 10, gets me in that algorithm.
I do the research, I know how it works.
But I guess one time I said...
SEO, SEO, SEO, yeah.
There's not much SEO on Instagram, there's not a lot of search.
Well, I guess there's kind of, whatever, doesn't matter.
Point is, I came back from the gym and said, oh, I just got back from the gym, I'm bored, ask me questions.
And then like two weeks later, Ben and Kaze and Munchie are all laughing at me saying,
I do Q&A at the gym all the time.
I'm like, this happened once.
No.
But now I'm just leaning into it, because it's fucking hilarious.
Kaze just, she brought up, she was like, hey, do you guys know about Tom on Instagram?
And I'm like, no.
And she's like, yeah, he's always just like, hey guys, just got back from the gym to have a little Q&A.
Dude, he goes to the gym.
The way she said it was so fucking funny.
And I'm like, wait, really?
And she's like, yeah, I'll prove it.
Let me look and find his latest Instagram.
And it's him saying like, hey guys, just got back from the gym, you know, let's do a Q&A.
And I'm like, oh, okay, I guess that's proof.
He does this every day, like every day to just get back to the gym.
Tom puts on his gym clothes.
He goes to the bench rack.
He lies down under the bench bar and he fires up Instagram.
And he's like, guys, just have a workout in my brain.
Send me those questions right now.
He's like in the leg press machine.
He's doing a little Q&A, like between each rep.
Oh dude, Tom goes, he stands in the squat rack to do his Q&A.
He's ready to go.
Well, people line up around the block to use that fucking epic legendary machine.
But Tom's going to need that to do his fucking Q&A.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm working out the algorithm.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Damn, okay.
Excellent.
So you're at the gym doing a Q&A.
Anyways, Ben, I was at the gym doing Q&A.
And all of a sudden I stopped and freeze because there's a TV on.
And the TV's advertising the keto diet as like a cool thing you should do.
Oh fuck.
Whoa.
Who makes money off an ad like that?
There's just some company was selling keto powder.
What was it?
Was it bulletproof?
No.
It was like some other, they just said keto in the name.
They're just like, you got to get on the keto diet.
People have been promoting it.
And all these fucking single moms talking about how they're losing weight and shit.
Jillian Michaels is against the keto diet.
It's going mainstream.
There's been a big spat over that.
Yeah, that was trending on Twitter a little while ago.
Yeah, that's because there was like a big tussle.
I think I'm going to talk about this less than what's-her-face and Al Roker.
They were in a little bit of a debate about keto.
Oh, Al Roker.
Oh shit.
Al Roker, he was one of the guys who was pushing it on like the daily show, whatever the fucking
it is, the morning show, something.
He was like a big pro keto guy, but you know, whatever.
Anyway.
It's mainstream and it's not cool anymore is what I'm saying.
We got to dig further.
We got to dig deeper.
Got to find something even sicker now.
Yeah.
What was the end of that Jim Q&A story?
Oh, the keto diet.
Just the keto.
Yeah, you saw that.
It's on TV.
It's mainstream now.
It's terrifying.
Once keto becomes moved off the internet.
What comes next after keto?
I mean, keto is just like the latest iteration.
You know, there was the Atkins diet, which is basically the same.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
Look, the next thing is just once we start seeing fuel ads on TV, that's when we know
all is lost because there's nowhere to go from there.
Where do you go from post food?
There's no food.
I just kill yourself.
I mean, I want to go straight to Blade Runner world of, well, okay.
I suppose Matrix World.
Like every shop only sells nutrition slop.
I only want the option to eat perfectly balanced nutrition slop.
I want no other options.
I want capitalism to solve my weakness for me by knowing better than what I know for myself.
Capitalism is not going to solve your weakness.
It's going to exploit your weakness.
You want the invisible hand of the free market to drive a forced consensus that becomes truth.
Yeah.
Exactly.
That's exactly how it works.
Well, it's how I want it to work.
If you buy, you know, all new...
It's how capitalists would work ideally.
All new nutrition slop now with trough.
Free trough.
Like turning enough slop box tops or slop tops as we call them.
I get a free trough from the mail.
I can see Nate setting up his shop now.
Brand spanking new food.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's just, you know, let's take it to the logical stream.
You just, you sit down at like a bar.
What you do is you just stick an IV into an injection port.
Nate, you got to start a new health brand called the best food ever.
That's a good idea.
But, okay.
Like in the matrix, they have those port, like in the back of their brain or whatever.
Just everyone on their arm or their shoulder or whatever just has a little like hole.
No.
You sit down at like a fucking charging station.
You just plug in the thing.
It just gives you the nutrition you need.
You don't even have to use your worthless gob of a mouth.
No.
Which is only for passing the word of God and nothing else.
What I want, what I want, is I want the Metal Gear Rising Future where you have a cyborg
body in order to replenish your life essence.
You just slice somebody in half, rip their spine out and absorb your electrolytes.
Yes.
And then you're immediately back at 100% HP.
Do you drink that?
Or does he just kind of absorb it?
He just kind of crushes it.
He just kind of crushes their spine.
Is it actually their electrolytes?
Yeah.
The guy, Doctor, the character who's of German doctor, spelled D-O-K-T-O-R, says you absorb
electrolytes to regain your energy.
So he could just as easily just down a Gatorade, but he chooses.
The spine is just filled with Gatorade.
Who has time to get Gatorade when you're slicing geckos in half?
You've got to do what's out on the field, bro.
You've got to play that fucking game.
It's so good.
Yeah, one day.
One day I'll get to it.
Dude, that's where Maka came from, Nate.
You know that, right?
Is that true?
I mean, in the end of the game, he says straight up he's going to make America great again.
Oh, hell yeah, dude.
It's the best fucking shit ever.
Well, now I've got it.
This is like two years before Trump.
No, no, no, no.
The Matthew Matosis video.
Like, I'm not a Metal Gear Solid guy.
I've only played the first one.
So, you know, I didn't play Rising, but like the Matthew Matosis video.
Yeah, when he's talking about Armstrong, I was like, this is the coolest fucking thing
I've ever seen.
Like, by the end of the game, I'm just like, I just want to die.
I want Armstrong to win.
He's so, so justified.
Armstrong is based.
Yeah, he kind of is.
In the way that, yeah, he's so fucking cartoonishly terrible that you're like, I love him so much.
So, Armstrong, okay, so he's willing to sacrifice innocent lives for the sake of helping America be the best.
Pretty standard American politics, I guess.
I suppose it makes sense.
Like, this is what we do.
How did Koji get America that much?
That's what's being a West Abuse all about.
That was just so fucking computer.
It's just like we get Japan so much.
It's the same thing.
I love Japan, period.
Yeah.
Nate, serious idea.
You're a fitness guy.
Yeah.
If you wrote, like, okay, like Tom, your friend, Jack's Blade, he wrote like the book.
He wrote a book, right, about diet and stuff.
He made a million dollars.
He made a hundred thousand dollars in two weeks.
If you wrote, like, a diet book and you just called it, like, the best diet ever or whatever, or best workout ever, you made, like, a health guide or something.
I bet you would make, I bet you would make.
If Scooby, if Scooby ever found out, okay, you know what I'd do though, what Scooby does, my fitness hero, is he'll make a video called, like, the bread diet, or like, he made the W diet was his thing.
And then we actually, and it's like, you'll get instant results in, like, one week.
That is a joke.
What it actually is, is, like, a technique to, like, get you to be accountable to, like, the calories you consume, because whatever.
The W diet is, you literally eat anything, change nothing, you just count the calories, which will just awaken you to how much you're fucking up with your diet.
That's the whole point.
And if I could also write a book that appears to be tricking people into thinking that it's just an easy solution, and then actually redpills them on how hard and how they need to take responsibility for this shit, that I could live with.
That I could live with.
So maybe that's the way to go.
That's a pretty neat maneuver.
I really like the idea that since you're a YouTuber and you have like, you know.
No, Nate, just fucking lie to them.
Just fucking tell them what they want to hear.
That's what the money's at.
That's fair.
It'll be like, at the end of the book, you'll be like, alright guys, thanks for reading my book.
Be sure to subscribe.
Hey guys, sorry I haven't written a book in a while.
That's something that's the first page of the book.
I'm going to ring that notification bell so you can see when my next book is published.
Hell yeah.
Start your book out.
Hey guys, sorry I haven't written a book in a while.
I've been pretty sick and I got a new microphone.
I got a keyboard, so sorry if the font is weird.
I got a new typewriter.
Damn, that's good.
The thing is though, I need to actually get in actually impressive shape before I write
anything along those lines.
Maybe this year.
Yeah, you need to be at least 20 feet tall.
You need to be fucking ripped for the photo on the front of the book.
That's unironically true.
It's unironically true.
That's true.
I think so.
Who's going to want to listen to some fat fuck who just like, maybe he went to school
for nutrition.
There's two ways.
You've got to be really jacked on the cover or you can be like a sort of old guy.
Like a healthy family man kind of thing.
You can be like a family if you're a doctor.
If you're a doctor you can just look like a pretty good shape family man.
Yeah, I buy that.
I buy that.
But that's what Scooby always says.
Like the reason that you're shirtless is like, these are the goods folks.
Take a look.
This is what you get.
The proof is in the pudding.
He says jiggling his pecs, pudding-like.
Gross.
Dude, you know who's pudding-like?
My dog.
Gross.
But he sits down.
Okay, I'm just saying.
Sessho, Lord's a showbrew.
Looks like a streamlined alpha male athlete most of the time when he's up and he's squeaking
on his frog pepe.
I didn't realize.
But when he sits down and his skin becomes loose.
He looks like a lasagna.
And it's dope.
Yeah, he looks like a straight lasagna.
I didn't realize he's like part corgi, right?
So he's pretty squat.
Sessho is half corgi and half beagle is what they tell us.
I don't know if I believe that.
But that's what they say when we got him.
He's pretty based.
He shows up in the new Weagua.
Go check it out, everybody.
Yeah, I saw you cradling him.
Oh, yes.
My new, my Poochiana.
He's a funny guy.
Dude, somebody commented, he is a funny guy.
He's a good lad.
I was like, oh, I caught a new weird Alolan Poochiana or a weird fucking Radita or whatever.
But someone said, no, no, no, Nate, you're wrong.
What he is is he's a, what, I think it's a rock and rough, like that rock Pokemon from
Alola.
Rock and rough.
Yeah.
Rock, rough and like and rock.
Rock, rough.
He is most like a rock, rough that guy.
You're right.
You win.
Why is there no corgi Pokemon?
Hmm.
I don't know.
There's not many dogs.
What was that crack?
Crack was a, was that big fluffy guy who's a Scotty or something.
Oh God.
What's, what's the fucking?
Yeah.
I can't remember.
Skit.
Oh, it was, it was a skit.
I don't remember.
It was, it was like, it was like, it was like Mayan.
It was like, man, I had my Spanish teacher in high school.
Mr. Remember Mr. Cibella?
Of course.
Yeah.
Mr. Cibella, he taught us how to pronounce like Mayan or Incan language and like, I
remember, I remember one word in whatever fucking language it was like, it was like,
like that was a word.
Yeah.
What do you mean?
I don't, whatever.
Like, I don't know.
That's important.
It had like, it had like, you know, weird glottal stops and like all these weird things
about it were important to the meaning that like in English is not even.
Damn.
That's cool.
That's how I remember it.
I think that's, I said it a lot.
I remember I said a lot.
So I hope I, I really want to, I want to learn a language like that or something like Chinese
where like inflection itself like makes a big difference in like what you're actually
saying.
It just sounds really cool.
I want to awaken my brain to that.
I took China in college.
It was very weird to speak it.
Do you say you took Chinese?
Yeah.
In college.
Oh, that's cool.
So, so, so you know a little bit about that.
Yeah.
It was weird like having to like, because like you have to know the different tones and
like they have like a tongue twister where like it's just the same word like five times
but the tone changes.
Yeah.
That's a good exercise.
Do you remember how it goes?
No, I do not remember.
Fuck.
There's a tongue twister in the thing and it sounds like all the words are very similar.
Dude, hit us with it.
What does it mean?
Okay.
So there's a very, there's a repeat of the word good.
Yeah.
So it's like good men drink good class in a good forest.
I think that's.
Wait.
Drink, drink good what?
A class.
It's a, it's a type of drink.
It's not alcoholic sort of.
It's made out of bread, I think.
Whoa.
Cool.
That's not keto.
Not at all.
Wait, wait.
Out of dark bread.
Say it again.
Get it, get it, get it, get it, get it, get it.
I love it.
I do.
It sounds like a one-piece villain laugh.
Like a special.
He does.
He fucking does.
Is Lithuanian, does it have any of that inflection stuff that like Chinese does, or is it just
like that the words are automatapias or not automatapias, but you know, synonyms or whatever
the fucking word where they sound the same, but they are the same.
Some words do, but in this case, it's just, it's just the words are very similar.
Yeah.
Okay.
In English, we got, we got the buffalo, buffalo, buffalo, buffalo, buffalo, which is a sentence.
Is it?
Yeah.
Buffalo the verb, buffalo from buffalo or something.
What the hell does buffalo the verb mean?
I don't know.
That's the one that fits me up.
It's like, it's like archaic, but it means to like bother or bully someone, I think,
like fuck with someone.
Okay, that's pretty cool.
Or no, no, irritate.
It means to irritate someone is to buffalo them.
Ladies and gentlemen out there, learn a second language because it's fucking dope and you
won't regret it.
It's super fun.
First buffalo, adjective, second buffalo, noun, third buffalo, verb, fourth buffalo,
adjective, fifth buffalo, verb.
I think there's a longer sentence like that.
She has six in a row.
How weird is it?
I mean, when I had, I had a good English teacher in like eighth grade, Mr. Clark, I think,
and he like taught me everything I know about like adjectives, nouns, fucking adverbs,
gerunds, fucking infinitives or whatever.
I learned literally everything I know about grammar from that man and he was based as
fuck.
But beyond that, I learned even more about English by learning Japanese and like having
to stop and actually examine the language I was using.
I think I'm learning Japanese every time, every time someone says learning Japanese,
I do that.
So I'm just kidding.
Well, let's make this the last time, shall we then?
I just, learning another fucking language is such a useful thing.
It's just so funny to me how I could have gone my whole life if I just hadn't had that
one class with Mr. Clark and I hadn't, you know, whatever, started to learn Japanese,
I would have never even examined the language that I'm using.
Like right now, I am not stopping to examine like the verbs and the nouns and the adjectives
and the sentences I'm using.
They just roll off my brain.
Yeah, it's just a way of like translating the thoughts.
It's pretty cool.
How are you so good at that?
Is that weird?
It's pretty fucking weird.
It's pretty fucking unique.
It's pretty unique in the animal kingdom.
Oh, that reminds me of something.
Like I was thinking a while ago about like drawing and how like, you know, everyone can
draw, but like the longer it takes for you to start drawing, the harder it is.
Because when you're a little baby, you pick things up incredibly quickly.
And language is like a prime example.
Like if you grow up around people speaking a language, you won't even need a class.
You'll just get it.
You'll understand it so inherently that it will be hard to like forget it ever.
And then it seems to be so.
Shit.
It's cool.
But it's also annoying because like if I wanted to learn a language, I should have been doing
it since I was 10 or any skill.
I heard that like kids raised in like bilingual homes that grow up bilingual, like are just
smarter.
They just like do better on tests.
It's just better, man.
It's just better.
I think.
I mean, I started learning English since I was four.
So I, and I'm not, I'm not smart.
You've got mage here, the counter example to this whole idea.
Meg Tao, Meg Tao, Meg Tao.
Mage Tao, mage Tao.
The funny thing about.
Yeah.
No, no, my weakness.
Tom, what were you saying?
I was just going to say the, cause you were talking about the tones and stuff and like
the different like, like annunciations on words.
The interesting thing I learned in the Chinese class was that the teacher was saying like,
oh yeah.
The interesting thing about Chinese music is that in order to like stay on pitch, you
have to like say the word with a tone that's actually a different word and you just have
to know through like context clues what they're actually trying to say.
That makes sense.
That's tougher.
Oh wait, by the way, I just want to say Tom, learn Chinese, communist, confirm.
Yeah.
Make sense.
All right.
Did you guys hear Econ speak any Chinese?
No, I don't think they ever have.
Not much.
Maybe he just did use around, but no, sometimes like, oh, we went out to, that's really funny.
We were, when he was first got here, we were walking around in like Chinatown, you know,
cause like, I think me and Munchie were just taking him, just going, oh and Zen.
It was me, Munchie, Zen and Econ and we walked around and we went to Chinatown and we went
to that bubble tea place, Tito.
Bubble tea.
And yeah.
That's good to hear.
Like, they wouldn't do it with no sugar.
Oh yeah, yeah, no keto.
He tried to order in Chinese and he was very disappointed when the people speaking there
didn't speak Chinese.
But then we went to a restaurant.
We went to this restaurant, Nate, we went to this restaurant later.
Remember that place with the round table, the spinny round table?
Yeah, it was Chinese as fuck, I remember.
It was Chinese as fuck.
And we went there with him before and he, the wait staff there speak terrible, terrible
English and it's very irritating cause they don't know phrases that they really should
know, like, split the check.
They should know what split the check means.
You should learn that in fucking English cause they're gonna fucking live in America.
But so, so he, so he.
Build the wall, build the wall, build the wall.
But he did, he talked to them in Chinese and they talked back to him.
That's cool.
And man, God, and he ordered that fucking, the stinky tofu.
The stinky tofu.
Yeah.
It was horrible.
It was the most horrible smell and taste.
It tasted exactly like it smelled.
Oh, he loved it.
I bet, I bet though, I bet Econ was just lording that club.
He was just absolutely dominating the social space.
He absolutely was.
But it's funny cause like his, his voice, like the way that he speaks, like he has a,
he doesn't have an accent, but he has a way of speaking that is unusual.
But when he speaks in Chinese, it makes perfect sense.
It's like.
Yeah.
I mean, what's his, is his first language Chinese?
I mean, I don't know.
Yeah, he grew up in China.
Really?
For some, I don't know how long.
For some reason.
Maybe he was born there.
I don't know.
I wouldn't have made the same choice.
He is huge.
I think he, yeah.
His first language is Chinese, but he moved to America when he was pretty young.
I mean, yeah.
His English is like perfect.
So, you know.
Yeah.
Anyway.
That's a.
Cultures are cool.
Languages are cool.
Seriously, people, you won't even know, learn a fucking other language.
It's so beneficial.
I feel so bad I have not kept up on my Japanese.
I'll get back to it.
I think he said that like he was talking to the waitress in Chinese and then, you know,
he's saying all his, he's saying all his weird moon speak and whatever and then he gets done
and he's like, yeah, she was, she was asking me if it was stinky enough.
Lol.
And oh, it was, I mean, she didn't need to ask in my opinion.
I really should like, I've always felt like I want to learn Arabic and I've never really
even thought.
I've never really even taken the first steps into figuring out where I could learn something
like that.
But I, but I feel like, you know, those Arabs over there, if you go to Arabia, if you go
to the Middle East, they don't really like Western white people.
But if you speak their language, they'll be like, I guess he's okay.
I guess, I guess we won't like detain him for no reason.
I hope you're saying it works that way.
They love Westerners and like, what's that one that's like the Dubai, like Dubai?
That's India.
That's a little different.
That's not India.
Dubai is fucking and it's like next to Saudi Arabia.
Oh, yeah.
It's like, it's like a little offshoot.
What am I thinking of?
Like Princeton or whatever.
I don't know.
You're thinking of India, I think.
Well, there's a, at least I, okay.
I got to double check this.
Are you thinking of like, Bouddha, the Buddha?
No.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm right.
Dubai is in fact next to Saudi Arabia.
Okay.
Well, I'm thinking of New Delhi or something.
Yeah.
Now, my English isn't even in India.
The interesting thing about learning another language, at least in my experience and Nate,
you could like totally fucking shoot me down on this since you've studied Japanese.
Is that priming my rifle and prepping my bullets?
I think I've studied Japanese.
Okay.
Last one.
Discuss.
You better be.
No.
Like, in high school, I took a little bit of Spanish and I took a lot of German.
I didn't learn anything.
It was very difficult for me, for my brain to understand.
Because I was learning Chinese and it was totally like different, like it was just like
characters and not like, you know, letters and stuff.
And it was just like so different from the language I was used to.
Instead of like looking at something like Spanish or German and approaching it thinking
like, oh, trying, like my brain was trying to like look at those words as I would in
English and like pronouncing them in English.
With Chinese, it was so separate.
I just like, this is something totally new.
And I took to it much quicker than those other languages.
Yes.
I took it about the same way.
Having to start from the absolute basic thing of you and learning what the fucking characters
say.
And like, just starting from that, forming the simplest possible things of that way, totally
made me step into it from a new perspective.
Yeah, it was great.
I studied, I studied a little bit of Japanese when I was younger and you know, I just learned
the very basics.
But it was really interesting just how like their whole sentences are just structured
like different.
It's just like the way that like the word no is used, for example.
You mean like the possessive no?
Yeah, the possessive no.
Yeah, yeah.
But how like the order is reversed.
How do you describe the possessive no?
You don't say, you don't say, you don't say Ben's cock, for example.
You say cock, you say cock-o-no Ben.
No, that's actually not true.
You say, I mean, if you want to say like my cock, it'd be like what Tashino cock.
That's what I said.
You fuck.
No, you put Ben second.
You said cock-no-ben.
No, I didn't.
Wait, really?
I think so.
Okay.
Well, the point is you put the pronoun or the noun or pronoun first, which, okay, maybe
Ben meant to do that, whatever.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, no, no, it's reversed.
No, dog, you say what Tashino like Ken would be like my fist or whatever.
Wait, no, it wasn't the order.
It was like that like, oh God, well, okay, but the possessive doesn't mean, see, this
is, see, okay, obviously this was a long time ago and I forgot shit, but it like, it doesn't
mean, it's not the same as like the possessive.
It's like, does, can you use the possessive to mean like other things than like ownership
or something?
Like, like, you can just use it to like say other things.
Maybe probably.
It has like a broader application.
Nothing comes to mind, but it doesn't sound crazy.
Oh no, I'm thinking of adjectives, right?
Don't you say like, don't you, you, you put the adjective second, right?
You do put the ad, oh yeah, I'm just gonna say like big truck.
You put like truck and yeah, yeah.
Something like that.
That's what I'm thinking.
It's a bit similar to German, they always put the verb second.
I just drew the verb.
And then if there's another verb, like a second year verb, these sort of put it last, something
like that, it's been a while.
Yeah, yeah, I don't know.
It's tough to keep all these things like that.
Languages are weird.
We all need to learn Esperanto, so we can all talk to each other.
I wouldn't mind that.
I suppose I wouldn't mind that.
Although, you know, when it comes to, when it comes to language, that's when I start
to think like, wow, cultures are cool because I like doing like looking at different languages
and it makes you think differently too, depending on what language you're using.
Like the fact that Japanese has different tenses for politeness.
Like that, when I learned that, I was like, what the fuck is that about?
That's just like, that's so informative of the culture itself.
No, for sure.
It's cool.
I think, I don't think something like Esperanto should like replace languages as we have now,
but I think everyone should just learn it.
Maybe that's just everyone new Esperanto in addition to like, yeah, yeah.
So like you had a way of talking to other people and it'd be a great way of like opening
up the world to more like experiences.
Like if you can just go somewhere knowing, being confident that someone speaks like the
same tongue you do and then like you can slowly like learn more shit.
This is relatively recent, but like at the UN, because like it's people from like everyone
in the fucking world.
The reason that all the representatives have those little earpieces is because they've got
translators like working on their staff who understand whoever happens to be speaking.
Maybe it's a fucking Arab guy and you've got like a French dude, they, they like on their
staff.
They have like a guy who speaks French and Arab translating live into their ear so that
everyone can communicate.
And it's like, I mean, that's really cumbersome, but like that's also cool that that's all
happening.
That guy's job is going to get replaced with Google assistant at some point.
That's true.
I give him five years, he better be looking for a new job.
My favorite thing about different languages and cultures is that, you know, I can Google
some, some cool shit and then I can get information as to like how to make, to come up with my
own world building.
Like I can base things off of stuff that happened in other countries that I'm not aware of at
the moment because like, you know, I'm thinking of a name of a place and I'm thinking what
sort of place it's like and I just researched places that exist and civilizations and cultures
and it's just like, you get, you get really good ideas because like humans, they're, they're
very different depending on where they like evolved and grew up all over the world.
I only know what it's like to be me, just like if I want to, if I want to write stories
about all sorts of weird, wacky, fantastical places, I need to know a lot about what humans
have done and it's cool.
Yeah.
My favorite thing about there being different cultures is that I'm in the best one, baby,
in the US of A.
Fill that wall, say can you see by the darkness.
It feels good to be number one.
I'm launching the nukes right now.
No.
Does England have nukes?
I don't think they have nukes.
We have nukes.
They're just like really.
I think you're bluffing.
No, we have a nuclear program.
That's all I know.
It was brought up in the recent, like, well, that recent, it's like what do we do with
the nukes, huh?
What do we do with that nuclear program?
Who doesn't have a nuclear program?
Yeah.
I got a nuclear program in my backyard right now.
I got a fission, I got a fission reaction for you.
Hey, remember in Watchmen when Richard Nixon is like, let's see, I'm trying to think their
way out of fission?
That's a stupid line and I hate it.
That's all.
Well, isn't that supposed to be like Nixon is dumb and that's why I said it?
Okay.
Yeah.
Shit.
It's embarrassing.
I feel embarrassed for him when he says that.
Hippo said that like, oh, isn't Nixon supposed to be stupid and then my brain immediately
got trapped and like, oh God, if Watchmen was made today, it would be some weird Trump
parody and it would be so awful and I would hate it.
It fucking would be true.
Wait, well, hang on.
Watchmen was set in the past when it was made, right?
Yes.
But I'm saying it would probably be like W. It'd be like W being stupid.
Yeah.
I don't want to relate to these things.
In a few decades, there will be something where Trump is like, you know, the bad guy
and he's like, ah, he's dumb.
I'm looking forward to future where we make jokes about how dumb we were back when we
elected Trump and what a crazy time in America's history.
Guys, isn't like the newest purge kind of like poking fun at Trump sort of?
And by the way, Trump, he embarrasses me every day.
Our country embarrasses.
You guys know what I'm doing.
I'm doing the Quentin reviews thing.
All right.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
I don't give a shit.
Just Trump really embarrassed America that much.
I just don't pay attention.
I think he sounds like an idiot sometimes, but I don't know.
One thing I always feel is that I hate, I hate them, the majority.
Like when the majority hates Trump, I'm like, well, maybe he's not so bad.
Maybe he's actually okay.
And then everybody in the normal media that I've known all my life to be annoying and
stupid is this time also being annoying and stupid.
And Trump is just kind of an idiot sometimes.
I mean, it seems super clear to me that it's just, so they're trying to apply the standard
rule set of like, like if Obama said the things that Trump said, like, yes, people would
freak out and they'd be upset, but Trump, like he's literally just doesn't give a fuck.
He just is like, I'm just going to fucking meme on these people literally.
And so it's just, it's just kind of weird to apply like the same standard because he's
not trying to do it.
And no matter, I just feel like people get that like, no matter how much they try to
say like, if Obama did this, you know, we'd all be pissed.
Trump just is a different guy and he just doesn't give a fuck.
And I kind of just respect that because I also don't give a fuck.
I mean, I respect not giving a fuck.
Yeah.
That's it.
That's all I'm saying.
Yeah.
We should have somebody who does give a fuck.
I guess that's the thing.
Yeah.
Actually, I take that.
The thing is, well, the thing like, you know, the current thing that's happening where the
government is shut down because Trump is not getting his way, um, well, it's not all
on him though.
It's not all on him.
The other guy is, you know, no, no, no, I like it because, um, it's the first time
I've seen a politician like push so hard for their own policy that they were elected
for.
Yeah.
And I mean, the horrible though.
But that's a fucking horrible thing to do.
Well, yeah, but like, I just, I just think that I would prefer politicians to be crazy
and very like, like, like, I would prefer them to be like more true to their word than
Ben, you know, they have been for the last billion years where everything they say is
false because they don't actually do anything that they're going to do.
People say that Trump is the most honest president we've ever had, which I don't have.
I don't have insight into that, but like, I just like the honesty.
It's really nice.
His name's Honest Abe.
Well, Ben, you say that it's horrible, but like, like from another perspective, like
what Trump's doing, you could argue, is fighting really, really hard for the, the one issue
that he mostly got elected on.
And isn't it fair for him to really fight for the thing that the people elected him
for?
Whether or not you agree with it?
No, it's not, it's not fighting.
He's shutting down the government is like refusing to have the fight because he knows
that if the fight happens now, he'll lose.
Well, that's not true though, because like the point, what the government shut down
over is that like the proposed budget that the, whatever, the Senate has given him or
whatever does not include allocation for him making the wall.
And like because he has said, well, that's unacceptable, go make one that does have,
you know, funding for the wall.
They have said, no, we're not going to do that.
So it's that stalemate that has, you know, like now the government is not funded because
that money has not come through.
So because we're in that position, it's like, okay, Trump could give in and say like, okay,
I guess we'll just fund the government.
Now those people who currently aren't at work or whatever.
Boy, and what a shame that would, what a concession that would be.
Well, I mean, that would be a massive concession because that was his main thing.
That was his number one issue.
You can't, you can't just not have the government because your fucking bill isn't going through.
I don't know, the libertarians are pretty happy about it.
But libertarians can go, can take a long walk off a short pier.
I mean, I feel, I legitimately feel bad for everybody who's like, who is, you know, isn't
at work because of all this shit that totally sucks.
And I, you know, like I'm very far removed, I'm very far removed from what's happening
at the moment.
I just like, I just like that he's honest and like, like pushes for his stupid ideas
that he has because I just don't see that anywhere else ever.
There's something to like about it.
Yeah.
I mean, you know, and then people can absolutely come in and be like, no, it's irresponsible.
It's not good.
XYZ.
But you just feel like the visceral, you know, Jesse-esque response of like, you know what?
Fuck it.
And there's something satisfying.
We should, we should resist that.
We should resist that.
It's bad and it's bad.
I hear what you're saying.
And it's fucking bad.
Just, you can't, this is like, you know, I'm no expert.
I'm no expert.
Maybe I shouldn't even fucking open my big mouth, but like, I've heard, I've heard
that like, this is sort of, this is like a Republican thing these days of just don't
have, just don't govern, just filibuster until just, you won't, you won't, you won't get
your way.
So just like stun, stunlock everything so nothing happens until you can get your way.
Why don't the Democrats do the same thing though?
Is it because they're like better people?
Is it as simple as that?
Well, yeah.
I mean, all right.
There's an innuendo studios video about this and he, he says,
Lib cuck the Lurt everybody.
He's got some blue pills dropping.
His argument basically is that just Dems are better people and more principle.
Like Dems are acting out of principle while like Republicans are acting out of, you know,
like this is what gets the job done, which I don't know, maybe whatever, who knows.
But the point, I mean, it's still fucking shitty.
I hate it.
It's a gay.
Let's talk about something else.
All right.
That's fair.
Something else.
Last few days, I've been going back to season one of Steven Universe and I wanted to re-watch
it.
Oh, no.
What's, what's, what's bad about Steven?
No, the first season.
It's turning you gay.
It's turning.
Here's the thing.
Didn't you hear he voted for Trump?
Oh, yeah.
Dude.
Yeah.
Steven Universe is old enough to vote now.
Think about that.
Feel old yet?
All right.
Like, um, I, I had heard all the time, like, uh, after I got into Steven Universe, other
people had difficulty getting into it for things like, uh, ugh, Steven screams all the
time.
He's really annoying.
And I was like, hmm, I haven't watched the season one in a while.
Is that true?
Does he, is he really annoying the whole time?
And I have composed a list of, of the Steven episodes.
I've watched the first season or the first half of the first season up until, uh, Lapis
was introduced and then she flies off into space.
Um, and I, I have, I have the numbers and I will post them in the chat.
Oh shit.
Okay.
Wait, what numbers?
What, what stats did you crunch?
Is this going to be a new, give or take, uh, compilation video?
Is that what you're, you're grooming right now?
This is, uh, the, the, the, well, you'll see.
Uh, okay, so this is, every episode is described as either good or shut up.
Steven.
And the link, the show notes, so like surprisingly, surprisingly, the first seven are not shut
up Steven.
They are actually good.
And I liked the whole thing, but episode eight, 10 and 12, he does scream like basically
all of his lines.
He doesn't have a single soft spoken line in the whole episode.
Uh, you can look them up or you can, whatever.
Um, I think, I think, I think 12 is giant woman.
He's like, please be a giant woman.
It's a really good episode, but shut up, Steven, like he really wants to see a giant
woman and I forgot how much, you know, don't we all know, I remember that like, I don't
understand that, that he has that particular obsession in that one episode, but the raw
emotions at the end where he's scared that, that, uh, you know, whatever, the opal won't
like him or something.
Oh, it's like, do you know who I am?
And then she starts singing.
Oh, yeah.
That's the best.
A C tune and two.
A giant woman.
Oh, yes.
That is Kino television right there, folks.
Wait, he has a soft spoken line because he whispers a giant woman, theory busted.
Debusted.
No.
It's hard destroyed by facts and logic.
Yeah, facts don't care about your feelings, hippo, this list of moots.
No, no, the shut up, Steven.
I mean, 12 was like on the fence.
I will admit.
So eight and 10 are like, God damn, I get it now.
I get why people are actually like, they quit at episode eight.
But some people, I'm sure quit at episode one because he does scream a bit like about
the cookie cat and stuff.
Right.
But like, overall, it's just a really good introduction to the whole like lore and the
gems and the three of them and the, you know, all that stuff.
Yeah.
And the action and the animation in the first like 26 episodes is really good as well.
It's just like, dang.
Hey, time for me to show time for me to be a pedant and gripe about how I still wish
they animated it traditionally instead of fucking flash.
Well, that ship is sailing now, hasn't it?
What did you say, mage?
I said you're an old fart.
Like every episode.
Oh, these old bones of mine.
Every episode.
No, they all had.
You complain about the youth in some form.
This isn't about the youth.
This is the new youthful way of making cartoons.
That pilot episode is old enough to be president now.
Are you old yet?
Okay.
Look, you know, it looked really cool.
It had that Rebecca Sugar style, which is way more unique than what we eventually got.
They all had the scary Rebecca Sugar Voldemort noses and also maybe unpopular opinion.
I know.
I know I'm not allowed to say this as a cis white male, but I preferred Garnet's long
straight hair to her big square afro.
There I said it.
That's a race war right there, ladies and gentlemen.
It has begun.
Yeah.
Okay.
So according to that's a race war.
I looked to my left.
That's a race war.
I looked to my right.
I do.
I do prefer the newer Pearl design in a way.
In a sense.
I don't know what I just think.
Oh, New Pearl is way better.
Way better.
I just didn't like her.
No.
Listen.
I just didn't like her old outfit.
It looked weird.
You mean in the pilot?
Yeah.
I don't remember what outfit she had in the pilot.
I just.
It's a gay ass shit boy.
It was way cool.
And the real show is lame.
But what do you even mean anyway?
Like with flash.
Like all the animation is drawn with a pen of some kind.
It's on a tablet, but it's with a pen.
Okay.
What do you mean?
Well, I mean, have you seen the pilot?
I haven't watched it in this rewatch.
Because I didn't like it the first time.
It looks way cooler in this man's.
But I remember Stephen being like a lard blob.
Yeah, it's a lard blob.
Look at these freaks.
Yeah, look at them.
It's great.
I don't like the pros.
Just for the record.
Episode 8, 10, and 12 are given shut up Stephen episodes.
And according to this list, Episode 8 is Sirius Stephen.
Episode 10 is Stephen's lion.
And Episode 12 is Giant Woman.
So there you go.
Those are the ones that suck.
Well, they don't suck.
I enjoyed every episode.
It was just like I could see what people were saying when he was shouting constantly.
The other ones, he does shout in basically all of them.
But it's not annoying to me until those ones.
I've said it before, but I have come back myself multiple times to just watch Stephen Universe.
Because Stephen Universe has a very unique, extremely...
I don't use this word often, but it's an extremely comfy atmosphere.
And I just like immersing myself in it.
Just watching the episodes of Stephen Universe.
Kind of in a way that I haven't with any other show.
But I imagine it's why people like Hitamari's sketch.
Probably for the same kind of reason.
It's just comfortable, I guess.
Since we're just talking about Stephen Universe,
do you know what's up with the new Stephen Bomb quote unquote?
Because it's not really a bomb.
It's not like weekly episodes, aren't they?
Yeah, but it's off the air now, right?
I mean, they're just...
No, there's one more tomorrow.
As of the recording on the 20th, the 21st is one more coming out.
Shit!
And it's like 44 minutes, isn't it?
It's our big one.
They actually made a real episode for once.
Not a piece of shit, maybe episode.
Well, I mean, I'm gonna watch that shit.
The last bomb I watched was so disappointing.
I wasn't hyped for more Stephen.
Look, White Diamond is cool.
The shit about Pink Diamond is pretty cool.
Connie was an idiot these episodes.
I mean, I don't know.
Honestly, no character is at all interesting or important right now, except for White Diamond.
The other two diamonds are kind of okay.
And Stephen.
Also Pearl a little bit, because we're gonna find out a little bit more about Pearl's backstory, probably.
So that's cool.
I feel like Pearl was...
I mean, it's pretty obvious that she was White Diamond's Pearl.
Me and Michelle have had an ongoing debate for years, I think, at this point.
I still don't accept that our Pearl was originally White Diamond's Pearl.
Michelle will go to her grave thinking this.
Why? Why not?
I just feel that way, I guess.
I don't know.
What would be so crazy about that?
My feelings don't care about your facts, Stephen Universe.
Okay, okay, guys.
I just want to say the only thing I could put my foot down, at least one foot on, that our Pearl was not originally Pink Diamond.
Pink Diamond's Pearl.
We know that for sure, yes.
Whether she was White Diamond's Pearl is...
She probably was.
I definitely feel like based on the way White Diamond acts towards Pink,
like, you're just a little, you know, whatever, little girl, just run along.
I could imagine that she gave Pearl to her to look, you know, to monitor her, to make sure she doesn't get into trouble.
But then Pearl was like, oh, but I love her.
And then they eloped, basically.
Why hasn't Pearl talked about White Diamond yet if she was White Diamond's Pearl?
She's got to have insider information.
She was fucking White Diamond's Pearl.
That's not even secret information. Just tell us about it, Pearl.
She could be the new replacement Pearl after the other Pearl was...
Maybe she had another secrecy curse put upon her.
Man, Pearl, fuck off. Just get over it already.
Just be real.
Just be cool, Pearl. Why can't you just be cool?
Like us and the procrastinators.
She needs to buy the I'm Just Being Cool t-shirt.
She does need to buy that.
Did you see Zen Huxtable's video, Responding to Sarah Z's video, Responding to Lily Pete's video about why set Rebecca Sugar as a fascist?
I don't... Oh, did you say a fascist?
Jesus Christ. What did you just say?
Wait, wait, you guys know about Lily Pete's video that says that the show is fascist, right?
No.
I'm up today on every video the little ones make.
I'm deep in there.
How can you be that little billy? Say that Steven Universe is fascist.
The video was a big deal. It made the rounds.
Okay, I guess I... Well, maybe I saw it, but I don't know.
I'm surprised. It was a little while ago.
Okay, so Lily Pete is an idiot and makes stupid things come out of her mouth whole.
And this other lady, Sarah Z, responded to it, and I'm going off of what Zen Huxtable says,
but responded to it wrong and criticized her on a bunch of things that she didn't actually say.
And Zen made a video responding to that being like, hey, there's all this legitimate stuff to criticize
and you fucked it up and just did it bad and made, you know, you fucked up, you dummy.
Sure, good.
Oh, fuck. No. No, I had a point, but I lost it.
No!
I don't know.
So how come you get mired in drama?
What were we talking about?
We're talking about her and how she's being cool and wearing a t-shirt.
I have had enough of, like, critique YouTube.
Like, the whole, like, commentator YouTube.
I agree.
Like, scene is dumb.
It's a meme that needs to die.
It's basically YouTube comments, but in video form, a.k.a. worse.
That's true.
I have to wait, like, a certain amount of time before I can run away.
I got it. I got it.
The point is that Lily Pete said something about, like, you know, people, like,
Cartoon Network released a video.
It's like, uh, well, here's all the hints that we dropped all along the way that pink, that rose was pink diamond.
And then there's a bunch of clips that do not prove it, that are totally, like, taken out of context
and in context don't really suggest anything.
And this is what Cartoon Network put out.
Yes.
But then, but Zen, I think Zen put in his video, like, there are actual hints.
Like, there are actual moments when you can tell early.
Like, there's moments where, like, it looks like Pearl, like, wants to say something but can't and it isn't remarked upon.
Then, you know, later you find out there's a reason for that.
So, like, there are actual, there are some actual, like, early hints towards it, but, like, Cartoon Network's trailer was, like, not them.
It, like, just showed a bunch of fake shit that, like, clearly was trying to make it look more, uh, like, more telegraph than it actually was.
Yeah, sure.
Which annoys me a lot.
Because I think it's dumb.
I think I, it's a lame twist.
It's a lame twist that sucks.
And, yeah, I was like, well, that doesn't do anything to you.
The Cartoon Network?
Yeah, yeah, I think I vaguely remember that.
Yeah.
It's poor.
It's poor form.
It was so unimpressed that I barely remembered it.
You guys think that's a lame twist?
I think that was a lame twist.
It's bad.
No, I mean, years and years ago, I suspected that, I mean, we all did, that fucking Rose was picked out.
I did, I did, too.
And that's why it was like...
We've talked about this before.
It's the combination of one.
They really obfuscated and tried to cloud the air so that we wouldn't be able to guess, even though everyone already suspected.
And then the payoff was just that, no, no, no, we were just trying to misdirect you.
What you already believe and have theorized about at length was just true.
That's just a boring twist, ultimately.
I think Gravity Falls did it better when they were just like, oh, everyone's already figured out the big twist.
We're going to reveal it early and go from there.
Yeah, fair enough.
We did talk about the same thing on the Steven Universe episode, which was what, like 100 years ago?
That episode is old enough to be your granddad.
Feel old yet.
That episode was out when I was listening to Procrastinator's podcast, episode two, when you were still in short pants.
Well, we did do a second Steven Universe episode, right?
Yeah, we did Steven Two Universe.
We got to do Steven Three Universe and something like that.
Yeah, that's true.
That's right.
Yeah, we did two.
We did two.
Okay.
That one's old enough to be your normal dad.
Feel young yet?
All right.
It's a lineage.
How about we get to the voicemails?
What do you say?
Let's do it.
I think it's time.
Okay, good.
Good, good, good, good talk, everybody.
Okay, so here we go.
Voicemails, people.
Speak pipe.
You know the drill.
Links below.
Send us your shit.
Okay, here we go.
First voicemail.
This is from Jaylin.
Jaylin sending in a voicemail.
Jaylin.
It's time.
Oh, am I in the right chat?
Yes, I am.
Go.
We all know.
Hey, PCP.
It's me, Jaylin.
And I just thought because I gave you a whole bunch of shackles this week that you could tell me that I'm a good guy.
And worth having around even though I just found the voicemail.
I know you've been waiting to hear from me for a long time.
Oh, yeah.
Please play me on the show and tell me how great I am.
Thanks.
Play me off.
Play me off, boys.
Thanks for the money.
I got none of those shackles.
I am not bound by any contracts.
That's true.
Unless you accept your Jaylin name because he's on my server.
He got a nickname.
He's not happy about it.
He's Jaylin.
Is he Jaylin?
He's totally Jaylin.
He's Jaylin.
Is he Jaylin like a felon?
It's just jelly.
And then at the end of the end, and Jaylin.
Well, great.
Glad we had this powwow.
Like a felon.
Like a felon with a lion.
All right.
Moving on.
Next one.
We've got another fantastic call from Cluster Punk Kitchen.
Let's see what he asks.
Oh, excellent.
Open a pack of Kraft Mac.
Free cheese flavor.
Cook on the stove.
Cook with love.
Take a handful of honey barbecue Fritos.
Mix it in.
That's your din.
Take a bite.
Change your life.
You just learned how to make Mac and Fritos on today's episode
of Cluster Punk Kitchen.
Yeah.
Now you're cooking with calm.
Thank you.
Thank you, Cluster Punk Kitchen.
Thank you so much.
We're dropping another Knowledge Bomb.
Mac and Fritos.
I know what I'm having.
Another alternative Knowledge Bomb.
Something else you should make a book and get rich.
That's true.
Cluster Punk Kitchen.
I know what I'm getting daddy to make me for dinden tonight.
Okay.
Next up.
Mix it in.
That's your din.
Take a bite.
Change your life.
All right.
Next up we've got a male from Female Spaghetti.
Let's get ready.
Go.
Hey, hey, everypony.
I just wanted to ask you, former MLP faggots at the PCP podcast.
Be honest.
How often did you used to masturbate to clop on hentai back in the old pony days?
And if you're not too much of a pussy to admit the fact that you used to jerk it off to clop,
please describe your favorite piece of pony porn you remember the most.
Thank you, faggots, for being my background noise while I draw autistic weeaboo hentai.
I love you all.
Thank you very much.
See, what I'm offended by is the presumption that we stopped jerking into popcorn.
Damn.
Dude, I regularly go back to Derpy Burrow to stock up.
Hell yeah, dude.
It's your one stop shop.
I'm going to be straight with you, Female Spaghetti.
Yep, did it in the past.
Would do it again.
They're anthropomorphized.
I don't give a fuck.
And the number one thing, my favorite clop porn of all, was it was called Apple Poker.
It's an Applejack story about playing poker and then she fucks Braeburn.
It's doggy style.
I guess it's horse style.
It's by Mitzis.
It's a game.
You can play it on the internet, Google it.
It's good.
It's high quality.
There you go.
Never.
No?
I don't believe you.
Okay.
You say so, kid.
I mean, I don't remember any, I think I probably did, but the thing is that I don't care that
they're horses.
Okay, okay.
I've seen clop porn that is bad and what's bad about it, when they do it with the boobs
are in there.
The horse boobs.
That's disgusting.
That's horrible.
When they're anthropomorphized enough that the titties are where titties should be on
a human, it's fine and it doesn't even matter.
The ones that emphasize their hoarseness are horrible.
Agreed.
You don't want to lean into that.
No.
I don't know.
Some people do and I can't.
No, no, no.
It's not for me.
I've fapped a furry porn, I've fapped a horse porn, I've fapped every kind of porn
out there except Goro.
I can't, Goro doesn't work for me.
Anyway, so, you know, fuck it, man.
It's about that there are human elements that I can sexualize in my brain and so I do.
That's it.
Hell yeah.
My hoof.
My hoof, bro.
Got it.
Okay.
So, from Sy's number one fan is calling in.
I'm excited for this one.
Sy's calling, everybody.
No, it's not Sy.
It's Sy's number one fan.
That's my point.
Sy is number one.
Okay.
Let's find out.
Go.
Greetings, PCP.
My name is Sy.
This isn't actually Sy.
Oh, he was right.
But I am.
Sy is number one advocate.
Advocate for what?
You might ask.
Advocate for Sy to finally get his guest role on an episode of the pro-crastinators podcast.
Think about this logically.
Sy has been a huge fan of this podcast for as long as anyone can remember.
Sy is a fan of all the creators from this wonderful podcast.
Now, I understand the fear that you guys may have.
If I recall correctly, the original reason why Sy went beyond that you guys were free
is that the video would be disliked bombed.
A similar to the video's on Mumki's channel.
When Sy would appear in podcasts, and the joke was, you'd dislike the video.
The shit.
I don't think Mumki's fans watch this podcast anymore,
so I think you're in the clear in that regard.
I feel you all have to do your due diligence to Sy.
I recognize that he is the perfect guest.
Me in the past has talked about how he feels that the guests don't really feel part of the podcast.
They don't fit in well.
I think Sy fit in perfectly.
So that's why I think Sy should be a guest on the next episode of the pro-crastinators podcast.
Oh, beautifully delivered.
I'm standing at attention.
I'm saluting.
I'm fully erect.
I'm sending the nukes right now.
Send them down to Texas.
Take Sy out.
Alright, next call.
Next call, that's it.
Moving on.
Next one's from Moonju.
This is directed towards Ben.
Oh God, not here.
Ben, you know what?
You're no saint.
You're no real saint.
You're a bad boy.
You're a scallowag.
You're a scoundrel.
You're a bitch.
You're a slob.
You want to know why?
You're a fucking idiot.
Because you think that giving to the poor from the rich would do anything.
One, it's evil because it's stealing, just like taxation.
Oh fuck.
Yeah.
It's really hard for that money.
I don't think he wants all that money to be taken from him.
I don't think that'd be very kind.
And guess what?
All those people who would take the money from him,
they'd just go ahead and waste it.
Sure, some of them would use it wisely,
but poor people are generally poor because they don't handle their money well.
And guess what?
If you give them a million dollars, they're going to fucking waste it.
It's been shown time and time again.
It was all this time.
So taking from Jeff Bezos and all the rich fat cats would do literally nothing
because it would all funnel back to the 1% who would want to take it back
using their smarts and their effort.
Is that it?
Yeah, okay, I guess that's it.
Okay, Moonjoo, you're right.
Jeff Bezos is, Jeff Bezos earned every single dollar with the sweat of his brow
of the half of his wealth that he now has, and so did his wife.
So did his soon-to-be ex-wife also earn every single dollar of that $70 billion.
Jeff Bezos did one push-up for every dollar in his bank account.
I'm sure.
That's why he's so fucking ripped now.
Jeff Bezos is just that smart.
Hold on, he's worth $70 billion.
How much does the average person have?
Maybe, I don't know, $50,000?
I don't know.
Okay, so if the average person has $50,000, Jeff Bezos is worth, how many?
Like 10,000 regular humans?
He is worth 10,000 regular humans.
I mean, he invented Amazon.
What was everybody else doing?
Just fucking around, you know what I mean?
Invented Amazon.
Invented selling shit on the internet.
Nobody else fucking did it.
It was him.
Alright, whatever.
We get it.
Okay.
A tabby nickel is calling in with something to say.
Let's hear it.
Subtabs.
I'm sick and tired of everybody who's calling out all these other discords like the PODCast
or the RFCK server.
I'm here to start a war with all y'all.
I will fight you anywhere, anytime.
I will beat your dick off on the street.
Do you understand what the fuck I'm doing here?
I will kick your ass and then I'll invite you to dinner.
Mark my words.
You can find me anywhere and I will fight you.
I think tabby nickel is single-handedly challenging every discord server at once to single combat.
Not even as a discord, just as an individual.
He's a vigilante.
He wants to fight the whole war himself.
Alright, you know what?
Every discord server needs to stop.
We need to stop fighting each other and turn ourselves to the real enemy here, which is tabby nickel.
Like the Christ, like the anointed one himself.
He is taken on.
He will take on the burden of all the violence.
He will end the shit meme war.
He will save us by taking it all onto himself.
Absorbing all the evil.
What's her name?
Demon souls.
Maiden Australia.
That's the one.
Exactly.
What a saint.
He's the real saint here.
Alright, next call is from Girl Pants.
Go.
Hey guys.
So I've been trying to get my friend Jonathan into the PCP for a while and I've been showing him a couple episodes.
And he's known about a couple of you before, specifically Nate.
I can't get him to like the show.
What he says is that pretty much that Nate is just the tard wrangler of the PCP and where's Lada?
Where's the lie though, you guys?
Where's the lie?
Where is the tard wrangler?
There's no debate to be had.
That's simply accurate.
I mean if you don't like that appeal, then you're not going to like the show.
Yeah.
No.
Nate's not the tard wrangler.
We're all his tard handlers.
Depends on how you look at it.
Sound off in the comments.
Do you subscribe to the tard wrangler theory or the tard handler theory?
Hashtag it.
Go.
Let's begin the debate.
This is the real debate.
All right.
Let's just move on.
I guess just ease him in.
Show him the best of the best.
I'd say show him the PCP highlights, but I gave up on making those because it took too much time.
But once bar makes some, I think.
So check with fucking once bar.
Hey, if we get an editor, we can have him make some of those.
Oh, damn.
That's another great reason.
Another great reason to get that.
Yeah, boy.
Make that happen.
We didn't.
Having slaves sure is great.
Having employees.
Sure is mutually beneficial in capitalist society, Tom.
All right, moving on.
Jeff Bezos sure has a bunch and look how he's doing.
He's doing just fine.
He knows.
Next call from Zoomer Bitch.
Zoomer Bitch.
Gross.
Go.
Hello, PCP Zoomer here.
Yeah.
Genuine one really on the low end of the age spectrum.
Speaking of spectrums, I would like to thank you all for turning me just fully gay.
But you always tell people that, you know, go out, make the video, make the art, do what
you want to do.
So here's the thing.
I'm a dumb kid.
Is there any way for me to make YouTube content because I've been inspired by all you guys?
Is there any way that I could make YouTube content as a dumb little kid and get anyone
to listen?
Dude.
Yes.
First of all, you got that.
What's that one kid?
You know that one kid who makes the communist why we need to be communist videos?
Yeah.
The fat kid.
Your youth is a very powerful tool.
Look at Munchie.
Yeah.
People are inherently drawn to a young person doing something that is more adult.
Just like how I'm drawn to young children sexualizing themselves.
There's something about that.
They're just being adults.
Uh-oh.
You should have said it like that.
See, Daisy.
Where's the line?
You know what I'm saying.
For Handler, Ben, one point for Handler right there.
Yeah.
Hashtag, hashtag Tard Handler.
I just want to say, Zoomer bitch, you already, frankly, look, I listened to a lot of voicemails
because we missed last week just now.
You had by far one of the most cogent, well rehearsed and like, you had a little effect
at the beginning there with the whatever fucking sound that the Zoom, I assume that was done
for.
I don't know if that was intentional, but it worked.
Yeah.
Because you're a Zoomer.
I assume that was the joke.
Like, you already have your shit together.
If you're smart enough to call in with a decent, with a good voicemail like this, I can already
tell.
You'd be surprised how rare it is.
Yeah.
No, no, you wouldn't.
How ahead of the curve you already are.
You are in fact ahead of the curve to be able to just figure out these basic level things.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you made, if someone, I mean, you know, you sound, you sound all of-
Sounds quite young.
Maybe like 15, 14.
Sounding everyone of his or hers, I literally can't tell.
It's probably 12 or something.
Like seven years.
Sure.
Whatever.
Yeah.
If you made content, if you made like the same content that like, you know, one of us would
make, like you would get more attention because it's more remarkable that you made it.
So, you know, I guess my advice would be do what every other fucking artist does and just
like copy someone whose content you like, copy their style until you can start to make
it your own.
Yeah.
Not a bad idea.
It's not about being a kid.
It is an asset.
Yeah.
Not a problem.
People might make fun of you and be like, fuck this kid, but you know.
As long as you, as long as you do the funny, funny jokes, then people will be like, ah,
he's funny.
Yeah.
Like if anyone's funny, they don't care how old they are.
You made us laugh just now, so.
Sometimes, sometimes, sometimes people can leave to becomes like, oh, you're only 10 years
old or something like that, whatever year old is.
And like, how is that even an insult?
You know what that is.
It's just like, it's like stating the sky is blue.
The grass is green.
Or how is that an insult?
You know what that is, though.
That's engagement.
True.
Is what that is.
It helps.
It literally helps you and doesn't hurt you at all.
Nah.
I like this guy.
People call you out for shit.
You're a bitch.
You sound like you got shit going on.
I like what you're doing.
You just, I don't know.
Yeah.
Like pick a project, dude.
Find something that you're interested in.
You know.
Don't worry about it too much.
Just get out there.
Start making stuff.
And you'll see if you like it.
If you like it, great.
Keep doing it.
If you don't, then you know, try something else.
Just get engaged.
Start making stuff.
Yeah.
Post it around.
Just do it.
You take it in a good step, calling into this show.
I'm already impressed.
Same thing I would tell anyone.
Make stuff and then post it around, you know.
Yep.
You know.
You've got such an advantage over guys who have got both feet in the grave, like Tom
and Ben over here.
You are way.
Yeah, bro.
So, you know, keep it up.
Keep it up.
All right.
Let's get to the next one.
Death comes swiftly.
It sure does.
Okay.
Steve.
Jess is best is letting us know how he feels.
Go.
Not only did we get some deep Winnie the Pooh lore last episode, but we also got the seat
and get angry talking about the PCP theme gets a little perturbed.
Hello, fresh getting angrier than wealth and capitalism.
All these chockers are flared and his Christ consciousness hits a million.
If you had put a plate of carbs in front of him at that moment, they would have erupted
in a blaze of hellfire hearing sustenance every week.
So I need to know what's the angriest moment you can remember.
It can include Ben or not.
And yeah, also the art for the last episode, the picture for the thumbnail, pretty fire.
Pretty good.
That's that Jesse quality.
Yeah.
And to Jesse brings that rage, the anger that he loves.
So I get it.
Is he talking about, is this guy talking about the angriest on the show or just, no, he means
in general.
He thinks he just likes people and people are angry.
It sustains him in general, I guess.
The angriest I've ever, you know, this is like a shit answer and I'm embarrassed to
say it, but it's the truth.
So I guess I'll say the angriest I've ever been was arguing with our dad at various
times.
There were a couple of times when I was incensed, like past the point.
I was like, just sputtering with rage because I just didn't know how to express my fucking
distaste and whatever shit he was telling me.
There's a thing.
I feel like this is similar.
I think he's the only person who's made me like straight up like incoherent.
You've punched through walls.
You've been so mad after, I think, you know, I was, you know, well, you know, he had me
on fucking, he had me on fucking medication that he fucking sent me to a, sent me to a
shrink briefly to get me on some fucking medication to keep me in line.
And it like fucked with my brain at the time and I, and I, I didn't punch.
I kicked, I kicked a hole in the wall.
That's true.
Yeah.
Which I blame.
I blame, I blame the drugs.
So by extension, I blame dad.
So there we go.
I'm, I'm innocent.
Where's the lie?
I don't feel, okay, I don't get super mad at work, but there's, there's a thing that's
sort of similar to that.
It's that like when I'm talking to someone and they, they won't engage my actual point
that I'm trying to say when there's a disagreement, they continue to either straw man or like
just, just ignore it.
When something like that happens and I really feel that if they just understood my point,
which happens a lot, frankly, I get so fucking angry on the inside and you know what this
happens at work, at work is where most, most often these days it happens and I don't let
myself get that mad.
I maintain rigid control because I can't get mad at work and freak out or I'll get fucking
fired or whatever.
But like when I'm, when, when I'm talking to my boss and I am certain that something
should be done a certain way, but they're just like, no, no, no, do it this way.
And I'm like, and I try to explain why it would just save time and money and energy for
all of us to just do it this way, but they won't listen.
That because like, I know that you are just going to get mad at me later for not delivering
this as fast as I could have because I'm wasting time doing this other thing.
And you know what?
Sometimes I get really mad like that and it turns out I was wrong and they were right.
That happens fairly decent amount of time.
But when it doesn't happen, ooh boy, do I get pissed.
I guess I just try to stay humble and think that maybe I'm wrong.
They're more experienced.
They know what's going on.
That happens.
Yeah, man.
That's when, you know, like our dad, when he just like thinks that he's right.
I remember arguing.
Yeah, I was gonna, I don't want to harp on the dad thing, but like, yeah, like the times
I've been real, it's, it's stuff like that when like I'm, when like my point is just
not coming across.
In the moment, it feels like I'm being willfully ignored or whatever.
Like dad, dad, why do I need to take a bath?
I'm just going to get dirty again.
This is flawless logic.
It's debate me dad.
Facts don't care about your feelings, dad.
But like, yeah, like maybe if I went back and like heard the conversation again, I would
realize now like, no, I was just not explaining myself like, yeah, like I was not making sense.
I was being stupid.
But by the time it feels like, why don't you just understand me?
It's just why won't you just agree with me?
If you knew, if you could, if you could think like I, if you saw things the way I think
you would agree with me, fuck you.
Yeah, you know.
Anybody else?
I can't.
Yeah, I'm, I'm think, cause like I'm, I'm pretty chill a lot of the time.
Every time you play Dark Souls, you want the world to end.
Let me just say, this is all way in the past, by the way, like I haven't been like really
mad at dad in like years and years.
Yeah.
Well, well, I'm, I'm, I'm pretty chill, but aside from video games, but I don't like
get like, like, um, like actually terribly mad.
I mean, if you had a button next to you, if there was a button next to you, when you
die at a poor moment in Dark Souls that just would destroy the world, I suspect you would
push that button.
I suspect.
Oh, of course.
Yeah.
But I mean, we all would at that moment.
It's, it's, it's like, I like being angry.
I think it's really fun to, to, to let loose and be like, fuck, like, like really get into
like an angry rant about why a game is badly designed and I'm right about it.
And I thought, I also think it's funny because I'm usually very chill and I have like a kind
of high pitched voice for a guy that like when I get mad, it's funny.
It just is funny.
People would probably laugh at it.
I have laughed at it many times.
It's just, it's just like, I don't, I don't take it too personally because, you know,
I look back on things I've gotten mad at and I'm like, you stupid idiot.
But it's, yeah, I can't think of like times I've wanted to kill.
Well, I, I can't, um, here's, here's, here's this one time.
I think I may have said this on the, on the podcast a long time ago, but, um, a young
boy, teenager, like 13, 14, um, walking home from school, didn't have many friends in school,
uh, had like, had kind of long weird hair at the time, not long, not as long as it is
now.
It's just sort of, it's just sort of went up, gravity hadn't really done anything with
it yet.
So it's sort of like a weird Afro.
Um, and I was picked on for that a lot.
Hippo, I got to interrupt you to say that I saw your ID card.
I saw the picture of you on that card with short hair, blew my face.
It was insane.
I can't even imagine it.
It's right.
Yeah.
Post every, post your social security number.
I want it.
No.
Post those three magic numbers on the back of your dad's credit card.
I mean, I, I'm thinking of cutting my hair.
The reason I haven't cut my hair for so long is because I built an internet presence and
everyone knows me as the guy with long hair and I'm like, I can't change now.
Now you can.
I can't change now, but I can totally change.
You can totally change now.
I cut my hair a little bit yesterday.
Uh, I just trimmed short sort of one side of my head, uh, like, like just kind of above
the ear.
Yeah.
Because I didn't like how that part was sort of like belling out on the side.
So I just cut that part short.
You almost can't, you almost can't tell the difference.
Like, like, uh, I saw a friend yesterday who didn't, he, he, he didn't even notice that
it happened.
He was like, Oh, your hair looks good.
And then I said, Oh yeah, I cut it and he was like, what, uh, I don't, I might trim
off the other side similarly, but I'm not sure.
I'm not sure if the asymmetry is good or bad.
Uh, I'm probably just going to carve it.
I'm just going to slowly carve it over the course of weeks into a, into a masterpiece.
Anyway, so I was walking home, um, and I walked by some other kids who are walking in a different
direction.
Um, they seem about the same age or younger than me.
So like, which is always the worst thing when bullies are younger than you.
Cause like,
you can't fucking beat the shit out of them.
Well, it's not even that.
They were, they were younger and they were taller because I was, you know, I'm a short
person.
So like, it's, it's like in every way, it's like the worst thing of all time.
One of them was one of these tall young bullies by any chance purple.
No, they were, they were male.
I checked when I killed them.
Um, they walk past me and like, they do the thing where they walk past you and they insult
you just as it's too late for you to turn around, like it's too late for you to do anything
about it.
Like they're already, you know, behind you and you're already walking still.
You have to make a decision to turn around, say, Hey, stop.
And then they're not going to stop.
So like they've insulted me and I can't do anything about it.
And I forget what they said.
It was just some bullshit.
There's like, you know, I, I usually have a bad day at school and this was like, God,
the worst thing to happen.
And I had that, that moment where it's like, I imagined if I could turn back time and knowing
that they were going to say that and also have a dagger on me, what I would do to them
as I passed them.
Cause they passed, like they were almost going to sort of shoulder barge me.
Yeah.
I was like, Oh, what if I just, you know, kicked him and kicked that one guy down and
stabbed him in the fucking throat and stabbed him in the skull and the other guy was like
horrified and I threw the dagger in his head.
Oh, that would be so cool.
And I was just walking home from that point thinking like, like imagining all like the
grizzly blood and the killing that I was doing in my head.
I was like, Oh yeah, that's good.
And then I got home and I was like, well, I didn't do that.
Yeah.
Good, good thing.
There's no chance that they would have said that if like it was just one guy.
It's only when there's a bunch of people, you know, they, you know, it's always about
pro, um, it's always about like, you know, doing it to bolster their friendship status.
Like I can make fun of people.
I'm confident.
We're the in group and we've excluded someone.
High five.
Well done lads.
Let's keep it up.
Yeah.
Keep up the good work.
Uh, all right.
Well, I guess we'll go on to the next call.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Um, next one is from, oh wait, this is for Munchie.
We're skipping this.
Was that, was that the angry question about the angriest you've been?
Yeah.
Okay.
Just checking if I missed one.
Skipping this one because that was for Munchie who is not here.
So Cam, I'm not reading your voicemail because Munchie isn't here.
So there you go.
Thank him.
Was that by Camry Blankenship, creator of AKA Laserbot, creator of Tales Get Stroll?
That, I hope so.
But no.
Yeah.
All right.
This is from Real Shonen Jump.
The Real Shonen Jump is calling in.
Wow.
Finally.
Hi.
This is Shonen Jump, the publisher of, you know, Manga and we wanted Ben to become
a comic book writer for us, except he actually would have to, you know, make chapters regularly
on a weekly or even maybe monthly schedule instead of yearly, you know, we don't do yearly
comics here at Shonen Jump.
We'd like to hear his reply.
You know, you know, I thought bullying was illegal, guys.
What the hell?
Hey, Nate, fuck you, you chose to include this out of my hands.
This is in God's hands only.
I have no authority here.
Yeah.
I should probably, well, okay, you know, I think about this sometimes, like, like, when
Vapors 2 was done, I was working, I was starting champion.
And I applied to Hiveworks.
I applied to become like a partner of the Hiveworks Comics Collective and I was not selected.
And I wonder if maybe if that had happened, right, like maybe what I would have done is
like focus on comics over everything else and just do that instead of like doing YouTube
stuff and endless war and whatever.
And I wonder what my output would have been.
I mean, I would hope it would have been better than it has.
I mean, I, yeah, I wonder too, I mean, because I did you this, I mean, I think about this
sometimes, like, what if I had just quit my job several years ago, like well before my
finances were stable at all and just done YouTube, would I be at, you know, million subs and
doing really great and then like it wouldn't have mattered, maybe probably not.
But you know, it's just, it's fun to think about, not even fun, it's just kind of wistful,
I guess.
Yeah.
You know, I realized, I realized, I had, I didn't really, I haven't posted a new page
in maybe, I think a little over a week now, but there, you know, a couple of weeks ago
I started posting Vapors three pages again and I realized that like without even realizing
it, three months had gone by and I hadn't made a new one and that was, I hadn't realized
it.
Yeah.
I was like, what?
I had thought maybe a month tops, but no, it had been three whole months since I made
a new page.
I don't know how that happened.
I was shocked and disgusted.
I've been busy, I've been busy, I've been trying to, trying to, I've been making pages lately.
I've been busy with stuff.
That's good.
I've been, I've been really productive lately.
For a while there I was pretty bad, but I've been a lot better lately.
I mean, I'm not trying to, not specifically on that.
I'm not trying to pressure you or anything, but I'm just curious, like what's like the
general ETA, like based on how things have been going of, you know.
On Vapors three.
Yeah.
If I were working exclusively on it, well, I could probably, I think, I think two pages
a week is pretty fair to, and how many, how many pages you got left?
If you know.
How many do I have left, maybe, maybe 10, max 20, maximum 20.
Okay.
All right.
But probably more like 10 to 15.
Well, cool.
I'll be looking out for it.
Yeah.
I'll be like seven weeks if I, if I focus.
Do it up.
There.
That's what I have to say about that.
Ben, do you ever wonder like how, how do Magica do like 20 pages a week?
Yes.
Um, I know they have assistants.
Well, I guess here's, I mean, the combination is one discipline and like, and they have
it all set up.
And two Japanese.
Yeah.
Like they have it set up.
Like they like go, they like go into the office in the morning and they sit down for
like an eight hour work day and they work and sometimes they like, I, like I just work
in my room and I wonder if maybe that's like bad for my mindset.
Like maybe if I had like, yeah, like a separate office where like I, um, you know, would go
to.
It's so, it's so easy to like completely go into I'm home, relax mode when you're sitting
at your normal desk that you only have one.
That's why I want to drive in studio one day that I go to every day.
When I, like even, even just changing rooms, when I need to write something, I write on
my laptop in the dining room and it's so much easier to focus even though I have the internet
and all that stuff.
It's just, it's a different computer and I'm downstairs and downstairs is the work time
place and upstairs is like at the end.
If I, you know, I mean they all, the other, there's that and then they also have assistants
and like having assistants, I think it would have, you know, obviously it would reduce
the workload, but I think it would have a big psychological effect too.
Like, you know, Oda, they say that Oda draws, he like he draws anything that's moving in
the panel he draws, um, and he'll leave like backgrounds and like obviously he'll sketch
the backgrounds or whatever, but like he'll leave, like the backgrounds will be inked
by like his assistants.
Yeah.
So, I think basically like you, the mangaka, can you draw what's important to you, like
you can draw the stuff that's like the most important and the most interesting to you
and then like all the, the incidental stuff you can pass them and that would, the effect
that that would have is like you could pass off basically what's to you, the busy work,
you can pass it off to someone else to do that, so like you would have psychologically,
it would be less of a drag, you know, like the drawing process would be less, you know,
rough.
I also think.
Not all mangaka have assistants, like I'm pretty sure that the guy who did Poon Poon,
you know, that dude, I don't think he has any assistants, which is fucking insane.
Yeah, because he had some detailed shit he makes.
I've talked about that show Man Ben on here, you know, the one where it's like they, like
this one mangadude, he like puts a camera in a mangaka's studio for a week and then
like him and the guy review the footage and like talk about like what they do.
I love that fucking show.
I wish every episode was translated, but a bunch of them aren't as far as I know it
fucking is mad, makes me mad and I want to, I want to consume all of it.
Learn Japanese.
But yeah, they did, they did, they did one with that guy and the guy just fucking, the
level of detail in his panels is insane and his process is fucking bizarre and insane
and he has no assistants.
He does it all himself.
It's fucking nuts, but like most of them have assistants.
You know, I think there was this one, there was this one woman who puts out like, she puts
out like fucking like 40 pages a week, but she's, she's got a team of like, she's got
a team of like eight assistants that are all like yelling about her office constantly.
I mean, I think another benefit of having assistants like this and just like, like being
in show and jump is like just having a deadline, a hard deadline, I think is a real benefit,
a serious and, and people depending on you, like your assistants and whatnot, pressure
is good for productivity.
I swear it's true.
It's real.
Like when you and I were doing T-Bap, I think just by virtue of us kind of depending on
each other pushed both of us to be real productive.
Yes, it was, we couldn't, yeah, we couldn't let each other down.
We both had to do it.
And also we had like, you know, we have to have it out today.
Our goal was like when it came out, there's no alternative to that.
And we fucking got it out before there were times when we were the first review out or
whatever and, and it was still an episode of T-Bap, aka not total shit.
So pretty fucking good.
I'd say.
What if we made like our own show and jump for that reason?
Hmm.
I guess, you know, like a weekly period, like a weekly periodical or a newsletter or something.
Yeah, a weekly, a weekly, a weekly something or other publication digitally and if, if
you have like pages for your comic, you can put them in there and it just be like a reason
to have a deadline.
We're in different mediums, but let's just say theoretically, here's a concept for a
show.
It's like a PCP people sent, it doesn't have to be called that, but it's like a basically
a variety show where we like, let Ben, like whatever, he produces like a chapter a week,
just, you know, to be crazy, like shown and jump standards or whatever.
And like, I don't know, I produce a wee ag before it.
I'm just, this is totally not real, but just theoretically, I don't know, Tom, I don't
know, like a blog update for his game or something, Davoo, maybe the same thing, Digi, some fucking
videos or something.
And like, I don't know, what if it was theoretically all edited into one video, wouldn't that be
a hoot and a half?
I don't know, just saying.
Like a roundup?
Yeah.
Like a weekly roundup.
But it's like, it's like a copy of shown and jump in that, like all the stuff's in there,
you know, like you go there for like all the things you want.
Yeah, I don't know, I'm just saying, it's a cool, same sort of idea.
I like the idea.
I like the idea of something that we are like committed to and like we are, we are always
together.
That's the thing.
I've always wanted to have a partnership of some sort.
I've always wanted to work with somebody.
I've always wanted the Bakumon style of like someone working with me, because I feel like
that would definitely increase my productivity.
I mean, it's to a small degree, but like look how efficient and productive, like specifically
the PCP podcast has been, we have not missed a single week, except I think after Radcon
3 we missed, I believe one week when we were just taking a break or whatever.
And yeah, like super productive, it's relatively lucrative for everybody.
Yeah, I mean, it's just a fucking podcast, we talk about bullshit.
So yeah, I don't know, the virtues, this is good, it's good stuff.
This is a good idea, I think we should, we should think about this more.
I think this is something we should do with the procrastinator's website, since it has
nothing going on, right?
Yeah, I mean-
Yes, that's basically-
Like a blog post every week.
And then the name would become ironic, because it's called the procrastinators, but we're
not busting our asses to meet a deadline every week.
Yeah, I still like it, I still like it.
Oh well, that's a cool idea, but anyway, let's talk about that more later.
Let's put a pin in that.
Move on to a call from Hipster Cthulhu, let's see what he has for us.
This guy sounds sick.
Okay, Nate, so on the last PCP you said the taxation is theft, and I thought I'd just
blackpill you on how it really works, or you see, you don't actually like own anything.
See, you can only own things if you have the ability to like physically defend them and
say they're yours.
That's how like borders work between countries.
So really, everything you own, the government already owns, because they're the ones with
the power.
Like the police can come and just fucking grab you out of your house and kill you if
they want, and you can't do shit about it.
And so like really, your money and everything you own is not yours, you're just the government's
child basically, you're getting pocket money, and then they're taking some back from you.
Taxes isn't theft, because you don't own things that can be stolen, because we're all little
bitches dancing to their fucking puppet strings as they woke.
Man, this guy's definitely watched Chymatica.
Yeah.
That's a pretty black pill.
I don't think I disagree, but I don't know what the takeaway is.
Okay, he's wrong, because his whole mindset there, I get it that it's true, like physical
force is what actually makes the difference, but we don't live in a world where physical
force is the only thing that we care about or value.
Like might does not make right.
So just because the government has, we set up the entire nation of America because we
wanted to have certain inalienable values like the fucking respect of property.
If the government came in and just took people's property for whatever, you could argue like
blah, blah, blah, incarceration of slavery, I'm sympathetic to these arguments, and whatever,
like taxation is theft, like sure, yeah, we can make those, but ultimately, we're trying
to protect virtues and values that we all respect.
So it's not that if the government just came in and started taking shit completely because
it fucking felt like it, like I like to think we would literally rise up gamers and like
stop it.
I think it would take a while.
I mean, I think on like a small scale, the government can do, like the government could
fucking, you know, bust into any one person's house and take their shit.
Yeah, and they could probably get away with it too, by just finding some excuses.
Probably true.
Yeah.
I bet they have in the past.
So, I mean, if they can do that.
They bust into your bank account and take your money every fucking year.
But it's not...
Look, I'm the one defending the country.
I'm defending taxation right now.
I'm not sure.
I agree with this guy's argument.
I feel like the conclusion of this argument is not that taxation is not theft.
It's just that it is, but it has already been stolen.
Basically, yes.
It is pre-stolen.
It's not theft because it's already not your property.
So he's kind of just circumventing the whole issue, I guess, by saying there's an even
larger injustice.
Yeah, you're going one step further than taxation is theft.
Yeah, he is.
Nothing goes even yours.
I mean, perhaps...
I think there's an argument to be made there, because like, you're talking, because Nate,
you're talking about like the government and shit and like social structure and all
that kind of stuff.
And like, as long as you're playing within that paradigm, then yes, everything you're
saying is true.
But I think even you wouldn't disagree that there are people with enough like influence
to play outside of that paradigm.
And at that point, like, there's no rules anymore.
They basically are like ruling everything at the point of a gun.
I mean, I just don't feel like we actually live in that world in modern day America.
I think that's naive to think that.
I mean, maybe that's true.
But I don't know.
I don't agree with this guy's premise that, you know, like it's, we don't control.
People, I think it's a little conspiratorial the way people think about like, look, Jeff
Bezos does not actually control the world.
He really doesn't.
He runs a really big business.
That's what he does.
And yes, that business has influenced.
I don't think it's about controlling the world.
I think it's like someone like, if you get to a Jeff Bezos level of like influence and
authority and wealth, like Jeff Bezos can do whatever he wants.
He cannot murder a man and get away with it.
Yes, he could.
Yes, he fucking could.
I would actually, it would shock me if he hasn't murdered people to get to where he
is.
That's no, that's too much.
Look, he just rode a tech bubble and he was in the right place at the right time and it
happened to be something that like the entire world population really values.
That's why he just made so much money because everyone wants a piece of it.
Question, question.
Okay.
Do you think that there are not people out there who would kill for what, for Jeff Bezos'
money?
I think there, like there are probably people out there who would murder him.
So like, I don't know, man, I think I could, you know, but it's like, but how many maybe
he's had to fucking kill people, you know, it doesn't seem, it doesn't seem crazy.
I mean, let's just say directly, obviously, if someone came up to me and said, Nate, listen,
here's a button, you push this button, I die personally as the magic messenger.
So I can't spill the beans.
And also Jeff Bezos dies, you get all his money.
And, you know, and like, and it's guaranteed no one ever finds out.
I'm not going to lie.
I will have to have a think about that conundrum because, you know, no one, you say no one's
going to find out and I get billions, ooh, that sounds pretty good.
Maybe I can just find a way to justify my soul murdering a man.
Maybe I can do that.
I don't know.
But I would, I mean, the point is, I just don't, I don't believe this guy's ultimate
blackpilled version of the world.
I really think things are more granular and like there is more individualism already.
I don't think the government really does that much, honestly.
I think it's just like people just have their communities and that's where things like get
resolved and figured out.
I don't think the government really does that much to shape the world.
I don't know, maybe in fucking like North Korea, I guess they do, but I don't live there.
I live in America.
I just feel like in this place I'm at, I do have some significant freedom and I don't
think a lot of people are going to fuck with it.
Maybe if I was Bezos, it would be like I'm more vulnerable.
When you're Bezos level, like at your level name, like the level of a human, like a human
citizen, yeah, like the things you do are not affecting like, you know, that many people.
When you're Jeff Bezos, everything you do with your, like you're like, yeah, you don't
control the world, but like your actions like have an effect.
Sure.
I don't know, like the businesses, like, I don't know, like where he runs his fucking
business out of will like, it will have like a marked effect on like that city's economy,
you know?
Like the government sets up things.
Like cities will vie for him to run their business in their economy.
They will offer him like, you know, tax loophole, tax incentives and stuff to like, yeah, run
your business here.
That like affects the economy.
You know, it could, it could displace people, you know, like not even intentionally.
Like, you know, people might have, people might have to move the house because, you know,
of where this guy just decided to live.
Yeah, let's say the setup shop, it gentrifies the entire native population can't afford
to live there because it's too nice now or whatever.
I mean, yeah, absolutely true.
This is like, these are like, these are like powerful forces.
But like the question that we're addressing here is not really related to any of this.
And specifically, it's like, like, is taxation not theft because we just don't own anything.
I don't, I think we do have influence over our lives, even in that situation where Jeff
Bezos can fuck us over by, you know, whatever, fucking up our community or whatever.
It's not even, the question really, Jeff Bezos is an interesting question, but like we're,
this guy was calling and saying the government kind of owns everything and Jeff Bezos isn't
the government really.
Well, I'm happy to say governments or powerful people or whoever.
Sure.
But I think, I think, I mean, the only thing that makes the government powerful is that
they have capital and resources to an infrastructure, I guess, but like the only way they can maintain
that infrastructure is through, you know, their capital.
Yeah, I suppose.
I feel like the whole thing is, is this idea that of like owning as a concept because like
literally owning is impossible.
You can't literally do it.
It's all about the laws.
Maybe it's protected by the law.
And since, yeah.
So like if a law says you own something, then you own it because that is a concept that
we've come up with.
Yep.
Again, like you said, unless you physically defend it, then I suppose you do own it.
If like you just have a gun and it won't let anyone touch your shit.
Reasonable.
Well, I mean that like that's like what the law does, like what ownership laws do is,
you know, empower private citizens basically to have, you know, the government will protect
your property.
But like, but like, if we're, but this isn't like bolster the case, though, like if the
government has rules of law that define, you know, ownership and property rights and stuff
like that.
But we also know that the government does like, you know, shit, whatever it wants, even
if like it's questionable legality, like, doesn't it just prove the guy's point like,
yeah, the government could, like it's beneficial to the system to say, stay relatively stable.
So like people like Nate feel like they have control over their lives, but like, yeah,
absolutely.
Yeah.
But the people, but the people in charge at any point can like, you know, quietly cart
Nate off and like steal his fucking lunch money and do whatever they want.
There would be, you know, objections.
Those people might go to jail.
But they're not going to do it obtusely.
It'll be done very silently and quietly and they won't notice.
And that's because that's how when you have that level of a power and affluence, you can
do things in the shadows and nobody notices.
Think about this.
Say you own some property, you own some land, right?
And you know, someone, maybe a homeless person, someone trespasses on your land and thereby,
because the law says you own this land, you can call the police and the police will be
dispatched and they will, you know, remove this person physically, you know, violently
if, if need be.
Basically what you have by this, the police and the property laws, you basically have
like a military force at your command, like a military force that is ready to defend your
property.
If you own like a huge amount of land, then basically you have, you have like this military
power to enforce that ownership.
Basically the government enforces your owner, your private ownership with violence.
Yes.
Correct.
I don't know.
It's a little, it's a little like you kind of, like if you're fucking Jeff Bezos and
you own a shit ton of land, you've basically sort of got like a little private military
of your own.
You're basically like a fucking, I don't know.
I mean, if you're, if you're Jeff Bezos, you're not going to rely on the cops.
You're going to hire a private security force.
Probably not.
Yeah.
You literally have like.
You know, this is all fine.
I just don't feel like, I feel like my property is reasonably well defended by the police.
And like it's, it's, it's a practical very thing.
And then it's also a moral thing.
I believe property is perfectly moral and is, is the right.
Thoughts.
Okay.
This, this is a, this is not a new observation I'm making here, but there are lots of people
without homes in America and there are lots of homes owned by people that are not being
occupied.
Sure.
Say, I don't know why, why is it that the, like a wealthy landowner who owns like lots
and lots of houses that he's trying to flip, right?
He's got all of this fucking property and like homeless people try and squat in them.
Why is the government invested in coming in and using military violence to remove these
people?
You know, why is it, uh, I, I, I, I, it seems weird.
It's, it doesn't seem weird.
It doesn't just seem weird on the base of it.
It only, I mean, okay, I see why it seems weird on like a base kind of initial emotional
level.
Like these people need houses.
Why can't they like they're not being used.
Just let them have it.
But I mean, the reason is one, because we've decided that property rights, I mean, we started
this at the founding of the country are important to be respected.
And that's for a number of reasons.
And I think a pure pragmatic one is that like, look, if we don't respect property rights,
we're just saying anyone can do anything.
You can just take anything from anybody and the government will just let that happen.
That's just chaos.
Uh, and that's not good.
And at the very least, again, purely pragmatically, that means like, who's going to want to come,
like who's going to want to build a factory in America?
If America has as a policy, like like Venezuela does or something, the government can just
say like, oh, good factory, we're actually going to take this because we've got homeless
people who need to live here.
We need a house for them.
So sorry about like the investment that you've made here.
We're just going to use your shit, you know, for that equitable.
I thought we were talking about houses that are like, it's the same, it's the same principle.
It's the same principle.
Like if you invest in a house because it's going to flip it, as Ben said in this example,
you're kind of changing.
You have made an investment.
If you're flipping houses, which is what you said, Ben, that's an investment that you're
trying to get a return on.
If they can just take your money, why would you, okay, I guess you just won't invest in
anything.
It becomes like, it's, it's like, I can understand the argument from like the perspective Ben's
arguing for at this scale, because it's like, it's a big house and like, you know, but it's
the argument Ben's making is the same thing as like, if I, I can have a laptop that's
going on sale on eBay right now, if someone's just like, oh, you're going to sell it anyway,
or it just comes in, like walks into the house and just starts using my computer, you know,
yeah, that's the same principle because it's, well, I mean, yeah, but it's different.
It's different at scale.
If someone like owning a laptop is not the same as owning like, you know, 100, 100 fucking
houses, look, either you respect property rights or you don't, I guess is really what
it comes down to.
And I, well, here's the thing, okay, I guess the difference is that I think, you know,
me personally, I think that a person, that it makes sense for a person to own a laptop.
I don't think that anyone deserves to be rich enough to own 100 houses.
I just don't think so.
I mean, that what that just says is that, yeah, you only respect property rights so far
and that you don't think people are entitled to the sweat of their brow.
Maybe because you think the system is flawed and like people don't really deserve what
they get.
It's like not.
That's exact.
That's precisely what I think.
It is literally an accident that some people own, you know, hundreds of properties and
other people have.
Yes.
I mean, it's not all an accident.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Some people are lucky.
Okay.
I see.
I got.
Ben, what you want to do, what your idea as proposed, this is a very, this is a socialist
idea that you want to get rid of all unfair advantages because everybody's the same and
we need to balance for things like luck because whatever doesn't exist.
And I agree.
I don't think free will is real.
You know, so we just want to, we want to balance everything.
Everyone should have an equally good experience in life that we can provide them.
But if we do things like redistribute stuff, like you aren't allowed to own 100 houses,
we're going to take them and give them to the poor.
You are crippling the incentive for people to earn anything, which is what has made the
world so much better across the fucking globe and pulled billions of people out of poverty,
which is what capitalism has done.
We need that incentive structure there.
Prove that it's done that.
I don't know, like India has been vastly improved by like the technological advances.
I don't have, look, I don't know, I'm not a scientist, but this is what I've been told.
Yeah, that's a, that's a, that's a bold, that's a, I think that's a bolder claim you're making
than, than you think it is.
I, I'm aware it's a bold claim.
It just seems to be true that like across the world, the, the poverty rates have just
been plummeting over the last several years and it's due to capitalism.
I don't.
I don't know.
Okay.
If we had some research before all this is going to take your word for that.
We're both ignorant of actual data, which is what you need to have a real debate like
this.
So I guess.
I'll admit it.
Yeah.
I could know, I could, I could know more about this.
As could I.
I guess, I guess I'm arguing from emotion here.
I think so, which isn't wrong, but isn't necessarily correct either.
And I, I feel the same about me.
The problem, the problem with the argument is like what you, cause like you'd have to
eventually define like what can a person have, right?
Cause there's a limit eventually.
Like I could make the argument, like, you know, Ben, like we're both artists, but you
make four times as much money as I do.
Why don't you give me half what you made?
Cause like I work hard.
Why don't I get, why don't I get a hundred?
And then you're in the business of policing things down to that level that as a separate
issue is also unsustainable.
I think we, you know, what I think your argument would be that you worked harder.
You have a more dedicated audience.
They feel your content.
I wouldn't say that I worked hard.
I don't know.
I do.
But, but I mean, I happy to admit.
I don't think free will is real.
Uh, I think everyone just is the machine that they were born to be influenced by their
experiences and DNA.
So like, why does ever anyone deserve anything better than anybody else?
They didn't do anything.
So I, I just, Hey, I, here's the truth is that we don't even own our flesh and bones.
We don't even own those.
If the government can just come in and take them from you, then maybe we don't, we don't
own shit, but we do own our dreams.
Don't get me started.
Oh no.
Oh God.
Uh, okay.
That wasn't, that wasn't a terrible discussion.
I thought you were dreaming, mage.
Maybe I was, maybe I was dreaming about a topic I could participate in.
I think, I think we've probably, that's a fanciful dream indeed.
I think we've probably hit, uh, hit the limit of what we can say about this.
I think this whole, we need more data thing.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah.
Okay.
Here's, here's, I'm, I'm gonna, I'm gonna suggest this right now, Nathan.
I think you're gonna like this bonus episode on capitalism.
What could be more capitalistic than giving us our money to listen to this episode?
That's not a bad idea.
We'll come with data.
We'll hash it all out.
Oh, but that would just require me to do work and find sources and stuff.
Oh no.
Oh, okay.
We'll see.
That's, that's a good idea though.
Okay.
Next one.
We got, we got three more here.
Sherlock, Aznebel.
Go.
Hey, this is a young X Christian boy here.
Just wanted to let you guys know that, uh, I had to tell my parents that I don't believe
in God anymore.
Not because they really needed to know, but I just didn't want to have to go to church.
It was, it was getting kind of to be a drag.
And, uh, so I blamed it on you guys because I figured it was a better fall guy than those
who are responsible for people dying.
But when I said that, uh, I didn't believe in Jesus anymore because of the PCP, uh, they
looked at it kind of funny and I think they might have thought, I was talking about the
drug, but, uh, no, I told them it's a podcast.
Uh, now they're telling me that I can't listen to the podcast anymore, lest I be kicked out
of my house.
So my question for you guys is, is it more valuable for me to listen to this podcast or
have a roof over my head?
I don't really know because, uh, you got, but podcast, podcast for sure.
You got to stick with the podcast, especially if, especially if you're on the page, I was
going to say as long as you're, as long as you're paying on the Patreon, I don't give
a fuck if you listen to that.
Um, um, uh, you might, you might, you might have to just, uh, you might have to just
bite the bullet and go to church for my dreams.
So I know that's the worst, the worst of all possible worlds.
Christopher Hitchens, I think, uh, not just an atheist, but an anti-theist, which I generally
agree with.
Um, you should, you should listen to the podcast.
That's true.
On speaker.
Uh, Christopher Hitchens, whatever.
Even he said, I think that like you don't want to like cripple your life, uh, first
of all, if there, if you can just avoid the subject, just avoid the subject.
And uh, that's what I did, uh, for a long time, look, my dad's religious, this is what
you got to do.
All right.
Your parents right now, they want you to go to church.
You don't want to go to church, but they have like this religious duty thing that's
in their brain that they're going to make you do.
Well, you got to, you got to embarrass them at church so they don't want to bring you
anymore.
Like, you know, they finish the gospel and the dude starts like the pre-starts going
on is like little like spiel that he always does after every gospel reading.
Yep.
You just got to call him out and call his God fake and gay.
And then the entire church will see that their son is causing an embarrassing scene.
And then they'll never want you to come back again.
And then you're free.
Possible.
You just got to shame them.
You got to, you got to be such an embarrassment to them.
You got to be that they have to be, Oh no, they're the ones with the atheist son.
And then they'll feel bad about it.
And then they'll try and erase you from the, the, the parishes like collective memory by
having you not come anymore.
Yeah, they'll try to erase him by kicking him out of the fucking house.
Just be as blatantly atheist as possible.
Just make everyone know that you're the God.
You got to lean into it, dude.
You got to lean in.
I have a huge moral opposition to lying about most things, especially important things like
this.
But what I would do is I would just not bring it up.
Look, if it's, I don't, I don't honestly know what it's like to have like super religious
parents, especially like if you're atheist.
I imagine it's really hard.
So I guess I just said tread carefully, survive, dude.
Don't get kicked out.
Do what you got to do.
Yeah.
Just do, you know, you can go to church and just not believe dude, tons of Christians
do it every day.
Fact.
Everyone who's going to church is faking to a certain degree, probably true.
Some more than even, even, you know, everyone's, everyone's, they're taking it on faith and
everyone sometimes is like, maybe God, is this all bullshit?
Ah, fuck.
But they just fake it, you know, they just, they just push those thoughts out of their
mind until they go away.
And that's, that's, you know, that's, you know,
AKA they reject their logic and, you know, thoughts for their feelings and to placate
the people around them.
You're all, you're all in the same boat.
You're all in the same boat.
You're all just, I'll just try to make it in this dog eat dog.
Survival comes first and foremost, dude.
So, you know, do what you got to do, but be a good, good, be a good thing.
And remember to thank the Lord for all that, for all that good, good wisdom.
From the PCP.
Yeah.
Right.
That's right.
Okay.
Next up, we got them snakes.
How many, how many more we got?
Two more or two more.
Cool.
And here's them snakes.
Hashtag team Ben.
I don't know, he's hashtag team Ben now.
So I mean, let's, let's see what we've got happening.
Ben's interested.
Ben said, I accept your proposal to join forces to defeat munchies.
There you go.
All right.
I fucking hate babies and munchie is the biggest baby boy I've ever seen.
Yes.
I am disappointed by the clear and obvious racism you feel towards snake people kind.
There I go in your territory.
I am confronted with stairs.
Do you have any idea how fucking difficult it is to navigate stairs as a fucking pile
of snakes?
You are not tolerating this snake phobic bigotry in this alliance, however, if you promise
to install more ramps, I may be inclined to not bite your ankles in the middle of
the night.
You fucking communist shit.
I don't have you, I don't anymore, next step of kill munchie is fucking gay.
Well, all right.
I like snakes.
Why are you so mean to snakes, Ben?
Yeah, Ben.
You know, it was a crime of ignorance.
I think, all right, we can reach an agreement here.
All right, first thing tomorrow, everyone remind me, don't let me forget, I'm going
to call my guy.
We're going to get some ramps installed in St. Ben's Cathedral.
That's nice.
We're going to let him fucking lurch and slither his way on up.
He's going to shamble his way on up to the narthex and we're going to have a little meeting
of the mines.
That sounds great.
Look at this image of the snakes from Baaljap.
I think them snakes might be related.
Damn, I think you're probably right.
Yeah, I think these might be the snakes that became them snakes.
Next up, we've got our final message, a final message, and this is from HardPP.
HardPP, let's bring us home, HardPP.
What do you got?
Why is my PP hard?
Is it because you listened to the bonus episode?
Did...
Who's that?
No, it's because he listened to the boners episode.
All right, that's it.
It's over, everybody.
Episode completed.
We've done our obligation to you.
Now continue to give us the currency, patreon.com, slash the procrastinators, $5 for bonus episodes.
There's 21 now, I believe.
Jesus Christ, that's a lot of content.
There'll be another one coming up, a couple of weeks, calm down, relax, it'll be here.
T.P.Crastinators on Twitter, send us more of that cool epic memory that we love so well,
and I guess that's about...
Oh, and of course, send us more voicemails to the Speakpipe, link down in the description.
That's great stuff, keep doing it, people.
All right, that's it.
Thanks for that.
Thank you.
Thanks for the outro.
Thanks for the outro, as always.
Best guy ever.
Yes.
You're a credit to the race.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
Love being white.
Wrapping it up here, everybody.
See you next time.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Yeah.
Oh.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I'm not working.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.
I'm not working.