What's Happening Gamers? Welcome back to another exciting episode of the PZP. I'm your host,
Cheesy Manfredo, and always with here is my lovely co-host, Tectonic Improv.
I've always been here. Yes, we've always been here. Every episode. And you know who we love.
That's the slogan. That's the slogan. That's the slogan.
Wait, who's that? Oh, is that? The Pro Crastinators Podcast. We've always been
here. Is that our guest? Is that our guest? Ben Saint, the infamous Twitter man, Ben Saint.
Hey, you gotta say Ben Saint, what are you doing on my review? Ben Saint, what are you
doing in my review of Green Ninja? I just thought I heard you were talking about
the Adventure Cats movie, and I thought we could have a little, I already did a review
about this, and you're not allowed to do it anymore.
Give and take, what are you doing in my podcast? Is that Dark Cheesy Manfredo? What are you
doing here? I thought I killed you in the last review of the Three Ninjas.
No, that was the Three Ninjas kickback review. Oh, man. Oh, no, it looks like I gotta do
it again. Cut to a video of me punching myself in front of a green screen. Except the other
you has a mime. Oh, he's a pasta clown, but his colors are inverted.
Yeah, it's like that episode of Powerpuff Girls where the clown turns into the mime,
and it was really scary for me as a kid for some reason, and it has that cool song at
the end. That's a pretty rad song. Not to flex. Oh, yeah, go ahead. There she is. I'm
so privileged to be a part of the PCP at last. I've been wanting to get on this show for
years, so I think I'm so blessed. Give and take, what are you doing in my review? You
just like squeaked. I tried to do it a bit, but then the bit of reviewer took over and
I was like, okay, I gotta do it later. Oh, yeah. Yes, yes, and it's always yes. She
dropped for a second. I was like, oh, that's just perfect. Just perfect. Drops immediately
as the podcast starts. Is this the longest intro? No. Every podcast is entirely intro.
There's no content. Yeah, intro and then straight to voicemail. Yeah, so I'm thinking voicemails.
I'm thinking let's head to voicemails. We're done. Let's head up to voicemails. Alright,
first voicemail is for me, and it's this next thing I say in the entire show. It's
everything I say in the show is a voicemail that is just responding like it's pre-recorded
and it's responding to everybody as they say things. I'm not even live right now. It's
already started. Kind of the game. Remember when Martin Luther King delivered his historic
I Have a Dream voicemail? That was a great podcast. I think I've already made that joke.
I wish the CIA didn't cut his voicemail offshore. The CIA said this is cringe. The CIA, you
know, the enemy podcast of the PCP. There's a flock of geese flying by my window. I don't
know if you can hear that. Dude, open the window. Let them in. Yeah, see if they want to join
the podcast. Grab them by the neck and then you can eat that. Special guest, a flock of
geese. Dude, we're really scraping the bottle of the barrel. Today we have some geese as
the guest. I know people would love it. It's been years since some geese made a video.
They're basically dead. That is true. They never finished their review of Synecdoche,
New York. I want to hear the rest. Is the movie good or not? I can't tell. I couldn't
watch it, but I don't want to do that. I'd rather wait seven fucking years to hear the
last of the review come out. I stopped an hour in because that's as far as the geese
got with their analysis. And I really want to watch more, but I'd love to watch the
movie, but I'd hate to be spoiled on the analysis. Yeah, exactly. What if I come up
with an analysis that's just greased with their analysis? I don't want to do that. Yeah,
that would be so cringe. You get canceled. I want to be geese. Implying I had a different
opinion. I don't want that. Bad news. Bad news. It would be very unpogged. Speaking of reviewers.
Are you going to review something live? Yeah, I'm going to review this dick. You guys want
to know how the instant win to get a popular tweet on Twitter. The instant life. I know
what it is. Tell us. In case for the audience, just shit on Doug Walker, the nostalgia critic,
and then just everyone agrees with you. They'll instantly retweet it. And if you do it enough
times, eventually some psycho is going to impersonate you and send Gorda people. It's pretty great.
Now, cheesy, I have a question. How do we know that the imposter isn't on this podcast with
us right now? Oh, no. An among us reference. This really is a review. Do they guess that
would be there? It is a little sus. Ask me something only cheesy would know. What is the,
do you like big breasts? Yes. Okay. What's the ending of the villain verse? What's villain
verse about? It's how great capitalism is. Oh, wait, no, I mean, no, it's, oh, no. We got
them. We got them. What is Monkey Jones favorite webcomic? Is that true? It's true. It's true.
It's true. What's his favorite? What's his favorite webcomic? The vapor. I mean, fuck, wait,
no, never mind. You can watch one of these old videos and see the, oh, never mind. Anyway,
so, again, what are you going to say after I rudely interrupted you? Huh? What? What?
You're going to say something? No. You're going to. I had a joke, I think, but it's gone
now. It doesn't matter. Damn. We can pretend to laugh. Things expire. These things expire.
Yep. Yep. I want to know, I want to know how much GME does everyone own right now? I'm
like so stupid because I haven't bothered to look into how to get one yet. You are so
stupid. All you have to do is hold. All you had to do was hold. Hold the line. Just don't
press the sell button. Just don't press the sell button. Just buy the dip and hold. Goddammit.
All right. Can I do it right now? How do I do that? You would need an account on something.
I only have exactly one GME. A giant erect. No, you fucked up. GME. A giant massive erection.
Gem is my name. Pretend I said a giant massive erection first. Someone said that.
Eleazar, make my joke work. Eleazar, make a funny joke. Eleazar will make a laugh, I swear.
I'm also going to buy stock stock. It's not loading. It's not loading. I'm just going to
say I'm pretty sure that it's too late. It's too late if you're looking to buy a game stop.
You might as well just, you're done. You missed the boat. It's not too late. It's not too late.
You could probably make a Robin Hood account right now and probably buy at least one stock
on the market. Didn't Robin Hood be the evil compromise corporation pretending to be for the people?
Yes, Robin Hood is bad and they will restrict your stocks, but they are also the easiest
one to get to open an account on, which is why people use them. That's why it's taken
Spork like five days to open a Robin Hood account.
I was just going to mention Spork. It took her like five days.
Yeah, it's still approving mine. Mine has been being approved for like three days now, so yeah.
I think you should just lie to them and tell them that you're an expert investor.
I've been on Wall Street. I like some Twitter memes.
Yeah, because when I made an account they were like, what was your level of investing
experience and I was like, hello, and I haven't been approved. I think maybe that's it.
Maybe I just had to lie to them and say, yeah, I'm a fucking pro. I do this every day. This is my job
and I am a hedge fund owner. I would never attempt.
Yeah, you fake it so you make it. You wear a suit and then you say, yeah, I'm good.
And then you get in. That's how it works.
Yeah, RFCK is a hedge fund.
Welcome aboard, sir.
Yeah, I run the RFCK hedge fund.
I do. I have a hundred and I have a hundred slime coins sitting right here looking at me.
What's worth more than all the GME in the world?
Oh, please, Mr. Wall Street, please take my slime coins, please.
Please, oh, please, take my slime coins.
Just like GME, the thing about slime coin is you buy the dip and then you hold.
You hold, hold, hold forever. You never sell. That's how you get rich.
My my GME is my GME is sitting comfortably around 300, 300 and change.
And this this week, this week, Melvin Capital is going to have to liquidate.
They're going to have to start liquidating Melvin Capital.
It's going to be fucking epic.
Just like just like still quite high.
I'm looking at the GME.
It's it's yeah, it's pretty high still. It dipped down.
It's going. It's got one of the dips.
It's only going up. It's only going up. Melvin has not liquidated.
What a Melvin.
I'm really happy to see to see all of these big hedge funds losing their marbles over over people doing what they're allowed to do.
There probably won't be huge ramifications for this that end up being good for us.
But in the meantime, the memes are very, very, very, very funny.
I mean, I think I think a few like like few.
I don't know what to call them companies or trusts or whatever.
Somebody's gone bankrupt already.
That's that's Pog. That's pretty cool.
That is pretty Pog.
I mean, they will they will if if it continues, which shows every sign of continuing.
Like shorting the market was the thing like they buy a bunch of stock so that they can make profit off of it later.
But if the stock goes up, they now can't sell it for profit.
And so they've basically wasted so much money and they're trying to trying to wait for the people to stop making the stock rise for people to stop buying and stop holding.
Yeah.
So they can't because it's costing them money in the meantime.
Yeah, it's costing them money every every second they hold on to it.
I think there's I don't know if it's interest exactly, but that something something.
It becomes more expensive the longer they hold on to it to sell it later.
And since the people the longer this goes on, the more damage it will do to these wealthy people who are used to fucking with the economy to make small relatively for them small profits by destroying parts of the economy for fun for gambling.
I think I'm a I'm a little optimistic about this because like, yeah, like some fucking Wall Street douchebags are going on CNN and and being like these these small investors are just trying to fuck over billionaires, you know.
Yeah, exactly.
Nobody nobody nobody likes them.
Everyone hates them.
Like, you know, we fucking Ted Cruz and AOC are both like fuck these guys on Twitter.
I don't think I think I think we're going to win.
Like, I don't think it is like acceptable socially to like, like, I know some people like like a Warren, like Elizabeth Warren was like, this is kind of economic chaos.
We have to regulate this.
But everyone hates Warren.
I think it's going to I don't I think it's going to be good.
I don't think there's they're going to like scramble to like legislate like a little like individuals can't bet on on the on the stocks anymore.
I mean, if they do that go to business, it'll be like even more obvious how fucked the the average Joe is compared to the billion.
That will be the turning point.
I think that I think the ethics of the ethics of the situation are transparent or they're obvious enough that I I don't think they can afford.
I don't think anyone's willing to stick stick their neck out and be like, no, I'm going to defend the hedge funds.
I think I think we got it.
I think we won this one.
I can't wait till President Biden rolls out the new regulations where you're not allowed to bet on stock unless you own land.
Oh, God.
That's how they get them.
But based well based by does it again.
Sleepy Joe.
He did it again.
No.
Sleepy Joe.
Sleeping on my fucking Stimmy.
True.
Sleeping on my Stimmy.
Sleeping on my my shrink in my Stimmy.
What are you talking about, Ben?
Every day.
Can't.
Can't wait for my fourteen hundred dollars.
He always said we were going to get eight hundred dollars.
The always we've always been at war with Oceania.
Eight hundred dollars.
Why would he want six hundred dollars?
You caught on millennials always wanting six hundred dollars from the government.
You should be happy that you're getting two dollars.
Just two.
Not two hundred.
Two dollars.
You know what?
Die.
Just die.
Six hundred cents.
Fourteen hundred dollars delivered in fourteen dollar installments like per annum.
Also you have to pay interest on the money that you already got.
So it gets less and less each time.
It reverse compounding interest is very complicated.
Don't worry about it.
We did the math for you.
Well, we just don't want these people spending their money on frivolous things like GameStop.
Yeah.
No.
That would be unethical.
It would just be unethical if regular Americans were given money to invest in stock.
Because then hedge funders would go out of business.
I've just learned something so incredible.
GameStop was founded in 1984.
Dude, this is literally 1984 right now.
Holy shit.
This is it.
Was it actually?
Yes, actually.
Whoa.
Biden was born in 1984.
What the fuck?
GameStop founded 1984.
That was Texas.
Now, I'm pretty sure Ben is the only one who's ever lived on the East Coast and I don't
know how big this chain was, but before GameStop, I remember that there was a store called FunkoLand.
FunkoLand?
Yeah.
Yeah, GameStop.
There was FunkoLand.
I think it became EB Games.
Something like that.
I think GameStop bought them.
We had EB Games over here on the West Coast.
I think FunkoLand became EB Games and then GameStop bought EB Games.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
Yeah.
I think West Coast had like Game Crazy or something.
Yeah, there was a couple of, ooh, yeah.
I remember a handful of Game Crazies.
Never heard of that.
But I've never really, even as a kid, I never liked GameStop because I liked FunkoLand and
where the FunkoLand was where I lived turned into a GameStop and I was like, well, when's
FunkoLand coming back?
Turns out, never.
It's never coming back.
Damn.
I mean, they were all pretty interchangeable, I guess.
They were all stores that had video games.
I don't know why.
Yeah.
I care because I was a dumb kid, so.
But Tec, good new bad.
But Tec, FunkoLand did come back with the amount of FunkoPops they sell at GameStop now.
Might as well call it FunkoLand.
That's true.
Although, it was spelled fun C-O, not fun K-O.
C-O-O.
I guess you gotta appeal to millennials by spelling things wrong.
Don't correct my English.
I do not respect his language.
No one does.
Okay, my GameStop story is that when I traded in my NES to, I think, get some extra money
to buy, I think a PlayStation 2 maybe?
I traded in my NES and they paid me absolute dog shit.
Yes.
And they gave me $8 for an original copy of Kid Icarus, which is a kind of rare cartridge.
Yeah, that's a pretty crazy game, especially now.
I think it's probably around $40, $50 or something for Kid Icarus.
Damn, you know how much you do it?
That sounds...
I mean, it's not an impossible to find thing, but it's not a super common cartridge.
And they paid me...
I think they paid me like cents.
They paid me like cents for my other cartridges and they gave me $8.
I think I probably made like $30 or $40 trading in my whole NES collection and the console.
And it was good and it was in working condition.
I shouldn't have done it.
What a fucking mistake.
Yeah, I think everyone has a story like that.
You know how much doge coins you get with an original Kid Icarus?
How much is a doge coin?
It's like a cent now or something?
No, it's at about 2.5, I think.
I got a complaint about this.
When doge coin was blowing up, when doge coin was blowing up, it was around like 3 or 4
and I was like, fuck it, it's going to the moon, I'm buying in.
Tom was buying and I was sold.
So I went and I just tried to find out how to do it and I couldn't do it.
I couldn't get any wallets to install.
You know, I couldn't get an account approved in time on...
Oh god, wait, it's going to the moon again.
It's going to the moon again.
Is it up to 4?
Oh my god.
It's up to 4 cents.
Holy shit.
This is just today.
I gotta say, I'm shocked doge coin didn't explode when the doge meme came back.
I assumed that doge coin would have exploded in price when that dog started being funny again.
But I guess it turns out all you really needed to do was have the entire internet start paying attention to stocks and hedge funds.
And then doge coin will be worth 2 cents.
People are talking about investing and then people don't know what it means and they're like,
hey, this is a funny meme about investing.
What's a meme thing you can invest in?
Hey, remember doge coin?
Let's do that.
And then they did.
Doge coin didn't have anything to do with shorting the hedge funds or anything.
It was just like, let's invest in something and doge coin is funny.
Yeah.
Well, high tide raises all ships.
Crypto and GameStop are just stocks.
They kind of just go hand in hand.
Chances are, if you're trading stocks, you know a thing or two about Bitcoin and its affiliates.
But anyway, as doge coin was passing around 4, I could not figure out how to invest.
And then it ended up rising up to like 8.
And I just watched it.
And I was just watching it like, well, I missed it.
I missed the rocket.
They made me watch.
They did it in front of me.
It's all happening.
Are you going to be watching too much again, Ben?
Is this going to be the same as the Bitcoin?
Is this the new key?
Probably not that bad.
Probably not that bad because I was way over-invested in Bitcoin.
I had like a large fraction of my entire net value invested in Bitcoin for a minute there,
which is like a terrible, terrible idea.
I'm not as, I'm only have like a piece.
I'm considering everything that I've put into GME now to be gone.
Which is the right way to do it for this specific holding.
Like with a healthy mindset.
Yeah.
Investing in Bitcoin.
Why don't you invest in some bitches?
Well, with the way Bitcoin's going, maybe I won't have to.
Wait, how is Bitcoin doing?
Bitcoin is, okay.
Bitcoin had a shitty like little meme jump there because Elon put Bitcoin in his bio
and it like jumped up a bit.
That's all it takes.
Bitcoin had almost back to 40 but not quite and now it's back down to like 33.
So, fuck you Elon.
I honestly, after GME, after GME is dead, I am seriously considering like shorting Tesla
because like Tesla has seen like, Tesla is a shitty meme company that doesn't actually do anything.
You talking about that?
This fucking clown is in charge of it.
Who survives entirely off of like, you know, the fact that stupid red editors think that he's cool.
His stock is predicted not to do well and I just think it would be fun to profit off of Elon Musk's loss.
So, I'm probably going to do that.
I don't care much for Elon Musk at all but isn't Tesla the car manufacturing thing okay?
Yes.
Tesla's seen among other things.
I mean, with regards to having like bunches of powering stations and stuff.
I know the cars are like premium like expensive annoying things but like, electric cars are pretty cool.
I guess electric cars have already existed for a while.
My thoughts about that, okay but Tesla's are only for rich people right?
Basically.
They're not like, yeah so fuck them.
That's not a solution.
I think the idea is that eventually they will become the standard but you know, you got to start somewhere.
Electric cars are kind of iffy.
Because you could kind of like, I heard that you could make the argument if there was better public transportation.
There wouldn't really be a need for electric cars.
I mean, if you move everything towards electric cars, you're going to have to get rid of all the old cars.
Which is like even more waste, you know.
I'm absolutely on the like build more trains.
Oh god.
Yeah, fuck Tesla.
Fuck Tesla, fuck Elon and the hyperloop.
Whatever the fuck that is.
The hyperloop is completely stupid.
Yeah.
I hate this whole fucking myth perpetrated by Elon about like, oh yeah, I slept in my fucking car when I invested in PayPal.
You know, because I was betting on it.
I thought like bro, no you didn't.
He did not sleep in no fucking car.
No you fucking didn't.
You fucking liar.
You know, he walked around, he literally walked around with emeralds in his pockets for game college.
Thanks dad.
That's a quote.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, emeralds.
Because he inherited fortune from an apartheid.
Whenever he's like struggling on a test, he just, he just poems the chaos emeralds in his pocket and he's like, let's go.
And then Live and Learn starts playing as his hair goes super and then he gets a 74.
Yeah, he eats.
That's what happens.
This is why Bitcoin exploded.
This is why Bitcoin happened because he fucking chaos controlled the price of it.
It's very vague in the games.
I guess it can raise cryptocurrency.
That's what the chaos, chaos control literally just lets you like make your god mode wishes into reality, right?
Like, isn't that what they're said to do?
It just like stops time or like lets you teleport.
It's really vague and weird.
It just is.
That's what it does.
I thought it does be cool.
I thought that their canonical power was that like chaos control just lets you like make your, basically make your wishes come true.
And just, I guess that implies that Sonic's wish is to be yellow and be really fast.
He saw Dragon Ball Z and he thought that's really fucking rad.
I think I'll do that.
Yeah.
Yo, that's way past cool.
In my fan fiction, they use chaos control to like abort like the anti-Christ.
I'm gonna have to stop you right there.
Okay.
Gotcha.
Yes.
Then what happens?
Then after that, Sonic's like, well, we gotta go save Popeye so they go back in time.
But Popeye's has already been corrupted by Megatron's mind control.
Popeye the character of Popeye the rest of them.
Popeye the savior, yeah.
He's very crucial.
You see, he has like the genetic sequence to activate the Eva, which is going to be important in like arc five.
But I don't want to tell you too much about that.
Yeah, sure.
Oh, naturally.
Dude, I'd love to see Popeye beat the shit out of Shinji.
Dude, you're getting in that robot.
Good, good, good, good, good, good.
I think Popeye should just be relevant again in general.
I guess he's just getting out of the Eva and just trying to beat the age of the fist.
Yeah, he'd take a bunch of spinach and like, no, he'd get like a shipment container filled with spinach.
And while piloting the Eva, he would eat that container and all the spinach would go in and it wouldn't work.
And he would be like, what's going on?
And then he would just do it himself.
Shinji, Shinji, Shinji watching Popeye on a stretcher covered in bandages like every time you won't pilot the Eva.
Popeye has to do it again.
Popeye has to pilot the Eva.
Oh, you ever seen those, there's like a, there was a clip flowing around where like Popeye's like in a fight.
It's from one of the old cartoons.
And even when he's getting his ass kicked, he's still like talking shit.
I imagine like the Eva has a pen.
I've watched some of the old Popeye's and he really just sort of mumbles like,
he's really like mumbly and like talking, like there's no lip syncing sometimes.
It's just sort of like the voice actor is just saying all of these things and there's sort of accent and then there's punch sound effects.
I really actually love Popeye.
The voice direction was just a go fucking ape shit. Just say whatever the fuck you want. We'll figure it out later
Popeye is insane, dude. We haven't really like
solidified the Popeye characters. Let's do whatever the fuck you want
Animation used to be good and then they invented anime. Popeye is Fleischer right? Yeah, down hill
Did you say Popeye is his red build?
Well, yes, but a spinach build really. He's a Fleischer cartoon, right? Like Betty Boop and stuff
Yes, well, I don't know. I don't know names, but he's from that era. Yeah
He started in that era. I'm sure I want Popeyes to show up in one piece
I think it would make sense. Would he be a long-armed tribe?
Remember, that's the only... Franky is already kind of Popeye. He would just be like a regular human who's just that strong like a garb
Yeah, that makes sense. He just has weird arms, but he's not a long-armed tribe. Yeah, some of these motherfuckers just have weird things
He's the thick-armed tribe
It's a new one. Yeah, I like that. I could imagine it in my head
Like that they were outside like a like a like a sailor bar and then Luffy is fucking
Crash through the wall because he got thrown out and then and then like smoke is coming out of the the bar
The giant hole that Luffy just made and we see the silhouette of Popeyes, and he's all like your garb's kid, aren't you?
He's a marine
What if he had like a like a piston double fruit which turns is like his his fists into like pistons like big O
Yeah
That'd be cool. Oh my god. Yeah, Oda, get on that. Can we get Popeye in here?
Please definitely like Popeye. I feel like there's no way he would have been inspired by him for sure
There should be a crossover movie. I could see them doing that. I like that Lupin movie they made last year
Luffy versus Popeye. Yeah, Popeye. Are we talking about Luffy? Whoever wins, we lose
Please stop defending pedophiles for one second. I mean Popeye would be a marine, right?
Yeah, no way. He's he definitely be like a
Not not an admiral, but he'd be like a what's Garth's vice admiral vice admiral. Yeah, he definitely be a vice admiral
True. It's cheesy. I'm surprised there isn't already a Popeye
I mean some some characters have big Popeye arms though. True. Yeah. Yeah
This the set the setting was mostly inspired by Popeye. I'm sure
Cheesy. What were you saying about defending pedophiles?
Is that like an actual news thing or?
It might have been like a year or two ago, but um, it was like it was a couple of things
First it was like, you know, you know, the you know the man get the anime at orico
Is that the cook the cooking one? Yes, like, uh, yeah
Yeah, so that guy turned out to be a pedo
And
Cuz they were friends and then the Roni Kenshin guy turned out to be a pedo and
Oh, they're not just out of but like all of shown in Jeff defended that guy and it was like very like
Man, I know I don't things are different in Japan, but it's an incredibly bad optics. Yeah, it's not it's not the same country
That's for sure. I did it. I I think the Roni Kenshin guy had like
Way more like they couldn't even collect all the child point he had cuz he had just so much of it. Yeah
Geez Louise
Like like terabytes like the real
I
Think it was like I think it was 2.75 terabytes. We can actually go hang on. Let's be a little more specific here. Uh,
Yes
Well, that sucks
I got a parrot everything yo-ho-ho
You know, you know when you hear like something like Tezuka may have said something racist in the past
You're like, okay. Um, that was that was in the past
But it was cool back in the past and it's like everyone was a bit more racist than they are today back then
But you can't it doesn't matter how far back you go or how old you are pedophilia is like terrible
It's always been well, unless you go like to the middle ages or something
I mean, you say you say that and yet like people were fucking marrying 13 year olds like all over the fucking place
So it's not like people were when I pedophilia. She was mature for her age. I swear
I know that I did that I didn't mean like all over the like throughout time. I mean like
People that you could even feasibly know of like ancient historical figures. It's like
Whatever like we we know the world was fucked in many ways back then
It's hard to like judge them by today's standards, but people who are like, I don't know maybe 50 60 years
You know
black and black and white
photograph people
Show me the show me the
Show me the commandments that says thou shalt not sleep with children. Come on
Yeah, I'm drawn up blank here. Well, good thing. I'm not a christian. Otherwise, who knows what I'm thinking with you. Yeah, it's like
Yeah, it's incredibly sucks. Um
I don't think like
didn't Tezuka like beat his wife. Wasn't that the big thing?
I I remember just hearing about like
I was it kimba and some other things where he's like drawn blackface and
a lot of weird
bit of like, um, you know
Not not
Yeah, racist. I think he apologized for those depictions and kimba like years later
But yeah, well, you know, he still did it
they um
They still continue like even up until like the 90s. They were doing things they were drawing a lot of like
You look at like early dragon ball
You still find like little traces of people. Yeah, I mean, I mean there's like mr. Black from the red ribbon army
Who they yeah like a samba character. They they just they didn't have as much of a
understanding because there's so few black people even in that part of the world
Much less in japan itself
So they would like they were sort of divorced from the idea of of like race problems
Like of like what what are the what is the black people in the audience going to feel about this?
You know, like they won't because like none of them are reading that. Um, yeah hot take
They just they aren't here. Take uh japan
Probably ain't that good
Probably ain't that good in place. I'll say bro. Take there you go. Yeah, you know a hot take. We need another nuke
Bro, no, bro. No, they made nintendo games over there
There's gotta be another wife
But we'll give them we'll give them like one more nintendo direct and then
That's that's the squeeze. There's never gonna be another nintendo direct
The duke didn't fucking do anything
The dude two nukes didn't fucking work. No, no, no, it's good because they made godzilla and that's cool
Okay, you know what never mind japan good actually japan great place best place in the world can't beat it. Um
What's that one shit that white national's love to say homo erectus
After those days, it's basically an afternoose day 10 out of 10. We love it. Wait
Well, the thing that the thing that white nation's like to say homo love
They love homosexuals
That they're white national is the love white people so much. They'll fuck any white person amander the gender
Um, just like just like trump said, uh those years after he got the covet
Oh, you know the last guy the last of us who?
Um pre-biden
Oh post post obama pre-biden
Uh, you mean the dark. Oh, yeah, there was like this guy. Um
I like to call him dark obama
You remember dark obama
He was he was that orange. He was the orange
In was in japanese languages. He's known as black obama. They had to change it in the western audiences
It was that was such a weirdest chapter in baki the grappler. I don't even know why
There's like a five page summary of baki monogatari about that. It's really strange. It's just like I didn't see that
I didn't watch that digi video
This is this is the most sus pcp episode in a long time
I cannot wait to see pcp episode. I cannot wait to see the pcp guy doing the sus face. It's gonna be so good
Oh my god, there's a sus face. Yeah, you know like the germa one. You not know about the sus face
Where he looks like um, he looks like apex twin on that one album cover that I was just about to say apex
Oh god what back in my day sus was just sauce. It was youtube poop and it was funny
What could you do I could suck he could suck
Yep, there he is unedited. Yeah
Oh my god, there was this fucking germa video I watched real face
I watched the other day of like his the thing stream and someone like he made like this
This wacky face and then someone in the chat posted a slightly edited version of that face
And he had a nervous like borderline nervous breakdown over whether or not it was real. It was super fucking funny. Oh my god
Oh that that happened so often
He's he was always looking at his like. Oh god. I'm so fucked up
In in he has like a stream like awards of like
The viewers vote on like at the end of the year on like a bunch of things related to germa streams
Like best joke worst joke
um
And then there's like things like worst noise where germa just does a plays a game and he's like
And he's like that's one of the candidates for worst noise of the year
and
It's it's it's really funny. He has things like
like
Like this like like people
there's a there's like a
What do you call it a not a community like a culture of people taking
Images from germa when he's got face cam on and then fucking with them and then sending them to him and he puts them on screen
And he's and he's like crying. It's like no
Crying or laughing like it's just it's just really funny and it's just like a fun back and forth
And sometimes it results in actually scary images like this
German is such like a he's a genuinely great showman. He's probably like
Like the best one of the best
Uh, I yeah, I would I would create is
like
Entertainers online
I'd say
He he's a good. He's a great. Um, yeah showman is is the right word
It's not fair to just say he plays video games on stream. He's yeah
Like you don't you don't do a live action twitch integrated carnival and not be carnival
Oh, yeah, did you have you not heard of that that there was I don't know
I I only I literally only know of germa at all like from you Gibb for the most part
Well, there was this one stream pre-covid. So 2019 2018. Yeah, a few years ago now and he had
Put funds together and he made a stream live stream
With a bunch of people who made robots that can be activated by twitch
Like integrated like button prompts like everybody says up left right and the robot will move
And with this concept like twitch plays with this concept
He was like like twitch plays pokemon kind of yeah, twitch plays pokemon
But twitch plays a physical robot with like a throwing hand or like a something and he creates
He made a carnival in a field
Where like chat plays like toss the ring or like throw the ball
And he does he did
My favorite one. I think was the dunk tank where he's sitting in a dunk tank
And chat has to try and shoot the ball at the target to get him in the water
And it's like it's that's is it a ball or was it a frog like a little
One of the carnival games was complicated. It's it was so complicated. It's like a whole team of people behind it
And sounds awesome. It's it's such a fun like
Stupid thing
And it's just great. I just like
No one else would even bother to do something like this. That's insane. I never I've never heard of such a thing
I think the cherry on top for this whole carnival thing is that like the day he did it. It was so windy and shitty out
It's like it's like the chef's kiss to it all. Yeah, germa has this
Uh this air about him when he's like
Performing where he he likes drawing attention to like things going wrong
and like
You know playing that up like he doesn't actually like it to be super clean. He likes it to be like
Hit him to be the butt of the joke if it looks like shit, then it's funny because he's like
Putting on a shit performance
But everyone loves it because he's trying so hard to make it like an interesting. Yeah, there's like a clear effort there
So like everyone knows he's putting in a lot a lot of effort and when it goes wrong
He you know, he draws attention to it and it's all
Everyone feels like they're part of like the experience and now that carnival is like the
In recent memory at least like the biggest one of the you know, the most germa 985 thing that has happened
Yeah, probably the best thing since the live action germa rumble. Oh, yeah
The live action germa rumble is like, you know the the uh the radcon roll rumble
I was gonna ask was that the inspiration? Yeah, germa germa had done
Royal rumbles with the same sort of wrestling makes shitty characters in his videos
He makes the rumble and like he commentates it like a an actual like a
WWE commentator
Yeah, and he's he's doing all this stuff and he does bits and then one day he made on his main channel
um a live action version of the rumble where a bunch of his friends
And him get into an actual wrestling ring and beat the shit out of each other
You know like a scripted sort of wrestling rumble thing
With like the shitty character people dress up as his stupid video game
joke characters
That was he has he has so like such dumb characters like like the egg
Is one it's just like a guy in all like white makeup
He's just an egg. He was just a dumb character from like one of his first ever videos and now he's just immortalized
Or like glue man glue man or like martin van pieren made of glue
And I think has this elaborate like basketball backstory. Oh, yeah, I forget where that comes from
I know it's on the wiki
It he just did like some like
NBA
like 2k video and
And made like this video like this basketball star called Gabe the glue man del glossy
And then like he fell into a vat of glue and became glue man. I don't know it's
There's there's it's so like stupid, but it but there's it's it's dumb, but it's also high effort
Yeah, it's perfect and like there's a lot a lot to learn
There's a lot to love a lot of lore here a lot to love. Yeah, exactly give
Uh, you obviously, you know germa
So you like watch the you watch you watch like a lot of like the tf2 like commentary stuff, right?
So you've seen star. Yes
Very have you seen the new video he did about I did basically
It was basically like hey guys. Sorry. I haven't uploaded in a while video, but it was actually like pretty sad
It was a bit sad star is a tf2
Tuber and he and germa did a lot of collaborative videos back in the day when both of them were tf tubers
um
And uh, and also like just playing games together in general and they were really like great comedy duo, but star
yeah, was
much more known for his like
Impressive tf2 ability and germa was more like a comedy goof and they sort of yeah
You know, they went there
Different ways and star when overwatch came out. He went to overwatch
He was yeah, he was all in he was thinking this was going to be the next big
Um competitive thing. He really wanted to try out that for that because he's always been like very
Like good at shooting games and he likes playing competitively
um, and his fan base that he'd grown
Uh, just wanted him to play tf2 forever and he just his recent video was him
like
like revealing how
Soul crushing it is to have a fan base that is extremely abusive towards him for not playing a specific game that he doesn't want to play anymore
and it was just him
kind of like raw
like like saying
i'm not gonna do it and
you
What this has caused like in my life as depression and and anxiety and feeling bad
He just went into everything that is that is like
I you know, you hear it the story a lot of times with youtubers being
Feeling trapped. Yeah by their audience and uh, yeah
That's a big one
Because star had not uploaded in a long time. He'd gone straight. He'd been on twitch doing
His own thing for like years now
And his his fans were like
Come back tf2. Just keep playing the same game. Just keep doing what I want
Reliving the the glory days from
I don't know when they were nostalgic
Show us more tricks like the the window and dust bowl
It yeah a lot like throughout the video pieces
This is this is me. This is me with krug smash when krug smash does uh when krug smash does uh a short for it
I say fuck you
More monster killer, please go back to build another big for it and and do a do a plot do a plot heavy for it
shithead
nah
It's pretty much when he plays them when he plays a d a door fortress mod
I say no base game only vanilla only tile sets. Fuck you ascii only shithead
This is me. That's I'm in so I get it. You know, I relate. Fuck that guy who won't play tf2
Yo, that's me when like ben say is making gummy worms. I'm like no no gummy worms
Give us the vapors the champions. I want the champions. Give me more biscapades. I need the vapor stop
No more gummy worms. I can't read gummy worms never make it for real. I'll never make another gummy again
I can't get the imo
I used to I used to have contempt for biscapades because ben was doing it while he was
Holding off on making vapors three and I wanted vapors three
Wow finally glad I finally got that off my chest
It feels good and then vapors three came out and you were like boy. He should have done
It's like oh jeez, man
Showed you, huh?
Grass is always greener. That's what I learned
I've been um
this uh, I uh
I stopped working on my normal stuff first because I wanted to do the uh
It took me a few days to edit the the the oolily a book reading. Is that the secret project? Uh, and then the
That is not the secret project. I was I was working on it. No
That was like a thing I decided to do kind of randomly and was like
I should just bang this out while I still have enthusiasm for the idea
I can uh
Relate to that. Yeah, and then um, and then um, uh
Oh, yeah, and then I like as soon like the day I published that the stock market shit started happening
And I've been occupied. I was occupied with that for the rest of the week
Curious, so this week it's back to the secret prod this week. It's back to the secret prod. Oh
The day. Yeah the day that uh, ben saint reads uh,
Legend of ten elemental masters game stop goes to the moon and dogecoin explodes. Hmm
Correlation does equal causation
Ben saint
Ben saint stein. Hey, wait, wait, hold on. Wait, wait a second there
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Hmm secret project more like
Secret project secret cabal
That's the secret is the secret project is the secret project terrorizing some children to extract their adrena
Perhaps I don't know
Fucking laser your jewish laser to start forest fires in california
Jewish moon laser
Ben couldn't keep the weight off with kita. So he's going to try he's going to try adrena. So it takes it out of the kids
Yeah, he's got to take the kito out of the kids. Wait, is the jewish space laser
Was the jewish space laser on the moon or was it just like on a satellite in space?
Because I remember that the idea guys terrorized chris chan with a moon specifically a moon laser
Was going to destroy quick fill. So I uh, you know, I think it must be it has to be the same laser
Is it maybe it's the space colony? No different laser. I don't know what the idea guys came up with but recently
Uh, there was a story about a congresswoman insane lady q and on marjorie taylor marjorie marjorie
Yeah, that's what I was referring to yeah, um who who thinks that um the fires in california that bush the big fires that
Swept all over the place were started by big funded space lasers
um
Um, and she heavily implies that without actually saying like hmm
I mean, you know, it's it's interesting that it was like these jewish companies that just fun
Like it's all like really stupid
I mean, I've seen old footage of her like talking about how she just is a q-believer
Yeah, like so. Yeah, of course
Of course you would think that there's an i'm a q-believer
A cute q-believer more like a q-t am i right?
A q-t
Not if I go into fight that bitch, um
She's she's you know what you know what?
Ah, what would we do without uh, what would we do without uh, you know once you get to know her it would be undemocratic to not
It would be undemocratic to not have some q representation in our in our houses of congress. Yeah, motherfuckers still be q
Wasn't didn't the date pass where like they were gonna gun down the democrats
Dude, when when people say I don't think she's I don't think she is publicly pro q anymore
But she was for a long time like before like before she was elected when people like say a date that something bad is gonna happen
And they you know rally around that date as soon as the date passes they just say oh, well it'll happen eventually
Here's a new date like that. It's always how they think it's it's either
They either reinterpret the date or I mean in the case of q the answer is like
Oh, the thing didn't happen on the date that it like the the mass arrested and take place
They're supposed to shit that just means the jewish cabal and the deep state are even more powerful than they thought
They're even more of a threat and they were able to prevent it
Like it literally just strengthens their results. Yeah, just trust the plan and it's in the slogan
To never to never stop. Yeah
To never like you trust the plan until it doesn't happen and then fucking trust the plan until it doesn't work and then
Form a private militia and take matters into your own hands
It's so annoying because if imagine like whoever was behind the q posts
originally if they came out
In in the way that they release information and they said sorry guys q has been a fake joke this whole time
It's not actually real. I I've been lying to you nobody wouldn't then believe
That post they would believe what they heard before
Oh, yeah, that's that it was all real, but as soon as the person comes clean
They won't believe it because now they're into this stupid idea
They're too far on honestly. Okay. I I don't
Understand the q business model like what exactly does q get out of being q?
Uh, maybe it's maybe it's cool
I don't know. That's that's one. That's a lot of it's cool. That's a lot of deep state questions. You're asking there ben
Yeah, hmm curious. I mean, it's it's I mean are they make I mean are they making money off it somehow?
I don't know. I feel like I never really thought about it, but I could imagine that the person who is q
Well, whoever they are I am Spartacus
Or even if it's one multiple people it could just be
They are as insane as the people who follow them and just I actually believe it
No, I don't think so. I don't think I don't think so because it's like some fucking palm reader shit
Like all the q drops are are cryptic to the point
They're like deliberately cryptic to the point that anyone could read whatever they want into them
It's it feels like it's like oh someone posted in a in a discord the other day a link to uh a
article by a game designer about how q is basically
It's basically an arg designed without any of like the safeguards that are meant to like
Prevent it from like new dead drop too far. It's at the capital like
Yeah, or like when you're building an arg
You have to you have to design it in such a way that like someone who stumbles upon it
Like won't think it's real like if the arg is a murder mystery
You have to make it so that people won't think that like an actual murder
Happened, uh, if they find a divorce from context and q is like an arg without I think that was a joke
That was a joke on trap on chapel trap house where it's like it's an arg for boomers
Yeah, I mean it kind of is yeah this article explained like here's all the same ways in which you know it engages people
You know, there's like the community aspect of that
It's like they give you clues and then everyone is meant to like work
Collectively on like deciphering what it means and the right answer to whatever a q drop means is just whatever the community
Collectively decides is like the most popular or most compelling interpretation
Literally the right answer is just whatever everyone likes the most and that's and that's what that becomes the truth
It's funny. That is kind of there's this podcast. I watch or listen to rather
It's uh, they're called the the argonauts and they they like every couple of weeks like talk about like an arg
Or whatever and just kind of like dissect it and how what like happened
During the course of it and it's really it's really cool. It's a really cool idea for a podcast
Yeah, that sounds interesting. Yeah, that's really all I had to say. I just I like them. Oh, I thought you were gonna
I thought I thought you were gonna make a point. The point is that that's cool. I always want
I always wanted to make an arg
Um, but now I'm old and it's COVID times. So you can't really do a lot of the cool stuff. Args do
All right, here's an idea for an arg. All right. So you um, you give me money
And then trust the plan and then I maybe I'll tell you where to go
You give me money. I mean, I guess I can't be a villain versus a villain
I
Put like secret messages in the paneling of villain verse like that sword quest arg
Um, I should say now that everyone should buy villain verse book two because I am in it
Oh, yeah, Ben. Are you I haven't I haven't read mine yet. Um, it might yeah
Yeah, yours would have been in it tectonic, which reminds me Ben. You gotta you gotta pay that invoice. They didn't pay the invoice yet
Oh, have I not paid the uh, sorry. Sorry. Okay. I'll pay the invoice
I'm sorry. Do you take dogecoin? I sent money to your Kickstarter and I got that um that drawing
Was I supposed to get the digital versions of of the books that were out of the time? Oh, I should
Did I not give you the link? Hold up. I don't think so
Let's see if I still have the link because I've been clearing out my my google drive. Wait, when did you have the kickstart?
No, it was uh, it was a yeah, it was a go for me for my computer
Yeah, oh right
I was like I didn't pledge to that wall. I think I pledged
Wait, didn't you give me like didn't you give me 20 bucks?
Who me? Yeah, didn't you broke for that? I shouldn't have you didn't deserve it
What it's it's cool. I want it back
You know what? I need to reinvest. Take me out of the book. Take me out of the book and give me that 20 bucks
Don't put me. Don't put me in the book. Take me out
All readers of Villainverse grab your white out find Ben snake and just just go over. I'll just go over them
White amount for one of my friends in a high school yearbook
And then just put your own name there
And then and that's that's the cheek. That's the life hack to becoming a cheesy patron without paying me
It's that easy folks
Send send send bent the cut out bent st cut out of the book in an on put it in an envelope
Send it in the mail and that can that's like a coupon
Uh, if you've defaced if you defaced me it's out in the mail wait a couple of weeks
You'll you'll get a gun and then you'll know what to do with that then you become the real villain. Trust the plan
Trust the plan trust the plan
There you go again. That's it's just a google drive with all the
All the at the time was just up to chapter three. I mean we're up to chapter four now
Maybe she's just giving chapter four for free. Maybe I don't know
Ellie is our make sure to put that link in the show notes by the way. Yeah, put that link. Yeah, everyone can read Villainverse
care
I don't care. Um, I just want more people to read Villainverse. That's it. That's all I want. This is all I want
Is that too much to ask?
There's so much that doesn't want to ask to be popular and people to break my the boundaries of my privacy. That's all I want
Uh, yes, it's too much
Damn
That's some shit. Um
Anyway, what are y'all?
What are y'all up to?
What are y'all up to nowadays?
Okay, um, just um, just getting mad on twitter
These these days it's about like wall street hacks and uh and uh msm cronies being like
Ooh, russian. Oh, no russian bots and and white nationalists are buying are buying a gamestop
Every time it's always the same thing every time every time every time
Yeah, I mean you've seen you've seen those articles getting posted around that like this is that the fucking game
Game stop stop shorts short squeeze is just gamergate too for some reason
It all leads back to gamergate
There was that one article where
This one lady was talking about how there is some there's a couple of people out there
Who have anti-semitism beliefs towards like wall street like they think they're hitting the jews where it hurts
Yeah, sure are I don't disbelieve that but
Yeah
It's it's literally the same thing as when uh when van jones on cnn when people were calling a bloomberg and oligarch
And van jones was like, oh, that's anti-semit. That's an anti-semitic slur. Is that the guy that looks like an ace attorney character?
No, that's not cowman. Okay. No, no van jones is like a normal-looking guy, but uh, whatever. He's just some he's just some talking head
Yeah, uh
But yeah, but the point was like the point was like don't like if you don't like how rich this guy is that and you say so
That's anti-semitic because he's a jew. That's yeah, that's so that's so fucked up
That's so fucked up and not to like let anti-semit's off the hook or anything
But like that's the kind of stupid thing that an anti-semit will point to and be like, uh, this is this is what i'm talking about
You can't criticize the jews anymore because they control the media. You can't keep getting away with it
It's just it's just falling into like a very obvious and stupid trap. It doesn't make any sense
Maybe some really fucking mad. I really I have to wonder then
like
The people who think that the like the rich are the jews like equal like and they're like the fucking over the rich
Do they think that?
Ultimately
They should just have the riches themselves. They just want to be up there and they just yeah
It's yeah, but but they're not but they wouldn't be jewish. So it would be okay
I mean, it's like it's that logic that most fascist beliefs have where it's like the enemy has to be weak
But they also have to be incredibly strong at the same time, you know
Because like when they talk about the jews like when they talk about the jews and they describe it
They're like they they themselves are proclaiming themselves to be the superior race
But when they talk about the jews, they keep talking about how the jews outsmart them and it's kind of like
Well, then isn't the jews like better than your race then by that logic?
Well, I mean, okay. I mean to them. It's all about tribalism. So it's like, yeah, okay
If the jews control everything that's bad because they're not me and I and we my tribe should control everything
And that would be better my tribe by the way includes me a tribe called quest. Yeah. Thank you everyone
Bass
Ow
Yeah, that's what it's about. It's it's just it's just the us the generalized us versus them
mentality
Um, man, uh, where how do you even get on this shit? No, I
I had there was something funny. I like noticed though. I remember I was looking
At that article. I mean, specifically the article wasn't saying that they were all antisemites, but there is like
A subsection of the people who are investing in these stocks in these stocks who well, sure
I mean, there's there's a there's a subsection of any group. No, no, I mean, no, I'm not like I'm not like
Thanks to jews control wall street. Yeah. No, I'm not like fucking saying I'm saying like she
She's saying she's not like she's not proclaiming that it's all of them are antisemites
She said there's a subsection of them and then like there's people in the comment to react saying like
Oh, they're they're not all antisemites blah blah blah
And then then right after under them you see people commenting
Oh, well, are you sure it's not the jews controlling everything and then they post like the general like they post a general like
poll charts with the like, um, weird how all these studios are run by jews, huh? And it's like
What's that got to do anything if true?
Yes, yes, sure
Uh, she's funny. I don't know. I used to just find everybody it's weird. It's weird how you see people
It's weird how you see people like claiming that like
That like antisemitism isn't real
Like or and like right alongside other people who are just unironically like actually jews do control
I mean if you like the media and everything and should be destroyed
They'll do it and like
Yeah, but like group a will just we'll just like pretend that group b either is just joking or that like they're just trolling
Or they're just such a small minority that they don't count
They just don't take the two seconds to kind of scroll down
And see that oh shit. There are people like that
It's sort of like a no true scotsman thing like if anyone does espouse such a viewpoint
It's like well, they're an extremist and no one takes them seriously, right?
It's not like a real opinion that a real person has, you know, that's just that's just some crazy talk, you know
I guess the the most annoying thing for me is that like not everybody who holds those views
Holds them strongly enough to know where the logical
Like conclusion would be so if somebody says oh you want the jews to die or whatever
They may not really have thought about that. They just think the jews control everything
Because they've heard that and they just think it's true
And they don't realize that they're in league with people who do want the jews to be killed
And then and then they defend themselves like I don't want I like jews. I know jews. I don't want the jews to die
That's stupid. You're you're you're you're making stuff up
And they just don't understand where their position would lead them logically. I'm sure there's some
Just pisses me off because it's hard to talk to those sort of people
They haven't thought about what they actually believe it. It's a lot of very surface level like answers
You know, I mean, I mean if you're very if you lack if you lack all historical context
I mean, it's not like every it's not like every
A party member in you know, germany in the 1940s or whatever was like
Like yes, I personally would like to execute people of the hebu race like
They weren't all like that most of them were just like yeah, you know
This is this is probably best for our economy or whatever
Swing kids, huh? Or watch that movie
I
No, I guess I'm the only one who's seen it then. Uh, it's a it's about these group of
teenagers in
nazi germany who
Uh, who like swing music, but it's like band or something
Cool
And it's it's kind of sad. It's kind of sad because they because they all they all get caught at like
I'm spoiling swing kids. They all get that
One of them gets beat in the street and killed and the rest like get caught by uh during like some sort of
Like underground dance or something and then they get uh drafted into the military and presumably die
That's so this is like it's like footloose, but it's like nazi footloose kind of is yeah
If kevin bacon was was there things would have been different
If kevin bake, I've never actually seen footloose. I just I've seen that scene in hot rod
That is a parody of footloose
I saw kevin bacon die in the first
Friday the 13th
He's in that
It's it's it. Yeah, I think that that's probably what happened
It's it's that episode of avatar where ang gets all the fire nation kids to have the dance party. This is what happens
So after after ang leaves
Yeah
After he left things are really wet
And you fucked up you fucked the man. Didn't you think about your actions?
No
So deep speaking speaking of fire
Um, I just finished reading the manga fire punch. Have you guys heard of that manga? Is that like fire force? No
It was uh, it was written by the guy who wrote chainsaw man
Was that before after chainsaw man? Yeah, I was right before chainsaw man
Any good and it's uh
I
It was it was good, but it felt very like
Like there wasn't like a
Concrete like goal it was heading to it was kind of like making stuff up as it went along
Yeah
And which isn't necessarily like a bad thing
But like I guess the problem with that is like
Like I mean, okay, so for example when you read like one piece like, you know
Since chapter one, you know what the goal is, you know, it's like oh become king of the pirate
So you said that becomes kind of like a rope for the story, you know, even though one piece could like fluctuating quality
You're still kind of like
Determined to see it to the end, you know
Yeah
So that like that like incentivizes you and then the problem with like manga that like doesn't have a concrete goal
Is that even like the slightest the slightest dip in quality is kind of a big risk
Right, so because it's kind of like why the noise is heading so I don't really want to waste my time, you know
um and fire punch
Well, at least fire punch is like consistently good
But it really does feel like this guy's like making it up as he as he went along
And what people tell me is that chainsaw man has more of a
Concrete cult goal and I guess that's why it lasted longer than a fire punch
I don't want to tell you too much about fire punch, but there is a lot of punching that with fire. So, you know
It doesn't lie. It was so like fairytale
Yeah, is there fairy tales and fairy tales. There's feet
Now fairytale the the main guy in fairytale is he uses fire and he punches
Oh
The base
Oh god, there's this um, there's like this five hour long video
on youtube called a fairytale retrospective
And like I I played that in the background. I was like
Uh cleaning my room to move out because I just needed some bullshit and it's not even a retrospective. He's just like
Reading the entirety of like the Wikipedia articles for like fairytale
You know this isn't a retrospective. You're just fucking just describing what happens
In fairytale now, I know everything that happens in fairytale and I hate it when when you know
slightly like more than the surface level of a subject a lot of youtube videos talking about something start to become
A lot more like Wikipedia
rereads like I've always felt that it's so much of like just
basic information
I was I was looking on like minecraft like I saw one video
Which is like what which is the best way to dig for to find diamonds in the most efficient way
And I was like I kind of want to know so I clicked on it and it was basically just
A bunch of boring uninteresting like if you've never played minecraft before you will learn something
But since I know a little already
It was so devoid of anything actually useful
And I and I cried I cried and I shit myself because it was such a shit videos bad
And I uh liked and subscribed. I um, I kind of had a feeling
similar to watching um
Um, you guys y'all know embleman, right? Uh, yeah. Yay
More or less. I've been like slowly phasing out of not being an embleman fan really, but
But like he made a video because he made that joke, right? What was that?
Because he made that trump joke. Yeah that
Yeah, like he deliberately put like trump propaganda one of his videos
But also, um, I I
That was like vague enough that I couldn't really understand the it sort of seemed like a like a trump like a trump was robbed thing
But it I didn't really see it like that. I could see how it would it was
He dropped the video it was vague enough that like if he said like no
I was just referencing current events in an ironic way. I could be like, yeah, I guess maybe
I mean he was referring to specifically as like, oh, we a trump is a necessity, you know, and it's like
Eh
Wait trump, I don't know. Maybe I'm thinking of a different. Um, I'll repost the clip
But um, that being said, um, he dropped a video talking about like villains and whatnot
And it just basically like it just felt like he was reading like tv trope articles
It didn't feel like he was really like doing an analysis on
Villains god. I I hate it. I was that for that video that thumbnail for that video makes me mad
But please finish your thought that's that's what um, that's what that's what most of the gun videos from ahoy feel like
it's just him like saying which guns were in which video games and
Just sort of like reading from a list
I mean, I could there's probably other better examples
But that's the one that jumps to mind that is the most like this guy literally just went on wikipedia and wrote a list and like
Wrote it in like pros format
And then read it we put video game footage over it
And this is wikipedia, but in video form
What was that guy that was like making cool videos?
And then you disliked him because he made like one about the gorillas
Which is so basic and surface level but people loved it because it was a nice reduced video
Oh, uh, yeah, was it captain christian? Yeah, I don't even remember that video, but I remember
What you're talking about and how captain christian is an idiot
It's just it's I mean this sympathy I remember seeing this. I'm like, oh, yeah, zuko. Yes
He responded to my tweet. He responded to my tweet being salty that I said he saw
pussy
Yeah to that guy. He just dropped off the face of the earth
Well, good
Like his first video was about a a
As a superman fleischer cartoon
Superman I'd never heard or seen of that so that was interesting
But then everything after that was like, oh, I've heard of this. Oh, I've heard of that
Um, okay. Do you have anything new do you have anything like good?
I didn't really
It kind of reminds me on uh, I don't know if you heard this podcast
But it's called the pcp and I remember a member on that podcast. That's right. I remember a member on that podcast said
I can't remember who it's probably didgy
Um, she said something about like you actually not know or this isn't a bit
But it's like something that they said that I do agree with a lot
About like a lot of times captain christian's videos and sometimes other people's videos
Sometimes super ipaduals videos are like this where it's basically like the thesis statement is like, oh this good
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure. Yeah, I mean, yeah tons of videos are like there's nothing really wrong with that
Like I've done that before I saw one. There's nothing wrong with that because like, you know, sometimes you like to be reassured
Yeah, the thing you like is good or sometimes you want to be sold on something, you know, yeah
I I
Yeah, I guess it's it's like there's nothing wrong with it, but it's it's the um
The highfalutin fancy pants sort of attitude about how cool
Yeah video is even though there's nothing to it
Especially I think part of it comes from like people
People really like when captain christian was making videos people were super into him
I mean me included too because like his editing was really good
so
Yeah, like the the first couple ones I thought they were pretty cool
And then I guess it was the gorillas ones. I was like this if he didn't say anything and like
It wouldn't bother me except that like I had liked the previous ones
Uh, you know it
No, no, that was that's pretty much
What what I think happened with me was that uh, like all of his videos are sort of the same thing where it's like
thing good with really good editing
All right, and here's why?
And and there's nothing really wrong with that, but I think there's this sort of
Like like he got so much praise for it. I think maybe there's part of a almost it's not
It's not like he's the only
Right, it's not like he's the only one who makes videos that are just
Yeah, he was he just sort of came out of nowhere and it seemed like oh this guy's like planned out his youtube career
And it's like wow, this is so like all of the thumbnails are like color-coded and
It's all very very well
Considered, but when you really look at it, it's nothing special
And you would completely forget it and never watch him ever again
And I think people like that and that's what I just sort of lost relevancy lately
I mean, I've never I have not seen videos like that for a long time. I mean there I mean there was
I mean there was a there was a bubble getting recommend. There was definitely a video
There was definitely a video essay bubble that was like captain christian sort of was around like right when it was peaking
Yeah, I mean nerd writer was maybe like sort of the
The the like front man of it for a minute there and that was when when nerd writer was peaking
That's when captain christian showed up and everyone loved his shit
And I think it has deflated. It hasn't like fully popped like people still make video essays
But um, I think it's deflated a bit that particular stuff
Wasn't there like a brief period of time where there were where like every frame of painting was still uploading videos
Hi, my name is Tony captain christian was yeah, this this was the heyday of every frame of painting too
It was around the same time in this specific era where all these video essays are coming out and people were like just enjoying them all
But then in retrospect a lot of them didn't really say that much
I mean every frame of painting stands up. Yeah, I still watch this must be a copycat guy
Well, every frame of painting has a really solid like technical analysis
That like the your average your layman's you were criterion doesn't he able to explain I don't I don't want to like like shit on this person
But I I always saw them
What's like, what are they called?
Now you see it
I always saw them as like an every frame of painting ripoff that was just not quite as good
I've seen their videos and I can't really remember any of their videos
Wait, I'm trying to remember now
It's it's a channel called now you see it and it's like no, I don't talking about
Movies and in the same sort of fashion of like look at this camera move or whatever
But it was just not as good and I just
I don't know. There was a lot of those as well
If something's popular people will copy it. You know what channel i'm really digging recently
Is a accented cinema
You guys heard of this channel? No, no
They um, there are there are chinese guys who like
Analyzes like not just like chinese movies, but he talks about a why like
range of stuff
right and um
I think one of my he did he talked about he said why he didn't he made a video called why I don't like shin godzilla
And I mean, I love a shin godzilla, but I think it's like
It's very I like it when
I do like hearing
Like when people have the opposites like why they don't like the things I
I like you know as long as they're like not you see I just get mad being reasonable
Because they're usually mad too
Yeah, this channel is really good. Um
They have one called how to film a good sword fight, which I think is very interesting and it says a lot of things that they don't think about
um
And they have one on uh, they have one on
Pulgasari you guys ever heard of pulgasari. Yeah, he has like a 4chan board, right?
Hmm, wait, what was that? He has like a 4chan board devoted to discussion about him, right?
Yeah, maybe I don't know. No, pulgasari is the north korean kaiju movie
No, wait, yeah, they all one of those
Oh, yeah, oh, you can watch it all you can watch it all on youtube
I'm actually if you want to hear an analysis on it. I made a podcast about it, but
That be that being said polkas what makes pulgasari so infamous is that the director was like kidnapped from south korea
And forced to make the movie
Is it right?
But the movie is like very interesting because it's I watched it and it's actually a pretty decent like
kaiju movie
But also it could be interpreted as like an anti north korean film or like kind of like
Trying to send a message to the north korean all we agree between the lines, you know
In a way. Yeah, like if you read
Yeah, hold up. I'll uh, you can watch the entirety of the movie on youtube
I'm looking at accented cinemas videos. I'm scrolling down. I see minecraft enslave the populace
I was like, oh, what cool interesting. Oh, it's april fools
So this channel I I hate it. I hate it when when the the april fool is that thing that is cool isn't real
Yeah, it's always better when it's like thing that is cool, but stupid
Is real wait, no wait, no ascented cinema is good. You haven't seen it. Y'all
I'm
Okay, yeah, here's the podcast where we talk about pulgasari. Uh, check out the sick thumbnail
Is that honestly cheesy? I gotta say I love this thumbnail idea where it's just picture from the movie with gun
Yeah, I um, I do that every time I do a podcast about any movie. It's always like, oh, yeah something from the movie with a gun
I just I did it with my uh, dragon quest your story podcast
It's just it's just so funny
I'm pretty sure this might backfire me in some way like youtube's gonna be like, oh if you have a gun in the thumbnail
We're gonna restrict your video or something
We will just kill you that
Christ
I had one of my videos recently like
Like automatically manually
Set as made for kids because I wasn't swearing in it or something
So that I couldn't make money off of it anymore
Like they they sent me an email saying we've uh reviewed your video like this hadn't been flagged or anything
It was just like suddenly we've reviewed this video and we've just determined that it is made for kids
So now it is made for kids
Oh, thanks
Which um
I mean it was one of my old pony videos. So I'm like whatever
Yeah, but you know, I can see why but like I don't like that. They can just flip a switch to do that
Yeah, that is annoying
It is incredibly annoying. I wish there was humans in between where you could talk to you about this shit, but nope
Nope, no humans cost money who we don't want to spend that
Is cheesy in a fancy world right now?
Uh, it's one of my roommates is probably playing the little piano and playing melodica. That's funny
It's telling me
More than half of the roommates here play an instrument
Um, you could have like a little band
I could I'll uh, I'll be I'll be uh, the the lyricist. I I know how to write man. I'm pretty good at it
Yeah, I could be that I went to um music videos. I went to a concert once remember concerts guys. Haha. Anyway, uh,
No, we're the
Welcome back. I'm back by the way and by tectonic the thing you said about uh, april fools
Uh, I remember you said the same thing in your rpg video
About the about the the april fools better when the thing is real. Yeah, okay. Just had to have someone dead
Yeah, but it's it's
There was I went to this concert once where um, it was like a
It was like a dual
Like a dual performance or whatever
Uh, or it's like two two headlining acts one goes after the other and I me and my sister
We really only wanted to see the the second act
but we went through the opening one anyway because it's like, you know, whatever uh, and
They weren't great. It wasn't really like it was kind of like boomer-ish music
But uh, they had like a hype man for some of their songs. It was just it was just this like
Uh, like lanky black dude with like a like a fedora and like a black suit
And he's just kind of like walking around the stage like getting everyone super excited and it it was
Confuddling me. I had no idea like what the point of him was
because like the music
It was it was it was just like rock music
So I feel like do you really need a hype band like that and is that all he does and it was it was all he did
He was like part of the touring band so strange
That is incredibly strange. Um, very it's very vivid in my mind. I don't remember the songs. I remember the hype man
One time I remember there was this girl. I had a crush on
And um, one of one of those artists that we both like was in town
And I asked him like hey, you're going to this concert and she's like, uh, maybe and then I'm like, well, it'd be cool to see you there
Am I right and then like the day of the concert
She'd be at me saying like you're still going to that concert and I'm like, yeah, and then she's like, okay cool
Me and my boyfriend are going to
I'm like, oh, I'm like, oh awesome. It's like, uh, actually I have covid so I can't go
This is like three years before I have a normal strain of the coronavirus. Oh, sorry
But um, no, I have that weird lung thing from vaping. I have uh looks at year
I look so anyway
I show up to the venue early because I had a bar and I decided to get stupid drunk
Because I did not want to meet her boyfriend sober and it was great actually and after that I realized
Whoa, I love going to shows super drunk. So now I'm super drunk at every show
I usually get like a drink, but I don't
Plastered
I love I love getting uh, super drunk
Getting getting getting plastered in like a public bar. It's it's the only way to feel
Like uh, you're not gonna
It's it's strange the only way to feel like you're not embarrassing yourself is to be a little drunk
So you so you don't actually
Makes the the last the last time I got drunk in like a public bar
I ended up like I ended up like, uh
It was when I lost my wallet and I kept asking the bartender where my wallet was and I like heckled
I like heckled a fucking like stand-up
I got told to shut I got told to shut up by the management
And uh, and then I went back when I went I've told this boy when I went back and asked the bartender like hey
Do you find what he's like you asked me this like 40 times yesterday? No, I don't have your wallet
He's glared at me and it was like the worst feeling that's kind of familiar
Yeah, yeah, I mean this was like this one. Okay. This was like a year and a half ago. Yeah, because this was pre-covid
But yeah, that was the last time I got drunk at all. Yeah, and I felt and I felt so terrible about it. It was traumatizing
It was just one time
Known as an annoyance. Yeah, when you didn't say
No, the fact the fact that that I was annoying enough that this guy who works at a bar where people go to get drunk
That I stood out in his mind as being like particularly obnoxious
No, oh
fuck
Yeah
Okay, okay
I think I think though that it was a bad influence because I was with because I was with that weird girl
And I think that she was the one it started heckling and I think I just kind of followed her lead
No, I think that's why it was the girls fault. I didn't do anything. I'm innocent
It was all the woman. It's always a woman's fault. She ate the apple. She ate the apple first
She's from she stole my rib and then she ate the apple
And that's why that's why mankind is like in a fallen state. God the problem is that we're raised by our mothers. That's the problem
I
one time at a show I uh
Think this was probably the last concert I went to was I went to see like Cara Cara Bonito in uh
In boston or whatever and I was getting some I was getting some cash out of the atm
And I noticed that there was an id on the ground. I was like, oh my god, someone dropped their id
Uh, I I should probably go pick. I should probably go report this or something. I pick it up. It's fucking my id
I dropped my id on the ground
somehow
I was like, I was like, what if you didn't realize that you well, thank god
What do you what what what venue was it at in boston? I remember it was um, oh shit
It it was somewhere. I've been
In
Was it the middle east? No, it wasn't the middle east. It it it was
It wasn't the paradise
Rock, oh, maybe it was the paradise rock club or something like that. Oh, I never I know it was
I have no fucking clue. Yeah, I'm just gonna say it was the paradise rock club
What if you went to go
You didn't realize it was your ideas id so you went to go give it to them and they looked at the idea and then they looked at you
And they're like, is this a fucking joke
The idea was kind of old
So so I don't know if I looked like the picture. I had sure I look like Mike. Uh, actually
Yeah, I probably look like minecraft steve and my fucking id god my head is so square. That's fucking cool as shit
Uh, man, I I mean, I don't like it. My my younger cousin would bully me
My zoomer cousin would be like shut up minecraft steve when they look at minecraft steve minecraft steve. No, no
Minecraft steve, please no
Won't you go mine diamonds minecraft steve? I never played minecraft. I don't understand what your zoomers are telling her saying to me
I'm hero brine
I am not minecraft steve. Oh god damn. I was
Oh, it's been a little it's been a little while since we did a pcp minecraft
I'm gonna say hasn't it been like isn't it's two weeks a little while? Oh man, maybe I guess internet time
We've been trying to do it more regularly. I guess word
Yeah word word did you uh the uh, did I did I tell you that I that I spent a while off stream?
Uh, just like mining marble. I mean, there's like there's like four chests full of marble. Yeah, and uh, what can you do with marble?
I haven't played minecraft since like we're building gibbs, uh abby's play 12 or something
Uh, also, um
Hey, okay, so we've been I don't know if this is the time to talk about it
But like maybe maybe those abby should have been made with like marble facades instead of full marble blocks
What do you mean facade? Is that a thing?
I mean
There's a there. I mean, I think one of the mods lets you make a yeah
Like you can make not a full block, but just like a very thin sort of like
Less than half a block of that has like the brick marble texture on it. I think
I mean, it's too late now
I mean at the moment I need like the I need like nether
um, nether quartz
Shit
uh
Well, I mean there's I mean uh, uh maren maren made the uh, the machine that is just like generating infinite nether quartz
pan
Oh, yeah
God those mods are so fucking strange. Oh
We still haven't I mentioned this before I I still next time we play I have a
A gift for you that will make maren very angry. Yeah, we should we should play. I can't fucking wait
Yeah, we should yeah for sure
And you should all go to the fucking pcb minecraft
uh
patreon
Uh, and uh, so you can have infinite nether quartz by a mage
No
I think maren runs it
Maren pan is a is uh the the one of the uh big time minecraft gods is what they is
Oh, wait, yeah, this might be off topic, but I did you see that like last week? I I um
I clipped out my my pan peaks are rent from that one pcb episode and I edited it right next to the pan
Yes, yeah, I saw and I finally uploaded to my channel
I saw that and like that got me like six new subscribers on the spot because of it
Dude six. I want to say
Okay, one one last thing about the pcb minecraft server is I was doing I was doing the top killers like art stream
Uh day before yesterday, I think
and you know, I was editing the top killers uh image and people the subject of um
Minecraft came up and someone maren pan was in the chat and
Someone was like, uh, oh maren pan is the guy like oh maren pan. It's cool. He built like he's building like the full scale
Uh, uh
New os angela city, you know thing in minecraft and everyone was like, oh, wow, that's really cool. Oh, well, that's really cool
and someone was like, uh like
But someone was like, oh, but you know, it's if you have to pay to get in the server and it was I was like
I was a little I don't know how to feel because I was like, oh, that's good
That like there's a cool thing in the pcb minecraft server that someone might want to like pay money to get access to
But also like, oh
These these rfck heads are like they're they're cut off from the
From the goods
It's it's only five bucks a month. It's only it's only five bucks a month and uh
maren pan's a full scale recreation of nlaka come is is always growing
Downtown I think is basically done and it looks fucking sick
Um, okay, I don't know. That was that was just an experience that it happened and I made me lull
Fuck you. Fuck everyone that doesn't uh, that's not in the server
Give us money. Give us money. It's pretty. It's pretty money. Give us money. Yeah
No, I I um
No, sometimes when I'm just like want to relax. I just pop in there and mine some ports or whatever
And usually there's nobody in there usually most people on the show for the streams
Uh, but not always sometimes people are around
Okay, that's enough. That's all I have to say about that
but but but based
um
Well, I've I guess one thing that I've noticed was interesting
I don't know how many people of how many of you guys follow philosophy tube
Oh, yeah
I mean, I'm not like caught up. But yeah, she she she uh has as abagail
Forced to tube made a coming out video, which is very cool
and
like very
Classy in in all aspects of the coming out very classical abby
I I have not I have not watched how did he do it better than I have not watched the video
Uh
Um, okay. Anyway. Yes, great. We love to see it
We love to see another pcp member transition awesome
They they're inspired by the pcp. Yeah, they um, they saw the jenny's
Gives did did anyone's transition. Okay. I'm sure I'm sure that probably nobody
I'm sure nobody else cares and nor should they but did anyone see peter coffins reaction to it. Yeah. Yeah, I was very
What did they say?
What did they say you fucking bigot, sorry
I'm very sorry
Pete peter coffins said peter coffins reaction to abagail coming out
And everyone being very supportive was to to tweet like when I came out as non-binary a mainstream magazine ran a piece on how
I was a male appropriating feminism
Damn, like just being salty. I mean, that's okay. That does suck like so
Okay, it it does suck it does suck but like
Why it's it's it's very sour. Why it's like, oh like it's it's like to to bring it to bring it up right then
It's like it's just pure sour grapes and it's really unfortunate. It made me pretty mad. Yeah
Um, you know that peter coffee used to follow me on twitter
Yeah
Yeah, they did for a moment. I followed them back but then like the more ridiculous their tweets came out
I was like, okay. I think this is enough. I think i'm just gonna stick to your ex who has fat tits
Speaking of fat tits abagail Shapiro
Um, uh, no, I don't I don't like her. I don't like uh, she like
She is look can I be a look can I be a little misogynistic for a second?
Of course, of course, of course. No by all means. No, she's gonna be the cheesy misogynist for a minute here
If I could just be ironic for a moment your honor. It's it's like she's not she's not really
She's not really that funny like not all
Dutton she's really not very little like banger tweets to be honest and she doesn't even
I don't even show that many like she's not funny. There's like there's like other if you say it's because of her boobs
There's like other twitter. Yeah, there's like other twitter girls with big boobs
Obviously people follow her because she's got huge tits. She's not that funny and honestly. I think her face is kind of gross
She's she's like talking about are we talking about the lady who has the
Yes, yes, I don't know who she is. Okay. I don't blame you
this is this
Uh much much like how peter coffin was caddy about the philosophy
To coming out this conversation is very caddy
True. I'm not being caddy. I'm just saying she's not that funny
People follow her for the way she looks and I don't like the way she looks. So what's the what's the appeal?
There's none. I'm being a big cap boy right now a big cap boy right now. Um
Fun. All I'm saying all I'm saying is that like I've seen other
lefties
Uh girls with big boobs who show more big boobs than actually does they're more praxis and funny
That
I want to say I want to say I'm not I'm not I'm not angry. I'm not jealous
That uh punish that punish that punish friday and flip friday and slip
I'm not jealous that um that ashley follows michelle. All right. I'm not jealous. That's not why I'm saying this
Wait, really does she yeah? Yeah, they follow each other. Why I don't know why
Because michelle also makes funny tweets, which are I think funnier
I think they have the same I do find michelle funnier even though
bishchelle is like my enemy
um
She's my she's my nemesis
If people if the audience don't know what i'm talking about i'm talking about michelle. Um
Girl girl nate girl best guy if you will
The best guy girl. That's we should get michelle on the show. Oh, we should
We should yeah, we should me. Yeah, cuz I yeah, we should. Yeah, totally. Yeah, didn't you listen to get her on the horn?
Cheesy didn't you listen to the intro me and tectonic? Yeah, you know
Veteran members of the pcp. Come on. I should have never played that game of blackjack
I I regret everything that has happened since then we're kicking out now. We're gonna kick you two out
And then we're gonna invite gamers tavern as a permanent member
And then the transition will be complete
No
All i'm asking is to put look if I if i'm a guest at the same time michelle is like that'll be a big fight and that'll be entertaining
i'm just saying
Yeah, probably back in the show and ben. Yeah ben there me and ben could double to hear her
Shut up. All i'm saying
All i'm saying all i'm saying is look at her face and look at her lipstick
And how her lipstick goes above her lips
It's so weird looking and it makes me mad. I hate it
I hate it. Is that about michelle? Is this the is it? No, it's about no ash
I hate ash's lipstick is bizarre
The cheesy misogynist and the biggest saint once again united together. Shut the fuck up. I hate you
I hate everyone honestly honestly. No unironically whenever anyone tells me that i'm being misogynistic because I think a girl is ugly
Fuck you. You are the you are the misogynist
Uh, it's it should be okay to say that about anyone. Uh, I'm so fucking mad. I hate all of you. I hate everything
I'm not the misogynist. You are
Yes, unironically. No, not me you. No, not me you every single time
I may be a misogynist
But at least i'm not a liar
You are though you're both of those things. I think I mean in this instance
Uh
From what I've seen like she goes to great lengths to show off her attractiveness
So to critique her attractiveness is not like misogynistic. It's just like thank you
It's part of what you know like her appeal and if you don't agree with it then
You know, I said the same I said the same thing about I said the same thing about maryc deville and everyone got on my ass about
You know what? You know what? I like to have what I like to state a formal apology to benzade. I'm sorry
I put you out on blast on twitter.com
Um, I un-cancel benzade right now
I'm free
I'm like a genie my my my gold handcuffs are breaking at the end of all
I'm free now. I can be as much misogynist as I want to be
Ha ha just kidding. I'm even more misogynist. Let the bigotry commence
It's the it's the sicko sky. Yeah, benzade is the sicko on the window. Yeah
Go in sicko mode
Oh, god. Ha ha. Yes. Yes speak. Okay. So anyway, I remember when we were talking about analysis videos earlier. No
Um, so anyway, I just brought that up
Because I was gonna I was gonna show my own analysis video coming soon
Doge dogecoin plummeting dogecoin plummeting cheesy cheesy
It was up to four. We need to go to four. It's going down. It's going down. It's
Oh, wait, no, never mind. Never mind. He's canceling his video. He's canceling his video. I'm canceling my analysis video. I'm canceling it
No, no, please. Oh god, it's dropping. It's 0.352. 0.35.
Is it gonna hit 0.3? Will it go below 0.35? You've crashed. I don't know what I want. Oh my god. This is it
Tom, Tom, get out. Tom, bail.
Get out of there, Tom. Tom. Tom. No. Tom.
Don't, no. I'm already dead.
Damn
I learned I learned uh
The real doge's name
It's very cute. The the doge that the the meme is based on's name is um
Oh my god
Fuck I can't kabosu. That's a weird name. It's kabosu. Oh my god. That's a weird name
Kabosu it's the name of like a citrus fruit and the owner named it that because it had a round face
Like a cut over and that is cute kabosu or an or or an orange. Yeah. I do love cheap
I'm a big fan of chimes myself. I think chimes is the best variant
Is it a is it a hot take that I think chimes is funnier than doge? If it is then I stand by it
I think yeah, I think chimes is better. I mean, I love love doge
Love doge, but I think I prefer chimes. Yeah, just objectively. Chimes just looks cool. Like let me let me show you a picture
Let me show you my favorite
I've seen I know what chimes looks like. No, let me show you my favorite chimes picture when when you see when you see buff doge
And and like the little crying yellow dog. The yellow dog is chimes. Look at look at this guy. He looks like an anime protagonist
Yeah, chimes is they're both cheapy. Yeah, it's not the same dog. Yeah once they are
Chimes chimes, uh, wait, let me find the original way his legs are sitting. Yeah
He's he has an anime protagonist that
I mean, there's the there's the meme image which is the meme image is like
Very similar to the actual picture
But like the actual picture is like funnier
Yeah, yeah, the actual picture is like is really good
Versus um versus this this is like the meme which is like slightly distorted and like yellow. I guess it's pretty much
That's not yellow. It's just a squish down. That's natural. I love his face. Yeah, it looks like he's stinking. He's having a big think
He looks like he's a little annoyed about something. The funniest thing about it. I think is that he has no neck whatsoever
His snout starts and his body begins. Do you guys want to see one of my uh, I made like a his name his name is his name is Baltzy
I did one of those like, um, I did one of those like gene addicts. He has no ears. No ears whatsoever
No, vulture. Don't steal it. I've never seen Spiderman. He's like got the um the same
He's he's got the like the same energy as like a seal that's squished his neck
Like his head into his body
Like like receding a receding dog
He's just like herm big think
Having a big old think right now
Wait, wait, sorry, but uh, I just I like
Oh
Hell yeah, Ben saying when you call him the size of this
Stop right there
How dad
I want to I want to photoshop it with like glasses that make a purple so he matches Ben's like
Oh
James is funnier. I didn't I didn't realize it was a different dog even
Yeah
Oh to be fair, you can't have cheese without doughers. So I think you know, you got to respect your elders
Yeah, all the same family there. Okay. I was reading an article
I read an article about you know, original doge 8 say aka kabosu and the article said that there's like another
Shiba Inu who was also sometimes called doge
And it's just some american guy's dog that wore a bandana and like I'd never seen this other one
before
Yeah, so like top notch aesthetics
And like I feel like the the article was like, yeah, these both of these dogs became
Doge and I was like, who the fuck is that other one?
Like this is this this one did not stand the test of time
Uh, which one?
I'm looking. Sorry. I'm there's an article. I'm going meme hunting
I am going meme hunting. Um
this is
Doge was what the article was called
Yeah, okay. It was from the verge. It was called what the article was called. Wow, this is doge
and
Okay, I this one
Like what is this
Yeah, I've never seen this. This looks terrible. Never seen it before. Yeah, but the article like makes like yeah
Yeah, this this one is also doge. It looks like a
Boomer mistake
I used to hate this. I used to hate the doge meme. I don't know. I honestly, I think I still hate the much
Wow, so whatever. Yeah, that's that's dumb. But the comeback was was really good
It was never that funny. What do you mean the come on to gen two doge than gen one doge
Gen one just had way too many like like bugs. Okay. I mean the I mean like the the wow much amazing
Is like fine. I don't know like it's okay. It's yeah. Well, sure
What's what's second edition doge? Is it like doge's v-teams?
Is that is that the revival like you know back in 2019 when when
Doge just started being popular again. It was more all-encompassing
Hmm
This is one picture now. We're just posting memes. All right, here's the stuff
Here's a free here's a free cheat. Here's a free team emoji if anyone travels
Cool, I just I just love how he looks. He looks so adamant
Some someone's got to make team coin and then the cycle will will close. I would invest in a team coin
I would probably start doing bitcoin if someone made it today
I probably would because I feel like it would be destined to like be a serious doge coin competitor
Finally a coin for me
PCP heads, you know what to do
Yeah, PCP assemble
Do your thing
Oh boy. So sheaves. Sheaves are pretty cute. I like sheaves a lot
I I have been um
In my room all week because I got covid
Uh, I didn't buy the shirt. I actually got covid 19
Esquire
Uh, and I work. I don't know exactly how I got it. I work at at a middle school
So it could have been something to do with that. I'm not sure
But um, it's god damn children. Yeah
It was it wasn't too bad like my symptoms were were mostly mild
It just kind of never went away and I still can't really taste things
Uh
Since I've been in my room all week, I've pretty much done like nothing but play video games and uh, yeah
And one of the video games I've been playing was uh, I picked up
Uh, like fire emblem echoes after not playing it for like three fucking years and then I ended up beating it
After after so long and now I'm in a huge fire emblem hole. I'm playing all I'm playing games
Constant fire emblem. I wanted
I wanted to do a video
on on the
The sacred stones the one for the game boy advance
Because I really I really liked that game, but I was I felt I was feeling like
Oh almost like an imposter syndrome. God damn it fucking
Among us has ruined the word imposter, but I I felt I felt almost you were you were feeling suss
I was feeling a little suss. I was feeling a little suss when I was a little sick
feeling a little suss
When I was when I was working on it because I was just like
Like because because I was talking about things I like in the game
But but I was also feeling like almost inadequate in a way because I don't really know too much
Like I'm not as big in fire emblem as some people are
Because I've played I played like the sacred stones like years ago and then I played echoes. I've played three houses
And I'm making my way through some of the older ones now. I'm playing through genealogy
which is like the fourth one that never came out over here and um
I I just I just feel
I don't know it's it's it's the first time I ever really felt like I wanted to do like a video on something
But I've also felt like under qualified in a way
And it's
I feel that
Uh, what do you feel like you gotta play the whole series before you can talk about it or
I I I just feel like I should I I should know a little more about the games because
It's it kind of goes back to what I was saying earlier about the um
About how like, you know, as soon as you know something about a series
A lot of stuff on youtube starts to feel surface level and I don't want to feel surface level when making
A video about a game. I really like like the sacred stones
So
Yeah, I I felt like that when I was making my my heroes of my magic videos
Yeah, where I realized that oh wait
I'm just just playing these and trying to make a video quickly because like more videos equals good
And so I didn't really get into the game for long enough to have much to say about it and
Anyone who has played the game
Would be able to immediately see that I have just not really into it
And it was like it's so much easier to write scripts about games. I played for years
And so like playing new games and making reviews on those it's like
I don't know that you can't really do much more than at first impressions
Unless you really put the work in to try and completely understand every facet of it
Then you can make something interesting and different
it um
Uh
In well while I was in this hole. I found this uh fire emblem guy on youtube
He most he mostly just like streams iron man
Playthroughs of the game where like if a character dies you just keep going and those are fun
But he has like a couple of video essays. You mean a normal playthrough. Yeah
Yeah, but like uh, you know how like sometimes without resets. Yeah without resets. Yeah
Yeah, so you just so you just I don't know. I feel like in a game like a fire emblem is like
Like permadeath is like a major like thing about it. I feel like you would be I don't know
I would feel compelled to not do any resets if I fucked up and someone died
I would feel like that would be that's how I play these fucking games and it's on
I'm kind of I'm trying to find a way to to sort of shake shake my way out of it and just sort of move on
Wait, you you you do the reset. I do resets. Yeah, that's how I played. I mean no judgment
I just think it would be more fun. No, no, it's fine
Yeah, I think I'd be more fun if like the stakes would be higher. I'd be like a lot of judgments
A lot of judgment on my side. True
It's like um, you know nuzlocke sort of yeah
Stakes and that's like kind of the fun of the game is that is that you get you get like named characters with backstories and stuff
But they can legit die. It's cool. It's a cool mechanic
And if you like reset, you're not really
Yeah, you're turning you're turning losing that character into losing progress
Which is a it's still you know, it still sucks because like you can get through most of a chapter
But if one of your guys dies, I think fuck when I was young I I never like considered
Continuing if a character died. Yeah, because I was always gonna be I was always afraid that later on in the game
I would not have enough power to even
Like stand any chance of winning and if you get all the way to the end there are like usually you get so many guys
That I mean, yeah, but they I've never really
Like I always reset if a character dies and I always try to maximize the amount of experience I get from every level
Yeah, every every um mission or whatever. That's pretty much how I play it. That's kind of why that's kind of why I like
I know it's like kind of a controversial
Edition, but I like that the uh, the newer games have that sort of rewind time feature
Oh, yeah, I guess it just saves time
But it also like
removes
Because like losing time having to do things again is a punishment that you don't want to happen
So it does raise the stakes and make you think more about what you're doing. Yeah, it's 100. That's definitely true
Yeah, sure, but this was uh, this is like the video that kind of got me
That that I thought was really good and and started making me think like oh geez
Should I be making this fireman video? This guy knows like way more stuff about these games than I do
So I just kind of been watching him
The video you've been wanting to make already
No, he hasn't
There's not really there's not the thing is with
I want to do a video on sacred stones because there's not really like a
A video that kind of just like really goes into that game in particular
I think it's kind of underrated
I'm good. Um, you can still make your video and then just admit that like oh, I got a lot of my
Information from this guy check him out. He's really cool. Sure. Sure. Yeah, I probably appreciate the shout out too
I uh, I'm not like a funny gimmick. You could be like, uh, how can you beat fire emblem sacred stones without pressing up?
something like that
Let's find out gamers
You get like 75% of the way through the game. It's like, oh you come
That's not satisfying
There's actually two areas where you just need to press up and that's it. So I flip the controller upside down and we're good
Hack
cheats tectonic cheats
Take that. I do donkey kong
Tropical freeze without using a single button just shaking the Wii remote
Can can I play minecraft at high volume without waking up my mother? Let's find out
No, no, I can't
Wait, mom. No. No. It's a stream. It's a stream mom
Oh god
Um, damn, I have a can I get through the day without mentally breaking down?
ha ha
Yes
Because I'm built different
Um, I built like a truck. Yeah, I have a happy truck. I have the opposite of depression
I don't know what that is, but I'm pretty sure I have the opposite of it
It's pretty epic. Uh
Oh pressure
Yeah, oh pressure because I'm brown. Yes. Oh, yeah, I like
Ethan Ethan Klein just tweeted uh to hold to hold the game stop line
Uh pretty well now that he said it
I was I was gonna sell but
I mean
Honestly, I I've been I've been having a lot of fun
Just going on r slash wall street bets and seeing all the top posts that are just like
I just poured in like $200,000 into game so hold the line and other people like I have literally a million dollars in game
Stop. I'm not selling no matter what everybody holds
Uh, it's awesome
Hold the line Bart
Part of me part of me
Part of me wishes I just put my entire fortune my fortune lull into uh like my whole my like all my money into game
Stop, but no not again not after not after bitcoin
Not not if if if the stock you have in game stop becomes huge
um
Then maybe you could consider but like hold the line. Well, but then it'll be too late line for
Yeah, I don't know that's that's the big question. Do you want to get a nice fat page?
I want to get a do I want to get a lot of money or a little over the billionaires a little bit
I do what the fucking billion is
I mean if if the stock blows up, I will make a decent chunk of money
I might I mean if it goes really high, I might make like a few thousand dollars, which would be pretty cool
um, but uh, I don't know that's seemed that's like the most optimistic
scenario
I'll I'll be happy if I don't lose anything, you know
That would be every day
I honestly the thing I'm worried about is like
Melvin liquidates they sell they they they buy back their shares
The market like goes up and but I like I miss it and then like it like crashes back down immediately after and I'm like, oh
It's too late
melvin brother of the joker
uh
Hey, I think so i'm working let's check in on dogecoin dogecoin is
It's bouncing back a little bit
Check in on cheap cheap coin while you're out there cheap coin cheap coin
Check it
So so i'm working on a little analysis video. Well, it's it's like a how-to video on a
On a on a very specific stream. Um, do you guys ever watch any of the adult swim live streams?
Back when they would do them. Are those the ones where they pitch cartoon ideas?
Oh, yes. Okay. Yeah, that's one specifically i'm talking about. Okay. There's a stream called development meeting
And it's legit hosted by the
The head directors of development at adult swim like they're the hosts these these guys aren't like actors
They're actually the development heads. Yeah, and every thursday you could call in
And a picture idea for a cartoon, right? And i've been watching them for like
They've been doing it for two years and they but they like stop back in december because
all the live streams got like um got cancelled because
You know covet they can't afford to do them anymore. I guess change of ceo blah blah blah
That'd be that being said i've been watching enough of them that i now understand the meta game that how to get a show
Picked up. Oh, and i was gonna make yeah, i i was gonna make a video talking about how to do it
I was originally gonna do it after i tried to pitch villain verse to them as a show
But then he got but then you know stream got cancelled and i couldn't do it on time
So i fucking uh, so i guess now why not now and i mean also i need more cloud anyway
Might get me enough cloud you could be like that guy that told everyone to do community posts on youtube and that drives engagement up
But for like adult swim
Yeah, um my video was gonna be the video was gonna be called something like um how to get your own adult swim show
Oh, perfect, and i i'm already clicking on it was good
Yeah, yeah, the video i only written down like
One fifth of it. I'm not gonna lie. It's been a while since i've seen any of the older streams
Of it, so i'm gonna probably watch a couple of those while i work on villain versus this next week
um
But yeah
Fuck i'm excited for that
You know that um, you know that pan pizza went on to pitch a show while uh gendi tartikoski was on too as guests
Yes, i heard of this and i heard it was bad
It was it was bad. I was actually i was i actually gave him some like pointers and advice beforehand
Um, i feel kind of bad. I could have given like better like advice, but um
He did he did fumble and it was very it was hilarious not gonna lie pretty on brand he honor
Yeah, it is pretty is very on brand like he on ironic
There was a part where like
Like the thing is that he just was too busy talking about the lore of his world instead of like talking about the actual show
Like like when you go on you have to like specifically they're looking for
They're looking for comedy they're looking for comedy shows
They want comedy shows and they really want you to talk about like the characters and dynamics, right?
If you could go on and describe the dynamic of your characters
Um to to to tell somebody the good dynamic is when like you tell the host
The dynamic and the host could already like figure out like stories with that dynamic. Yeah, right?
That's when you know, you have a good show. Unfortunately. No one gives a fuck about your lore. It's
Yeah, yeah, they gotta make them care surface love
Yeah, I there's there was a whole point that like pan pizza was bringing up with his
With his pitch where it's like, oh, you know in my world, uh, like they banged cartoon and they could have like half human
half cartoon children and
But here's the thing if you actually read his the comic like that literally has nothing to do with the plot
And how okay, which how
How does uh pan pizza's cartoon pitch compared to a mysterious mr. Enter's cartoon pitch
Which one which one's more based?
Here's here's the thing. Uh, this look. I love pan pizza. He's a friend of mine
Um, that that being said I could see I could miss fruit
Through full force of will I could probably see mr. Mr. Enter getting at least some
Not not getting an actual show on a network, but actually getting like a pilot
done
Like maybe before pan because like at least mr. With mr. Enter
It's kind of like he's just like at this point. He admits it's a terrible idea, but he's still gonna do it
Yeah, like he he admitted that like, oh, yeah, this is gonna make no money at all. I'm still gonna do this pilot
What a fucking idiot. It's like god. No, that's
Idiot
It's this weird kind of like
Throw your fucking baby right out with that bath water and get a new baby and new bath water
I don't know like when like there's something interesting about like when someone has an incredibly
Bad story or something but still wants to go through with it. Like oh my god
Like this this probably means something more to them than people realize
No, I don't want to know which one is going to get made. I want to know which one was better
Oh, well, like I mean it's different because mr. Enter didn't go on like the development meaning to pitch it
Um, we have a lot to go on with pans. Anyway, no different versions of the same story
Uh, yeah, pan just keeps soft rebooting it. But the the general gist is that um
Uh, I think pans has a stronger
Premise it the thing is that I think the premise is very good with pans thing
The problem is that like the characters don't have a strong dynamic because it's like
Oh, there's like a little like pan described this character that had a bunch of assholes
But if you read the comic, it's like they're not really assholes. They're just kind of like regular people
Maybe if like one maybe if one was a piece of shit and one was a straight man
It'd be a lot better of a dynamic, but it's not they're very like I don't know. They're very normal
Um
Well, I'll gonna I'll say this right now. I'm definitely not going to go and read pan pizzas cartoon pitch treatment
I don't know
It's on a it's on a stream you could um
You could watch actually I'll link it right now
I can't like I can barely watch that like that toy story. Let's play
I can't watch like him like bombing live in front of industry veterans
Oh, wait, wait, wait, you get to see him like do a pitch live
Yeah, it's like a live stream. They did not hear me. Okay. That's a little interesting
Adult swim hosts like a live stream where they just get on like random. Okay, cool. I here's a link with it timestamp
Um, it this is when pan pizza jumps in and he starts pitching it and it's like, oh my god, this guy fumbles oof
And um, it's so funny because like at the end after he gets off
Uh, gendi tarakoski is on the stream to as guest hosts also mike laszlo
former c
It's lasso from camp lasso
Mike lasso, I mean
Mike lasso and who's the former CEO right former
CEO adult swim. Yeah, and um, and the thing is after pan pizza leaves, um, again
He said something very interesting about his pitch like he says like
um, the problem with like pan pizza's pitch was that
Um, it's like it's like if you're trying to sell someone on finding on finding Nemo and you tell them it's about the ocean
I see, you know what that in a way, maybe it's good. He bond because that's really that's
Uh, that's pretty profound
Yeah, that's uh, that's I know exactly what that means
Yes, I have lots of insight. Hmm quite
I get it. I get it though
So you're so as you're saying that pan was like focused on like the setting and the premise but not on like the story of it
Right. Yeah, like he like I've talked to pans. I've been in like I I actually been helping him a lot with uh
this
With the comic as much as like as much as I can to the point where like if I do more than what I do
He's gonna have to start like paying me or put me on as a co-writer or or that would be just terrible
Put more critiques and capitalism in and then maybe I'll keep doing it for free
Yeah, exactly. Um, no, but um, no actually
I wonder if you can pay me in price. I already told other people actually
I actually asked pan like look
I could probably help you like really rough out the story a lot more if you put me on as co-writer or something
Because like at this point it's like too the stuff I'm doing the stuff I would suggest
Would just be too much that it's like to put in this much effort. I would need something in return
Right and I and I asked him about that and he's and he's not like, I don't know
It wasn't down, but whatever
Yeah, I already got my own comics
um
So wait, can I I can I just say can I say that pan pizza is not a good artist?
damn
I like his art. I don't
I I don't even know what it is. Pan pizzas are pan pizzas artists like yours, but worse cheesy like yours, but like way worse
I don't know if I agree
Is art kind of reminds me of uh wonder waffle and I like wonder waffles like uh, it's worse than that too
Oh, no, no, and I'm talking shit about my boy wonder waffle. I mean, I don't I mean, I'm pretty neutral on wonder waffle
Hold up. I'll show you some of wonder this development meeting thing. Yeah, is this something anyone can do?
Um, not anymore because the stream is over, but yeah, anyone could do anyone could jump on and pitch their idea
Are they starting it up again?
Uh, hopefully
But there has been no word about it. They do in the last episode they mentioned that they would be so down to come back
But at this point, I don't think they can afford to do the live streams
Uh, wait a second. Here's here's wonder waffles art
Uh, and I think it's really good
Yeah, that's pretty good
I don't I don't I feel like
I feel like pan pizzas art
Is probably like if he wants to do comics, he's gonna have to like rearrange the art a little bit better
But um, you mean he looks like he's drawing
For animation, but he's not
And it's it's bad. I think he majored in uh, I think he majored in
Graphic designing or something. These are made these look like they're made to be flash puppets, but they're not
I I google pan pizza and it is images of pizza
A rebel rebel taxi pan pizza
Because the channel is called the rebel tag. Look at this. I'm looking at the stream. I'm looking at the
I'm looking at the pitch document images. I'm sorry. These are garbage
These are garbage. They're trash. I think my biggest issue with pans art isn't the quality of the art itself
It's that it's the thing cheesy said is that like it's kind of hard to tell what's happening with his characters
I I can't I can't get over the quality of the art. That's honestly, that's it. That's that's all that's all I need to see
I'm not even gonna think about it any further
I'm mad. I'm actually mad
You know, you know me like I like the majority of artists. I don't think there's any artists. I this means you have no standards
Wow, okay. That's like that's like you're like the jake. You're like the jake english with movies
Wow, okay
Fuck you
Who's jake english? He's the guy. He's the homestuck guy from he's from x6. I don't know. He's the he's he's he's all
He's all he fuck you die. He's all grandpa. He's all timeline grandpa. Did you watch homestuck?
I watched I was one day in like high school. I was like, you know what I hear I hear a lot talk about homestuck
I think I'm gonna get into homestuck and I went on my tablet and I went to homestuck.com and I couldn't get past the first panel
I literally got stuck
Shut the fuck up. Oh, it's not very good. Yeah, that's because it's not very good
That was like that was a complete
Yeah, of course, of course, that's bad idiot
That was so like, you know blonde beard guy. Yes, like homestuck already's bad. Yes
Wait, what do you know?
We know wait, this is wonder waffle by the way
Oh, why do you keep showing me? I don't care. I don't care about wonder waffle
Uh wonder waffle is great my wonder wonderful. He's awesome. Why do you even what honestly? Why why is why are we even talking about wonder waffle?
Who gives a shit?
Oh
Also, I thought I thought wonder waffle was a girl. Well, yeah, that's that happens a lot mostly because his avatar is his little robot girl
Yeah, uh, oh well
Oh, well
So anyway, I'm working on it. I'm working on analysis video talking about how to win at
Making a pitch like what's like the killer things you need to do to to get
How to game
I don't know but here's the thing here's that's going to be like the end joke like at the end
It's going to be like, oh you ready to do your pitch now. Well too bad. It's canceled. You can't do it. It's too late
Owned
Classic cheesy tricking people
Tricking people to watching my content and then at the very end I'd be like
It's canceled now villain versus never going to be a show
And that's how I sneak in the little the little ad
Sneak it in. Yeah, you know a little
Never happen all because wink
Wake villain first. What's that?
Oh
I don't think you need to sneak it in. I think it's better if you just say also read my comic you fuck
You just say that
Okay, I'll do that
If you sneak it in it seems like you got something to hide
So I'm a sneaky guy. I'm a I'm a
I might you might call me a villain if you will. I'm a sneaky little villain. I sink in my ad
You might be calling a villain a verse
I'm a verse to
Here's my verse on villainy if you will an unverse they call you might call me a stinky little piece of shit
You know a villain
Oh god
I was looking at my comic lord of ghosts and I was like, oh, this is pretty good. How many um chapters are there a lot of ghosts?
Uh
The chapters
Let me five I think give and take dot site
Click that in click that in right now everybody. All right. I'll do play along. All right. Uh, given given date
Given date dot site
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah wrong
Um
Given take trans is the first thing on uh google six seven seven chapters and 94 pages so far
Tell me on the lord of ghosts. Why should I read it?
Um, the lord of ghosts is about a ghostly person who is uh
He's so fucking quirky though
um
He right there's a world that's uh
There's slime and there's no no you're talking about the ocean. You're talking about the ocean. Don't talk about the ocean
Um, don't uh, can you go for an episode of the lord of ghosts?
Can I go for an episode? Yes
I don't know what that means never never mind. It's a bit. Okay
Yeah, last you're logic. You're sorry. That's it. You're five minutes are over
Doesn't make grammatical sense what that's you are the weakest
Give when you pitch when you pitch when you pitch you gotta gotta go in with the log line
You gotta give the log line. You gotta talk about the dynamic. I know that if you said give me the log line
I would have known what okay. Give me the talking about
Oh lord of ghosts is a ghost trying to remember his past and and uh, he's uh swept up in lots of
Little adventures and he's he just wants people to be dead. He just wants people to be dead and that's so much to us
That's good. That's good. Okay. He what is there like a
No, he wants everyone to be dead like him. That's good. What what's the stakes?
What's the stakes in the lord of ghosts?
Um through the heart he's gonna he's gotta
He's gotta is a little ghost gotta find his way home little ghost gotta find his way home
You're in okay, so a little ghost gotta find his way home and also make sure everyone's dead
Yeah
Yeah, the most the most we could give you is 10 seasons. You think that's gonna be enough to tell the story
Uh, I'll have to no deal have to cut out. I have to cut out some of the uh, some filler have to cut out some of my
My my bonus content, but
Ten seasons lord of ghosts lord of ghosts is a one season long anime squeezed into 10 seasons
Just like the hobbit movies
Yeah
Was it the battle of the 500 000 armies?
I can't I want to do a lot of armies fighting each other
Like five armies. That's kind of like a lot of
How do you even fit that many armies in one battle?
Oh, because they're all hobbits. That's why because they're small enough. Oh, they're all hobbits. I thought they could have five armies
Makes sense. Yeah, five armies is is fine. But you know, if the if they're made of small people that makes them
One hobbit one human is like three hobbits, right? So you can have like five armies. Yeah. Yeah
Anyway, go read lord of ghosts on gibbon take dot site. Yeah, I agree. There's my pitch
I I I want to get back to to finishing it because it sort of ends right now on a cliffhanger
There was supposed to be something that happens afterwards, but it's changed in my mind since then I need to rewrite it
Just recently I dropped
it's been
A year and I and I dropped another
comic on bongo and luna on webtoons
But this comic was talking about how like hey, I'll bring back bongo and luna if my patreon reaches the 200 dollars
And um, it has not but it did reach to 100 finally
That's pretty good. Yeah. Yeah, uh, but apart bongo and luna should become
Like a political platform. They should talk exclusively about how capitalism is fucking stupid. I just I just might
Yeah, yeah, they should they should be one of those
cartoonist
Like bread panels. Yeah, bread. Yeah bread
Bread a bread tuner. Yeah, bongo luna is already bad. So I just got to add the politics and it won't change. It won't change
It won't change at all
Should be like
Luna stop squeezing my tits instead. We got to squeeze these greedy capitalists out of all their money
You gotta squeeze we gotta squeeze the short on game stop luna
Uh
Luna stop looking at my ass instead. We gotta look at the crimes that the
And start and start looking at these green candles on the wall street exchange
dude
Something really funny about like the exact same way of like hey
Stop looking at my ass stop looking at my tits like every single comic exactly starts the same way
Like entirely sexual. It's like instead of that. How about this political idea like cutting all of the like the nuance and the
Subtiffusion, you know the sleight of hand out of it. It's just like power one sex panel two politics
Luna stop jerking off. We got to get rid of these jerks off of wall street
Yeah, I ironically do that. That would be really
Luna stop looking at my ass remember how bill clinton bombed that that pharmaceuticals plant in syria
Whatever reminds me of there is a comic like like that
I think where it's like this one girl
Like the first panel would be like a guy is being like like hey, hey, baby
You want to suck my dick and then the girl like kills them and that's like every comic
It's just like she does she like violently murder. Yeah. Yeah. It's so funny. I think I've seen that
I think my my favorite one is like where she's like in the first panel
She's hanging out with like a guy friend and this guy called a race car johnny
Like in the in the first panel and then and then she's all like all right
That was a that was a great dinner guys
I'll see you guys later and then race and then the the male character like shakes race cars johnny's hand
And then hugs the girl and then the girl says hey, wait a second
Did you did you shake his hand because he's a guy and hugged me because i'm a girl and the guys and the male
The male friend's like uh, uh and in the third panel she like punches him
But then race car race car johnny's like right there too and all race car johnny says is room room
room room
Do you guys think it's time?
I love you guys think it's time to go to voicemails speaking of messages
Or is it?
Well, I guess you're right
I think it's time to go to voicemail. Yeah tectonic. I think you're right us us hoes should go to the voicemails now
All right, sirs. I have prepared I have prepared the voicemails for your pleasure
Thank you. Thank you
Thank you. How's the pleasure rule about this? Okay, so
All right first
Okay, disavow so
first voicemail is called uh
to to me j
Toom toom j y
The best channel on youtube
three two one
Go i'm here to shout out the absolute number one best youtube channel
on the entire website
um
That is david razi
Uh, he he has about 24 000 subscribers. So of course he should have more
um, so what he does
is say a
long-running narrative
animatic
Which isn't an animation. It's like a a comic or a storyboard, but uh, narrated
You know
What he does the story
Is about him the creator
In college in art school not having any fucking idea what he's doing with his life
Or why he is there and it's about you know
Motivating yourself in like a post jesus society
You know what the fuck uh finding your purpose or whatever
Uh, it's great is full of pathos pathos
It's a long-running narrative
um
so, you know
You can start with the first episode or there's one about uh working at walmart. It's great
And it can be a good place to like you know meet the character get familiar with the feel
Which is uh number 19 called where you're going uh watch it
I think i've seen this before
So he just somewhere he just this is a really kind of cool channel idea. He just shows on the youtube channel
No, wait, so this is um
Is it like
inspirational content?
If he is he could be doing way better. Is it like inspirational stuff? Is it like just bio comics basically?
Yeah, autobi. He's the original story time animator says his twitter profile. So yeah, it's it's like the story time
YouTube videos, but it seems like it seems like obviously this guy was doing it for fucking longest years ago
2013 I think
This is pretty cool honestly that voicemail. However
Needed more lo-fi hip-hop and editing
His last technical day of episode was three weeks ago, huh?
I don't know. I hate autobiocomics on principle. So I think yeah
Yeah
Isn't isn't one of your comics? Yeah, I never made another one
Um, is it like vapors kind of autobi?
No
This is veneer. That's right. That's what yes
Is at least at least have the day had the decency to pretend that you're not just writing about yourself. That's what that's all
It's totally not actually
All fiction isn't always like always just about the author. Yeah, first of all, Vincent is white. Okay, so there
That should be the dead giveaway. That's it's literally not me
um
Okay, okay, so
Next one is called is another is tommy j. What the fuck is an LLC?
three two one
go
Does anybody know like
Where corporations even came from like where we got this idea that an organization
became like a person
Like a legal person
How does nobody like they must have done this on purpose, right?
Like I don't see how you couldn't foresee this as soon as you made something like this
The people who made it who made the fucking the corporation
They're literally called limited liability companies or some shit like it's like
Created specifically the entire concept is just that whenever anything goes wrong
Whenever your pollution like kills a bunch of children or something you just disappear
You just resign you jump ship
and pass all the bullshit on
to your
Your your the shareholders who don't see a company coming. We're probably like
LLCs are probably massive investors from the middle class and
You pass it on to your employees and you pass it on to your customers and let them deal with the bullshit, you know
How yeah for real how or just you know
The shit you cause just never gets resolved and the victims just just just sit there
Be poisoned or whatever
I give welcome back. Why how?
It's it's cancer kill it kill corporations
That was that was a great voicemail. Uh, next one up is uh, Tommy jay. What the fuck?
What the fuck is an what the fuck is an LLC part two?
Jesus Christ
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Not this one. Not this one. Uh, it is
Yeah, what the fuck is an LLC part two? Uh, three two one go
Honestly, the worst part maybe I don't know. There's lots of bad
A bad part is it I hope you guys are ready?
I hope you guys are ready for what the fuck is an LLC part three after this and none of the ways that are like
A detriment to being a person like if an american person
Went over to china and just like kidnapped a person a chinese person
And just forced them to put together plastic crap for them until they wanted to kill themselves and jumped out a window
And landed in a suicide nest net then like when that person got back to the u.s
They'd be extradited to china and then face consequences for that shit that they did
But a corporation just gets to use magical bullshit
You know what? I like legally nonsense to avoid those those repercussions
You know, it's it's bad. It's honestly. This is very basic shit with power
Maybe if comes responsibility with right comes the responsibility for the shit that you do
I'm going to kill you. Um, how how the thing is that it's in the name. It's a limited life
So the liability is limited so they can't get in trouble. Here we go
Limited my ability makes you think
Make really really does really does make thank you the voicemail. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, but look at this
Look at look at this image and tell me that this is okay
This is fine. Dude. It's wait. Yes. Yes. That's like that was in the pitch. That was in the pitch
Oh, I don't like that. I don't like it either very hound. What is this is a picture? This is a picture reference
Why do white girls always want to fuck dogs? Oh my god, it is
Oh wait, you're a white girl and I know it's hard, but you gotta stop banging dogs
You guys know that song? Hold up. You can rely on the white man's come. You can oh, that was a song created
That was a song created by like, uh, my my friend a yellow swag. He made he made this song about white girls. Hold up
I only oh mr. Yellow
I love this guy. I interviewed him on a couple cheesy counts ago. Oh, oh, I know this guy. Yeah on twitter
Yeah, he's cool. Love him
um
Hey, tell whoever that is in the background a shout out
It's a dog. Um
Oh, okay. Next one is uh, tommy j. What the fuck is an llc part three? Oh my god. I'm gonna talk over this
Three two the thrilling conclusions three two one go
Okay, so while this goes i'm just going to find more, uh screenshots of terrible pan pizza art
Uh to prove my point and if a if a corporation is a person
I did
The income tax rate that like a person actually gonna you know, he has a podcast called a special tax rate that
I think it's lower, right? I'm can't I can't hear you over tommy. It's awesome. I have to declare war
I'm interested in what he has to say to us or whatever
deductible what if tommy j is actually saying very
Profound things about the concept. He might be a real person, but his presentation is very dull for me
That i'm not interested. I'm sorry tommy j. It's all it's all wrong. Nothing against you. I think it might I probably agree with you
Everything I'm always gonna tell you this right now. I probably agree with everything you have to say
except indie games
And like dudes on pay but patreon is bullshit. So even the dudes on on patreon are
Like knee deep in the bullshit. They're not making the bullshit, but they're in it. Does pan have a
They're on a foundation
Probably be able to put something together with like a fucking public bitcoin
I don't know what i'm fucking talking about. I just know it's all bullshit. It's all okay. I found the trouble
It's all a lie
It's been talked on this podcast of like investing
in
These in these these mutual funds. Okay, look at this
Um
Look at this. I don't know
The money's not real. So who cares it looks like a smear frame drawings aren't real
That looks like a like a murdoch from gorillas smear frame. This is like this is like
I don't know this I can see he's going for like a for like a fairly odd parents like very graphic designy look
But like it's just shit. I don't know like he just failed at it
I did
How is it that butch Hartman's art has like regressed
Over the years because like dany phantom and fairly odd parents the guy who does
But then you see him draw the characters now the thing is that he didn't even really design those cartoons
It was uh, steven silver. I know he wasn't really big on dany phantom
Like a big part of it
So that was me. I'm really pitchy pitch dany phantom. I assume he drew the original cosmon wand
Yeah, he um, he pitched dany phantom and fairly odd parents
um
I just remember reading that that uh, someone else whose name I obviously don't remember. So that's that's the guy who is
That's the guy's style and he's he's also the guy behind other kim possible
Oh, that's shit. That makes sense. Yeah, he sounds like a cool dude. Um, I like butch Hartman
Is more of a rude dude
It's could be worse could be junkay. Okay
Uh, dude instead of that look at look at one of my favorite pages from the lord of ghosts
Wait, oh, this is a cool page. I like this
I don't even wait. I don't even remember this one to slime city. It's very near the end. Yeah, haunt haunt dude. I love this
Oh, this is so fucking cool. I got it. The lord of ghosts is so good
Makes me happy
Yeah, but I think um
I think it's just a draw more comics and I'm not talking necessarily like
Loki rl like you need to better
understanding of like
Images within panels you get me. I guess cinematography panel
Are you still looking I mean are you still looking man? Yeah. Yeah, I'm still I'm just going through his tumblr and like
some of these are okay
I would say his art range is from okay to bad
I
I want to say I want to say that I
I like yeah, I think it's fine. It's just that it might not be the best
For a comic or to do a comic consistently. It does take him like a couple of months to do at least one
issue
Then again, I think that's a majority of people
I I think that his art
would look better
in like an
It's like he's drawing for animation, but he's not so it just looks like shit
That's that's what I think doesn't work about it. I'm trying to remember. I don't well. No, there's more to it than that
I just think he has like a shit like um
sensibility of like what looks cool
Uh in in addition to his like misguided
It's just misguided uh, uh, uh, you know technique in general
Individual lines look pretty good, but the the whole okay doesn't really work. What is this?
Like what what is this on the right?
That's uh that one chick from myzakin
Yes, I know but it's it's garbage
an idiot
Yes, it's like uh, you know, I think I think
I can tell that he's going for he's just sort of failed on on like capturing the
like
It just sort of feels like she she's melting
Like it's it's going for like why I know it's I know it's going for a squash and stretch
It's going for a squash and stretch, but it doesn't look good. There's like uh, it's not just design is a word
There's like a full style. There's like a philosophy thing, but he's going like half measure. It's not like it's
Stylistic enough to feel like it's deliberate. It feels like he just fucked up
It is feel like it's half it's half measured. Okay. What really pisses
Okay, the line of action like look at the arms like the the the arm behind the body
The arm behind the body
Like it's like curving in in like the same direction. I just noticed. Yeah, like the way the arms are positioned is very strange
Like I can tell he did he drew it as like a it's got like this
It's like an over adherence to like the line of action like if you look at the silhouette
It just looks like it's like a blob that sort of curves from the left to the right
And like the arm follows that line, but it doesn't actually look right
It it's it's like he's trying to okay. Wait hold up. You guys ever seen this. This is like uh
Yeah, this for the cartoon one over yonder and it's kind of like lava theory
It sounds like a spongebob video
It's like how kind of like certain shapes of characters like
Fill into each other when they're standing next to each other and I feel like pan is trying to do something
Similar, but a lot a lot of times it feels like a lot of the lines
Contradict each other almost. Oh, you got me. I got I found another one
God, I found another one
I like the machete drawing. I think that one's pretty. Yeah, the machete one's okay. And the the bionicle is okay
Oh, that one this one's old this this comic is like this is like the probably look at that hand second or third incarnation
Okay, I mean this is from this is 11 months ago. He posted this 11 months ago
I think this is a repost maybe okay, maybe whatever. Well, it looks terrible
All right, if it's if it's not representative of his style then fine, but I think it is
It's it's whatever, you know, okay, you know what?
Um, how about how about we all cool our heads as we listen to tommy j. What the fuck is anything?
Um, oh my god three. This one better be short. Nope
It's it's really long. It's really long three two one go. I thought I was like
Hey, stop this. Um, you mean, you know, we don't have to listen to these, right?
Like I've been I've been waiting for you guys to be like fuck this guy. Let's not listen any more of these
You're the one. You're not that's why I'm talking
That's why I'm talking about
I'm talking about pan pizza. We're talking about pan pizza over these
Uh, I'm willing to go tyrannical as hosts this podcast no more Tommy. I'm willing to put this guy in voice jail
Honestly, this is making me this is making me actually mad like this is discussed. Um, he's too good
He's Tommy j just just too good for him. Just put all your wishmills together and make a fucking video like a no
Yeah, no, okay. We're skipping all of these. Fuck you. Tommy j
Uh, next one. Okay, the how many more the real next one is cringis bingus three
Yay. Oh, I'm into this
Wait, wait, wait, let me count. Let me count. Let me count how many we're skipping. We're skipping. Um
What the fuck is anything? What the fuck is defamation? What the fuck is prohibition?
What the fuck is an and cap? Why is london calling so good? What the fuck is a union?
Oh god, I can't stop making these. What the fuck is talking to people? What the fuck is hate?
What the fuck is sex and what the fuck is a monkey is a monkey and I think there's more
Ladies and gentlemen, my name is total biscuit and welcome to wtf is
Do you think um, um, some advice is sick. Tell me j
You might want to like, I don't know you can tell your friends about these before you make these into voicemails. I don't know
We are his friends. Oh god. Oh, that's right. That's right. That's right. I forgot. Okay. Yeah, I'm not
Okay, cringis cringis bingus three three two one go
Hey guys, it's cringis bingus. Yay. First of all, I want to say thank you to ben for saying that I
Was empathetic the other week in the first voicemail. I said because I cringed at him losing bitcoin
I would like to think I'm an empathetic person. Anyway today
What this week what I cringed that
Is the fact that I have to go get a covid test because my mom got covid
She's gonna be okay. She's recovering
But she was very sick and now I have to go get a test
See if I'm sick because I live with her. So that's gonna be fun. I have to get the long thing up my nose
I'm not excited about it. Oh
Um, but I'll be okay. I'll survive
Um, what I bing would you bing? What do you bing this week was um
I binged uh, I binged some episodes of avatar the last year, but I'm not familiar with this one
I listened to the podcast at work and they shut up. I'm trying to listen to cringis bingus
Uh, but some of those early episodes are kind of are kind of silly cartoony
But it's a good show still I think I like it
Uh, cringis bingus signing off. Goodbye. I'll see you next week
Cringis
Wait, wait, wait, wait, cringis cringis if you're listening to this right now
I want your opinion on the pan peaks of art style
Yes, absolutely. Please. Cringis bing
Cringis call next time and tell us your opinion on pan peaks of art style. I'm really interested
What show did he say he binged?
I'm sorry, Ben. I wasn't listening. Fuck all of you. I'm going back. I'm listening again
All right, we'll wait on you. Thank you to do that when I bing
It was the early episodes of avatar. Oh my god, shut up. I'm trying to fucking listen die
It was avatar the last airbender lol fucking christ
He is right though. The early episodes are kind of I wouldn't say they're cring, but they are but
But they're they're definitely rough
Uh, or just like they're definitely he's right. Um, like average kids show
I'm sorry for my internet keeps clicking out. That's pretty cringy. Wait, uh, what's I mean?
What's wrong with the early avatar episodes? I haven't watched it. There's nothing specifically wrong with with them
But they're not indicative of the quality. They are, um, unassuming. I think yeah, but I don't know whether that's a like
Like ultimately makes them good because they're unassuming and you you get a it's like, oh, it's just a fun adventure
And then it grows and grows. Maybe that is an aspect of it that works
There some of the episodes though are just like are just bad like, uh
Like bato of the water tribe that one is is just like not a good episode and like everyone gets in the great divide
uh, bato of the water tribe is the one where
um, ang finds out that uh, that
uh, uh, katara and sakka's dad is going to be, uh, nearby
And uh, he withholds the information because he's jealous
And uh, hijinks ensue
Ang is jealous that they have a dad
That that he won't be paying attention
Yeah, um
I think there were a couple of different writers in the early seasons. I
I'll of but uh, erine has took
One one that I remember
Finding annoying for some reason was jet and I don't know why because I thought jet was cool initially
Jet is like the the
I don't I like that episode because jet is a character jet is like the the typical like based but actually cringe character
He's so he's so typical. Oh, yeah, I remember this guy
Because he's he's based because you know, he has like a stick in his mouth and he wants he wants to free
Like he's he's cool. Katara gets a lady bono for him. Yeah, it turns out he uh
Is cringe kind of cring at he's kind of cring. He's kind of cring anyone and he just kind of wants to kill people
Uh, he is a good. Oh, that's that's pretty base. I don't know what you guys it's a
You know, it comes and goes
Um, he has a good art scene. I've never seen avatar the last ever. He's only in one episode, right?
He's in he comes back
Uh, uh, very very briefly for like a a uh, like a couple episodes point into the earth's kingdom
Like I remember he uh, he's trying to be oh, yeah, he gets some he gets taken in by the uh, the uh
The diely who like brainwash him and then he comes back and it's like a bit of a whoa
And he you've totally changed literally
He tries to be based and he just he can't help it. He's just constantly cringe
I okay, okay next voicemail next voicemail. It's called it's called enough of this avatar horseshit. Thank you for the voicemail
Uh, thanks for the voicemail. Uh, next one is called direct to democracy
three two one go
Ghost beneath the saints is the people's revolution
Put that one nerd on the show the one who called much voicemail. I can't want to be on the show
Put him on the show
The fuck you doing with the show?
Wait, was that tommy j was tommy j the one that sent his his resume
I can't remember
Wait, let me let me confirm. Let me confirm. Uh
Why is this tommy j? Is that why he dropped like 30 minutes of voicemail?
He dropped 30 minutes of voicemail to just get it. Yes. It was him. It is the same guy
Oh
Crane crane crane crane
That is pretty cringey. This is cringle, dude
Yeah, it's not us. It's not a situation of throwing stuff at the wall until it sticks
We go through all the voicemails. So if you put or or we don't spam it, we're not gonna pay attention
Or we don't in situations like this
Uh, yeah, specifically because the spam
Don't ever put me in a situation
Uh, all right. What is that one is called?
I don't know. I just forget about it
I saw a funny I saw a funny picture of a frog with a gun that said don't ever put me in a situation
And I just realized it
um
Thanks what it's called. Hey, that's just a theory a pcp theory. Uh, there it is
three two one go
Hey, so everyone here in the pcp theory crabney community has been talking and we're pretty sure we know what's in the kawasaki scrolls
Ben, can you confirm whether or not the scrolls contain the secret samurai circumcision technique?
Like you just take out your katana
Do one big slash walk past the guy and she their sword and their foreskin just pops off
Are we all right, Ben?
I I don't speak japanese. So I don't know I can't read them. I can't even read them. I don't know
This but I have pictures ben. I'm not sure if like this means I can't read pictures very late
To the whole circumcision like arc is funny or not. I'm I'm the jury's out for me
You know, it's it's been long enough. It's been long enough. I'm no longer mad about it
Yeah, it's been long enough. It's been long enough that I'm not mad about it. So
I can stomach it better. That's my opinion
It's an nostalgia
It's it's yeah, it's just all the good old days of like a month ago
Uh, okay, the next one is called hi ben three two one go
Kringus bingus is not only the hero of the downtrodden that we so desperately need in these trying times
Kringus bingus is a holy warrior
All three sides of the holy trinity
And he needs to be respected as such. I absolutely agree. Can you do that in the pretty voice the father the son and the kringus?
Next next voicemail is called hi ben two three two one go
I think it's an impression
Pretty good impression though
What the fuck were they saying?
That's how you know
I don't know. I don't know
Uh, but all I know is okay. Next one is another tommy j. Uh, what the fuck is a virgin? Uh, no
Uh, next one is uh epic thing that you guys might like mostly tom though
Okay, here we go
There it is three two one go found this cool thing
I think you guys might like uh mostly tom, but also everyone else might be interested in it
Um
It's called pico eight. It's like, you know how emulators they'll run like an nes or a game boy bands whatever
This is an emulator for a console that doesn't exist
You can go to the website. Just look up pico eight p i c o eight
And uh, and you can play games there that people have made, uh, you know the game celeste. It was actually prototyped in pico eight
Um like the the creators the the original version of it was in there and then they made it like a full epic game
You know swag mode. Um, but
It's really restrictive. It's like 128 by 128 resolution. There's only 16 colors you can pick from
And it's like 36 32 kilobytes something like that
Okay, why a little bit lesser than an nes, but like not like Atari levels of shit
Well, why make a game for pico eight? It's pretty awesome people make some cool games where and there's even
You can look up hashtag tweet cart on twitter people make the idea
Is that is that you you work it in like a maker?
And they'll post it on twitter and they'll post like the entire code
Uh, I remember no no
They're in the sweet limit like the 280 characters or whatever about this thing. Uh, so you can check all that out. It seems pretty cool
Um, but obviously it's cool. I thought it was cool. That's why I made this voicemail
Uh, okay. Oh, okay, so the idea is like
Get back the like the limits of of like old like data. Yeah hardware or whatever. I think I think the pico
Did did he mention this in the voicemail that uh that you can
Run this in browser. I'm pretty sure like that's the appeal of the pico. I'm playing it. I'm playing cellist two in browser
Yeah, that's that's the appeal of the uh of the pico eight is that it's like a it it's like a website game boy
It's it's cool
That's pretty cute. That's pretty good voicemail. Thank you
Well, this yeah, this does look pretty rad. I guess I better check it out pico eight
Uh
Lexiloffle
Is a fantasy console for making sharing and playing
Oh, okay
Um looks uh pretty
Winterwood
Okay, this is this is kind of this is kind of neat check it out. Uh
Yeah, okay, let's all check it out later. Uh
Yeah, load it up a game called winterwood for me, which looks kind of
I don't know what it is
Okay, next next voicemail is called. Um
YouTube warning very funny joe boy
Okay, three, two, one go you fucking people are always like oh
I don't want to keep making youtube videos
Well, have you ever considered giving thought to starting to initiate the creation of videos for p2p?
Yeah
No, I'm not going to stop sending these I won't stop. You can't fucking
I kind of ruin it
Yeah, you should have cut it off after the punchline
Let's continue making video for a poo
There you go. I have actually yes
Yes
YouTube I thought uh next voice
Uh voice grail
No
I'd rather give it to the pico eight. No if if if if if tommy. Yeah, I mean there's an argument there
Next one is okay next. All right. I'm tempted to play the next one. It's another tommy j
But it's called what the fuck is an apology. So I'm thinking. Okay. How long is it? It's 28 seconds. So it's not that bad
All right. All right. We'll give we'll give you we'll give it a shot. We'll give it a shot three two one go
If you do something you kind of get the feeling that you're supposed to apologize for it by convention
Uh, but you don't actually feel sorry about it. Oh should you because that's like lying, right?
Because you say you regret doing it even though you don't or you say you feel bad
No, this isn't what I was hoping. What do you do you lie or do you like this is a good question?
Do the thing you're supposed to is it a good question? I mean what's the answer?
I guess it's fine
um
Oh, what do you think if you threw the lens that he thinks that we should think that he's sorry for sending all these voicemails
Uh, I think it's interesting. I don't I don't think it doesn't make any sense. You're right. It doesn't I don't think that
This is actually about the voicemails
I mean you could you could read that into it if you wanted to I am invoking death of the author
In which yeah, yeah, I sure in which case what this means is that no, he is not sorry
About sending the and so he will suffer. Yes. I I just I just think that
I don't think panpeaks art style is that bad really. I hate you. I hate you. No, I hate it. I hate it
I'm bringing it back, baby. Is that is just not that bad. It's okay at best. It's okay at best and you know when I call something
That's okay at best. I call it bad
Okay, I call it bad
Bad saint
Is like, I don't know. I don't like it when people fake apologize. I don't think
It's something that should be done, but I guess if
if the only
Like result from an apology whether it's fake or not if it's like a just too quell
anger
that is I don't know maybe
Unjustly bubbling over
No, I don't know. It's not it's not as clear cut as like yes or no. I think I mean
I mean if someone is apologizing to me if if someone did something to me
And then and I didn't like it and then they apologize. They came and apologized to me
But the way they were apologizing like I sense like they don't mean this they're lying to me. It would only make me angrier
So sure that in that situation, but like what if I don't know they apologize
They didn't mean it, but you bought it and now you feel better
well, if I
Oh
So is it if you want to
Maintain a relationship with this person. It's best to apologize even if you don't the point is the point is like
What is the purpose of an apology? Is it more for the listener than it is for the speaker?
Oh, I see. Okay. So like is an apology
There so that like an opportunity for you to make amends or is it just like a social gesture designed to like
maintain
a like
You know
relationship
Right, what is an apology a miserable? I would prefer all apologies to be like sincere, but
I don't know like in a perfect world, you know
I mean I honestly I think it's like if you care about the person if you don't really give a shit about them
And you just are like I need this person not to be mad
Then yeah, sure
You can make a fake apology and as long as they buy it it it does what it's supposed to do
But it but it sounds even worse. Well. Yeah. Well, that's what I think
But if you if you do care about them, then like you're doing you're you're disrespecting them and doing something pretty
Pretty nasty to them by like going to them and saying like you're mad about me doing this thing
I'm not sorry, but I'm gonna pretend that I am so you'll stop being mad about it
No, it's pretty bad the way I'm thinking about that
But like it just depends more on like public apologies for like saying the wrong thing
Like I think I don't know
I guess it gets more complicated
If you don't if you don't actually think that you said the wrong that what you said was wrong
Then no, I mean, I think the right thing to do is not apologize for it even if
Everyone's mad and think they want you to like if you really if you really don't think it was wrong
I believe in sticking to your guns. I think that's good. Yeah, I I think that's
It it it most of the times say what is true
But I don't know there's like there's like a tiny bit of like leeway that I'm like unsure about
well, I mean, I mean if like there's a
I mean if someone is like
If someone is like attacking you
Unjustly and like doing harm and you can stop it with an apology even if you don't mean it
Yeah, but in that case it's like a well, I don't I don't actually care what this person that this person sucks
I'll apologize to them just like to make them stop
I don't like them because they're bad, but like
The apology will prevent damage
sure
I I think so there's there's space for that
It's very cynical, but I don't think you're wrong
I mean, I think I think you I think you should you should make an insincere apology when an apology is not actually warranted
But like it needs to be done
Uh, you know
Yeah, yeah
I mean, it's a it's a concession. Okay, uh next one is called
Uh, I'm skipping the next one. Oh, I'm actually I'm skipping the next two. Actually, there's there's two more Tommy J's
Okay, Jesus Christ. Yeah, three from now is called
uh
Gibbon coin
Uh, it's
Wait, there's so many
Gibbon coin greater than
saint coin
Right. Yeah. Gibbon coin
I'm listening without without hearing anything Gibbon coin greater than saint coin three two one go
Why are you speaking the book?
This is a let's read not a let's speak
Is this that snakes?
I mean
It could be
Remember that week that everyone had voicemails like this and it was scary
That was only like two weeks ago
It feels like it feels like an eternity
I I think they might be referencing this one wasn't creepy. This one wasn't unsettling. It was just like, uh
Just wacky
It just I felt very weird for the sake of being weird
Yeah, I didn't I don't do you remember that video I made like years ago on Gibbon take
Where it was a let's read and I just opened a book and started silently reading the book on camera. Ah, that's good
No, I don't I think that may have been I don't know if they knew about that, but the idea of Gib coin better
Sorry, it's actually titled Gib coin greater than saint con
Uh, so I don't know
Make make make of that what you will
Yikes, you had a typo
Arguments dismantled voice jail voice jail
Your argument is invalid
Next one is called uh squilliam fancieson
three two one go
A couple weeks ago
You guys had on a pcp fan artist who had done a bunch of art for you guys
But when are you gonna represent
The real silent majority of the podcast listenership the fan artist. That's right. It's me. I did I did the pcp fan lectures
Oh god, they're taking me away. Please
Oh, I know this guy. I'm
Yeah, I know I I I haven't actually got
I've watched part of the um
The elder scrolls lecture. I think I haven't watched the whole thing. Uh, yeah, he did another
I mean, we've we've got someone who did a
PCP ask lecture on right now. So fuck you squilliam. Uh, we're doing it
Twice even already happened already happened. Yeah, what he did he did squilliam did one on on the elder scrolls
And he did one on was the other one. He's done more than I have
He's done two and the other one was even plays elder scrolls. I'm right. I I mean not me
Which is probably why I would I would probably get more out of that lecture than a player
Yeah, not not I said ben sey the majority the real silent majority. Yeah, true
I believe this. Okay. I believe this is the video
Yes, yes, that's the one
Okay, it's harry sante. The next one is called reacting to let's read
And it is from gibbon tibbon at fibbon.com
So, uh, okay, so sorry about three two
Three two one go and we'll dive into the treasure of the pleasant valley. Yes, this is a video I was talking about frank. Yabi
Old old face
Don't ever watch videos of mine
This is just gonna be
It's still going
Oh my god, that hit me very quickly. Oh my god, wait
That's kind of what I was waiting for
This character's fucking gay
Negroes in it
Oh
Someone's getting canceled. That's what it read. That's what it said
Yeah, this is like getting canceled for reading huck fit in class
It was an old book a lot of a lot of blacks in this one. Oh two
A little too many of you asked me to a black
Wait, what book was it? It's
The treasure pleasant valley
It's like an old like no cover like 1910s sort of
You know book written before stones were invented
Interesting curious and they had the word they they had the n-word like the the the old n-word the negro word
That's a yeah
Yo, I think it's just as bad
No
No, it's fun. I wouldn't say it but I wouldn't call it as bad. You probably shouldn't say it
You probably shouldn't say it. It's not a slur. Don't think it don't say it. It's just an archaic
It's just an archaic term. It's out of fashion. It's an archaic term, but like the
You finally say it if you're gonna say the Spanish word for the color black
The other one is just a slurrified version. No, it's a country in africa
Slurrified the captain. They used to say negro before they said black and now you say poc
You know, it's all it's all good. Oh my god. He's still saying it. Yeah, but the reason the reason the n-word
Um, the more, you know, the colloquial one. Um, it's not a bad word. You shouldn't really say it
Oh my god is because
Is is because of like the connotation it has
Right, it doesn't have any connotation and the the the more
The slavery maybe no, you know, it's not it's not it's not a slave word. It's not a
I uh, it it's it's just it's not it's just too sussable word nowadays to use is that word again suss
Uh, there's yeah, that's the real slur
Wow, wow, wow, uh, uh, big it big it big it
I gotta say the same in the same episode
Christ
What I just don't think I don't think there's like a
I don't know
Like a significant difference between the old n-word and the new n-word for the older room
Yes, there is more okay. Yes, there is no you're an idiot. You're an idiot because all right
Literally both words existed at the same both words were used at the same time and they were different words
They were two different things and one was the correct term and one was the one was them the the slur
One was always bad and the other one was okay
They both could be used as slurs
Said by white people about black people to dehumanize. No, that's not true
That's not true. The the regular one was not a dehumanizing. It was just the word for I mean we call we call
We call them you could say the same thing about calling someone black like oh black is just what you called someone to dehumanize them
No, it's just it's just the word for it. That's that was just okay. Maybe maybe maybe I don't know the history of the word
I just always assumed that it was like Martin Luther King said like a disparaging sort of word because
It was it was like the the words to use but also because black people were so maligned. It was also like
Like I mean they were called in the way that in Europe too, which like didn't have slavery. Oh, yeah, Europe wasn't racist
I'm not I didn't say that
This is so dumb
This is by this by this logic
You could be like like literally anything that you've called that they used to call them is like automatically racist because people
You know, I I agree this conversation is dumb. Let's
I'm furious
I'm not I'm not I'm not budging until I know like I've looked up the definition of the word more like like the history of the word
And and it's use because I may be assuming things but like I know I know how I know how we can settle this
We got to look it up on urban dictionary.com. That's gonna
All right, uh
Wait, where is the next one there it is
Wait, no, it's me. Um
This one is called the real reason why Nate isn't on the pcp hashtag bge exposed
3 2 1 go
This isn't actually like that serious of a thing
It's just so I felt a comfortable saying it before because it's not actually like a major issue or anything
I just wanted to slip it in so everyone's been commenting on like when's Nate coming back
Where's best guy ever etc etc since the whole brad garling house thing and like I hear what you're saying guys
I understand where you're coming from like why isn't Nate back? But here's what you gotta understand everybody right now
Nate doesn't want to come back on the show. He's doing his own stuff. Do not expect him back
He may come back someday or he may not it is up to him and do not count on it
So everybody commenting. Where's the best guy ever?
This is your answer. He's not coming back anytime soon. He has made that explicitly clear
He is going his own way the proud mig towel that he is
This
This guy sent in a voicemail the last time I was on of like a of a nate best guy ever
Yeah, we'll we'll sent in a voicemail the last time I was on of a very similar sounding speech
I just thought that was interesting that they decided to call it again when I'm on
Okay, I'm sorry to beat this. I'm sorry to beat this dead horse, but I'm gonna read this from wikipedia
Okay, this is from wikipedia. Best guy ever is
In the english language negro plural negro is a term historically used to denote persons considered to be of black african heritage
The term can be construed as offensive inoffensive or completely neutral largely depending on the region or country where it is used
So there you go. Okay wikipedia is on my side. We were both
Once again, the white man is correct
I mean, I would still not use it just because the only times I've I've heard it said in like
Modern times is by extreme far-right racists
Who are also boomers? It's a suss word, Ben. It's just a very suss word to use
Okay, but like if it's like it's not it's not bad if you read it from a book
No, it's not bad
I wasn't like saying. Oh, I mean, I wouldn't I wouldn't like call I wouldn't I wouldn't like call someone that I wouldn't like call someone that
To in like, you know
A regular conversation
Like like maybe maybe
Would do maybe the word is like equivalent to using the term african
Which is like just a description descriptive word in in in that case then sure, but like I feel like like
Generally speaking people associate it more with the n word. Maybe just because it begins with the letter n
Is a n word kind of no, it's literally it's literally it's because the slur is just a like bastardization of that word
Which was the like
Yeah, polite word
I mean if you ask like just random people, I feel like they would assume that they carry the same weight even though they may not
They don't words change definition based on the popular opinion
So like I don't know it's very it's very suss like using the word like using the word boy
Like come here boy like that, you know
Fine, I don't what do you even disagreeing with me about oh, fuck you. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, obviously don't just go around like calling people
It's weird. It'd be really weird to do that
Fuck her
I'm gonna try not cancel you
All right. Okay, Ben. Okay. Ashley's ugly. All right. I agree. She's not good
She is she is fucking ugly. She does her lipstick like a fucking idiot
She's not okay. You won. Yeah. Thanks. Good. I win. I all
I don't think you're okay, Ben. Hands aren't so isn't that good. All right. I always win. Okay. I always get my man
Next next voicemail is called uh, not the samurai. Uh, there it is three
One go
First you skip my exciting earnest voicemail series and now you shit on webcomics making almost none
I still remember the emptiness. I felt I'm from my second rereading on one of my favorite webcomics
Gaia
I first did for more quality comics and remembered a certain ccp member talking and hustling around his scribbles all the time
A venture to his website went through all its contents in a very
Unsatisfyingly short amount of time and stayed dumbfounded and flabbergasted having a brain freeze over there not being
anything more
You can only tremble under the weight of the heaps of published content of giants like penny arcade and control alt delete
I couldn't get into penny arcade, but I hold control. They'll
Deep in my heart
The Kickstarter for their collective comics was the only one I ever successfully backed and its six kilo kilos of
Quality hardcore remains one of my most priceful sessions
I still remember being emotional about the mean loss
Since I wasn't plugged into the internet
I guys at the time
No matter
Also, Europe is in deep this funny voice. That's just his voice around any time. I don't think he's I don't think he's putting on a
Maybe he is I don't know who even knows
I don't know. Is he just saying like like ben saint, uh, where's the quantity? I want quantity not quality
That's fair. You know what I respect it
I
I want anything. I can't even disagree. I can't I I I want more ben sane comics. Well, yeah
I'm a fan of Ben Sane's comic after I finish the secret project. I will go back and I'll make some I'll make some of that stuff
I promise I promise
uh, but
I never read uh, penny arcade much, but I did play penny arcades on the rain slick precipice of darkness 3
I I have not played the
Uh, and I like that. I don't you I don't think you listened to the last week's episode
But uh, I was saying then like I don't I don't think I don't think anybody likes the penny arcade comic
Like I don't know anybody who actually thinks they're good. Um, the rain slick precipice of dark rain slick precipice of darkness
I've never played it and I don't particularly want to but I am like amazed every time I remember that such a thing exists
There's four. Yeah
The fourth one is like made by like a different studio or something, right?
The third and the fourth one are made by um, we're made by zboy. Yeah, boy
Like cthulhu saves the world in breath of death seven. I think
Is how you say, right? I want to hear this guy's opinion on millenverse
A bunch of a bunch of the uh DLC the penny arcade dlc podcasts involve them talking about like
Oh god this week was such a fucking uh, I had to like write all these item descriptions for the game
Or I had to like I had to like do all these like these art assets for the game or whatever
I had to
You just like a bunch of them are them talking about like their role in the like creative process while for the studio
That was making one of the rain slick precipice of darkness games
So I'm like interested in them as like an artifact
Uh, I mean, is it good? Is is number three? I would
Uh, the the the one I played. Yeah, I actually kind of liked it. It's uh, it's like a simple jrpg
it kind of has it kind of has combat like, uh
I think I think it's like found fancy 10 or like vagrant story or something where you can like you can see the uh
You can see how like how the turn order is going to play out before you do anything
And uh, it's it's pretty easy game for I remember because they heal you after every battle, but I didn't really mind that
That's pretty funny too. It's been years since I've played it though. Okay
It's it's just
Every everything everything that exists
Because of penny arcade is like a weird thing that should that shouldn't exist but does and is funny
And it's it's it's more interesting than the comic itself. Absolutely. Absolutely. I wish that was me
Me too. No, I just I I don't like penny arcades comics
Damn, but I want to I just want to like steal their skin and live their life
I'm gonna do something called bill and con
One of the days is gonna be great
Uh, the next one is called
cross
hotly debated question
3 2 1 go
How many chuggas come before the choo choo?
No two
chug it's never one chugga chugga chugga. Choo choo
Chugga chugga choo choo. It's either one. I would say okay
I Chugga, conroy. That next question. Okay. There's a graph imagine. There's a graph like it's it's up really high at one chugga
And then it's down really low for two and then it's kind of medium for three
If you're going short chugga chugga choo choo if you're going long chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga choo
Yeah, I was gonna say you would but never to chugga chugga chugga chugga choo choo awkward awkward
Yeah, yeah, yeah seven seven I would go for seven wait tectonic when you mentioned chugga conroy
six you ever um
There was a there was a I think it was years ago when like this one company was was saying like a
Pitch is an idea for a movie and if it's good
We'll pick it up and chugga conroy pitched his idea for a movie and it was called water falls and it was about a guy called
I think his first name was waters and he was basically like a waterbender
No, it's called water I need to hear your hands you need to send here's the here's the kind of here's the kind of like
It's like lost media basically his pitch is because I couldn't find it
I think he took it down because it was kind of a very silly ass pitch
It's called water hands. Yeah. Yeah, we'll call it water hands or something and the character had a sister called water falls
And I remember him and I only knew that was chugga conroy years later because I
Needed to like pass a level in a game and I looked up a left play and I found chugga's and I watched a little bit of it
And he mentioned it for a brief second like oh this I think it was a Mega Man game
He's he's like, oh, yeah, this this power kind of reminds you of my character from my my idea for a series of called water
Hands and I'm like wait a second. This is the guy who pitched water hands. Oh
God a fame a fake shock. You know, you know chugga conroy as the water
And not I mean, I know he's a let's player, but it's so
Just so funny
The next next voicemail next voicemail is called poke. Well, no, it's called Pokemon
But if it was good three two one go black and white
I'm like a month late on this topic
But use was asking if there's a Pokemon game that doesn't suck shit and drop the ball 20 times in a row
Well, I got one for you. It does everything the fans have been clamoring for it has every Pokemon
It retains all the mechanics from previous gens. It's an MMO. You can have your mom's follow you outside their ball
It's highly customizable. You might not have heard of it. It's called the procrastinator's Minecraft server Ben
You fucking Dweebeheimer. How does this always skip your mind when the topic of Pokemon done right comes up?
Pixelmon is the solution to the game-free question or GQ if you will not only that it's also the endless war Pokemon
Romhack except a thousand times better because it's CW and 3d. That's right. We're recreating lock a common 3d
And it's fucking based it's being slowly developed
But one day it'll be home to all the rough houses and cop kids to commit gang violence to their hearts content
As of this podcast going live the server is free to enter for the next week
I've decided this is just canon now and there's nothing you can do about it
Actually, you know, I have any rck people getting for free forever. Fuck it. Can it bam, whoa, okay?
Does he can he do that did we give him the permission to do that
Um
Me and tectonic are the host so we get to the side. Yes, you can do that. Oh god
Yeah, okay. Fuck it. Go. Well, I guess I was wrong
I guess I was wrong when I said that you have to pay to be in it. Fuck
Well, okay, well
nice
It's true that else do we got just like just like two more. Okay, uh, next one is called actual do
There it is three two one go
Hello, my name is actual do and if you are reading this I am gone
I'm writing this letter as a way for my memories to not simply vanish from this place
So that some may learn from my mistakes
Ben
You utter fucking moron
because of you and your
simply
Disgusting interest in the stock market. I decided
Maybe I should understand it better. I don't know much myself
And me being autistic. Well, I need the cause-and-effect relation
To understand
So I looked for it and I looked and I looked and through the halls of
Investopedia I read and the more I read the less I understood the more I I fucking
Grasp to the difference between an option a future a currency and a commodity the more I could feel my brain
implode from within
Do not try to understand the stock market some things are meant to not be understood
So fuck you Ben you motherfucker
Say you know
All you have to understand about the stuff it's so easy all you have to understand is buy a game stop and hold
Just buy a game stop and don't sell high American Psycho. Just don't sell it. That's all it is to it
Couldn't be couldn't be simpler. You know that one scene where Christian Bale like
Kills that guy with the axe imagine Ben and it's Nate is the guy that he killed but Ben is talking about
He's talking about what's the name that one strip search that one show with Katie Rice strip search
Yeah, he starts also penny arcade joint he starts playing it and it goes to number today's like have you heard a strip search?
And then he starts talking about it
Like it's a gem that no one talks about that often and then finally kills the first couple of contestants were a little too
Mainstream for my taste there. Yeah, they were too amateurs when they eliminate when they eliminated Tristan Falcone
I think they really came into their own
Tristan
You didn't oh, yeah, that is Amy Tristan now. I believe so. Yeah, whoa, okay. I follow them on
Twitter no, they're actually one of my favorite contestants. I
Just tried to search Twitter on Twitter. That is
That is that is so wacky
Okay, that's interesting
lol
Okay, last voicemail is
is a
This one is from Eleazar Eleazar sent this one in at the last minute. It's called I got bored editing
So I did this
Son of a wait, so I did this son of a bitch song. Oh, well Eleazar wrote a song
Three he got bored editing. He did looks like we need to it looks like you need to give him stricter deadlines
Yeah, yeah, oh absolutely absolutely gotta squeeze him gotta squeeze him
He's got free time to do this. Hmm
Hmm, if you got time to if you got time to sing you got time to bing
Kring and
Okay, three two one
I won't bless that guy that son of a bitch
I won't bless that guy
Son of a bitch
Son of a that that that horse son
Hey
I hate hearing myself what about voicemails
That fucked me up
I thought Eleazar was gonna
I thought Eleazar was gonna edit in more other PCP members voices in there what other members
I thought I thought yeah, what other members I thought he would just edit in
Endless just trying to justify saying the n-word in there. Oh come on
Who uh, I don't even remember that lol
Who uh, who are we talking about calling a son of a bitch and a horse on
I don't know
I must must have felt pretty strongly about it at the time. Yeah, I said it so much
We sang a whole song about it
That was honestly
Honestly, why the fuck not why the fuck not?
Eleazar make that the new theme song fuck the old song. It's maybe the voicemail song make it for
The old in with the new
Maybe the episode after this because if this is a nice little punch line to end the podcast with
I agree. I agree
Man speaking of ending the podcast when this is all over
You know when this when when 20 when the curse of 2020 finally lifts and this podcast is over
I'm gonna I can't wait to make myself another sausage egg and cheese sandwich. I made one before the show
And I'm gonna do it again. I'm gonna do it again. Do it again. I swear. It's so fucking good. So fucking good
Sounds good. I like that. Oh amazing. Ah
Hey listeners. Hey, listen, you should all all treat yourself treat yourself to a nice little sausage egg. Sausage sandwich
Just like uh
On me, but I'm not actually
Let's pack up on you as you pay for all for the procrastinators
Email email ben say email ben say in a paypal invoice to cover the charge. I get yourself some extra fries too. Why don't you?
I
I said last week
I said last week that the behind the scenes clip episode bonus episode to be out. I was wrong. I was lying
It's actually but it actually will be out for this episode. Uh, I think
I hope
Uh soon
Patreon.com slash the pro
Crastinators uh for bonus episodes. Uh
Shit tons of content uh for five bucks. What's uh, what's uh, what's your fucking problem? You're not doing it
Um, what's your damage speakpipe.com speakpipe.com slash
The pcp voicemail to send us a voicemail. Don't
Send 40 fucking voicemails. Send one preferably. It's not it's not as funny as you think you are
We won't we won't be is better. We'll think they're cringed
That's very good. That's not big. We won't be we won't we won't instead of bing
We won't bing that which is cring
That's the lesson you must learn
Uh here on the pro procrastinators podcast
yo
Uh anything else anything else you want to fucking discuss
About current events. I know it's been four hours. I don't know. I mean like it's that beats our time. Isn't that bad?
Like I don't know what the big uh, uh tectonicandpro.com shoutouts to large chat. Thank you for watching
Um bill inverse read bill inverse read bongo luna
Bye bill inverse digitally gumroad
It's great
Goodbye. Bye. That's the end of the podcast. Good night. God bless you
The first fascinators
Okay, no more no more
Isn't it a great one