It's the podcast. It started. The PCP. It's a duo again. It's me. It's Gibbontake, right? I don't like that. I get lost. I get lost in that one. Gibbonsake? Sake?
Oh, for Gibbonsake. For Gibbonsake. Speaking of sake, I'm hungover. My head hurts. Yay!
Yeah, Ben, do you have a story or did you forget all of it again?
No, there's not much of a story this time. By the way, it was really funny when I wasn't on to hear you and Tom be like, oh, I think he's hungover. Oh, I think he's drunk. Or I think he's dead. I was like, to hear that later and be like, yep, they're correct.
Well, I was hanging out with Munchy and Kazzy and on our way out, we went to get food and on the way back, I decided to buy some hard seltzers for myself and then, you know, just going to have one, just going to have two. Drank the whole case. Don't worry about it.
When I hear seltzer, all I can think of is the crusty the clown, seltzer water, flour, like, smooth my flour gets here.
You know, because I have the ingredients, because I've been doing my gummy worm experiments, I have all these like, flavoring ingredients. I've been, sometimes I'll just buy a case of like, what's the word, sparkling water and just mix up like, malic acid and like, fruit flavorings and like, colors and stuff and stevia and just mix up like, some like, soda for myself.
But it's never as much, it's too much work. It's too much work to mix like, one glass and it goes flat really fast. So I can't like, make a whole bunch early on and like, keep it for later. It's a little disappointing, honestly.
I wonder how they do it.
They do it, I don't know. They can do it on, they do it on a mass scale and an industrial scale. So it's easy for them. They have the infrastructure. They own the means of production. Not like, not like me, Prol that I am.
I have a couple things to talk about today.
Cool.
The Tezuka comic that I've been going on with is, it's like, it's well into the inking stage. And I'm still streaming weekdays over on twitch.tv slash give and take. So drop in.
We reached a goal where I had enough subscribers, I think I just needed 15 to get an extra emote slot for the subscriber like tier one.
I'm hoping we can get to the next one by the end of the month, which is like nine away at this point. It's not that far.
I mean, aside from the comic, have you been, is twitch being good to you? Is it like, worth your time? I don't know if that's what I mean to say. Do you feel like streaming is going well as an endeavor, apart from the drawing?
I mean, I never get enough viewer base in order to like get up my way to partner. You need to be getting an average of 70 something.
But you've got 15 subscribers.
Yeah.
Which is kind of a lot to get in like one month because you started with zero, right?
I think I had one or two already.
But yeah, mostly, mostly zero.
So yeah, it was like, it was a big hype thing. And then a lot of people were invested in what was going on already. And they were like, yeah, sure, Amazon Prime, ding, you know, free. It's easy.
Excellent, excellent.
Yeah, I don't know. I don't know if I'm going to like use this as a stream like springboard. I think streaming is just sort of thing, a thing like a tool in my tool belt that I go to sometimes that I'm not really ever thinking of making it into anything bigger.
So sometimes nice to have an audience while you do something, be it video gaming or drawing.
Makes sense.
But yeah, I'm 20 pages into the 50 page line art thing.
You've lined 50 pages.
I've lined 20 pages.
I've lined 20 pages, yes.
What's the deadline?
The deadline is 1st of September. So I've got,
You got time.
I've got time.
I'm trying, I'm going to go for like getting to page 40 by the end of next week if I can do like four pages a day.
And that'll be, that'll be great.
Sorry, my voice is cracking a little better than I know why.
You are really fucking going for it. You are really making some some headway on this and I'm very impressed and intimidated and infuriated.
Thank you.
Good job.
I mean, at the beginning of last Monday and Tuesday, I was like, oh shit, my line art's not good.
Oh no, like I was starting the line art and it was like, oh no, I'm not like a God.
I can't do it yet. I thought I would be a God by this point by the amount of drawing I've been doing.
But no, it's like, it's good, you know, it's on the level of Lord of Ghosts, maybe a little bit more.
But the time it takes to get a page done is, you know, you can't rush through something like that.
You have to do all of the steps and it does involve a lot of control.
Control Z.
Well, but you know, overall, I'm pleased with the way it's looking.
I've accepted that it's not going to be like a fucking super masterpiece, but it is going to be pretty good.
And like on the level of stuff I've done before, if not a little better.
Everything, anything finished is better than anything unfinished. You know what I'm saying?
I do.
You understand the words that are coming out of my mouth.
I, you know, you know, I didn't think you could do it.
I thought you were a stupid dumb bitch, but it looks like I was wrong. Good job.
Holy fuck.
What?
You probably can't pick that up on the mic, but like there's a massive thunder booming.
So if you hear that in the background, that's probably a storm.
Awesome. I'm jealous.
It's, um, it got, it got cold here all of a sudden.
Like it's been like, it's been like terribly uncomfortably hot.
It's been like 90 degrees around here.
And then like yesterday it was like sub 70 and I couldn't believe it.
It's exactly the same thing over here.
So much for global warming. Am I right?
Yeah, I'm right. Yeah, you know, I'm right.
Man, oh man.
Uh, hey, do I have time to gripe about my personal finances?
Uh, sure. I don't know what I could say.
Do I have permission? Well, I just got to say last week I was so excited about my,
about my credit card, about my city double cash card, 2% cashback, but I fucked up.
I fucked it up, Gib.
What'd you fuck up?
If, if I had gotten, um, okay, I won't, I won't.
There's, there's no need for me to explain all the intricacies of why this is the case.
But, uh, if, if I had gotten the discover it cashback card, I could have gotten,
I could have gotten like $200 plus back on, um, on like the, the, the buying the,
the RFCK pins and the, um, and the vapors to book printing.
I could have gotten like more than $200 back.
Uh, if I had gotten that card instead with the double cash, I'm getting like $60 back.
So better than nothing, but, uh, I beefed it.
That's, that's free money down the drain and I'm bummed about it.
But I guess what are you going to do?
So you're still getting some free money.
It's just you found a better deal.
I could have gotten, I could have gotten significantly more, but it's pretty cringe.
It's pretty cringe and they won't approve me for that one.
For some reason, too many inquiries, I guess, I guess because I applied for this one before,
but like I'm definitely under 524.
So I don't know.
I feel like I should be good.
They're watching you Ben.
They, they heard the podcast.
They know what you're going to do.
They heard the podcast.
They hacked my computer.
They saw that I was going on R churning and reading this, the flow charts.
And they're like, this guy's no good.
This guy's trouble.
Black, black bag him.
Oh well.
Live and learn.
That's my, that's my, that's my personal tragedy this week.
Oh, I'm out of things to say.
Oh, well, I got a thing to say.
This is my second.
I'm floundering.
Okay.
Um, I guess this wasn't the case last week, but I started doing, I guess,
some sort of public gender confusion tweets.
Yes.
Where I started, uh, I posted like, like a thing like, Hey guys,
I'm just going to try using female pronouns.
Hmm.
Okay.
That's all law.
Don't think anything of it.
Just do, do that.
You know, um, and that was a nice, people were very nice about it.
Um, and it, it really was an experiment because I just wanted to know.
Yeah.
If the, the, the feeling of being, uh, uh, spoken to with the, the female pronouns would
change my views on the whole trans thing because I had been thinking a lot of trans
thoughts, um, ever said a lot of, a lot of dangerous trans thoughts ever since, uh,
revolutionary.
Yes.
Ever since recon four, when I cosplayed as punk and I was like, Oh no,
I like wearing tights.
Am I gay?
This, this is bad news for me.
That's fucking gay.
Yeah.
Can't believe this.
Okay.
All right.
Sure.
So I was like, hmm, I don't know.
And I was thought like the, the pronoun thing would be a way to like solidify in one direction
or another, whether or not I'm fully trans or some other thing.
I think after this, I am not fully trans.
If I'm going to make a public statement about it, I think I am some sort of weird thing
in the middle, a non binary that can, you fucking centrist pig.
I know.
I'm always me, always the centralist.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
From that bad guy.
Uh, so.
Okay.
If you have any questions, I will answer.
I have my, my, my, I mean, my only question, I guess, is how, how did you feel about it?
You did, you went on Twitter, you said, Hey, try, try the female pronouns.
And then when I assume people mostly did so, uh, uh, how did that feel?
What did you think about that?
Very initially, um, it felt, it felt great.
You know, it was like, ah, it was so nice of them to immediately accept the thing I was
doing.
Right.
After a day or two, it just sort of was like, I was seeing more of them and I was like,
yeah, you know, fits, you know, it doesn't feel incorrect.
Um, but I'm also not like going crazy about it.
It's just sort of like, yeah, it's like those pronouns fit just as well as the male ones.
Um, hmm.
Okay.
So she felt correct, but, but, uh, he did not feel incorrect.
Yeah.
Like it, it was.
It's why it's been so like confusing for me because it's, I really wish it was more clear
cut that I was like, Oh, I hate being a man and everything to do with masculinity on that
gender, like no thanks, but all of the female stuff, I'm all for it.
Then I would be like, easy, just transition, do the other gender.
Um, but it's, it's, it's not as simple as that.
I feel like there's no, cause you know, I personally believe that if gender is like mostly
societally built and it's, and it's, you know, the things that about the gen, the language
of gender can change over time.
There's no like permanent anything.
You can, you can cherry pick what things you like and just do that.
And so when it comes to like deciding on a pronoun or a gender, it doesn't really make
any sense to be so, be so final about any, like be so.
Sounds.
I don't know.
I don't, I don't want to jump into a label, I guess is the thing.
Sounds like, well, not, not to label you against your will or anything, but it sounds like you're
a little bit envy.
Uh, non bar.
Yeah.
It's okay.
I forgive you.
Cool.
I understand.
Cause like I was having hangups about it specifically because I was thinking, ah, non binary.
That's lame.
That's not interesting.
That's just, you didn't make, you didn't do completely the opposite of what you were
before.
That's not crazy.
That's not wacky.
That's, that's not a, that's not a scoop.
I say a throwing down my, my notes and my, my quill for as I, as I, as a throwing down
my reporters hat, my journalist badge.
Yeah.
Like the headline is a man decides that maybe some female things are good.
I'm not going to be, this isn't going to make the front page.
So like,
This isn't going to be trend on Twitter.
So when it comes to like pronouns, I guess either, I like, I like she and if people are
okay with doing that, that's fine.
Um, if people, I think that the weird thing about it is that there's definitely a contingent
of people who would spitefully call me he knowing that I was a man.
Yes.
And so it would be, it would be hard to, to parse whether or not somebody calling me a
he was calling me a he just because, or calling me a he because they hate trans people.
And so it's, I don't know exactly how to, to approach that.
Um, boy.
Gee, I don't know.
Okay.
Well, everyone needs to put in their bio, whether they're saying he because they don't
know anything or because they are a mean, a mean jerk.
We need that in bio, please.
In my bio, transphobe or not.
Stop, stop, stop shoving it down our throat.
Stop forcing us to put pronouns in bio.
You just put your opinions in bio.
And so we don't have to do it.
Okay.
That's, it's better this way.
Yes.
It's on, it's on you friends.
Cool.
Yeah.
So when it comes to other things like changing voice or dressing differently, I'll probably
dress differently.
Occasionally, you won't see that because that's me.
That's my personal life.
Correct.
But I don't think I'm going to try changing my voice too much.
I don't know.
It feels pretty, I don't know.
What do you think?
I only know my voice from inside my head.
And what do I think about your voice?
About like whether it has like an androgynous quality because it's not very deep.
It's probably more masculine than it is feminine, I'm sure, but like.
It's hard.
I mean, it's a, it's not a particularly deep voice.
I wouldn't say it's particularly Andrew.
I don't know.
I mean, I think of it as a male voice because I've thought of you as a male for this whole
time.
So maybe I'm a little biased when I say that it sounds like a.
Yeah, it's fairly masculine voice to me.
I would imagine most people, even if it's not super deep or anything, I would imagine
most people would assume it, but there has been like one time I think that somebody
thought I was a girl from like a give and take video, a pony give and take video that
I made.
Just one of those reviews.
They thought I was a girl from that.
I remember that.
Epic.
Do they think your pony was a girl pony?
They may have been talking about that instead.
I'm not sure.
Didn't you give give and take like the girl pony face?
Wasn't that like part of his design?
Yes.
That was explicitly like, I don't like the way the male pony snouts look.
Yeah.
No, nobody does.
Nobody does.
So yeah, that's, that's.
It's my gender confusion.
It's still not like finalized.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Hilarious.
It's, it's the funniest thing I've ever seen.
Speaking of the funniest thing you've ever seen, did you see, did you re, did you rewatch
the French history lecture?
Did you see that that came out yesterday?
I did not rewatch it because I was, I was rewatching it in a call with Munchie to go
over it to see if there's any problems.
I saw some, I saw some screenshots being posted in the, the Golden Child Foundry.
Is that, was that like, he was like editing it or whatever?
Yeah.
He was, he was thinking, all right.
No, it was just the raw footage.
We were going through like both cameras on screen at once.
And, and he was just wondering if there was anything people pointed out like, oh, you
should do this is a suggestion.
So I watched most of it through that.
Well, not most of it.
It was four hours long.
But yeah, it was just great.
Just re-living the Munchie time.
I feel, you know, there's not, I was re rewatching it, not the whole thing, but just like bits
and pieces.
And I was like, there's not a lot of like audience.
Like we don't say very much.
Like Munchie mostly just talks the whole time.
Only occasionally does the audience speak up.
Like I was editing, I was going back the other day and editing the Sonichu lecture, Sonichu
102.
And it's like, it's constant.
Like, like you guys speak up like all the time, which is fine.
Like that's good.
And I was thinking like, should we have said more during the French Revolution?
Like I didn't know what to say, but that is not because like I was like bored or anything.
Like I was interested.
No, it was, it was, I didn't have any like comments to make during it or anything.
It was because Munchie explained it in such a way that it seemed like he was always getting
to an explanation and exploring a new thing.
And you weren't left being like, wait a minute, what was that about that?
Like he was talking like a thousand miles an hour for four hours.
It was, it was like so much information.
And you know, I don't think any of us were like big history buffs.
So we were just like, yes, nodding our heads.
Like, of course we trust you.
The thing that every man wants unwashed pussy and unrelenting cuckold drink.
The UP you see.
I saw that part just a minute ago before we started recording and I laughed.
It's good.
So what do we got?
We got two.
We got my lecture, which is going to be coming out soon because Sixten has a, I think I haven't
heard his latest take on the music for the slime and punishment finale, but I think we
are almost done.
And I'm going to be releasing that soon.
Oh yeah.
That's all linked in.
It is all linked in.
And then the Sonichu one of two lectures to come out after that.
Very exciting.
And then Digi's lecture, whenever that's ready.
She said September, but I don't know if I believe her anymore, but I guess we'll see.
I really want to see that because it was really funny and cool and good.
I want it out.
Hmm.
Yes.
Hey, you there?
I'm just like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, and then we got, and then we got the, we got the.
Girl.
Should I, should I say the other things there are the radcon four things?
Are they secret?
I don't even remember what's supposed to be secret anymore.
Don't talk about the Brad stuff.
Okay.
We know the knowledge that there is a lecture is out.
Obviously, because we said we would do that.
But don't slip any secret deeds about it.
Okay.
I think I was just about to slip some secret deeds.
So thank you for catching me.
Thanks for catching me.
Anyway, I was reflecting on this yesterday.
You know, I was downing, I was downing hard seltzer after hard seltzer.
Talking a munchie about this yesterday and I was reflecting on, you know, I feel like
once everything that we have in the works, once every radcon four related thing that
is in the works is done and out, I think people will be, I think people will be hard
pressed say that we did not deliver on, on, on the, the, the whole, the whole promise.
I think people will be, I think people will be easily satisfied with the amount of content
that was delivered for, you know, the meme $34,000 because there's a lot.
Yeah.
A lot, a lot, a lot.
We worked hard.
It was.
And we played hard.
It has been like a bit of a, like a downer period.
It like, not just for us, but in the world.
And it's, it's kind of because of the downer period in the world that, I don't know, like
all of this stuff got delayed for a bunch of months, but like things are getting into
place.
We got, we got lectures coming out munchies done with his fucking, well, the channel's
back.
That's definitely a good thing.
Losing the channel, losing all that red content.
Yeah.
It was just so disheartening.
And we got more things.
You are nearly done with slime and punishment, which is like a big thing that's been building
up.
I, you know, I feel bad.
I, I like, I'm, I'm very happy with how the finale looks.
I'm, I'm excited to release it.
It's not, I feel like it's not enough for the amount of time that I've been talking about
finishing it.
Uh, but like, I don't know what would be.
You know what I mean?
Does that make sense?
Uh, it's been like, I was talking about the finale at Radcon 4.
Even at Radcon 4, I was, I was like, about to make it.
And here we are five months later and I'm like ready to release it.
And I'll be perfectly frank.
It's not, it's not five months worth of work.
It just took me that long to like focus myself and actually get around to doing it, uh, instead
of all the other things that I was doing.
And I feel a little bummed about that.
Does that make, make a sense here?
Yeah, yeah.
I feel that as well.
Like sometimes the amount of time it takes to make something is not literally the amount
of time it takes for it to come out and it feels like you're, you're, you're being a
shithead like, oh, all of those hours I could have been working.
I didn't.
But like, I don't know.
Sometimes life gives you, um, ruined lemons and you can't make lemonade.
It was, it was a combination of having other things that I was working on that distracted
me and just being sad and like depressed and upset and like not being able to focus is,
is both of those things together.
And that's why, and that's why it took me five months to get the finale done.
Uh, and I don't know.
Do I feel good about it?
No, but it is what it is.
Yeah.
But that being said, it, I was showing, I was showing Munchie and Kazzy yesterday and
I think they thought it looked cool and I also think it looks cool and I can't, it might
even be out by the, it might even be out by the time this podcast that you, the viewer
are listening to this.
Yeah.
I know, I know.
Very exciting.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Yeah.
So, you know, we've got all that stuff.
We've got rad content coming.
We also have, uh, the podcast is back after a hiatus.
Is it?
Yes.
We made an episode catching up four chapters.
There's a lot of cool shit happening in these chapters.
Are you, are you caught up with One Piece, Ben?
No, I never did get caught up.
I think I'm like 70 or 60 chapters behind.
Wow.
Yeah.
Um, um, I, I, I'm so stupid.
I'm so stupid.
I, at Radcon, I was, I was like, I'm definitely going to catch up so I can be on the podcast
at Radcon and I, I read it on the plane, I read it on the trip and then I would like
stay up at night in bed, like reading the chapters, like trying to get caught up and
I didn't get caught up.
The only thing that happened was that I was just tired every day because I like stayed
up in bed reading One Piece trying to get caught up.
Is that, is that why you were in bed so much?
I didn't realize that you were like staying up late into the night reading One Piece.
To a, to a large extent, yeah, that is why like, my sleep schedule was all fucked up
and I like slept through a lot of stuff because I was like trying to get, I was trying to
catch up on One Piece at night.
There was so much very, very stupid.
You left.
I mean, not to like shit on you, but you left a lot of things right to the last minute.
The poster, you drew in like one hour, like extremely fast before you got on the flight.
No, I didn't, you are a fucking fool.
That's not accurate.
I was drawing that poster for like a week.
I did finish it very close to the deadline, but I was working on it for like a whole
week beforehand.
Well, yeah, but like, it's, it was like, we needed the file so that Munchie can print
it so that Munchie could bring it.
And we had a very clear deadline for that.
And it was like, oh shit.
Oh, shit.
And then like all of it, I mean, you're right, you're right.
I did.
And it was like, I did leave it.
And then also like basically all of us did not study for our lectures and we had to study
at Radcon, including you and me.
Yes.
It was like, Radcon was kind of a shit show, but you know, sure, I, I enjoy that it happened.
It's the same way.
I mean, it's the same way I did my first lecture.
Well, when you, when you say that I didn't study, I mean, I, I read through, you had
the material in your head.
You was just like, I did.
Yeah.
I did read through a unicorn jelly.
I did read through the JDR comics and I did read through Sonichir before.
I didn't make any notes though, which is like the hard part.
Mostly what I'm thinking of.
Yeah.
True.
I really, I mean, I didn't do fucking any research.
I, I thought, I thought I could rem, remember Homestuck and I kind of did, but I couldn't
kind of remember Homestuck.
I remembered so much, but like it wasn't enough to make it like well formed.
Oh, I suck and they gave it a, a, a cruel name that means half formed quasi-modo.
Amazing.
Anyway, that's, that's the past, but the future is now, um, canton is a thing.
Yeah.
Whatever.
They're, they're doing that.
No, I like it.
I like the fact that, you know, this idea of doing a show weekly is like actually finally
a real possible thing now that they're living near each other.
Hmm.
Imagine, imagine some friends getting together to release a recording of themselves talking
once a week.
Where, where could I, where could, where could I find a content of that, of that nature?
Hmm.
Gee, I don't know.
Where could such a thing be?
Nobody, nobody knows.
It's a mystery.
Good thing canton exists to fill this, this dis unfilled niche.
I mean, I don't know.
The mark, the mark, the gap in the market needed filling and now it's here, praise be.
People were going insane last episode wanting Nate.
They were thirsty for him.
They really want him back.
No.
There was, Tom mentioned this two episodes ago, ever when it was, when it was just you
and Tom, right?
Everyone, like nobody, everyone was like, I like the, like the low energy, like the low
key nature.
This podcast is relaxing.
I don't miss Nate.
Last one ever, there was, well, there was a split.
There were people saying like, God, where is Nate?
Why isn't Nate on this podcast?
And there was another group being like, fuck all these Nate heads, Nate heads molding,
get wrecked.
So, so we have an ideological divide.
And Digi said that it was probably because of the name, responsible fiscal planning,
which does seem, you know, if you're,
It does seem like a Nate head, not a Nate head, a Nate himself, a topic.
Sure.
Possibly.
However, you know, that's, that's the twist.
You think it's Nate, but it's not.
It was me all along.
That's the trick.
And you fell for it, viewer, you Rube, you fell, you, I lay the trap and you walk right
into it.
I mean, all of this stuff, I, I do want more people to appear on the podcast.
It's fun having the little shows, you know, just chatting about stuff, but it's, it's
very clear that like, unless there's a lot we can talk about, we only have what we've
been doing that week to, to really focus on.
I mean, more people means more material, more, more things, more items of interest.
I'm like, I don't know.
The gender, could I talk more about it?
I don't know.
It's.
You could.
If you wanted to.
I mean, I don't know what really to say exactly.
No, sure.
Sure.
Um, this is, this is a, you know, yeah, I don't know.
It's like I'm saying, like, where could I find a weekly recording of some people talking
with where, where could such a thing be?
Hmm.
I don't know.
Uh, I feel, I feel like, uh, should I even talk about this on the podcast that I feel
like it's weird that like, that like attendance is down and I don't know why is this, is this
too real?
I mean, if it's, if it's true to life, then you may as well say it.
If you, if you think that I have, I think I have said this.
I don't know if I've said this on the podcast, but I've said this to you guys.
Is that I genuinely don't understand why someone wouldn't show up to be on the podcast.
It is a, it is objectively a good use of one's time.
I never feel bad about it.
I always feel good about it.
I always make a point to show up because it's worth it because it's not a mistake.
But everyone else, everyone else, I guess I, I'm like one of the few people that feel
this way because people voluntarily like, nah, I'm not going to be on the podcast.
Why?
I, I do not understand why anyone makes that decision.
I don't know.
That's all I can say about it.
It doesn't make any sense to me.
Yeah.
I, I, I, it's hard to, to like, I'm, I'm sure on a, on some level it's just, I don't want
to be on the internet today.
Like if, if they, if they perform badly, I'm going to get bad comments.
People are going to say, fuck you.
Like I'm not sure.
I'm sure people aren't like running away from that specifically, but like if you don't
need to embarrass yourself by making, making, making a podcast and being like, then I don't
know.
Do you feel, do you feel like you embarrass yourself on the podcast?
I feel like by the nature of being an internet man, it is embarrassing inherently.
I kind of, I kind of know what you mean, but I feel like that ship has sailed and there's
no like unembarrassing myself at this point.
There's nothing I can really do.
Like the people like hearing me talk.
So yeah, I'll talk, whatever.
Some people fucking hate my guts apparently and it's like, well, you know what, I'll keep
talking.
I'll keep talking every day, every week.
You got to, you got to show the haters.
You got to show them that they're not going to get you down.
Yeah.
Fuckers.
Um, I, I, I don't know.
I just, I just don't, I just don't know what went wrong.
Um, remember my little pony?
Dude, I fucking do.
I do remember my little pony.
I was, that was like a pretty good show.
I had like jokes for adults too.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
It had like, it had like adult humor, like sex on screen as my favorite parts.
It had like, it had like, remember the episode where it was just, you just went on Derpy
Buru and we're just, just jacking off, just jacking it to porn, to porn on the pornography.
I liked that one a lot.
I did watch that Jenny Nicholson, uh, Brony Khan, death of a fandom video.
Oh, had you not, had you, had you not seen it before?
No, I hadn't had a chance, but I love it.
I love that video.
It's great.
It's like reminiscing with an old friend about the good old days.
It is.
It's like, I, I like all of the, all of the, I mean, I feel like we probably made a PCP
about Brony Khan, but.
We did.
I, I love the atmosphere and the, and the, the, like the unabashed, like cringy embracing
sincerity of everyone there.
It's like, wow, I don't ever think I could ever be in a place like that again with people
who are like not cynical at all.
Yeah, right.
It was, it was cool.
I liked that too.
Uh, and it's gone forever.
It's gone forever.
Nothing gold can stay.
We just have to, we just have to make my little pony too.
We just have to create the next, we have to be the Lawn Foust.
You don't, I mean, nobody owns it anymore, right?
Like if the show ended and now the name is just like free and anyone can use it, right?
That's how that works.
We could, we could be the change we want to see in the world.
We could just make it again.
We could just remake it again in HD.
Yeah.
We don't even have to do any work.
We could just find the files and upload them and we made it again.
We could be like, we could go on 4chan and be like, Hey guys, I hear they're releasing
this show about ponies.
Uh, uh, wouldn't it be ironic if we went and watched it?
Uh, and everyone will fall for it.
They'll climb and sink it.
Yeah, yeah.
We just do it again.
Here we go again.
We could, we could literally just do it again.
Like we wait a few like generations until like the 4chan user base is a different bunch
of people.
We just, we just wait, we just wait until like everyone who's currently alive dies.
And then when there's a new crop of people, we just do it again.
We're like 98.
Hey guys, Hasbro, Hasbro made this new show, what do you think?
We can look this up.
We know what this was.
It was like, Oh no, we failed.
We waited for 19 years and it didn't work.
We fucked up.
It was a foolproof plan up until we did it.
Uh, but we can't know it won't work.
You can never go back.
You can't.
You can't reclaim the past.
It's gone.
Uh, only the future remains only the, only the nightmare, only the nightmare that is
the rest of our lives awaits.
Cool.
Yes.
2021.
Only the horrifying reality of the economic recession that we are facing on top of the
last one that didn't even end before.
I can't wait for COVID adult UK with their own recession to be hit with Brexit in October
and get double recession and be completely destroyed overnight because nobody was paying
attention to it.
And they forgot.
Are they, are they still going to do Brexit?
I mean, they're still doing it.
The last thing I remember was we have written it in law that this will happen and it is
final and it will happen on October the 30th.
That is it.
Okay.
And then the point of that was to pressure the rest of the nations into just getting
their shit together and saying, fine, let's have a deal.
And it was a gamble because the, they may not decide on a deal by that time.
When you say deal, what are the, what a kind of deal?
What do they want?
A trade deal and various other things related to like make a trade deal in order for them
not to Brexit.
No, a trade deal as in like, this is how we're going to organize trade from now on.
This is our new relationship between the UK and the EU.
This is how we're going to sort out, you know, the different allowed materials and how the
tariffs are going to work is all this paper work stuff.
And obviously the EU hates the UK for even doing Brexit.
Why are you doing this?
Or they say, fuck you, you fucking racists, you stupid idiots.
And we're like, wow, give us a good deal.
Yeah.
And, and I don't think this is going to happen.
So we're going to get, we're going to fall out of the EU with no deal as, as was, as
was, you know, thought about a many, many of a time.
If it's, I mean, if it's about like, if it's about like not looking weak or whatever, I
feel like UK, if they don't want to do Brexit now under these terms, I feel like no one
is going to blame them if they're like, listen, I know we said that.
But like, shit got really fucked up since then and we're going to rethink it a little
bit.
I definitely think that, that is like an excuse people will generally be like, yeah, okay.
I mean, COVID.
I mean, I would be like, yeah, of course, of course you changed your fucking plans after
COVID hit.
I mean, I hope so.
Yeah.
No, nothing, nothing will ever be the same.
There was a contingent of people, myself included for a little bit that was just like, I'm tired
of hearing about Brexit.
This has been going on for three years, going on for, just decide, like make it final.
Don't have it be hanging over the heads, over our heads anymore, because the, the uncertainty
of it was already affecting business.
It was already making the pound devalued.
It was fucking us up before anything had happened, just the idea of it.
And it has been like that the whole time is like, we have to make a decision and every
decision is bad.
And it's just, it's a nightmare that will continue to be relevant for years to come
whenever it does like, quote unquote, happen finally.
So it's like, it's just like, it's, we've already been fucked over here.
And then the whole world is also fucked.
It's like a double fuck.
We're getting fucked involved.
We're getting fucked at the same time.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, um, you, it'll always like, until you break, until Brexit happens, it'll
always be like on the table, like, unless you do it, like the option to do it will always
remain.
Right?
Yes.
So, I don't know.
If you don't want it, if it's bad, then you probably shouldn't do it.
Well, yeah, it probably doesn't, it probably doesn't, yeah, it doesn't make, it doesn't
make any sense to me.
But I'll definitely be voting for whoever's trying to not have it happen because I, right.
I don't want this anymore.
I did.
Yeah.
Uh, oof.
Ah, cringe.
It's just a thing, it's just, it's just, it's just something that popped into my head.
It was like, oh wait, yes.
Even before all this, there was a terrible thing going to happen this year.
Yeah.
Uh, uh, and then, yeah, and a fucking Super Tuesday happens.
I feel, I feel a little bit the same about Bernie losing the primary.
That was, that was a nightmare.
I guess you guys had the same kind of thing with Corbin.
Yeah.
Uh, she was, she was already pretty bleak.
She was already pretty bad, in my opinion.
When are we going to die?
I'm tired of all this shit.
At least, at least we can, uh, make content and distract ourselves.
At least we can make, put funny videos and podcasts out on the interwebs and pretend
that we're going to have a future.
I, I think that I consume too, I consume too much content.
I watch too many like fucking like people telling me about a thing on YouTube videos.
Yeah.
I do.
It's, it's bad.
I, uh, I, uh, I, I listen, I listen to people repeat my opinions back at me too much and
I don't really get anything out of it except annoyed, except annoyed that they're like
famous for thinking the same thing that I do and I'm not even though they told you about
it.
Yes.
Yeah.
And it doesn't make any sense because like, yeah, I learned these things from you.
So like, of course you get the credit for saying it, like what, I didn't do anything,
but I'm still like, I agree with this.
Why don't people, why don't people know me as the guy who thinks this thing?
Uh, I'm a very, I'm a very, uh, very spiteful, uh, uh, uh, jealous person, a grasping, uh,
covetous goblin, uh, of a man, uh, and it's very sad.
Hmm.
Yeah.
I've been, I've been listening to a lot of just videos.
I recently, that H-bomber guy guy, I'd never really gotten into him cause he's a bit too
much of a wacky YouTuber on top of the, the stuff he talks about, but I, I got into a
few of his videos and I was like, you know what, yeah, yeah, he's, he's pretty good.
A lot of H-bomber guys videos are not like, yeah, a lot of them are just kind of too weird
and wacky and like lean too hard in the comedy bits and ways that don't really do it for
me.
Um, have you seen the one about control, all delete?
That one's really good.
Uh, I have not seen that one.
That's, that's probably my favorite H-bomb, uh, the one about pathologic, pathologic
is pretty good.
Uh, that one's not particularly wacky, uh, yeah.
The one's about like Sherlock, I don't like cause I don't know anything about Sherlock
and I don't want to.
I, I enjoyed that one mostly because of his, um, his Doctor Who analysis, which I am very
much interested in and I'm like, yes, of course, all of these things he's saying about the
showrunner makes sense when I think about those episodes that I watched and how I don't
give a shit about those particular series.
Yeah.
I don't know anything about Doctor Who, so it's not for me.
It's not for me, man.
My dude, my dog, my brooch, bleh, H-bomb, I don't know, I have mixed feelings about H-bomb.
I guess he's okay.
He's fine.
Yeah.
He's not my favorite.
He's okay.
He's, he's great.
He's my best friend.
I love him.
Mwah.
And kiss him.
Yeah.
Like, I, I, I've, I only watch YouTube videos at the weekends now because of Cold Turkey.
I blocked it completely.
Um.
You're so, you're so, you're so like, um, I can't believe you stick with the Cold Turkey
thing.
If I would cheat, I would cheat with Cold Turkey all the time.
The only reason Cold Turkey is so effective is because it's very difficult to cheat.
You cannot, you cannot change a setting during a block period.
Um.
Yeah.
You cannot change the block while it's, it's running.
And I have it running 24 hours a day, five days a week.
So if, if I want to, on the weekend, I can decide to let myself, you know, change it
up.
I can change it up during the weekend.
Yeah.
But I just forget and I don't really give a shit because I can get through basically
all of the YouTube videos of the week during the weekend.
Just binge it.
Like, ah, yeah.
TV time.
Relax.
Yeah.
Just do nothing in particular and, and watch this garbage and I'm like, hmm, that was
tasty.
Well, it's all gone.
I don't really need YouTube anymore.
So I'm okay with it being gone for the next week.
I have just been, I have just been having fucking red letter media videos just on in
the background.
Just constantly.
We've all been there.
Yeah.
Uh, there, there's never not one going, there's never not a best of the worst on and I don't
know.
It's, it's like, uh, it's, I don't even, I don't even see it or hear it anymore.
It's just, it's just the soundtrack of my life.
It's not even diegetic.
What you should do to like make it so absurd that you realize what is happening to your
life is open like five to six of those types of videos at once and just bask in the cacophony,
the noise that is generated from all these people talking about movies or whatever.
And then you'll be like, oh my God, this is what I've been doing all day, but like all
at once.
Yeah.
I see.
I don't even, I don't even like movies.
It's weird.
But I don't, I don't think I like movies very much.
Like I'm not interested in them.
I haven't even seen Avengers Endgame or the first one.
The Avengers Thanos attacks.
Munchy and Kazi were trying to get me, they were trying to convince me or they were talking
about watching, um, hereditary.
And I was like, uh, I don't want to watch hereditary.
And they were like, no, you should.
It's good.
And I was like, no, I don't think it is because like I watched, um, they got me to watch Midsommar
and like Midsommar is a good movie.
It's a well-made movie, but I didn't like it.
I didn't enjoy it.
And I feel like my life is worse since having watched it because sometimes I will think about
the things that happen in that movie and they'll make me sad and upset.
Yes.
I've heard that it's very gory and scary and will make you upset and poop your pants.
It's yeah.
It's, uh, it's just upsetting and, and, uh, I don't like thinking about it.
And my life is worse that I, that I have the memories of its events.
And so I'm like, I don't want any more of that.
I feel like this is like pussy shit.
I'm describing like pussy shit opinion that probably like, I don't know, I mean horror
movies are, you don't need to enjoy them.
I get scared.
I get scared by like fucking jump scares in Resident Evil one.
I still do, even though I know they're happening.
When the dogs jump through the window, I like clench the controller so hard I snap it in
two and I can't play the game anymore.
Every time I'm, I'm extremely easily scared and I just like a little moth flies in front
of me and I'm like, I spazz them out and I need, I need to kill it.
I go into a, you know, you go into a beast mode.
So it's like, I'm not good with scary things.
So I don't watch horror movies and that's perfectly epic from my perspective.
I'm not, I'm not good with scary things and I'm prone and I'm prone to dwelling on unpleasant
thoughts and it hurts my mood.
It makes me unhappy and I'm like, I should probably, why not, why not limit the amount
of those things that I can dwell on?
It's just, it's just not for me.
The, the, the horror movie experience is not for me.
I don't get anything out of it.
I think I've decided.
It's funny when you are the scary person and you are scaring other people, but when you
are the one who is being scared, it is not good.
Um, yes, I like to cause harm rather than receive it.
I like to be the goblin in the dark to just, to jump out.
Here's, here's a fun give and take lore fact.
One time, um, we're, uh, me and my brothers were on holiday and the, there was this big
old field and it was dark.
It was pitch black around the country.
Um, and I ran away from this like garden lamp, this, uh, out by the patio, there was
a garden lamp and it was illuminating like a circle and it felt like a video game is
like, oh, the light only goes this far beyond that is completely dark.
So if I run into that darkness, I'm invincible.
I mean invisible and, and so I ran into the dark.
My brother, little, little baby at the time, you know, I was like 12 or something.
He was like, oh no, he's gone and he didn't want to call me like he didn't, doesn't have
an object permanence.
It's like a complete idiot.
12 years old.
He hadn't figured it out yet.
Okay.
So I was like, okay, strategy time.
He thinks that I left.
How am I going to defeat my baby brother?
Yes.
How am I going to best scare him and kill him?
He saw me run out of the, the circle of light, uh, in this direction.
He thinks I'm still in that direction.
I will circle around hoping that the light can't reach me.
And I was right.
He, he didn't know where I was.
He was completely blind and I got to the side of him and I jumped at him like a werewolf
in Bloodborne.
Um, and he screamed and it was the funniest thing I'd ever done.
In my life.
And that's, that's my story.
That's my gibblor.
I scared my real brother by jumping out of the darkness.
Did he ever forgive you?
I don't think he was terribly scared or traumatized by it, but if he was, he has never told me.
He's never told me if that was the case.
I mean, we're definitely, we're definitely cool, but like it would be funny if like in
the back of his mind, every, you know, every so often he wakes up in a cold sweat, thinking
of, of me, beast man.
Yes.
Excellent.
Uh, uh, I mean, I used to, I used to torment my little sister.
I would put her on a swing.
We had a, we had a swing, like a, like a disc on a rope.
You know what I'm talking about?
Like a disc that you would sit on.
Yeah.
I know.
One of those kinds of swings.
And I would like, she would get on it and I would grab the rope and I would like,
plant my heel in the ground and just like spin around as fast as I could, uh, uh,
terrorizing her and traumatizing her.
Uh, uh, and it was cruel and unusual.
Uh, but what are you going to do?
Not do it.
No.
Shut up.
Wrong.
Did you traumatize Nate?
Um, uh, I mean, we were close, we were closer in age.
So he was not as easy to tear, you know, it's, it's only, it's only cool if you're
terrorizing like a literal baby who is totally defenseless and can't fight back.
That's the only way I get off on it.
You know what I mean?
Based.
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
Um, so, you know, being mean is pretty good and I hope people, people do it more.
Yeah.
In the comments, be as mean as possible.
If go, go find someone who's defenseless and can't fight back, do something cruel to them
and then tell us about it in the comments and tell us about how good and how much of
a big man it made you feel like.
Yeah.
I went into the store and I coughed on everyone and I gave them all COVID they'll show them.
Free speech, baby.
Uh, fuck yeah.
Did you watch, um, you watch the, the brownie video, did you watch the, do you watch other
Jenny Nicholson?
Have you seen her other stuff?
I, I just, I, uh, very occasionally it's, it's not usually subject matter I'm interested
in.
I watched that one about like the worst reality show ever, which was interesting.
I like, I really like all of her videos or all the ones where she like talks about a thing.
Um, she has a new one out about like her trip to go and get a giant spider plush.
That video is great.
I love that shit.
I love, I really like, I like the idea of a giant spider plush.
It's a lot.
It's, um, it's the one from, um, it's a big giant, like limited edition plush.
It's the one from Lord of the Rings, I think, or is it a Harry Potter, whatever it's.
Aragog or Shilob.
Yeah.
It's one of them.
They're, they're interchangeable.
They're just big brown spiders.
Wait, Aragog.
Aragog is Harry Potter.
Oh, that's the one in the woods, right?
Yeah.
Follow the spiders.
I'll, I'll eat you Hagrid raised me that guy.
Yes.
Great.
Spectacular.
Uh, that's right.
That's right.
I'm a Harry Potter whiz kid.
Not a wizard.
Um, fucking millennial.
I've probably listened to Harry Potter so many times because my mom had the audio books
or she would, she would borrow the audio books from the library and she would just play them
in the car like all the time.
So I've heard every Harry Potter book like multiple times.
Uh.
Oh, Harry.
Oh, cool.
Uh, Jim Dale had a very weird way of speaking.
And I remember his like weird inflections and the way he would say, cool.
I do not know that one.
I had the Stephen Fry version.
It's so weird that they, they got Jim Dale to do the voice in America and not Stephen
Fry.
Cause like they're both English.
Why did they get just get another English guy to do it for the American release?
It doesn't make any fucking sense.
Maybe they, maybe the producer was like, I want to give two of my friends a paycheck
or something.
Maybe.
I don't know.
They're like, oh, Stephen Fry is a homosexual.
That won't play in America.
That might actually be it.
It might actually.
I don't know.
Possibly.
I think people like Stephen Fry over here.
Do people know about him from anything?
I do.
He might not be as famous over here.
No, Stephen Fry is a household name.
Everyone knows that fucking guy.
That's my opinion.
Ow.
Uh, you know what?
Hey, let me tell you something I'm worried about.
I'm worried about copyright, not copyright.
I'm worried about a demonetization because in, because, you know, my, my, the biggest
video I've ever made in terms of reach was Sonichu.
You know, it's a million views.
It's incredible.
Yep.
So I'm, I'm, you know, I'm hoping that a Sonichu 102 gets a lot of views, gets a lot
of play, you know, makes me some AdSense revenue.
But there are Nazi Sonichus and I do talk about the Nazi Sonichus and I'm worried that
just saying the word Nazi in the video will get it demonetized.
Could you not like just look up what words like surely people have figured out by now?
Um, I did, I did Google it and I found on a thing about like which words in the title
will get it demonetized.
But that's not the same.
Like nobody really knows for sure.
And like I've heard people, yeah, I've heard people bleep out words like Nazi and stuff
and in, in, like in the video because they're worried that just saying it in the video will
get demonetized.
So I think it is a thing that happens, but I don't think anyone really understands
like, well, I think it's kind of random and it would be, it would, it would be very sad.
I'd be very upset if like I, I, I upload it unlisted.
It says good for monetization.
It goes, I put it out, it's out there for a while and then at some point in the future
it's like no demonetized because you say the word Nazi.
And I'm like, how could imagine like knowing YouTube that would happen.
Yeah.
I think it's better, better to be safe than sorry.
Just get some, some way to explain what word you're saying without saying it.
Maybe an image on screen, just flash up.
So that it gets past the sound barrier or whatever they, they call it.
I would hate to, I would hate to like censor that word for no reason.
You know, it would be very embarrassing to be like overly cautious about it.
I just, I just don't want YouTube to fucking not pay me.
I, I just don't want them to steal my fucking money.
I don't think it would be too embarrassing.
I mean, you're taught, you're doing a school lecture about Sonichu.
Oh, it's already, it's already very funny.
Like people aren't going to be like, oh my God, this guy has no integrity.
He censored the word Nazi.
What a pussy.
I mean, yeah, but I'm not, I mean, yeah.
I mean, it's strictly, I'm motivated strictly by money.
I'm motivated strictly by self-interest here.
Yeah, do it.
I'm not doing, I might, yeah, I might do that.
Be the, be the based coward that has hundreds of thousands of dollars.
Be the worthless baby that you want to see in the world.
Maybe I will be the money baby.
It would be, it would be incredible.
It would be incredible if Sonichu wanted to did numbers like the first,
I'm sure it won't do as, as many numbers as the first one.
I mean, it took the first one like three years to hit a million.
Man, if I had two million view videos, I would be set for life.
I would never have to, I would, I would quit the podcast because I'd be like,
ah, fuck that.
No, it's not even worth my time.
I'm too fancy.
Oh, then it would just be the give talks about absolutely nothing in particular for an hour.
What a, what a fucking sucker.
What a fucking sucker still on the podcast, still doing this shit.
Still doing the podcast, getting all of the money from the Patreon.
Give me a, give me a break.
You got to, you got to fucking, you got to get on my level.
You got to make a fucking son, just make another son, just,
just re-upload the Sonichu lecture and get the million views.
Yeah, just mirror it.
That's how it works.
Mirror it.
Just mirror it.
Like zoom in on me, the, the, like, like, whenever I'm seen,
that's like a point to the red arrow point to myself.
I wrote everything you're saying.
Just, just a download or like screen record the, the, the, the 3D camera version,
the 360 degree camera version.
But just all the footage is just, just the cameras focused on you.
But it's the same.
Yeah.
Okay.
So that's the plan.
That's how I'm going to get the, that's how I'm going to get demonetized on YouTube.
It's, it's, it's bullshit.
It's bullshit that I even have to worry about it.
It's bullshit, yes, but YouTube is no longer like any kind of like prestige platform.
It's, it's like a, it's like a sludge hut.
It doesn't matter that it's like not like super crisp and clean and perfect in every way.
It's, it's content.
People eat it by the bucket load.
They're not going to worry about it.
Yeah.
True.
Man.
Shit.
I feel like I had another thing I wanted to bring up, but it's gone.
La-Mow.
Um, we can go to voicemails.
We've been going for an hour.
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
Did you, did you said she was going to jump in?
Yeah.
Did you was in the chat.
I was kind of, but that was like 45 minutes ago.
I was kind of hoping she would jump in and then I would talk to her about gender stuff.
And that would be like some sort of a dialogue, a conversation, but she, she was eating something.
And how long does it take to fucking eat brunch?
Also, who eats brunch?
And also it's 3pm.
It's too late for brunch.
Everything's wrong.
Yeah.
You get linear with what I'm seeing here this time.
It's fucked up.
Second brunch fist.
Uh, yeah.
Let's, let's, oh, I need to open up the, let's fucking do it.
Speak pipe.com slash, uh, the procrastinators.
Is it that simple?
Um, I mean, I just, I'm logged in.
No, I mean for the viewers.
So if you want to post your voicemail, where do they go?
Oh, PCP voicemail.
That's what it is.
Speak pipe.com slash PCP voicemail, send in your voicemails and we'll listen to all of
them and we'll cringe if it's cringe and we'll base if it's based.
We'll dab of its base and we'll thrash of its cringe.
That's my promise to you.
The viewer.
Okay.
You got it.
You looking at them?
Yep.
All right.
So first one.
First up.
David from Ohio.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, procrastinators.
My name is David.
I'm six years old and I'm from.
Ohio.
Now there's, there's only two things I love in life and that's apple juice and Jake Paul.
So the other day I asked my mom to get me some Jake Paul merch, but then my, my, my stupid
older brother, Timothy told her, no, Jake Paul's bad.
And so now my mom won't get me any Jake Paul merch.
So my, my question is to the procrastinators is what is their opinion on the aggressive
marketing towards children that most upper echelon YouTube channels have taken in recent
years like Jake Paul with their marketing tactics towards children.
Thank you guys.
Okay.
Good question actually, but I think stick to the apple juice kid.
I think the answer is pretty simple.
YouTube.
I mean, children on YouTube have always been like a massively numerous like viewer base
and therefore they also, they watch ads because they're stupid.
And so it's also extremely lucrative for, for YouTube is in general to appeal to kids
in some way.
Yeah.
Like like game theory and stuff.
Kids are, kids are easy, easily impressionable.
They're easy to convince to do things.
But I think because the YouTube has been like sued or something, I forget exactly what
the terminology was, but they, they're not allowed to advertise to children anymore.
So merchandise is the next best thing to get the children's money is, is my thoughts.
Are they not allowed to advertise to children?
That doesn't seem like an enforceable rule.
Well, do you not remember the whole thing?
It was like.
No, I remember the whole thing about like, is this video appropriate for children?
And you have to, yeah.
I mean, it's quote unquote, not enforceable.
YouTube just makes it so that you can't monetize it.
If it's, you have to say whether it's for kids or not.
And if it's like for kids, you cannot monetize it whatsoever.
Wait, really?
That's, that's, that's the point.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
That's the system they came up with.
And the idea is if you lie about that, if you have videos that are marked as not for kids,
if you have them, yeah, marked as not for kids, but you are clearly getting a child audience on those videos.
I guess I don't know how they would like tell whether you are deliberately being child friendly or not.
I think they, they had a weird list of parameters like bright colors, appealing visuals, like stuff like that.
So stupid.
But if they decide that you are breaking the rules, they can take your channel down or something.
And that was a big controversy for a while.
But I don't think anyone has been affected by it at this point.
I've seen some people have their videos demonetized because they were marked as like child friendly.
I've seen some people complain about that on Twitter or whatever.
So it's like you, you can't appeal to children anymore.
Even though you might, you may just happen to and, you know, whatever.
But now I think merchandise is like the way to get the children to spend money.
I mean, I mean, they're still stupid.
Jake Paul was aggressively marketing his merchandise before that happened.
I think it was just like a natural progression of like, well, if kids are my audience,
because it's the most lucrative thing to be kids also want things.
And they say, mommy, daddy, can I have this please?
And parents are like, fine, I don't care.
I don't like you.
I don't know.
I mean, I think it's bad.
Like, I think it's bad that like kids are being aggressively marketed to, but like, that's nothing new.
Like that's just, that's just capitalism.
That's just like in a world where you want to make as much money as possible.
Children are like a vulnerable market that is like easily swayed and easily convinced to do the things that you want them to do.
So like, I don't know, it's bad, but like, what are you going to do about it?
It really is funny to think that like the natural reflex of a child to cry when they are upset is a lot of the reason that merchandise even exists.
What do you mean?
Because parents don't like to have to listen to their child whining so they will cave in.
That's the whole reason selling things to children works because they don't have money, but they can cry.
And their parents are like, I don't want to listen to that shit.
I'll buy you the fucking thing.
And that like that desperation from all the parents is the thing that is is feeding the economy.
It's like parents being tired.
That's the that's the that's the money maker.
I guess that's probably part of it.
Yeah, true, true.
Uh, uh, fucking.
I don't know.
Merchandising is bad.
Jake Paul is bad.
The kids are stupid.
Apple juice is good.
Stick to the apple juice.
That's my opinion on on that.
Next one.
Yep.
Okay.
Aged eggnog.
Three, two, one, go.
Yo, what's up?
It's me.
Aged eggnog.
So like y'all, I've got a shitty podcast with a weird community around it.
And I recently made some aged eggnog for Christmas.
Put it in a bunch of Mason jars.
And the first thing I did, what happened when I posted is one guy in my discord saying, Hey, yo, dude, that's like, come, I drink nine jars of your comb.
So yeah, what do you do when you're confronted with something like this?
Like, should I ignore it?
Is it good to embrace it?
It's pretty fucking weird.
I kind of hate it.
Thanks.
What the fuck?
I mean, if it's pretty fucking weird and you kind of hate it, tell him, well, actually, I guess the answer is a little nuanced.
Try to ignore it.
Don't encourage it for sure.
I'm confused.
Is the problem that this guy is like, is he like continually harassing you with like that aged eggnog looks like, come, I want to drink the come.
Is that it?
Because like, this seems like something someone would say one time and like that would be it.
If they keep bringing it up, if they keep bringing it up, I don't know why that's weird and they should be banned.
Yeah, if it's just one off comment and you don't want to encourage more of them, just don't respond, I guess.
Yeah, which you've already failed at because you made this voicemail.
But aged eggnog, that's not real, right?
Like, that's a joke, right?
Like, you don't age eggnog.
I don't even know what eggnog is.
Is it like an alcoholic drink?
You fuck.
You don't know eggnog?
No, it's not a thing over here really.
You stupid motherfucker.
The first time I heard about it was reading a Simpsons comic and I was like, why would you drink eggs that doesn't make, that's disgusting.
That's fucked up. This is fucked up.
What are you drinking eggs for?
Eggnog, you monster, you're a criminal.
Eggnog is, it's a holiday drink.
It has like egg yolks and cream and I don't know, it's like some spices like nutmeg, I think, is the thing that gives it its flavor.
I love eggnog.
Eggnog is great.
You can put rum in it.
Sometimes you put rum in it and it's hard eggnog, but you don't have to.
And I don't think you age it because I think it would just turn into nutmeg flavored cheese.
So this has to be a meme.
Stop making aged eggnog.
It's fucked up.
It's unacceptable.
That's what I have to say about it.
Maybe you should try eggnog.
It's really good.
I love it.
My favorite part of the holidays.
Maybe I should come over to Boston for Christmas.
Fuck.
Yes.
The flu season and I'll catch COVID for sure.
It's like absolute guarantee.
Yeah, unironically do it based.
Yeah, come do American Christmas.
Yeah, fuck my own family.
You'll never go back to England.
You'll see the air of your ways.
Don't have eggnog, do in Brexit.
Nothing's good.
Yeah, I'll get out while I can.
Yeah.
Next one.
Rumpelpack 64.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben.
Yeah.
Well.
Okay.
I think he got us.
Is there is there going to be more?
Wait, there's 10 more.
There's six more seconds.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe I've been had.
He got us.
I can't believe he would waste 23 seconds of his life
just to just to get us.
I can't believe I fell for it.
I feel owned right now.
I should have seen it coming.
I want to know what Rumpelpack 64 meant.
What is Rumpelpack 64?
We'll never know.
God damn.
Jesus Christ.
Um.
Hey.
Before we before we do the next one.
Uh.
Yeah.
Did you happen to see.
Did you happen to see somebody posted a.
Somebody like, like composed.
A song.
I did.
I saw.
I saw the thing that didn't work in the voicemail.
And he posted it on another thing.
It was the dream thing.
Yes.
I will post.
I'll link in the description.
Link in the description.
Andrew Oaks.
Composed.
A.
My version of my dream song.
It's pretty cool.
It's, it's, it's nice.
It's got bells and whistles.
I think he did the.
Some of the melody to the way you sang.
That thing you sang.
I think.
Yeah.
That's cool.
I.
Okay.
Link in the description.
Check it out.
It's good.
It's funny.
Next one.
What's.
Soup.
But like the.
The SO is in parentheses.
So it's like what's so up.
It's two seconds long.
Okay.
Two seconds long.
Three, two, one.
Go.
What's soup.
Nice.
Next one.
You want to answer the question.
Do you have a response?
It's wet vegetables.
I guess.
Yeah.
True.
True that.
Next up.
Fuck voicemail.
God.
In quotation marks.
Three, two, one.
Go.
Hey voicemail.
Faggot.
What the fuck do you think you're doing?
Call up to you.
You submit a bunch of shitty goddamn voicemails about fucking persona and other shit.
Fucking die.
I don't want to hear your fucking voice on the goddamn voicemails ever again.
You son of a bitch.
You know.
He makes the good point.
He makes a compelling argument.
I wasn't quite with him until he screeched at the end there.
Yeah.
I was like, I'm not entirely convinced.
But then, but then I was convinced.
Never, never, ever send us a voicemail about persona five ever again.
None of us have ever even seen persona five.
That will get you fucking banned.
My friends.
I promise.
Voicemail God.
I don't know.
Fuck you.
I guess.
Next.
Next one is a bullshit, but not really.
Wink.
Three, two, one.
Go.
Howdy.
What do y'all think about the ration?
Do you know what the rational male is?
I don't.
But I can assume if he's talking about pickup artists stuff, then it is a mode of thinking
that is like, I am a man.
And this is my how I conduct myself in order to be a good man.
I don't really know anything about it.
So I can't really call it.
Oh, it's a, it's a book.
The rational male is a book.
Let's see if I can find a synopsis.
The rational male is about being as most based as possible and least cringe as possible.
In this 10 step guide, you will learn how to punch down.
You will learn how to.
The rational male is a, is a rational and pragmatic approach to intergender dynamics and the social
and psychological underpinnings of intergender relations.
The book is compiled, the book is the compiled 10 year core writing of author blogger, Rollo Tomasi
from therationalmale.com.
Rollo Tomasi.
Rollo tomasi.
Rollo .
Rollo Tomasi.
I can't make a judgment call yet.
I used to read stuff like this and I and like I'm all for I'm all for like
people like writing honestly about like what they think is up with like men and women and stuff
like like I'm all for like you know go discuss that discuss like how they interact with each other
discuss like you know what is successful and what is not successful that's that's all fine but like
in hindsight a lot of this stuff is very is very like um uh uh uh evolutionary biology in
like a pseudo scientific way a lot of this is very like presumes it presumes a lot about like
what is natural that is like not really based on it there's a lot of like there's a lot of um
ideology do you think it's like mostly anecdotal sort of stuff like from what a person can see
this is the the information they've gleaned as to how generally things work there's I think there's
a lot of like hidden ideology under the surface of a lot of this kind of writing that is that I
don't necessarily agree with there's a lot of presumptions about yeah like what it is to be male
or female or whatever um I'm you know uh I guess I I don't like fully hate this kind of stuff I
don't think this stuff should be banned or anything but I would like read it with skepticism read it
with a healthy grain of salt question question what is the thinking behind a lot of it is how I feel
about it now yeah yeah so that's how I feel it's like it's stupid bad voicemail no not really
no not really it's good thank you thank you for your call uh uh wink next one is uh ranting raw
wool three two one go do you like croutons on your salad no stop it croutons don't belong in salad
right that shit is designed to be eaten you spear all your shit with a fork and you just like
skewer everything you can't skewer a crouton because that shit is hard it's like yeah the
opposite texture of everything you want on the salad and it's like the only way you can eat it
is either you just like scoop that shit into your mouth like a barbarian or you scoop it up with your
fork but you don't scoop shit with your fork the fork is there to spear shit you're not eating
your salad with a spoon so croutons are just they don't belong in fucking salad Jesus fucking
if you spear if you spear some lettuce with a fork then you have a big leaf on your fork
and the crouton can just kind of be like held on the leaf you don't need to individually spear
the the crouton the crouton can just kind of be like caught up in the fork load of stuff
it's fine i like croutons they're good i've never had a crouton on a salad i think i've seen them
but like i think of croutons as a soup thing oh weird i think of them as a salad thing
do people put croutons in soup yeah like a soup or like a stew or something
actually maybe not a stew i guess i could see it they sort of soak up the the moisture and they
they lose their crunch but not too much of the crouton you gotta eat it at a certain time it's
like cereal you can't let it get too soggy did you did you listen to the ben cast voicemail
anarchy oh i didn't i heard about the things that that happened in it with there was a lot of salad
a lot of salad questions a lot of salad questions hopefully we've um i had thought that we had
solved all our salad problems but i guess there are some dissenters out there uh still got a bone
to pick an axe to grind a fork to skewer uh next one do wane sua three two one go
hey pcp just wanted to say i appreciate everything you do i think it's great yeah especially uh
recently thank you i've been helping me through these tough times um and so one thing that resonated
with me a lot was i guess gib's idea about having to engage with the cringe to uh you know understand
the the based reality beneath it um so i just i guess i had a question like how important do
you think it is to recognize the cringe within yourself you know either in the past or in certain
aspects of yourself that that you know might be cringe in some ways but they are like they make
up what you are so you just got to roll with it i don't know just a thought but keep up the good
word guys anyway um i i would say that it's it's really just like a terminology is like funny
right but the the the point of that is is sort of to not take yourself too seriously if you find
the cringe things about yourself and it's just learning to laugh and learning to like
self-deprecate and it being okay like nobody's perfect i don't think you can be based unless
you understand your own yeah like like there's nothing more like and i like super cringe than
someone who is terrified of like a really innocuous fact getting out into the public and they're
trying to like cover it up it's like it doesn't really you don't have to like spill the beans on
everything you've ever done that is stupid but if you have like things that are like pretty obvious
and you accept them and laugh about them then you're laughing with everyone else and it's not
cringe it's based absolutely 100 agree uh so yeah that's it how important is it to recognize your
own cringe very it's true it's critical uh it's it's gender critical it's it's it's jk rallying
uh lamal uh no yes um violently jerking off to reruns of frazier three two one go
hello it is i the former sensei of beno sento some kind of reader
beno why did you join no antifa stop you say because i'm better
amades antifa communist why are you want to amades this is a lie you left for the sweet
to antifa boy of pussy yes so you did okay until you next time what would there be a next time
why do you keep asking you keep you keep asking me the same question
well have you answered it yet no i no and i know why ben i don't owe him i don't owe him any
explanation why did you join antifa i saw the application form i don't i don't i do it's not
your business it's none of your business i um i just uh i just wanted to dad stop calling me was
it because you saw an acute antifa girl is that it no no no uh uh you know you know it makes me mad
you know speaking of cute antifa girls you know who it makes me really mad what uh i think i think
i've been seeing i don't know if i'm crazy i don't know if i'm imagining it but i think uh i think uh
uh shoe on head and uh and ash b coffin i think i've seen them like flirting on twitter i think
they're like gonna fuck each other and it makes me really mad it makes me really mad um because
they're they're because you want to fuck ash they're both they're both pretty cute and what how can i
compete in a world where they can just fuck each other how can i compete oh are they both women
yes okay i was i was trying to make a lol ben is gay joke but i didn't know who the other person was
ash b coffin is a female woman oh wait no i've seen her she's got ginger hair she's uh yes brave
literally uh what what a world what a world women should be illegal that's what i think
okay on that note uh no i know what you're feeling i know it's it's it's sad when it's like this like
the nightmare but you're finally you know you're doing the thing where you're strutting your stuff
and you're like hey ladies i'm trying to get laid you hear about that and and then they're like
hear about that and then they're like um sorry we're we're taken by each other and you are
completely out of the picture and it's like well what the fuck am i supposed to do about what am i
supposed to do about this huh that's not that seems a little that seems a little unfair i don't
know it's not like that other women i i really feel like you actually owe me some sex right now uh
so please stop this stop this nonsense get out of this phase you're in uh please give me a kiss
okay you can't do that to to the ben that's a sexual harassment that is it's sexual harassment
for you to fuck each other instead of me um makes me feel bad uh sexually that's cuckledry which i
think is illegal um okay so that's fine that's my opinion about uh this so that's so in short
that's why i joined antifa um po next up po po dead cast question mark uh three two one go is the
body cast dead i think you already answered this one yes it's not dead um due to like nate moving
and just various things it was just gone for a while uh basically an entire month i think
almost an entire month but now we're we're back we're gonna do this base uh next one property
taxes are immoral three two one go property taxes are the most immoral form of taxation that exists
as they reduce the population to nothing more than serfs who can never truly own land and instead
are forced to simply rent it from the government discuss i agree do you agree do you think it's
the most immoral form of taxation uh i mean i was that what he said did you say the most um i think
he said the most well i don't know whether but you agree that they're bad yeah um i don't know
i feel like well i guess it depends on the property but you know what you know what i think i feel
like people should be able to to own land that they pay for part of me is thinking like okay
but owning land like the like land is a means of production in a way right like if you own land
you should theoretically be doing something with it should be using it for something um and they're
talking about land or just a building like i'm thinking of houses as land i'm making maybe that
doesn't count well i think i think the property tax is specifically on the land i think that's the
property and like a house is just something that may or may not exist on the property it might raise
the value of the property and if i'm not exactly sure how it works i guess you know if you're like
a fucking industrial producer or whatever and you own like a lot of land and you have like you own
like a factory or you're like you're like a farmer you own like tons of land you have like a big old
fucking fields and stuff and you're producing and you it's your livelihood it's your it's the means
of production i feel like you should be taxed on that i guess i would agree there's like cars
going crazy and honking out my window i don't know if you can hear it i can lol uh what is what is
what is going on oh it's just somebody's alarm okay whatever um i would agree that i think it's
kind of bullshit that you're taxed on land that is you just live on i guess i would say that there
should probably be like a threshold and it's like you can own up to this much land you know like
enough land for a person to live on and like beyond that you should be taxed on it i guess i
guess i would say that it would be better like that i'm so sorry for this fucking horn um what do
you think about that yeah i mean i haven't really i'm not like um well versed on on taxes and and
you know like i just hear that the the idea of money being taken from the by the government i'm
like no that's why i just generally dislike that but i understand that they need taxes in like a
hypothetical situation where like i don't know a bunch of guys own like an unbelievably a large
amount of land of a country and they just decide to not do anything with it and they could be farming
they could be creating resources for the people to to live off of but they just decide to just
not do that and then the the country just has no space left to make farms then it's like that's
unfair they clearly need to to get some use out of that land i like um i like the government
taking money from oh my god it just keeps going what is what is wrong with you what is fucking
wrong with you just throw rocks at it they're they're driving away they're driving away with
their alarms still going it sounds like they're it's not the owner of the car is driving away if
that's the case oh my god did i just witness a jacking i mean i don't know i don't know
dude what's the number plate say it out loud i don't know it's gone i can't see it anymore
it went behind a tree very strange um okay all right um i like the government taking money
from people who are making a ton of money off of stuff i don't like the government taking money
from people who are just trying who are just trying to live and so i agree i do think it's
kind of bullshit that like if you don't own a property you know you you rent you rent a property
you're paying your landlord whatever but even if you buy the property you still have to pay
what is effectively a kind of rent yeah to the government just to like live in a house that you
own i do think that's bullshit um you should you should you should you should be like especially
if you fucking pay the money i mean i think that housing is a human right and should be free uh
but if we're not gonna do that i think if you fucking buy it you shouldn't have to pay if it's
just for you to live on if you're just trying to do your thing and you're not like you're not using
it to like you're not use it's not the means of production that you're running a business or whatever
you're not using it for like industrial purposes you only own as much as you need to to live yeah
no i don't think you should be taxed on that that's bullshit it is bullshit i agree 100 uh unless
if you're a landlord you should be taxed on it uh but maybe you should just be taxed maybe it makes
more sense to just be taxed on your fucking rent revenue that you're making from the people that are
you're renting it to i don't know uh or wait or is that bad because then that would incentivize you
to raise your rent so maybe that would be a bad tax maybe you should just be uh oh whatever the
landlords not pay tax already they must i mean they must pay tax i mean they must pay the property
tax and they must pay the tax on their income which they get from renting so yes i'm i should
they be taxed more i don't know taxing the more we just raise rent uh oh fuck man what a sticky
what a sticky wicked part i don't know what to do i don't know i don't know how to solve this
problem short of just abolishing landlords which is what we should do lament yeah um but i guess
okay i think i've come down on the side of yes property tax is bad
unless you have a lot lament okay whatever i've talked enough about this uh next one
is yeah three two one go you know what i guess nate's gone mine's gone it's the perfect time somebody
gotta do it i'm pissing on the pocket no this is horrible this is a nightmare i hope you're pissing
on a dog i hope he's pissing on the dog you know what some he's right somebody had to do it
it doesn't sound like it was landing a toilet oh my god he's back he's fucking back why why is this
happening you should yell hey i'm podcasting here i am podcasting here why would you do why would you
come back he's driving away again where is he going where is he going that this problem will solve
itself you fool you absolute rube yeah get out of here get off my fucking street asshole what a piece
of shit what how embarrassing what a fucking maroon um all right thanks for peeing on the podcast
mr guy uh next one setting the record straight three two one go
look femboy a man who wears makeup or wear or wear men in clothing in order to appear more
feminine big men intentionally a trap is any man who could be mistaken as a woman excluding
trans a trans is a is a who takes pills and shit and tries to look female whatever
a food is a woman with a penis there is no ifs ifs or buts there's not a dude
can you understand any of this i i i got glimpses i think something went wrong with
this recording i don't know exactly what but it was very blippy and jumpy yeah that sucked that
he was saying something about the distinction between trans and food and trap and i'm like
okay whatever that's stupid who gives a shit uh okay next one uh i'm worried about you
three two one go okay this is an open message uh i don't think that this is shown the voicemail
got this i think there's someone else but who's ever leaving the fucking persona
in the 30 trillion uh streaming service piracy is bad actually uh gmail please make a friend
to please stop leaving voicemails please please please please okay if you want you can add me
on discord it's a bev uh hashtag uh three five six four okay please please please just stop leaving
voicemails i'll talk to you i'll be your friend to please just stop voicemails i'm begging your
parents are worried we're worried it's okay please make a friend thank you it's okay they've stopped
they've they've yeah they've they've given up they've given up uh lemal uh we we punish them into
submission uh next one is from uh bev but douzhing i think it's supposed to say bev but drunk uh so
let's hear that uh three two one go okay ben first off your racism did come across poorly
yeah i know i know i'm really wasted um and i'm just curious then uh how do you feel about drunk
voicemails broadly and how do you feel about being drunk uh thanks for all you do um i feel like
almost i should play this out more but i want uh cheers um nas drovia uh god bless i hope that's
a hard seltzer yeah yeah yeah yeah okay uh the the drunk voicemails can be funny um if we were
getting tons of them we would probably have to stop playing yeah but whatever as a rule they're okay
an occasional like incomprehensible wild drunk something or other would be like fun just because
we don't know what's happening but not all the time mm-hmm agree hard agree uh next one
poochie is hungry for beef oh wait wait what do you you said what do you think about being drunk
oh um when i do it i like it and then other times i'm like that was a mistake
and i don't like it like i'm hung over now and i wish that i wasn't so it was a bad idea
very very bad idea don't don't do it kids it's wrong and it's a sin god is watching
uh anyway what do you think about being drunk um i think that i can avoid it pretty easily and
i enjoy one beer occasionally i just be just a little bit going when when i drink i usually i'm
just like i mean i'm doing it i might as well go for it and then i fucking go for it bro if you if
you go for it every time then you'll run out of alcohol it's true i drank the whole i drank the
whole case i had drank the whole case of hard seltzer so you're you're not wrong um uh i don't
know when i'm it's i think it's fun to like get blasted yeah at a special occasion like a new
year's or just a party that hasn't you know you don't party that often getting you know with
friends it's like yeah that's that's a nice fun thing to do yeah just to get a little crazy
i wouldn't do it regularly no it seems like a really stupid idea that idiots would do yes
that's why i do it ooh a man um uh yeah you know i feel like i feel like um i didn't use to be
i use i used to like drink more responsibly i used to just like have a few and be like yeah
this is good this feels good uh i think um i've become a nihilist i think i'm just like i've
become more nihilistic and just like ah fuck it you know nothing matters uh uh just just
fucking down it just fucking lose yourself in the moment uh and uh and that's and that's why
i am like this now uh it's not good though it's not it's not great uh yeah that's all i
that's all i have to say about that uh poochie is hungry for beef three two one go hey poochie here
the guy who caught talking about beta may or sound pretty faggot to me why don't you bullet these
balls you fucking faggot hey what the fuck is he talking about Australian wrestler why don't you
hold back into your mother's pouch you can't do faggot hey think i'm talking about it should be
old max why don't you relax and suck a dick you fucking faggot okay i i couldn't understand a
lot of him but i think he was just started to make you starting beef with other voicemail we're
getting a lot of we're getting a lot of pushback this time against other voicemailers like the
the people are starting to revolt against the voicemail hierarchy they're going crazy down there
this is what happens when i when i declare anarchy it becomes it becomes open it's it's open
warfare it's it's house to house warfare um and i'm i'm i'm okay with it i'm here for it uh next
one the real reason piracy is bad apab three two one go it's like i was listening to this
latest episode of the pcp and this guy calls in with a voicemail about how piracy is bad because
it's illegal but but but but but see here's the thing right he has a point but it's not because
it's illegal well it's like like pick any piece of media right uh like just on my shelf we're on
my bookshelf right here that i'm looking at right now uh uh mostly harmless by douglas adams that's
the pirates are the bad guys in that like in in all media that where pirates exist uh like pirates
of the caribbean and uh like jack sparrow is the good guy assassins creed for one piece pirates
bad guys all of them what is this guys it's bad i don't know if this is a parody it's it's a joke
it's just like very badly delivered i don't under yeah okay well that was a waste of a minute in a
second all pirates are bad i think is the acronym he's going for definitely um that sucks die voice
jail i think i'm i'm thinking i'm thinking apab do we want to put apab and voice jail yeah it was
terrible apab we gotta we gotta show like like make an example of someone occasionally yeah we
gotta make an example of someone speaking out against crime by putting him in jail that's what's
gets you fucking locked you're locked up apab you're done you're out of here the pirates have the
access to the the penal institutions everything flips the pirates pirates have skeleton keys
that could unlock your jail your cell door but because you spoke out against them they won't
use it to get you out so you know i hope you've learned a valuable lesson here today uh uh
better luck next time jack okay next one is called nate's podcast three two one go since
nate and digi left to go make the new rival faction known as content in the pcp universe
it's now ben's podcast um it was never nate's podcast uh nate was nate was our accountant
he was he was around a lot and he seemed to be in control because of his it is uh
uh booming makismo and he's like hello it's me nate the best guy ever i'm the king he said
every time uh nate was our civil servant nate worked for us uh uh which he still does i mean
he still does the accounting uh it was never it's nobody's podcast it is uh it is a it is
an anarchy podcast it is a worker co-op uh it is jointly owned uh it is uh it is uh we're selling
we're selling shares actually we're going public we're selling shares on the stock market invest
now we're going to the moon uh but uh yes but it is my podcast now that's right i own it now
i think it's no no no no no no i think i think you'll find it's my podcast i think that i bought
it for zero dollars best best i ever spent okay next one pancakes drunk ben is not base oh no
all right three two one go hi pancakes here listen before we start ben we worry about you yeah we
worry about your safety that's right all right this whole drinking thing you know it hurts uh the
children think about the children ben do you ever think about them i don't think so i don't i'm sorry
made threats to you to people even me i mean look at this evidence
however scared you are you should be more scared because pancakes the thing about drunk ben is that
i promise that i will come to your house no and uh eliminate you was that me i rest my
sounded like it it sounded like munchie i thought it sounded like munchie too but i think it was me
and i don't know why i said that i think it must have been another time that i got drunk and munchie
asked me about pancakes and i don't know why he would do such a thing but it's the only thing that
makes sense but i don't know i kind of think that was a little based of me honestly making threats
i kind of think making threats is cool now death threats included especially i mean if you're
you're gonna if you're gonna be threatening you might as well go all the way with it why why half
acid i'm gonna break your leg say we'll half the way no it's just it's just like drinking if you're
gonna drink your elbow if you're gonna drink anything you should drink it all and if you're
gonna injure someone you should completely you should injure them 100% onto death why why do any
less uh is drunk ben based give drunk but come on he's pretty big he's pretty big i mean i have
not seen drunk ben in person enough i want to see drunk ben in person i think i've seen you
tipsy but not like fucking like dead like i was pretty drunk i was pretty drunk at radcon the
first time that first night i was pretty you were pretty drunk that was pretty but but i feel like
nate was doing worse than you at the end during that first stream uh yeah i think that's true i
think that's true i did have to throw up though i mean there's that that famous gift of you
like okay explaining something explaining something to to nate who is sitting there like
no energy and like completely dead eyes like uh and i'm like spazzing out and like yeah that was
late into the night i think nate was done he didn't he seemed like he didn't he doesn't seem drunk
in that gift he's just kind of sitting there just like it was the aftermath of all that right um
okay well it's an open question as to whether drunk ben is based lamal uh next up next up give it to
me gay three two one go hi it is my goal to deal better with interrupting and getting interrupted
so suppose we're in a social or political conversation do you have a morality on talking
over someone in one of these situations which would be satisfied about your ability to get
your words across and do you ever seize back the topic after someone interrupted you how do
you do that respectfully i've learned to never interrupt i always let others finish also when
they're interrupting me now i never tell stories and also confuse people who thought i was finished
talking uh i i know this feel um sometimes i mean historically on the pcp i have started a story
and been interrupted by somebody thinking that my my point was uh over and that i didn't have
anything more to say and i couldn't wrestle wrestle back the conversation to to finish my point
occasionally when i got the chance i just forgot what i was gonna say and it sucks
unacceptable unacceptable someone should be punished for that yeah so uh i think in in a real
person real life conversation um you could use body language uh a little easier to like make it
clear that you you're not done or like i don't i don't think saying excuse me i wasn't finished
that's that's like sort of brings the room down yeah i think what you should try to do is if people
are trying to interrupt you you you like jump into the headline of your next point like if you're
trying to set something up if and they're not letting you set it up just go straight into the
weird thing that is the main point and and and then they'll be like wait what and then you can explain
afterwards if somebody explain the setup after the the punch if somebody interrupts you then like
it's automatically okay for you to interrupt them back um i i if if they sort of like psych you out
like you're talking they start talking and you continue talking and you both are talking at
the same time and you're sort of playing chicken like who's gonna stop and let the other person
speak first i think if you were the one talking already you're allowed to to snap and say shut
the fuck up i'm speaking yeah yeah uh i'm okay i'm not i'm not a opposed to interrupting all the
time i think if you like if you need okay if you're saying something and then someone else changes
the topic and you weren't done then i think it's okay to interrupt them to bring it back to what
you were gonna say i think that if someone is talking about something and you feel like you
have a really important point to me i think you know it's it's uh it's like it's bad form to interrupt
but i think if your point is actually good and relevant and like you need to say it right then
i think it can be okay to interrupt them and just like say what you want to say and and if it if it
is a good point then it justifies itself so it's kind of gamble it's a gamble if you make a bad point
that way then you look like an asshole i've noticed ben your way of doing that um uh is is to to repeat
the thing you had just been interrupted with louder really and just repeat it until you're
sure that you have the room again and then you continue the sentence because it's sort of like
annoying to hear but but just but just but just but just but just but just but just and and then
like you're all right fine i'll let you finish your thing you're clearly trying to say a thing
wait that's that's me i'm saying but just but just but just um i mean everybody does that to some
extent but like it is yeah i've noticed that you do it as well uh that's probably true that's probably
true uh when it when it comes to like a nate versus you thing you know you need to finish your point
you haven't finished it yet you you you do that i feel like nate interrupts me and i and i interrupt
him back and because of that people say that like we both are interrupted i don't think i'm that
interrupted i think i'm pretty good about letting people talk it's only when i get interrupted
or i i think i think that it's only when i get interrupted that i become interrupted back but i
don't know i i i don't think it's necessarily always that i think it's just when you haven't
quite got to the point and you're here is the the money shot here is the thing that i was building
to i gotta say it um i won't shut up even though you're trying to tell me to shut up by speaking
over me right well yeah and it's like yeah that makes sense it's it's a good tactic it works you
can't if you're if you're if you're on a roll if you're on a roll you can't let some idiot come in
and knock you off it you can't let some idiot redirect your momentum like that fuck you up ruin
ruin the climax you gotta you gotta go for it you gotta just barrel on to into the horizon do you
hear the horn again this fucking idea this fucking idiot is back is he just like is it his
current he's like why is the alarm going i i oh gosh oh gosh how embarrassing and he doesn't
know what he's doing i don't know but it stopped it stopped why is this a problem why does this
keep happening what a fucking more what a maroon anyway um anything else to say about interrupting
um don't be a honking car don't that guy is the worst about it that guy is cutting me off i was
building to something and he ruined it um okay next one she pollution about animorphs three two one
go hey tom just wanted to thank you for letting me know that animorphs is actually good only watch
the first bit of your lecture before deciding i'm gonna read it myself or listen to it actually
some company i've got a name is making audiobooks for all the books and the quality is really good
too bad it's gonna take ages before the audiobooks are made right now they only have the first 10
and i think the coronavirus delay the production i'm at book four now i do have some pet beefs like
why aren't they collecting tons of animal morphs right away but i can forgive those book three with
tobias was really really sad such a unique and interesting character study so yeah thanks a lot
too bad i can't read discussions and forums since i don't want to be spoiled but i'll get there cheers
uh man imagine reading animorphs i can't i've never seen it i mean i read i read animorphs when i was
in like second grade third grade or fourth grade or whatever like that that's that's the mark i don't
know an audio they're really short like an audit like 10 animorphs books like each one's gotta take like
fucking like two hours tops like they're only like 100 or 200 pages if that they're very small
um but that that sort of length makes me feel like i could just easily read it uh yeah they're
they're basically light novels i think that got said in the lecture um but uh the i don't remember
okay you say they don't you say why i don't i don't know if i should talk about it if i'm
going to spoil but i kind of thought that they do like one of the first things they do maybe not
immediately but there is sort of like an early arc where they go this is like right at the beginning
they go to the zoo and they get like they get some really good like like morphs right like they get
there they're iconic like rachel gets the bear and jake gets the tiger and marco gets the gorilla
and so on and so forth um do they have a finite a number of no no they can have as many as they
as they want i think so yeah i guess there really is no reason why they're not just getting like
getting as many as they can all the time they are a little bit i guess they're a little conservative
with it they're a little bit like they only get a new one if they're like hmm i need to
accomplish a specific task perhaps this animal would help me do so i must go find it out and
touch it and now i can do it yes yes i did narratively that would be the easiest way to
keep things fresh yeah instead of just like have like the first couple books is just like oh an ant
oh there's an ant in my room i gotta get the ant okay got it oh a spider oh i gotta get the
spider okay i got the spider oh oh there's a there's a bird i gotta shoot the bird in the
wing so it falls to the ground and they go and get it while it's not before it dies okay i got the
bird uh now another bird oh uh we could go we could go to a bird sanctuary or petting zoo we
could pet all the animals and get all things um you could swing with dolphins oh we gotta go do that
yeah yeah and then that's just the whole series it's like there like there is there is an alien
invasion happening but like they're not engaging with it at all they're just like going to like
meet animals like like no no i'm not ready i'm not ready to to fight them yet i'm not ready i need a
i need a silverback i need a i need a giraffe i gotta go to the aquarium i gotta go to the zoo uh
yes i'm gonna go find a killer whale brb yeah exactly uh boy oh boy so um good good job good
job reading the animals i guess uh the the i really liked the like side books like the side
story is like the andalite chronicles and the horkbezier chronicles and stuff they're like much
bigger and i thought those were fucking cool as hell uh but i don't know if i'm remembering the
lecture now it's so it's such a great little story it is all of that lore all that stuff is so
inventive strange it's just it's like a strange thing that these books exist and are the way they are
they're like fucking scary i don't know uh but it's cool it's cool shit uh uh all right next one
i think this is the last one is fuck three two one go fuck man she leaving the pcp just hit me
hard man um mage leaving was sad like mage just was already out when i started listening to you guys
but um man he's like three days um younger than me so now i feel that since he has left i will have
to fucking start doing something with my life too and it's too much pressure and i want to kill myself
and if you guys could also try to hold him back in life so he doesn't
spread his wings too much it would be appreciated spread his wings too much yeah we'll hold him back
just so that he you can be on a similar level to him i hate i i hate this attitude so much this
this really maybe i'm maybe i'm crazy maybe i'm like taking it too seriously but this this attitude
of like oh so and so left the podcast to go and like do because because they had something better
to do like because they had to spread their wings and move on to greener past like what greener
pastures like what are they doing instead what is anyone doing with their like two hours on a sunday
afternoon that is like so important that like being on the fucking podcast would have prevented
that from doing i know the answer it's nothing this is like a complete like this is like a total
like false perception but don't you realize ben that um we only exist on the podcast and we don't
do anything else besides this yes of course here i am on the podcast that is drawing rapidly to a
close at which point i will wink out of existence and cease to be until next friday at 2 p.m eastern
standard time at which point i will resume my existence in your ear and then and the cycle
will begin anew uh so i don't know the way the way that people talk about the way that people talk
about like people being on the podcast leaving the podcast it's see if it's very weird it's
saying they're leaving the fandom yeah it means so little yeah i agree to be on the
podcast is just to be present when the podcast is being recorded it doesn't mean necessarily
anything i mean i don't know munchy maybe his greener pastures in his mind but they're like
like then they have nothing to do with him leaving the podcast there's just
there's like he has things he wants to do with life and like two hours out of his week is not
going to be enough to stop him from doing that if he decided to stay on the podcast he just
prefers not to be on i'm gonna say it i'm gonna say it um being on the pcp is like such a like low
commitment thing it is like such an easy thing to do i actually kind of feel like not doing it
is like irresponsible and i'm kind of like every every week i'm kind of like shaking my head and
all these people that are not on i'm like what are you doing like what are you thinking why
you're fucking up that's that's how i feel um it doesn't make it does not make any sense to me
uh hmm i hope i'm not coming off like whiny or anything i hope i'm not coming off like a
little bitch this episode but i guess if i am i don't know maybe i just am a little bitch
maybe i'll just maybe let's just up to the viewer to decide i mean it's it's fair to be like
where's everybody where's everybody it's it's been you me and tom for a while yeah and before
that was you me terminate for a while i just i just want i just want it to be known that like
it doesn't that i do i don't understand it i do not understand the thinking that that that leads to
people not being on the podcast people leaving the podcast or whatever it's it's bizarre i don't
know that's and that's and that's how i feel about it and you know and this this uh the greener
pastures thing no it doesn't hold new water doesn't make any sense uh doesn't stand up to
scrutiny if you think about it for even like a second and this and i'm saying and i say this
as someone who directly benefits from other people not being on the podcast because i make
more money the fewer people are on the podcast the more i get so it's like it's good it's actually
good for me for people not to be on but i'm still just like but why aren't people on it's it's what
they think yeah kind of a little bit yeah i'm having a miserable time talking to you
um oh no shucks uh oh see oh no i guess i'll never come back another friendship ruined gibbs
leaving the podcast um ben ben doesn't like me ben's too mean he broke up the podcast because
he's too political he was so political of him to say i'm a bitch uh okay i've i've
spealed about that for long enough i think i don't know what do you what do you think um i mean
people coming on the podcast i i would like them to come back that's all i really have to say about
it yeah i i like speaking to him the money is like whatever it's fun doing the show it's fun
speaking to people weekly it's good yeah it's it's uh i mean i don't know not every not every time
is it like sunshine and rainbows but like i don't feel like we've been arguing that much in like
recent months or years even it hasn't been that bad no so i don't know why people are like so
apprehensive maybe they assume that things will get bad if they mix with with uh with i don't know
ben if you if you have if nate comes back and then oh suddenly it will become political we haven't
talked about politics really that much i don't and it hasn't been like very contentious stuff
if it hasn't but like if nate comes back does he think that there will be like a bunch of politics
i mean the times when i the times when i get mad about politics are generally the times
that's nate or someone else says something political that i disagree with and then i
have to talk about it i feel like that's when i get that and it's not fair it's not me it's
it's not just a me problem but everyone says oh ben's political oh ben gets mad about stuff
ben's mean ben yells at people and is cruel uh it's very stupid it's very small brain smooth
brain opinion to have um i don't know is this is this like um this is like a is it a is it a
bad look to be here on the podcast discussing like why isn't anyone on the podcast anymore
is that is that cringe i mean maybe people have reasons and that we're not like uh thinking about
and they'll be like ah come on guys it's this reason that i'm not here so it's like uh whatever
like i don't think it's too much of a bad look because it's like the the viewers feel the same
i think a lot of people are just sort of like where is everyone it's a it's a very like visceral
feeling that is happening yeah i i guess i'm just as confused about it as you are dear viewer
dear listener uh hey we got another one we got another one do we have it wait from our boy margar
he sent it in 40 minutes ago just now yeah uh let's let's give it a listen margar save us save us
from this hell three two one go margar here it's week three in voice jail the living hell
they've got me breaking rocks making license plates uh i'm not being paid a cent none of us in here
are i've started to have correspondence with some of the other inmates in the prison here
and no one is being paid it is slave labor to be frank it's legal it's legal in the united
states people in here are innocent as i am i am convinced that we were not sent here because
of the crimes we committed we were convicted because they wanted our labor and they made up crimes
so that we could get in here we need reform we need abolition fully of the pc police state
i can't believe that you would spout such insane conspiracy theories as positing the
existence of the prison industrial complex absolutely ridiculous margar i hope tell apab
tell your new friend apab who's in there now uh hello for me and get back to busting rocks
yeah those rocks won't bust themselves no we need that labor we we need it more than
we need you to do that labor more than you need not to do it so there's we're we're causing a net
increase in the happiness of the world it's good trust me you're you're doing this you're doing this
to save the economy okay COVID is bad the economy's in recession somebody's it's a tough job but
somebody's got to do it and you're it you're and you know what you're welcome you're welcome for
the privilege of being the hero that we need right now i won't pay you in pc pennies i'll pay you
i'll pay everyone in voice jail and kisses thank you thank you for busting rocks sir uh delightful
like like like a piece of paper with a makeup uh like like lipstick smack yes signed ben saint
xo xo xo
and then you can trade it for cigarettes you say you save up your ben kisses
fuck that's it we've we've listened to all the voicemails yep are we are we concluded
i think we are concluded for today's pcp episode remember to go to patreon.com slash
the procrastinators and pledge five dollars for the monthly bonus episodes listen to listen to
the tits cast listen to the tits cast when the big booby boys are are alive and well
it's the best podcast you too can be hash can be a hashtag big booby boy but only if you listen
to the tits cast and have an opinion about it the right opinion uh yeah speakpipe.com slash tp
procrastinators the procrastinators for voicemails okay one of the whatever speak speak speakpipe.com
slash pcp voicemail for voicemails okay um and uh the oh the patreon also one dollar gets you
access to the patreon lounge which is a place that exists on the internet online for you
and if you haven't already check out munchies uh french revolution lecture it's very funny
i know that i know that history is boring so boring but uh but munchie uh he delivers
he delivers it with aplomb and it's very fun it was rewatching it earlier and i was laughing
having a good old time yep all right i think that's it i think we have finished our grim work
yes twitch.tv slash give and take yes watch my drawings and goodbye farewell