Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Yeah, there you go. We always record a podcast. And if you think we won't, well, that is similar.
I'm the best guy ever. And Steven. Yeah, and Steven is here, aka Hippocrit.
I'm Pearl. It's me. I did it. Oh, by the way, I think we should mention Munchy is not here
because his voice is dead. Go watch the video, live and learn on Munchy's channel. You will
understand. Indeed. Please do. Please go watch that video.
Wait, shut up, everyone. Let me talk more about which crystal gem I am. I'm actually
amethyst, and let me give you a long, let me give you... Because you are a literal trash
eater and a garbage person. No, I'm amethyst because I have tender feelings and you just
shattered them. Yeah, that makes sense. Do people not like amethyst? I love amethyst.
Ben, did you not see the new Steven Volley? It was confirmed that amethyst is the most
emotionally mature. Amethyst is canon. It's canon. They said so. Well, I don't like her
as much anymore, but I used to like her. But Ben, she eats trash, so you know. Yeah, and
she's fat, like me. Yeah, I guess that's true. Ben's here. We're past that. Tom is here.
She likes horses. Ben. Oh, sorry. She is a horse. I'm here. There he is. I'm great.
I still like Peridot. Peridot's good. And Mage. Mage is here. It is I, the Mage. Mage
is like Garnet because she's a lesbian. I'm not a lesbian. I'm two little lesbians in
a trench coat. Yeah, that would make sense. That pretty much sums up Garnet right there.
Yeah, there's not much else going on there. I'd say I am like Ruby, who also is my favorite
of the Crystal Gems, because I'm a little Spitfire with a big attitude. Nate, are you
a part of me? What? Yes, you are my mother. You birthed me. It was a traumatic experience.
That's incorrect, and it's the opposite sort of. Garnet is sex. That is what she is. Garnet
is like if two kids gave birth to their own mom. You're right. That's true. This is the
quality Steven Universe discussion the internet's been missing. I love Steven Universe. I do like
Lapis Lazuli at least design-wise, but Garnet is my favorite. Lapis is best design. Seems like a lot
of sad girls really like Lapis Lazuli. Like broken women seem to really enjoy her. I wonder why
that could be. They might see to relate to in that character. You know what it is? I want to
criticize real quick everyone who likes relatable characters. Y'all are basic as fuck. You bore
me with your opinions on things. Well, I think that Amethyst is more aspirational than relatable
to me. Yeah, eating more trash. Even believe not just eating it, but living in it. You know,
much like Ben, I hated Amethyst intensely at first and still do. I actually warmed up to Amethyst
quite a bit. Amethyst was like the barrier to entry for anyone who saw Steven Universe because
she's like, oh, she's fat, she's sassy, and she's sort of kind of black. This is one of those
Tumblr shows. I don't know about this, but then you watch it and it's like, hey, you know what,
they're all cool. I like them. Amethyst became good. Well, okay, I can't remember when I started
to like it. It was sometime in season two. Maybe I'll resign that subscription to fucking Stormfront
after all. The main reason I like her is because she's purple. That's a good reason to like something.
Like her hair. Relatability? No. Color? Yes. The best thing about Amethyst by far was that time
that she met the other Amethysts and belonged for the first time. That was great. It was the most
endearing moment of hers by far by a huge margin. What the fuck was the name of the Amethyst and
Steven Fusion? Oh, Smoky Quartz. Smoky Quartz. That was a big fucking funny guy. It's a problem.
It's a problem that's real. Absolutely. I mean, we all agree it was hideous, right? Yes. Really
just unpleasant. That's the worst thing about it. That's the weird three arm thing. What is that
about? It's up. It's like it splits at the elbow and that bothers me. Yeah, it's really fucked up.
Don't you like Nika Robin, Nate? But Nika Robin is temporary only. Nika Robin is like
artistically symmetrical. She never does things in ones. Nika Robin is all about style. All about
style. Smoky Quartz has never even heard of the word Gucci, which is a serious problem. She lacks
style entirely. That's my main point. She is gross. She is very, very gross. I like the Yo-Yo
fight thing. Yeah, it was all right. It was okay. The episode where she appeared was kind of weird,
though. Is that the one where they fight orange in the quarry? And then there was a game show. There
was a game show in the next episode, which is very weird. Yeah, it was that one. It was the same
bomb. Different episode. Why can Steven fuse? It doesn't make any sense. The gems are made out of
hard light and he's made out of fucking flesh. Why can he fuse with fucking connet? It doesn't make
any sense either. I mean, no. That makes just as little sense. Yeah, even less, I'd argue. The
gems fusing makes perfect sense because they don't have physical bodies. I don't know. It bugs me
out that Steven confused the physical body. It actually makes zero sense. It makes 100% sense,
more or less, the gems confuse. And I would say it does make zero sense that Steven was especially
the molecules, I guess. But what about magic? Steven and Connie die in the moment because
their molecular structures change and then they revert once they infuse. Fusion is just like the
transporter in Star Trek. See the video by my favorite brony analyst, Night Sphere the Gnostic,
discussing why Twilight actually died when she became a princess because her body was destroyed
and an identical clone of her was reconstructed. Does this majorly interfere with his love of the
show or is it not a big deal? Of course not. Okay, well, that's good. They have teleporters in
Steven Universe and maybe they're always dying. Well, we see them move though. It feels like,
you know, they don't get deconstructed and reconstructed. They go through like a wormhole,
like two things or space because they get lifted up. You see them go whoosh. Yeah, you see them in
the like hyperspace continuum or whatever. And didn't the first time Steven goes through the
teleporter like they showed him like getting stretched out before they get to the next place?
So that's safe. That's that's that's existentially safe teleportation right there. I agree. I agree.
Thanks, Rebecca Sugar. I appreciate that. By the way, spoilers for Steven
Universe. Steven Universe season five, I think is officially over at this point. There was just a
Steven bomb, which is why we're here doing Steven Universe part two. Remember episode two of the
PCP more than two years ago. Episode three. It's back. It's back. No, oh, sorry. You're right. It
was episode three. I forgot. That was two years ago and like, more than that. Yeah, nothing's
happened. That's not true. But it's not enough. You know what? What was happening when we talked
and that actually is relevant. So what was happening when that happened was we were we were
going through the time it was like after Peridot had been redeemed. Yeah, that was like what just
happened. It was the end of that bomb. Yeah, I think that's right. I think that's right. And the
things that have happened since then, the cluster thing happened notoriously was kind of
unsatisfying. We like met the diamonds went went to the yeah went to homeworld went to homeworld
and now learned a lot about the diamonds. Yeah, the stars and all that. And that's really that's
really it. Connie Connie spent an entire bomb being broken up with Steven for reasons didn't
make any sense. Oh, I think she was on her period, guys. You know, that's probably what they were
going for. I liked it. You know, what was weird about that specifically is that she spent that
whole bomb like broken up with Steven, she comes back. And in this, this bomb, there's a big final
battle with the the the two yellow and blue diamond and Steven and Connie do not fuse once.
They don't get together to do a big cool thing. They just the soul breaks in Connie is there was
so much emphasis on Steve Vani recently. I can explain to you why this didn't happen. I think
it's because Steven Universe sets out to resolve all conflicts through talking and understanding
Stefani would be, you know, them fighting and most likely losing. I mean, I wouldn't have I
understand the talking part, but like they did have a lot of fighting and Stefani coming together
be like, Yeah, we're gonna fight and then they get hit apart or Steven gets knocked out or something.
And then Connie could have been they could have done something, but they just didn't.
So, so did you guys like the newest bomb? Yes. Yes, I did. Yes. Why this bomb was good. It was
good because it didn't fuck around. It was just like, they didn't have any bullshit for the most
part. It was just good. Yeah, the first one was really weak. The first episode I like grown the
whole way through. Wait, which one was the first episode? The amethyst and Steven looking for Ruby.
I completely forget that. No, you just referenced it when you said that she's the most mature one.
Oh, yeah, they made that conclusion. I didn't think that was a way that was character development.
It's fine. Wait, what did we learn about amethyst that she doesn't think that Rose's problems are
her fault? I don't know. That doesn't seem like a premise for the entire episode. I think the
interesting thing about that episode was that like, like, like for the entire show, like everyone
has like been dumping their shit on Steven. And like, Steven's been like the character that like
interjects and becomes like the focal point of like the problems, like like Pearl's problems
be ends up Steven's problems, Garnet's problems end up Steven's problems, even Ruby and Sapphire's
problems are now Steven's problems. That's the whole point of the episode. But like this entire
time amethyst has all the shit that she's going through. And the point of the episode is that I'm
not going to dump this on you. This is my burden. I'm going to, you know, you already have enough
shit going on. I'm not going to give you more shit to deal with. I'm just going to like,
you know, suffer in silence and keep it to myself and not put that on you as well. And that was
the point and it was good character moment. I don't want to say like, I think the idea and the
message and what they did is really good. I liked it. I liked the concept, but the execution of it
within that episode is what I decided. It was just kind of slow. It was just felt kind of slow and
patted out. Well, it did feel a little patted out. I could tell this was like part of the beginning
of the Steven bomb, but they needed to like have each part of the Steven bomb be an episode's length.
And so, you know, they couldn't have half of the next cowboy episode in the first episode,
even if it would make more time, makes more sense. Like they have to be their own self-contained
episodes, despite being released in a bomb format for some reason. But yeah, it was slow. I did
kind of like how Steven didn't really know how to react to it though. It was just like even the
pizza and it was like- You know what? You guys were actually wrong. It was the second episode of
the bomb. Yeah, the first episode is where they find out about Pink and Garnet unfuses. That was
the one that I was okay because that one starts off and it's like, now let's all talk and discuss
and deal with the fallout of this massive revelation that Rose Quartz is Pink Diamond. And I rolled
my eyes and was like, oh god, I don't want to. I don't want to see this. It's the same episode.
No, I'm looking. It's there too. There's two episodes. The first one is now we're only falling
apart. And that's about they tell Sapphire the story of how- Oh, you're right. They tell Sapphire
the incredibly tedious story of how Pink Diamond becomes Rose Quartz. And then the second one is-
It was super tedious. And it was so bloated and weird.
Okay, it's the second episode. Right. Okay, the first episode. Forgettable, obviously.
Well, whatever. It was insane. It wasn't too bad though. I mean, it was-
Oh, yes, it was. Let's- I didn't have a huge problem with it. I think the problem is that
most of it, most of that stuff we already knew as the audience just threw like infer-
Yeah, it felt like a recap episode maybe. It felt like a recap episode and like the
I don't know. I get that the characters would be stunned by this revelation, but I'm already over
it, so I don't care. Well, that's because this show has like huge gaps in between it. Like,
if this was a normal show, like we would have only found out last week and it would have-
I don't think that's the reason because I did not find the reveal that Rose Quartz was Pink
Diamond to be surprising or interesting. Well, we haven't talked about that.
To go back to that for a second too, like- Yeah, that's a good one.
This bomb was good, but like the last time we talked about Steven Universe was way the
fuck before. I think the fact that we went on this whole fucking like year-long side quest of like,
no, Rose and Pink aren't the same, even though that was like the assumption for a while,
and then they went so far out of their way just to be like a U-turn of like, actually it was
exactly what everybody thought the whole time. That was a whole waste of time. That was like a
waste of a year. It's profoundly unsatisfying to have the- like everyone had all these theories
and then they really worked hard to fight against our expectations that that would be true and
then it just was true and here we are. Yeah, so obvious and I was like, oh, yeah, it was dumb.
I didn't- I didn't like that. We made you think you were wrong. Yeah, I was right. Did we not say-
Oh yeah, go on. Yeah, I was- I was wondering about this when it happened. I was like,
why is this not satisfying? Why is this not interesting? Because like,
it's- it's not like- I've already blown my load over Rose being Pink like three years ago and-
Well, I didn't- I didn't like know like the fan theories or like piece that together.
So it was like a surprise, but I still wasn't that interested because all it meant was that Rose's
mom- I mean, Stephen says this in this current- in like episode two when he's talking down with
this in the pizza shop. He's like, well now my mom didn't kill Pink Diamond, so she's not complex
a character. She's now like less complex a character and I don't know how to feel about that and
Stephen says, yeah, I don't know how to feel about that and like, yeah, this is stupid. But now I'm
just in like- in a weird like side step. Oh, now she just like is a liar, so let's like lump in those
weird mixed emotions here and we'll have to like sort it out. What am I supposed to be mad at Rose
about again? It feels like an asshole because like there's like- it just seems like, oh, if she's
like one of the three most powerful people, she couldn't find a way to deal with this without
like starting a war against herself. It just seems- well, well, the other two are like definitely
stronger than her. Like sure, but it seems weak. It seems weak to me. I agree Tom, that it does seem
weak. The excuse they gave was essentially she tried to reason with them and they simply would
not even meet her any of the way after the fact. So it feels like, oh, like this is kind of a weird
plot hole. I guess we can semi-try to justify it. And I suppose so. I mean this whole situation is
extremely like Ben was saying, it feels super unnecessary to have this weird double reach
around explanation for Rose. They should have just played it straight or they should have
happened to be separate characters. The reason they do it is because like I remember Rebecca
Sugar saying something about writing herself into a corner. Really? But like in like a cocky, like
yeah, but it's okay. I got it. I sorted out. I'm sort of the best writer. This is it. This is what
she wrote herself into a corner. What she did is that yellow and blue diamond are too powerful
and they hate- they loved pink diamond and Rose killed pink diamond. So the only way for like
Steven to, you know, beat them is either like literally overpower them, which is a bit much,
I guess, or to like reason with them. And if he just so happens to be pink diamond,
then they're now allies and they can fight white diamond or something. I guess that makes enough
sense. I absolutely believe that Rebecca planned from day one that Steven was going to be pink
diamond. I absolutely believe that. It just wasn't like pink diamond wasn't really even mentioned
for like the first three seasons, I think. Something feels- No, that's not- Season one,
we see pink diamond, I think, on the wall of one of the- I mean, there's a lot of like-
I can't remember exactly when we first see her, but I know in season one we do see the diamonds.
Well, remember that episode where they go to the weird Rose field with all that stuff? If I
remember correctly, I believe in that episode on the wall. I know that we at the very least see
some of the diamonds like on the wall, so the diamonds more intended. You see the insignia
like pretty early on. Yeah, the pink diamond insignia, I think beyond a shadow of a doubt,
proves there was intentions to make pink diamond a thing all along. Well, you know, something feels
cheap. Like, I think it would have been better if the revelation had come earlier and it was like-
Well, that's the story of Steven Universe. This whole thing is dragged out way too fucking long.
And Rose was just like a name that pink diamond had taken, but like the fact that she was literally
shapeshifting like the whole time for thousands of years, I don't know. Does it strike anyone
else as dumb? Absolutely. I think that is what we're all kind of feeling a little iffy about.
I mean, it was also weird. They showed like the flashback episode and it's like- and Pearl's
was like, oh, why don't we go down to the kindergarten and you can shapeshift as one of the
Quartzes. And so she does, but like she doesn't look like a Quartz. She looks like Rose Quartz.
She makes herself a special Snowflake Quartz. We have to do that.
No, no, no, guys. When they shapeshift, they can't- I haven't seen them change the color. For
instance, when Amethyst shapeshifts into things, she's always purple. She's always purple, but
she doesn't- but the shape is the same. Like Rose gets this weird fucking hair that isn't the same.
If you look at pink diamond, pink diamond is pink and Rose Quartz has flesh colored skin. So
that is a change. So that fear is right in the fucking garbage right there.
It's a bit off. It's a bit off.
We have other Rose Quartzes and so we can't think they have Rose Quartz.
Exactly. Therefore, it's a very odd choice for her to blend in with these Amethysts as a fucking Rose Quartz.
Well, she's being a stupid idiot. And Pearl is explaining that you're gonna draw attention to
yourself. I don't mind that too much, but I did notice that the skin color thing was a bit off.
But what I want to know is how the plus size community on Tumblr thinks it feels about this
betrayal. Pink diamond is fucking skinny. People literally committed suicide over this.
Oh my god. I didn't even- I didn't- No, there was a suicide attempt. Yes, real.
What? Okay, what actually happened was there was a fan artist lady who drew a skinnier version
of Rose Quartz and she received so much hate and death threats or something. That's right.
Such that she- I believe she did attempt suicide. Yeah, I remember that. I really hated how the
community bullied the person for drawing a thinner. It wasn't even like skinny. It was just like thinner
Rose Quartz. And in protest, I drew a skeletal Rose Quartz on my DeviantArt in protest. Yeah,
you did. I love that. But like- Fuck you. Real question. What if they knew at that time that
she had been pink diamond? Would that have made any difference, do you think? No, probably not.
You don't think so? They would have been mad at the fan artist and at Rebecca Sugar.
Like we're talking about kind of like identity politics and it's kind of like a weird-
I mean, identity politics and Tumblr people are linked to the show. I think like people were mad
that one of their fat icons was being drawn as you know like skinny, right? And it's like that,
I think is what they were rebelling against. And ironically, she was probably like the most like
normal proportioned character. She, oh my god, she's literally a- she culturally appropriated
fatness. She is in fact the worst offender of all time. She is a skinny bitch and she needs to-
Was that fat face? I really like pink diamonds design. I'm kind of annoyed that she didn't
keep the hair like that. Yeah. That was cool hair. Yeah. No, again, like we don't know how other
Rose Quartzes look like. So when she shapeshifted, she should have, you know, she'd probably look
like a Rose Quartz. I totally understand that. My question is that if she wants to blend in with
the regular Quartzes, why be a Rose Quartz? Because she cannot change color and I don't think-
Mej, we saw her change color. We have seen- Mej, not really. Days upon her visage that is different
in color. Mej, Mej, Mej. I'm not talking about the shade. The entire shape of her hair and her
face is different than the other Quartzes. And like, Amethyst can mimic anything. It just doesn't
have the right color. That is clearly done. Okay, now we're getting lost. What matters about this
debate is that it was clearly done as a visual indicator for our benefit as the audience. I
don't think this is something to really be criticized. Look, I'm an Autist and I get bogged down in
tiny details. Well, okay, this is my hypothesis. She looked like that because that's what Rose
Quartz looked like. Okay, well, but that's like a weird backwards logic. They had to make her look
like the character that we know and love. Well, okay, here's what I think would have been the
right move here. Okay, we have never seen another Rose Quartz ever. Does that mean that no other
Rose Quartz exists? They can't be true. They probably do. They can't be true. Because it wouldn't make
any sense for her to be named that. They think it was weird. We saw it. We didn't know that. Yes,
we do. In one episode, they've bubbled. They've bubbled all of them. They do. That is a plot
point that they bubbled all the other Rose Quartz. They bubbled them all because she was evil or
you know, because she made them hate them all. That's right. Right. Okay. Yeah. I mean, it wouldn't
make any sense for her to call herself Rose Quartz if Rose Quartz is not a real kind of gem.
Like, it's a real genocide, by the way. That's a real Rose Quartz genocide. The diamonds would be
like, wait, a Rose Quartz. What? That's not, that's not anything. Okay, but Mage proved it. They're
real. They are a thing. They are a thing. But here's my question though. Why did the show runners,
the directors and whatnot, choose to not show a single other Rose Quartz at this kindergarten?
Because it was an Amethyst kindergarten. Or a regular Quartz. But then why?
And that's my question. Why did she become a Rose Quartz? It's stupid. Maybe we can get
a geologist in the comments. Geologists in the comments explain, like, are Amethyst Quartz's
is a tambourine also? Here's the thing. The thing was, like, they could have gone to any other
number of, like, kindergartens that had Rose Quartz's on earth, if there were any. The reason
they went there is for that one scene where the the troupe was waiting for one and Amethyst is in
there. And that's like, because this is like our kindergarten. Within the universe, though, within
the universe, the reason why they went there is just like, oh, they're about to emerge. And she
wanted to see it to be there when they're emerging. That's like, in universe reason why she was there.
In Steven Universe. Yes. Also, like, I also have the issue with the fact that, like, it was all
Amethyst and she was the only Rose Quartz. Like, the main reason, like, the main issue I had, it
was no one questioned why a Rose Quartz was an Amethyst. That's been my point the whole time.
Yeah, it was very silly. Within the universe, no one questioned. They were not all Amethysts,
right? They were all Amethysts. I think they were a few higher rank ones. Some of them had other
names. I don't remember what they were, but they were called things like Tanzanite and whatever.
Yeah. Purple Rock. You know what, okay. I can't guarantee, but I don't know. Those are just their
names to distinguish between the Amethysts, I think. Well, you know what? You know what? If it's
a combination of things like, okay, Pink Diamond is pink. Rose Quartz was also pink. She's like,
ah, okay, I've got it. I'll be, you know, the other type of gem that is the same color as my gem.
And I'll, you know, rotate it so it looks like theirs. And I remember only seeing Amethysts,
but if you're saying that there were other gems too, then it's like, okay. Well, I guess there
probably was. I'm pretty sure they had other names besides Amethysts. No, the names they called out
were their numbers, sort of, so that they could distinguish between all the Amethysts.
Did they? Okay. I think that's the impression I got. I could be wrong, but I think that's the
I suddenly, I feel like I need to go and rewatch it for commenting. This is a small point, regardless.
I'll give you that, though, then. I think there might have been higher ranked gems that were not
Amethysts that were ordering Amethysts around. I didn't pay attention to that part, so I can't
say for sure, but it makes sense. If so, those might not have been born in the kindergarten.
They might have been from somewhere else. Yeah, but I mean, like if there were other
than Amethysts, then, you know, maybe this rose quartz was also, you know, one of the
others for some reason. Yeah, yeah, true. So I think we, I think we have enough ambiguity here
that we can assume that the disguise made sense in context. I think I just googled it and indigo
quartz is a real thing. So I guess like you could just put quartz after the end of a color and you
could get like a quartz, like that's like the default size for quartz is that tall and that,
you know, thick, you know what I'm saying. Nice, nice. Yeah, fair enough, fair enough.
I went to go pull up the episode. Didn't Amethyst come out like thousands of years later?
Yes, she did. Yeah, she was a freak. I guess it's a good thing that didn't, this annoys me.
It annoys me that things with gems happen on human time scales. Like all of those
quartz is emerged like within minutes of each other and then the one outlier took thousands
of years to come out. Well, she was pretty fucking defective. Not that much. She's just
all retarded. I mean, to me, I think I feel like they would all emerge over the course of maybe
like a year or a decade. I don't know, like that they would all come out within minutes of each
other. Maybe this is nitpicky. It just feels weird. Okay, one thing I sort of want to bring
up now, I don't remember if this is Canner was just a fan theory, but like when gems stay longer
or stay too short, they become different types of gems. So if she stayed for over a thousand years
or whatever, she should have become a different gem. I think if that's possible, I'm not sure how
Amethyst worked, but you know, those theories or whatever. We're gonna have to tweet at Rebecca
Sugar. She'll clear this up. By the way, I googled more. Amethyst is the name of purple quartz.
So Amethyst is quartz by default. Yeah, they're quartz. I am actually, I've just clicked through
the entire episode, the entire scene of her. I mean, they're there appear to be only like
big burly quartz like her, but there are no rose quartz at least on screen. But also I care
very little about this issue. So I'm just yeah, you know, I mean, none of the quartz there seem
to give a shit. So I knew do I? That's yeah, you know, I think we can just assume they were others
or something. Um, my God, does anyone have anything else to say about Steven Universe for the love
God? Let's move on to questions. Diamonds though. I mean, the diamonds are new.
I like the diamonds. You do like them? I liked the battle. I liked the fight at the end.
Oh, I love the battle. I was fucking sick. It was the best fight in all of Steven Universe.
Their boss battles were cool and like it didn't feel okay. It felt like they felt appropriately
powerful. Like it didn't feel like the diamonds just were suddenly like the diamonds were struggling.
No, sorry, the crystal gems were struggling the whole time. Like they're pretty strong,
but like they still had a really hard time even against just one of these diamonds.
I guess I'm I'm quite glad that they didn't overpower the diamonds because it's just like,
you know, they're built up to be like so powerful and so big. We have to protect our power scaling
for sure. Yeah. And if like a handful of gems could have defeated them, why didn't Roscoe
with an army? I would imagine a fusion would probably like they fused all together into
Alexandrite or whatever. And I think Alexandrite is like as big as a diamond. So it's as big.
I think it's smaller. Well, maybe. I mean, we didn't really see him next to each other. I don't
think. But I mean, I was glad that they did that and then address like why that wasn't working.
But they could have fused later on in the fight. I mean, they could have done that.
I thought that I thought that blues like crying aura was really cool. I loved that. I was into
that shape. That was like she's just like she's just so sad that she just like fucking emits this
field of like pain and like everyone in it is like incapacitated. Dude, that was literally
Kino. It was literally Kino. And I fucking loved every blue diamond. Also her voice is sexy as
hell. And I love blue diamond. She's the best. She's the best garbage. As soon as I saw her in
her fucking veil and her fucking pangolin. Yeah, what? No, what's the thing?
No, pangolin is a little funny animal. Damn it. It's a pangodopolis. I can't remember.
The thing everyone pronounces wrong. Walker. Palad box. AT-AT Palankeen. Palankeen. That's
what it is. And with her veil and her Palankeen, she was the coolest immediately. Also, did you
notice that the diamonds faces were really cool during this fight? This episode, no, no, no. This
episode, I got the impression like it had some pretty cool looking faces. And I felt like I think
this episode might have been storyboarded by an anime person like maybe someone from Japan.
I'm not too sure, but I saw something on Twitter. So, you know, take it with a grain of salt. But
I think one of the storyboarders actually has a manga going. I fucking called it.
It's called Naruto. Oh, no. Palankeen is also not the most
Kino form of transportation you've ever seen in your life. I love them, again, intensely. And the
scene of Blue Diamond more like crying over the pink overgrown Palankeen. Again, literal blood-borne
the best. Just so cool. Just so cool. I really appreciated how the fight scene was satisfying
enough, but it wasn't overindulgent in fighting because the show hasn't got a lot of fighting in
it. But when they do, it feels cool, but it's never enough. And with a thing like this, you want
all the characters there. You want all the guys doing all the moves, and you get enough of each of
them that you don't feel like anyone was shafted and everyone gets their moment to shine. And then
it's over. I still am waiting for Peridot to do anything. Yes, please.
She was adorable, though. She is the comic relief now, and it's kind of unfortunate. I don't want
to either. She was fucking dope. She was scary because of the threat of Homeworld that she
represented. She was physically powerful with their thing. She was a data analyst.
She had like little robots that did her fighting for her. She is not like a fighting gem. She
could get those back. I don't necessarily want to. I'm just saying if they gave her metal
bending powers, she should probably do something with it besides floating a soda can. She's done
literally nothing with it. It was a cool character thing to say. She had to rely on technology
because she didn't have any powers. But then they give her a power, and it's used for nothing but
jokes. It feels like it ruined an aspect of her character. That's true, but they haven't developed
her power yet, so her lifting something has to steal. It's been like a year and a half. They've
had to have it. I don't want her to be an ass-kicking badass. I don't want that to work.
I don't want her to become a badass. I just wanted to do something.
Fuck's sake. I'm trying to smash in my car into the lane just so people can cut me off
constantly just for breaking everything. I've killed seven children. I don't care. I want to
say this thing that Ben was already saying. I don't mind that she's not a combat person
in the same way they don't want Greg to suddenly become a super badass fighter.
I want that. That sounds pretty sick, dude. I want him to join Lars and the Stars.
Oh, that's a good idea. That's a good idea. He could be like the, you know, what's the...
He's the universe, man. I'm trying to think of like a musician, Brooke. He would be the
Brooke. I mean, Brooke has a sword. He needs to be... He's the bard of the party. He gives them like the
funny guitar melody and they go, yeah. Wait, wait, I just got to say Lars, Lars as fucking Simone
on the ship with the fucking jar with Greg's head in it, like Lord you know.
That'd be good. That'd be good. Greg needs to be like the guy.
I'm not sure how useless Greg was in that episode. It's just...
I mean, he's always used. I mean, Greg can't do anything to fight.
Yeah, but he felt like a little disconnected from the whole severity of the situation.
I mean, that's... He's a dead.
When everyone else was like just prepared to do something or like evacuating, Greg stayed in the
house, which is like, you know... Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh, I was just gonna say that. It's a little weird.
We have like these fucking starships of these like cosmic entities that have come to Earth to like
fucking destroy everything potentially and Greg's solution is like, I'm just gonna wait inside.
That's a very Steven Universe thing to do.
Okay, but first he said it's time to turn on the old Greg Charm or Steven Universe Charm or
something, but he joked. What does that even mean?
He was gonna fuck those diamonds.
I think there's some... Because he did have this whole long
conversation with Blue Diamond and talked to her as an equal for a while.
So maybe that was what that was referring to. That's true.
Wait, do you remember when she first comes to Earth? Like they both have this whole conversation.
I completely forgot about that. You are absolutely right. That's actually a good thing.
But it's not like Blue Diamond was walking up in person. This was like her arm ship,
which by the way, the arm ships are pretty cool. They're pretty cool.
I don't know. I don't mind Greg making a joke, but I do think that
going, like go inside, like this is the ship is like the size of a mountain.
Like going in the house is not going to do anything.
I wonder where they're going to go with that one-eyed cat that they have.
He's just going to be a mascot. He's going to be there.
That's going to be a plus to sell on Cartoon Network.com.
It's a ton of runway of what to develop this cat into.
No, no, I feel like it will be a plus point in the future.
They'll develop the cat into a line of toys that they will sell for massive profit.
Sure, sure. Maybe he'll be the new Cookie Cat mascot.
Get the cat, get the pumpkin, collect all two.
Do it. I want a plushy pumpkin.
Collect all one-eyed.
I want like a funny, like a gooey, ewe, gross, sticky pumpkin plastic guy.
I do like pumpkin a lot.
They're going to throw at the wall and have it stick.
Pumpkin's pretty iconic, I got to say.
Just a little question slash trivia.
It's a Calico cat, I think, so it should be a female.
And I think it was established as a female.
Was it in the episode?
Oh yeah, they call it a bit.
Yeah, they're like mature.
Only like one in a thousand are male.
So hopefully it's not a special snowflake male Calico.
Hey, here's a crazy headcanon.
Pumpkin grows really huge and he's got four legs too.
He will be Steven Universe's Palin Keen.
Right? Pretty good.
Well, like Cinderella?
Yeah, like Cinderella. It'll be a thing.
Did you just hear my joke?
No.
No, we don't want to hear it again.
Is Pumpkin Keen?
Oh, yeah.
Well, that was a big bingo.
He's knocked it out of the park.
Can we talk about the whole headspace scene?
I really, really loved it.
Sure, sure.
I was a little disappointed that we weren't seeing the fight anymore.
But I guess I was pretty happy with what we did get,
like with Blue Diamonds' cool boss battle,
like fucking bullet hell attacks.
I was actually kind of like,
I enjoyed the fact that you could see them fighting
and it wasn't like a lot of scenes like this,
you know, Steven would give them the courage to move on
or like he would say something in the midst of battle
and everyone would be like,
you know what, I will keep fighting.
But the way it happened in this is a very unique way
that I've never seen anything anyone do before,
like to have the battle going on inside.
Like you could traverse them in a weird head area
that I don't know what it is.
Was this a pink diamond power or something?
I think it must be.
It had to be.
Pink diamonds is all about...
What's the explanation of why this happened?
I love when Steven Universe just pulls out new superpowers
when necessary.
That is what this was.
To be fair though, this wasn't actually...
What he's done before is he's shown like dream
contact with like people's bad minds and stuff.
He's got new powers all of a sudden before,
like the whole healing period.
You can't just say because Steven Universe
just randomly gets new powers.
No, no, no, no, no.
Like him getting new powers is the whole thing he does.
No, that's not my point.
My point is the whole premise,
the beginning of Steven Universe is Steven,
you know, he doesn't know really what he is.
The gems are training him to become a crystal gem.
At the very beginning of the show,
he didn't really have any powers.
And through the course of the show,
he gains new powers all of a sudden.
Oh, okay, but that's probably unsatisfying.
The tears, and now this one.
So he's over the course of the show,
he's learning new powers.
I guess he has done this before,
like he fucking possessed Lars' body.
Yeah, I feel like this is a version of his dream powers.
I feel something like he was, he was...
Okay, earlier in the episode, you remember this,
he couldn't contact, remember this,
this actually would make me far more charitable to the scene.
Remember when he has to go to sleep to contact...
He talks to the cluster, yeah.
The cluster, in almost the exact same sort of way,
seems to be what he's doing when he is unconscious,
because established, he has to be unconscious,
which is what happened, he got knocked out,
then he is able to contact the souls of these gem guys.
So I feel that they were going for a similar thing with those.
So I really, upon the second watch,
I was like, okay, I sort of see the connection here.
Yeah, and also pink diamond.
I mean, all the diamonds have a theme of powers.
Blue diamond's the most obvious, it's sadness,
it makes people emotions, and they cry.
Yellow is electricity.
Well, yellow is a big bird, and she is like tough and zappy.
I don't really know what her...
Hey, I have a head cannon, I have a head cannon,
that yellow diamonds, her electric powers,
are what are used to make those disrupter things
that they zap people with, because it looks the same.
Oh, definitely.
You think so?
And pink diamond, through Steven,
we understand is all about healing and defense.
And so in this new power to commune with people,
and the fact that Steven loves talking,
it just makes sense that a pink diamond power
would be on this sort of like grand scale,
be able to talk to people through...
It was familiar.
Yeah, like to talk to people through the minds,
like to literally incept them from the hit movie Inception.
In the Captain Planet of Steven Universe,
he is the power of heart.
You know, I literally think that may have been like,
they thought that was a funny meme, but you know,
like, what if we actually made a show
where the main guy was that, and he wasn't a joke,
and then they did it?
Yeah, something like that, something like that.
Yeah, and then the bomb was over,
and that was the best part, the end.
Let's go on to questions.
Did you guys enjoy...
I just have to bring this up.
So like, there was a preview at the end of the episode
that showed like, they're gonna be talking to yellow
and blue next time, and the bomb...
Wait, there was a preview?
I've missed it.
Yeah, I mean, after the episode, there's like...
Okay, this is baffling to me.
Me and Michelle watched this, and we...
Our mouths were agape when we saw...
So this wasn't relevant to this particular Steven bomb.
It was relevant to...
It was a commercial for like, the last Steven bomb.
And this was a commercial running
all during the last Steven bomb,
and only on the last episode do we actually find out
that, you know, Pink Diamond is Rose Quartz.
The... I swear to God, this is true, but it is mind-boggling.
The preview that they put together
that aired at the end of each of the episodes
of the last Steven bomb.
So like, the first episode, this airs.
Second episode, this airs.
Before the last one, it starts off with the words,
Amethyst screaming,
Can you believe Pink Diamond?
It was Rose Quartz?
Haha, no way.
I swear to God, I swear to fucking God.
They spoiled in like, the preview for every episode
of the fucking thing that this was going to be revealed
in the final episode.
It's just like, what the fuck were they thinking?
That was a commercial before the last bomb?
That was the commercial that aired during the last bomb
in preparation for the final episode of that last bomb.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I'm 100% serious.
We did the research.
What the fuck?
It's real.
They really did that.
I remember something about this,
I think it must have been this on Twitter,
like people were pissed because there was a huge spoiler
and like, even like the Steven Universe team was like,
What the fuck, Sienna?
Yeah, because the cartoon network is so bad.
Put together this preview
without conferring with the Steven Universe guys,
obviously.
They just spoiled the hugest twist
in like the whole fucking series.
Well, that's pretty funny.
That's pretty fucking funny.
Just unbelievable.
I feel like whoever put the preview together
has never seen anything of Steven Universe.
I mean, no, I don't know.
They don't know that this is a fucking yes.
Look at this dramatic line.
This is a great way to cold open a commercial.
There's two things that matter to millennials.
Spoilers and feels.
You don't fuck with those.
That's right.
Fuck with both.
Hold on, hold on.
Wait, I got to make a joke,
but I got to look up some historical facts
before I can make it.
God damn it.
We'll get back to this joke, I guess.
Okay, imagine, imagine.
It's 1979.
Okay.
You really enjoyed the first Star Wars movie
and you can't wait for George Lucas's second masterpiece,
The Empire Strikes Back.
A fucking commercial comes on TV.
Can you believe that?
Vader was Luke Skywalker's father?
That's exactly what it is.
That's exactly the kind of thing this was.
Unbelievable.
Fucking come see that revelation.
Imagine if that was like in the theater.
You watch the theater adverse
and then coming up next,
the Star Wars movie
that you just paid a ticket to see.
Yeah.
Can you believe?
Dark Vader was Luke's daddy.
Man.
Good.
Very, very fucking good.
I've never seen anything like it
in all my years of public broadcasting.
Speaking of weird stupid things
related to Steven Universe,
what do we think about the Steven Bombs
and how sometimes some of the Bombs
are just beach city people
that I could not kill us about?
Can we agree that like...
That we have Steven Bombs?
For all of the anime influence Steven Universe has,
why do they have to copy Shonen filler as well?
Like, like...
Okay, no, no, but like,
they say that Steven Universe has no filler quote unquote,
but it does.
No.
What they do is that they force you to watch the filler
because at the very end,
Steven learns a little bit.
That's right.
Like it has a little bit of character development
that you need to know going forward
because he'll reference it.
That's exactly how they do it.
I don't mind the Bombs format.
In fact, I think I like it,
but I do.
What I mind is just the glacial pace that episodes come out.
I think the biggest problem is that they,
Steven Universe starts like four or five different plot threads
at the same time
and then doesn't solve any of them
and lets a bunch hang.
And it's not like a regular show
where like a plot could hang around for like four or five weeks.
It just hangs out for like a year.
Years.
Yeah.
And it's just like,
I don't even care anymore at this point.
Yeah.
I guess it's not that bad
because in the last year,
24 episodes have come out.
About 20,
it's slightly over a year,
24 episodes,
half length episodes.
I don't know.
That's pretty fucking sweet.
That's terrible.
It's,
regardless of how slow it literally is,
even if it's like the normal amount
for like an anime or whatever,
it feels way slower because of the Bombs.
Like I don't like binging.
I think binging is stupid.
I like watching a couple episodes of anything.
Say if I want to like watch.
It's complete.
Yeah.
Even then,
I don't like it because like you get through it
and then you forget most of,
because it was just one long blur of stuff.
And like things that are supposed to resonate with you
because they come out weekly do not.
I like binging because I forget things over time.
And that's why I hate the Bombs
because I forget to care and no one's come out.
I watch like,
if I want to show like the Game of Thrones or whatever,
I watch like a couple episodes
or three episodes per day for a week.
I don't watch like 10 in a day.
I don't watch as many as I possibly can.
I mean, the maximum is three.
Usually it's just one.
Sometimes it's like one per week.
I don't like binging because it,
like I don't like waiting a long time,
but spreading it out is just sensible
because it allows you to appreciate what you've just seen.
So what did you freaks and geeks think
of the whole fucking Ruby and Sapphire marriage thing?
I just want to quickly say,
I really liked how in that one episode,
like Sapphire was trying to use future vision
and she was like, why is she a cowboy?
And that felt so random.
But then in the next episode, it makes sense.
Oh, but like, that would be a perfect reason.
I had seen the preview.
So when she said that I knew that it was a thing
that was going to come back and I was like, uh-huh.
Yeah, good job.
That was one of the things that I was thinking.
Like if they had spread that out,
that would have been way funnier
because you would remember, wait,
she did say like a couple of weeks ago that there was a cowboy
and I thought it was just a silly joke, but it was real.
Yeah, I sort of agree with that.
Though, I mean, there's like two,
there's two ways to like watch a show.
It's like being up to date and like currently aware of it.
But then I also always want to think about like,
well, what's it going to be like in a decade
when the show is all out
and somebody just watches all the episodes, you know, for fun?
I hate binging.
I will kill bingers, binge slay.
In whatever format they want.
You know, one episode a day.
I'll destroy it.
I respect you less if you binge.
You should, you couch potatoes.
You are, you should stand up to-
Well, binging, you're not binging.
Can we all agree that the whole bomb format is just bombs?
I mean, I like it.
So I kind of like it.
How do you-
I kind of like the mini binge thing.
I don't know.
It's so slow.
No, like maybe it would work if it came out more frequently.
Yeah.
I would prefer consistency.
I'd rather just come out once a week
and I could just like become part of my weekly routine and-
Well, you know what?
It doesn't necessarily have to come out like once a week.
I think a regular schedule, whatever,
like if they have a bomb every two months,
then you can get hyped for the next one.
But, you know, you're still waiting.
But you're not like waiting like there's no reason to think about it
because I have no idea when it's coming out.
And I'll never know anything.
So I'm just gonna forget about Steven.
Yeah, exactly.
That's how I feel because like when the bomb's over,
it's like, okay, time to wait another 300 years.
Because I wish I knew when's the next bomb coming out.
I hate the fact.
I hate this.
I hate.
Oh, man.
She just hates.
I just hate everything.
About to get a little violent up in here.
Hating everything.
Let's talk about this gay wedding.
Oh, yeah, I like how I have become enlightened
in that I didn't even realize,
I didn't even realize that it was like potentially
like a breakthrough in animation to have a gay wedding.
I was just like, yeah, cool.
Oh, yeah.
It's like, it's not even, well, you know, here's the thing
that I think I've said about Ruby and Sapphire specifically
is I feel like it's kind of cheating.
It doesn't feel that gay because, no, I'm serious.
Because this is their only option.
They got no choice here.
Well, okay, yeah.
For one thing, gems are only female.
So that's like, well, whatever.
And then second of all, Ruby is the most,
is like the most masculine gem.
She wasn't in the dress, so it's all okay.
I was surprised.
I was really surprised by that too.
That Ruby wore the dress and Sapphire wore the dress.
She looked really cool though.
I didn't like how Sapphire looked.
The little suit and her hair tied back.
It was adorable.
I loved it.
It was great.
I mean, Ruby looked terrible, but you know, whatever.
No, she looked adorable.
I thought she was really cute.
I thought she was really cute,
but I felt like her hair may have,
she could have done something about that cube hair.
She should have done, her hair is just terrible,
basically all the time.
Ruby looked great in the cowboy hat, in my opinion.
I was into it.
I was pretty into it.
I liked how the top, the top hair puff,
kind of fit right up into the 10 gallon region.
What is known as the 10 gallon region of the hat.
I guess I would just say on the subject of the wedding,
like I feel similar to Ben.
It's a little bit of cheating, but like, I don't know.
I feel no-
It's just never, Sapphire and Ruby,
and just the whole fusion that it's just never felt,
they try to be like, oh, I mean,
they don't come right out and say it,
but people talk about it like,
oh, it's groundbreaking because it's gay.
And I'm like, well, maybe it is technically.
It just doesn't feel that gay.
I don't know.
It doesn't feel like any ground has been broken here.
This male ciz cuck is projecting too much gayness
that he doesn't even understand.
And he doesn't know that they're just normal people.
I don't know.
I mean, if people, if people want to get excited about,
that's fine.
I guess, I just want to say that.
It doesn't seem like that, that noteworthy.
I feel like it's good on this note to just,
although now they actually had him kiss.
Because like, I feel like-
Yeah.
That was definitely like, oh, we can't do that usually.
That was such an anime kiss.
I don't think so.
Okay, because it's been like, basically the whole time,
it's been really obvious that like,
a fusion is like a relationship.
Yeah.
But they've never, it's never, it's never-
They've never really been allowed to,
but now they've gone away with it.
It's never been like straight up fucking.
But like, that kiss was just straight up fucking.
Like, these tensions, but yeah.
You guys know what I'm saying.
Okay, Ruby has had her sordid kiss before,
but rather like, I think Ruby was kissing Sapphire's neck
or something.
So it wasn't like a lip kiss.
No, no.
Okay, but it's the first kiss on the lips when they fused.
Well, what I was going to say is,
I agree with all that sentiment,
but I feel like it's good,
even if this is possibly not satisfying.
Ben, let me finish, god damn it.
I'm sorry.
It's, even if it's a slightly less gay thing
than it could be, perhaps,
due to these various biological gem reasons,
I feel like it's kind of good and not too cheap in it.
It's good to like get it out of the way.
Because like, oh, okay.
Now we've got just like a children's cartoon, gay wedding.
Great. Okay.
Now here we are moving on with our lives.
You know?
Yeah.
And I'm not, I don't really care about this kind of stuff at all,
but it's just like an updated outfit outside her dress suit.
Well, she's got the rings now, right?
I hope the rings, I hope she keeps wearing them.
Hey, hey, you know what's going to happen, guys?
You know what's going to happen?
You know why it is that Lapis Lazuli and Peridot got poofed?
It's so that when they reform,
they can have stars on their uniforms instead of diamonds.
That's what it's for.
I'm telling you right now, that's what it's for.
They're going to look cool.
They're going to look different.
They're going to look better.
That's pretty good.
You better, you bet, that better happen.
So I'll be so disappointed if it doesn't.
Imagine if Peridot just reformed still
with a fucking yellow diamond.
Oh, but she'll be a little bitch.
I will kill her if she does that shit.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
She'll be destroyed.
She'll be quickly mentioned.
That'll ruin the whole show for me.
You've potentially ruined Steven Universe for me.
That would be awful, yeah.
Guys, Bismuth.
Yeah.
Oh, Bismuth did come back.
Yeah, she's going to be part of the group, I'm guessing.
Did she get poofed?
Did Bismuth poof?
No, no, she was fine.
No, she fight.
I liked her armor.
I thought it was cool.
Oh, yeah, me too.
I liked all the Bismuth puns.
Did you Bismuth me?
No, no, no, no.
Bad pun.
No, I love them.
I love puns.
Terrible.
The most they are the ones I love them.
I know the point was that they were terrible, but they're still.
What did you guys think of Steven's song at the beginning?
I loved it.
Loved it.
Was way into it.
I couldn't.
I wasn't sure.
I was like, sometimes I like it.
I don't know.
I usually don't like Steven Universe's songs with the exception of a few,
but this one was nice.
I like the part.
I think it just wasn't in the mood.
I think I wasn't in the mood to hear a song.
It was nice to hear Steven.
It was very, what was that one?
One where Twilight pushes out the door and she's like,
ah, everything's going to be fucking great.
It's a great day to be a gay horse.
Yeah, this day is going to glimmer.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I mean, I liked when he was like, you know,
he really embraced who he was and was like, this old Ruby rider.
That's me, Steven Universe, aka Ruby.
No, I was just going to say that I really, really liked Ruby's song.
I loved that as well.
I mean, that was really cute.
That was really cute.
I really liked the whole episode of Ruby going off
on her own was like, it was a real like emotional journey for me
because I was like really excited.
Like when Ruby was getting excited about being his own,
sorry, her own person, I was like, I was like, cool.
Like, good for you.
The problem with that is that I not for one second
believed that was going to last or like, you know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I didn't either.
Like I knew that of course Ruby's going to decide,
oh, I need Sapphire.
And I was almost like sad.
I was like, no, but Ruby, like, what's Ruby going to be like?
What's the new Ruby adventure?
Yeah, that's what I want.
Be your own gem.
But, you know, I don't know.
I guess they sold me on it.
You know, I feel attached to this very day.
Because when Steven, because when Steven talked to Ruby
and she was like, oh, you know, I just really love being with her.
Yeah.
And I like thinking about her.
Because I was gone.
Yeah, kind of, but I was sold and it was genuine enough
that when she finally went back, I wasn't that disappointed.
I was like, you know what, I'm happy for her.
I knew that they were going to get back together.
But like what really sort of like got to me a little bit
was the, just the thought of like garnet ceasing to exist.
Like if they actually split up and never came back together,
garnet just dies basically.
No, we can't.
Mage, we can't depict a negative homosexual relationship.
We can't do that.
Well, by the same token, if garnet does exist,
then Ruby and Sapphire pretty much die.
So, you've got to trade off here.
And he's just being, I know, I know, but it was like.
Why do you hate Ruby and Sapphire, Mage?
Why?
I don't.
There's just like, what, they're together.
Where's the giant woman?
Like they're, like, garnet is the trench coat.
And they're the two little lesbians in it.
But when they're apart, there's no trench coat.
But, well, the good news, that's true.
The good news is when Ruby and Sapphire are apart,
we can get cool different types of fusions with Rubies and Sapphires
as opposed to a big old fucking garnet.
I wouldn't be opposed to seeing those fusions.
It's just like the idea of, like, garnet to stop existing.
It's like losing a friend.
A character's death in a way, and it's weird.
It struck me as weird at that moment, the thought.
I'm just saying, you know, the thought of it was kind of weird to me.
Also, I don't like the Steven Universe.
What if Ruby cheated on Sapphire by fusing with someone else?
I was just going to say, I don't like Steven.
The one thing I have with fusions,
I don't like the, they try to have it both ways.
The fusion is both like a romantic thing,
and it's also just like a thing you do for utility.
Like, I guess it's like, I don't know.
Like, let's say...
It is.
It's muddied.
It's like, it's like...
It's like, it's basically like doing donkey raises at the gym with your gym, bro.
Which is, here's what a donkey raise is.
It's where you bend over 90 degrees forward at your waist.
Your bro sits on your back with his legs spread wide,
and then you do calf raises with him, you know, sitting on your back like so.
Like, it's a very intimate act, but it is for utilitarian purposes, you know.
I don't believe you, unless you're utilitarian being gay.
It's an intimate act.
It's an...
Well, that's like, it's similar.
Like, yeah, like...
Well, like, yeah, you could do that, like, with your significant other,
but like, okay, there's also reason to do it, you know, get sick calf gains, you know.
It's so bizarre.
These are equally valid things to do.
Please draw this picture, everyone.
This is too gay, even for the Steven Universe.
My favorite thing about Ruby is that, is the voice and how it sounds just like
the classic shitty character guy who doesn't know who Batman is.
Yeah, I do love her voice.
I mean, it's like, oh my god.
It's the voice of all the other rubies.
It's true.
Does anybody remember that shitty character, though?
Are you talking about Jimmy Olson?
No, wait, that's...
No, the man who doesn't know who Batman is.
Oh, the big fat guy.
Like that, the guy who works for the...
No, it was a character Jesse invented on the Katamari stream at Redcon.
I guess none of you were there.
People who know are laughing their butts off, remembering it,
because it's the funniest character in the world.
Sapphire sucks, though.
I could not be less interested in Sapphire's whole life.
Yeah, that's how I feel.
Yeah, I agree.
Ruby's better.
Oh my god, the web of possibilities, everything was...
Okay, first of all, first of all, what the fuck was she even talking about?
Like, there were no possibilities other than the set path until Ruby did like...
What? Can you...
Don't you read like the multiple pathways of the future?
Here's the thing.
It's that future vision.
Future vision is Steven Universe is just literally exactly the same
as thinking about what might possibly happen.
No, because it's like...
You're right, you're right.
No, her future vision only works if like nothing has any possibility of going differently.
If like everything...
If like if there's any random elements, like an unpredictable person like Ruby,
then it doesn't work anymore because it's not predictable.
Well, that's right.
It's just a way for smart people to say they're magical.
Yeah, it sucks.
So what you're saying is that Sapphire is a fraud and always has been?
No.
I'm saying was she...
It just doesn't...
It doesn't mean anything.
It's all the fucking tricky double speeds.
Okay, right now because of Steven and Ruby or they're being unearthed,
there's so many possibilities that it is kind of a bit useless.
But back then when she was, you know, a Sapphire of a diamond,
diamond, like the whole gems and stuff, the...
Everything was very strictly all.
Everyone had a purpose.
They had a place.
And like there was not a lot of room for deviation.
I guess thematically it does work.
Like like even in this bomb, like it was...
I think it was Pink who said like Earth is like full of possibilities where anything can happen.
And that's kind of like been a through line throughout the entire series.
Yeah, that's right.
Remember that episode where Garnet acted so random?
Dude, remember when she worked at the donut place?
Oh man, that was planned.
And then she like did a backflip over the counter or something?
I don't know.
Yeah, she ran out in the rain because it was so unpredictable.
Damn, that was a good answer.
Nobody would expect that.
That episode was basically the monsters podcast.
You're not wrong.
The best one.
I like that the monsters podcast is now a meme.
I love that it's a meme.
Now everyone needs to go listen to it a thousand times.
Be our most viewed episode.
Personally, my least favorite Steven episode is the one about the rivalry between pizza and fry town.
That one was a terrible chore.
I'll tell you what my least favorite episode of Steven Universe is.
And it wasn't in this Steven bomb, but it was a recent one.
And it was the one where that fucking Saint Kevin does everything to repair Steven and Connie's relationship
and gives great advice about life.
And yet the narrative insists on mercilessly shitting on him
as if he has zero value as a human being and is merely an object of pity,
despite helping the characters and being a positive influence in their lives.
Well, but Kevin was a big douchebag in previous episodes.
And today it's time to, like, they gave him the charity of like,
oh, he's only the worst person ever because he had his feelings hurt once
by some relationship or something.
And then, but then they proceed to Connie says like,
yeah, he seems like he deserves it or something like that.
It's like Jesus Christ.
You can't even give him the slightest.
I felt like that was a just, like,
they hate him, they hate him.
I wonder when they'll pick up the little
guys even think here, uh,
by the genocidal monster diamonds of space can be redeemed,
but not Kevin, but Kevin, it's true.
Kevin has to be shown, Kevin has to be shown to be wrong in all of his doing
because he represents the idea of like,
he represents like, like, you know, non genuineness or something.
He's a guy.
That's why he's like, he's like a corrupted,
he's like a sort of older kid who's like,
he's like, he's been corrupted by like the evils of the world,
you know, like, like the pain of life has turned him into a monster.
And like the show needs to.
Okay, guys, I mean, they redeemed Lars eventually.
Maybe they'll redeem Kevin eventually.
I will bet you right now.
Kevin never gets redeemed ever.
The reason the reason Kevin is now here.
He's a straight right now.
Because Lars is gone.
The worst enemy of all of progressiveness, probably.
I don't think he is white.
Well, he's kind of like off.
He's like reddish or something.
I do think.
But he's, he's characterized as bad.
So he must be white.
There's, there's, I mean, let's, let's just real quick run through the characteristics of Kevin.
He's absolutely vain.
He's absolutely superficial.
He is absolutely willing to like use people and only cares about like societal status.
He's, he's, he is also forward basically overall.
And all of these things are depicted as inherently bad things to be.
And Nate's personally insulted.
I mean, I, I, I know this is a personal thing.
You, you like him.
Well, I like him too.
That's a character.
I like him too.
I think he is absolutely not a good person.
He is a damaged individual.
I don't know.
I don't know if we'll ever see him again.
But I think that if we do, I think he can be redeemed.
And I think the show will probably go out of its way.
I want more Kevin and less Ronaldo.
We've, we've seen, I mean, we've humanized him in that episode.
Yeah, guys.
Okay.
My, my, here's a quick theory.
I have absolutely no basis for this, but when they bring up the pink hair girl,
the pearl heart crush on for episode two.
Yeah.
When, when, when they, when they bring her up, I think Kevin's going to cut Pearl.
That's it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Like around the same time, I feel like they'll bring back Kevin for better or for worse.
I have no basis.
Are you aware, are you aware of the, girl?
This is a theory I've heard once or twice.
That girl is the girl that he mentioned who like broke his heart.
I mean, there's no basis for that.
Wait, wait, the girl he mentioned, he did what?
Well, like in this, in the episode, he talks about like how he'll never let what happened
to him with insert name of girl that I forget.
Like he'll never let that happen again.
So he'll be vain and superficial and winner back and blah.
I hope so.
I hope that's true.
I hope it's her.
Oh, dude, dude, imagine a Kevin Pearl love triangle.
Imagine those two like having a conversation.
The thing is, some of that is like, is, is, is fucking.
Like that girl is clearly a lesbian with her funny hair.
Yeah, that's an assumption.
That's an assumption.
And I mean, the pearl is a lesbian, but she might be bisexual.
I don't know.
They can't not be.
Yeah.
Like Kevin was shunned by her because he's a douchebag or whatever.
Of course it was at least bisexual, by the way.
But what if, what if they, they, they make Kevin into the first trans cartoon character
where he goes through the motions and he's like, I'm a girl now.
Now I feel better.
Now, now I'm not a douchebag.
Now that I'm not a filthy male, that's what they're going to do.
I think that's what they're going to do.
That's going to be very funny.
Jesse Pearl making those bedroom eyes at the horse amethyst.
Sure did.
I saw Zen Huxables tweet.
You guys saw Zen Huxables tweet?
Yeah.
It's like, yeah.
I think it, did he say below that, what did they mean by this?
It was something like that.
He drew them.
He redrew them.
Oh, did he?
Oh, I didn't see that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cool, cool.
Yeah, the show hates men.
That's, you know, that's really all there is to say about it.
You know?
That's why, that's why Greg, I believe that Greg will be killed in the next
God, I hope so.
Set him free.
Before being, before being symbolically, after being symbolically castrated and then literally castrated.
I don't know, stuff.
Well, I don't know.
What else, what else?
There's more to say here, I guess.
Imagine, no, okay, I'm just going to imagine, imagine if Greg gets remarried to one of the other
diamonds.
Okay.
Wait, no, he never married, he never married Pink River, but you know what I fucking mean.
Sure.
Um, imagine, what do you think?
Like, like blue diamonds?
How likely are we on a 10 out of 10 scale?
On a what?
On what?
He's fucking gonna, he's gonna hook up with the diamonds.
He's gonna hook up with blue diamond because, you know, he got with the diamonds before.
Because why not?
He is rich.
Why not?
Tell me why.
Yeah, he's rich.
Just give me one fucking good guy.
I mean, she is a giant woman, so I wouldn't be surprised.
Yeah.
There we go.
Yes.
Please do this.
I mean, there's a new Steven.
What a great show.
Blueven.
Universe.
No.
Does, does, does, does Greg like giant women because he's a manlet?
He's not a man.
He's pretty, I mean, he's a decently sized guy.
I think, no, he's, he's pretty short, I think.
He's pretty short.
No, he's just fat.
He makes him look short.
I mean, he's way shorter than, um, I feel like he's the shortest guy in, like, any scene that he's in.
I'm going to check this right now.
Steven Universe cast.
I'm going to see how.
You will never find, like, the heights are never consistent.
You'll never find an image that actually confirms anything.
Remember, remember when Amethyst and Steven were the same height when she was,
when she was putting those flowers on the fucking thing?
Exactly the same height.
That was so weird.
And I was like, is she transformed?
Like, is she going to fucking grow again?
And she didn't.
And I was like, what?
Steven was, like, knee-high for Garnet.
I mean, Steven is, like, kind of like.
So when she was, when Garnet was, like, messing around and doing random stuff,
his size, like, changed eight times, I think.
Like, in the wedding episode, Amethyst and Steven are, like, exactly the same size.
Yeah.
I didn't notice that.
The one thing I can say about that is, like, they have been, like,
there was a few episodes about, like, Steven is growing, but just really slowly,
because he is getting older as a, and he should be taller than he is.
The people who make the show are on record saying they do not use ref sheets
for any of their characters, which I think is a huge mistake, and it pisses me off,
and I don't like it.
I mean, largely, largely, I don't really care.
Like, it doesn't bother me while I'm watching the episode, but whenever I think,
oh, yeah, that, that seems, I mean, that one bit where Amethyst is exactly the same height,
that's a bit too obvious.
She's a little bit taller, no matter how much taller.
But it, but when I reflect on it, I'm like, what an utter lack of, like,
professionalism and caring about your product, to just be like, I don't know.
I guess they're just whatever.
Tom, that is the white cis male in you that cares about these sorts of things.
We care about expressing ourselves, feeling, feeling the drawings,
feeling how big Steven is relative to Amethyst.
I need to take, I need to take this opinion back to Prager, you where it belongs.
As a purple female, I agree with Tom.
Well, there you go, there you go.
If a woman says it's a problem, then I can say whatever I want now.
I have the shield.
Blue Diamond is the best.
Here's a, here's a hot take that everyone agrees with.
Yellow Diamond looks like ass, and I hate how yellow her skin is.
She looks terrible.
Yellow Diamond looks better now.
I mean, I didn't like her initial appearance because of that crazy neck.
Yeah.
Because of that top of that neck.
But it's been toned down in future appearances.
I mean, I don't think she's anywhere near as cool as Blue Diamond.
If they just turned down the saturation on her skin specifically,
I think she would look 10 times better.
On her what?
Like on her face and skin.
Like, you know, if you turned that saturation down.
I do think they're a bit, she in particular is a bit too like one tone.
Yeah, exactly.
It's like, I agree with that.
That's why, that's my problem with some silk months.
Blue is better.
That's why like Reshiram and Zekrom and like Ninetales and Vulpix,
like they're cool and all, but they're a little too,
I don't mind Yellow Diamond's color palette.
And I think when Yellow and Blue Diamond are together,
they compliment each other quite well and they look good together.
I just don't like Yellow.
I think Yellow looks worse when she's on her own.
We've had our issues with Yellow on the show in the past.
Story history.
The cycle continues.
Yeah.
I didn't realize I still have fucking PTSD over that.
Yeah, you do.
Clearly.
Clearly it's manifesting here.
What do you think about Bismuth's redemption, such as it is?
Steven really just went in there and was like, hey,
remember when you tried to kill me?
Let's knock that shit off and be friends.
No, it's fine.
Because he learned something new about Rose Quartz
that recontextualized how he felt about the whole Bismuth thing.
It was fast because they cut away from the explanation,
but I think that was good.
I didn't want to hear all that explained again.
Yeah, for the third time.
Yeah.
Well, I mean.
I feel like at any time if they had unbubbled Bismuth,
like with all of them there and talked to her as a group,
I feel like they could have resolved it earlier.
I agree.
I still think, though, she might have had her reservations emotionally in Bismuth.
Yeah.
And I mean, let's not forget Steven on his own,
unbubbles and restores this murderous individual that attempted to kill him
and only barely escaped with his life.
It's just like he really should.
Like, I know if the other guys had been there,
they probably would have said, hey, maybe this isn't a good idea.
But just, I don't know.
I guess I'm just saying it seems like a bad idea,
but he is a child, so whatever.
Steven is a history of making bad ideas.
Yeah.
Question.
Does the fact that Pink Diamond was not shattered mean that no diamonds were shattered in the Earth Rebellion?
No.
Yeah.
Yeah, it does.
No diamonds.
But what about, no, it depends.
Well, there's only four.
Wait, what do you say, Mage?
No, wait, you said diamonds, right?
No, I made any gems.
Yeah, I was talking about gems in general.
Pearl has mentioned the friends who were shattered.
It's been mentioned.
Guys, we literally have the cluster, which is made out of shards of gems.
That's true.
Well, was that made from any more?
Mage is the only one on top of the Steven Universe one.
Well, no, I mean, hang on.
Wasn't the cluster put there?
The Steven Universe averse.
The cluster was specifically put there before the war, because that was like how they were going to colonize the place.
Well, okay, in the beginning of the few seasons, they were gathering shards of gems as well to bubble them,
like the remnants, the remains of their friends as well.
Well, some of those were corrupted specifically, right?
Yeah, but some of them were shards.
I think like in the episode where the little shards possessed like the pants, there was only a fraction of a gem.
I think you're right about that.
Yeah, yeah.
And I think when Bismuth came back, she looked up and saw like shattered fragments of her friends.
I think she mentioned like bubble because otherwise they would have like unbubbled them as well.
It was pretty cool when the ground cracked and like other fucking ghost cloud came out.
Oh, let's talk about that.
The Lord of Ghosts.
Okay, all right.
Tumbling down, tumbling down, tumbling down.
The cluster.
Let's talk about the cluster.
Because am I the only one who was peeved?
The heavy pee.
I was peeved though.
The cluster is very ava.
That it didn't like, so the cluster comes alive, the thing that we've all been trying to avoid,
and it simply was not a problem and was in fact a great boon.
Yeah, that was little.
I think the reason that that was set up is because Stephen has already solved the problem of it
potentially being an enemy by being a nice friend and saying, don't worry, you freak.
I'm your friend.
I mean, that is true.
I'll give you a bubble and now you'll have no nightmares and they're like cool sick.
I guess it's the same way as Bismuth that like they probably could have unbubbled it
and it would have been all right.
But yeah, no, no.
Like at the end though, at the end, yeah, I think it did.
I don't remember specifically in that episode, but I think the bubbling kind of helps it to
keep calm and at the end when it helped was like, okay, do you want to go back into your bubble?
I think that's what Stephen said or something like that.
You're right about that.
But he distinctly like we see the bubble pop when it is like coming out and he doesn't like
reform the bubble or anything.
Yeah, we do not see him reform the bubble, but he did ask about it.
He did ask.
So I guess he's going to later.
Is he going to drill down to the center of the earth again like they did previously?
Is that the plan?
He's just going to do it with mind bubbling.
You can't do that.
That's not a thing.
He's going to bubble the entire.
He can pull that power right out of his hand.
Okay, guys, one, there's already a giant hole leading to the cluster that the cluster made
itself.
Second, Stephen has floating power, so he could just probably just float down the bubble.
Well, Stephen distinctly says, what about oxygen levels?
I mean, he can dive.
I mean, if the cluster, he can make a bubble around himself.
He can survive in space.
Well, he does need to breathe.
I refute that by disagreeing.
Okay, Stephen specifically says, he specifically says to the cluster as it's retreating, like,
do you want to go back in your bubble?
Now, to me, the implication was, oh, the bubble isn't popped.
We, like, poked through the bubble with our little arm here, which would just make no
sense at all.
It seemed like the bubble popped.
And we saw an explosion.
So, I don't know.
I think he meant to re-bubble it, but, you know, that was.
I mean, maybe he just did something.
And maybe he just meant, like, do you want to go back into your shell?
Like, do you want to just be alone for a while, buddy?
Okay, I'll talk to you later.
Wouldn't a fucking giant cluster going from the core of the Earth all the way to the surface,
like, cause damage significantly to the planet?
No.
Okay, to be fair, the Earth in Steven Universe is already massively fucked by, like, even
having the cluster to begin with.
So, I guess it's just, like, different.
I was like, there's certain man masses missing in Steven Universe.
Yeah, there is no center of the Earth.
There is just the cluster.
Did that arm extend all the way from the center of the planet?
I mean, it must have, right?
Well, for, I mean, for fuck's sake.
Like, that's, like, I don't know how many miles that is, but that's like a lot,
it's like, it's probably like thousands of miles to the center.
And, but then, like, it gets up and the arm itself is like, you know,
you know, maybe like mountain-sized, like.
If you think about it, okay, I mean, well, I think, like, the United States is like a
thousand miles across, I think, or maybe a couple thousand.
I think it's more, yeah.
Okay, you know what, whatever.
So, it was definitely thousands of miles, like, to the center of the Earth, probably.
I mean, it's a lot longer than the arm that we see.
Yeah.
So, I guess it's just a weird coincidence that the size of the arm that emerges from the Earth,
of what is left to emerge from the Earth is just the same exact size.
Yeah, I think they just decided not to go further than that, for some reason.
I mean, I mean, it worked out, you know, that was an appropriate length to form.
Yeah, maybe it just decided to match the other two, but like, why not be bigger?
Because we had to have this cool arm wrestling scene.
It was this fucking sick shit, dude.
The rule of cool.
You make comics, you know it.
I, yeah, I get it.
I mean, it was kind of cool.
I like this, I like the ships.
I didn't really like the weird arm cluster, but whatever.
It looked like a muscle.
It looked like muscles.
It was, it was theming.
It was organic.
It represented the Earth.
How was that theming?
Because it represented the organic nature of Earth versus the clean.
Oh, so it's incomplete, it's raw, it's bro, it's damaged.
It's raw, it's mean.
The cluster is hashtag our boy now.
I mean, that's true.
Yeah, it is, it is.
I always, I still, I think I remember saying this in the previous Steven Universe podcast,
but I want to see what happens when the cluster fuses with someone.
Oh, that's.
Specifically see, Steven.
Becomes God.
Steven fuses with the cluster to fight white diamond or something.
He becomes like a giant, like big boy.
No, the thing is.
How convenient.
The big bad is white diamond.
Oh, yeah.
Of course.
Now, until we learn of the secret overlord, black diamond, which will be, you know, truly, truly powerful.
I want there to be a black diamond.
I mean, that sounds cool, you know.
Black and red diamond.
Black diamond.
Uh, I want to learn lore about where the diamonds came from.
Well, then I can make actual gems like on earth.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, you Google it.
You see.
Wait, what is this?
I can't go over right now.
Oh, okay.
Are you asking if on earth there are black or red diamonds?
Yeah, there is.
There is such a thing as a black diamond.
A black diamond.
Okay.
Yeah.
I was just, just making sure.
What about a, what about a trans diamond?
What about a gay diamond?
We need inclusion.
No, black diamonds, black diamonds only exists on ski slopes.
For when you gotta be the old champion skier.
Black diamond is just a skiing champ.
It's, it looks almost chrome.
Well, fair enough.
I can't, I'm, I'm finding Google images,
but they all seem fake and dumb.
Hey, here's a thought.
I'm pretty sure.
It doesn't mean anything.
But remember how the, how, uh,
Peridot showed up in a giant green hand?
Is there a, is there a green diamond out there somewhere?
I mean, there was a blue and a, you know, yellow.
It is.
Yeah, yeah.
I was thinking about that.
It's a hand as opposed to an arm.
So I guess that like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Peridot showed up in a hand and the diamonds show up in arms,
but like the hand seemed like bigger.
Well, the hand seemed about the same size
as the, as the hand of the arm.
Sizes are a little bit weird in Steven.
I guess I can, I don't know.
I really was hoping.
Does each of these arms just command a fleet of hands?
I don't know.
Um, I like it.
Okay.
Guys, color theory, blue plus yellow equals green.
Wow.
Yeah.
Did you go to art school or something?
Pretty impressive.
Well, and what does the theory consist of?
It's just like, I think that the implication might have been
that like Peridot is just, you know,
subservient to both of the diamonds, even though,
I mean, she's definitely yellows, but.
Yeah, Peridot is yellows, man.
But like, they work together, like blue and yellow.
So.
It is strange and makes me wonder if there's some kind,
if the green is some, like, I mean,
there's only two things that make sense.
And one is that the green is like some kind of coalition,
like blue and yellow coalition color,
or that this ship was made specifically for Peridot,
or maybe for Peridot's plural.
I mean, that's probably, I guess, what it is.
I mean, you know, Peridot wasn't special at the time.
They probably send Peridots on these kind of missions
elsewhere as well.
I think, I think if we're thinking of color theory,
if we're thinking of color theory,
we've got yellow, blue, and pink, which is like the red,
which is like the three primary colors.
So I don't know whether there would be any other diamonds
aside from white diamond that are secret.
I mean, I'm assuming not.
I'm assuming not.
By the way, guys, here's a conspiracy theory
that a lot of people are bringing up that I think makes no sense,
but you can weigh in on.
There was, there, remember that, remember that time,
when Greg, Steven, and Pearl went to the city,
and that's when Pearl sang her song about Rose being gone,
and she kind of got over her hatred of Greg.
With the top hat.
That's the one.
Yeah, yeah.
So in that song, Greg is depicted as yellow,
and Pearl is depicted as blue.
And people are making connections to blue and yellow diamond.
I see zero connection here other than Pearl was sad about stuff,
like blue.
What kind of connections are being made?
I have not even paid attention to what they are.
I mean, secretly Greg is yellow diamond.
How would Greg even be yellow diamond in any way?
It's because Greg represents-
No, dude.
The white, he went into the house.
He went into the house, and he hid,
and he came out as yellow diamond,
like the ends, as you've seen them together.
It's in the same room.
Yellow diamond represents toxic masculinity,
which Greg is the human embodiment of,
and that's how he stole Rose with his toxic masculinity.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
Of course I'm right.
I'm sold.
I can't wait for white to be the only male gem.
That would be interesting.
That would actually be kind of cool and neat.
It would literally be the patriarchy, is what that would be.
Yeah, I mean, it would be.
At least they'd be honest about it.
Yeah, it won't be.
Like on the surface.
Men are banned.
It will never stop frustrating me that the gems are all female,
because if everyone is female, then no one is.
It doesn't even make sense for gems to have a gender at all.
It's just an artistic choice, really.
Yeah.
I mean, okay, I guess gender is performed.
I don't know, whatever.
Right, right.
What does that even mean in a world where nobody has sex?
But they all have girlish forms.
Well, look at Ruby before example.
Ruby is very real.
Also proper amethysts, as well.
Yeah, look at what's her face.
Tansanite?
No.
Who's the orange one?
I can't remember.
Jasper.
Yeah, Jasper.
Jasper's very good.
Where the fuck is she?
What the heck happened?
I mean, we've been told they're all female.
Yeah, they're all female, but like, I don't know.
It rings a bit hollow when you think about it.
It's like, well, technically, they're not even female.
They're genderless, but they use female pronouns.
But like, why would they even use female pronouns in a society
where there is no such thing as male or female?
Well, they have to have some sort of pronouns,
and I guess it's easy for the watchers to have.
For some reason, the gems speak English, and in English,
you have to have a pronoun.
Well, yeah, that's the real reason.
I guess that's very wrong.
No, you don't.
You don't have to have pronouns if you don't want to.
Well, I think Rebecca Sugar just wanted to make them female,
and so she came up with reasons.
Well, sure.
I mean, yeah.
They just want the porn.
They want the porn, they want the Rule 34, and so do I.
But in the universe, I don't know, when it's like,
all the gems are female, my question is,
but what does that mean, really?
Like, what does it, what does that mean?
Rule 34 is what it means.
In some cases, I think it makes more sense than others.
Yeah, I don't know.
It's a stylistic choice.
I don't know.
It's fine.
This is why I wonder, and this is why you gotta ask the deep questions.
Like, is Sapphire and Ruby's marriage really a gay wedding?
Nobody knows.
Scholars debate for it endlessly.
It's a very funny wedding.
Kind of genderless and just reproducing.
I mean, if you just saw a really sexy starfish,
starfish are genderless, but like, if it looked kind of feminine.
Patrick.
Would you call it like, like Patrick?
Just because Patrick has a rockin' bod,
it does not make him female, you know?
Yeah.
Nor does it make him male.
Rule 34, Patrick Star.
Oh, God.
Yes, this is good.
Hey, well, who's your favorite gem?
Mine was Ruby for a long time.
I think I'm back on Pearl.
I-
Mine was Pearl for a while, but I think Amethyst.
I think Garnet has always been a favorite,
but Lapis Lazuli is second.
I have been thinking since the beginning of this podcast,
when I couldn't decide on what gem I liked the most.
And I think I still can't decide.
But maybe it's Lyon.
Lyon's not a gem, but he thinks it's funny.
My favorite gem is the gem that I made for the last even podcast,
Stibnite, sweet precious Stibnite.
Oh yeah, my favorite gem is me, Aquamarine.
I miss, what's his face?
Mexican, whatever the fuck his name was.
The fusion guy.
Whoa, God, yeah.
Remember that guy?
Is it Mexican cherry opal or fire opal?
No.
Something like, I'm gonna Google it.
I'm gonna Google it.
I think it was Mexican cherry opal.
I think you're right.
I think it was a fusion of two, you know,
whatever's, and that was cool.
Mexican cherry opal.
Yeah, it was awesome.
It's like everyone on Homeworld is like,
what is a Mexican?
What does your name mean?
And I'm like, stop misgendering me.
Even on Homeworld, they need to build the wall.
Yeah, that's right.
May I choose your favorite gem?
I'm gonna find my old image.
Where is my funny guy?
Oh, you're your little, it's on my butt guy.
Yeah.
Right?
Where is he?
Oh, I don't think I have it.
I mean, if you look at the PCP, Steven Universe,
like we did edit them into the opening of that episode.
We did.
They are all there?
Yeah.
Here, I'll link for your pleasure, you know,
which is people in this gem.
Mexican cherry opal.
Mexican, all right, thank you, thank you.
Yep.
They're all here.
I mean, it was me, Jesse, Gib, Tom, and Ben.
Why is it Mexican?
Well, that's just the name of the opal,
and it was so silly that I was like, well, that works.
You know, it's funny.
I'm laughing.
Help me giggling.
Yeah, I've had a good, I've had a good chuckle.
Uh, oh, Mage can't hear us, but that's her problem.
Where'd she go?
I think she's just having audio issues.
Oh, no.
Fuck, and I'm...
Well, I don't know.
She'll, she can read, I mean, we're all doing the right thing
in this call.
Hopefully she can.
You are, you are not the first person
to make a Mexican cherry opal fan.
What?
A gem sona.
Are you kidding me?
Well, actually, actually, that's,
I don't know if who's came first.
I found one.
Let me, let me see.
This was January 10th, 2016,
is when this episode came out.
Okay, let's find out.
Let's find out.
I need to know so bad.
See this one?
Wait, there's several actually.
What the fuck?
Why would anyone else have such a retarded idea?
Um, because they're fellow scholars,
such as myself.
All right.
Oh, I heard you, Mage.
What are you saying?
Yeah, nothing.
I couldn't hear you guys for a prolonged time.
Yes.
You missed.
We would just talk about our gem sonas.
Oh, I have a gem sona.
I almost missed this.
What is it?
How do I find out when a tumblr post was made?
Is there no date on the post?
Oh, wait, this was,
this was July 23rd, 2017.
Ha, I win.
It looks like you beat,
looks like, yeah, okay, okay.
Yep, yep, yep.
Okay, what's the contest for?
I'm looking, I'm looking at other people
that have made Mexican cherry opal gem sonas.
As was mine.
Whether Bestie Boyz here was the first.
Can I see Mexican cherry opal?
Can you say it?
Can you, can I see it?
Oh, if you click the piece,
the Steven Universe,
just click play on that in the main chat.
It's like, he's the first guy that shows up.
We all made gem sonas for that episode.
Remember when I used to make like effort
in like the openings of these episodes?
Yeah, no more, no more of that.
This is, this is July 23rd, 2017.
I'm still in the lead.
No one can beat me.
I mean, Jesse had a tiger's eye.
I would bet there's some tiger's eye
that go back a ways.
Tiger's eye, tiger's eye is canon in the show now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck, that's right.
Fismith said it, yeah.
Isn't that like an actual crystal gem,
tiger's eye or whatever?
It was like one of their friends or something, right?
Apparently it sounded like it.
That's what they said, what's her name was saying,
but like, yeah, that was like one of their buddies.
So this monstrosity is in fact canon as fuck.
This misshapen freak.
This is actually the corrupted version,
canonically, of tiger's eye.
It looks like Jesse's OC.
Well, this one, this one says it was one year ago.
So I don't know if that might be rounding down.
So this one, I can't tell.
Okay.
But it's really bad and seems to be colored with colored pencils.
Oh, well discussed.
Disregarded.
Anyone who's interested, please Google Mexican Cherry Opal.
Yeah, let us know.
Mexican Cherry Opal and actually a disproportionate amount
of the results are in fact gemstones.
What, are you kidding?
Oh, I'm going to Google this shit now.
We're getting lost over here.
Pretty shocked actually.
You know, this is a rabbit hole, I'm glad.
There actually are quite a few.
This is shocking.
Well, I see just some normal Cherry Opals as well.
In fact, I see way more Cherry Opals.
That's true.
Okay.
Oh my God, this one has a gun.
Whoa.
This one just has a gun.
All right.
This is not good podcast content.
Let's see.
What is it?
There's, they can't see the images.
Fine.
Let's fucking Google it.
Yeah, just Google.
Everyone, kids, kids at home.
I mean, I don't even know what more I have to say
on Steven Universe at the moment.
No, these are really good.
No, these are actually really good.
I mean, please edit them in someone, I guess.
I don't know.
I guess that's the thing to do.
No.
Google it at home.
Okay.
Just Google it and just experience what I'm experiencing.
Yeah, do that.
Do that.
Okay.
All right.
I'll shut up.
Who's got anything else to say about Steven Universe?
I mean, I forgot my feelings out there.
I really liked, I really liked the one where Ruby was a cowboy
and I liked the fight at the end.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I think my engine has been weird at 3 a.m. in the morning.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I liked, I really liked the cowboy episode.
I liked the fight at the end.
My overall feelings about this bomb were, it was all right.
I liked it.
I'm invested again.
I'm cautiously optimistic because I'm almost certain
that the next bomb is going to not be this good.
It's going to be meandering again.
I mean, the hook that the gems are like, they know now.
Like everyone knows, it's pretty neat.
And I'm interested to see what, I am interested to see what happens next.
I am also interested to see what happens.
It does kind of feel like we're reaching like the end of the storyline.
I hope we are.
I pray and I know that we are.
I really hope that the next season is the last one
of the tie up all the loosens.
I like that.
Frankly, they've answered every question except I just want to know
who's white diamond and where does like gem society in general come from.
But even that, I don't really care.
I also want to know who the pink hair girl is.
The pink hair girl.
I don't, I don't care.
Well, she's just a girl.
She's just some.
I mean, well, they introduced her and then like they whisked her away.
I want to see something with her.
Well, all right, fair enough.
I would like to see her again.
Yeah, I do want to see her again.
I want, I want Pearl to smash.
Yeah, didn't she like give her number to Pearl or something?
And Pearl has been steadily learning how to use a phone.
I think that a fucking Pearl and Kevin love triangle sounds like great.
The kind of filler episode that I totally want to watch.
I'd like that.
Because some of the, some of the Steven Universe filler is good.
And I like it.
Some of it is, but, you know, onion, get, get, get at it.
The filler's biggest problem isn't even that it's bad.
Well, I was going to say the reason the problem with Steven Universe filler is
even that it's usually bad.
It's just that it's usually like we're in the middle of this really interesting plot arc,
but we're going to put it on pause for like the rest of the week.
And then you're not going to know how it turns out for another like month and a half.
The week for the rest of the six months.
You have a Steven bomb.
Right.
Exactly.
And it's like a string of episodes you don't care about.
And then something right at the end.
That's why it's so inferior.
With like a weird new thing.
And I'm like, well, fuck you.
Remember that episode where, am I wrong about this?
Where Sadie, Lars and Steven get trapped on an island and then Sadie,
the angel herself, like just doesn't tell them how to get home.
Remember that?
That does happen.
Why is she like good?
Like she did, that's fucked up.
Why are we like okay with that?
She did that.
Because of her feeling.
She literally kidnapped two people.
She kidnapped them is what she did.
Because women get away with everything.
Come on.
Well, I guess so.
She was she was upset.
She was upset.
So everything is justified.
Okay, guys, this is this is hilarious.
A double standard kind of.
I mean, it's not about the same people.
But like recently I was watching TV like a pub.
And I saw we bear bears episode where like there were two people
stranded on an island.
And you know, the little bears washed up.
They were children at that time.
And like the two people was a guy and a girl.
And the guy he had like provisions and like a raft and stuff hidden from her.
A way to escape.
And he was vilified in the episode.
Poor hiding.
As he should be.
As she should be.
As should Sadie for being a bad person.
The reason he hid it because he liked the girl and he was like,
Oh, we're going to.
That's literal rate mage.
That's literally rape.
I was like, I'm going to reveal it as soon as she falls in love with me.
And it's like, I don't remember the episode with Sadie and Lars, but wasn't like.
That is pretty much the same thing.
It's not too dissimilar.
Yeah, I guess.
She she just love being falling in love.
It's like, like she was enjoying him to a pilot.
Was she waiting for him to apologize?
No, no, no, no.
She was just enjoying being trapped in a place with the guy she's into.
And so she was like, that's it.
That's all it was.
It's like the same shit.
And when he finds out he fucking flipped shit as he should.
Not enough though.
Not enough.
It was all just because she was like, she was like feeling underappreciated or something.
So yeah, that means okay to kidnap someone.
That's why I like as like, it feels so good to know that like as a father,
like when I have kids and like my wife gets custody once we inevitably divorce,
when I go and just take them from the house, that'll be allowed.
Like no one will stop me.
That'll be great.
I really look forward to this.
I can see you defending yourself as you would.
You would not hire a lawyer in court.
I'll bring up this Steven Universe episode.
Look.
I'd like to admit Steven Universe into evidence, please.
And then the judge will pull off her wig and reveal that she's got like a bright teal
side cut like Tumblr do.
No.
And she like cased his smiths.
It is in fact Rebecca Sugar, my judge and jury.
Are we done?
I feel like we're pretty exhausted here.
I am extra exhausted.
Yeah, I'm sure that's true.
I feel like we've really run Steven Universe into the grave.
Well, hey, we didn't.
Well, you didn't mention a mage's lovely OC over here.
Spirit courts looking good.
Looking good.
I do want to mention that I am a little disappointed that Sadie's music career did
not get brought up.
That is a side plot that I'm kind of invested in.
I, yeah.
I mean, I'm interested to see where that goes.
I don't think it'll go anywhere fast.
It's going to be brought up again, I'm sure.
There was a little bit where they showed like the people in the town reacting to something
and you could see Sadie hanging out with everyone.
That's good.
And Mayor Dewey at the donut show.
I'm glad that she has quit.
I'm like that she's done that.
I remembered.
I just remembered something neat.
And I don't know if this is true, but I'm pretty sure this is the deal.
When Ruby writes her goodbye note, she's her name.
Like she writes Ruby, but before Ruby, there's like a little crossed outfit.
I think what that is is that she started to write Garnet.
And then remember that she's not Garnet.
Yeah.
I think so.
And I thought, yeah.
I paused and went back.
I couldn't see a G. It just looked like a little scribble, but I was like, it's gotta be.
It's gotta be.
Perhaps she's just retarded.
She just wanted to.
She just doesn't know how to write.
She just doesn't know words.
No, no.
It can't be.
Mage, Mage.
I have a quick query about your RC.
Where is her gem?
Is it her hairband?
Is that what it is?
No, no, no, no.
Her thumbs.
She is a fusion and both of her thumbs are her gems.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
That's cool.
And also the eyebrows are actually a pair of tiny eyes.
Oh, that's kind of cool, actually.
I like that.
Yeah.
That's good.
I like that.
That's like, I don't know.
They remind me of like Geisha eyebrows a little bit.
Yeah, they're whatever.
They're cool.
Geisha.
You said it, sister.
The rest of us already have those series from the last episode.
Yes, Stibnite.
Stibnite.
Stibnite's good.
Go watch that episode if you want to see those guys in an animated little intro at the beginning.
I mean, it's not much, but it's something.
All right.
Well, I guess we're done.
Anything else?
Steven Universe?
Are we going on the questions?
Is that what we do now?
Well, before questions, we have an announcement, everybody.
We have an announcement.
Uh, so the fan art, I think, is the next thing.
But due to massive backlash on all-
On all sides, Ben.
We've decided that it just doesn't really seem like we want to do fan art in the show.
So we're we're planning to retire.
It's it's weird to do it in an audio podcast.
Yeah, yeah.
We just want to keep, I guess, that stuff to, you know, at most a show note sort of thing.
Well, we might feature it elsewhere.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know.
Let us know what you think.
Well, we always feature fan art that is tweeted at us.
Oh, yeah.
We'll happily retweet them all day.
Those are great.
We love those.
And here's your warning.
So because you didn't have warning for this, what we're going to do is,
like, this is your warning.
Next time is the last one is what we're doing.
So, you know, you got one more chance.
If you still want to make something, feel free.
It'll be in there.
If you still want to make something yourself.
I mean, yeah, you still got a chance to hit the spotlight.
Maybe this will want to be a contender.
Maybe this will drive up massive amounts of fan art because people know.
Like, it's now or never.
It's now or never.
Yeah.
We should do that every single time.
That was the plan for the entire podcast.
Yeah.
That's what it'll be.
So, oh, but speaking of which, let's go look at the fan
chart of the week.
All right.
Everyone go to the fucking fan art thing over there, the fan chart thing.
First one.
First one is from at HH Minaj.
It's me and Ben.
Oh, yes.
It's me and you.
It's the bros.
What does he say?
He says, it's also ugly and best guy ever.
Here are the two best brothers as the true best brothers.
Yes.
And that's clever wordplay.
Wow.
I want to do them rest in time, but procrastination doesn't let me do it.
Hashtag max revive t-bat.
I fucking love this.
It's great.
And a 10 out of 10.
Yeah.
Well, you're describing it for audio listeners.
It's just me as Sanji from One Piece and Ben as Zorro.
There you go.
Just works really good with my fucking hat because he wears, he wore a hat for a while.
I didn't even notice the poobah on the sheath.
On the sheath thing.
Yes, the little poobah, I don't know what you would call it.
Charm?
I guess.
Charm.
Yeah.
Katana Decoro.
Massive problem, though, that seems like it'd be unwieldy as he's walking around
because those things will jostle, that Charm will be flying off in no time.
What I would have done is put a poobah hanging from his ear, or perhaps three poobahs, you know.
That would be way too small to see.
Well, you know, put a little microscope.
My eyes, my eyes are so small and beady.
I look so, I look so guarded and sinister.
Just like in real life.
Yeah.
That's true, that's true.
And I look very confident and proud.
Quickly before we move on to the next fanart, I just quickly want to say thank you for the
fanarts that were featured in the last episode that were for me.
You guys did a bad job at saying that they were nice and I like them and they're good and thank you.
Well, I'm not you, I'm not going to speak for me.
Fair enough.
Yeah, but you were like, I think it was bad, mostly like, oh, there it is, so there it goes.
Sort of.
Well, it was a little bit after I spent like five minutes like trying to scroll through the chat
and looking at it, and then by the time I found it, I was in because it was a funny
punchline that you had seen it before and is like, oh, whatever.
Well, I did like the editing, but yeah.
No, no, no, the first two.
I didn't see that part yet.
The first two images that you showed were of me and you dismissed them and I'm sad about it.
They were nice.
So thank you for me personally.
I definitely saw them.
And there you go.
And then speaking of mage fanart, next from at the Wolf Art, my boy Edward D. Al.
Edward D. Al.
Look at this incredible Tsukabon mage.
It is absolutely gorgeous.
Super good.
I love it so much.
It's fantastic.
The only thing that I think could have improved it
was if it was a bat with nails in it instead of a katana.
Well, no, it's Japanese though.
It's Japanese.
Yeah, he's going for a thing.
That's what's going for a thing.
There's nothing more quintessentially Japanese than a bat with nails in it.
It's literally a thing, isn't it?
I mean, it is.
Okay, okay.
But I mean, this is also a true.
He's going for a slightly softer form of delinquent than that, I think, which is appropriate,
which I love this.
I love this.
I really like the petals and the little thing with the leaf
in her mouth.
It's just all so good.
Isn't that like, okay.
I haven't seen Kill a Kill in a while, but it's sort of familiar.
That is a school uniform.
That is not a Kill a Kill.
Yeah, but like, I think it doesn't look kind of like the middle school uniform.
I guess.
Yeah, it's just like because the red, it just, the thing, the red one, it kind of reminded me.
It's the kind of school uniform that the Kill a Kill outfit is like.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What it's called.
Saifuku.
Based on.
It's the Saifuku.
Okay.
Right.
Well, in any case.
You know, I actually have, I actually have a couple of Shinae in my room right now.
Whoa.
Hey, remember, we actually have two.
I actually have two of them, so I'm stronger.
You should, you should put like five in each hand like Zoro did for Maximum Sword.
And then hold six and six in my teeth.
Yeah, like he did for Maximum Power.
Makes sense.
More swords is more power.
That's literally his reasoning as a child, and I absolutely love it.
All right.
Well, this one's great.
Moving on.
Yeah.
Edward D'Al is.
He's a legend.
I mean, this guy makes some high quality shit.
He's done really great work before.
For sure.
It's fucking sick.
All right, here we go.
Kind Overlord at Kind Overlord.
I mean, we got a, we got a gift here.
We got a gift here.
This guy did want, he did a gift of me earlier in the week, and then he, he busts out this,
this, this classic piece.
It's, it's the, the Radcon Arena.
It's the Dark Souls of Arena Shooters.
Radcon 3 IRL.
Radcon 3 Arena IRL.
This, this, yeah, this guy's killing it.
I really like the lighting, lighting effect.
Yeah, the lighting is nuts, the glow moving around and stuff.
This is so fucking cool.
Someone, someone, someone get this guy on a, someone get this guy on the art team of an indie game or
something.
Yeah.
I don't know.
For sure.
Like the whole gif looks like an indie game sort of title.
That's true.
Yeah.
I, I particularly like, I think, uh, bottom left, uh, the hair.
Like the, the, the lighting on the hair is like kind of bubbly like the hair, and it's like,
yeah, that's, they, they, they thought about that.
He puts the work of his.
I like the little tiny, tiny strands of hair as well.
Yeah.
I know.
Those are nice.
Oh, a lot of detail.
A lot of love.
Pixel art's always great.
All right.
I mean, we got one of Munchie here.
Should we just skip this Munchie one?
I mean, it's just Munchie.
I mean, I don't know.
The guy's talking at the last episode.
Frankly, I'm sick of the guy.
Okay, no, but like, luckily, uh, there's a reflection in his, uh, glasses.
It could be just, yeah.
Like, like.
Oh, well, yeah, okay.
Is it potentially, now I'm not, I'm not too sure, but it could potentially be like the
setting for Red Con 3, like the house.
Okay, well, we might as well put this one.
Robert J. Lazarus one.
I mean, here, here it is.
There's Munchie.
So you can join the discussion now.
I mean, I think that's an actual painting.
So I'm, I think it's pretty.
I mean, I love this.
I think this is, I think maybe this is him at Red Con 2.
So maybe the reflection is the, is the classroom.
Oh, it's like the lecture.
That can be.
It might be.
That's my best guess.
Right.
Well, feel free to clarify in the comments below.
This is a pretty, this is a pretty fucking good painting.
If that's like physical paints, like.
Yeah, I can see the bumpiness of it.
The, you know, capturing something like a reflective surface is pretty difficult.
And the fact that I can instantly tell that those are like mirrored shades,
reflecting a room is sick.
I like the little sort of the shape.
It has like a little bounce to it.
It's not like a flat surface on the glasses.
You can see the little bend.
The reflection of glasses would do, it's really good.
Yeah.
All right.
Next one.
Here we go.
Mr. Upload at XG Upload.
I saw this on Twitter before.
Yes.
Oh no.
Oh, it's a weed guy.
With his, with his, I mean, it does, it's not an Ava.
It's a Gundam, I think.
I mean, it's got that look.
It's a G with his weed Gundam.
Maybe this is a like G Gundam style.
It's definitely, it has such a G Gundam vibe.
Yeah.
I mean, um.
We Gundam.
And the perspective of it is really interesting.
See what I, one thing I appreciate about this is that in this,
this clearly takes place in New Los Angeles city,
AKA Neo Milwaukee, AKA the location of ratty focused cop killers.
And Digi is clearly a killer in this image.
I think you're right about that.
Yeah.
I mean, like the slime green bandana,
just the whole, the whole aesthetic.
I would have, the Gundam is purple.
It doesn't get more rowdy fuckers than this.
But he's purple.
But the Gundam is purple.
Exactly.
And killers own, killers own the color purple.
Oh, okay.
We copyrighted it.
Okay, well what about green?
Well, that's just slime.
Green is, green is fair use.
Green is fair use.
I mean, uh, you know, this isn't me, so I don't care.
So moving on.
I mean, yeah, sure.
I just want to, just the perspective,
like the, the attempt of the perspective is really neat.
I think.
The perspective is.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, I think there's a little bit of a mistake there,
but I don't have the time to describe it.
How so, but like still the, it's really good.
I think that the perspective is maybe a little too intense,
because I think that the robot ends up looking not that big.
He only looks maybe about like 10 to 15 feet tall, I say.
You ain't wrong.
Which I think would be small for a Gundam.
I think like, well, let's actually,
Digi should probably be in between his legs.
No, no, sort of.
No.
Yeah, I think the scale is a bit,
the robot doesn't seem that big.
It's just like the way the arms,
especially the one closest to us, it's right hand,
the way the fist is sort of looking at us.
It implies, yeah, it implies sort of like,
Digi should really be like under the mech,
but it's also in front of it.
So it's a little bit odd.
It's possible that Digi is way closer to the camera
than the mech, you know.
But look, that's still an issue.
Yeah, I agree.
I agree.
The perspective is a bit.
We need something in the background,
like give us perspective in some way.
Well, no, no, no, no, we would like really ruin it a lot more
if there was a background to just like-
I just realized that,
I just realized that the things coming out of his shoulders
are blunt.
They're blunt, yeah.
Yeah.
How do you feel about that?
I was wondering about that.
Yeah, I thought they were like bat wings, but no.
You know what, maybe those blunts like open up
into big like weed leave wings,
and he can just soar like a gazelle of the sky.
I think that maybe he like, maybe,
maybe, okay, imagine this.
He puts his wrists fold back and exposed to flamethrowers.
Yeah, right.
With which he lights the two blunts.
Which he then like, he expands his chest cavity
to breathe it in, to like smoke the blunts down to his shoulders.
But they also serve as fuses for dynamite.
A round of explosives in his arm.
You know G Gundam, you know burning finger.
This would be blazing finger.
That's true.
Blazing finger.
Which so, just defeating his enemies in one fell swoop
and getting him majorly out.
All right, fair enough.
No more of this, thank you.
Okay, moving on.
At a sleepy guy, we got a little sketch
of child bestie boy me, young Nate in the fighting episode.
Mom, I'm busy.
What are you holding?
I'm holding various sticks attached to my body.
Oh, okay.
And pine cones and grenades.
Yeah, you know.
Oh, yes, from the story.
Yeah, from the story.
This art style is cute as hell.
Yeah, way into the style.
I love it.
Yeah.
It's super great.
Wait, what was the story about sticks?
Oh, I mean, I just told about how like,
I didn't want to go to summer camp and then like,
like mom would come back at the end of the day
and I came back like decked out with many sticks and like
grenade pine cones as described by me in my belt.
And I'm like, mom, go away.
I'm in the middle of something now.
I mean, we're in a war.
We're in a war.
You need to leave.
Yeah.
There will be casualties if you stick around and they will be you.
So here is captured for all time in digital scans of physical media.
Excellent.
And that's it.
Pretty, pretty painless, right?
Dear friends, pretty painless.
All right.
Here we go.
Moving on.
Oh man.
That was pretty good.
That might be the best one yet.
I think so.
I mean, that made you wise.
I feel, I feel extremely pain.
Me too.
I sprained my ankle watching this fan out.
All right.
Here we go.
Moving on.
It's time for those PCP themes people.
Hey, don't forget when you're hearing this,
it's going to be around the fucking 13th.
You've got one, two.
Yeah, we're doing questions last, I think, right?
Oh, okay.
Yes.
You got three weeks left people to enter into the goddamn PCP theme contest.
Let's, let's see what you got.
Full disclosure, I have not listened to any of these.
So these are all going to be a surprise.
I probably shouldn't tell you that because then I,
you'll know that I don't screen these.
But regardless, here we go.
Here we go.
With the first one.
Oh, and this is by...
Wait, wait, wait.
What's the first one?
Okay.
The first one is this is from at Moe entrepreneur.
Listen to PCP.
It's immaculate on SoundCloud.
Okay.
So it's called it's PCP.
It's immaculate is the name of this.
Or is immaculate.
PCP is immaculate.
Yeah.
In weird brackets.
All right.
So here we go.
Begin fucking now.
No matches.
Okay.
Sorry.
Hang on.
Wait, I can see you.
Wait, are you, are you playing this?
Will I be able to hear this?
It's going to be pushed through the thing.
Don't worry.
Okay.
That's why I'm a robot.
I don't know why that didn't work.
Hang on.
Fucking is this right?
Okay.
Here we go.
Play now.
Is it, is it posh?
Yeah.
It's going.
It's starting.
Oh, slow and sharp.
Here it is.
I can't hear.
Turn up the volume on the button.
It's playing too much.
On the bot?
The rhythm bot.
Oh.
That's a little better.
Oh, that's ASMR.
I hate it.
He's just what he's wishing for.
Shut up.
Sorry.
When's the drop?
I feel like one's coming.
I like how sinister it sounds.
Yeah.
Oh.
Okay.
Well, there you go.
ASMR opening.
I mean, I'm just surprised after all our talk of like trying to set a hype mood for the podcast.
This was the approach you chose to go with.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I couldn't hear like any of the words.
I'm sorry to say.
Hopefully.
I couldn't.
Yeah.
Hopefully our viewers.
He said he was whispering the PCP.
Oh, it's immaculate or something.
Yeah.
I heard that.
I heard that much.
It's kind of funny.
I love the music.
I really don't like ASMR.
I'm sorry.
I don't.
I just.
There you go.
It's got the main veto.
Well, here's an idea.
Maybe this, maybe we don't use this as the theme song,
but maybe we just play this subtly in the background of every episode all the time
to subliminally influence the audience.
They are signing all rights to the usage of this song forever by submitting it to this contest,
as agreed previously at some point.
So, yeah, I mean, this is all ours for the taking.
Thank you very much for giving it to us.
Remember the ASMR bonus episode?
Oh, I sure do.
Who could forget our best episode ever?
Um, fantastic.
Fantastic.
Okay.
Here we go.
Next one.
This is from at Slam Rarn.
And here it is.
What's it say?
Oh, Sixten.
Hope Jess is okay with me reworking his melody.
You can credit me as Sixten Machado,
since Slam Rarn is unpronounceable.
Well, I mean, he's not wrong.
That's not that unpronounceable.
Yeah.
I figured it out.
But here we go.
Oh, and it's called, apparently, it's called Four Exposure Crastinator,
as opposed to Procrastinator.
Oh, I like that.
Oh, I don't.
Okay.
Here we go.
Impress me.
I mean, well, that was pretty juicy.
That was very juicy.
But was that Jesse's melody?
I couldn't even detect it.
He probably like took the main melody and like,
I don't know, did something with it.
I mean, it didn't sound like it.
I think you changed it to a point where you can't recognize it, which is-
So I'm sure Jesse will not mind, as a matter of fact.
Yeah, that was juicy as well.
I mean, that was really good.
That was really good.
I liked a lot of that.
It's pretty sick.
I don't know.
But it didn't have any-
It didn't have any fucking jokes in it, though.
Yeah, I mean, you're not wrong.
I'm not laughing.
Yeah.
The only joke was your submission of that song.
Got him.
Yeah, I know.
That's why I said it.
Sixten?
Oh, that was Sixten.
Well, I mean, thanks for the submission.
I don't know.
I'm going to add that to my ones in my brain of ones to review
as we get closer to the finale here.
I will put that on the serious consideration list.
Yeah.
Man, I don't even have a list for that.
It hits the-
I'm going to make it later.
I don't have a physical list.
I mean, it hits the tone.
The tone is exactly right.
Yeah, the tone is really good.
The tone is really good.
The tone is exactly right.
Like, if there had been a voice over it singing about like,
memes, memes, memes,
hand voice, memes, memes, you know?
Cut that clip of that audience.
Just remix that on top.
Remix that on top.
Just have Nate saying memes.
PCP.
Memes.
And just shift it.
Yeah, there's some more for you.
I don't even-
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
That'll work.
Some combination of that.
All right.
Well, let's move on to the next one.
Okay, here we go.
This is at Alex with lots of A's and S's.
Just listened to the recent episode,
so here's a cover of Jesse's song.
But with Eurobeat Sense and some PCP fan art
for our boy, the PCP guy,
having a good drift.
Okay, so make sure this fan art's on screen
because it's actually fucking dope.
Do you guys see this?
Can you-
Yeah.
Are you seeing this in the-
Oh.
In the PCB Themes channel?
Oh, I'm seeing it.
He's drifting like a motherfucker.
He's Tokyo drifting everywhere.
That looks fucking incredible.
It looks fucking incredible.
Max revived the PCP guy right now.
All right, but let's play this.
Here we go.
I want to hear this tasty jam.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, I gotta do this weird thing
where I have to like paste the thing into-
Oh, it's on YouTube.
Okay, hang on.
And here I go.
Play now.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Oh, I like those sinks.
Yeah, that's nice.
It's nice.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, can we use that?
Well, the very end of that is like really good.
Yeah, I really like the end.
Can we use that for our episode on the 80s?
Can we do that?
I mean, all right, I guess the 90s, all right.
I don't know.
Anyway, that was really good.
That was pretty tasty.
Yeah.
I really like the synth.
It was pretty tasty.
I mean, I like a lot of that.
I really like, as soon as the synths kicked in.
Is it cheap to use one that's just basically
a synth remix of the old one?
Not if it's good.
Is that an anticlimactic conclusion?
I would say that, okay, for me, it is.
For me, it would be anticlimactic,
which is why this would probably not be my choice.
I would rather get something new.
I have to admit it.
Yeah.
Also, that was a little bit like more downbeat.
You know, if that's the right word, you know, what I'm thinking of?
Yeah, yeah, it was kind of chill.
You know, these are all, these are my thoughts.
Maybe not worth of a theme, but generally, I really like the sound of it.
Yeah, I mean, I really liked it.
I loved it so much.
I wasn't much into the vocals, but I like the synths when they kicked in.
Like the very end, when I did the,
but in the synth.
Yeah, that sounds great.
But it was fading out.
If you could like send me like a version that is just that without the fading out bit.
Yeah, do it, Doug.
So I can, so I can max gain it and put it on loop.
By the way, you did some good work, person.
Click on the main chat and look at like the way that the thing looks.
Like this is like the image that went with it.
It looks fucking sick.
I've got a solution.
I've got a solution to this whole quagmire.
What if, okay, like we end, we end the contest, you know,
we pick a winner and all that, what if, what if we, you know, aside from naming a winner,
we, uh, we just take all like our favorites and just have them be outros like whenever we want
this, or at least once, just do them in sequence.
And then like, what if just like forever after, like anyone that wants to submit like a song,
like if we listen to it and we like it, we can put it in the rotation and we can just,
we can just close out episodes with like different people's songs all the time.
I gotta tell you, I sure don't hate that idea.
Say it, say it, fam.
I'm interested in hearing what the fans think about that idea.
Like, like, yeah, like what if it was just a continuous thing?
Like, you know, you make a PCP fan song, we fucking play it as the outro to the episode.
That sounds like a pretty good idea.
Sounds like a pretty, I know.
I personally, I mean, as is the purpose for this entire contest, I'm way into the idea of
having a theme song that is the theme song.
But for the outros, I'm way into that.
I'm way into that.
Yeah.
All right, well, you know, keep talking about it.
Let's, let's get to the next one here.
This is from at Eric Seabase.
This is his second submission and it's called, I believe it's called crazy.o or crazy.zero,
one of the two.
And it goes a little something like this.
Oh, that bass.
I can't say no to the beat.
Yeah.
Oh, well, that is so good.
That was just, that was just irresistible.
Yeah, I love it.
I love it so much.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Oh, it's like vaguely reminiscent.
I'm not saying it's copying, but vaguely reminiscent of that style of like,
you guys know the song?
Oh, now I forgot it.
I just knew it.
I'm so excited.
I forgot everything.
Darude sandstorm.
It's a little long.
It's a little longer than I would prefer.
You were made for loving me.
Yeah, that song.
I don't know that one.
Sort of like the beginning.
I know that one.
Yeah.
It's a very old song.
The beginning.
Well, you know, man, I mean, if it's too long is the problem.
We can't always like fade it out sooner.
You know, I, that's not major.
That's true.
I mean, yeah, again, that's another one that hits the tone.
Yeah, it really does.
Right on, right, right where I'm looking, right where I'm looking at, Boyo.
That's a good one.
So good.
Next song.
What do you think, Gib?
What do you think?
Oh, yeah, I liked it.
It was very well produced.
Yeah.
I think it was this like a better version of the one he already made.
It might have been.
It sounded familiar.
This is a second submission.
Yeah, I was going to say.
You know what?
Let me check his SoundCloud real quick.
Oh, well, if it's a remake, then I take back everything.
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
He, you know what?
He made one called Crazy.
Oh, that is very similar, but not exactly the same.
Yep.
Yep, yep, yep.
Throw him in the garbage.
No, wait, no, this is another level.
He's improving on his work.
Destroy him.
Ben.
Mining his old work for new content.
Kill him.
Oh, he's improving on his work.
Second drafts for checkers.
You want to listen to his previous one just for comparison sake?
Improving on his work.
Yes, I do.
You mean he wasn't as good as, you mean that he didn't have 10,
he wasn't born with it?
I know, that's offensive.
Fuck.
Yo, let's listen to his old one just for comparison sake,
just for fun.
Okay, here, here.
Go.
Yeah, I remember this one.
Okay, there was voices in it.
I kind of like this part of it.
Yeah, I miss this part of the other one.
The other one doesn't have.
And I like that one too.
I kind of like that one.
There's things I like about both of them, I guess.
This guy, this dude, I like his style.
This was the one, this, it was the super basic,
was the newest first guy, the super basic.
I mean, I really like, I really like the vocals and the haas.
Yeah, I see.
But I also, but I also really like the super basic.
I mean, his name is Eric C. Bass.
So of course, his bass is true, must be true.
Oh, no.
Hey, you know what I'll say, Eric?
He's C. Bass, he plays.
I think you have a winner here.
If you make two changes, one, in some way add back those ooze
and aahs because they're cool.
And in two, put some sort of spoken word intro
that is good in some way at like during the bass or something.
You know, here's my thought about words.
Yeah.
Is that most people don't have like a good singing or like voice.
And not to be mean or like,
like, like if we have like words baked,
I would just pay us to sing.
Yeah, yeah.
We're immaculate.
It's, it's, it's not that we're better, but like, I don't know.
The music is always like great.
People are good at making the music,
but not necessarily the singing.
Yeah, I prefer the ones that don't have the things,
unless it's like very funny.
To me, making a music track like one of these is like
very far beyond what I would know how to do.
Yes.
I'm very, I'm very impressed and a little confused by all of these.
That's how I always feel.
Yep.
You know, this is not my, this is not my wheelhouse.
Well, all right.
I mean, I don't know.
Take that advice, do what the fuck you want with it.
In the meantime.
There's one more.
Let's go to the next one.
Yeah.
Uh, let me see.
This is from, uh, Doss Biggles at Doss Biggles.
Oh, Doss Biggles.
Yeah.
A barrel roll violet intro cut.
All right.
Here we go.
And a one and a two and a.
Whoa.
Oh, we're in the future.
This is, this is like a glitchy Steven universe.
He is.
Whoa.
Okay, it's fading out.
That was neat.
That was, that was.
Wow.
That was cool.
Like today, today's submissions are just like killing it.
I liked it and not necessarily maybe for the theme,
but just overall that's like, that was amazing.
Yeah.
I was way into that too.
That was really interesting.
I was thinking, I've been playing some nuclear throne
and that, that one brought me right to the crystal cave.
Okay.
I have, I have a small tiny question.
If let's say I decide to do something for it,
for my channel, would that be okay?
I guess you'd have to take it up.
You'd have to ask, you know.
Yeah.
You know that.
So ask him this guy.
This is no guarantee.
But I feel like you're your odds are good mage
because in the description of the tweet,
it says violets for life.
I'm assuming that's a good sign.
That's a good sign.
I don't know.
I don't want to make it.
I wouldn't assume, but I'm saying
the odds are good.
We got his Twitter.
You know, you can tweet at him, whatever.
All right.
Well, that's it.
That's all the...
Tweeting your strangers.
That's all.
He's not a stranger.
He's a violet for life.
He's a violin violet for life.
Oh, also he says PS Play God Hand
is his other note about the submission.
So...
No, I hate video games.
Oh, no.
Fair.
All right.
Well, that's done.
That's done.
All right.
Let's go to the questions guys.
We're all done with this shit.
You got like three more weeks
to get those, those themes in everybody.
So, you know, get to it.
I have a question.
Oh, you do?
Oh, that's good.
What do you got?
It's by Chip Weisman.
If you were all Sailor Scouts, like Sailor Moon,
what celestial bodies would you represent?
And why?
That's great.
Also note, not limited to moons slash planets.
So...
Okay, okay.
Hold on, hold on.
I'm trying to think of one that's good.
I know exactly the one.
Wait, what was the question?
If you were a Sailor Scout, what sort of celestial body
would you represent?
I would represent the Pillars of Creation,
which is a nebula.
All right.
Settle it down, Ben.
Settle it down over here.
It's a fucking cool nebula.
I want to be a cool nebula boy.
Yeah, all right.
All right.
What is a nebula anyway?
I'd be...
No one knows.
It's a cloud of fucking space gas.
That's pretty gay.
I was going to describe it as space gas.
And I am actually right.
That's what it is.
Well, it does.
Don't...
Gas gas gas.
Yeah.
Sometimes they congeal into suns.
Gibba's saying something, right?
What do you got?
I don't know.
What do I...
What do you think I am?
Planet World.
You be a Sailor Moon.
I don't think that one's taken yet.
That's open for business.
I have a...
I'd be a Sailor...
I'd be a pirate Moon.
Look, you're a Sailor.
Like, you just have the hat, you know, on a boat.
Oh, yeah.
You know, Sailor...
I'm a pirate.
I got...
I got a space submarine.
I'm just going to Google cool ass celestial body.
While you're googling, I would be Sailor Meteor
because I want to destroy the planet.
Whoa!
Oh, there she goes.
There she goes.
On the other end of the spectrum, I would be Sailor Phobos,
which is Mars Moon,
because that's like on a trajectory
to crash into something and destroy itself.
And that's the...
That's mine.
Oh, damn.
That's a good one.
It is good, though.
You know, I'll just go with Sailor Europa
because it's the Moon where there might be life possibly
orbiting around Jupiter,
and that's pretty cool.
I like that.
I like Sun Europa.
Sun...
...Homely.
European.
Yeah?
That was a joke.
Fair enough.
One other question.
I found it funny.
Oh, Sailor Black Hole.
Oh, that's a good one.
Though super edgy.
That's like if Shadow the Hedgehog were a Sailor Scout,
he would definitely be Sailor White.
No doubt.
Also known as Ryuko Matori.
Yeah, pretty much.
Oh my god, you're absolutely right.
She is Sailor Black Hole.
Making Satsuki Sailor Sun?
I guess.
White Hole.
Ooh.
She's got a nice white hole,
if you know what I'm talking about.
What does that even mean?
I don't know.
All right, moving on.
I guess I don't know what you mean.
I don't know either.
There's another thing.
It just means it's well-lived, that's all.
Yeah, okay.
I'm just going to put out there.
I'm talking bleached asshole.
That's what I'm thinking is what, you know,
just bringing it home.
All right.
Anyway, there you go.
A quick question is like Batsling asks,
how many mages does it take to screw in a lightbulb
and has like four people with the emoji of shit?
And I just thought it.
Oh, no, mage.
No, bad questions are banned.
We're trying to elicit good questions.
I see a pretty good question here on the Twitter,
so this is going to be our pity question.
By the way, Bats is one.
One.
There you go.
By two Fry Mcguy, hashtag askpcp,
have you guys ever been caught up in a fad or trend
that you regret or are embarrassed about?
Besides MLP, of course.
That's funny.
Well, I'm not embarrassed about that.
That was very funny.
Yeah, yeah, I feel the same way.
I mean, I would never be embarrassed
with that sweet T-Bap Patreon money
rolling in week after week to this day.
Proud ex-Brownie.
Wait, no, no, never.
I'm not ashamed or regretful.
I never called myself a Brownie.
I'm just glad to put it behind me, I guess.
Okay, well, aside from that.
I mean, I was really into this movement
called homosexuality for a while,
but looking back on it may have been a poor choice.
I was really big into Gamergate,
and I think they made some good points in hindsight.
That's a joke, by the way.
It was not actually a Gamergate.
Well, there you go.
But I was into the Nazi party.
It'd been World War II, we might have heard of it.
Indeed.
No.
Anime.
That was an embarrassing, terrible phase of my life.
I liked anime.
Liked video games for a little while,
but that was a mistake.
I guess I was...
I don't know.
I can't really think of anything.
I mean, okay, I was just...
Oh, sorry, sorry.
No, here, go ahead.
I'm stuck hanging.
I was tweeting pictures.
I was at our parents' house,
helping them get my shit out of there
because they're moving.
I tweeted some pictures of some of my old junk.
I'm not really that...
It probably should be embarrassed about it.
Okay, some of it I don't think is that embarrassing,
like my marble collection.
Those are nice.
Sure.
But then some other stuff...
Some of those are pretty cool, by the way.
Got some lutses?
Hell yeah.
But then there's some other stuff
that probably should be embarrassed about,
like my collection of fucking goth jewelry from...
Yeah, now we're talking.
Now we're talking.
Yeah, I got my sword with a dragon on it.
Like, forget about it.
And then Celtic Cross, fuck yeah.
And the...
Oh, and the big pile of fucking brightly colored,
like many of them have like Japanese symbols on them,
like nylon, Hawaiian...
Oversized nylon, Hawaiian shirt.
I had a bunch of those too, dude.
Middles in high school.
Yeah.
Well, mostly Middles.
That was my life in high school.
I wore my shirt in high school as well.
Yeah, yeah.
Yep, yep.
I was sad.
I was sad to let them go,
but I was like, I need...
This needs to be in the past and stay there.
Should have busted them out, dude.
One more round.
I had a...
I almost wanted to.
I had a phase myself.
It was around the time where,
like all these labels, like,
oh, it's the golf prep,
prep, emo, jock, yadda yadda,
we're like hitting Lithuania.
At least it was new to me,
and my circle of friends, and whatnot.
And, like, all the magazines that my friends bought,
and I was too poor to buy,
like, oh, they were talking about all these,
you know, fashion, whatever.
And, like, I sort of...
For a short while,
I considered myself golf,
because I dressed in black.
But, like...
Yeah!
I wasn't...
Like, it was, like, the fashion.
After a while, I actually learned
what a goth is,
other than, like, you know,
it's not just dressing black.
You know, there's a certain style
of fashion and stuff like that.
And after I learned it, it was like, oh,
that's kind of silly.
You know, I'm gonna be, like, a punk goth.
Like, because, like, in those magazines and whatnot,
it said, like, you know, like,
a female goth had, like,
all dresses or skirts, long skirts,
and, you know, lots of makeup and whatnot.
I was not about that.
I liked dressing in black,
and I was more, like,
baggy trousers with, like,
lots of pockets in them,
and, like, a black shirt
with an edgy-ass dragon on it.
And, like, I dyed the tips of my hair red.
I wanted a full black, but my mom didn't let me.
Ooh, where do you go?
I settled for the tips being red.
This is after your feral period, right?
Yeah.
I was in my teens.
Like, I was a teen, a young teen,
I think, 13 or so.
And I also collected skulls.
Well, rather, like, skull-related accessories.
Oh, okay.
I thought, like, like, literal things.
I would go, I would punch through their eye-sock.
So I'd see skulls out of their head.
That I'd find in the streets.
Yeah.
That was the violent-violence finishing move.
Yeah, exactly.
At least I come back weeks later
after some of my victims,
after they've had time for the skin-to-blood off.
Well, isn't it a Mortal Kombat finisher
where you rip the skull out of somebody's head?
I think somebody has that.
If Majors in Mortal Kombat,
that would be her finishing move, for sure.
Somebody mod Mortal Kombat 9
or whatever, get Majin there.
Yeah, yeah, that'd be good.
Take that, you know, there's that girl
who already wears purple
with the big, scary mouth, you know?
Wouldn't be too hard, wouldn't be too hard.
I was a, I was a goth.
I was a big goth.
Yeah.
I had, I had all the things.
The, the hair.
The, the eyes, the things.
Man, I was surely a goth back in the day.
I wasn't a goth.
I was boring.
But I want people to draw me as a goth
because it's really funny.
That is really funny.
Draw us all as goths, everybody.
The most embarrassing, the,
the most embarrassing thing about me
is that I wasn't part of a stupid embarrassing thing
and I don't have any funny stories.
Oh, I know.
I was just like kind, I've kind of shy and timid
and I did as I was told and then school was over
and I was like, oh.
That's what I was like.
I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't have
any funny silly things that I could look back on
and be like, oh no cringe.
Like I was just, I had brown hair and I didn't do anything.
When I think about like my, what made me cringe as a youth,
it was, it was like my attitude more than anything.
Cause like, you know, like I liked like transformers
and like, you know, like when I was like,
when I was like eight or nine or something,
I was really into like Power Rangers.
I don't see anything to be embarrassed
about being like a kindergartner
who's into like Power Rangers or anything.
And like I liked anime ever since I was like 10.
I still do.
So, you know, I mean, you know,
you can be a mid-level ashamed about that just in general,
but unironically, I'm just, I'm just not.
So I'm totally over that.
So I don't really know.
That sort of reminded me.
I was a thing, I'm like, I'm not necessarily ashamed of now,
but I used to be at that point.
Like I was like, I know I was over eight years old
and remember I was a tall boy.
I used to really like coloring books
and I was really embarrassed about buying coloring books
at that age because I felt like I was too old
or at least looked too old to buy coloring books for myself.
So I was, I love it.
That is so adorable.
It's like, go to the store to buy coloring books
for yourself to color in.
I would never, it's never crossed my mind
that one would do such a thing,
but that's super adorable.
I love that.
I mean, they have like legit coloring books that are like,
you know.
A type of coloring books I really liked.
There are adult coloring books, aren't they?
Isn't that like a thing?
Oh, but they're stupid.
Yeah.
Are they?
Okay.
All right.
They're just like a bunch of shapes.
Mage, did you color them all in purple?
I was gonna say, like you would go from like the crayon box
to the coloring pencil box to the markers
and every purple color would be gone.
You would get a whole thing of like 20 different colors,
but you would throw them all away and keep the purple ones.
My purple face started in my teen hood.
No, like what I would buy,
I did the favorite type of coloring books I used to like.
Oh, they were like paper dolls and you could like put like,
you cut them out like, and then there's clothes.
You can cut them out and put them on them like for paper dolls,
but you color them in yourself.
And like, I was really into making paper dolls at that time.
And like, I even made like Dragon Ball Z dolls.
I remember I made one of the cheetahs.
A who?
A Vegeta.
Vegeta from Dragon Ball Z.
Oh, Vegeta.
Dude, that's sick.
Yeah.
Like, uh, like me and my friends were like all about that
making paper doll craze and we would make our own clothes
and color them in and stuff like that.
And those paper dolls were like more official looking,
of course, because, you know, we couldn't draw for shit.
But it was real.
It was real great.
I was a big fan and it was embarrassing.
Anybody else want to chime in on this?
Or I got another question.
I've got another question.
Okay, yeah, go ahead.
This is by Rugae in the progressionators lounge.
He says, let's say you want to have a specific character trait,
traits.
How do you do that?
Do you force certain behavior in your everyday life or what?
I thought this was really interesting because, like,
I have had similar thoughts.
He's asking, like, if you want to be a certain way to have, like,
to be a certain way in, like, normal life without trying,
do you have to force it all the time and until it sticks?
Yes.
Because I've never managed to really do that.
Yes, same.
I think everything that is, like, accidental.
The only time in my life I succeeded in this kind of a quest of
consciously trying to change myself was with my, like,
forcing myself to go out and, like, talk to girls in college.
And I didn't even succeed anywhere near, like, the, like,
the stuff I was, like, reading at the time about, like,
how to be more, you know, social and stuff was, like, telling me to.
But, like, it long-term manifested in a much larger degree of,
like, willingness to, like, talk to people and, like,
do things and, like, kind of take initiative in life.
So even at the time, it wasn't, like, a huge change right then and there.
But I did actively have to force myself to do things differently.
And I do believe I changed majorly long-term as a result of taking those actions.
I mean, I think if you force yourself, if you force yourself to
regularly engage in a behavior that you were not, it, it, it will definitely have an effect.
Okay, okay. Guys, I do agree with you, but I think it still takes a certain type of
person to do that because for me personally, I had some personal experience with it.
I tried forcing something and it's just, like, at some point I came to the conclusion,
like, I was failing despite constantly trying, but at a certain point I came to the conclusion,
like, like, I am trying this and I'm forcing myself to do this, but at what point am I living
a lie because it was stressing me out and I know I'll never be this person that I'm trying to be
despite all this attempts and, like, even if I was successful, then I'll have to go on being
this person and I don't feel comfortable being this despite wanting to be this. So I stop.
One is reminded of the adage of the oak tree that, that groweth tall and true.
And as it grows, you can shape it and kind of guide it along a certain path, but once it's
grown too far, if you try to bend it in a certain way, as opposed to how it's already started to
grow, then it can bend to a degree, but eventually it will snap, or it could just not, you know,
it just might not go that way. I think, like, certain things can be changed, for instance,
like wanting to be able to speak more or speak up more or speak faster, something like those things.
You can't definitely push yourself. Well, major, you're making this point about people or about
yourself. And I know people. I mean, just general. I just, it's speaking because you were talking
about how you're speaking to girls and stuff. Yeah. You know, you can force yourself to, you know,
change certain things like that, but they're like. Because that was hell. That was absolute hell.
Yeah, I mean, the change did happen eventually, some sort of, it did manifest in some way, but
they're like some things that are more core to you, like core personality traits. Sure, I agree.
I agree. That will, that linger to you. And it's like, maybe some people are managing to change it
legitimately, but some people might end up living a lie. And you just have to notice, you know,
which one are you? And at some point, and make the decision, do you want to keep living a lie,
or do you just want to try and be yourself and see where that leads you? I agree. I agree.
Anybody else?
Trying to think, if I've ever, I mean, I feel like, I feel like I have done a lot of
not doing that in the recent past, like a lot of like, meaning to like, oh, I'm gonna do this,
I'm gonna do that, I'm gonna start being like that. And just, it's not, not even that it doesn't
work. It doesn't, it's a total non-starter and doesn't happen. Yeah. That feels, that's, that's
been, that's been my, that's been me for a long time now. I think certain people just tend to like
be better doing things one at a time. Like, instead of regimenting their life in ways to,
to improve it, they should just set up situ, like, set up situations where in the future,
they know that they will likely do like, something in particular, like, I'm trying to think of an
example, but like, instead of like, regimenting your diet, having someone else force you to like,
or like, take, like, lock a certain cupboard so that you can't get something, and so you'll naturally
do something else, like, to set up your life in a way that you do what you usually do, but in a
way that benefits you rather than... That's kind of what I do. That's how I kind of get stuff done
with like deadlines, arbitrary, that are just like, like, for example, like today, I just promised
my girlfriend, because I thought it would be helpful, and it is, that I would count all my
calories today. She doesn't care. She doesn't give a shit. But for some reason, when I promise
someone that I will do something, it does get done. It's when I leave it kind of like, vague and up
in the air, like, yeah, like, I should definitely count my calories today. Then I just won't do it.
And I, but you know, once I promise someone, it gets done, gets done. I don't know. So that's
that kind of mechanism of tricking myself, kind of forcing myself to do it. But I just recognize
that I need that. I think if I try, I think if I try to promise things to people, I will just
avoid them.
It will end up, well, yeah, well, I think I avoid making promises in the first place in,
because I'm afraid that if I do mess up enough times, my promises will start to mean nothing.
And then I can't do that anymore.
That's kind of the motivating factor.
That's the stakes. That's the stakes that keeps you from breaking said promise, right?
Yeah.
Or that's the idea anyway.
For me, yeah.
Because like, I could promise that I will make a video or something, but then
I won't care about it at some point. And then I'm like, well, now I promised I would do it.
I do it with stuff that's like, when's Rayman 2?
Oh, no.
I do it with stuff like, like today, I promise I will go to the gym. Like, I've done that. And
Michelle, like, doesn't give a shit. It's just, it's helpful for me. Once I've said I'm doing it,
like, because this is something I want to do is not any more time than like, I wanted to spend
doing it anyway. And it's just like a regular thing. But it's just a helpful mental trick
that I use on myself.
Yeah. Like, people used to say like something similar, like back in school,
like when people wanted to cheat and, you know, write down
somewhere secretly, like the answers and stuff, like actually writing down those answers helps
you memorize them. So it's just the power of like, you know, saying it out loud or writing it down
is just like, makes it more official and it sticks with you a bit more than just thinking it.
Sounds rice to me. I said, it sounds rice to me because I'm currently adding brown rice to my
calorie calculator. Got them.
What sort of calorie calculator do you have? Is it like a mine or something?
This is called, you can get on your phone. It's called My Fitness Pal. And there's also
ones called Lose It and there's a bunch of them. But I like My Fitness Pal. And all it is, is it's
just a thing. You can, you type in like how many calories you want to eat for that day. So like,
that's, you know, you got to figure that out. But there's lots of tools to do that. And then you
just, you go in and like, whenever you eat a food, you just pull up the like, the diary, the tracker
and you type in, look, I had brown rice, chicken and broccoli for lunch today. So I'm typing in
brown rice, going to add that, how much I had, like, I had like a cup and a half or something.
That's like 150 calories chicken. It's like 200 calories and broccoli, you know, 20 calories,
something like that. Sounds cool. I'll actually try it out because I need to.
It is hugely helpful. Sounds. The issue with Lithuanian food, they don't actually list how
many calories. Unlike in England that everything has, yeah, everything has listed how many calories
the food has and like. Fuck them dog. Go outside the system and get this app. It's super helpful.
Yeah. Everyone, someone called everyone Bobo asks, when is Ben going full homeless boy?
What a puss. What a, what a bust. What a, what a puss. Oh, what a puss. I don't know what he's
getting at. Never. I'm actually fucking iron. Could you have that confused with Tom, perhaps?
I know. Maybe he's talking about me. I feel like maybe. Yeah. Yeah. Are you in, are you in,
are you in Braintree? I'm in local homeless. Yeah, that's true. I'm probably leaving tomorrow.
I think. That's what you said last week. Yeah. Things keep changing. I keep having to like,
my orders that I keep ordering to get all the last stuff for the card keeps getting pushed
back further and further. I'm like, oh, I guess not. Wait. Just be homeless, you coward. I know.
Is the house, is the house actually, are you actually kicked out of the house or are you
choosing? Like, are you just, are you staying until you get the car? Sounds like this is a downhill
slope, but he's going to have to leave eventually or something, right? It's, it's, it's complicated.
Yeah. Well, fair enough. Okay. Okay. Hey, I got a question. I got a question here. It's a good one.
Here it is. It's from Acid Biggie. And this is a deep one. Do you think the PCP is a good influence
on people? No, no. I saw that. I think, I think podcasts in general are a waste of time. What
if you do it? What if you do it while working out? That's true. That's true. What if you literally do
it while working out? If you're doing while doing something else, yes, but a lot of people don't
do that. Sure. Sure. I think that people are going to get whatever they're looking for out of it,
you know, like, it's entertainment, like most entertainment is, is, you know, just, I think
we have our good and bad moments. Feels time and it's fun, but like, I wouldn't say we're changing
people's lives in like, a profound way, except when they're depressed and they feel better. Like,
we're doing what entertainment is. Well, you know, one of my favorite things was this, this like fit
boy thing that we did recently with the fitness podcast and whatnot. And a bunch of people seem
motivated. And even if they only tried it out a little bit, the handful of people who did that,
I mean, it's pretty good. It's pretty good effect. Even if they just went for one job. Even if they
went for one job, they now have the experience of what a jog is like under their belt, if they've
never done it before, and they can build on that. You know, I think, you know, it's only one episode.
I think that it is, I think that it is, you know, I think it's like, I think people are going to get
what they're going to get out of it. I pretty much agree with that. People are going to get what
they're looking for. Yeah. Like if you're an art guy and you listen to this for like inspiration to
do more art, then like that's what you're going to get. Am I making any fucking sense here?
You are. You are. Like I think a lot of the people like, I don't know, would people who like, let's
say, let's say just like an insane person who has like a crazy worldview is going to listen to this,
like what's more likely that they'll like be converted to like, ah, yes, rational discourse.
Yes, everything's good. I mean, not that we even necessarily do that, but like if we did that,
versus, or they're just going to be like, well, I mean, I'm not going to listen to these guys.
You know, I'm out. I'm going to go listen to whatever validates my opinion.
That's probably what's going to happen, you know, for the most part, but it's the people
that you already got in your web that you can give positive messages to. Like our whole thing about
school, we can be a little bit over the top about how evil school is, but I do think it's an actually
good service to do to encourage people to be really critical of what they're going to get out of like
investing in an education, like a post-secondary education and, you know, saving themselves money
and, you know, try another stuff before committing on that, especially if they don't actually know
what they want to do. And you know, there's like things like that. Like I would, everyone thinks
they're a good guy in their own mind. I don't say anything except possibly as jokes, which I do a lot.
I don't say anything that I don't think is going to make the world better, like is true or good.
You know, again, unless it's like a joke, that's obviously for that purpose.
So like, I mean, I would argue that anyone who acts more like me is acting like in a more good way.
So like in that sense, I definitely think it's like a positive influence for people who...
You want people to be like you.
And I think everyone wants people to be like, well, okay, some people don't want that, but yeah.
Yeah. I see a question.
How much truth do you think there is behind the notion? Oh, this is like Kajoro Bitterthorn.
How much truth do you think there's behind the notion? You get more if you pay more.
What matters more to you? The objective or the experience around it?
Example, tasty cheat meal versus the same thing and a fancy restaurant with great ambiance,
presentation, etc. I think that you do not get more if you pay more.
Basically at all. You have to pay a small, a bit to get like good stuff,
like food that is actually nutritious and not bullshit, for example.
But beyond that very low requirement, I think that anything other than food,
anything other than nutriment to sustain your body and four walls and a roof over your head
is an unnecessary luxury and pure vanity and totally unnecessary.
And you're kidding yourself if you think otherwise.
I mean, I think he's... Oh, and a computer, and a fucking internet.
Of course. There you go. I did it.
The getting more doesn't necessarily mean like more bang for one's buck, but like more satisfaction.
Like is it better to just sustain yourself with food or is it better to have a lovely meal?
It really, I think it's a personal... That costs a lot.
I personally don't care about a lovely meal hardly.
Right. It depends on what you're looking for.
If you're someone who gets enjoyment out of that atmosphere and stuff,
and of course you're going to get more value out of that,
but if it's someone like me who doesn't give a fuck,
I'm just going to go there and feel uncomfortable and be like,
I'm just wasting my money, you know?
Yeah. Why did I spend $550 on this plate of asparagus?
For one of my friend's birthdays.
And I was disgusted over the fact that I have this dinky meal
that I'm cooking myself I have to pay $150 for. This is retarded.
Oh, like a Korean barbecue or something like that?
It was... I don't know. I don't think it's... It's like they just have...
Was it a fondue place?
Something like that, yeah.
Okay, okay.
It was retarded and I never want to go back in my life.
Yeah, I hear you.
Yeah, I don't like... A lot of the time, especially with food,
because you eat it and then you shit it and shit doesn't...
It's shit's not good, so I've ruined it.
I've ruined the stuff that I spent all this money on.
Well, it's not ruined.
Flush it down the toilet.
It's sustaining your body.
But like, I feel a lot of the time when I pay money that's expensive,
I think about how much I was ripped off and how cheaper it could have been somewhere else,
or like how if I went to the right shop where it's like a local family restaurant,
where they just do things better because they're like, you know,
the old lady with the Italian special recipe, she just,
hey, I'm gonna do the specialist sauce and she does the thing and it's like,
they do it cheaper because they're a small restaurant,
but they do it better because they're good.
And I'm like, if only I found that restaurant instead of wherever I am,
then it would be... I'm always thinking, fuck, they got my money and, dang it, I don't like...
You know, but there's something to be said.
It's a bad feeling.
There's something to be said for rolling up to a fancy restaurant,
you know, getting your tiny little slivers of meat in asparagus,
sitting across from a beautiful dame and looking out the window at you,
rabble, gazing in at me at this wonderful restaurant,
you know, just enjoying my superior, social superiority.
That's the best thing.
I'm looking through the window and I'm mocking you for being a fucking weed charge.
And I'm mocking you for being a poor boy.
Look at this child, look at this man.
It's not the having the thing, it's the knowing that others don't have it.
It works when you have, like, a significant other to take there to impress them.
But going there alone is like, what am I fucking doing in a restaurant?
Yeah, going alone is kind of... Okay, I want to...
My employee, like, I generally sort of, like, like the idea of sort of a fancy restaurant
and fancy meal, but at the same time, when I actually think about going to is like,
nah, man, I don't want to pay that much for that little.
And it's just like, I'm hungry, dude.
I want to have a nice, nice meal, but like, not for that much.
I like the aesthetics, I like the idea behind it,
but it's like fancy restaurants are usually mega super expensive.
So, no.
The fucking thing I hate the most is when I'm traveling and I'm in the airport and I'm like,
oh, I have to eat.
How much are they gonna extort out of me?
And it's like the shittiest food as well.
It's like a fucking panini in a microwave.
Five euros.
I usually go to the convenience store if there is one and get a pre-made sandwich
and a packet of crisps, and those are usually guaranteed to be normal and understandable
and edible.
I gotta go to the convenience store.
I gotta get me some of that zero calorie Arizona iced tea at Dollar Can.
You know what's good, though?
Guys, you know what's good, though?
Oh, you can eat buffet.
I love that.
Well, sure.
I never been told.
Oh, because he's a British boy, you know?
No, I've been.
Do they not have those in England?
No, they do.
I've never seen one.
I've been in one.
This is the first time I've been in an all-you-can-eat buffet was in England.
I actually, me and my boyfriend later, we sometimes go to Pizza Hub.
They have like all-you-can-eat pizza between 12 and like three or something.
No, from when they opened.
Oh, my gosh.
How much did that cost?
Just had the curiosity to get all-you-can-eat pizza.
For one person, it's 750 pounds.
So that's like, I don't know, $9, $10.
That doesn't sound bad.
That does not sound bad.
Like, the pizza, one single pizza is more pricey than the other pizza.
Yeah, exactly.
Nate, did you know that they have that at Papageno's now?
And I could eat much more than a single pizza in the same thing.
Nate, did you know they have all-you-can-eat buffet at Papageno's now?
They do?
What the fuck?
It's six bucks.
Six bucks?
Yeah.
What?
That doesn't make any sense.
Jesus, I have never been more happy back in New England.
They give you the slice pie slices, too, so they're big ones.
And you can also get pasta.
You know what they do?
You know what they're doing?
I've got it.
They're expecting you to have social anxiety
to prevent you from going up to ask for another pizza.
Ben, go to Papageno's.
Report back.
But you know that's not a problem.
Of course.
I've done it before.
We've gotten entire slice pies and then some.
That's great.
You guys should go.
The good thing about the Pizza Hut,
you just go get the slices yourself.
You don't have to bother anyone.
Well, see, I like that.
I do like that.
It is good.
That is good, Ben.
Less standing between me and my infinite pizza.
A lot of different pizzas as well.
I like to vary it up.
Biter just eats the one pepperoni pizza,
maybe margarita if they have margarita.
I like margarita.
I think the reason I've never been to an all-you-can-eat
buffet is because I don't eat that much.
And I don't think I would get.
I think I would actually lose money
by going to one of those things
because I would eat less food than it costs to get in.
It really depends on the buffet.
Another buffet I've been to that closed down
was the actual first one I've been to
when I came to live in England.
It was a Chinese food buffet.
And I just sort of dug into the food they had,
like what's it called, not snacks,
but the food you have before the main dish.
Appetizer?
Appetizers.
Yeah, I really love the appetizers so much
I would just get my fill in appetizers.
Oh, man.
I went to...
But it was really cheap.
It was like $4.50, I think.
I went out for Pokemon Community Day catching squirtles.
I got my fucking purple shiny Blastoise
with the sunglasses with the Kazi.
It was out with Kazi and the Busty Coins.
I got a bunch of squirts, but no shinies.
Yeah, they were...
You had the request.
The request that lets you do get like...
Man, what the fuck?
Son of a boss.
Whatever, boys.
Yeah, I got my fucking killer Blastoise.
It's sick.
Anyway, the point is I went to PF Chang's
and I just ate...
Doing keto, just ate fucking ribs.
I just got two orders of appetizer spare ribs.
I ate one, I got one for six bucks and I ate it
and I was like, that was great.
I want more food, but I don't want a side dish.
I'm just going to get a second set of ribs.
It was only $12 for like a shit ton of fucking ribs.
It was really great.
Sounds pretty good.
Highly recommended.
All right, enough.
This is almost three hours.
All right, he's right, he's right.
Oh, I need to go to bed.
That sounds good.
Oh, God.
And now I'm really hungry, but I have to go to bed.
Me too.
This is a terrible question to end on.
I haven't fucking eaten all day, so thanks, guys.
Let me end this episode on a prayer.
I found this randomly on Twitter.
It's from atchorpsaway.
And here it is.
This is Squall from Final Fantasy VIII.
And I quote, I just don't get it.
You can't have a boneless chicken wing.
It's just a saucy chicken nugget at that point.
Thank you, everyone.
For being on this episode of the Procrastinators podcast.
Have a good day.
Have a good night.
Good night, everyone.
Patreon.com slash theprocrastinators.
$5 for all the bonus episodes.
$1 to get in our extra special patron chat.
And then the world's your oyster above that.
What else?
A red bubble.
There's some shirts.
Go buy them.
You know, that's cool.
You can buy that fucking bonus content from Radcon.
Go check all the Radcon shit if you haven't.
Watch the playlist.
Don't be lame.
Be cool.
That's my recommendation for you.
All right, that's it.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
We'll see you next time with an extra dank meme.
Yeah!
Get ready to do that, everybody.
All right, I'll see you later.
Bye-bye.
Good-bye.
Yeah.
Oh, dude.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.