Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast, a podcast
about internet people talking about stuff.
I'm the best guy ever and we're joined today by Munchy wears tiny hats.
Don't let my mom know I'm here, I'm sneaking out, I went to the, we're in the back of
a Barnes and Nobles where they sell the porn.
Don't let my mom know or she'll know that I have carnal sins and that she will kick
me out of my satertium.
Yes, excellent. Hippocrit is here.
I haven't eaten in hours and I have a burger in front of me and if I make a noise I'm sorry.
Okay, good. Tom Oliver is joining us.
You're not supposed to know I'm here, it's a secret.
Oh well now the cat's out of the bag, and Mumkey Jones.
Jon Tron just put up a new video!
One of you could go. Impressive shrieking.
Didn't I start to feel a riot?
Alright everybody, let's not fuck around.
Today our topic of discussion is, it's apropos that you mentioned Barnes and Nobles because
we're reviewing The Secret, the world-famous book that everyone loves that taught the world
to love again, to feel, to be a real guy.
I thought it was The Secret, like ooze and slime come out of it.
Like secreting ooze.
Yes, yes, that too, it's all these things.
When you said secret, the first thing I thought of was like secreting anal juices and I don't know why.
I don't know why juices are there besides poop or diarrhea.
There's a lot of anal juice you don't know about Nate, that's one of my secrets.
Got a lot to learn.
Well there you go, okay you know what, let's all scrap that.
The secret topic of the episode.
I forgot Hippo was eating.
Yeah, I was just gonna say.
Oh fuck you, this is what you get.
Oh, thank you.
I'm into eating fags.
So yeah, we're talking about secrets everybody.
We're talking about secrets.
That's the real secret of this episode.
And here is the Urban Dictionary definition of secret.
Here it is.
Can't tell you.
That's it, that's the whole thing.
Okay, here's definition number two.
Information, you tell someone when you spelled with just the letter you,
when you want it to become public knowledge by morning.
That's perfect because that's every story I have to tell about this topic.
Oh, that's good, that's good.
Yes, that is good.
I like this.
Secret, strong enough for a man made for a woman.
These are all great.
Urban Dictionary, you're killing it today buddy.
Urban Dictionary is the main success of the PCP, yeah.
Yeah, we owe them everything.
So secrets, they are good, they are bad, they are gay across the board.
What secrets do you have, Munchy?
I'm paranoid, just to start out.
I might be the most paranoid PCP member next to you, Nate.
I am very paranoid.
That's a tall order.
Yeah, yeah, you're more paranoid than I am.
But needless to say, whenever I look at someone,
I instantly just assume they want to kill me.
And therefore, I have to assert my dominance.
I have to have emotional power over them to ensure that they want to talk to me.
Therefore, it's in their best interest not to kill me.
I know just how you feel.
I don't trust anyone.
I don't trust anyone at any time.
And I need to know that I have leverage over them in some way, even if it's just social.
Yeah, that sounds good, man.
Yeah, yeah.
So, I don't really have a lot of secrets per se,
but I allow just knowledge.
I have knowledge and smarts and wisdom that I keep inside my brain.
And any person, and if you were to look inside my brain,
you'd be like, ooh, tasty, and you would slip it all up, and Jesus, get out of here.
I would say to you, prying into my brain.
Yeah.
I don't like it when people know things.
Even, common, I don't like it when textbooks are out.
I don't like it when people are learning.
So, basically, you're against non-secrets.
You think all information should be contained in the form of secrets
as no one should have access to it.
I'm against education and learning as a concept.
I'm against self-betterment in any sort of way.
The fake news advocate.
Oh, you're the number one champion of fake news in the world after Hillary Clinton, of course.
Incredible.
Let me get some hand sanitizer.
One not secrets.
I love hand sanitizer.
You guys don't have to be my friend to know that.
Everyone knows when I get out my dinner of hand sanitizer, and I just slip you down.
Okay, good.
Is anyone else have any secret story?
I mean, Mom, you were implying that you had a couple stories about secrets.
What do you got for us?
Well, last episode, during the incest discussion,
we all heard the great tale of how I got cucked by my best friend and his sister.
And that was supposed to be a big secret that she confessed to me
and made me promise I would not tell anybody.
And as Urban Dictionary, let us all know.
The next morning was when I pretty much let everybody know,
because here's the thing about secrets.
I would like to think that I'm pretty trustworthy.
I would like to think if somebody gave me a secret,
they didn't want me to tell anybody.
I would stay true to that.
However, and I think this is a rule that should apply to everybody.
If the secret somebody is confessing to you is something that completely fucks you over.
Like if a girlfriend is telling you, oh, here's the secret.
I cheated on you.
Why in the fuck would I be expected not to tell everybody?
That's the front page of Facebook tomorrow morning, my friend.
You know, I forget the name of it, but that reminds me of this great episode of the boondocks,
where like the two, I forgot the name of the two white guys who are played by like Samuel Jackson
and another guy.
Yeah, like, it's great.
It's great.
But that, like the episode is about, I forget the name of like the rule or whatever,
but it's about like Riley gets like his shit stolen by those guys.
Like they're huge assholes that just take his shit,
but like no one will talk to the cops.
Like no one's gonna, what's it called, snitch it, no snitch it.
That's sort of the word I'm looking for.
So it's all about how like these guys are like terrorizing the neighborhood
and everyone's like looking for them because they're just ruining everyone's fucking life.
But Riley insists on not being a fucking snitch.
And because he's like the only one to witness them.
And then I believe actually, okay, so they don't do anything necessarily bad to him,
but at the end of the episode, so they're just in general ruining the neighborhood,
which has a minor impact on Riley's life, which kind of sucks.
But then at the end of the episode, they just steal his bike and like ride off with it.
And he's just like, they just like treat him like a punk bitch and totally fuck him over.
And then the cops will walk up and they're like, son,
does something happen here? Is there, is there anything you'd like to tell us?
And you can see him like, like tears are fucking leaking out of his eyes.
He's like clenching his fists and just screaming at the injustice of all.
He's like, nah nigga, I see shit.
It was fucking great. That, that non snitching rule is,
and then you see like in the background, as you say that to the cops,
they're just joyriding on the motorcycle being like,
yo, this bike is fucking dope dog.
Gonna smash this shit. Gonna fucking wreck that bike pussy.
Yeah, it was a great episode.
I wreck that bike pussy every single day of my life.
Mom curious to see if you guys agree with this sort of philosophy of the morality of secrets
in that if, if the secret you're holding makes your life worse by not confessing it,
do you have a right to confess it?
If it will improve the quality of your life by.
I mean, I guess if it comes down to like, if you break the promise,
what happens to your life?
Do people not trust you?
Or is it just the person that told you the secret doesn't trust you with knowledge?
Because like, you gotta, you gotta weigh the options of what will happen to you.
If your life will become so much better by confessing that it doesn't matter if people
think you might not be trustworthy, then of course.
Like I don't, I don't see the, I don't see the point in having a pride about being
trustworthy if your life is shit because of it.
Yeah, yeah, that's the thing.
That's what, that was Riley's problem, you know?
He, he fucked his life over by just being too committed to his ideology there.
I, yeah, I think that, I think that the two are kind of discreet factors,
but there's a context for everything and there's, there's a limit to how much you
should like hold any one position like that.
Like truth is really not always the best policy.
If, if your hoe ass look fat, she don't want to know her ass look fat, you know, you just.
Well, sometimes she does.
Well, sometimes.
Again, it depends on the context.
I don't think it's a secret that that hoe's ass looks fat.
I think she knows it anyway.
But, but here, here's the context.
Like if you're going out for a, for a night on the town with your lady and she says to you like,
do I look fat?
You say, no, you look beautiful.
You know, you can, you can say that shit and that's not, that's totally fine.
It's a white light.
If she is like in a fitness competition and she's been working and training and her ass
does legitimately look incredibly fat and she's totally unprepared for the competition
and she's like, okay, dude, does my ass look fat?
I need to know for this competition.
I don't want to get humiliated up there.
If you lie and plakie her and tell her like, no.
Exactly.
And then she, uh, well, in her ass does in fact look fat.
And like, like that's you sort of fucking her over through lying that way.
That's like, see, that's the two different ways to treat that particular example.
You know, yeah.
I don't know if it's, I don't know if it's wrong per se, you know, ever.
Well, okay.
Wrong.
Like it's not like against the law to fucking tell a secret.
I guess lying and secrets are two different things incidentally.
Yeah, I was going to say.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
But, but, but, well, okay.
But they're kind of linked to you.
They're kind of the same thing.
So they're linked, they're linked.
Well, that there's, there's secrets that you keep the secrets that you keep for other people.
And then there are secrets that you just know and that are, you know, nobody confided in you.
You just know something and you don't know whether to tell anyone.
And when you do, they now have your secret, I guess.
We all have a secret.
It's like having the knowledge that you know that Osama bin Laden isn't the leader of the Taliban.
Like everyone wants to pretend that he is, but you don't want to tell the government because
you know that if they find out the truth that you are actually the leader of the Taliban,
they call that for you next.
It's a situation like that.
To that point about how I am the leader of ISIS, you know, it's like, it's, I do think that those
are two discrete factors to, to a monkey's point there.
Like if you decide that you want to like, you know, like, okay, for example,
like the common example people bring up for stuff like this is like you're a Catholic priest
and like a murderer confesses, you know, and then like, okay, so like this guy is a murderer.
And let's say he doesn't immediately plan to kill anybody else, but you never know.
You know, he's an unstable kind of guy.
He's like, I'm sorry, father.
I don't want to do it, et cetera, et cetera.
Like, first of all, I don't care about religion at all.
So I don't give a fuck about any of their like religious oaths.
But in terms of like the social standing there about how these guys like come here just to confess,
like frankly, the whole confession thing to me, I guess I'm going on a little bit of a tangent,
tangent, but like the confession thing is sort of a way that like these guys get to like ease
the burden of the sins that they've done.
And I don't want them to be eased of their burden.
I want them to be crushed under the weight of the crimes they've committed because they deserve it.
At least, I guess not every single time, but you know, with stuff like this.
But in any case, yeah, like if the priest decides that it's, he really needs to like
come forward, that like really does help the world.
It's like a good thing to do if you're like getting a guy like that off the streets.
But you are showing that you are willing to like break your oaths of secrecy and shit.
Just a negative consequence in other ways.
Do you think that there's a delicate balance between justice and secrecy?
Or do you think justice should always be more important than like keeping an oath?
You know, it's tough.
Since we live in the real world and not a fantasy world where you can like always expect
perfect justice all the time, I think sometimes it is appropriate to conceal things that might
help people if it would cause other problems, you know?
Like if you tell someone that like, fuck, I don't know, like if someone's got amnesia
and they used to be a murderer and like they now that like they had amnesia, they woke up,
they're in a new place and they're just like a new person and they're a really good person or
something.
Like does it make sense to then like sentence this person for the crimes that they committed before?
Like I know that's a crazy example, but that's the sort of idea I'm getting at.
But wouldn't it bring like peace to the families because now they know who killed their person
and like all that stuff?
That's true.
But again, like you're weighing a family's satisfaction at a man, you know, being locked
up versus like now there's a guy who, in this one example, who isn't causing any problems,
who you're going to lock up because of, you know, a situation that's basically been resolved on his
and no one else is going to be hurt.
And you know, it kind of comes down to the whole idea of like, what is the purpose of it?
You're assuming that there's going to be no like resurgence of memories where he's not going to
then go off and kill again.
Like it's very, like you know everything about the situation.
Yeah, by that same logic, like you just be some murder who didn't lose his memory,
but still decides, you know what?
I killed that one guy, I got it out of my system.
Now I'm just going to be an upstanding gentleman and like for the rest of his life he never does anything.
He goes to prison.
Well, hang on.
Okay, there's actually a cool example of this.
There was a guy recently who, fuck, what did he do?
I don't know.
He had done something and he was sentenced to like, I think like 20 years or something,
maybe less than that.
And when he was a kid he committed some crime, got sentenced, whatever.
And so like, so there's a thing when you get sentenced, if you're on bail, like
you get sent like a note to like bring yourself to jail, like report to jail now.
They don't fucking carry you off unless, you know, they like have you the whole time.
If you've been bailed out, you got to report yourself to jail.
Like this guy just didn't go and then nobody ever came for him because like paperwork got fucked up.
So then he spent like 40 years like constantly terrified that like someone was going to come
and nab him because he knew he had done this shit.
And he like started a family, did all this crazy shit.
And the thing is he really turned his life around and became a great guy.
So like did he pay the price of like, you know, committing the crime that he did legitimately
commit?
I mean, according to the law, no, but in the in the grander scheme of things,
the suffering that he went through of like living life on the edge all the time and being so afraid
of fucking anything up and getting his name like in the legal books in that way,
that's a punishment in of its own.
Talk about a secret, secret life and it's funny.
He didn't even tell like his wife and kids.
So like later on when they actually like the paperwork did get sorted and they came for him.
Oh God.
That was, he was like, honey, there's something I need to tell you.
Incidentally, in that case, they let the guy go because like it was such a clear case that he had
just, he had served his sentence basically by making himself a real nigga.
And what's worse, being in prison or having a family, I think he's paying for his crimes.
Yeah, you got a ball and chain on you either way.
Yeah, you're fucked.
Tom, tell me all your secrets.
I want the whole.
We got all night, baby.
I don't know.
I don't really, do I have any secrets if I do them?
So they're so innocuous.
Tom, tell me what they are.
Tell me this, Tom, you never liked my little pony.
You just did it for that Oculus Rift money.
Yeah, I actually have like seven Oculus Rifts.
I have one for every day of the week.
Oh my God.
Yeah, it's fucking great.
Fucking scum.
I even have an HTC Vive for the weekends.
It's fantastic.
I'm going, I'm a fucking ballin' over here now.
He played us.
Anybody had an experience where you shared a secret and that person was not trustworthy?
Yes.
Good question.
I don't know if I have much.
Muchy, what do you got buddy?
Yes, when I was in fifth grade, there was some sort of a school dance of some sort
where all the little babies would touch their flabby meat against one another
and would be a disgusting display for only the depraved and twisted to have any sort of,
you know, illicit reaction to.
Anyway, I went there with my friend, Rocky.
Rocky is like the source of my music for all of my fucking young life.
Whenever I hear the name Rocky, I instantly get like fucking like PDST.
Yeah, okay.
I just want to jump out a window so I can get away from the sound.
Anyway, I go there and I'm ordering, I'm ordering fucking Sprite and Skittles and I'm
fucking going, I'm going all out.
I'm fucking, I'm going on a bender, bro.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna fucking wake up in a ditch after I'm done at this place.
Anyway, so I just, I just fucking, I'm just walking with them and he's like,
fuck it, I love Wii Sports.
I'm like, dude, I know.
Anyway, here's the big secret.
Oh no, you spilled the beans.
No, no, then I forget what happens and, and, and, and I was just like, dude,
what if like girls weren't awful?
And he was like, dude, I'm going to go tell that girl right now that you, oh no.
And then I was like, what?
That doesn't make any sense.
And he went and did it.
And then I was just like, I don't know who you are.
And she was like, it's okay if you love me.
I understand.
I'm beautiful.
And I was just confused and scared.
And I ran to the bathroom because I hate women.
And I, and, and, and, and that fucking Chad was just going to fucking ruin my night.
And I couldn't finish eating my fucking, I accidentally dropped my fucking gummy worms
on the floor so I couldn't finish eating them because they were on the floor.
I just wanted to eat my gummy worms and spray.
I just wanted to eat what I came to the dance floor.
I wanted to eat the gummy worms.
Did you guys ever have, I think they're called like dirt cups or whatever.
They're chocolate pudding with Oreo crumble on the top.
And gummy worms in them.
Snow secret.
Those are the best things ever.
Slam dunk.
All of you.
All of you are beautiful.
F, all of you for the slam dunk, dude.
Yeah.
Okay.
Good.
Gib.
And I've forgipped him immediately because I had no other friends.
Oh, you did.
That's the way to do it.
Gib, tell me your secret.
Okay.
Gladly.
Actually, hang on.
I just got to take a bite of this, this burger.
It's been sitting here this whole time.
I'm really hungry.
Okay.
Now's your chance.
While your time to speak has come.
That's the perfect time to make a big fucking bite out of this burger, dude.
Okay.
Don't worry about us.
Okay, go.
Well, my secret is one slime of the worm and I broke them.
Keep it going.
And God, excuse me.
This is juicy.
And then I tried to eat the other one.
And it just didn't fit.
You buried the body there?
What the fuck?
Oh, no.
I'm sorry, hippo.
I can barely understand you.
All that anal juice in your mouth.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
But yeah, that's basically what happened.
I couldn't understand him because he has a stupid accent.
Look at down below.
Here comes the net.
A slammer come come come.
Go to the hero.
Yeah.
So yeah, that's my secret.
That was a bombshell.
I've got a story of the time a friend betrayed me and did not keep a secret.
Mm-hmm.
It was third grade.
I was eight years old.
I had this friend named Hunter and I lived out in the country.
So whenever I went to go stay the night at Hunter's house,
I could finally be out in the suburbs, baby.
We could raise some hell in a place where there's actually people.
And I'm not just alone in the middle of nowhere.
And Hunter has this checkbook of blank checks.
I don't know where he got it because he's eight.
But we thought, you know what would be funny as hell?
What if we filled out one of these checks for a million dollars?
And we went to our friend Will's house and we put it in his mailbox.
That would be the funniest thing of all time.
And thinking back, I don't know why we thought it would be funny.
I have no idea.
No idea.
So we do it.
And it's this big secret because we know,
we know for some reason that it's the biggest law in the world.
It's some big federal law that you're not allowed to touch anybody's mailbox
for any reason unless you're a mailman.
So we're like, oh man, what a big secret.
Oh man, we did this big prank.
We put a check in his mailbox.
We're going to get in so much trouble.
We're going to get arrested if they find out.
The next day at school.
The special something teacher.
She's not like a special ed teacher,
but she's like a guidance kind of bitch.
I don't like it.
She's the type of feminist bitch where she hyphenates her last name.
So it's like her name, dash, husband's last name.
Disgusting.
I hate it.
Pick a side, you fucking horrors.
One or the other.
I don't care if you want to empower yourself and just keep your name.
That's fine.
I would prefer that.
I don't give a shit.
But to hyphenate, disgusting.
Fuck you.
This bitch shows up to the classroom that me and Hunter are in.
And she says, Jimmy, Jimmy, come here.
I'm like, uh-oh.
Uh-oh, that's not good.
They're going to interview us one at a time.
That's not good.
So she sits me down.
I'm alone in the room with her.
And she says, classic.
So did you and your friend Hunter do anything yesterday?
I'm like, no, no.
I don't know what you're talking about.
And she says, you know, I heard this rumor
that you might have put something in someone's mailbox.
Oh, no.
Red alert.
What are we going to do?
I got to make up some sort of crazy lie.
But at the same time, Hunter is also going to be interviewed.
And if he doesn't have the same crazy lie as me, then we're fucked.
That's the classic divide and conquer interrogation technique.
Absolutely.
So I say, oh, oh, that was just a joke.
We made up a joke that we did that.
We didn't actually do that.
It was just a joke.
And she says, oh, uh-huh.
OK, it was a joke.
So she takes me back to the classroom and says, hey, Hunter,
can you come with me?
In front of everybody, there's 20 other kids,
two teachers in the room.
And I say, hey, Hunter, yes.
She wants to ask us about that joke we told.
Remember that joke?
Well done.
Nice.
Yeah.
I thought I was super conspicuous about it.
Like, hey, you know that joke?
Go tell her about it.
About five minutes later, Hunter's back.
And she calls me out again.
Uh-oh.
Fuck.
And of course, she's more mad that I lied to her
than that we put something in someone's mailbox.
Because as it turns out, we're not in trouble for that.
So I don't know why she even called us out in the first place.
So that's the time Hunter betrayed me.
He couldn't keep the secret.
And he didn't know what a joke was.
Fuck you, Hunter.
I hope you burn in hell.
What a shitty teacher to just interrogate them
on the off chance that you can get in trouble from it.
Yeah.
I mean, what was her?
What was she actually interrogating you about?
Because like, she didn't know about, I mean,
the mailbox thing wasn't a problem.
I just want to see if these kids lie to me
so I can beat the shit out of them.
I don't know.
You didn't get in trouble for the mailbox stuff.
Like, I have no idea what the point of it was.
But it was over 15, about 15 years ago.
So maybe I'm missing a detail in my memory,
but I just remember that part.
Monkey, I want to know, in your school,
did every time a single person,
like, can you come to the office, please,
did the entire fucking room go, ooh?
Oh, of course.
And it was me every time.
I was going to go to his office every other month
in elementary school.
Calm down, Mark Simpson.
I remember one time, if we want to tell stories
about how we got in trouble in elementary school.
I definitely do.
The first time I got sent to the principal's office
was because when I was five, so this is like kindergarten,
recess is over, and we're all lining up to go back inside.
And I don't know what came over me.
But for some reason, there's this girl named Lauren,
who I kind of liked.
In front of everybody, I just fucking yell,
hey, Lauren, take off your pants.
And I have no idea what came over me,
why I would even say that.
I don't actually want to see this little girl with pants off.
You were just getting straight to the act.
You're getting down to business.
I guess so.
In your instance, yeah.
Next thing I know, I'm in the principal's office.
But luckily, this principal was the type of guy
who would say, so what'd you do?
And then you tell him what you did.
And then he laughs at your story
because you're a stupid kid doing stupid shit.
And then he says, don't do it again.
And then you go back to class.
So at least the principal was a cool guy.
That's good.
My elementary school woes are as long as fucking
scripture verses.
However, however, one that's somewhat related to this
is one time, again, with fucking,
what's his fucking ass, bitch ass name?
Rocky, Rocky, Rocky, Rocky.
There was another friend I knew named Sean.
And he was like this fucking weird sort of like-
He was an audio engineer.
Yeah, he was an audio engineer.
He was like a fucking, he was like a super hall monitor.
Instead of like a hall monitor, he was a world monitor.
He monitored every action to every system.
And a hero.
Yeah, yeah.
So-
I'm picturing him as the all-seeing eye of Sauron.
Yeah, yeah.
About the hallways.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, exactly.
But with the badge on.
And in a way to show off the badge.
Like, even when he was-
And even when we were in golf school,
he would just put his badge on over his fucking shirt,
just no matter what.
He'd just be like-
A world monitor.
And whenever I said-
And then whenever we got into a fight,
he would just say,
Dude, look at the badge, bro.
Look at the badge.
Look at the badge, dude.
Look at it.
Respect it.
Yeah, respect the badge.
Anyway, so Rocky just makes up this lie
that I've stolen his video game
because he's fucking Rocky.
Because he's fucking Rocky and get away with anyone
because his parents are divorced
and everyone has to be sorry for him
because his parents are divorced.
I don't care if his parents are divorced, Rocky.
I hate you.
Me too, dude.
Anyway, he makes up a lie
because he wants to get me back
because I think I like-
Because I beat him at Wii Sports
and he got super fucking pissed
after his controller.
And as we've established,
he loves Wii Sports.
Yeah, you look at-
He takes this kind of embarrassment, right?
In front of his whole family and clan.
He needs to redeem himself.
So he wants to fuck me over.
And so he gets Sean to interrogate me.
He's like-
And Sean comes over here and he takes me aside
and he's like, dude, I heard a rumor.
Is it true you're a thief?
Is it true that you've broken the law?
Those are some serious aspersions we've heard about.
Jesus Christ.
And I know I'm innocent,
so I just say, what do you think?
And I spit on his badge.
You spit on his badge?
Fuck your authority, world monitor.
And he's just like-
He's like, you're reckless,
but I believe you.
What the fuck?
Greatest turn of phrase.
Okay, all right.
That's what the policeman says
at the end of the thrilling action movie
where he's been intellectually dueling
with a goal-hearted criminal,
which is you in this case.
Fuck, what was it again?
What was the line?
You're reckless, but I believe you.
Yes.
The moment when respect was forged for a lifetime.
Brothers in arms.
And so what he does is,
me and Rocky are in the same class
and he's like been like eyeing me,
like fucking off,
fucking look at this fucking guy,
look at this fucking guy.
And then I walk back and I'm smiling,
I'm smiling wisely,
knowing that my superior errant life
has gotten me out of yet another jam.
And then Sean fucking like is like,
Rocky, we need to talk now.
And so Rocky starts losing his fucking shit
and is like scared that his life has been found out.
So he walks out and I hear,
like I don't know about this during the time,
but then like I meet up with Sean after school
and he just says, I told him,
I told him that I found out the truth
and that he can't hide the truth
from the world monitor himself.
Yeah, actually, by the way,
he called himself the world monitor, by the way.
That wasn't me making up.
He really did?
He called himself the world monitor.
Wow, you give a man a taste of power
and he wants to take it all.
He wants control of everything.
It's his better, his ill nature,
got a hold of him, his senses.
Anyway, so Rocky was shamed from the entire class
and Sean just said he was untrustworthy.
But after school, Rocky said,
I don't have anyone play Wii sports with me.
Can you please come over now?
I was like, okay, but I have to have a Smarties.
I have to have a Smarties.
I need to have one of your Smarties.
And he gave me one of their Smarties
and I played Wii sports and I beat him again.
He yelled at me and told me to leave the room.
It was a good time.
Wow, it was a good time.
What a journey.
Real quick here, also in middle school,
I was known for picking people up.
That was like what I did.
I was the person who picked people up
because I was just so massive and girthy
that I could do whatever I want.
And so I would pick people up.
And people like line up for like 10 people
would line up for me to pick them up
and just like set them back down.
I was the main attraction to the fucking playground.
Anyway, so this-
Maybe they actually just wanted a hug.
Yeah, maybe.
So this stupid ass fucking punk ass crippled motherfucker
rolls up in his fucking wheelchair and-
Ah, Jesus.
Always causing problems the goddamn disabled.
Fuck off.
A fucking apologizer, right?
Apologize already.
Anyway, so he's like, please, let me get a ride on arms.
I need to know it's like to feel young again.
And so I'm like, you know what?
I'll take pity on you fucking disabled, disabled man.
And so I lift him up and immediately he's like spying cracks.
Like he like-
Oh, Jesus.
He gets the wind taken out of him.
And so I set him down in his wheelchair
and I'm like, this is what you fucking get.
And then he rolls off to tell the fucking principle.
What the fuck?
Yeah.
Was this a kid or an actual old man?
No, this is like, you know, this is a child.
What's the difference between a child
who's that weak and an old man?
There is none.
They're basically the same thing.
Okay.
Anyway, so I get in trouble for him wanting me to pick him up
and providing that service for him.
There's no justice.
I did what he wanted me to do and I got fucking-
Dude, and the worst thing is I would like-
He like went to tell the principle
when it was like end of lunchtime.
So I just went to class.
And then like I heard-
I was like some sort of like computer science class
or some of that effect.
And we were just in the computer lab.
And I heard people looking around me
and they're just like, did you hear so-and-so
who got the fucking Winby down?
Yeah, I heard someone fucking throw him down the ground.
Right.
I was like, no, it's not true!
Down on the ground, you fucking cripple!
It's not true.
I'm a good boy.
And then I went to the principal's office and he was-
And he-
And like I walked into his office
and he was like looking through the Venetian blinds.
Everything was dark and he was just like,
he was just like, menacing.
What did you do?
And I just like started-
I was like, I provided the service he wanted.
I provided the service he wanted.
I'm a good guy.
I'm a good vendor.
I'm a good host.
And then it was just like, it's not good enough.
And so he sent it to me to detention.
It was a scary time.
That was a big secret, guys.
It was a big secret.
Yeah, good secret.
Good secret.
When I think of secrets,
a lot of the times I think of gossip.
Because that's usually like-
It's never been said, hey, here's a secret.
Blah, blah, blah, this and that.
It's usually like, oh, I heard from one person,
a friend of a person, that they're going through this.
Did you hear this?
Yeah, you're not really supposed to bring it up
unless you want to be a gossipy person.
I don't know.
I don't really feel like I have any secrets
that I remember holding or getting given.
Because despite being the kid that never said anything
and was known for not doing any words out of my mouth,
like nobody thought, this guy I can confide in.
I guess nobody had anything to say, or at least not to me.
And I never had anything I cared to say to anyone else.
Because it's like-
Never under any circumstances.
Because a lot of the time, it's gossip.
It's like, why would you tell someone else about this thing?
Because you want to feel the rush of it going behind someone's back,
or I guess.
And I don't get that.
I don't feel that.
So I never had a secret.
I think gossiping gives people a sense of empowerment.
When they're sharing new information with someone,
that's a gift they get to give out.
And they get to watch the person give them credit
for being the one who shared that.
Something like that, anyway.
I would say I am the duality of man.
It personified.
If I do say so myself.
Dr. Munchy and Mr. Hat.
Yeah, exactly.
Uh, I like am gossipy, I think.
But if you tell me to not say something, then I will not.
Like, I get off on being loyal.
If someone's like, don't do this thing, I'll be like,
fuck you, I'm not going to fucking do that.
I'm going to fucking-
I'm going to take this to the fucking grave.
I'm like that.
But if it's like, did you hear that I have fucked a dog before?
What do you think about that, huh?
I'll be like-
Everyone's going to know about this guy fucking that dog.
Why did you tell Ben's secret?
He's like, I guess I'm gossipy like normal,
like a normal human level.
Like, if somebody is brought up in conversation
and it doesn't seem that bad to say,
hey, I heard that they eat shit, like, you know.
Not that bad.
Like, they're well-known for eating shit.
I just thought, you know, you might like to know,
I want to be part of this conversation.
I got to say something.
But like, I don't know.
Like, I don't-
I'm just like discussing things and like,
I'm gossiping in the sense that like, if there's a problem,
if there's-
If like, someone's like working through a problem,
that's like not-
Like, it's not like a secret.
Like, I'm having a fucking clash in my soul.
If it's just like, yeah, I don't know how to fucking do this thing
with this guy, whatever, do-do-do-do-do-do.
Then I'll want to discuss that and like,
like with other people and like, come up with like,
I want to like, task force fucking like, police.
Like, how do I get this person to be happy?
Kind of like a-
Actually, wait, I figured out why I'm thinking.
I figured out why I can't think of any secrets.
It's because I don't think of them-
When I think of a secret,
I think of something you want to tell people.
And I don't care about anything that I'm told.
If somebody says something to me,
I won't ever say it to anyone else, really.
And if they expressly say, please don't tell anyone,
I'll be like, yeah, yeah, of course.
And it won't even feel like a secret.
It won't feel like I'm-
It's just waiting to be unleashed on people.
Like, it's not even part of my brain anymore.
It's just sort of like, oh yeah, I guess I know that.
I get it.
Calling something a secret can kind of
give it a red flag in your memory
and it'll make you kind of want to talk about it.
So yeah, sometimes you're better off.
It'll make you want to secrete it from your anus.
Hippo, we're trying to eat over here.
Let's discuss in brief.
So this has been coming up a couple of times.
So like, are we all in agreement that honesty is not always the best policy?
Does anyone feel differently from that?
I would say it's usually the best,
but there are times when you lie and it is just better.
All this has to do with deals and absolutes.
I like being honest and being known as someone who just-
Like, if I say something, I want people to know that that's what I mean.
Unless I'm obviously doing it in a silly voice and it's a joke.
But like, I hate people who hope that you understand something from-
like, you know, they want you to get it without them saying it.
I would rather just be a person who says it.
You're talking about women.
You're talking about women, right?
That's my secret.
I'm gay.
In fairness, men do it too.
Oh yeah, yeah, of course.
It's not really a secret after the fetish episode.
I want to know what you think.
I also like being like honestly known as like,
if I say this, then it's like real.
I do like having to not specify this isn't a joke, by the way.
This is a real thing that I truly do believe.
But I never believe anything anyone says to me, almost ever.
I always have to be like, really?
Is that really?
And then like five more rounds and I'll be like,
maybe I believe you, possibly.
So basically, you'll believe things the more times that they're insisted upon
by the person as long as they don't change the story or crack
under the psychological pressure of your interrogation.
I like to believe that everyone is real and that everything they say is completely true
unless otherwise specified because especially on the internet,
thinking any other way is confusing and time consuming.
Just think about like, oh, are they real?
Are they saying that for real?
No, they're completely true because they haven't said,
by the way, I'm lying yet.
I think you have to take the opposite approach online.
I think you should assume everybody is lying until proven honest.
I basically agree with that.
It's funnier if I just think everyone's real.
Well, even not just online, but in all aspects of life,
I was going to say that I don't think there's a single person in the world.
I mean, it depends what you mean by truth.
But I think that everyone is constantly wearing different masks
and they're presenting themselves differently to different people.
And that doesn't, in a situation like here, recording the PCP,
I behave a certain way.
And then in a different situation, I might act differently
if I'm with a different crowd or like when I'm at work.
You know, when I'm at work, that's me.
Is it me keeping a secret that I don't present myself at work
the same way I do on here?
I don't think so.
I think everybody knows you have to have a professional attitude when you're at work.
I don't think you've, and everybody you know at work,
that's not really them.
That's like them putting on their serious face, you know?
Sure.
And I don't know, I don't really think there's a moral issue with most secrets,
unless there's, you know, some important thing attached to them.
If we're talking about like masks and shit,
I feel like the masks you wear the most often is the true you,
but it doesn't really matter too much whether you're true all the time.
I don't think that's the true you, but okay.
Well, like all of the different masks are you,
but like you can only see a couple of them at a time.
If you want to say as a matter of convenience,
like when you like go, okay, so when you're at work, you're like doing a job,
you're interacting with people, that's you acting a certain way.
Then when you like, when you get out and you go home and you're just like chilling,
like maybe that's the true you.
But here's the, here's a question though.
If you spend like, let's just say your job is incredibly intense,
and you spend 16 hours a day at work with your game face on,
and then you only spend eight hours a day at home,
does that mean the true you is now the work you,
based on the time, the percentage that's been?
I don't know, I just threw that idea out there.
Is it your resting position?
Maybe it's your resting position.
I think it's the true you.
If you have to, if you're at any point,
if you're filtering your thought and actions through like what you believe
is socially acceptable in that situation,
I don't think that's your true self.
Your true self is when like, I'm just going to do what I want,
and I'm not worried about consequences or judgments.
That's who you really are.
Yeah, but then everybody would be a rapist.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Like, but the fact that I have never,
well, okay, that's not going to be personally,
but like people.
Yeah, it's not a secret podcast.
It is, that's true.
We all, I mean, you know, we've all had a desire to like,
ooh, that's a nice piece of candy.
It'd be sure nice to pocket that and just walk out.
I'm not going to pay $10 for this fucking lollipop or whatever.
Yeah, you know, we all do converges.
If you're charging $10, you have a moral obligation to steal that candy.
Yeah, that's true, that's true.
Okay, okay.
I would describe your quote unquote true stuff like this.
Imagine a nice roll or ball of slime and gel,
and sort of, you know, delicious meat kiss.
Don't gotta tell me twice.
I have mine here before me, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Would it be green?
It can be whatever, whatever color you think most represents your soul.
So in your case, it would be a putrid yellow.
Possibly have a blood clots in it.
And since.
Oh, no.
How am I eating here?
Anyway, okay.
So you have that like nice, that nice slime layer.
Then you get like like on for every context,
it's like a new like cheese grater you have.
It has different sized holes and like the shape of the holes are different.
Sometimes they're really big holes, so a lot of slime gets through.
And sometimes like only a little bit of slime gets through.
And then when you grate that slime to like residue that comes out,
the slime that gets out of it is like the bits of you
that are still within your mask.
But the like the mask is the cheese grater.
You know what I'm saying?
It's always going to be parts of you.
It just depends on each context, how much comes out of you.
But it all is still you.
Oh, so so so wait.
So wait, what if what if mind meld technology was created and you could you could you could you could
blow your brains together like digitally and like go into each other's consciousnessness.
And then you'll be like, I know this guy perfectly truthfully.
And then you come out and then you're like, hey, I get it now.
I get you and he gets you too.
Would that would that be like knowing the true self?
Is that what it means to be gay?
To have a soul mate?
Yeah, something like that.
That would be like literally like fucking the slime, bro.
You get right up in that shit, dude.
Straight up.
I would just like to say that YouTuber,
monkey jones has definitely never worn a mask.
That's ever.
Never ever.
I mean, I mean, he's taken it off so far.
It's like so long ago that the pain doesn't even really get to him anymore.
No.
Yeah, it's not even painful at all.
Pain without love.
Pain can't get enough.
Pain.
Exactly.
But I like it rough.
And I'd rather feel pain than nothing at all.
You know, it's interesting that that's my seat.
That's, I don't know, that self-censorship kind of thing.
It's not really self-censorship, I guess.
It's just the stuff, like the fact that I'm not saying all kinds of like racial
expletives, you know, I could if I wanted to.
Naked.
I could say, yeah, there you go.
There you go.
Naked.
What you're trying to say is you're a secret racist.
We get it.
It's fine.
That's how I like it.
Nate, Charlie's Fills.
Charlie's not there.
What's up, kid?
And Hillary's not actually there.
It's just cardboard.
Don't worry.
What?
That's not true.
I don't know what you mean.
I'm here.
I'm here, folks.
I just want to announce me and my betrothal to a big fairy tale fan,
creator of Minecraft, founder of every website in the world, especially neopets.com.
Hillary Clinton is here.
I love her.
And here she is with a quick message to everyone.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Hillary Clinton.
Is that Jeff Foo?
I love you.
Yeah.
All right.
That's it.
She's gone.
Not 50 points ahead.
I don't get it.
Dude, did you guys hear that she just came out with a book and audio book
narrated by herself called What Happened?
And it's about the election?
I do actually want to read that.
Was that?
I've listed that audio book.
Is there a question mark at the end of that title?
Is she asking the question, what happened?
Is it saying, oh, this is what?
Is it a declaration or a question?
I don't know.
We'll have to look into that.
A question would be hilarious.
Hillary doesn't have questions, only answers.
I have to assume that she's acknowledging all of the reasons why she lost,
because a lot of it was on her back.
I mean, if she's just blaming Trump the whole time, then that's not an honest answer.
You're just going to open up the book.
There's going to be tons of blank pages.
You're going to halfway through, and then in big fucking letters,
take out the whole page, patriarchy.
And that's it.
What's happening?
Oh, yeah.
I mean, honestly, I think there's no way that this person will not, like,
she's definitely going to dive into all the excuses.
Like, what's her goal?
It's her goal to be like, you know what?
It's time to do some self-discovery.
You know what?
It's time to look inside.
That's what I would hope for.
But I hope that the book, like, chapter one should be called I'm Unlikable,
but it's going to be called Patriarchy.
Yeah.
If she's trying to preserve political capital,
then she's going to be the dishonest, you know, continue to say that.
In my head, for some reason, it is a bright pink with fluffy pink fluff on the outside
and a little pen.
And it's just a diary, but with Hillary's face on every page.
And you can write it.
And you decide what happened.
It's in the Diary of the Wimpy Kid format, but with Hillary instead of fucking Greg.
Yeah.
Dude, that should be your next thing, monkey.
I'll do a Diary of a Losing Candidate.
Well, I mean, okay, okay.
It's not even fair to say that, you know, you know, Hillary was serious.
Well, because everyone just loved Jill Stein so much.
How was she not supposed to be like it?
You know, she was just overwhelming.
Yeah, yeah.
I believe I tried to vote for Jill Stein and failed in doing so.
And so I believe that that was my attempt.
Should we move on to questions, folks?
Let's let's do it.
Let's do it.
Yeah.
That was a fun aside.
Oh, it's Jeb Bush.
If anyone doesn't share their comments, feel free to.
It's Jeb Bush, the guy I was thinking of.
I was thinking Jeff Thu every time.
Every time.
Same.
His name is Jeb Bush.
But his name is Jeb Bush.
Not the son of Jeb.
I thought they were like completely different.
Oh, no.
So no one should make like the chart where it's all fucking yellow and Jeb is like doing a power pose
when they have that with Jeff and the PCP subscribers or something like that.
That's a good idea.
Okay.
Oh, I love Jeff.
Just note here.
Tell me all of your secrets, guys.
Come PM me.
Tell me how many people you've touched in such a way.
As Jeb touched the nation during the 2016 election.
Yeah.
Good idea.
Okay.
Let's see.
I'm going to Twitter to get some questions.
And we've also got some, I think.
I shall get some from the data.
Wait, wait.
Before I do questions, I have a secret.
One time, I touched a girl's hand and I was like,
No!
I touched it.
I was, it was a prolonged exposure.
No!
Did you ask permission first?
Because I'm afraid I've got some boys in blue who are going to need a report to your domicile.
She grabbed my hand.
She was, she raped you then.
She didn't guess for consent.
All right.
Well, she's in jail now.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
Jess has been sent.
That monster is locked up.
That woman's name was Hillary Clinton.
That's why she wasn't available for, yeah.
It's my fault Trump won.
Well done.
Mozilla Fiddick can ask, what is the most powerful bug in all caps?
Sizer.
Scissor.
Whatever you want to call it.
A beetle possibly?
Maybe.
Scissor could just vour a pincer.
Oh, oh, guys.
He would just use aerial ace and win.
Exactly.
Recently, I was in France.
And in France, they have hornets.
There was these hornets.
No!
And they, yeah.
But it's, it's weird.
They're sort of like bigger wasps with long, thick thighs, right?
That just dangle down next to them.
But they're so stupid.
They just hit walls and can't stand on anything.
They're actually adorable.
I love, I love hornets.
What I would say to a scary hornet is like, dude,
Beedrill isn't even competitive.
You've got to get the fuck.
I'm not intimidated by you.
He has like one speed.
Have you seen Megabedrill though?
He's like the coolest motherfucker in all of them.
He looks retarded.
Megas are bad.
Megas are bad all of them are horrible.
Beedrill is Gurren Lagoon.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
The closest to Gurren Lagoon is without a doubt.
Scissor.
And I like scissor years before I even saw fucking Gurren Lagoon.
Okay, well whatever.
Uh, here we go.
Question.
I got one at Jade Moreau, our old friend.
What are y'all's opinion on love songs?
Gay.
Love songs.
My favorite one is the George Harrison something.
Something in the way she moves.
That's a good love song.
The rest are bad.
If I remember correctly, shit, who was it?
Not only is that song, uh, great.
I believe it was-
Charlie Ray Jebson with Call Me Maybe.
Great love song.
Some, some world famous-
I actually do like that song.
Some famous love song singer who I can't fucking remember.
Oh no, I love song.
I love songs, that is.
Wake me up when September ends.
That's the, the guy from Green Day wrote that
because his dad, I was really hot in the-
Yeah, that's not a love song.
It's like about some guy who died.
Not about his dad.
It's about daddy.
Wake me up inside.
Wake me up.
Can't wake up inside.
Say Jesus.
Wake me up when pedophilia is legal.
And also incest.
I love my dad.
Uh, he's a question, he's a question.
He never thought of the song.
It was, it was, I was just gonna, I can't,
I can't think of a good song,
but it was, I was gonna say about, uh, Gibbs.
Some famous love song singer said that George Harrison's song,
something of the way she moves,
was the best love song I've ever written.
Oh, Frank Sinatra?
I think it was Frank Sinatra.
What's new pussycat?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
That's the greatest love song of all time.
What's new pussycat?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Reg's girlfriend in the PCP patient lounge asks,
how do you be productive?
Stop being a bitch and fucking do it already.
Jesus Christ. Yeah, yeah, you gotta you gotta remove obstacles from your life. I have I have I have I have a video
Watched by died. I watched by me about Van Harman
Who was talking about this a very thing? How do you be productive out here?
He said that the whole idea of like having deadlines and forcing yourself to do it is okay
It gets the job done, but it's not good for growing yourself at being able to do stuff
so the the whole it's better to
Not force deadlines upon yourself
But to just not take anything you do as seriously as you take it and just make shit and make it bad and go and go into it
Wanting it like making sure that it's shit because otherwise nothing gets made and that's that's how you do it
Apparently that I like that a few episodes of the latest season of Rick and Morty. Oh
I don't know
Okay, here's a question at the Vajita asks hey, that's a just joke. He stole that that's that's true
There's underscores here. What part of your everyday routine is the worst?
What part of your routine is the worst for me without a doubt it's waking up waking up is by far the worst part of my day
I
Hate getting out I said I said literally ten alarms for myself every morning cuz I cannot no no no
No, I mean, I mean, I know you have a job so you have to but I would have I would advise against
Alarms because I've never had I've got rid of alarms and I've learned to just wake up at the right time
It's way better. I feel so much better. I wish I could do that
I can't trust myself though. If I if I could like guarantee that I went to bed by a certain time
I'd try that but yeah, I'm just abusing my body every day that I like
It's not good for you, it's not it's the most it's the most terrible way to begin getting up when I am
By a loud noise when I'm free for my fucking wage slave job patreon.com slash best guy ever everybody
Let's hit that $5,000 per month market. I'll be fucking free today. I
I
Yeah, I'm hurting myself
I will wake up at any time I want it'll be great
Alarms are cool because then you can set your own custom alarm clock sound and then you can like go to your friend at the bar
You can be like, what's your alarm sound and you just say my dad screaming at me?
Look at my scars
Also alarms make you hate whatever the alarm is I have PTSD for the default alarm sound from my phone
If I ever hear it again, I will get so upset that I might shit myself
Are you ever walking around and then you hear someone's phone rings and it's the noise that you use as your alarm?
Yeah, oh my god, it's gonna. I'm gonna die. Just thinking about
Obliterated
That's that's like that's what's like for me
But even worse because my alarm clock sound is a is a song from Homestuck. So whenever I'm listening to
ography I just get that sound I just fucking oh
No, no, no, no, okay
So you're making a big mistake. You never put a song you actually like as your alarm sound. That's that's you can't do it
It's not legal can't be done. You know, it's all about
Cosmetic and duality and your whole
Right, you know, I used to do that
I used to use anime songs as my alarm clocks, but then I start to dislike anime and I'm like I can't go down this road
I can't this is too much of a risk
I'll die. I'll lose all all identity if I keep this up
Milady from the PCP patreon Lana asked would you rather know the date of your death or the cause of your death?
You have to pick one. This assumes that I will die in my life. I would
That's true, I would much rather know the cause than the day I do not want to know the date that fucks you up in all kinds of ways
Yeah, cause could cause could happen. I know the cause I can train and be ready
Well, assuming that it's it's always
I've been ready to die for years
Yeah, but like if you if you hear like the cause of your death is a train crash
And you're like, okay, I'm never gonna go on a train again
And then then it's obviously because a train crashes into you like what you you can't avoid it
But if you do any planning, it's gonna be in vain
Because like yeah, you just be like scared of knives for the rest of your life or whatever
But if I know the date I know like okay, well, I have 80 years now to get all these projects done
I guess I better start doing them. Well, you know, that that that length of term
I mean, what if you find out it's in let's just say like five years like how are you gonna choose to spend five years?
You know, that's that's a time you're gonna you're gonna panic, but you're gonna get a lot of stuff done
Yeah, which could be good if it turns out that the guy who was telling you that you're gonna die is just a crazy man
Yeah, that's yeah, that's I know I have five years
Cuz like either way you're gonna die in five years, so at least I can spend those five years being productive rather than
Because you think about it, I mean none of us are gonna be alive in
Download myself to the vapor net
I agree actually I actually
Is gonna is not it's gonna it's gonna be it's gonna it's gonna be a gonna be a good robot
I I don't think that consciousness is real
And I think we're basically seeing like individual frames
String together like a film that's constantly playing so it gives us the illusion of a sense of self
In a sense of like continuity to our consciousness. That is a moment to moment. This is too stupid. Can we go to the next question?
The least stupid thing I have the dumbest thing I've ever heard you say dude, dude
I have a tangent
tangentially related to
What you were saying?
That's just thinking I was thinking earlier in the week about like robots being like the literal
The the the the next evolution of humans not humans with robotic parts, but like literally just robots
We make them and they live much longer than we can so they're literally our children
They're gonna last longer than they're gonna be able to go and do whatever, but they're not going to be like us
Preserved they're just gonna be new people
I want to build I want to build a robot daughter and I'm gonna call her risk and she's gonna be
Unbeatable and she's gonna live forever in the universe and it's gonna be like yeah
I should do an episode on transhumanism. That's a great idea. It's a great and there be robot. Penethilia
Okay, it depends it depends what you mean
You got to find your terms because like can a man look at a baby looking robot with lust in his heart and be called a pedophile
I say yes, can a baby robot in fact be the victim of a pedophilic sexual act?
I say no so that's you know
Cuz then they could
After wait 18 years to fuck it. I say that's bullshit exactly if you if you got a robot
You could just turn that crank to to make the whole whatever size you want
Doesn't even matter. I've imagined like an old steampunk like a big old crank. You got a like
Over the vagina
I'm gonna make that hole as big as a cave so I can walk inside and I can learn where babies come from finally that makes sense
That makes sense. Oh, by the way, what's the name of that? What's the name of that ship? Okay? Well, okay, just a
There's a there's a name a sycophant. No, that's not it
Okay, so like if you if you take a ship and it's out sailing and it gets damaged and you repair a piece and you keep doing that
Keep going and eventually every single piece has been replaced by something. So it is in fact
Well, okay, so it's like it's still called like the same thing as it what it was there's a name for this but I forget what it is
It's not is this a fist is like the hill that the guy puts the rock up, you know
That's the sycophane thing or whatever. It's got some other name that I can't remember
But the point I'm getting at is like it is theoretically possible that a human being can in fact just become a robot in a sense
If like let's say that you take your brain and you replace one piece of it with an artificial piece and then you okay
you live already you're dead and
Why so well that's the question like at what point do you become a robot?
And if there is no clear point where it happens, I think you could maybe replace every single piece and just then be a robot
Oh, you know what you know what I'm gonna do. What's that? I'm gonna become a robot that is just has a human penis
You're real human real penis. I'll be like oh, it's a real human penis. Whoa real
That's just doesn't happen anymore
And my future robot self will have so much fun
Oh Christ
Okay, any other cookies
I
Yeah, who knows man, I don't know something in some way. I think okay. No, it wasn't let's move on. Yes, okay
Yeah, here's one at Lord Saiba says if you were with Digi what unspeakable acts would you do in his big-ass room?
I take a shit
That's what I would do
Yeah, of course I did yeah, yeah, yeah, it was great
It was great on his house. Yeah, you know that's awesome
And then we pissed on him and then we pissed on his brothers, and it was great. Yeah, you know, don't you dare?
Yeah, I love Vincent. He's my favorite
Bro, it's okay, monkey. He had an umbrella. Oh, thank goodness
I don't know how you got taller than Victor, but good job. He's a powerful stream. It can arc quite
That's his secret power. It's his cutie mark. We introduce Victor to challenge pissing where if you
Piss six feet straight with the air and not get wet you get no dumb payment in your next car visit
Hell
All right, there's no more good questions on the on the Twitter
Is there anything left in the incredible question? Okay?
How do I support the PCB and get into a cool fucking patreon lounge says some bitch in the audience?
Oh, yeah, Jesus Christ. Why don't you just go give us a patreon dollar or two?
Get into a discord chat
He's he's right folks go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators give a dollar and you'll be in the patron
Exclusive chat club where all of us actually go and hang out and talk we act we actually hang out there
And it's not we don't just in there just to hang out place
Yes, we keep out the sheep the weak-minded people
Good person sheep over is a good person because she's in that fan chat. I think or maybe she's not
Okay, she's bad like all the other sheep. She's worthless in every way
Yeah, okay, and also get yourself some shirts from the links in the description go buy PCP merch people
And also don't forget the five dollar patrons get the exclusive monthly bonus PCP
No versus death. No, thank you. That's what it is guys. That's it's death note V death note
It's it's the clash of the Titans who could possibly come out on top of these intellectual juggernauts
Go ahead never made a video comparing the new movie to the anime
We're the first ones to do it if you want to hear how it goes go put that five dollars, baby
That's what you got to do folks just what you're with just to what you're what you what your whistle audience
I have listened to I
May have downloaded the wrong file
I may have tormented the wrong file to listen this movie and it may be in a foreign language
I do not understand without
So if you want to see me trying piece together the plot from just looking at people's mouths move then head on over there
Well, there you go folks. You can't miss it people. It's gonna be an event of the summer. All right. We're done
Thanks for listening everybody
I'd make sure you tweet us at a TP crass natives and use hashtag ask PCP to get your questions on here or be a member of
The discord where you get exclusive shit where we actually care about who you are as a human being and go
To the Tom and monkey suicide perch
For YouTube monetization everybody yeah, that's right. Just was it actually demonetized?
Well, it got yeah, it's not
Yes
I'm not I'm not surprised to be honest based on this. That's how you know. We're legit. We're not fucking around. That's true
Yeah, that's true. Well, thanks for listening everybody. We will see you next time everybody say goodbye
Bye bye bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye by our products by our shirts by our merch Jesus
I'm
Don't want to do